[Music]
a
n
[Music]
pap
n
[Music]
a
n
[Music]
a
n
[Music]
a
Kik
oh uh uh uh whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa good day everybody
hello all right didn't we play it
without this s
[Music]
this AGG doesn't like sushi I guess
that's
okay when you see not takanasi kiar but
Ki takanashi in that order that's it's
like an invitation to sing the
[Music]
song I guess that's
okay hello hello welcome to the stream
yasa and I think it was here was I like
here and chat I don't know you can go
make yourself comfortable over here for
now oh wait the more on the left side
the better cuz there's
subtitles okay I hope everybody
can accept the
truth accept the
reality um I think that is something we
have been
learning hopefully all of us are
learning to accepting the truth mhm yes
you
do I remember how to play the game we W
see let's go what is she on about I'm
I'm just talking about Final Fantasy
that is
all really hot takes wait why am I
playing for
OBS I hear Angry Dog about to eat me up
okay now I'm not playing through uh OBS
don't worry this is the crew we are on
alert what happened last time I guess
we're just coming out of the moment
where it was revealed to
us uh wait is this double
audio that we are the ones who killed
our
brother uh we are the second
fire what was it called
fire not emblem uh
fire uh icon yeah
I was just thinking of
emblem um so this is the audio kind of
double think I can turn off this
one
probably yeah we are in INF
[Laughter]
engage and uh yeah so the realization I
think just hit I guess can we talk to
her
no I don't I don't I don't know what
we're doing but
uh do I remember how to
fight can I go to the practice grounds
right
now no I don't think I can go anywhere
huh yeah no
okay well
then what was it how a work again
potions potion
mention um button match until it comes
back to you H it it will come back to me
but what's like the
main
thing oh God it will it will come back
to me it will come back to me chat is on
top of health bar well there's no health
bar now but okay later then I guess uh
then then where did I put you last time
to
well not in the middle maybe like
here it will show buttons on top left
well yeah okay yeah that's not that's
not the main okay I know I think it's l
L2 for changing the
icons what's R2 for again was R2 dodging
or was
R2 FOC no we we'll figure it out we'll
figure it
out tole what is it yeah what is it
nothing good old wager come on and
suddenly there's like a dunun sound R2
was for my specials square triangle
square triangle that's the main attack
oh yeah square triangle square triangle
square triangle or square square square
triangle square square Square Enix
square square square triangle square
square square square triangle I don't
know oh [\h__\h] I feel
like is it going to be a big fight
because obviously I'm not
ready DOA D what's
up
R2
uh what who who are the dudes what
happened a pokey
poke you want to fight Imperial
legionaire how do I focus on them you
pay for
this okay ah there we go we've got a oh
what are you doing here answer me all
right how
to
okay and then uh like this kind of stuff
sick tole sick him
tole thank God these are weak enemies
get them
oh
oh no surv I'm lazy I don't want to
move I feel I swear I don't feel like
doing
anything oh there's a lot of
them I just want to lay in my
bed what is that a limit break oh oh
this is the first time I'm doing it
outside of that big battle oh wo w w
w oh my
God is it already over cuz I'm not shiny
anymore sick tole sick
tole get
him why she looks like she's not doing
anything is she doing
something get the war
worm a worm you are tiny little worm
small smaller worm I did
it oh there's
more isn't this where the uh where all
the people are like you know my mom
they're like you know they love me
thought you could Escape us did you
brand wait we go to that wizard dude no
you die once no kill all
them yeah the [\h__\h] man H how does this
work what what is this oh what was
that
well okay chill chill chill chill chill
chill that was a Parry okay I didn't
have to do anything right oh no in the
moment of a
par sick of was I supposed
to you know what to is the fighting
audio too loud by the
way
ow oh I'm ready for the
thing get him
boy
hey oh stop
it get him
boy can I I can't turn into actual if
right it's all I can do weak get not
impressed sir oh wo Gambit
counter excuse me I did
that get them all you've got
boy that's did that sick tole sick
tole staying true to the title of this
oh wait you get that so
often
keep
dist oh
wait where are the
enemies oh
what come
here don't let them get
away
yeah sick of tole look out with the HP I
think my HP is
okay
get him boy all what is that
all I limit break heels I'm not dodging
yeah
well all must burn the bearers and those
who shelter them my Empress anabella's
command Empress
Anabella
Anabella have I I met this lady before
this
why yes I know I can
wait oh
oh oh yeah he's a fat man I cannot
ah what what is he doing oh yeah he's
he's strong and bulky yeah I got to be
careful oh w
what do you want what do you want fight
me wait I
should whoa what did you do to my dog
you
f piece of
[\h__\h] don't hurt my dog I had this
terrible terrible
dream where like I was man there there
was so much weird [\h__\h] going on in my
dream again get boy but part of it was
like some evil
lady who was supposedly the mother
of
ouch of uh
like uh a whole life member which is
messed up
[Music]
ow cool was like um about to
oh give them all you've got boy don't
let them get
away take like off the the Paw of a cute
either a cat or a dog I don't even know
I think it was a cat this
time and and I was trying to stop her
from doing that yeah what the [\h__\h] right
that's that was my my impression to
though
oh [\h__\h] I keep on forgetting I'm get
him no I was about to dodge
it give them all you've got more I'm so
bad okay we're we're warming up I know I
know so now he's halfway I remember that
I got to do that when they're
halfway and and and and yeah punish him
a little bit for that
and at least it didn't hit
me warming up against bulky
enemy oh yeah oh yeah oh I did
that get them oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] sick of
tole
all right 10,000 and I didn't even I
barely had all the
attacks thank you Jill oh oh I was ready
for it you little [\h__\h]
oh get him all right all right
[Music]
you know what to do
boy so anyway because of the dream I
feel very protective of the
doggo I I I don't know how long that was
ready already I didn't see it until now
kind of
late yeah the limit break I forgot about
it uh cuz it's
new who but hey we didn't die yay we
didn't die
so happy but they all died oh man what
about the the old
dude I'm sorry lady Anna
indeed you deserved so much
better all of these people did [\h__\h] up
man why did they do
it
she gave me the clothes
[Music]
oh we're too late no why are we always
so
late
life but so fashionably late like just
late enough or early enough to still see
what's going on and feel like [\h__\h] if I
only I would have been 1 minute
earlier and they could have been like an
hour late and then it wouldn't really
make much of a impact we knew East pole
was harboring barers thought they were
safe enough hidden up here but someone
must have let
slip if they'd have only come to us
sooner none of this would have had to
happen just one minute
sooner my mother always did despise
bearers the way father embraced them
when the other nations spat on them as
slaves an accident of birth gave them a
power that others
lacked but why kill everyone they meant
no harm they just wanted to be
free this world judges that a crime
punishable by
death which is why we're going to change
it
gav we want to help hello Governor
thought you'd got your own stuff to be
getting on with we do you mean mean this
lady I want to get it on with that
lady in that case we should head back
and tell Sid you about a change of heart
he was always on it yet to join us all
right and we'd best be quick last I
heard he was planning another Excursion
what about the
villagers
hey going to leave you's lot to take
care of things here of course we'll make
sure they get a proper burial
thank you all of
you when you're ready
then okay uh let's read some [\h__\h] to
also remind us what's going
on Annabel Las ah former Duchess of
rosaran now Empress of the Holy Empire
of s it was ever her purpose in life to
preserve her Phoenix bearing bloodline
for which reason she betrayed her
husband that she might enter in League
with a force she judged the mightier now
she rules over Rosaria as Visine of the
Imperial province which she rules with a
cruelty and contempt for the baseborn
that was unknown in aruk 's
day I don't need to hear about bears
duckle loyalists ah those who maintain
allegiance to the late Arch Duke elwin
and work for the Revival of the Fallen
Dutch of Rosaria after Rosaria was
incorporated into the Empire most SW
loyalty to their new Visine the empress
Anabella even more converting after they
saw how those who refused to change jet
Al allegiances were
persecuted
uh their persecution was to only grow
culminating in the burning of east poool
by Imperial troops on the pretext that
the reluctance to surrender was live
bearers to the cabulary proof their dis
loyalty to the holy Throne
what that they reled to surrender to Ros
be con
constabulary
what the term had a different meaning in
the time before imperical occupation
Rosaria was founded by the union of
several small independent nations each
led by its own Noble
House I sound like gladus I wasn't
trying
to sound like AI I am ai ai
these has remain powerful even after
unification sometimes leading to
friction between the Loyalists who
argued for the arch Duke's ultimate
Authority and the separ separatists who
pushed for a return to
autonomy wife of Rodney Murdoch Lord
commander of the rosarian army since her
marriage she resided in the Murdoch man
mayor in East poool remaining there even
after her husband's death at Phoenix
gate alas her time was also to be cut
short at the hands of the villainous
Servants of empress
Anabella yeah
yeah a
hamlet
Hamlet
Hamlet located in the eastern part of
the Imperial province of raria I thought
Hamlet is like a yeah like a like the
name of a
play Oh I thought it was like the name
of a
person oh it's a small village it was
once surrounded by fertile Farmland but
the southw creep of the blight
eventually drove out most of the
inhabitants
n it's also
person Hamilton is the name of the
person
no well G okay what's it Sid's faithful
Scout he the ever agreeable fellow
volunteered to follow after dominant
that Clive had long been hunting only to
find him himself been hunted in turn by
The Imperials as luck would have it CLI
arrived in a nick of time to save his
life forging an unbreakable bond between
them
unbreakable
unbreakable oh done now rats lead me to
your Nest who are you your forehead
iser's message for your leader
surprisingly bigger than mine knew where
to send
it looks like a
dad it's quite an accomplishment to have
a bigger forehead than me
man oh oh we can only go here
[Laughter]
okay
he go sneaky nyyy nyyy NYY sne sneaking
like gum snake Sol
then aot to
discuss I heard barking at his lot
earlier hello mle
cute wait do I have to go
upstairs what's
upstairs don't mind me just taking a
quick bre
uhhuh hi Jill we can keep
running or we can walk through this door
I can't walk through the door I have to
open it first sorry Jill that's like I'm
not physical physically capable of
walking through a door like you try it
show me how to do it then how can I you
walk through the door I want to see it
teach me that skill
oh I have to open it
first we can walk through this door
thanks Jill for not telling me how to
walk through the
door man I need clear
instructions this place is getting more
crowded by the
day I tell myself the bustle's a
blessing there'll be time enough for
quiet contemplation when I'm
dead so did you find the answers you
were looking for
uh I still don't know what to make of
this gift
curse or whatever it is I've been
given but there is one thing I can say
for certain
H I am a dominant if
fre and there is nothing I can do to
change
that it is a burden I must bear until my
dying
day the way he's listening to
it forgiveness and in turn salvation can
only begin with
acceptance It's a path we all must walk
no matter how colorful our histories Sid
you once told
me that you wanted to build a place
where people could die on their own
terms I did I've been thinking about
that why not a place where people can
live on their own terms
whoa W years killing was all I knew so
obsessed with death that I never stopped
to consider the lives of those around
me lives that what a concept scarcely
worth
living be they bearers or
Beggars most but March blindly to their
end never realizing that they too
deserve a choice
wow and I dare not turn a blind eye to
their suffering any
longer so atonement then is
it
oh lo that was the answer we found she's
the only one we
need I'll be expecting your both to pull
your
weight and we
will well then with a Sprinkle of Fire
and Ice this planet mine might just
work oh okay fire fire on
ice what trouble are you looking to get
yourself remember that kfp the best kind
we're going to sneak into the imperial
capital and pay a visit to Mother Mommy
Mommy yeah let's go Let's Make Her Say
sorry son not sorry
Mommy it's a reference to something you
will find out at some point this looks
really cool sheesh the way they built it
in the shape of the
Mountain ice Spike the last of our farmh
holds in the Eastern provinces has
succumbed to the
blight without their ye you'll be hard
pressed to F the capitals granaries
before
winter
if there is a capital by then the black
creeps closer as we speak these people
don't seem nice and yet you do not but
fall and
Bluster
oh your
Radiance
oh oh or flam what the [\h__\h] is that name
the capital of the Holy Empire of s
located in the North Eastern storm on a
peninsula that dominates o o oil oiled
Bay and it's home to the mother
Crystal known as Drake's head
Drake what happened old Empire's major
institutions are located here including
white worm cat Castle seat of holy
Emperor and meeting place of the
Cardinals ah ah these are the the church
people
[Music]
n if it is fertile land the Empire
requires we need but look
South uh if you mean the crystalline
dominions hold buildings we are bound by
Mutual Accord theirs is a neutral state
whose borders we have sworn to
respect gentlemen did we swear to see
our people's star well I really
do the gates of oriflam buckle at the
flood of those come seeking Refuge from
the blight if there is not grain enough
to feed those within our walls how prel
will we feed those
without but instead of setting your
minds to riddles such as
these you lock horns with an enemy from
across the sea sending our soldiers to
the slaughter in their
thousands the Empire bleeds and you sit
here prattling like crones in a tea
house and you fancy yourself El leaders
of
men sanre is not without her citizens we
are but their
servants if their land is being rested
away wait they did it again they did it
again duty to claim new lands I zon out
for a
moment your Radiance you cannot mean a
war of
Conquest that is exactly what I mean it
is time we expanded our
Dominion okay this is the will of great
griger there will be uproar then we must
find a way to distract the citizenry but
how much will that cost of our Legion
shall we raise the first so someone will
have to contend with the delx I will not
keep you you all have much to do
something cracked in my
boob you can't you can't even
relate sometimes things crack in boobs I
don't know why it would be interesting
to find out who is my son why the Lord
Prince is currently garrisoned at the
straight of orur
if it please you I can send word
requesting his immediate return to the
holy
Capital that won't be necessary tell him
instead to see to his
wounds confed strength will be needed W
his wounds bullet as you command maybe
you need a tole to tend to your
wounds must be a phoenix thing no not
the ribs like something inside the meat
I must have misheard
you mean to tell me that the mother
crystals are the reason the world is
dying okay guys stop imagining wab boot
I have been that on occasion but no not
today think of think of uh your own Firs
hand where once were Green Meadows land
drained so dry of its ether not even the
rats remained no but where was it all
going I spent years searching for an
answer and until I saw it standing right
in front of me uh-huh there in the
self-same crystals we look to for their
so-call
blessing
owl all right
listen take this Crystal mhm how does it
allow us to conjure Magics answer by
drawing ambient ether from the air mhm
and where do these crystals come from
the mother crystal that's easy they're
mine from the mother crystals I got it I
had it they're one and the same although
admittedly this and they say I don't
listen but the mother crystals are
massive some as large as
mountains so you see the problem imagine
just how much ether can be drawn by
something that size mhm mhm as to where
it's all going mind well I can't M
everything can I we are taught that the
mother crystals are Divine their ether a
gift from the heavens wasn't
this centuries Nations have fought and
fallen for want of that gift if what you
say is true yeah how did no one else say
exactly like how did no one like make
this connection before maybe the truth
was
inconvenient it's very obvious
inconvenient to whom
exactly
the higher ups the gods
themselves yeah Aura you should have
voice active for this
game and what we're not helping bearers
and dominance anymore I didn't say that
I made a promise and I intend to keep it
but if we continue down this path
there's only one fate that awaits the
realm and we can't very well set our
people free if they're all lying dead in
a blighted
ditch not if we want to create a place
where they can live on their own terms
anyway I know what we can do sort of
defeats the
purpose I know what we can do so if we
have to bring the old world crashing
down in order to build us a new
one sit on the streets and block all the
horse carriages is from
passing no matter
what I suppose it's about time I repay
your
faith let's glue ourselves to the ground
too could have just said
I but it's nice to have you aboard all
the
genius oh choco B carriages
lever
sounds what have I got myself
into I'm going to need more than a few
potions for you
potions oh he's speaking straight to
me man he knows I used up all my potions
a
he knows I like to overdose on the
potions anyway dude what's up see I'm
busy
here you have something new flame
tongue that's what they call my tongue
too what a coincidence no
what wait what does my current + 15 +
okay I should make this
right should last you a good while
no what else a dark sash no these are
weaker the battle chains also
weaker that it okay fine can I craft
potions do you have an energy r
no no
so what God's
for the wait what and what business
would you L having the only Capital
second thoughts I don't want to
[Music]
know uh
potion Poli all of them even though we
might collect them on our
way anyway oh there's a new one
gradually fills limit break go for 30
seconds speaking of orlam I the trading
routes leading South have seen more than
double the usual traffic perfect if you
ask me some fowls brewing and a in is B
te perfect let's let's sit down right
between there see Oto will you all
right really thank you sassy Slayer
thank you
make it quick I'm at Max gy and they
give me another one in the
Overworld gy over lord I feel like
soorry what it be I didn't really have
that issue that
much I can't upgrade my current
sword can I oh yeah cuz those you can't
upgrade was that the thing but I could
upgrade my accessory wait no this is re
yeah why does it make it weaker when I
oh cuz it's not what I'm wearing when
I'm wearing is
stronger uh well then I don't know I
don't think I'll upgrade
anything cve was it I heard Otto barking
at his lot earlier didn't sound happy
can practice a little bit I think I'm
fine it's it's it pretty much all all
came back to me Chen
hi he jumped and reacted to me oh
hi cute it's
you it's you oh wait I was supposed to
talk to someone over
there oh hi Oto so you're really going
through with it has been talking about
bringing down a mother Crystal since
I've known him but that's all has ever
been are we like going to blow it up
also in the background oh my God is that
in the oven the capital shortly look at
the
oven well you couldn't have picked a
better moment okay it looked more clear
before the the royalists gave him wasn't
enough to dampen old Sylvester's Spirits
his Legions are on the March again this
time doe Sur I think another War all as
the great green wills it looks like
sweet donuts with sugar
glazing it's gods for you in it and
filling inside might work to our
advantage on this occasion Wars breed
Chaos on the front lines dunin donuts
and at home with a fair wind behind them
a handful of light-minded neru Wells
could melt into the back alleys of orlam
no trouble is making it to the capital
is the problem
the checkpoint donut that's right anyone
traveling in or out of oriflam has to go
through North reach lucky for you I
might just know of a
way
this well no not
that that gets you an audience with the
D and it's the Dame who'll see you
safely through North reach I'll send a
stus in the morning let her know you're
coming
we go way back and she's a true friend
of the
cause I'm sure you'll get on like a
house on fire that's good of you but who
is this Dame and where will I find her
she's the proud proprietress of North
reach's foremost house of ill repute The
Veil The Veil this is quite a woman if
you know what I mean a
woman
right don't go blind you know with your
child does she also have a
12y old boy sucking on her booby when
you get
back talking about Game of Thrones
guys talking about Game of
Thrones The
Veil The yeah it's a reference
okay Alliant Aliant reports are now
available for viewing by speaking to
God
[Laughter]
you at the Aliant Alliance report
counter in the Hideway mess these
reports compiled by The Curse Breakers
contain information on quests currently
available so side quest you mean yeah
okay I suppose that's everything there's
just some honey in the tea nothing else
it's a green
[Music]
tea it has nothing to do with how I'm
acting
[Music]
oh uhhuh yeah yeah I think I I know that
they're like you know boss weapons
mhm E I always put honey in any tea
green tea fruit tea black tea is my my
sweetener and also my way of making it
more you know soothing on my
throat I know I haven't been using the
Manuka honey I'm first like finishing my
other
Honeys well well well someone's in a
hurry just following
orders funny I never took you for the
type can all be as obedient as you
gaav
fine day for a little Mischief wouldn't
you say no I'm drinking the expensive
one is this all of
us actually gav won't be
coming oh just the three of us face
Drake said is the Key Stone of the
Empire he was like what the chaos yes
but that doesn't mean we can March an
army through her Gates the fewer our
numbers the better our chances are going
unnoticed and should that plan fail well
we have our icons to fall back
on see I I don't know if I can if fre
still seems
to come and go as he pleases ordinarily
primary and icon comes naturally to a
dominance but then you are no ordinary
dominant well he still got the blessing
of the Phoenix doesn't he not to mention
what he tooked out with
gude
and did I ever tell you about how he was
once the greatest shield in Ros areia
you know I reckon he could probably C
apart out of the capital on his own if
need
be let's try not to find out we're less
likely to be spotted if we travel
separately I'll meet you in North reach
in a few
[Music]
days you two be
now
he's so disappointed he wants to
join all right we're going here let's go
to last Wing ikim let's
go
uh so this place in
northrige and will I find Sid and Gill
before this Dame Finds
Me Wait why did we not go together what
do you mean meet them that'll be enough
for today we don't need you risking the
curse for a barrel of
Shad but how did the grer know his
daughter had been stealing off to the
vineyard to see the lad there were
purple handprints all over our skirts
what what's this gossip where am I
supposed to go
I'm going to get so lost again
[Music]
uh it's probably over
there oh this was a dead end was
it yes
yes
uh
it's confusing there's too many
layers who would have thought that I
would dislike layers
once I think I'm on the right
path
yay where am I feel I am is it safe to
ride some nor now can you adjust the
brightness do you want it to be brighter
or
darker I think it's pretty normal right
now
oh there we go finally we're rushing
what what what what with what point does
he decide to rush like what do I have to
do to make him
rush no
mistakes hey
nice killing more bugs like I did
yesterday sometimes this not the first
time I had a ladybug but it's not even
ladybugs apparently uh
infestation it's not even the first
time but seems like it's like season the
season again for
[Music]
this those were not normal ladybugs
guys get him boy yeah lady Beatles which
is apparently a big difference in terms
of if you want them or not tole sick
them tole
T the
season don't let away T the season of
Love and
Understanding oh [\h__\h] why did I you got
why did I I messed
up I did it
wrong Merry
Christmas
everyone
[Music]
okay I know I know I I'll get into the
groove again of using everything in the
right order soon TM get him too
slow this
time oh wait huh there we
go ow was waiting for
this I'm skiing Halloween yeah [\h__\h]
Halloween no but my my family feuded um
stream basically is my answer to us
seemingly not having anything really big
planned at the moment with like
everybody like there's no VR stre more
So
currently in the making I was like
well people probably already have a lot
of solo streams already planned for
Halloween or like smaller collab
streams so I uh I'm planning for the
30th instead or like 29th depending on
your time zone just a little Family Feud
stream cuz I I had it
like um that was an idea I had for a
while now so I requested perms a while
ago and then
I wasn't quite ready for it when I did
get the
perms but ever since I saw wami and
finana play it over at nii Sanji I was
like well this looks
fun I want to play it
[Music]
too unfortunately there's no online
co-op so I'll be
controlling
the um
oh hi
chos like typing in everything and
currently uh we're like in total eight
people let's make this quick why why I'm
trying to fight these I hate these air
enemies get down to do
boy get them all youve got
for there
boy you know who's attendant
yeah but I'm not sure if I should say
yet because some people might still
change their minds I don't
know
um but some I think I think the lineup
is quite
nice yeah there's still like some time
to go um but uh Fu M are participating
and they're like already including it in
their
schedule so I thought I should like say
it as well cuz it's not even going to be
in my next schedule for upcoming week
cuz it's Monday for
me it's going to be the Monday in the
following week so I'm not even going to
include
it they I guess see it as a Sunday
stream
oh yeah yeah uh yeah and they count as
two people in this case cuz I need more
participants and I'll put them on
different teams I'll make him
compete
oh oh [\h__\h] I thought he was like the
other the other kind of stagger all you
got sick of
tole
[Music]
hey breaking the family literally
literally family there's literally
family in this family
feud down I have new skills oh oh
really get him I'll look at it another
time you know what to do
boy
hey hey no I thought I could do the the
half stagger
thing
distance give them all you've got
boy get him I took too long what on your
H over
here
get
him anyway what was I what was I saying
before that before the Family Feud
thing get him
boy you know what to do boy not this
time
[Music]
just press square yeah ah the ladybugs
oh yeah yeah yeah so in case you're not
on Twitter I had a ladybug infestation
cuz I had my I had my window open for
like days days Days days so they had
plenty of time to get in I guess but I
didn't notice until
yesterday and there were so many holy
[\h__\h] I tried to get most of them out by
the way was there no chest try to get
most of them out with um just like you
know I have like this feather duster
which is really cute I barely get to use
it um but yeah that was only possible
for the ones that were really close to
the edge of the
window
so then some people were saying they're
toxic and I was like okay maybe I should
get rid of them
properly
but that they can also get really stinky
if you just vacuum them up normally and
also I have like a filter in my vacuum
so it would get stuck on the filter next
time I clean the filter I'm going to
have like [\h__\h] ton of these like dead
stinky lady beetles I don't want to have
that
so so somebody gave me a tip to try with
a a a stocking or
so they used a a stocking that was kind
of nice with some
lace but I didn't I I haven't worn this
one in like million years so I was like
I don't need this so I'll throw it away
including with the
Beetles I'm sorry they probably are dead
by now but they are a pest
apparently so I put the this is like
incredibly actually efficient and
working I put the I I like squeezed the
stocking into
the
um the the vacuum shaft of the long
stickers used to speak of the
broth and then north of the checkpoint I
like turned it over on the edge and put
a the
D and I put
a I put a a a
um elastic band around it to secure
it and then I vacuumed them and it
worked I got them
all amazing life hacks
sheesh Next Level life hack I will
remember this one I simply can't decide
I'll just have to
take what did you say was fresh fish all
from the sea
of we've read with the right to
confiscate any objects forbidden by the
oh my God so many people talking B on
the gates for Citizens not
oh wait what where am I going I want to
go inside maybe there's a side
[Music]
entrance
oh ah this
lady oh cute dress so
colorful
a moment my
lady very very
subtle I doubt you could afford even
that much of my time oh
branded wow my
mistake no mine upon reflection you
don't have the scent of a brandid about
you the flowers Otto always did know how
to please me more than Sid ever did
anyway oh oh my do you think Sid could
pleas dated a lot of women didn't
he you're the
Dame
H let us leave such impersonal titles to
my less preferred
cantel you can call me Isabelle Otto was
assured me I could trust you I can trust
you can't
I you can trust me yes
but why would you help
you because that's what we
do long ago Sid did me a kindness when
no one else
would I have never forgotten
that without it I would not be where I I
am
today and so I make it a point to do the
same whenever
possible which brings us
here to the final obstacle between you
and whatever it is you seek in the Holy
capital I fear the guards are not likely
to let a masterless bearer pass
unmolested
unless
unless unless of course his master
dained to appear what
yes that will do nice calm down woman
but I shall expect a favor in
return wait
what de me
[Music]
I think she likes me you say these are
all from D fruit's not getting any
fresher what the hell are you doing T we
cannot have people thinking I tolerate
Disobedience from my brandid the men who
gave me this and no more my masters than
you are
but it's not as if I can hide it from
the moment you acquired it that brand
has done not but take but today it is
going to give you exactly what you want
uhhuh just play
along
wow should fit well to B why cuz she's
horny back to the vi already yeah but of
course we must make ready to welcome you
my
dear and who might this be why my new
escort the streets aren't safe for a
girl what with all the royalists
about well don't work him too hard well
that rather depends on you now doesn't
it I'll see you all at
Sunset boy hold
up
what you want to know tips on to on how
to flirt with women you're lucky you're
with a
d now get out of my sight
filth
okay that was the
plan that wasn't so
bad wasn't so bad they might have
recognized me but they your problem even
if they had they wouldn't have done
anything about it the gentleman of the
Garrison are some of my best customers
we have an
arrangement as do you and I now am I in
the right assumption that she we speak
more at the veil has intercourse with
people for money doesn't seem like I
have much of a
choice
okay well then we're
in
oh that part looked like the place where
they had the L of the ring if anyone
requests her company tell them she is
feeling
unwell oh she protects her her ladies
Madame you look stunning as to you my
dear
shall I have one of the girls draw bath
that won't be
necessary Clive my darling welcome to
the
veil is that her her her
business it's not quite what I expect Ed
when I heard about the
[Music]
veil thank you for seeing me through the
gates my
lady I am in your dead well that was the
whole point wasn't it and I told you
it's Isabelle whatever wound you so
tight I wonder it's certainly not Sid's
influence you uh mentioned a
favor what is it you'd have me do I I
don't want to keep my companions waiting
if you mean Sid and the girl you needn't
worry they have yet to reach the
checkpoint yes why do we not go together
me to help them as well but to answer
your
question I need you to find someone for
me one of my girls tatienne has been
gone for several days now having left no
word of
explanation and I began to fear the
worst I feel as if I've spent my whole
life searching
okay no
sneaky I trust you'll do your best oh
and take
this the moon and stars seal Pro of that
trust and hopefully enough to keep
prying eyes from looking too closely at
that handsome face of yours now I have
matters to attend to at the iron flagen
if you find anything ask for me there
okay then we will look for the girl did
we get a
name I should probably start here
here hello Veil
cortison you wear the Dame's brooch she
must trust you enough to help me look
for one of your colleagues she's just
horny for me a Woman by the name of
Tatian she's still missing then oh if
only I'd comforted her you saw her
before she disappeared the day before
she was in tears she'd lost her comb a
gift from the Dame it wasn't anything
fancy but you could tell it meant the
world to her you see tan was an orphan
and she looked upon the Dame as a mother
as do we all so she was upset and I
didn't lender my
older but perhaps someone else did
Tatian shared a room room her chamber
mate may have seen something she's over
there sitting by the pond thank
you let's see what her chamber may can
tell us
then
hello talk to me the new escort the
girls have been talking about they
already talking about me on an errand eh
it's been one minute boy you'll be
knackered before the real work begins
later on tonight I'm told you share a
bed chamber with Tatian
did she say anything to you before
before she went missing only that she
needed to meet with someone she didn't
mention a name but I know exactly who
she meant oh you
do lab from The Garrison annoying little
[\h__\h] spent every Gilly earned on taen
and picked fights with anyone else who
tried to buy her time followed her
around like a lost puppy ttian was
flattered at first but it didn't take
long for her to get scared huh she
thought about saying something but the
Dame was so proud of her for how much
she was bringing in and she didn't want
to let her down H this man from The
Garrison did you ever see him of course
I did he tried to sneak into our room
enough times slimy s's got a scar over
one eye claims he got it in
battle you've been very helpful don't
let him get away with this find him and
you'll find
her
so he abducted
her seems a trip to the barracks is in
order kidnapped her what I haven't seen
you around the veil of
late don't tell me you've grown tired of
us that's the day done
then wow fancy
magic okay let's find her let's save her
from the fangs of a creep heard the
bones fell favorably I'm looking for a
man with a scar oh they look so similar
looking for a man does this look like a
bruffle branded [\h__\h] off hold your
tongue why do Bruff not why why are
there why is there not a GFF in the brff
good there's only one man in the
Garrison with a dodgy eye his name's
Yanik I haven't seen him around lately
though on account of him being in more
yeah yanet left a few days back said he
had dealings with a merchant there the
Dame thans
you I know they go both ways but if what
you're expecting there should let
his most likely fool was there n on then
it should be a
g or or the people that for the people
people that go there is maybe it's
called a brle for that but then the
other way around it should be called a
griffle a gel I think GLE sounds
funny I know I don't have to go here but
it looks so
pretty there's a fancy choco B again a
green
one okay control yourself waa stay
inside although there's an item
items must be taken a Gil
bug a money
buug
uh wait where
[Music]
up the massive C makes you think it's BL
of the
Rings
huh I don't know why that would make you
think of
that why Clive tell me you bear Good
Tidings that remains to be
seen
oh tan you could have told me this Yanik
the soldiers I spoke to believe he's in
the village of Mo according to them he
claimed to have some business with a
merchant there though that wouldn't
explain his continued absence and you
plan on traveling to Mo to ascertain the
truth isn't that what you want oh it it
is but I fear sending you there may
cause more harm than good the people of
Mo are rather set in their ways you'll
find they have little love for bearers
and they will not hesitate to report one
such as you to the
constabulary there is a man in Mo who
owes me a favor more than one in fact
more his name is ber and he works at
staes tell him I sent you I shall return
as soon as I find
something
[Music]
po
chips
[Music]
okay so addicting oh my
god
wow I mean I know you guys were
correcting me saying it's not a mountain
or whatever it's a the mother Crystal
yeah I get that
how many bearers suffer to keep your
granaries full they do we recreating the
shape right that looks
funny I like it
though wait what did I see an item
uh-huh
[Music]
uhhuh oh the music jump scared me you
want to fight all
right you know what to do
boy sick of
tole you know oh man now it's not only
Birds this shitty wolf as well that's
enough yay you know what to do boy sick
the fake to
go
stop it
now I I want some fried chicken give it
to
me fried Cho ball don't let them get
away K fried Cho
ball I'm
hungry there boy feed
me
[Music]
m
YY you know that's enough for today
branded I met some friends on
Friday and I did my makeup and my
hair and yeah I don't do it that often
so it's very special to me as
well and
when my friends saw me like one of my
friends has a very new blunt way just
like me of saying
things
and the reaction was like something's
something's very different about you
you're just so so
different and I'm like what this just
because you haven't seen me with makeup
for a long time and it's just the one
time I don't look like a
hobo and then we all started laughing
cuz we're like yeah yeah that's it and I
roasted myself like yeah for once I
don't look like
I'm yeah homeless and you know for once
I look like I belong to the
society and yeah we're just making fun
of
me that's
enough and I don't mind because it's
true there's still work to be done I
just look like [\h__\h] most of the time but
when I try I tried on that day then I
can look like a decent member who lives
in this Society people of more are as
intolerant as Isabelle says it's no
wonder the Empire never sent my unit
here it's just normally it's not worth
the effort you
know looking for chests guys maybe
there's one on top of the hill can I go
up
[Music]
there get
him give them all you've got boy it's
over you
lose there
boy H you see a chest in the lower left
what
stupid
stupid nothing up
here lame
ah all right then we shall proceed to
our actual Quest
goal y yum
yum ah is that a merchant need something
what do you have don't touch
anything
what is
this a new
song thanks for nothing yeah
literally you're
welcome are you Bertrand I forgot to
drink my tea the Dame sent me sounds
about right only time I hear from her
thank God I have it in in a fous cup we
go on then what is it one of her cortis
an has gone missing and I need to find
her a soldier who may have information
on her where
many Traders stopped to Pedal their
Wares on their way to the capital but
only On's been seen quarreling with a
soldier oh is he still here the trader
oh yeah stubborn sod stood his ground
till the soldier got tired of shouting
from what I hear if you seek him out
keep your head down fact is folks around
here would sooner hang at branded than
help him and that's even with the Dame's
broo for protection
understood
uhhuh by the way I did ask um I don't
know if you guys were aware of it for
my for my uh pre- chat messages but
there was
like uh a Japanese bro who
found that there were some part some
important vocals missing in pineapple on
Spotify and every other music
service it wasn't missing on like the
music video but everywhere else where
you could listen to it and that was
quite disappointing to
me so I pointed it out I was like can we
can I get an explanation why it happened
and like also can we make sure it
doesn't happen on the album the
CD and so they explained it to me but I
just like read over over it really
quickly when I saw it when I wake
up and uh yeah so some mistakes have
been made and um they can switch it
out from the digital version but they
said for the album
version if I want them to switch it out
then it will delay the shipping a little
bit
more okay that means they already put
the wrong version on the CDs as well
the
[\h__\h] but I want it to be right so we're
doing it I guess just so you know like
it's going to take I don't know how
long I don't think it's going to be like
a like a huge delay but it will delay it
a little bit
more but it's a physical CD it's got to
be right things should be in final
form
kind of disappointing though this a
branded where's your master must I call
for a constable I come to you from North
reach at the beest of the
Dame perhaps you've heard of
her why of course I have I am the good
lady's
servant what is it that she requires of
me rumor has it you were seen arguing
with a soldier some few days ago a
soldier with a scar over his eye yeah
good that we noticed so last yes that's
right minute he had a comb which cuz
otherwise it would have been the same on
the CD and I said he wanted I would have
been able to F but old though it was an
antique it most certainly was not as I
told him good Japan bro I'm surprised it
was a Japanese bro who noticed it cuz
it's like an English song So V about my
appraisal I feel like it would be more
difficult to firm however notice such a
different
how did you guys not know what this is
still purchased a new comb all be it an
in you have to listen more closely to my
songs and do you know where he went
after that my customers aren't usually
in the habit of telling me with they why
brain cell but as it happens this one
did Yonder ruins strange as it may sound
my
thanks not at all I would do anything
maybe there's other things different on
it too that I just I just don't know
about it be sure cuz I don't have
Spotify I don't have apple music I don't
have any of these
things maybe other things are wrong as
well what do you use I I used to use
Amazon music a little bit cuz it came
with
prime but then I became incapable of
logging into it for some
reason
cusa it smells of death here too so I
didn't even check Amazon Prime uh Amazon
music we can't let them get any closer
to the
village stay down bloated they're called
bloated wolves blo bloed from what
he K distant hey hey hey hey hey that's
enough
there
boy it's
over
to give them all you've got Bo stay
down
boy you know what to do
boy
it's
[Music]
over damn it all
bodies a man and a
woman oh they came here together and
then were attacked by the
wolves oh my God she got the com the
comb oh dear this is really
graphic well the wolves have been
busy but the blood is I guess it could
be
worse like having the head ripped
off so it is
you
Tatian
rip if that's true then the body next to
us will be oh hello the girl Yanick went
off to Sea every night you said her name
was
Tatian
yeah did you follow me now why would I
do
that unless you think I'd have good
reason
to but no I was sent to find Yanik by
the looks of
things I have we both found who we were
searching for h n he was a jealous sod
couldn't stand the thought of his w
woman with someone else then one day he
sees her with a new
comb thinks she's got herself a new Gant
tells the Garrison he's going to find
the man and kill him oh we know it's all
talk but then he disappears off to more
for some dealings and doesn't come back
a misunderstanding
corner it was a gift from the
Dame if i y Anica bother to ask eh so
true so true you might not be rotting on
a
hill she think he meant to ask her
something
else he stole the old comb and bought
her a new
one in the Hope they'd wed wed where
would they' have gone certainly not back
to North reach with a Dame waiting and
we all know what happens to
deserters tell the Dame I'm sorry for
her loss when the lads come to collect
Yan's body I'll see that Tatian is
delivered to the veil is that wise
there won't be any covering up this
mess the most we can hope for is that
the Dame doesn't hold it against us
speaking of which I saw her in more just
now could you tell her what happened H
might sound better coming from you uh
sure leave it to
me St
outcome man can now perhaps the com will
give her something to remember ttian by
well well that one's not even the stolen
comr right it's the new com it's not
even her
own where's the stolen
one or is it the stolen one cuz they
said he bought a new one weren't
expecting any new
branded if it was
a you were still in one piece I see you
pleased to hear that your companions
have
arrived okay I can't make it louder
right now
sorry after they said they would meet
you at a little chapel to the east of
here thank you but you need have come
all this way just to tell
me I was on my way to see you you you
found her
then see
senorita
here I
see my dear
tati It Is by no means uncommon for a
client to fool for a
cortis especially a client who's young
and far from
home but rarely do such Tales have happy
endings
I found this with
Tatian I believe it was
yours
oh I only have one choice of course I'm
giving
it you thought it was by Design thank
you for returning but it's in the MV
version I shall see that it has a place
I didn't even listen to the one that has
it
missing but it must sound so
empty
pineapple one two one two three in my
brain I auto corrected with I'm
going Pine apple one two versus
pineapple I'm going one two one two
three it just makes me wonder maybe it
has a few more other things missing like
maybe some back vocals or harmonies that
aren't as no noticeable when they're
gone but they they just are gone cuz
it's not the final version I don't know
I don't
know doesn't sound weird to you cuz you
listen to the Spotify version First
oh this is why the MV sounded more
[Music]
smooth yeah so if you guys want to I
don't have these Music Services but if
you want to compare any version I upload
onto YouTube like the music videos at
least I don't know if the if the ones
that are automatically generated by
YouTube could also be missing
something so for now you C you could
compare with the mvs that I uploaded cuz
those have the final versions for
sure
yeah I should
go before before you do yeah I have one
last gift a case a token of my thanks
the veil counts among its Patron several
high ranking officers of the Imperial
Army of course it does according to one
of the looser tonged gentlemen it would
appear that the legions are planning to
March South uh to mention the same
thing but did he mention that it was all
of the
legions this is no mere skirmish were I
to guess I'd say the emperor planned to
abandon the capital it's no SC couldn't
possibly be true now could it it's a
campaign take care Clive I
will
bye-bye well even the Skirmish as I've
learned can be pretty hard and
challenging I do plan to play AOE again
next
week and Final Fantasy 16 twice on the
weekend
yeah yeah yeah and members
[Music]
stream and planning
perhaps this is not final but I was
going to put like slight of spire in
there cuz I didn't know what else to put
there but I don't know should I squeeze
in number two of the car review cuz like
I don't know if it's better to do it
ASAP
or if I should should spread it out a
little bit
more will people even come to a part
two you have polar next week I don't
think so I don't think so don't want to
do it too much too
often space it out it's hard to spread
out in a car
oh well by the way I I think it's a good
idea like what one idea I read is that
maybe I should like do a few less uh
criterias even though I think my
criterias were
funny um so I might like ditch
like two or three or even half of them
so that we can go through it
faster yeah I liked it but I want to go
through more but also I don't want to
like speed through them I think it's
nice like the the pacing that we had
until the end where we were going really
fast I think in theory was fine I just
felt like obligated to check as many as
possible that's why it took so long but
generally I don't want these streams to
be that long
either I'll think about it can I delete
my post and give better pictures yeah
but it's going to be a little bit
difficult for me I guess to find the
ones I
haven't cuz there's so so many posts I
have to go for all of them
again might not go for those that were
in the beginning cuz those like we went
through them mostly
already might not even look for them but
yeah you can re a
bit yeah it's just a lot of submissions
and they were so good so it just feels
like ah it feels like such a waste to
not show them
off
no that's funny that some of my ceria
were natural opposite that's fine like
the Cera being a little bit
ridiculous is
[Laughter]
fine that's fine I like that I like it
that way no spooky games next week yeah
like so far I have nothing planned but
next week ends with the 29th then Monday
is the 30th and Tuesday is the 31st so I
can still put some scary games
there isn't the reason why I cancelled
that one waya collab last year because I
didn't have um yeah per permission so I
have to ask in advance I don't know if
she has time for
it can you take a
frame how how I wonder how early I was
supposed to check for perms
okay I'll ask Mama
M
oh rain
now hey remember last year when we were
going to do Fatal
Frame do you want to do it this here
[Music]
finally if yes m
4 41st do you have any time around those
dayses but yeah for me personally like
just doing some scary games on the 30th
and
31st is enough for
me cuz I can't help it I currently want
to play AOE okay
so [\h__\h]
Halloween I'm want to play AOE I'm going
to play Final Fantasy going to play all
these things not going to not going to
let you know although like you know I
already did like some things that I
always wanted to do for Halloween
streams that I felt like I want to do
like doing the pumpkin carving I did
that before so you know and and then I
mean I could I could maybe do something
else like that but yeah maybe I can make
a Halloween themed cooking stream I
don't know
but candy tear list snack
books
wow Halloween only once a year
yeah are you going to dress up for
Halloween streams um if blue will draw
me a
costume I need a
costume
pumpkin soup isn't I was thinking that
too but isn't making pumpkin soup kind
of easy
anyway so I'm just running around so I
can talk in peace without being
interrupted I'll think a bit more about
uh uh like yeah what to do for
Halloween but I I don't think I need to
theme a whole week around that she made
a car prop blue blue you honestly need
to DM me when you made something cuz I
I'll miss
it K of
props there's a car
prop
no the
the okay now I know we'll use it for the
next
one the next time yeah yeah
yeah
and my tummy hoarding a little bit
again I have an upset
[Music]
tummy all right racing waa I love racing
waa but I don't know I guess with my
swimsuit outfit swimsuit you could draw
a lot of things on top of that
huh it's just going to still move a
little bit funky but there's not so much
fabric that you definitely have to
cover did I finish GTA I
didn't sneaky
gaml maybe I play Metal Gear
Solid
I None worth mentioning as I was telling
Jill it's worse than I thought the
capital's crawling with
soldiers and here I am the deserter come
home which is why we'll be taking the
back
door which one I'm sure there's many
doors we're we're taking the door where
are we bringing it
to why are they always try to do funky
things with doors we should just open it
and walk
in
don't make it so
complicated ah the
volume oh that looks nice that looks so
British the pleasure I don't mean you
know it's the color and the alley and
woo wow
wow
nice
[Music]
cheer up you
two can't think of a safer place in the
Empire than
it uh
uh really doesn't seem very
private
he's paying her to be quiet so then how
do we proceed we'll be using the glass
what what is she going to do is she
going to like walk into the room where
they're doing things and be like hey
here's money be
quiet that's kind of awkward the the
dude who who's like in there is probably
not going to be very happy about that
tonight just after
sun where the shards are loaded for
transport that is one of the most of
SRE but not the most which is a
stu besides I know a shortcut straight
to the heart oh a
shortcut and how exactly did you come to
know about this fatal [\h__\h] in the
Empire's armor that's just say I may
have attempted something similar
before may have ended up running for
dear life after being
disced but that's not
important Sid if the mother crystals
truly are the cause of the blight if you
wound me Jill what I'm trying to say is
if the powers that be know all of this
why do they sit idle and allow it to
continue in case you haven't noticed the
God-fearing people of this realm and
their Pious leaders care for but one
thing themselves and they'll do whatever
it takes to hold on to power the rest of
us are just a means to an end the moment
you raise your voice against them you
decried as an outlaw clapped in irons
and slung in a cell to
rot and
Outlaw whoever controls the crystals
controls the realm but our kind can
wield magic without them to our rulers
we must seem the most convenient of
tools and the most dangerous
M but what makes them think they have
the right to use
us to leave us to die when our bodies
are
spent does a nobleman weep for a broken
mug a t tunic that's just how it is back
then Our Fate means nothing to
them no this isn't a battle you can win
with
words believe me I've Tred
but nothing ever gets through the world
is simply not ready to listen so to hell
we're talking if they won't give us a
say we'll decide our Fates another way
you can't blame a man for wanting to
bring an end to all this can
you no I can't but what of all the
people you mean to Rob of their comfort
I'm happy for them to call you outlaw s
me
outlaw I'll wow don't insult yourself so
much at least pretend to take it
seriously five have a little faith Jill
even if you don't think much of my
choice of
digs it means my deeds will be
remembered I'll gladly play the role of
villain oh I'm a
villain but first we have a gate to
crash and once we're in there'll be no
turning back so your best Make Ready the
world won't save itself now we're
crashing get why not open
it are we the
baddies
bad catch me if you can't and I don't
even like that song just saying why is
it in my brain get it out of my
hand where are the K-pop fans
huh oh we should hack into the gate
right
ha the
gate and oh you've reached a pivotal
moment in the story if you continue you
will not be able to
return feel like I've already reached
many pivotal points and you didn't tell
me about
this well what do I say should I
save uh how do I save
now I can't go into settings
I guess I'll just go here for
now you won't be able to do any side
quests you haven't done yet oh
no my plan's to do all the side
quests oh while we're here in this
menu what should we activate we have
1,100 points oh I was saving up for
these wasn't I and like upgrades here
but I still don't have
enough what this summon the storm of
fireballs that Circle around Clive
damaging nearby
Targets wait how do
I how would that be
activated is that like one of the r uh
R2
skills well look at that
skill attack while charging
mhm
should I then let's get this
one cuz people like this
one replaces a phoenix SK okay I'll
upgrade it too while I'm at
it oh summon a tornado that slowly hunts
down nearby enemies and upon in snaring
them inflicts multiple hits is this one
good
hey but like can I do anything while I'm
waiting for the tornado to
end do I just watch it it's not really
good you won't see
[\h__\h] I was I was thinking like okay what
do I do while this is happening uh
relax makes your life a bit harder oh
really okay maybe not that necessary to
have that
one
[Music]
okay so w wait we're we're
replacing one of these uh maybe maybe
the heat wave I don't really even like
it that much we'll do ignition instead
and check it
out uh I
think what do you
think he oh you wanted to replace heat w
W to awesome
awesome um I still have 4 481 points but
I might
just I might just uh save
them yeah I might just save
them speaking of
saving oh I can refund Heatwave you
think I
should
damn
okay 110 120 points
back this is how you do it you just like
get rid of some that you're not actively
using damn
okay some smaller things I could
upgrade
ooh should I master charged
magic I could upgrade
this what happens if I upgrade
these yeah I I do use charge magic a
lot okay oh yeah yeah
yeah reduces charge time oh noise for
like the the like the long
charge I I guess I don't use the the
charging that much though I just go like
the I use the quick one on
mostly yeah near instant at Max oh okay
well if I'm like in a moment where I
want to take distance from an enemy to
also maybe think
about what do I do
then while keeping a safe distance I can
shoot a bunch of those stronger magic
balls
maybe okay so we
saved pet
tole
okay get it boy a good boy oh s tole oh
my wounds boy oh thank you does he even
know the difference of these words
anymore they're all the same to him
probably at this point Sorry I saw an
item I have to pick it
up there's another one in the back but
let's just tangil all right um ah wait
one more thing that I wanted to
do the effects could be a little bit
lower voice over doesn't get any louder
but I can make the master higher and
then the music a little bit
lower oopsie and this a little bit oh
actually yes turn it
off I I didn't hear my controller making
any any
noises brightness too
dark
really can't change it here ah
here
all
right I'll just you know in
between maybe your screen's too
dark okay do I have to save again to
save the options that I just did
maybe
onion it's called onion sword
what what
oh it's something I can
claim what
what wait I got an onion
sword that's so weird
[Music]
what ah I should have used it earlier
and it would have been pretty
strong H it's a class in earlier games
what it's a reference
an onion Knight does it look like an
onion not
really it's weaker anyway ooh
Invictus what that's fancy
too okay anything else we want to
[Music]
change no
no healing potency go go go
damage
okay ready to
go you keep
to Drake's
head
oh
wow this is the back door
basically
there are not nearly enough men here
then it's fortunate the city guard
doesn't take Sentry assignment as
seriously as you
do this BS well I'll be a first this may
not be such a terrible plan after all
and what exactly is that supposed to
mean only that your last secret shortcut
was nowhere near as secret as you
claimed but that's half the fun of it
Life's too short for perfect plan
plans you want a plan that will keep you
on your toes stop you growing old and
complacent worked for you has
it Clyde my boy even life's smallest
challenges offer the opportunity to grow
and to change you must Embrace these
moments allow them to suffuse your heart
with a deep sense of
fulfillment narrowly escaping death at
the hands of an enemy is not my idea of
fulfillment why Jill such a side
character my God they should give her
more
dialogue just wondering if the two of
you had
finished right we might for the
mother right destroy it and the whole
thing should come tumbling
down and if the passage to the inner
sanctum is
guarded then we embrace the moment and
use it to grow and change she has a
major arc later okay I'm looking forward
to
that just shy for
now just Jill was wasted sad sad this
way let's go to stay how can you run so
fast I can only go sneaky NY NYY
sneaking like a
snake don't worry the is EMP
to oh rats ew go
away we're sneaking so fast wow wow wow
wow normally when I sneak I go slow dude
chill all
right let's get this
whole what what do you mean with
that your jump in Kill Them
All what does he mean we get this over
with he means jump
right they not from the garison I swear
this passage used to be enemies Upon Us
of course it did
Perfect Plans di Perfect Plans was that
a stronger
one that's n it wasn't you cuz somebody
said it's almost
uh almost instant so I far that was
already it second to
go
oh what I can even change directions I
think while I was doing
that I I think the battle music is
louder than before the master volume I I
made too
high oh wait that
oh [\h__\h] there I go go again oh I cannot
do it oh but it still uses up all of
the damn
it
o accepted the truth too
late yeah music too
loud
here there we
go
R2 they love doing that they love
implementing that they never stood a
chance you're welcome well can't walk
through it have to break
it the main tunnel infiltrating the
system that be my guess there is
centuries everywhere
centuries what
centuries
uh oh there we go a guards
oh why climb over it did look like you
could climb
over well no we want to break
it
and all good things must come to an end
we might have a bit more company from
now on all right Captain they all come
from summon the Canon at
[Music]
once why are you up so
hot you got oh my
God to by the way guys I
think I I think
don't let them get away stay down I
think I remembered the thing you know
what to do boy and this time I wrote it
down the other stream idea that I had
that was kind of related to what I did
last
[Music]
time you know what to do boy cuz it was
also something with where I have to
purchase something and then compare
it so my other
idea is to
we uh what was that website where this
like American website kind of where you
can buy things pretty cheap was it
called
[Music]
fiber not wish I mean like a commission
I think this I want like commission
things on Fiverr
what have we here and then review them
insects come to be
squashed you will find my mortar and I
only too happy to oblig yeah yeah yeah
shut up looks nice though damn do the
talk then let's shut him up yeah cuz
like they have like anything right that
you
could uh
commission and the stuff that you can
get there even for a good quality often
is out
quite good
actually oh you can't move this guy with
that skill actually
wow L fire what a
flamethrower a
flamethrower wait I I oh I was not quite
sure yet if I want to oh feel do um like
buying again one cheap
one then we better make this expensive
version of one thing and then compare
that or just generally just generally
hire a couple of things
from fivr boy and judge it just hey hey
hey hey to hey hey stop that I don't
like
that get
him get him
boy sick of to oh wait did I miss the
50% thing again yeah I
did this rating would be fine
to see look at look at my oh not this oh
look at my 10 times Precision Dodge
[Music]
W hey no
hey don't let them get
away all got [\h__\h]
you yeah okay I already used up
everything
you know what to do boy it's okay SI
tole get
him why won't you
die is
he to paint Miniatures for him ranging
from 20 to $200 oh yeah yeah so sopite
Dad see again it's like something that
YouTubers have already done a lot but
the stream
format for
YouTubers there's
nothing we haven't done that really
let's end his tourment haven't taken oh
the
opportunity you know what to do
boy sick up tole sick up to woo w
what
to where am I going
got wait his HP is full again wait wait
I didn't realize his HP is
full don't let them get
away
all right
then face two he mored
indeed nice dodging
W oh the fire
again like he blows himself up now I
like that ow
[Music]
you know what to do
boy and The Rocketeer oh [\h__\h] he does it
twice okay
okay I underestimated this guy a little
bit
ouch get him
boy not this time no not this
time stop it I don't like it when you
laugh for [\h__\h]
sake this
time stop it for [\h__\h] sake okay yeah
uh you is this like gu where you can
also add a lot of extra hits I
wonder you know what to do for me oh he
wasn't even staggered for that long cuz
that one fire attack is like pretty long
actually I
[Music]
guess
hey Max
dagger too
[Music]
slow oh stop being so
annoying get
him too
slow d boy
he always he just always blows himself
up now I love that I love that for
him get him boy there we
go don't worry I
remember
get
ah not this
time sick come
tole uh uh
uh oh I did it ability finish
Imperial
con slay
yes
yes the favor of The Inferno increases
ignition ignition the one that I I'm
using now damage by 12% oh thank you
guys it wasn't the best fight but uh
it's fine I underestimated him I didn't
think he would have a face too I'll
never get used to
that Kiko know he was still a man
I'm only drowned in ether there's no way
for anyone to go just like
orix come
on bit sloppy
yeah not as sloppy as a sloppy Jo death
sentence in this place what's a sloppy
joe again not that Sylvester car is that
some kind of food
right
hopefully
yeah a bad Burger a bad
Burger wait why are some people reacting
weirdly the messy burger right yeah yeah
yeah ground beef sandwich that's a
burger ground beef sandwich who said
Being a dominant doesn't have its
they're gross Sid really this is an
ether flood there shouldn't be one here
should there the workers couldn't
survive this well well it wasn't here
last time I can tell you that which
means we need to be quick The Ether
won't hurt us but I'd rather not find
out what it's done to everyone
else that reminds me a bit of uh other
games I played but I know the jrpg curse
of similar
stories
a soupy
burger by the way when I was in
Japan um I went to a special Tonka to
place with jenma finally when did I we
promised to go to eventually like I
showed her once and we've been planning
to go there for a
while oh they turned into yeah evil
people who can't control themselves
Monsters of
them put them and I took a little video
cuz there's this uh this YouTuber back
the
capital who makes why food videos in
Japan she said you could call Japan
eats never mind if ever there was a
reason to Up Sticks an ether blood I
really love that dude's videos his voice
is so calm and the food he reviews it's
really
interesting they would keep the casik
in
casik take too many
risks yeah yeah yeah yeah so like in
that style I I took some footage of the
food that I was eating and I want to do
a voice over and make it like it's a
jpad eat
video going that way
huh sorry I was really excited to talk
about that video yeah they were talking
about akashic and
Isabelle
yeah I was going to upload as a
short but I'll just wait for the moment
when I need uh one right now I don't
need it so I'm just keeping it as a
stock
H
oh oh no no G doesn't look that far G
all right no
cond
no
ah oh the
flag oh yeah and a
[\h__\h] bloody hell
mate some help hold
on these late
[\h__\h]
don't drop him don't drop
him okay if we didn't drop him then what
was just seen
for freaking dramatic something's going
to come out of that like not quite as
spr as I used to be bottom I'll take
that is it thank
you look on the bright
side at least you won't get
lost no b rock yeah I'm waiting for the
b
rock no no all right okay then what was
that for what was that
for why did he not fall down lame lame
make him fall down and make make me have
to pick him up somewhere and struggle
until I get him again cuz now I'm
missing a party member you know that
kind of
stuff war cry some opponents will use
the Ability war cry to invigorate
themselves enhancing performance in
battle look for the H icon and try to
defeat them before they can deal too
much damage oh
okay is that a work PR just
now you know what to do boy are they
really that
dangerous did one of them do it did you
do it oh he did
it accept the
truth
yeah [\h__\h] him up [\h__\h] him up cluck him
up cluck him up don't let them get away
kfb clucking
now over here your war cries are worth
nothing go cry in your
bed there boy of your mommy's house you
know what to do boy get him boy can't
see
him got him
stuck get
clucked toxic
[Music]
toxic I'm a DI you don't you know that
you're toxic left or all
right cuz I love what you do don't you
know that you're
[Music]
toxic well is there another path over
there
too there's an
item there was a small hole to crawl
through on the other side
thank you for membership gift
hey okay this is a dead end okay good
good good
good small smaller
ho small
small doesn't make me faster man doesn't
make me faster at
all run button
doco for real for
real hopefully that doesn't collapse
while Sid is under
it
potion I've got a
potion all
right uh ignition out of combat yeah
can
you I can use normal
attacks dead
end
oh where did they come
from got them
both
bad boy bad boy bad boy what you going
to do what you going to do when wa comes
for you sick tole sick
tole get him
boy here that's
enough it's over but at least we
won okay so is the door open now did
they
it's not open how did I get
through if we can open
it could we have opened the other doors
like this too the other
Gates I have perceived the lever my per
perceiving check has succeeded did you
hear narissa
amazing Sun cover of down down down by
the
river I told
her that it was amazing I even had to
tweet about it
twice like holy
moly give them all you've got for it and
I feel like she should do
more more stuff like that
maybe even make an original
song
woo in that kind of
vibe there
boy get HH wasn't too I was too late
again h
over
here nice Hammer
though get
him
ouch this hey there was a raid oh can
stream
over oh sneaky sneaky NY NY NY NY
dead beat sneaking in like their
snake uh wait wait wait let me do this
one new enemies approach I'm not even
done with this
one keep your distance
boy his voice when he talked to too was
so
scary his voice gets so
scary keep your distance boy it's like
from [\h__\h] hell poor dog you must be
like who the [\h__\h] you scared the [\h__\h]
out of
me where is the
focus not this time over
here oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
hey is she healing me how nice of
her you know what to do boy give them
all you've got boy I will oblate you let
them get away I love you
Togo too you're such a good
boy scary
man freaky [\h__\h]
12K iconic just like I
am [\h__\h]
yeah good boy good
boy stylish
wow what a flexi Kick K
kick I want High potions not normal
potions come on
can't we combine the normal potions into
high potions when I have access a coral
sword
interesting I see they replace that
wooden door with something a little more
sturdy
sturdy let me break heels too yeah I'll
use it in combat next
time okay uh 3 2 5
3 what happened to two we need
car where's the rest of
them
five once
more hi soon as you're trying now
they're not even sinking up they have to
sink up it's
delayed
one hand sign now they were on time as
if that was going to keep us
out it what do you mean it was too late
did the what did the skeletons do when I
didn't notice that they were raiding
me ooh we got my light on
again sneaky NY NY NY NYY NY NYY saky
sneaky like their
snake should I wear the new sword it's
just a coral sword is it actually
better no I don't want to see that shut
up gear
it is coral while razor sharp is also
painfully
brittle cool the mother Crystal's just
up ahead is it I can't see a thing oh
she's saying everybody keep it solid in
my head it was everybody keep it silent
cuz you're silent when you're sneaking I
don't
know NY NY n n
n oo
pretty
shiny it matches my my hair
accessory silent snake the famous silent
snake there's no one
about yep that's a part of a mother
Crystal mhm
mhm it's
me what legit though
big but
this there that's our way into the inner
sanctum
sick
oh you'd think that have patched that up
by
now sorry St the Empire is
it I can climb over don't you don't mean
act like you
can't my little game of hide and seek
with baham ended here at tragic cost to
this remarkable
architecture don't blame me he started
punched a [\h__\h] hole in the wall but
how did he make it get out of
life now walked you should try
it I
walked what is he talking about what is
this thing called
Walking oh
no them again is there something you
want to tell me maybe later yeah they I
wanted to say they're familiar to
[Music]
me get
him stay down stay
down don't want to hear nothing coming
out of your mouth
again get him down
down
[Music]
oh my HP is full was I
healed by the
[Music]
game but how could those creatures from
Phoenix gate be here in the mines the
two places connected
somehow
pretty are they
connected
I don't know maybe it's just from the
ather you know these creatures just
appear wherever there's
ather
nice do you enjoy the game I
do I definitely
do
is this
Rivendell not quite letr you who knows
maybe it is
inspired hey
oh nice
heal don't let them get away it's
over
give them all you've got
boy there
boy sick him tole you know what to do
boy over
here it is a fun
skill let's
go don't let them get
away
uh oh oh there's a big one oh yeah that
one
my ah hey
okay dodging like a
pro get
him hey
get him boy sick him
tole get
[Music]
him
ouch I like the sound that makes the
[Music]
the get him
boy
not this time
whoa sick tole I thought I was going to
be too late there
boy you good
Jill Jill is such a mommy
name especially cuz I'm watching Home
Improvement
man give them all you've got for
let's
go Jill's the
mommy in Home
Improvement oh nice Parry good
pares get ah nice oh my God like the
sound of when I can do that it just blit
ends in so much with all the other
flashy sounds
sometimes I don't know
this [\h__\h]
hell what is this thing over
here
oh nice more more more more more more
more more more more more more and more
more and more oh suddenly
dead he dance with the reaper oh yeah
the Scythe yeah really cool weapon she's
trying to reap me but I won't let
you I shall not be
reaped how many more nice surprises do
we get cuz I'm running out of potions
when I was in the Imperial Army soldiers
assigned to the glass gate would tell
stories about something they called The
Guardian can't say I saw anything like
that when I was last here then again I
can't say I made it this far H let's
just be careful then okay seems like we
have reached the end
actually I so just getting normal
potions I will fail at least once
but I will give it a legit proper try of
course first can I walk through that
door maybe there's Potions there secret
no okay all right yeah I appreciate this
for a
moment
wow damn this looks like an end game
kind of place but we're still just mid
game fake
door where did that come
from oh if I had to
guess
baham poor Beast no another victim of
the
flood that's too small
Yu-Gi-Oh ice
dragon oh you handsome has a Scher fight
he wants ready Clive no
always what's
that get
[Music]
him over
here keep your distance
boy sick to it's so
big you know what to do
boy sick
what solar
beam there boy give them all you've got
boy almost 50% get him
boy ah he did we get it
no almost
almost now now there it
is when I look out for it I always
notice it like too early when I don't
look out for it I'm often too late over
here oh I should have done go [\h__\h]
wasted
there boy but so far damage not from
like the damage I take hasn't been too
bad watch me regret what I just said
really
[Music]
soon sick of tole I got some fancy magic
shots
too get him
boy too slow
sck tole there
boy sck
tole nice yeah pretty
predictable over
here damn get
him but his HP
man [\h__\h] damage Sponge Bob
That's What I Call You SpongeBob get him
boy sick of what a waste of my
time get
him okay now it's my
time give them all you've got
Bo give them all I
got don't let them get away
1,000 oh h where's he off to
now he wants to show me his fancy dance
moves
o dud I DOD it completely wow where is
he going where is
he too slow not this
time oh [\h__\h]
I thought it was over and Kaboom okay
n I've slowly made my way to you
again just here to talk come on give me
a
chance sick of
tole accept the
truth deny the lies
let me attack you you little
[\h__\h] why do you go to the head I don't
like that can't even do much there over
here there
boy oh uh uh
what
[\h__\h] I messed up the% spend timing again
Yoo there
boy it's
okay we're doing it
easily sick of
tole not this
time
oh
King a distance
boy let go give
the don't let them get
away there boy 6,000 I didn't even use
go
16.6 oh Dragon Dance yes dance for
me too slow oh a fourth one oh oh he's
spamming oh he's spamming
everything not this time
[Music]
wa nice I have the situation under
control have I even healed one over
here get
him I don't think
boy not this
time you know what to do boy oh no get
out of there okay okay okay okay
nice get
him
give them all you've got
boy oh sick of
tole
ciz
oh yeah yeah I know that procedure I do
it at kfp every
day wait you don't fly away when you at
50% man there we
go come here what come
on get him boy almost
there if this is like the biggest fight
they have here then okay if there's
still something after this then what the
[\h__\h] get him so unnecessary
then you know what to do
get
him get him
boy be careful Sid you're right in there
you're right in there
hey all
right
okay yeah why did it have to be 20
minutes like it wasn't even difficult to
dodge anything from this one that was
well it's too long but I barely got
damage is it just because the enemy is
too weak or is it my my my high level
gamer girl skin skills hm which one is
it too easy for me either
way are you all
right
fine
on the inner sanum lies just beyond
chances are the Palace guard knows we're
here we should move a palace guard not
that any sane Commander would send his
men into a place a wash with this much
easther
mhm cve I the the stoning if this all
works and the blessing Fades things are
likely to get worse for Our Kind before
they get better being the last to wield
ether will make our talents that much
more sought after by which I mean Hunted
I just hope in the end they'll see that
we didn't have any other choice that it
was the only way to get us to a better
place
mm and here I was thinking I was the
uncertain
one we all have our uncertainty two
three of us have faith in
you then it all starts here I've heard
I've heard several arguments that like
it's early in the game later on it'll be
better because your skills are going to
be stronger but like they should balance
that that's not so
tedious just because it's early in the
game it's not even we're in mid game
now missing title Sid the vicious was
it
[Music]
I'm not okay
well I'll know when I reach mid
game it feels like mid
game what awaits us behind the Gates
we're almost there anyone having second
thoughts me I have third thoughts we're
with you to the end Sid then what are we
waiting
for
potion I need a high potion please what
the [\h__\h] why do they only give normal
potions so
lame and
horse hey I should do an M horse with
that I think I tried it before like can
I do a horse and I did
like hey not too bad but when I was
practicing it I was like nah this ain't
going
anywhere I'm
horse I'm horse that's enough that's
good enough it's
beautiful don't touch it
SRE don't touch
it don't get too
close
oh well that didn't work what if it's a
delayed reaction your biggest
sword mine's
bigger mine's bigger thank you Clive but
I meant that
figuratively the Call's clearly made of
sterer
stuff blow it up become uh your icons
going to have a fit when she is about
this stand back it's about to get
cramped in
here okay they doing what I just said
right they're listening to me they're
sentient stand back he's
moring sod soda show us your
power
oh
no power is
power that's more like it his beard
looks like chunky
wonky oh why does he get to do the cool
stuff Clive
look what is a black
hole what is that
Revenge
oh that's why he got to do that so that
he gets hit and not me
him wait this is literally like that the
Japanese horror
thing come to me I can't do this without
you
die Dieu it will come to
you yeah that go again male
version where are
you uh creepy as [\h__\h] what is that
supposed to
be oh come on what is Jill doing by the
way can she turn into her f
sha oh he's still there
[Music]
cool we going to have an intervention
later with
C what the
[\h__\h]
where the hell am
I oh no what is that oh with with the
thing in him
okay he going to open his eyes oh there
are open we going to fight or
what
to I've been here
before
what we were
we you you again where are you what do
you
want
[\h__\h] it's still alive
[\h__\h]
oh yeah just keep it in I
guess
never accept your truth moment I
see get out of my head I don't answer to
you I'm leaving one way or
another don't make me fight these stupid
minion that's
enough I may have enjoyed the Minion
ride in US
J Universal
Studios but I'm not enjoying this Min
R
taka the jokester Phoenix comedian of
all
[Music]
times two birds with one stone two
minions with one
attack comedi
hand what what is this what is stuff
what is the stuff on the ground by the
Flames
Yoo oh oh oh what the this
[Music]
time fancy
[\h__\h] oh why'd you go to that one I
wanted you to go to the other one
you're
finished W forgot the MMO raid mechanics
in any MMO that I played like I played
so many I never really was the raiding
type of
person like big raids I only really what
I was fine of like Dungeons
yeah I like doing
dungeons what else can he do with a SM
smaller
party hey don't split it there
what okay good no no
problem so
young
W that's
[Music]
enough oh
splitting Get Wrecked
you strike me as a ff14 Glam kind of
player probably
yeah very distressful ala yeah yeah yeah
I think so too like they're fascinating
but like that doesn't look fun anymore
it's like ants
fighting for no
reason oh oh
okay
once you learn them they're fun as
hell I want to do other
stuff and some of the mm RPGs I played
they they would have like like an
arena PVP Arena small small small I
enjoyed
those chilling around those too just
hanging oh
music what's going on
but this is
mine let me accept the truth
again
oh what's this scene
man I think this dude that we're facing
is the rotten core that I have in side
of
me I remember
now I am
fire okay so
tacky I am okay calm down what why are
they so tacky my
God I'm Bing if again mhm meele ranged
they jump yeah
press triangle after executing a
fireball burst to perform a de
devastating melee finish known as
backdrop uh
okay so
twice that's what they do
yeah uhhuh okay okay okay
H Wildfire Sprint over extended distance
wow
[Music]
M
damn he can lunge so
far
easy tyen it's called
tyen
what I don't
quite do they just mean the the magic
first
combo oh wow what's going
on
oh
oh what dodging like
wildfire use l while holding uh circle
is an effective me okay
okay
another oh my
God
[Music]
baa B Baka Baka baka
I know the dance for that by the
way
[Music]
okay you you happy yet you done all
right it's done not surprised right it's
a fun dance really
easy
we oh he's back he's
me the rotten version of
me how many more can there be
e
is is he giving me some more power or
what oh
freaking oh
[\h__\h] it's all in my
head this whole game is Just Happening
all in my
head
need a
hand who okay that looks pretty cool
that design what a glow
up I don't want
to As You Wish four arms but no legs he
Speck into legs
[Applause]
maybe all right the music
do waa you little [\h__\h] Fire Light by the
way what's that is that not a
heal ah
oh it is a
heal doesn't sound like a
heal
yeah
techno holy
[Music]
[\h__\h]
I'm in the
air yeah I know what you want to do let
me go oh
what this is
like this is
like like those
games
what but you have to make your body in
the shape of the the stencil
K what what the
[Music]
what
oh wa I need to rub my
nose wait who who
up
okay a you little
[\h__\h]
oh let's
[Music]
go he
staggered but I don't even really have
any of those like cool attacks so I'll
just keep on doing my thing they're
strong enough on its
own oh you staggered for a long time
[\h__\h] 5 100K
damage all right all
r i no
no wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
how am I supposed to make it when I'm
there when my starting point is like so
ah
hey no I hate this
sucks I can dodge through it oh well I
tried it once but it didn't seem to be
working I guess my timing was
wrong but it seems like we're
[Music]
done oh
oh [\h__\h]
[Applause]
meteor
eat
this ball a I pressed the wrong
button never have I ever pressed the
wrong button in a scene like this oh
[\h__\h] no please have mercy don't kill me
now
hey
[Music]
hey just trying to show you possible
options but I stand up and I come back
even
stronger engulfed in Flames like on a
golf
course I shall
now fire in the AER let's [\h__\h]
go what what button was it what button
am I going to
press uh
uh okay I can do that I'm trying
Clash no 500 with one 500k with one
punch
typh
vanquished so who was this Typhon when
will I know I say it's me in the end
it's all just
me everything's
me I am all there is to
be Typhon not Typhon it's Typhon and
know somehow it sounds the same why does
tyen and tyen sound the
same Ty tyon
Typhon why does it sound the
same of my accent how do you say Typhon
with a t and tyon with a p t t Tyson
Tyson but that's too much of an S
Tyson
typh I never thought about that until
now were I saying it wrong all this
time eating Mike Tyson's ass but that's
also
different all
right enjoy your nap you're
wounded this it's on here
scratch all right the we we'll find you
a
Healer
yeah no you
won't
[Music]
what I think Final Fantasy is plenty of
a horror game guys I know who you
are and if you think I'm going to let
you have him
[\h__\h] oh oh Sid do you Chad think again
you want to [\h__\h]
chat c you you
nutcase you
puppet [\h__\h] puppet letting himself
be
puppeteered stop talking in tongues I do
not understand life does not see the
subtitles okay we do he doesn't or does
he does he see the
subtitles one left I'll do me one
left of those
there's oh one left of the cigarettes
that he
has try not to talk don't
die don't
don't die to this
music Clive
yeah for so
long I thought I had all the
answers but then I met
you and I learned it wasn't a good death
we should be fighting for but a better
life it's all very well man reclaiming
his
fate but if he can't choose how he meets
it what's the
point
so I made a
[Music]
choice he's going to give me his
power
don't do
this
oh got to catch them all the rest is in
your
hands
s blessing is a prison I thought he was
in it for the long run if it's an outlaw
the world needs to help it break
free
stop please oh s do sits always die
early
none
better than you is that just what they
do no not
always oh
man wait is there some lore maybe on the
things that I saw
no not
really when a heart shatters so two does
the mountain around it oh okay so when
we're out of here the mountain should
have shattered since the since time IM
immemorial sanctuaries have been built
around the hearts for the worship and
protection of these Irreplaceable
Treasures there's something new here he
makes plans to see the mothers fall that
valesa and her people might be
saved H okay so nothing about the
weirdo
[Music]
maybe that's why they did that stupid
bridge
scene
oh respawning already or
what
in Ashen grip let Ember glow to Kindle
Flames a new
Joshua is he attacking me or is he
attacking that weird AO
[\h__\h] oh
oh oh he's so pretty
now his
[Music]
lashes
just I'm sorry
Clive had I arrived but a moment
sooner
T good
boy do you remember me
boy I saw you protect them that was very
brave I know you're there Tima
timal
oh youve learned our
name what else have you learned Phoenix
respawned already as I
said my travels have revealed much about
you and your
Ambitions I know that it was you who
tore me from my
brother okay and I know that it is his
power that you seek he
knows but know this Phoenix FEA hey if
you want him don't drop you'll have to
go through me they're
precious very well oh breath of mine
ancestors fill these lungs that I may
dispel the songs of
suffering a
disturbance
you oh
is AI my
brother alone let's
go I'm glad we're not fighting anymore
this is getting us
nowhere we
agree no more games
phixs we are come to claim our
vessel
but slow he's so slow and I said no
slow like a [\h__\h]
slop
[Music]
oh yes these Flames are
nothing you will know what it is to
burn yours is a fleeting form I'm not
fool enough to think I can harm you oh
but to protect my brother I don't have
to T me te me te
me sick him
[Music]
too he's truly
me
yeah oh wait
he didn't he didn't know yet right that
he's alive right he was still under the
impression he's dead right
right
waade wait these are not flames of
Destruction yeah he didn't okay have you
forgotten already sorry guys Final
Fantasy 16 spoiler
[Music]
alert
is he like sucking it
in W it's like a vacuum
cleaner do it with a panty hose though
with the
[Music]
stocking that won't get so stinky
inside o just try and get to my brother
now SL
seemed oh okay we should maybe get out
of here
um She's So unbothered by that right
next to him couple of centimet next to
him just everything falling
apart well he's a phoenix
so beautiful that's pretty it's like
wait this is like Disney
it's gives me Disney Vibes the castle
like oh trophy earn I'm
Lawless no I'm
sidess don't know who law is but I'm
sitless Sur you H me
God no that's my hang out
right must be
here ah it's the five head
guy we're all [\h__\h] dead oh Sid is Sid
is dead guys Sid help us where is he oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] bastard he'll survive right he'll
just have one
eyeless and he'll be sneaky NY NY NY NY
NY NY NY sneaking like he's snake we've
got to
go he's alive he's alive not without
this why why will they kill a sid but
not Gaff what the
[\h__\h] Sid is not among the dead shall I
sender stol
us he is among the Dead
actually well
actually oh yeah oh
[\h__\h] is that
the what the [\h__\h] wait
what Titan but TI wait Titan was uh a
Titan like not an icon where the hell
are is a Titan just a
Titan where the hell are
you no he is okay okay it's the it's the
benedicta guy where did he come
from the big guy
right what you mean cupcake the finest
silks from the master Weavers of Randa
come come feel it softeners chak CH
sausage all from Green
Farm how can you take a
bite oh this this is giving me I've got
peppers and peas beans and beets if it
goes in a
pot
cives it's all
freshes restoratives restoratives
restoratives hu ointments
puses might I interest you in a potion
my lady perhaps a soothing Sal to ease
the aches of the road the
eggs eggs eggs
eggs F wait what five years I wish you
well but may the mothers guide you five
yearsa curatives
restoratives o
peses cures
restoratives
what what we went under cover for 5
years doing
what there it is 5 years
later
what it's good to see you 5 years and
still wearing the same
clothes
what have we
learned and same hair
length to the to the millimeter the
bearers are locked up in an Old
Courthouse on the edge of town oh but
did he always have a beard like that
tell you who is there to make sure they
stay that way the Beards new ca's
private
guard waa
immersion and not a very good one at
that took him 5 years to grow that
guys
testosterone not
existent 5 years to
grow another what does he hope to gain
from
this I'll have the captives free before
nightfall you do nothing of the sort our
comrades didn't give their lives for you
to get your throat slit in a God's
forsaken
slum that's not going to happen so those
in the courthouse should be be left to
suffer that's not what I said I simply
meant it doesn't have to be you who
frees
them damn it
all you're as stubborn as the old Sid
was I'm the new
Sid
what so there's two s don't say I didn't
warn you in this game you're s now and
if anything happens to him we're
finished what why why am I taking his
identity cuz better than my own or
what I'm sick
now
I am Sid am
Sid please we don't know anything you
have to believe us we'd help you if we
could but you're helping us
already forgive him my Lord he did not
mean to offend quiet you no sign of
Hugo wager he thinks as highly of his
minions traps as we do then this should
be easy don't hurt us I beg of you quiet
means quiet branded
scam
yeah now that Sid is dead maybe Jill
will talk more it's going to be all
right I'm here to even the odds any
objections thund it's him the outlaw sit
here yeah yeah totally I'm s yeah
exactly did I put makeup over my
mark come on
go summon the
others the bear is
[Music]
safe
okay the power of Thunder C is claimed a
portion of Icon ramu's Essence ATT
tuning with ramu not only changes the
elemental aspect of Clive's magic spells
but also allows the access to several
new iconic abilities such as
thunderstorm which rains Le bolts down
on all nearby enemies knocking them back
ability details are found in the
abilities tab in the main
menu Rambo iconic feet Blind Justice can
be used to launch a barage of ball
lightning at up to nine targets
determined by locking onto them the
lightning will temporarily remain fixed
to the Target and can be ignited by
striking
it epic reading baby she dies here I
registered none of
that pile
Drive what is that what what do what
does that do what what is that what what
what what
what what is that do oh a little shooty
shoot what that's it
what what it's just a pew
pew I mark up to okay how do I wait like
how am I like like this and then is
there
[Music]
more okay
go
okay hold hold do I have to like go over
them with my cursor in here bring me his
[Applause]
head how many are
there Titan sendes
regards uh-huh
uhhuh did that hit them
okay what is this SP
storm this
[Applause]
one there let's go to that guy over
there Stone scepter seems like he can do
some magic that we don't want
involved
over
here it chains
attacks yeah yeah I know it's supposed
to shock multiple enemies at once so let
him play with the K didn't use it
much they brought a pet well if there's
really like this many then I understand
with this many enemies okay then I think
it makes
sense meow
no you'll pay for what you've done
s those things are fast we'll have to be
[Music]
faster not that fast
tph
get him what was
that
meow whose cat is
[Music]
this ni job they lost their
cats I hope they they're
chipped a wait uh oh y now when you have
three of them you have to look through
them even more more but I made it in
time I was like Hey them out there they
to do something there too slow go and
see I didn't forget about the Precision
counter it just didn't really work well
today until this moment over here
because oh your
because I was just not really you know
there yet today and this this just kind
of also works better with this
enemy too slow when I'm close to it like
this it gives me quite a nice
[Music]
opening oh [\h__\h] I say that and then I
continue to
fail
[Music]
spe get
him
go over
[Music]
here cute oh was these
maybe we should bring out the the cats
next maybe then it will be
nice this is exactly how smoovie behaves
in the morning so we're really familiar
with it
TB oh there we
go oh catnip could work too yeah no
honestly this cat might be on catnip
right now that's the
problem is going bit crazy it's having
it the Zoomies it's having the
Zoomies remember the
story did I tell you about the story of
smoovie and the
balcony did I tell you about
that
yeah that happened like ages ago ages
and I finally recently met the neighbor
that lives there for the first time I
don't know how I've met so many other
neighbors but like this this is the
first time I met that neighbor please
tell again uh to make it really short um
like uh my cats they're like okay
they're a few years old now um and I
never had an issue with them acting
weird on
balconies um they were never even like
showing interest in jumping on top of
the the the fence or whatever they were
not really interested in it but there
was this one time when I had smoothie
outside on the balcony and she just came
from the toilet and when they disc come
from the toilet they're like so zoomy
sometimes and then she like suddenly
starts
zooming running to the side where it
connects to the neighbor and like jumps
like really quickly like there's no way
for me to stop her but she goes so fast
she jumps up she jumps on the fence
takes like only touches it with two
steps and you know jumps over there and
I had a heart attack watching that it
was so scary and um then I was trying to
get her back but it was kind of a
difficult situation like I couldn't like
when I was trying to reach over to reach
her it was like dangerous for me too I
could have fallen off too if I not
careful and she was just like exploring
the other balcony like sniffing around
and I she just was not paying attention
to me me and I was hoping that maybe the
neighbors would notice but it seemed
like they're not at home cuz then after
a little bit of me trying to you know be
like smoothie smoothie come come here
and she not her not being interested uh
and occupied with sniffing everything I
really quickly ran like the like from
the outside I ran out of my apartment to
their apartment's door trying to you
know get someone to open the door
ringing the bell but nobody was opening
so I quickly ran back CU I didn't want
to leave any pairs of my eyes off of her
cuz I was worried she would try coming
back in a moment where I wasn't there
and then slip and then fall like I
wanted to be there when she would
attempt to come back cuz I wasn't able
to get her back um without her you know
attempting to do it but I wanted to give
her
support so I ran back this whole time I
was like freaking the [\h__\h] out was
losing my mind I and and I was at the
same time also trying to keep chunky
wonky like
away and then uh yeah I came back and
then eventually I I got her to like
there was like a a planter that she
would jump on first and then on the
fence from the neighbors so she came to
the planter planter but she wasn't like
quite like she seemed also uncertain
like about how to get
back but I I I bent bent my body uh over
the fence and over this like weird
wall in in quite a dangerous Manner and
try my best to grab her quickly and
bring her safely over back to me it was
kind of
dangerous and since then I haven't let
her outside on the balcony really yet
anymore cuz I'm too scared like it only
happened once in how many years I don't
even
know yeah you don't remember I was
telling us that the part of me rescuing
her but yeah so I never talked to the
neighbors before I never saw them before
this other day I saw them at the like
one of them I'm sure they live there as
a couple at least but I only saw the
lady and I you know we were like waiting
for the elevator and I was like hm well
you know I don't like being akwardly
silent at the elevator especially if
it's a neighbor so let me tell her what
happened so I started telling her this
crazy story about um my cat jumping over
to their
balcony and I told her don't worry it's
never happening again cuz like I'm not
letting her out anymore but I was hoping
for you guys to be there and all
that
yeah it was a interesting story to tell
in the elevator and made it less awkward
but but also like what the [\h__\h] she was
probably thinking what the what the
[\h__\h]
interesting I just felt like she had a
right to know that um her elevator her
her balcony was um involved in something
like
this will movie ever get balcony
privileges back um yeah maybe if I never
get to like make it cat safe
um maybe you know now it's going to be
winter time so maybe maybe in spring or
something
mhm what the long version have been I
can't really when I say long story short
or so it's still going to be
long you can count on
that
meow so be careful all cat owners when
they just pooped they're excited
probably someone said this before and I
think it might be true they're like they
feel like so much weight is lifted off
of
them cuz they lost hug all the weight
from the
them there's been more than enough
Bloodshed for one
day suddenly feel so
flexible
hey guys you
good he also so
handsome you mad murderer all of our
friends are dead because of you huh do
you hear me they used us as bait bait
till you're you out of your stinking
hole all because you couldn't just let
things be what are you even doing here
we never asked to be
saved did you think we'd thank you
she reminds
me of that
YouTuber uh that everybody was like
worried
about um that
she was like being yeah maybe boxy too
but I think I'm thinking of someone
else
uh yeah I think she was
anorexic yeah Eugen yeah yeah yeah yeah
that Eugene No Marina Joyce okay she
reminds me of all of these
people Marina Joy boxy all of them but
the way she talks and the hairstyle and
the makeup very Marina joyy or yeah more
Marina than Eugenia but all of
them I did watch
um like a what was it like a documentary
or so recently about what happened to
Marina and like she like changed she's
still on the internet but she changed
wow wow wow
W right that was Marina right was it
Marina yeah I think so was it Eugenia I
don't even know anymore in my brain
that's the same
person they'll never forgive us we're
all mugged now
that's so
Marina for five years we fought to
secure a better life for our kind to see
that we are treated equals do you not
want that what we want is to be left
alone every time you show your faces it
is we who
suffer it's all right it just gets
me I'm
sorry we fell for a trap I
guess was fun
though fighting the the
people okay
bye just leave us be this is our home
and this is where we'll stay okay
shees Sid told us this wouldn't be easy
they'll come
round if you say
so we should
go doggy
boogy all right
now we're going to go oh
to okay how does this look oh it doesn't
have the mother Crystal
anymore no I was wondering about that
okay okay let's
go how old is the dog all right
well how old is it now you could
probably figure it out cuz it was a
puppy in the beginning that night 5
years ago we destroyed what for many was
a symbol of Hope for a reason they'll
never know just
pretty we cannot blame them for thinking
us the cause of theiry 18
now though it's to give them a better
tomorrow they see only that we've made
their lives harder
today yet the boil must be lanced if it
is to
heal deep talk I can't help but wonder
if we've made the right
choice when Sid said that he wanted to
create a world where we were free free
to choose our own
path maybe he has a different lifespan I
honestly don't think it mattered to him
if that choice was right or
wrong only that it was our
own I miss
him me too a world but we can live and
die as equals that's what he wanted what
we want
and that's why I bear his
name it's why we've all chosen to bear
his
legacy
and I'm not going to let anything stand
in our
way rides over love birds home sweet
home love
[Music]
birds
nice oh
wow it it always look like
this
oh oh it's a new one
okay hi way to was asking after you
let's go and see him never a dull moment
it looks like annoying to get around
here finish with that log so we can call
it a morning are they un ironically
calling me
Sid or are they
Inon
hard Otto will want to know what
happened in
cnis I expect he'll be in the mess
okay
they know it's just a
title that's so weird name becomes title
that's so weird look it's said stay Al
this time but they're saying it like
it's my
name say my name say my
name no one that's around you say baby I
love you while you playing games my name
my
name acting kind of crazy the others no
we oh there you are Clive he calls me c
word of your adventures arrived this
morning at least one of you sends his
thanks Adventures I doubt Koopa will
miss the fools he sent to catch
me not a single one of the bearers we
Sav showed any interest in coming with
us no one seems Keen to join hands with
an
outlaw any news while we were away none
worth mentioning gav's still off keeping
an eye on the Republican Army
G
understood if anyone needs me I'll be in
the
oh that's me leader of the faction
believed responsible for the shattering
of Drake's head in
ag73 if this single act of infamy s name
quickly spread to the four corners of
Vala and Beyond wow I'm
famous
the the
turtle turtles capable of transmitting
the thoughts of others specifically
those with whom they are tuned it's a
turtle in response to an ancient
incantation they LIF LIF lifi lifi
lified third eyes store these thoughts
in the form of Aer allowing them to be
passed on as when required though only
uh to the intended recipient ooh can you
can you not
like um manipulate them somehow like
hack them I don't
know it's a turtle H stoles are mainly
kept by Royals Nobles and other figures
of Authority for the purpose of sending
secret or urgent messages and are seldom
available to the common folk the
incantation owe me a lost Alan to isak
can be Loosely translated as my will is
now that burden never C our bond shall
be it's a
turtle the last one we saw got hacked
literally all right so that's a
yes chief steart of Cav's Hideway Alto
continues to serve the same role he did
under Sid being the primary person in
charge of all
monies and information coming into and
going out of the
Hideway established under the leadership
of Clive rosfield who took on the title
of Sid after his former Leader's passing
and Titans destruction of the old
Hideway here a community of likeminded
individuals from across the realm have
gathered to build a place where people
can live and die on their own
terms is that a like a gr grammar
mistake cuz I read it automatically as
have because it seems more natural to
me has
have I guess the community has gathered
have
[Music]
gathered like its predecessor it is
built within the fall within Fallen
ruins deep within the deadlands of
central storm decidedly unlike its
predecessor however it is located in the
center of a lake Ben num across whose
Waters any invading enemy can easily be
spotted long before the rebel true
noise not a
h it's I guess it's singular Community
work that one
out there must be better places in the
hull of a gutted Airship to bury your
nose in a book good it is sheep and this
is where she's chosen to be sheep and
I'm sure she has her
reasons let's talk to
her
I trust I'm not intruding oh pretty back
from your mission um I'm beginning to
think your habit of surviving cannot be
attributed to luck alone kind of what
might say the same of you Vivian
Ninetales nine I'll have you know that
only four attempts have been made on my
life and none was especially memorable
so to what do I owe the honor could it
be that you've come for one of my
lessons
is that so hard to believe L's very well
then shall we start with the state of
the realm to absolutely no one's
surprise she finds herself at the mercy
of armies and
outlaws well mostly armies though that's
not for want of trying is it Clive but
the real question is how did we get
here how did we get
here
long though s's dominion over
Northeastern storm has endured recent
days have seen the blight rest ever more
land from her
grasp for which reason she has continued
to wage war on her rival across the
straight hoping to claim less blackened
pastures but Odin would sooner porn his
sword than wud relinquish Ash ah she
speaks in such complicated ing good
issues so the lady uh that was our mommy
she is fighting this land on the right
side because she wants more lands that
are not blighted yet right
right
right just
confirming
yes okay and the Empire pays dearly for
every blade of grass bent beneath squa
boots Little Wonder then that Sylvester
set a sight on the crystalline Dominion
an altogether easier Target possessed of
no less
ether it was 5 years ago what while you
were busying yourself with the
destruction of Drake's head that the
Empire made its move subjugating its
there to for neutral neighbor a nation
which could legitimately claim to be the
center of the world which was the the
like like the the church people that we
saw
right
Switzerland no oh s SRA was the church
people
what oh I've never really seen them oh
okay wait some break however was it the
church people and my
mommy those like belong together
right okay okay okay okay they just
don't bring up my mommy anymore I don't
know
why a nation which could legitimately
claim to be the cent of the world
oh certainly there is no better place to
Stage an army mhmh from there the holy
Empire's reach spans the twins what the
nonaggression treaty was the only thing
keeping them in check but if they truly
broke The Pact without
provocation it is only a matter of time
before others reply in kind what
twins the holy Empire the dalakian
Republic the kingdom of wud and of
course our friends in
yaran who will be left standing I wonder
when the last drop of blood is
spilled wait
no well you were born in twins
side do you not fear for your
two islands oh dark clouds are W to
gather over the
Dominion yet in spite of it all she has
ever endured and when the storm has
passed I am confident she will
remain now as to the matter of payment
for today's lesson for that complete a
simple errand for me and we shall
consider ourselves even
even right H return this volume to old
Toms in the shelves tell him it was
adequate what I suppose it wouldn't hurt
to visit our resident
historian is that a loot
[Music]
book this is an amazing place to have an
Hideout at and it reminds me of one
piece but just because in the water
that's all I
guess harpocrates that sounds so
Greek
uh I was trying to remember how to say
hi in
Greek I
forgot norsman
harpocrates now that is is a name I have
not heard for a long time so long in
fact I had half forgotten it was mine
welcome home Clive you were missed as
always I believe this Belongs to You
Vivan asked me to return
it on Gods and
Men containing findings of one
anaximander of canver a renowned
theological olian who spent most of his
life chronicling Val's diverse religious
history okay so not
lud damn
ready our resident scholar devours books
faster than young tet does lemon tarts
would that I could do the same but alas
I know longer possess the necessary
Constitution for such Indulgence either
in words or TS
that said I have continued my search for
mention of the creature you encountered
at Drake's head but without access to
the great libraries of oriflam more the
Dominion I regret that I have been able
to find wait do we remember seeing
Joshua though sorry please do you do we
think don't apologize it was in our head
I'll send word to our Associates see if
they can't furnish you with more books I
fear it is not more books that I require
but the right one
mayhap we look in the wrong places there
are still libraries to the north I'll
see what I can do you are too kind there
are not many in this world who would
indulge the whims of a tired old
historian not too tired to go filing
Koop nuts though always got our pocket
for him next him off the
mle hush now we all know there's no such
thing as Mo go
H
what the twins seem
well I yet they laugh far too little for
one so young some people don't see the
loss of their parents weighs heavy on
them however well they hide it Titan
took much from us that night from some
more than others just because you don't
see them doesn't mean they're not real
they are not quick to heal
which is why we must give them all the
time they
need that we must just as I must give
you the time you need to recuperate good
day Clive good day maybe it's like a
Peter Pan kind of
thing I should get some rest while I can
only if you have the innocence of a
child or something like that then you
can see
them m
ah Clive a moment if I may you'll be
pleased to hear that I've completed
another volume and while my collection
is still far from becoming the Thousand
tones that young Crow has quaintly
dubbed it I hope the knowledge
chronicled within might yet be of some
benefit to the
Hideway of course I would not have
penned half as many volumes without the
tales you and the others bring back from
your travels for which generosity I
shall be forever
grateful I don't believe you've read
this particular chapter
[Music]
before the Thousand tombs is a
comprehensive compendium of valan lore
covering everything from basic terms to
important per so the lore the ah the
past active time lore entries basically
I have compiled some new entries if you
would like to see them
funny
o ravenous reader extent encyclopedia
there is a rather fascinating excert
I've been meaning to show you
interesting what this
ah which
one
m
should I read them
all I'm almost out of potato chips you
guys will be free from the crunch sounds
very
soon don't you love it when you are at
the end of your potato chips bag and
olders left is like the tiny ones the
small crushed
[Music]
ones you hate
that you hate the small ones
really I like collecting them and then
eating a lot of them at
once
they feel kind of
Juicy I always go for the smaller ones
and then I pile them
up E I didn't know this would be such a
like split
thing
n
you love all potato chips
equally pull it with my greasy ass
[Music]
hands m
actually the inside of my mouth is now
kind
of
um what's the
word wait sore
yeah quick
[Music]
um
um idle meeting
break I'll be right back and then we
read the lore let's go I I I think I
think I don't know should we read it you
guys tell
me and I'll wash my hands so that I
don't have greasy fingers
anymore no no no should I stay I'll
stay I can be in two places at one
time
ah
hello
guys I I love
you I appreciate you thank you for
waiting for me
thank I love you guys thank you where
that come from I don't know I saw you
guys writing cute
things thinking I wouldn't see
them that's kind of
cute just man I love you
guys was a cat captured and I have uh
encountered one and slightly pet
one chunky
wonky but she was not
captured
eh the Continental Accord an
international PCT made at the dawn of
the present
era what does that mean like at the
beginning of now in which such matters
as the treatment of beers and the
establishment of Realm wide currency
were laid out it formed the bases of
much of valan society as it stands today
including The Branding of baras and
their status as
non-persons like uh saying they're not
real people like not actual like people
people it also put in place a universal
calendar thank you uh marking a symbolic
Fresh Start for mankind El baate one
which put magic users at a crippling
disadvantage
sheesh uh uhhuh the dating system used
throughout the twins which marks the
years of the realm that have passed
since the signing of the C blah blah
blah blue
blah well okay
not maybe the
flounder there's so many things okay
we're not reading all of this what
subject shall we consider today
[Music]
oh I don't
know
nothing
although oh this is all the
enemies
o
oopsie then there's the bottom ones are
related to that
Titan hug kopa oh that was his name that
was his
[Music]
name
turtle
a cup that's why you guys call him
cupcake that's what you guys were
saying wle the wesle of Valia two great
C that's what storm was implying the
continent with its frozen norn reaches
its tempered marshy Midlands
and uhuh what what the other one
called is it going to be this one
one
wow
[Music]
w
wow Ash storm and
Ash
o so much information so basically a
collection of all the ls that I've seen
and the ones that I've
missed
[Music]
oh
interesting oh not bag a blink and
you're already off solving everyone's
problems it looks good Clive that lady
goes well with the skull I'd had that
brand for so long I'd forgotten what
life was like without it what it was
like to be
myself and it's all thanks to you T
she's makeup SC did most of the work ah
before I forget a rider was here with a
letter from gav Auto left it on your
desk not a
sters all right I'll have a look and
then you get some
rest so it was always an option to kind
of get like a surger like uh what could
a surgery for
that just remove it into the to I hear a
new ship's just arriving
cl cl what do you want we'll make a 11
bolt waa it combines flame tongue with
lightning
sh let's go no scratches
right
no
no reinforce oh yeah right I can't
reinforce it that's F fine fine
medieval surgery so why does not
everybody else do it cuz is it actually
like expensive and hard to find someone
who can do
it it can't kill
you it's explaining D oh really okay we
risk
that the reading table reports letters
and other important m
addressed to Clive are delivered to the
reading table in his Chambers new
messages are always arriving so make it
a point to check the reading desk Upon
returning to the
Hideway the Republic's
play
oh give the Republican Army Marches On
The Empire empire at the twin side and
the men of the rock have been summoned
to the front something break is brewing
I reckon I'll see you're done to wear
upon my return
or something like did what does gav have
to say the Republican Army is on the
March leaving randar in Hugo ca's charge
Randa with him and his men occupied with
the defense of the capital they're less
likely to trouble us good news
then it's more than that this is our
chance let go the one we've been waiting
for not a bad impression really it
sounded more like
OT but look how far we've come all that
we have here our friends the Hideway are
they not cause for Joy 5 years five long
years if I could only command this power
I've been granted felt kind of short
have achieved so much more but each time
I reach for it it's like something is
holding me back you still got issues
with that summoning an icon exacts a
price not easily paid skill is you your
body knows this only too
well it's merely trying to save you from
yourself and every burden I cannot bear
Force to
you this mission of ours has made me
question everything I thought I knew but
one thing has become abundantly clear
the crystals take more than they
give mhm in exchange for momentary
Comfort we must enjoy a lifetime of pain
war after War loss upon
loss and
now now they rob us of our very homes
leaving not but dust and
Ash but you're trying to change that we
are trying to change
that and to me that's no
burden I know
but try not to
forget we're only here because Joshua
gave us a second
chance it would be a Pity to waste such
a precious
gift
oh H he did he was there
uh-huh it wasn't an
illusion oh I heard him call out to
Altima
if Joshua is still alive he'll be
looking for that that
thing do you think he will ever come
back I know he will and we must be ready
when he
does
happy
birthday happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you happy birthday happy
birthday to you here cheers to you
crystals to fire the
elements just
sit
cheers hey
clink
o finally he's got some cool clothes
still with the
girl
girlfriend and so the north is
lost I knew that the blight spread ever
more swiftly or Grace but
this this is far far worse than any
could have imagined it is only a matter
of time before the twins are no
[Music]
more the world marches ever closer to
its end and here we Chase
Shadows tell me
brother are our efforts in
vain
well why don't you guys just not team
up and talk
directly you're right Master Clive a
moment if you he's chasing I'll help him
my apologies I didn't mean
to intrude too logical not at all too
EAS we were're just discussing strategy
speak freely Otto I from the in she's
going to miss we totally helped him
anyway I'll be in the mess when you
finished very
well the Gathering storm what would make
Martha leave the
rest are they trying to make a pun about
the continent also being called storm
wall of
memories
oh
cute what the
music created the day CLI pledge his
allegiance to Sid this Crystal Shard
transfixed with twin daggers is a
powerful reminder of a promise made a
friendship forged and a Legacy Legacy
inherited we only have one
memory sweet
though nice open
[Music]
Windows
sweet I really like that
music o treasure W Goblin
coin
and have to go
around
this
way bye
Jill
uh here
okay over there all
right again
layers invest in Cobble coin gobble
gobble gobble
gobble
Oto my man what do we know Otto some
Lads from the Imperial Garrison in
roseria started a fight over at Martha's
rest blood was spilled bones were broken
the usual but somewhere in the middle of
it all Martha vanished without a word to
anyone and that ain't like her Clive
something's not right you think this was
planned of course it bloody was ever
since East part
the Empire has been tightening its grip
around the duchy balls they've strung up
everyone who's ever set eyes on a
runaway claiming their traitors to the
holy Throne conspiring to restore the
house of rosfield to power and now it
sounds like the bastards have turned
their attentions to the poor bearers
Meek enough to stay put naturally old
Martha could see the way the wind was
blowing complained that it was getting
harder and harder to take bearers in and
now now she's missing if she's fallen
into the hands of the Empire we could be
next couple of Curse Breakers are
already on their way to the Inn they
should up speed up the search but if
this is as bad as I think it is you
might end up having to save their asses
and all don't worry of them I'll make
sure everyone gets home
safe
okay well about the
cars I definitely finally got some
inspiration
no from that
stream that was
interesting but I'm still going to wait
first of all I have to I would have to
save money for a
car
um what happened here but as long as I
don't have a license I'm not going to
get a car find the others and generally
my idea was I won't get a license
until as long as I'm in whole
life cuz I don't think I really want
to like I I can't split my attention re
the boys from The Garrison might still
be nearby I don't want to do
anything where I have to learn something
seriously cuz I'm my brain's too
occupied with other things let's get you
to a physical shall we isn't that hard
well I don't know I don't I don't even I
don't really need it now anyway you know
I'm
fine I want to focus on it when I have
time for it one said you'd be coming
well I'm here I trust you don't mind
also thought you might need some help
and it appears he was right you uh could
say that yes but kids learn things
easier like a storm they pick up things
easier Spar their
Fury tried to step in and calm things
down but all our efforts got her were a
pair of iron shackles in a hard March
any idea where judging by their tracks
They headed towards Sor wise Bay to The
Abbey Sheltering Martha's
bearers
bastard Jill and I will go after them
you take care of the people here we
will but um before you go one of the
locals heard something he said the
soldiers were talking about a culling
I don't know how big this is but it
doesn't sound good be careful out there
Sid you do the
same it sounds interesting
that what if I do studying for driver's
license
streams a lot of you guys can even help
me
and it's kind of
relatable content Cole is right that was
no Tavern brawl it was a mess message
but a
culling bearers are the property of the
Empire you think I can do the Garrison
wouldn't have the authority to act alone
the orders would have had to have come
from higher up look sharp I could even
make a like a vlog video of me doing the
actual like practical driving
test putting the camera wearing gloves
and like putting the camera on my on my
head again like I did with you know
previously hey will be kiwa's driver
license acquirement
Arc too many
repls don't worry that will be cow
Carr's
problem is he
here gokart Vlog hell yeah if those or
touch M's
head imagine the back seating no that
will be a Blog so it's on the stream so
even if you back seed can't change much
of my actions
anyway roll back seating you want to sit
in my back
seat is there any way to escape from a
fight
faster
want the
items where am
I I'm not going the way where I should
be
going I can't help it it's the RPG
player in
me
I wonder if I'll get to this path
naturally
[Music]
probably so apparently I can't pass here
okay well I feel like there must be a
chest or something here I haven't found
a chest in a while that much
recently
sus most of the random items are trash I
know but I have to collect them
[Music]
anyway oh there's a quest to get a thing
that helps me rush
through
all right I'm going the right path
now literally I'm a walking
tangent a monster
repellent look up
ahead oh Martha are you hurt don't worry
about me it's them at the Abby who need
you you have to do something okay tell
us what what happened what happened the
damn black Shields that's what happened
the black
Shields the bastards caught wind the
Abbot and I were helping bearers they
were going to hang us both when the sick
Rose from their beds poor souls turned
on the
Imperials distracted them long enough
for me to get
away then they may still be alive Martha
do you think you can make it back to the
Inn Cole is there with the other Curse
Breakers I think so thank you
Clive yeah
bye-bye yeah yeah yeah I remember is
this some sort of to I'll go the other
way first there's only ever been one
order of shields in roseria they for to
defend all her citizens control yourself
even for the
Empire control your body tangents very
well just feels good to pick up things
you
[Music]
know
guys I have some interesting
sponsorships coming
up so look forward to
that um but they might also be at weird
times partially cuz they want me to do
it
at uh prime time and hey prime
time no I mean interesting when I say
something like that don't expect like
Red Bull
no ra Chanel
Legends no it's not like
that it's not unexpected it's like oh um
that makes sense kind of too late
sponsor still be someone
inside must be someone inside uh let's
look around the house and look for a
chest there we go there we go a my
Cravings my
urges oh I shouldn't have said it and
now I'm getting you guys' hopes
up it's just a game
collab
not collab game
sponsorship
ooh
[Music]
a
no too late damn
it you're always too late I thought you
lot were all
spent
murderers they drove the bearers to this
wait eston Martin these two aren't
turned that [\h__\h] of an inkeeper must
have sent them don't you call her that
colluding with the enemies of the shut
up I'm not going to even give you any
voice
lines and for their crimes shall they be
punished nice armor though such is shush
to dwell in darkness that we may Purge
the night and welcome lasting Dawn is
this person important on these are
swords we swear
how dare you spake those words have you
no honor
Clive this won't take
long all
[Music]
right we'll see we'll see if there'll be
enemy uh damage spawn just
again take quite long after
[Music]
all
this
one what is what that attack seems
stupid gives them too much of an opening
they both don't really seem very
[Music]
efficient yeah I want to change it worst
icon really
Dam takes you out of combo it does
yeah damn way to promote you no like
compared to what you guys are coming up
with now it's
like if that all of
them I think so one isn't the game one
okay I have like two sponsorships coming
up and one is the game that's kind of
like oh that makes sense
and then the other one is not a game and
I know so I just want to say ahead of
time when this
happens um I know very big like kfp fans
like everybody who's like who watches me
all the time will have some
doubts about why am I involved in this
okay but I just want to say they asked
for me okay okay so don't question it
too much and just act act
uh according to the situation okay okay
Fe be on my
side it's it's uh interesting an
interesting sponsorship uh cool down
time by 3 seconds
uhuh I didn't see the Abbott he may
still be
alive alcohol fish well yeah I mean
something like that like something that
just doesn't
quite
oh the abot Mal
roll the chya
collab the Paris died protecting him
him calling upon what little magic they
had left in their
bodies Clive he's breathing
oh my friends of Martha were here to
help hard the
Imperials dead they
are every last
one
if only that were
true the black
Shields will
return the
cullings will
continue Rosaria will never be
saved unless we save
her tell
mother to beg his
age and tell
her this wasn't her
fault
I I
shall
s where are
you s in here we found a
Survivor was that gath or
Clive
oh he's
gone once again a little bit too
late and not
g we've laid the aott to rest just a
random [\h__\h] boy they didn't need to die
like look at that
face no no they didn't but it was their
choice they knew the Fate that awaited
them and chose to meet it on their terms
fighting for those who fought for them
Martha said they Rose from their
beds threw themselves at the Imperial so
she and the abot could
Escape I've gathered The bearer's
Remains we should consign them to the
tide there's a drawbridge not far from
here rik's jump the currents there are
Swift if the Abbott was still with us he
have taken the dust there himself and
perform the
casting I'll get someone
to I'll do
it of
course Cole and I will remain here and
see to the
[Music]
Imperials your mother made the black
Shields to imitate the real Shields that
were to protect Joshua in the past
that's why Clive got so mad maybe
there's something here oh yeah an order
of knights instituted by Empress
Annabella in one of her first acts as
Vis Serene of the newly established
Imperial province of Rosaria they are
tasked with purging the impurities from
the province which in practice primarily
involves slaying barers upon the
slightest pretext or yeah oh
[Music]
yeah
yeah so they're
[\h__\h] where are you going now oh
down here
okay change all change ramu skills
Ramos uh ramu
channeled oh there is space
for
uh
one 2 3 four five more maybe
[Music]
no feel like this is like U not quite
enough space for one in the middle and
one next to
it maybe just one
one
two three
more but this is me meta gaming I
guess
so
um I already know well if I think about
it but let's not think about
it what do we have Al so pile drive this
already I I have I don't like it and I
don't like this
[Music]
either then we would have lightning
rod create a ball of lightning that upon
being struck chains lightning to other
nearby
enemies oh complicated
[Music]
it uh
well so this is
uh this one's so
[Music]
expensive no think just do the left
purple one activates instantly that's
probably your taste this
one yeah if anything better than this
one lightning rod and judgment bolt are
good
ones yeah I don't have the points for
this one
though maybe for now I'll get get
this and
[Music]
then we switch this
out but it's also kind of
weird no oh well we'll see we'll see
we'll see this blind just is so weird uh
in terms of
my accessories should I change like to
this one is the free seconds worth it I
would say
no burning blade damage
7% 12%
ignition 12 seconds cool
down
wow should I do ignition
one is that the one that goes like yeah
the fast one yeah
sure let's test it
out
some nice ruins here is there a chest
hidden
somewhere oh it's a
graveyard no no chest for
real okay
okay hey wait which
way huh yeah okay I have to go around
this
curve
Dusty we already I already heard that
today but it wasn't from you was
it oh what the
[\h__\h] you think this is funny what oh is
this like like a oh you get Bounty for
this oh cool okay okay okay this is
fun
oh
oh this one's really tough let's see is
spotted us tole what am I saying of
course it has it's a floating
eyeball it uses thunder and
[Music]
fire no no no hey let's go no no you
have to like what what is that what is
this what is this what is
this yeah no
oh what is this no no what is
[Music]
this nice
try
uh this one can I also do the 50%
stagger
[Music]
yes nice
try
another new
thing
fancy oh oh I staggered
him no where you
going he didn't go straight into him he
went around him
uh you're a fine
hound no what is this thing I don't
understand
this what is what is the what do it
mean like when the it's like a
countdown this
work yeah yeah okay okay Rod of
redemption why did I get a TR trophy
now too
slow
s too
[Music]
slow
go I wait I missed the 50% again
[\h__\h]
hard to control that one
sometimes kill okay but this not such
a as as hard to deal with as I
thought okay just got to get out of the
circle and then we're good
ouch ouch where where where are
you too
slow oh
[Music]
nice yeah I got it I got it this time
let's go go go go go Scaro
Scaro
kill on the
[Music]
countdown no problem no problem oh no
problem
[Music]
M and now we're staying in the same spot
let's go oh I did
it w today so far no
[Music]
deaths I faed this floating eye
enemy yeah
KY died to this the first time
oh don't jinx it I don't believe in
Jinx he didn't see that
[Music]
coming looks
funny
SC I was a bit intimidated in the
beginning but that was fine
I do like how the enemies in this game
so
far um have a lot of variety in how they
attack what kind of skills they
have like they're all quite
different so it's always something
new feels refreshing I don't don't feel
so much Variety in many other
games
even even you know the non Big Boss
Monsters Just the like mini bosses and
all that
[Music]
too I should be well prepared for the
next Souls
Borg maybe this is what I needed scatter
remains
a maybe this is what I needed to get
into old born
games nah so shall the waters cleanse
thee of thy
burden and bear it out to sea rest in
peace rest in the
water and now they are truly
free I hope
so what of the
Imperials a p was made it's more than
they
deserve we should go back Cole is
worried about Martha all
[Music]
right
okay can I teleport there
yay that was only C rank made until an S
rank
judgment bolt is amazing damage when an
enemy is staggered especially when you
master it by the way since I know you
love hearing about Final Fantasy
14 they added fall
guys we're best off staying where we are
for now I reckon what do you
mean what do you mean why would they do
that add C life before you add going on
uh The Fall
Guys no one survived
then I'm
sorry before he passed one of them B me
tell you not to blame
yourself doesn't mean I won't doesn't
mean their blood's not on my hands Cole
said You cast their remains that was
good of you but it should have been me
this was all my
fault
how you couldn't have known but I did
and I turned a deaf ear to the warnings
like the fool I am the rumors started
moons ago of black clad Devils
descending on villagers in the dead of
night to Slit the throats of sleeping
bearers but I assumed it was all just
nonsense concocted by the Empire nothing
but a ghost story meant to make folk
think twice about lending a hand to a
fugitive Bearer and in ordinary times
you would have been
right what these black Shields are doing
is
Unthinkable which begs the
question why do it at all my mother
obviously has a hand in this on my other
screen I cannot make sense of her action
the dark parts of the game look picking
what goes on in that woman's head
ridiculously time on their hands right
now I need swords and men to wield them
preferably big ones if those Imperials
think they can come in here again and
threaten my people they're in for a r
that that one is like kind of more
before I forget a sto us from a land
before and more saturated the gav has
returned then we must as well doesn't
look good yeah the GMA will you be all
right here Martha we can stay longer if
you wish is it not that much for you
guys I'll be ready should the Imperials
come
calling though I I wouldn't turn my nose
up if you were to lend me a pair of them
strapping young Coast
Breakers this good looks all right okay
okay okay then it's just that monitor it
looks fine on my middle monitor
mostly I just noticed over
there peeking that it looks pretty bad
I'm not sure which of which one of my
mod monitors is more
accurate probably the middle
one
no
MAA
plus was plus the sign on the side quest
that I should do right right okay okay
okay okay I was like wait a second that
doesn't look normal
should I be doing
this oh he's standing by a Cho bow is he
going to let me ride
one that' be nice you handy with that
sword of yours of course you are bet
you're a bloody Marvel with the thing
now question is are you willing to use
it or not yeah cuz A Flock and Noble
choco BS are in need of help CH
chos you heard me right wild birds yeah
not just any Chocos at that fancy ones
whiteart and her flock are the bravest
Birds you ever did see what they protect
Travelers around these parts from
Bandits and the like
chocobos fighting Bandits wow it's true
why might just be a pads Only Yesterday
go on then
okay all right there's a good can I I
saw cut AC you save I'm sure the map
will tell me thank
you The White Winged Wonder it's
you let's
go help you out and then maybe can I
have you as a
companion I'm coming for you that's
quite a name for a chocobo I'm guessing
it's a white choco ball looks like a
chicken
a big ass
right
wait items
first white chocolate
Bowl M white chocolate haven't had white
chocolate in a long time
ooh I want is that a feather from the
white chocolate Bowl it
is
a white
feather yeah yeah I said I was going to
do important I thought Ambrosia was one
of a kind this is one of
them speaking of Brave
Bird looks like they went that
way you guys are easy to
find this
way
I don't like it when people say white
chocolate choc aren't going down without
a fight is not real
chocolate that statement disturbs
me so I don't want to hear none of that
nonsense they're in
trouble oh it's
pretty shut
up we got you corned feathers you didn't
think you seen the Last of Us did you
basically a chicken you bad for
business because you all
right all yours
to yeah all yours too I'll just sit back
and
chill
so how do this
work like what what do this
work I don't
understand get
him hit the thing over here oh wait I'm
I'm hitting it the whole time I thought
I was hitting
the and
then
and but if I hit it like they have to
touch it first or
[Music]
something it does damage around it oh
okay not all stay down stay down
wow
chest
oh
get
a strong
boy oh
[Music]
uh oh I missed it what the [\h__\h] I wasn't
that
late
oh
all yours
to
okay H H oh yeah wa I got it get him uh
uh I have
nothing
ouch 20K that was good damage
right
uh okay let's
go punish him with the Lash shankla
[Music]
this we need a lash shankla icon and
lash shankla punish
ment oh no the Ultimate
Weapon slap your butt with L
Jun you're safe now does it have a scar
on the ey white heart I
presume it shakes it
butt do you know
shake shake that's
go it couldn't
be oh I don't even remember this even
now that you're showing me the pictures
Amia I have
[Music]
amnesia it is
you you survived I don't remember that
guys not at
all and you found yourself a flock
a is it over cute though good to know I
thought I'd come and see how you were
getting on oh you sort of the bastards
then of course I did I knew you
would
and the whole flock made it through
unscathed thankfully they
did and not only that ala
chocob it's not the only bird the
Phoenix is literally a
bird I remember the
Phoenix well I'll be I never stopped to
think our Aro here might once have been
someone's Mound we were right on that I
dare say she'd suit to fine fellow like
yourself can I have it again Our
Feathered friend must have learned a
thing or two from her master kindhearted
Warrior that you
are bird like her would have cost a
princely son oh you born a lord or
something um
well something like that oh no sorry
sorry I I didn't mean to pry don't
matter who you are you done right by but
he just believes me that this was once
my bird I could have made up that lie to
then get the bird is it girl and now pay
she wants her master back I all that
money but okay it seems to like
[Music]
me told you and it seems her Pals agree
is that
it you want to come with
me true well bugger me if this end a
heartwarming sight this is true let's
Down The Stables will be hearing about
this
tonight oh stay right where you are
you're going to bring me some nice
mounting
stuff
ooh
damn fits perfectly to even has the ey
patch why does the CH get an iPads cut
ANS and figur and gav doesn't she does
indeed how much do I owe
you few scraps Leathers the very least I
you old whiteart oh I'll be sad to see
her go of course but she's earned her
right to happiness and more besides
don't you worry we'll get along just
fine without her
you hear that whitee heart you've earned
yourself some time off you don't have to
scream at me I hear you just fine says
white Cho
ball these stupid humans be on my way
always be screaming at me to the both of
you thinking I don't understand them
like I'm some I'm
some old old
Grandpa you take care I'm half blind not
de it's so funny cuz it's literally
phenomenon that when there's like for
example a Dev person or a mute person
like or even just like a whatever
something some kind of sick person
you're like are you okay like they talk
slowly and loudly and it's like oh I'm
not
deaf this is the same with this choco B
right
now I may be blind on one eye but my
ears are fine thank
you
oh the same also with like language
problems you notice when like maybe you
guys do that
too maybe sometimes I do that too I
don't know but when when sometimes
doesn't understand some someone doesn't
understand you not speak your language
and you speak the same thing that you
just said slower and louder will surely
make the person Now understand it
right
yeah yeah if you speak louder and slower
they okay slower might sometimes work
but if the person clearly doesn't speak
even an ounce of that language then no
matter how many times you're going to
repeat on AIA or whatever it's not going
to work it's not going to make them
understand that really is so
annoying don't brute force it you can't
Brute Force language like
that I don't know use like you draw it
draw or use your body language I don't
know some very easy Ian words slowly and
louder and they understood yeah for
Japanese people like when you say
something some English word much slower
they might understand because when you
say it quickly they don't register it so
much honestly if you say it with kind of
like a Japanese accent like as if you're
turning the English word into
Katakana it might help like for example
instead of
asking where is the toilet like really
in a fluent way you could ask where is
to and they honestly might understand
better this just an example
choco B
unlocked
damn after 18 long years Clive has
finally been reunited with his faithful
Steed hold our free while in the field
[Music]
shees hi so what if I don't ride you you
just tag
[Music]
along
what it it's slow as [\h__\h] oh wait Gall
up
hold yo what's rain
in ah a
break yo speed can I pick up items when
I'm on top of
it let's see
I can pick it up Y and I don't I can I
can be still be fast even when I'm in a
battle let's go this is what you were
talking
about okay
nice uh where are we supposed to go
next
mhm
amazing
the CH Melody no where's
gav hello G
now
G curers
ever ah Clive how I've missed that
scowl where's my report look at them in
the back got no kind words for old pav
with my his kind words you're after
fishing in the wrong
Barrel now sit down you
fool what sure you remember how quick
the empire was to occupy the Dominion
after the fall of Drake's
head and how pissed off all the other
nations were that they didn't think to
do it first no half a century of
Independence gone at the whim of a
Madman so much for their bloody treaty
clearly the promise of unbled land and
the world supply of crystals was too
much for his Radiance to
resist go and now the republics finally
decided to follow suit using Liberation
as an excuse to declare war on sambre
lined up right outside the Dominion's
Gates as we speak looking to starve the
Imperials into
submission and now all eyes are on the
straight of
Arthur well the two Nations beat their
Shields the r sharpen their daggers
ready to sit upon the war weary
Victor they'll never see us
coming it's time we moved on the mother
crystals [\h__\h]
yeah four mother crystals remain in
storm and Ash Drake's breath near iron
home Drake's Fang in
D Drake's spine in
wude and Drake's tail here in the
crystalline
Dominion one question do I know how were
these
crystals like how how did they create
themselves in those locations in the
first place
I don't know yet how do you know that I
don't know oh okay is it in the active
time
[Music]
L cuz I'm like wondering if we destroy
them can they grow
back you
know oh wait here though the people of r
on the Crystal from
the S post that it is in fact the mother
C and their ability to draw AA from the
earth that is the reason for the
deadlands advance the few who learn the
truth are hunted down by those in
positions of power those whose power
rests under control of this crucial
resource
no
okay it's kind of a weird dynamic going
on no spoilers no clue like a player the
people in this land believe they are the
gift from the gods uhhuh that's what
they believe okay with the bulk of the
Republican Army march into twins side
Drake's Fang will be left
exposed that is exactly the move kopka
would
anticipate and if there is anything
these past 5 years have taught us is
that he loves his traps so he'll go
there mhm there is one place however
where nobody will be expecting us to
go Drake's
breath there's a shitload of sea between
us and it and I've never been much of a
swimmer I have an acquaintance in por is
older who may be able to help who's that
then my
uncle Byron
rossfield Byron Lord Byron rosfield at
the seven High houses the trade magnet
with Holdings in over 100
cities weird this is very game with
frony right
now and you're a rosfield of
course my uncle's name gave him his
start in the world but it was his acuma
which earned him his
fortune along with a handsome Fleet of
ships well it's settled
then will he be happy to see
meuh
we'll take this one
down good old
nepotism
nepotism like there's there's some
there's a like a kop Las seraphim
Clipper person YouTube channel fan
clipper and and and and they always have
this like uh is that opening or ending
but they they
they it's like you know yudia probably
gets
it um this cap of idle group uh the one
of the girls she like once said nepotism
so nicely that they use it all the time
as their ending I think it was an ending
or or opening and and it just stays in
my head how she says
nepotism you
don't the
[\h__\h] why don't you know
nepotism like she's just sitting on the
couch I don't know the context she's
just sitting on the couch
chilling relaxed and then she just says
nepotism
nepotism yeah maybe next time I find it
I'll show you
yeah what a let
down
uh oh Alliant reports the Patron's
whisper the hunt
board and me saying I'll play OverWatch
is like not
really I tweeted it directly at
OverWatch thinking if I get their ATT
maybe they want to sponsor me
though
but I'm not like that intrigued just
because the
sarapin I mean it's
cool
but I don't have time for that anyway
right now you
know I have so much other games going on
I have to play Tes of Rise DLC
[Music]
soon
a the blacksmith
[\h__\h]
what can I go back still do you think it
was wise to leave gav he didn't seem
pleased we always leave him behind and
nose in
Delia he only got one besides he has a
knack for that sort of
thing
and wasn't it Sid who said that matters
such as these are best left to dominance
especially should one of his beloved
opportunities to grow and change present
itself
N I always knew that I would return one
day return to iron
home
for
what after learning the truth you were
given the chance to face your past well
you
weren't but I wasn't if I am to continue
at your side huh I must do the
same I could not predict her sentence we
will face it together
then
to the
end chill let's
go come
on come on come on come on come on
baby
Bloodlines how far do you think your
mother's reach extends will we find the
same tragedy in the South as we did at
Martha's rest more than likely
which is why we should hurry um there
are still many settlements between here
and P his Alder we visit as many as we
can and hear their stories starting with
the village of
Amber okay
um
wait are you into
her
Ferrari I want to check can I move there
uh yeah
yeah
yeah yeah yeah I can still go back
okay I have to
uh
[Music]
upgrade where is the I hear there's
trouble blacksmith
here uh I think it's all right to touch
him
there yeah touch him he's nice he's a
good
boy so what it
be uh wait what was I going to even
upgrade you guys were like no upgrades
and I'm like what am I supposed to
upgrade oh
[Music]
craft it's nothing
really that
it
fine is it business or pleasure go on
then do I need
potions what's Alex here insul restores
all
HP that
price you insane the high potion already
re uh mostly recovers all of my
XP maybe later on when the potions
aren't enough anymore and I have so much
HP but also so much
money but that's
crazy Y what the
hell Cho
[Music]
Bell oh that's the chocoo
music straight home oh [\h__\h] oopsie sorry
no go back come
back sorry for giving you mixed
signals run like the
wind time to
fight look there's another a pretty t
b but you're
prettier OWI
to
so fights are still a little bit tedious
but running for the fields is now much
faster can you
fly
almost where do this go I know I don't
have to go there but I want
to just want to run around with my
Choo Cha At Your Service let me be the
sun to shine your day
no okay I'll go back up I'll go to my
goal
now another Cho B oh it's a it's it's a
gel on a normal choco B oh man can we
not at least give her like a blue bird
choco this
[Music]
one yeah I saw that with money of
justice is what it is Lord elwin would
never have stood for this everybody
wants to steal my book you think we're
loyalists Jill
look
oh Rosaria must be cleansed of the stain
which Beals her that she might rise once
again From the Ashes to welcome a new
dawn what we uh pity to make examples of
you all for the transgressions of but a
handful of course your lordship you
shall have our full
cooperation okay
what business could the black Shields
have in a village this
small there's barely room to hide a
bearer then they must be here for
something
else it was so funny to me though when
jig like the Miller son when Mar was
like oh I'll be your mommy right Mommy
Mommy right and then babo just calls her
obas
son obas son she's like
what and I'm like damn
C she may not speak Japanese fluently
but she got the important words down to
absolutely obliterate her uh collab
Partners let's go protect your
relationship with
Mommy I'm your
mommy excuse me but what was all that
about earlier you haven't heard
someone's been stirring up trouble yeah
she said which is a stolen but still
even say was murdered old the Empire
wants answers and what the Empire wants
Empire gets don't they
just keep your ears open eh the black
Shields will pay good coin for
information on the
culprits keep
them we're going hunting for
outlaws who
else talk to
me I'll just take
your your fancy stuff don't mind
me a
there you seen them didn't you yeah I'm
sorry coo really sticks to the dynamic
Shields just now you've seen them didn't
you no God at least I think there was a
black shield I don't know what you mean
can't say I ever saw one before that was
nothing was this the first time they
visited the village what do you think
Amber the are send of nowhere and they
thought we might be arboring fire Brands
huh if only we were I might have turned
them in and become a black shield myself
H you don't think these fire Brands the
Empire is looking for could be us do you
I know I think yes but we need to find
out but if they're on the side of the
black Shields and I'll be taking their
stuff even more those nights
father anything else that I can
take greetings friend we are Travelers I
know that what do you want we couldn't
help noticing those Imperial soldiers
who were here earlier don't you go
telling these strangers a
thing
I speak for the people of this Village
and we have nothing more to say to you
you are to leave Amber and never come
back may I ask
why I don't know who you are or what
brings you here but your presence puts
us all in grave Danger The Empire is a
harsh Master its demands are great and
it's just as Swift but as long as we
keep our heads down and pay our tributes
we are left alone some might call it
submission but if it will spare my
people the visc rin's Wrath then I will
gladly submit that makes sense this
Village will not become another East
pole
okay then we shall be on our way
yeah makes
sense I won't give you your things back
though those are mine these people live
with a knife to their
throat in the mistaken belief that if
they cooperate my mother will show them
Mercy obedience Bought With
Fear you all
right sorry
I it's nothing we still don't know who
the black Shields are looking for well
whoever they are the Imperials deem them
worth pursuing to the back of Beyond but
other than Martha who else in rosari
would have the courage to stand against
the empire
a new ally would certainly be
welcome can we find them before the
Imperials
do maybe they mean josua more
answers
perhaps I don't
know because also
Fire Let's Go makes sense
maybe ooh this PA will take us through
the mountain work time have fun directly
into the path of whoever or whatever
lurks
here what the [\h__\h]
shiny ever since the otry we've seen
more and more of these
Echoes what you think is waking them the
mother crystals collaps I have an idea
nah you're not going to like
it
do you want me to fight more of my
mother's men seems like I don't have to
but okay he
Des if it's black Shields we got to take
him down over here stop him from causing
any more troubles is there a wizard here
yeah get out of here never come
back
attack over
[Music]
here surprisingly
[Applause]
squishy what's your shield made out
of
jelly I watched a video on Pottery
today and it was
so satisfying I want to make my own
plates and bowls and I I thought about
doing a pottery stream for a while now
but when it comes to Pottery I really
got to take off those gloves gloves that
was really funny to me when I was
watching nissa's stream and she takes
off
the gloves only to reveal skin colored
gloves
underneath first I thought she had some
weird filter on that made her skin look
like
interesting here the Bamboozle this
one over
here like I'm like where are her nails
does she have some skin moving filter or
something
her hands look nice
though and I like that she went for some
crafting stream you know just like just
like her Idol takanashi
kiaha crafting streams are nice and
original content aside from games we
love that [\h__\h] we love
it she didn't use hot GL wait what just
like me for real for
real
really perh house wait has someone told
her how much of a djab Vu that is to her
beloved takanasi
kiaha attack no wait I used blue didn't
I it's more of a dja vuu
pom she should have watched
my my stream from back then
I
did oh yeah my house it was standing for
a long time in my
sh
attack
go where am I
going all right you can still fight even
when you go so far out of the
battlefield I thought it would stop me
there on the
edge here it
took okay it it did bring me to an item
so I appreciate
that we're not alone easy spam where I
go it up burn the spiders with
fire
hey I'm like a
drill it's a fun skill when I'm actually
hitting them and not like going around
them
uncontrollably
yeah okay that is very
bloody what a mess and still
[Music]
wet yeah
do you were told to stay in your homes I
wasn't told so though the black
Shields you know who we are and still
you would bear your steel yeah why then
we owe you our thanks you have saved us
the trouble of an
interrogation to dwell in darkness that
we may Purge the night and
[Laughter]
bl no need to hear what they're saying
that again they're dying
soon I'll show you a true Shield of
Rosaria I got Al
fre hey
sick him
CLI sending them on a nice roller
coaster get
him get
wrecked fall off the cliff please Clive
the cliff
hanger a walking Cliffhanger he will
hang you off a
[Music]
cliff tell me what I want in the end
will'll be swift so tell me what I want
and I really really want tell
me why
you we come bearing a
message your friends have been
found the brandid you freed from our
camps and you killed them or what they
await you in
order Guardians of the
flame is he
wheezing
no those are old Hill's Gates then we
hurry sorry he's
like can't even I can't even replicate
it he dies so K's laughing of course I
am he's the enemy [\h__\h]
him mild content warning
uh-oh why not
spicy I guess somebody's going to get
teared AP
part torn apart
in find something
boy such a death such a dog
person Callie's here
founder oh
[\h__\h] why is one upside
down that supposed to mean
something
oh there's also one this more like
handmaid's tail than Game of Thrones now
this was my mother's
doing but
why why would anyone I don't
know I never truly understood her
but
this
Clive
yeah I will learn what Madness drives
her and I will end
it do be kind of Lannister
like a little bit should go depending on
who is in charge at the moment
yes D can't leave them here like this we
won't but if the black Shields have made
it this far south they may already be in
Port is
[Music]
soer
well that is messed up but I I like that
they're like not scared of like getting
kind of like more intense and extreme
with showing things like that in this
game like I'm not to I'm not used to
jrpgs
being
so
brutal the game is M right I don't know
what the m means but oh mature
I guess that's
deserved first for FF then they really
liked Game of Thrones a lot didn't
they demon T Mage oh a nice find I must
say worth worth looking around I would
[Music]
say oh
yeah while
onapp help
one one might also harness their power
and channel a portion of
what
sheh nice
[Music]
item anything else I feel like that must
have been the the main find in
[Music]
here I don't want to miss out on any
good items
must have been a nice Village here like
I like
the the
nature
here oh they have a little
dock
H
well
sad that's too quiet oh I found another
chest chunks of w too
quiet everybody
dead
[Music]
everybody oh nice
Shore
man
I'm appreciating this place because
there's no one else left to do
so we're approaching bu
Bridge no I doubt the Empire would let
us cross over to
roosth Taco Ball time oh not Taco Ball
music it's too sad for Cho
music okay hi CH
ball we're always too late this kind of
annoys me it's my new pet peeve just
always being like a love to right from
here this is just too
convenient didn't happen to come by way
of old did you uh saw some Imperials
clad in Black making for the docks just
the other day
the next morning you couldn't see the
Sun for all the Ravens
sheesh boy did Mommy I could hear him
shouting from down the road no don't go
there though it's very graphic you're
too young for to sell my wees if they
would they're all
raran but this is their
home but I'm
hungry hungry Ambrosia won't help me
here oh okay
I don't know maybe eat Jill's choco
ball she can ride on mine we can ride
together come
on I mean can you not ride a Choco B
with two
people woohoo ah he's
flying like lowkey flying just like you
guys
feel like if you have more confidence
you could do
it just got to believe in
yourself cepy
Clap The Lazarus oh what happened to
this place my mother happened my mother
happened the Nobles who lived here
didn't stand a chance damn i' told my
Uncle F
better you may have the worst mother in
existence that's the main
gate and it looks like we're not the
only ones hoping to get
in okay so this I can't open
on well if you wouldn't just like
immediately run
away let's
go just wait for a
moment
okay
oh let's go in Al oh did it activate
that Waypoint probably right I call it
Waypoint as if I'm playing Ballers
gate
uhuh we have
arrived us same thing right my children
are starving have
[Music]
mercy I want to eat the Christmas
cookies that I
bought dogs they are you can't ignore us
forever let us in or we'll die on your
doorstep better
out enough they're in another room
bastards those crystals to us
all fil back to
your Cut You Down where you stand just
try it no chance of slipping through
unnoticed we'll need to find another way
in and my choco Bo is always there
really
what behind my
camera I thought we might be able to
reason with the
guards or at least bribe them I suspect
everyone in that crowd thought the same
was that the only way
in officially yes strictly speaking no
my uncle once told me that the Nobles
had tunnels built so that they could
visit town without having to walk
amongst the rabble it's carrying the
camera
Lazarus
camera sneaky we'll find our way into
the city there through the tunnel system
okay if you're
sure the entire place looked abandoned
mhm do you think it's
safe as long as it is
abandoned I got linta
Alan they're
like simple buttery cookies with news is
we haven't seen a single black Shea Jam
in the middle and a hole in on the top
layer
middle run like the
wind good
stuff but they've they've had them in
the stores for a while now so maybe
they're not even like completely
considered Christmas cookies but I think
they're very common as a Christmas
cookie uh you deserve a
rest wear please post that yeah yeah
wear always posts the snacks I talk
about on the stream on the Twitter
hashtag I always see it makes me hungry
again to eat it more but I like that he
does that you guys have to watch out for
that can lose it cuz it's nice if you
guys understand what I'm talking about I
like
that can relate more
to what I
say any cookie you eat at Christmas is a
cookie Christmas cookies cookies blah
blah blah blah blah yeah but these
Christmas cookies are also available
outside of
Christmas so it's like are they really a
Christmas
cookie not abandoned
then oh
visit
visit apologies we'll show ourselves
out
really
it
threatening why is
he all right let's
fight oh
not all yours
toal
noay this
one
oh my God am am I am I a Villain Like
the Way I fight feels like like so
merciless over here no no no no no
so when I fight against someone like so
close stop fighting
that it gives them extra
[Music]
damage I'll we the
baddies that's really what I'm asking
you I've only ever seen one man fight
like that stationary and he's long dead
then perhaps it's time you joined
him
oh we're done messing around the
blessing of the
Phoenix it can't be I was there when you
died he you look
familiar it does look familiar to me
actually more than the Cho
B There we go friend forgive me my Lord
I knew not whom I addressed you have not
to fear from from
us founder it really is here I remember
that
hairstyle it
is so wait let's
go a I was about to kill
[Music]
him oh we can speak inside no not even a
proper greeting to my lady what the
hell no only dad dies for plot
reasons man and those who wouldn't bend
the
knee we left before the Empire could
make examples of us though we didn't go
far and we banded together to form the
guard Guardians of the flame soon
after
alas there is only so much a handful of
Aging Shields can do against the might
of an
Empire but we've seen to it that their
stay has been anything but
Pleasant of late though we've had our
hands full just trying to keep the
duch's few remaining bearers out of the
imperial's
clutches the cullings
we saw what happened in Old
Hill I the foul work of the black
Shields and their
mistress you mean my mother mhm but it
doesn't make sense even knowing what I
know about
her her hatred for bearers was no secret
but she wouldn't have been ignorant of
their value to the realm
h no offense my Lord but in case you
haven't noticed the Lady Annabella
couldn't care less about the realm she
barely even cares for her own home that
much has been plain since the slaughter
at East
poool and since granting the holy
Emperor a new Heir her obsession with
bearers only seems to have
grown as to why I don't know maybe she
can't bear the thought of anyone having
the power to challenge her beloved
Son we should have her have a face off
of Joshua the black Shields are broken
Camp they March in full force for Buick
bridge then so do we make
ready we should have her meet him maybe
they'll this is their main host help if
we remove the head
perhaps it will per perhaps we can
prevent what happened at the do I'm
happening somewhere
else if I do nothing then the blood of
their next victims will be on my
hands yours and
ours we will the crimes these men who
dare call themselves Shield committed in
my mother's
name it cannot be allowed to
continue we must put a stop to this
madness
we
must so let us go with
you for the good of
Rosaria I was hoping you'd say
that very well side if that is your wish
I would be honored to serve at your side
a and we at
yours so wait
let us do our
duty with pleasure my
Lord I imagine this endeavor will
require more than just our WS then let's
hope sir Wade has a good Quarter
Master you're telling me that's the
AR Guardian quarter allow me to tend to
your needs my
Lord what
expensive limit break generation
amount
damn the
prices I'll buy one high potion as you
wish my Lord thank
you oh hi
wait tell us then s waade what is your
plan nothing fancy you lady Jill and I
make for buitt bridge and provoke the
main host at their encampment sensing an
opportunity to end the Guardians the
black Shields will call for
reinforcements who will be met from the
rear by parties of my brothers hidden
throughout the surrounding Hills M this
will allow us to wage battle on the
bridge without fear of being
overwhelmed while the black Shields have
an advantage in numbers you see they
prefer to fight in small units which we
can use to our advantage M how small
exactly small small enough now that I
have you and Lady Jill for
company I doubt I could have done this
on my own but that was your
plan you haven't changed a
bit so
Wade the bearers from old have been laid
to
rest very
good now make ready for battle Revenge
command shall be served
cold icy cold thank you s
wait perhaps now they will find peace
there is but one thing which will grant
them peace putting an end to the black
Shields we'll do and so we shall
yeah lukewarm that would
be more comfortable perhaps for us but
no no mercy party members rather main
our CL often be joined by various
companions who are Keen to lend their
assistance however depending on C's
destination they may choose to remain
behind the highway
okay confront black Shield's main host
okay we'll keep them from the bridge the
Phoenix go with you thank you wow I'm
too stupid to open the
door how long have you been pursuing the
black Shields since they burned their
first Village we Tracked Down the
bastards responsible and fed their
corpses to
stillwind suffice to say that got their
attention it's been a game of cat mouse
ever
since let's
go yeah yeah I was you know exactly what
I'm looking
at is that an item that I can pick
up oo come along now want to get my
hands on your shiny thing
them there they
are on your command my Lord uz shall be
the
command what is it now I told you we
bear a message for the vice rine from
the Guardians of the flame h H you
presume to tell us that a pair of filthy
vagab could guard ought against the
might of the black Shields
die stupid Forest Area Forest Area B
area why does Jill not say it is she
like not get getting paid enough to have
more voice lines these are swords we
swear m
[Music]
maybe she doesn't like raria that much
it's over it's a
mystery bloody hell oh that's easy
reinforcements from the far Bank bring
it on
to
oh
hello nice try oh [\h__\h] I should use a
potion what am I doing your
to this one ah ah ah more Dragon wait
works the Imperials aren't taking any
chances I can't say I'm flattered but
wait there's
more ooh let's
go he
dead there we go
okay would you like to come down from
there get
him attack just small worm go too is too
attacking the Thunder like I'm so
confused seems like a h very dog thing
to
do
oh a noble stand oh allbe it that weapon
is mided
one in taking it you have but proven our
point that this land is in dire need
drag of cleansing let's go Bring It On
fast boy
[Music]
right yeah yeah you still got the same
moves Dron
moves
oh can my automatic healing keep up with
the damage he does to
me
hey all
right
I missed
the Embrace moment cuz there was too
much going on to be honest oh my God
[Music]
ready this
one
oh
now
nice it's a party there's no one left to
keep them occupied we need to finish
this you mean finish
him get
him oh there's new people yeah okay okay
okay I'll keep myself busy with this big
boy I'll kill you ler
yeah
kill [\h__\h]
yeah this
one you love to see
it
okay I am
overpowered let's
[Music]
go that wasn't even that long maybe now
is the time when the fights don't get
aren't so so long anymore so
spongy imper Imperial
link Dragon
[Music]
Talon yeah I remember fighting him the
first time a Dron I don't see anymore
long time
ago nor do
I the plan worked it did it bloody
worked we sent every last one of the
rotten bastards straight to the mud my
uh Lord perhaps this will be enough to
stop the cullings Lord for the time
being at least perhaps hopefully though
I doubt my mother will take this lost
well she'll move swiftly to see her
minions ranks replenished and then it
will all begin
again I often wonder if the nation we
once knew is gone for good her Fields
rot
her people starve we battled to preserve
the flame that was but for every foe we
fell another Springs up in its
place seems be that as it may it is
still our home and we must fight for it
as we always have and always will for as
long as the Firebirds flame Burns in our
hearts the duy cannot die and her loyal
subjects may dream of a day when the
rosarians standard flies over roosth
once
more motivating nice
speech think we should fall back to
Porter's Alder before the Garrison sends
reinforcements a sound strategy my
Lord what see is puppeteering me again
I'm being once again
puppeteered Clive is always the puppet
the
Muppet cing cing
cing
no don't leave Jill home I need Jill
some feminine woman power I need that in
my team something nice pretty and
elegant and how long has my uncle been
funding you and your comrade's endeavors
since the beginning oh Lord Byron was
the first person I turned to after
forming the G why so Lord Byron is a
good guy of this tunnel back then I
wouldn't almost have been hanged by the
city guard for trying to sneak over the
wall I suppose a formal request for an
audience would have appeared suspicious
and appearances must be maintained were
the vice Regency to catch wind of Lord
Byron's involvement in our movement
they'd seize his estate and send him to
the Gallows where he would be of no use
to anyone and so though it sickens him
to the soul he plays the part of the
loyal Lord not knowing that one wrong
move might prove his downfall it is why
he remains ever
Vigilant don't be surprised if he
refuses you an
audience especially since you're
famously dead oh then I will have to
think of a way to prove that I am
neither rith nor
wrongdoer I might have something which
could help with the
latter recommendation letter or what
it's the mark of the
Guardians display it and those who love
roseria will know where your loyalties
lie your smile looks like a mouse a
rat I shall wear it with pride be sure
that you do I don't want my men
attacking you again unless you deserve
it if only sir Tyler could have been
here to see
you or the Lord
Commander well well thank you
soit if there is ever anything you need
I know
I need you to save the world and restore
peace so go do
it
fast
cute
Richard get on it wait I've been
waiting waiting wait has been
waiting okay
sorry but how
accommodating do you really think they
believe we are who we say we are not a
chance cute November wallpaper is
[Music]
done oh my God it's so pretty all right
I guess my uncle believes we're impos to
Rob him and means to string us up
himself
oh the cat in the
back imagine my surprise when I was told
my nephew had come to
visit hello darkness my old friend cve
rosfield died long
ago I've come to speak with and for
uttering his name here you shall pay
with your tongue oh
no listen give me a moment I shall
[Music]
explain you would mock me as
[Laughter]
well it is I sir Crandle of Camelot
oring a loyal servant to her Serene
Holiness St cibil the unshot that what
he once
said he's act thou vile sorcerer for thy
crimes against church and Crown I shall
have thy
head
curse the Infectious flax wench even in
death must thou plague me
still very well I shall open the gates
of hell that thou might see thy charge
once
more was that
[Laughter]
Shakespeare Bravo Uncle you're still the
finest m in the
twins oh Clive my dear boy it's really
[Music]
you you always were fond of that scene
from the saint in the
sanct never did let me place a
[Music]
crle
a both crying I have a favor to ask
Uncle Byron raford inform the kitchens
there'll be guests we D don't say you
have no time to
dine you can't very well regail me with
the tale of your miraculous preservation
on an empty stomach preservation like a
bug go on sit like
[Music]
a ancient B I see that you use the good
plates
rord so you arrived late to one of her
cullings did
you too many of them coming vicine
Annabella has been a constant thorn in
rosaria's side but these atrocities are
AO something has changed quite what I
don't know but the woman we knew is gone
and a monster sits in her
place a monster for better or worse I've
been charged with governing this town
and thus must maintain the illusion of
obedience that's all I can do to Aid
Wade and his merry band of
revolutionaries where's the food so he's
told us you have risked much for resera
our nation will be forever in your
debt
it has been 20 years Clive the nation
your father and your forefathers fought
to defend is no more oh they done oh
perhaps it would be otherwise had I the
courage of my
[Music]
brother
oh all right if it's a ship you require
a ship you shall have we also need
someone to control the ship believed of
her cargo she can be outfitted for the
voyage in a matter of weeks so you
believe us then about everything of
course believe you H only a fool would
believe even half of the things you
claim and you are a
fool until tonight only a fool would
have believed my nephew still
lived besides I have it on good
authority that Clive is telling the
truth
whose
authority wait your own of course you've
always been a terrible
liar is that true that true it's not
untrue I'd say no more about it eh it
wouldn't do to linger on my nephew's
greatest
failing the one thing I cannot believe
though is all this about you being Sid
you're always such a good boy but now
you're quite the outlaw it is confusing
which if I'm not mistaken would make me
an Outlaws
Uncle he's so nice right then who shall
we pillage first ruford fetch me my
catus what's with her this will be fun
[Music]
nervous yeah I'm happy he's happy some
finally some happiness man after all the
darkness a fine ship isn't she
sadness once outfitted she'll bear us
across the boiling sea to drust us in
the space of 3 days
boiling the fish are ready to be
eaten something on your
mind
buttoms
monsters when I served the Iron King
Dima I did so because I saw no other
choice
because once they learned that lash
would not move
me they turned it on those who
[Music]
could and so I became their puppet we're
all puppets I let them pull my
strings telling myself it was not my
hand that swung the sword but in
others that's okay I removed myself from
the truth so I wouldn't feel the pain it
caused it's a good
cope and before I knew
it I no longer felt
anything anything at
[Music]
all I
had
become a monster
no
Jill I don't want to be a monster
Clive do you understand yeah that's
fine I want to choose a different path a
better
path
to live on my own
terms but before I can do
that I need to come to terms with my
past and when you
do I'll be standing there with you just
as you stood with me it's kind of hot
don't don't get so
close thank you
life doy
do do I must atone for my
sins only then when it's
done will the monster cease to be this
is so
romantic just promise me that you won't
die with
it now let's get some sleep the journey
back to benir is long and there is much
to tell the others Den
so even tole is thinking like why did
they not kiss like what these dense
people no
like you know him like understanding her
and like giving her like you know the
security and all that that's romantic
you know it's like and the way he treats
her and so close and um the the
what the whispery low voice you
know
anyway
um what we're going to the
highway 5 years in the relationship has
not
progressed so it might
never only the found in the iron Kingdom
but Vivian could probably make an
educated guess
ban
Westwood typical
[Music]
Nobles hi weird woman back again Lord
knowledge I'm that you should find me
such good
company it is not your company but your
Council that I seek on this
occasion why you asking
Amad what will it be to today then is
she late again Kingdom I need to know
what to expect you'll soon be setting
sail for Drake's breath then I take it
the mother Crystal that rises from the
boiling sea there was a time when a true
blooded rosarian had only to Brave the
waves to visit it but then the iron
blood made their
move well am is not K can tell you that
as you know the iron kingdom rules over
the islands to the west of storm or
rather it's Church does but this is not
the pragmatic approach to State religion
employed by the holy Empire to
manipulate the
masses no the iron kingdom is the
literal embodiment of the crystalline
Orthodoxy and so if one is to understand
it one must start
there as the name implies the Orthodoxy
holds the mother Crystal sacred and they
do not take kindly to heathens
plundering the objects of their worship
for the means to fill wash tubs and
light lamps with frivolous Feats of
magic indeed the faithful consider ether
a sinful thing a poison no less and to
them a dominant is an instrument of evil
albeit one they have proven only too
happy to turn against their
enemies some 80 years ago in Northern
Storm Drake's eye collapsed soon after
in pursuit of ether and with the blight
at their backs the Northern Territories
descended upon the grand duche of
Rosaria and when the shields of the
flame marched North to meet them the
iron Kingdom spied an
opportunity a few short days later the
Crusaders landed on the island of Mount
trannis Home of Drake's breath and
plucked it from the duchy's
grasp Rosaria tried to reclaim it of
course but to no avail I doubt more than
a handful of duy men have set foot on
its Shores in your lifetime I have no
idea what she's talking about like to
again my brain is not registering it
meaning the iron blood will keep their
Island and with it the foothold they
need to march on Mainland soil when next
they spy an
opportunity iron Kingdom sto Rosaria
kingdoms Crystal
the mother crystal is both the object of
the iron blood's worship and their
gateway to the continent making
dustiness the holiest of holy
grounds from which the Orthodox Crusade
shall one day sail forth to claim the
remaining mother crystals or die
trying my father and my grandfather both
traded blows with the iron blood for
control of Dre's breath had things
unfolded differently at Phoenix gate we
would have sent our entire fleet against
them but instead they sent their Fleet
against
Rosaria sacked the capital killed the
men and captured the women including
Jill I'd say you'd be forgiven for
wanting a little Revenge
Clive my only aim is to destroy the
mother Crystal
then thank you all the same
not much else to do
here let's see if chill's
ready excuse me please thank
you an
archipelago Nation what does that
mean situated off the west coast of a
sto of storm what does that mean
aripo island chain with it capital at
KAG
the M Crystal Drake's breath rises from
a volcanic island situated just within
its borders and is worshiped as a God
just as the state religion the
crystalline Orthodox dictates uhhuh the
same religion decrees the use of magic
to be
an what and the bearers in dominance who
use it to be sinful aberations leading
to even greater
discrimination than that suffered by
their bre on the
mainland given their state desire to
control all the
mothers just like me I that's my desire
not not really my desire but it just
naturally happens the iron blood
attitude to other nations is one of
indelible
antagonism so basically iron
Kingdom uh are in special location of
the map and uh they want want
to um hurt everybody else and they have
a religion that I thought basically
everybody has but everybody thinks these
are Gods but okay seems like the same
way of thinking all the other idiots
have to be
honest and they were the ones that
captured Jill that that's I
uh picked
up
dominant of Shiva and trusted Covenant
of Clive leader of the new highway
together they Contin blah blah blah okay
the boiling Crusade a surprise attack
launched by the iron Kingdom the ones on
the left
right uh on the duy of Rosaria in the
year 860 Rosaria was critically weakened
at the time having lost Arch Duke Elin
rosfield and been plunged we're from
Rosaria
right plunged in oh oh plunged into
chaos in
the
oh is the yes for that yeah okay my chat
was kind of late
and aftermath of the attack on Phoenix
gate the iron blood Unleashed a wave of
murderous destruction on the rosarians
and returned home with human spoils in
the form of countless young women and
children Jill work among them
[Music]
yeah okay okay cool cool cool
cool it's easier for me to understand
when I read it than when she tells me
hey there's a PL story being posted
every a plus side list oh am I glad to
see you there's something
wrong he's black for he ain't himself if
I'm honest he ain't been for a while oh
that normally it only takes a couple of
drinks to perk him back back up but not
this time something's getting him down
and whatever it is he ain't telling it's
like he's lost his spark you know he's
barely got enough fire in his belly to
get the UMP about stuff but I'm thinking
he might if we both bent his ear cuz he
respects you Ain it so what' you
say uh
sure fine if you think it will help oh
you think they are not worth it but if
he doesn't want to talk we let him be
he'll open up when he's ready all right
all right now it'll only smell a rat if
we both turn up at once so I'll go first
and you can meet us at the forge wait a
bit then head over when you're
ready
okay this one's not important H well I
already like talked to
them so I should do
it I am going to help him out well you
know we
we use the service of the blacksmith a
lot so we shall help him
out what's wrong what's
wrong what's wrong with him that
Monster's taken quite a liking to Lady
Black thn come on chin up he's probably
just thinking deeply about
Metals heavy
metals first August and now you what you
pair up to what's it got to do with me
August was worried that something had
been weighing on your mind I thought you
might want to talk about
it did you know men don't want to talk
about the I told you not to stick your
nose in my
business what you go and do Clive just
wants to help in it what's so bad about
that talk to him you never know you
might feel better for getting it all out
in the open please mate
I'm worried about you what a nice
lad Phil shut you
up it's nothing really stupid not the
sort of thing you bother people about
why don't you tell us all the
same Karen and I have an arrangement I
keep an eye on guts and she shows me
what the competition's up to interesting
arms and armor things like that wow
anyway the other day she shows me a
curat she's come by Masterpiece of level
work light Supple and tougher than it
had any right to be uh okay made my
stuff look like he's really worried
about something like that I knew it I
should have brought the bastard thing
there and then just to study it but I
was too proud eyes moving now every time
I reach for my Amma did you just
reminded I'm not the Craftsman I thought
I
was there you happy you got what you
came
for now piss off all right we're
[Music]
going yes it was toilet
time oh [\h__\h] I I always thought of black
as a bit of a force of nature like a
storm cloud full of Ale didn't think
anything could rattle him least of all a
stupid piece of lever blackthorn's
always taken pride in his
craft questioning it means questioning
himself something tells me this is only
going to get worse if he has doubts it
will affect his work which will only
answer to his problems we need to nip
this in the bud I couldn't agree he said
he should have bought that Cur
ass perhaps we should track it down for
him you know assuming you're happy to
help that is who bloody right I am glad
quite quite common first things first
then cramp for me we need to speak to
Karen you know when like in your foot uh
on the
inside uh not you know like to inside I
mean like not the outside but the
inside uh where your big toe is between
the big toe and the F the
heel there's like this like soft meat
right in between there
that's where I I I got the crap I get it
a bunch of times these days these like
every once in a
while that's not
the the inside what
yeah you know where what I
mean am I supposed to go there
no yeah yeah yeah yeah I know when you
get a lot of cramps it means you're
missing some
[Music]
ah Karen do you have a moment
Blackthorne mentioned that you'd
recently come by a leather Cass an
Exquisite example of The Craft from what
he told us and he ain't been himself
since he saw is that to so buy it for
him sorry sold it already didn't think
Blackthorn cared for it the way he
turned his nose up he's chilling with
the old lady probably cuz she gives him
nice treats if the Blu made it is a bit
of an odd
one on me travels makes all his stuff to
order but the fellow who commissioned it
refused to pay he didn't like the color
of
summer so I took it off his hands for a
fair price you don't know where we might
find him do you like I said he's a bit
of an odd one don't even have a workshop
don't trust Hunters neither which me as
muching beasties as he does work in the
rides I see I forgot again I was
actually taking like medicine tell me
suit though uh apparently his next
commissions G Greaves pushing medicine
there a griffin on the hump board The
Curse Breakers were placing bets on who
bag it but I forgot it thank you at
least you it sounds like going after
that Griffin might be the I'll leave
theun while you get good idea so I
didn't take it for a while
well boost yeah not
push but those yeah those are basically
vitamins
uh they speak fast wouldn't be half as
bad without all the bloody
[Music]
dust I [\h__\h] this is
misleading this door when it's just my
balcony when will I learn it's the
second time I fell for
[Music]
it this way maybe I don't
know so
[Applause]
confusing nah I think I went the wrong
way again how could this place be any
more confusing I feel like I'm just
getting further
away or am I where am
[Music]
I NPC dialogue I didn't even
listen just zoning out
aha oh there there it is just went
like
feels like I
just I just did I like yeah I went from
here around here around here to here
when I could have gone from here to here
to here to here to
[Music]
here oh
well
M come on I've been looking all over for
you oh yes Our Mysterious Mughal friend
nectar was
it NE thank you very
much cute I'll stick with nectar if it's
all the same to you what seems to be the
matter not you little
[\h__\h] the matter is this
Cooper the hunt
board it's where the Curse Breakers post
sightings of particularly Fier and
beasts those that might pose a threat to
our operations if they were left to roam
free just because they can't be dealt
with when they're spotted doesn't mean
they can't be dealt with
later was that what you wanted to
know of course not I knew that
already that's why I need your help and
I need not to remind you Koopa I am the
mightiest of all the mles no fend
of so I need you to SL a
m that's right it well leaving your
mightiness aside for the moment the
people of Alesa are going through a lot
already but with the blight in the wall
is this a different side quest the last
thing they need is ungodly fiends
terrorizing on top of everything
else so if the Curse Breakers are too
busy to help then perhaps I
can or at least I can
try oh than
you someone who want dance
me oh it is I said the huntboard
tutorial
H
uh did
iar then do I have the B For You
especially harble one the look called
do oh I did this
one did I get the money already or do I
get it
now this one they want me to
do
okay use The Humper to locate the
[Music]
Griffin I I was hearing sound crackling
you can do them whenever you want okay
so it was this side quest just
introducing me to the
[Music]
huntboard what does it say where it
is some brick nor and west gate well I
don't know if I'll come across it I'll
I'll do it uh for now let me continue
with the main
quest okay goodbye KO a sea Voyage this
time is it I can lend you an oil skin
you to keep the salt off your back oil
skin it will be over
soon don't
jump
so
chill I love you when you told me you
had to come to terms with your
past you weren't talking about
destroying dr's breath were
you
no
I spoke of
Imran the leader of the crystalline
Orthodox the man who made me do all
those unspeakable
things I'm going to kill him let's go
it's what I need to do to put the past
behind me and a human
life to move
forward and I know that I can do
it if you're there beside me a
and I'll be beside you
too oh no we'll bring down the mother
Crystal together they're Des all while
Sid looks on for each other we make him
proud they'll always have each other are
so
cute we're going there now they're going
to blow it up woo but I'm going to get
my Christmas cookies oh how long should
I even going to be playing so it's
almost 7 hours but I want my Christmas
cie
[Music]
Christmas
see was she was uh making such cute
chirpy
noises and then I was
like trying to get to her but she was
like running away making me Chase her
bab
bab my grumpty Grumpy
Cat do you want to
say you want to say something to the
audience
huh you always always say such
interesting wise
things
no
no what if I give you a kiss you're
going to say something
then
no she just likes the
kisses it's chunky wonky chunky
wonky m
[Music]
okay
byebye I just yeated
her a she's so so F soft she's like a a
huge ball of fluff now let's see if
these cookies are any
good they look they look pretty
good
the holes are even heartshaped
wow
oh
M what
nice could be a bit sweeter
even
H maybe I will make Christmas cookies
maybe I
will different ones this
time useful trick freezing and throwing
the spray to make
Mist how did you learn to use your
powers like this oh
the Masters made me do it when the
Crusaders took to the Seas to keep the
fleet's movements from prying
[Music]
eyes I'm fine are you though no you're
not nice M me this may be the only
chance I get to go back my only chance
to put things right I have to do this
m whatever the
cost all
right are we in mid game
now
okay
there she
is the iron Kingdom's mother
Crystal Drake's breath
mhm
sick why is it called the
breath
strong currents sharp rocks
and cuz of dragon's breath is f is a
natural Fortress I forgot but safety
breeds
complacency allowing a single rowing
boat to slip in
unseen the sanctuary is inside the
mountain if we follow the old Trail we
should be able to enter by the back gate
all right let's
go okay very
nice I always imagined when I came here
it would be to reclaim it it used to
belong to raria didn't it once though
it's been in the iron blood's clutches
for far too long as was I let's take it
back for 13 years this rock was my home
I know it Secrets only too well
this path was abandoned after an ether
flood they don't guard it anymore the
perfect little
shortcut good stopping point I will not
stop
now we've been here before right they're
all a
cash The Ether flood must have spread
never as bad as this before and the only
way past them no okay somehow a little
bit familiar looking get
him yours
tole over here sick them tole tole kill
tole kill wow that's very
direct well no misunderstandings of an
order like
that
now you
lose okay
easy any chests here
[Music]
no all right door opening
R2 I didn't say who to kill well don't
worry he will not attempt to kill me an
earthquake G time that wasn't even a bad
one it's nothing to worry
about
yeah
yeah UL free let's
go any anything left no
good attack limit break heal you nice
way ah all the attacks dude I thought
just like somebody said I get healed for
what I thought it meant just
automatically even without doing
anything another no holding
back to
slow over
here
sheesh anger issues nice
try what's with the
camera please
I needed
that
oh nice nice hey the kind of a and ended
it
early okay I still have this one
k not the worst over here too
slow let's try oh can't get me you too
slow oh
oh go
attack Oh I thought it would already be
too too much damage done cuz like the
bar is already was already so low but I
did press it early
on so it's more about the time and not
about how much the get him um that
actually already went down in the
bar
nice this
one okay almost
dead get
him OU [\h__\h] why did I let that happen at
the
end all right I know he's almost dead
but let me get a little bit of HP back
the old aror is just up ahead we'll
enter the caves from there
okay wasn't
much what did she
say you can also upgrade limit break to
have more bars oh so that it's longer
but it also charges
longer wait can I can already activate
when it's only one bar then I was
wondering about that cuz now it's two
but it makes a special cutting even when
I only have
[Music]
one
oh
oh nice
Battlefield look at this
place what a
mess
wait that looks
weird yeah
yeah
yeah oh hello wait do you look familiar
it's
turned nothing a sh of frera can't
handle oh this is this one stay
stary just like old times be sure to
keep clear it more believe me I mean to
wait I'm down that's bad that's foul
don't breathe it
[Music]
in
stinky ah he wasn't 50%
Upsy it's okay
oh all yours to come on better ready
[Music]
this
one I might not be getting
everything right as well as last time I
played but it's okay we're
still we're still
rolling just got to stay behind all
right
okay I know I know this I should have
done this
[Music]
first oh he's
moving
oh ew
no no thank
you this attack is
perfect oh
[\h__\h] hey how many times you going to do
that stop
it I still can't believe they can jump
Le things
Roots that's better thank
you wait be careful
La
attack worst breath it's worse than
everything we've ever
experienced I
die give me give me HP
no no
no I'm
crumbling
no I don't want to die I'm Too Young To
[Music]
Die
attack oh I missed it
again is to is tole even trying to heal
me at
[Laughter]
all my WS
boys first death
today it's okay yes but your health but
is to small oh
man
go too slow get
him I still can't believe they can jump
but these things have
Roots
w
[Music]
I don't want to deal with this make it
go
away oh
uh
finally finally where am I come on come
on come
on yeah get him down
[Music]
over
here oh [\h__\h] bad timing for
that almost staggered
come
no kill no not Dar not
go
[Applause]
wasted lock on betraying me so so
bad now
tole okay
oh wait wait wait it's almost time it's
almost
time come
on let me do it oh
good
ready
okay deadly
takedown
it shall indeed be your
death get
him nice
your oh give it all you
[Music]
got okay okay that's good that's good
first one first attempt didn't need to
be so messy but it's okay that was the
only time today then I messed up a
little
bit and that's fine it do be like that
sometimes
yes was I making use of the rod a little
bit I think I
was hardcore monster it was a damaged
sponge that's for
sure o is it so hot I guess it's a
volcanic
region okay oh it's been 7 hours it's
11:00 p.m. I should end it here this is
also a good point to
stop if
any I could go longer I would go
longer but I kind of want to still have
motivation to cook after the
stream which probably won't happen
anyway but you
know I want to give it a try solid point
right did I save properly I think I did
okay last time the PS got really the PS5
got really angry at me for not turning
it off properly again I'm so sorry okay
ah what is that what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
scary turn
off
yeah but today was super comfortable and
I don't get the hand cramps anymore even
though we did a lot of fighting
today so looking good thank you
10 kogam cat wanted to be H for all 7
hours what a great weekend for
you that sounds like a lovely way to
spend the weekend with your cutos thank
you for watching all seven hours
everybody who stays here for a long long
hours even when Wawa runs out of
tangents I appreciate you thank
you
okay uh I'll read Super Chat we don't
want to fall behind as we did before
after all but should still not be too
many streaming
least
so
uh
wait am I
reading wait why does it not have my
collab from
[Music]
yesterday on
hyzer all right I'll go on my Super Chat
page
then that's weird maybe it's cuz I
edited something but even
then check ra down no it's okay I I
don't need it oh it's fine I usually
it's really helpful when I'm like far
behind so I can get to the point faster
I don't need to scroll endlessly
what did my Kyla crutch help tweet mean
oh
um you will have to wait a little
longer for all those
tangents oh yeah oh wow one person
remembered it and really insists on
finding out more
but just a bit longer I think don't
worry you don't have to ask for it again
because I I'll probably remember myself
to tell you some stories um
music
uh uh what could we
do
uh
[Music]
I love this one so much and we shall go
to here
oops wait I'm cleaning up can you like
wait outside for a
[Music]
moment
oh speed
[Music]
cleaning a bit too loud yeah
okay how about
now Halloween is close yeah I need to
set up my Halloween room I think Eden
finished it but I need to set it
[Music]
up
ah today Sunday the week is over oh my
God what a weird
[Music]
week only one week left of room that's
fine starting from tomorrow I'll use it
but I will be streaming on Monday I
think
pretty sure I'm taking the day off
tomorrow and I'm hopefully going to sort
out some things for my upcoming delayed
meeting with my tax
[Music]
lady I hope I
will I have
[Music]
to I have
uh a few interesting
appointments next
week set her straight no no no no no I
I'm not I I can't really get angry with
her cuz I'm a little
bit you know usually always kind of late
like not late late like not late past
deadline late cuz she doesn't even give
me a
deadline but I'm also like not on top of
everything so it's
[Music]
okay yeah so we're going to read super
chats from the car rating stream which
was
[Music]
fun I really didn't think we would get
that many submissions but I at the same
time I thought well if the Tweet reaches
the Japanese Bros they're definitely
going to submit some
itas
but I underestimated a little bit how
much it would actually
[Music]
be there it is also
the the graphic for the thumbnail man
it's
perfect normally I give chy like more
detailed instructions of what I want
like even sketch out the post sometimes
um but for this one I pretty much just
said I want narissa posing sexy on the
car and me in the
front uh yeah just looking cute or
whatever thumbnail game too
strong yeah looks like a meme
template it it
does I love
it makes me happy to be able to create
like fitting um thumbnails thanks to the
fry poses that chy makes for
me
yeah more interesting
thumbnails I thought she was getting run
over oh a really dramatic way of like oh
no you hit me
ah I can see that too yeah but no she's
supposedly posing sexy on the car for a
magazine I guess as my criteria said
we're testing it out if this car is
[Music]
suitable I can see both situations
that's funny
actually is narissa sexy
[Music]
yes okay so jaob 47 m h Lun thank you
for the red super chat
oh misunderstanding I won't do it today
but I'll do it another time when we're
doing it again okay you guys got to
remind me cuz honu is ordering um a a
Polaroid but we're not doing it
today so next time okay there was a TOA
fan meeting yesterday I remember K's fan
meeting at popcorn last year don't get
me wrong I didn't go okay okay don't
dare will be come will come a day when K
performs a solo life as well right I
want to see you one more time a solo
life in an actual
[Music]
venue probably
not probably never but maybe at a
convention you know like something small
smaller
scale um
yeah I I'm always like aiming for it but
not everybody gets the same
opportunities at the same time it seems
so maybe we either got to be extremely
patient or I don't
know for now we just got to deal with
what we
have
yeah so number 17 for next time okay
okay okay
okay
I will
remember
k
no
chicken
pasta
[Music]
what
uh
y
[Music]
y oh my chicken pasta is soft
and right
what are you trying to
say oh maybe number 17 was the cooking
uh chicken and that's how that is
related oh
oh did you make chicken pasta can you
make chicken pasta for me chicken
alfredo
please chicken alfredo
ch next time I make polar word okay
checky was was Neil doing something
weird
hey I'm asking for chicken alfredo
CH spanking thanks for the Super Chat
have two muscular cats oh I know it
doesn't count but R and T are right next
to each other on the
keyboard are you sure they're
muscular like 10 kg of MUSC
[Music]
Muses yeah let's just say our muscular
yeah
sure where how what's their workout
routine to get 10 kg of
muscles I mean of course not all of it
is muscles but spank
andhe I doubt they're too muscular and
that's okay you know
cats are lovely when they're chunky
[Music]
wonky wobbly
chunk
fluff it's good good not like so chunky
that it's like a health risk of
course but cat does not need to be
muscular to be
loved than you Spen Heim mAh
maybe one day cat review then you can
participate with your muscular
cats
banana Mony
JT
D Evan Granger or gr Granger thanks for
the red chat to be a muscle car it must
be American be front engine be a sudden
based Coupe that part I don't understand
horsepower needs to be over
200 yeah not
a problem is I can't really see what's
inside the front but I'm guessing that
the reason why those cars are so big in
the front is because the engine is in
there
huh so yeah that's why they're so wide I
guess and so so
big coup is a two door look oh has to
have two doors
[Music]
what would even be the criter on a cat
review um being a cat that's
it big V8 entrance like that that when
people were like oh it's a V6 it's a V8
that part I absolutely did not
understand
so uh brain
empty checks out
so thank you Evan I am a
te yeah than I found the buttons
again molent molent
than small two doors of high horsepower
engine usually V8 can be modded V6 or I6
bigger engine 10 why do the why do these
people assume that I understand what
they're
saying they must not be common kfp
people cic D Billy k
d ad Damian award
D tahan to thank you for the right of
chat I got here late but I'm excited to
see what I missed later my Ian nohi and
boss and her newest wife collabing make
for a fun 30th birthday present also 30
years of membership let's go oh my God
30 birthday
w
and wait did you like become a member on
your 27th birthday 27 28th no 28
28th 28 29
yeah no
uh
29 28 2 27th
birthday
right yeah I think
so must be the 27th but
because okay we'll just leave at that
congratulations happy
birthday for supporting me for such a
long time and I'm happy I'm still your
number one oi I had ride the first time
what well well well also I hope you
enjoyed the VOD maybe we'll do another
one
I don't know if you submitted to your
car but hope you enjoyed it thank soon
for all the support hope you had a
roaring 30th birthday and you still have
your whole life ahead of you so I wish
you all the best may all your dreams
come
true and may you stay healthy and
happy muchos
success and love than you soon don't say
that
it has only just begun
right yeah yeah don't do uh if you're a
smoker if you're a smoker then stop
smoking then you can en lengthen your
life for 300
years
yeah it's a
fact while you're at it you could stop
drinking alcohol too
[Music]
I was thinking it might be a little bit
funny if me and
[Music]
um
uh what was her name [\h__\h] name brain
empty moment right
now um
uh
ladin yeah it's me and
then we're like doing a one-on-one
collab where I just as a joke try to
convert her to straight edge
lifestyle and cuz I'm her Senai she must
you know be respectful and submissive to
a certain
point so I want to see how much pressure
I can put on
her yeah she smokes and drinks drinks
which like she very openly proudly
announces which is fine like you know
it's fine it's fine no problem with that
I actually think it's like nice for
change that someone is ruining their
health no uh that someone is like like
kind of like different in that sense uh
makes her like speak to a different
group of people in some ways makes her a
bit more relatable to a certain group of
people um even though it's not
healthy and I will not endorse such a
lifestyle but it's uh interesting you
know CU normally you know nobody nobody
really like at least like alcohol yeah
but like smoking it's actually
surprisingly uncommon when I think about
the fact that it's not uncommon in Japan
in general to be a
smoker a lot of people smoke in
Japan but
oh kfp is a non-smoking Zone yeah if you
want to enter kfp and there's no smoking
in here no
[Music]
smoking mostly a guying in Japan yeah I
can see that that it's like
um there's definitely a lot of women
doing it too but men are probably the
[Music]
majority and some younger ladies might
like Teena teenagers who just got to the
age where they're allowed to smoke I
don't know when the age is 21 so young
adults ladies maybe like some of them do
it because they think it's cool just
like other in other countries you know
it's seen as cool but I I
I don't know I do get the image as it's
like definitely a majority of men in
Japan who
smoke ladies
[Music]
what yeah I'm not sure what the age in
Japan was for
[Music]
smoking I only I I don't know because I
don't need it so
smoking
[Music]
collap in aad
16 which is yummer than a lot of your
guys'
places did Mama to ever smoke she's smok
smoked for like her whole life but now
she's
vaping only smokes when she runs out of
the
[Music]
juice you saw the other two Regal girls
tweeting do you too the
other
when I only saw
[Music]
one
M actually that seems like they changed
the law in Austria now it's
18 I I feel like I heard about that but
I just completely forgot it because I
grew up with it being 16 so I'm used to
that and it doesn't apply to me in the
end so
whatever so anyway uh back to
topic thank you so much
tahan hopefully I still have you around
for your next
birthday
Drifter Jim Tracy dun AA dun J dun mp53
garlic dun thank you
oh I wonder how many people were really
seriously like kind of like not insulted
but like hurt by me saying Kia seems
[Music]
feminine and hopefully nobody was really
like insulted by me saying some girls
are not like really the sexy type of
course anybody can be sexy if they like
show themselves like that but I think
like generally if you just look at M in
her basic outfit talking
normally doing her d d thing like come
on come
on
to I see toai more as like cool and
pretty but okay I mean yeah I her outfit
is
generally we are pretty sexy I guess
[Music]
like yeah in the end it's subjective but
when I think of sexy types I would think
of choco sense they where not only the
outfit but also the like General
speaking voice and the the you
know the personality
also is on the sexy side you know what I
mean yeah yeah like for Cho sense I
would say yes
[Music]
sexy is Rea sexy or cute uh visuals
could
be
considered sexy but I don't want to put
her there cuz I know her personality so
well and she's like dork yeah just a
dork
[Music]
depends on how you're judging it
honestly no I'm not going to do a sexy
tier list because that's just giving
people a reason to [\h__\h] on me for my
opinions so no thank
you Brian water race than soon Pono
thanks for the red super chat all I
learned from this collab is that kfp
would steal or already have stolen every
car in the
Stream no we wouldn't steal cars no no
no like I mean I
wouldn't so you
wouldn't good
[Music]
chickens yeah people get upset over
small small small SM
thing
I obey the law so shall
[Music]
kfp almost every answer was yes for sing
car well that crer I will admit that was
weird like the fact that it was even a
positive thing is just weird but you
know some weirdness is nice thank you
Pono
m z d space waterful z i a
te thank you oh I appreciate it I I I I
think it was a great stream if only it
was like more compact I wanted it to be
compact that's my my only um problem
with
it like I chose like 30 34 pictures or
so and even then I was like damn is this
too little or like generally I just want
to show more like people are going to be
disappointed but there is so many good
submissions that beep is super loud I
don't know how to change
it I don't know if I can
change the volume let's
see I don't see any way to change the I
think I know
why wait testing
I see I see I see I see yeah
um I
understand yeah I I really hate this
mixer I want to go back to the
XLR go
[Music]
XLR I hate this mixer it's so
stupid the reviews the like I watched
lengthy video reviews before buying it
and they were really
promising why did they support try stop
supporting it I don't [\h__\h] know the
team just left they just [\h__\h]
off it's ridiculous when so many people
are relying on it are you staring Korean
these days
an me I have to study
Korean
honestly I'm I [\h__\h] I'm so [\h__\h] I have
to study at least on du lingo what do I
have my premium dualingo for I was I was
trying to actually study on my plane
ride but then I realized it does there
not a single feature works if you don't
have
Wi-Fi
what that's lame that's so
[Music]
lame the one time where I felt like oh I
have time let's do it I feel like it
let's do
[Music]
it is dingo actually that helpful I
would say no but like it would be good
for repeating the knowledge I already
have like getting it back in there
keeping me from forgetting
it just a small tool on my
phone to you know remind myself a
bit just a refresher yeah not to learn
but to
refresh actually you know what maybe
maybe I'll do
it um before I go to sleep a little bit
H
[Music]
uh holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] it's
gone it's gone I need
to I think I need to
do little um let me go to my
calendar ohy I've been logged out of
YouTube let's see next week can we
squeeze can I squeeze in a
[Music]
lesson
oh Minecraft sports
day uh explan oh do I have to
[Music]
be do I have to be
there um
maybe well it's it's just got to be like
one or two hours Korean
refresher I don't know how I would how I
how I would even do the stream though
like like just going from my own
materials is kind of still like
[Music]
messy I don't even know where to
start yeah oh k k what are you
going the Singapore collab looks really
nice right it's um Singapore has a
collab Cafe
starting uh which looks really nice I
really like what they prepared for for
it it's myth plus um start
end so
aquai an interesting
combination I like the the school girl
art that they did of me and the others
especially mine I like how it turned
out but I like and I rarely see
Singapore Super Chat so I it's hard for
me to tell if I have Singapore
fans how much people how many Singapore
viewers really are there for me probably
more for myth in general
but
H my merch sold
out
[Music]
really Mal Asian which is
close maybe I'll check my demographics
but if I ask
now will anybody say hey I live in
Singapore I mean probably a bad time for
Singapore viewers to be awake should ask
during a different yeah kaid SGD I have
to keep an eye open for SGD I didn't
realize it my brain it didn't click that
kitle was
Singapore
[Music]
well okay so Korean
Doo maybe I'll just make myself some
time to study privately without a stream
but I feel like I I I I won't really
I'll like push it away and I'll be like
oh I have no time today too bad I'll do
it another time and I won't do it unless
I make a stream out of
it
I don't know where to put it I want to
keep I'm planning two days off for next
week I want to keep it that
[Music]
way
maybe ah
[Music]
difficult
ah [\h__\h] maybe I'll
just I don't know I don't know where to
put
it the somewhat shorter streams that I
have planned on the day uh that I have
planned on those days during the earlier
hours of the day I have some like
meetings
so it might be a bit difficult to
squeeze it in
there and then on the weekend I'm doing
Final Fantasy 16 so those are long
streams on Friday I want to do
AOE which I'm starting currently my plan
is like 5:00
[Music]
p.m. I could do it before then
maybe maybe I
will I'll I'll I'll consider it
there always next week but I'm
forgetting it with every minute that
passes I'm forgetting
it I don't like
it freaks me out there's Rush there is
[Music]
Rush no it makes a difference you know
nothing yeah I did remember I talked
about it today Koto I did remember
somebody add the stream idea finally and
I wrote it
down it's about like doing fiber
commissions and then reviewing them on
[Music]
stream just don't know what I would
commission I was thinking like music
like little background music tracks
could
[Music]
work I don't know what else you can
Commission on there I just remember like
back in the day when we were um when
myth was about to
debut um and we were preparing things I
was like uh I don't know where to get
this from I don't know where to get this
from I think I'm a uh recommended or
like not recommended but like talked
about using fiber for like smaller
things say it's really
easy yeah so uh I had it in the back of
my head but I never made use of
[Music]
it how did you come up with this idea I
don't know I just like when I was
thinking about the other stream idea
that I
did I was like oh and I could do this
one
too just was kind of like a chain
reaction voice lines are
popular why would I commission voice
acting work for
[Music]
what mem otes
oh
maybe um
[Music]
maybe well the the best would be
something you know digital
right so yeah
a new a new intro or outro that would be
nice too
yeah oh I wonder if someone on Fiverr is
doing chat box
[Music]
commissions
brain shutting down W brain shutting
down W brain sleep
now W brain sleep
[Music]
now how can you pay on fiber what other
the payment options you
[Music]
know
oh commission original song
maybe like an opening
song would be
[Music]
cute paper cool okay
okay that would be
cute um where was
I where was I I'm a chiy
[Music]
ring and
J woohoo
W that's it for these
[Music]
ones chocolate insomnic thank you for
the pinky hey wa I wanted to let you
know that I recently got promoted at my
job o I may have less time to watch you
no live at work now but I'll be watching
the the ups and downs of a promotion but
I'll be watching the V and tuning in
live on the weekends also I will have
more funds to invest back into care
a but I'll miss
you hopefully it won't be too big of a
difference
but um good for you I'm proud of you
good
job
congratulations I'm not sad at
all more meetings
man tell them you have no time you need
to watch
Wawa you have a private meeting with an
orange
bird m
but yeah good for
you I hope you're enjoying your
[Music]
job yellow a
yeah I I thought I was going for that
too in my
brain and Jacob 47 Al Studio Rob D for
the pinky T and the on and true Phoenix
y That's me forget about Joshua Joshua
is an
[Music]
impostor thus I shall take him down
sooner or later when the time is
right thank you Studio
Rob Jeff
starving hey D as of yesterday twitch no
longer enforces exclusivity oh I I
noticed something like that yeah cuz I
saw um the 8bit drummer streaming on
YouTube and will now allow streamers to
simultaneously stream on any platform I
was wondering if you you will start S
casting on T see
that is like such an easy way to solve
the thing that we were talking
about you can just do both and you guys
don't have to move over
there you don't have to go to
Twitch and use their chat you can just
stay here to chats though I guess y I
don't think I want to show two Chats on
the stream and then maybe they won't
feel as
included well it gets busy on the
screen
[Music]
oh you go to best college in Korea oh no
pressure like I think any college is
fine also I mean I know in in
Korea probably the pressure to go to
college is bigger than in Austria but
just remember I did not go to
college and look at me
[Music]
now yeah but it's okay don't worry about
it you'll figure out your way you figure
out your own path you'll find it and I
think you'll be fine you will be
[Music]
fine Jeff star thanks for the pinky oh
wait I already read that so uh I
think uh I'm I'm like too busy to like
set anything like that up now but it's
definitely something to look
into I I hope that I could reach more
European viewers over on Twitch to be
honest like cuz I I I saw
when I did the collab with noodles Sama
that there are so many European viewers
over
there yeah and we could get some cool
emotes yeah we'll figure it out we'll
figure it out I have to set up a channel
and
[Music]
stuff or you think they only support s
casting if the priority is twitch the
main channel of twitch we'll see we'll
[Music]
see I mean
no oh how could they I
[Music]
mean uh maybe for those of a contract
yeah just don't directly tell people to
go to YouTube channel yeah no
no I'll just continue streaming as I
always do just uh simultaneously casting
to both
places there's also a big Korean
audience on Twitch
[Music]
seemingly
and green welder oh my God a
rainbow good day T I must say I love
everything you're doing lately keep up
the great work in particular it's fun to
see you play AOE although I haven't
played AOE since it was new I've always
been a big RTS fan regarding the
difficulty jump from Modera to hard from
my experience that's a common thing in
RTS games this might sound crazy but in
some games I've actually practiced
fighting against two normal AIS on a
team against me a it was actually easier
than one hard AI those I can't guarantee
if that will be the case in AOE speaking
of RTS I'm not expecting an RTS R to
start but did you know there's a Lo the
Rings RTS oh that's an RTS called Battle
for Middle Earth the mechanics are
pretty different from AOE but I liked it
a lot I also love the K of Polaroid idea
do you think in the future you could
pre-save various poses yeah I I want to
do that yeah in various outfit so we
could customize our pictures a little
more by ordering a specific chicken as
well as a specific waa that's the plan I
have currently yeah
so I'll have to expand the menu a little
bit to also give you menu choices for
the
Wawa I guess I'll just uh not show the
pictures but like be like hey uh casual
choose casual WWA
choose uh default WWA and this that
there will be no choice for smaller
smaller head waah
wa but you
know give you a few more options like
that and then also the frame options if
we have more frames maybe but uh it
might be like too annoying to switch
everything when we're just doing a
normal one so the frames the different
frames should only be a thing for
special occasions I think cuz imagine
how I would scramble when I have like
five different things for you to choose
from in the menu and I have to switch
that all out accordingly each
[Music]
time one more thing I was thinking that
might be a bit faster
maybe is
um this was kind of originally how I was
thinking about
it uh
but uh wait a second let me find
it what was I doing
[Music]
resources two head
cement here I was thinking like what is
if I I the process might be much faster
if I do it in
OBS and then each Poe would actually be
individual cuz I can move and you can
take a screenshot whenever you like
ha you know like this and then the
signature I think there's a way to draw
on top of OBS
somehow if there's no Plugin or so then
I I have a different way of doing it I
think like green screening um Photoshop
basically uh where's quality well we can
make myself bigger you know I can be
bigger the polar Road can be
bigger then you guys have to save it
though and it's a little bit less uh
convenient especially for people who are
maybe on the
[Music]
phone if you recorded it could be a gift
true yeah
so it's an idea yeah I have but it's
less convenient for you guys so maybe I
won't do it but then you would get much
more different
poses oh
no no no it's not that
easy yeah there's pros and
[Music]
cons I'll think about it well make it
better and
[Music]
better oh oh no no no I will do it for
you just not today not today I I have
you in my brain number
[Music]
17 also I noticed last time the pictures
I sent you guys they uh cuz the edges of
the Polaroids were like kind of
transparent uh there was like the
background peeking through right I'll be
careful careful that that doesn't happen
next
[Music]
time but yeah thank you green
Wilder I love you and thank you for the
ideas I had the exact same ideas so we
are working on one brain cell
than and for AOE don't worry I'm not
giving up yet I have it planned for next
week
too I don't
know what to do exactly to get pass the
hard AI cuz it seemed so difficult last
time seemed like impossible for me but I
I want to still go for
it I still want to give it a
try and I want I want somebody to coach
me to be honest but I need to find girl
AOE
players some people recommended me some
players last time on Twitter but they
were
men and I want a girl a
lady the cast girl I I went through like
my uh like other AOE like I Googled AOE
players I looked through Twitter I
looked for people who had AOE in their
description and all
that I just couldn't find her anymore I
don't remember I asked you guys to
remember it for me but nobody remembered
I
can somebody remember that
girl any 4K oh my God Val Valerie
Valerie why don't you come on over
[Music]
Valerie
valer did I follow her we will see did
I I did she doesn't follow me though
though she doesn't give a [\h__\h] about
me I'll no here I'll write her a
message openly I can't DM her so I'll
write it openly she seems somewhat
active on Twitter does she reply to
people though oh she does last one was
October 15 when she replied to
someone well guys when I do this now can
you not like reply reply because then my
reply will be like all the way in the
bottom she might not even find
it hey there I found you a long time
ago through AOE tournaments and I
actually um have been trying to get into
AOE
recently oh
AOE more and
more and I was looking for someone nice
to oh I can closer PL to to maybe coach
me a little
bit on my
stream if you would be interest
interested in doing
that
I send me a to many times
[Music]
um count I mention there we
go that' be lovely I'm sure like if I
have an actual person coaching me I
could get past that barrier
free to sweeten the deal I don't think
she gives a
[\h__\h] I wonder if she knows what vtubers
[Music]
are maybe she even speaks German cuz
she's from T
Switzerland is speaking German quite
common in t like it depends on the
region as far as I
[Music]
know ah yeah they speak German
officially there apparently yeah oh W I
should write to her I should write to
her in German and then it should her the
coaching stream should be on my German
[Music]
channel oh content for German
Channel 200
IQ you have a German
channel the see I'll ask her if she
replies to me then I'll also ask if
maybe we could we I think about do I
even want it to be on my German Channel
cuz then you guys will not understand
much but AOE to me is like such a German
game
too gives me German
[Music]
BDS
okay
[Music]
last German Channel don't ask me I'm I I
keep on uploading videos but some force
is like holding me back man I don't know
why I forgot my
password no no no no like even like
people who are in Switzerland uh they're
Swiss German but a lot of them can also
speak normal German and apparently
people said she speaks normal German
too thank God I found that person again
Valerie you're the absolute MVP throwing
that name out there like you had it
written down and ready to
go that would be
awesome that would be so awesome I was I
was actually hoping to get coached
before the tournament
but thinking back now I would have been
too op if I would have been
coached imagine how I would have
obliterated
everybody to stream 10 hours ago all
right she's in my time zone so it's not
even that un Unthinkable that she would
reply to me
[Music]
soon no I was thinking though if I would
get myself uh a coach then the others
might also try to do the
same and there would be a big coaching
AOE Arc but in the end now one barely
anyone even did a practice stream wasn't
I the only one with a practice
stream it's probably because it's a pain
in the ass because you have to like
schedule it
[Music]
beforehand not everyone has your super
schedule
well
[Music]
any did a practice stream Anna wanted to
but PRS
[Music]
oh they said some said they' practice
off stream Alena didn't she told me by
the way she was like oh I didn't
practice at all I'm going to practice
after uh I wake up a little bit I'm like
oh okay what wa wait it show
that she didn't play for a long
time anyway Sky D B
[Music]
hi yeah
yeah pinky you have new skills from E
you might like Willow whisks it turns
you invincible for like a minute if you
upgrade it letting you rush in without
worrying about dodging oh I didn't look
at that one I
think oh that would be
nice M that would be
nice maybe if I think about it next time
I might want to activate
[Music]
it it's a funny
move it's not a duration based
invincibility it's a certain amount of
hits
auh it combos with the lightning that's
s it sounds so
complicated f d thank
you
[Music]
morally
imoral I don't understand this one
Ultima thanks for the pinky we have been
waiting oh we have been waiting for a
long time but now it is finally time to
reveal ourselves to you
Phoenix Arcane entity once wait what is
the name once not known as Al timal MK
every step of your journey has been a
part of our imination so now you that
you are aware of the truth what do you
intend to do next destroy
you I will destroy
[Music]
you b b b let the ban Hammer rain from
the
sky now you you're good you're
good I haven't had like a role play
Super Chat in a while I feel like SP for
D fire the elements happy birthday I
already sang for you a little bit happy
birthday to you
congratulations again
[Music]
again I feel honored you guys want to
spend your birthday watching my stream
what the hell thank you I hope I hope I
didn't waste your beautiful day where
you should be
celebrated eat some cake but don't don't
eat the cake that I ate cuz I don't know
if it was really good
[Music]
still oh I'm okay I'm
okay
[Music]
actually like until that point where I
ran
off like for around 20 minutes I was
kind of suffering but I was just hoping
to end the stream quickly I didn't want
to like change the mood that was like
really
happy uh exciting
funny by saying tummy
h i trying so hard to drag it out and I
think the fact that I was like dragging
it out was making me feel sicker and
[Music]
sicker yeah I was making it worse so but
I'm I'm okay I'm okay I'm okay I I
really am fine today again my tmy felt a
little bit like sensitive but it's
fine
yeah you wouldn't have guessed it right
I mean I was trying to end it also
because I just wanted the stream to be
short but also because I was feeling
sick you put R's ability to improvise
the test oh I need to watch that section
when I came back I was hearing through
the headphones already from afar that
she was actually judging the car
properly like I told her
[Music]
to
so she did her
job I love her you know you know I love
her I really love her like
we we we click on Vibe so well cuz like
she just already came in here loving me
so I don't have to like feel like I have
to make her like me like I already know
whatever I do she likes
me so I'm I'm just
chilling
ah right I forgot to
say oh narissa are you
[Music]
watchinga watch me watch me
now
what's she
doing normally when I Rite her she
immedately turns
[Music]
onlinea
Lisa ah she turned on
onine
y it
worked ah German always works D always
works
yeah there she is
ah wait I'll call
you are you able to pick up I
wonder I hope I have the right
micro why is my Discord so Japanese now
hello hello hello wife hello how are
you good how are you
um well I'm
tired are you in bed no I'm on my
computer oh well aren't we always tired
yeah you know I was reading super chats
and I uh like I I I we were talking
about our
stream yesterday and then I all
remembered one
thing cuz I was talking about how much I
love you and how long how much I get
along with you
and then and then it struck
me that yesterday we wanted to announce
our wedding right oh yes and we didn't
but no it's not a wedding but so i' we
forgot to say it so I thought I should
call you in to say it with me now okay
you know what right uh I I I hope
so okay we let's finish each other's
sandwiches okay oh okay okay okay um on
this lovely day me takasi and uh me and
narissa
ravencraft would like to announce um
with mucha's
happiness
that we have planned our honeymoon
location before even planning our
wedding and thus together we are uh soon
in in a few months flying
to the Maldives the
males let's
go I'm so excited to go with you K yay
and right before that noisa will make a
little stop uh at my place and we'll
just hang a little bit and then we'll go
together to the males and we'll spend a
fabulous honeymoon is time
woohoo I'm so happy yay yayay I'm happy
that you're joining me on
this glamorous vacation thank you for
inviting me I'm really looking forward
to spending uh some personal time
together I couldn't think of
anyone better just kidding there's many
great people to go with but you know I
want some bonding time with you mhm I'm
excited to go to um your house oh yes
yes you will see my
Catos chunky wonky I love cats and SM
smino they will love you I hope so yeah
if if you sleep in my bed
then especially if I sleep there too
then the cats will sleep there and you
can sleep basically in the same bed as
my cats and pet them as you fall asleep
ah that sounds so nice M that's what I
always do but my problem is like always
like like uh I want to pet both of them
while I fall asleep but they're usually
like really far apart so I can't so I
start by petting chunky
wonky and then eventually I go to
smoothie and then I fall asleep with
smoothie and then eventually I wake up
being in a weird position in my bed so I
move over back to chunky wonky but I
feel like chunky wonky gets jealous a
little bit so I would be great to have
another body to um cover that area of
the bed well I'm always happy to share
beds with my friends so I personally am
not but you'll make an exception maybe
then I will wear clothes when I sleep
just for you I do have a a guest bed
but let's see if we will make use of
it
I'll think about it I'll consider it
yeah and the mold will have to
share yes but that'll be fun that
that'll be fine big bed and yeah yeah I
I've done it before so I can do it again
you
[Music]
know that's all I wanted to announce
with you
together yes
the I'm so excited I can't wait I've
never been so I'll be excited for your
prowess in showing me around well it
will be a different place than last time
but it's it's it's okay it's pretty much
the same system yeah same thing same
thing yeah I'm excited well y yeah me
too all right I'll let you get back to
your stream okay byebye love
byebye can I takes all her wife to mtiv
yes one after another it's the honeymoon
destination
yeah we've been planning this and I've
been like really I just can't wait you
know I'm so excited for this we will be
streaming during our
stay with
[Music]
you mold season two different bir right
right next year I'll have to bring
another different bird to the moldes
just it will be my tradition every year
I bring a different Birds to the mes
maybe the next year I can bring
subai like she would like she already
was so jealous about my experience with
waya there when we were flexing it to
her but I think for subu like she's
always so busy with work it will be
difficult for her to um go there if it's
not planned like at least half a year
ahead of
time migration yeah
BP
migration or we can do even more than
just one BP at a time we can try to
migrate as a
group maybe we
should maybe we should migrate as a
group does sub even have her passport
yeah that's also a
thing that's also a thing they all
should get their passports ready at any
time Japanese
[Music]
members yeah cuz like when I look up M's
hotels most of it is like rooms for two
people right but some some of them have
like nice um
family uh like
Villas and I wish I could book them but
they're not feasible with just two
people but I've seen some that have like
for example even uh slides slides water
slides going into the
water they're really
big yeah with a big bigger
group could afford it so maybe maybe
another
time whole to plus internship yeah if
you want to go again after
that we rent a big
one bird bird uh uh
Invasion that'll be nice it'll probably
be easier to invite subu to Okinawa
somewhere yeah we in Japan
it will probably be way easier also to
just
accomplish uh more flexible
probably H
yeah but the moldes are amazing you have
to witness that once in your life she
can go to Oka
anytime but I'll help her out with the
moldies cuz like she's anyway like
nervous about going overseas without
English speaking people so that's what
we're here
for we can go to Oka Shore but she could
go to Okinawa with anybody any Japanese
member alone
whatever got to go to the
mul now that's far in the future for now
I'm going with Nisa for a nice bonding
time together I'm excited I really need
this vacation
again
and this time it will be not off
[Music]
season which is really exciting I'm
exciting to see the beautiful stable
sunny weather which will burn my
skin ah yeah that's the thing I wanted
to say narissa uh uh can you bring me
American
sunscreen cuz when I was in America a
long time ago I found like really high
SPF
sunscreen and somehow I can't find like
decently priced one in
Austria oh I don't remember the brands
but uh it was it was like a normal
normal normal
store it was over
9,000 yeah we need it believe me we need
a high one high ass
mofo like it was like a 90 80 I don't
know don't remember should have taken a
picture Arizona strength
SPF I turn into a tomato oh me too me
too me too me
too
yeah let's put sunscreen on each other's
backs
the they went surprisingly high like I
don't even think I've seen that high SPF
in
[Music]
Austria so okay back to where we were
map a thanks for the pinky great job tal
but that was only C rank wait until an S
rank judgment bolt is amazing uh damage
when an enemy is staggered especially
when you master it by the way since I
know you love hearing about oh yeah The
Fall Guys what the [\h__\h]
I have to look it up FF
14 fall guys like what do you
mean okay I see like The Fall Guys side
collab it's yet to be seen what it looks
like on the Final Fantasy
side people said it didn't start yet
[Music]
so well the outfits are cute the outfits
for The Fall Guys characters oh my God
there's a Choco ball outfit it looks
almost like a chicken outfit it
basically does cuz it's so
round that's
amazing that is amazing on the fall gu
side I think it's funny I just can't
imagine it fitting into the final
fantasy world you
know H the guy d
[Music]
what I I don't I don't remember either
train lover
d get your recipes for the best gear in
the game oh okay then I think it might
be good to do black for
quests oh any other plus Quest will
improve potions oh really andun we SP
time thanks for the red we
they showed it at FanFest it looks
[Music]
good how how was Ariana Grande
implemented in Final Fantasy what was
she just like singing a song
or thanks for the nice long stream game
with your 10 kogam cat wanted to be held
for all 7even hours yeah I already
reacted to this I love it I wish my cats
would do that maybe if they get older
and they'll grow
bolder
[Music]
like like heavy as a
boulder just like your 10 kogam Boulder
cat she was
playable what I the mobile game ah not
the not the big
[Music]
one wait I want to look that up was she
like looking
Final Fantasy Ariana
Grande oh and
pixel in her in her in that outfit uh
okay like who asked for this who wanted
this who thought this is a
match I love Ariana I I like Final
Fantasy but I do not understand this
what that's so
[Music]
weird that's what everybody was
saying
[Music]
man I know the Louis Vuitton thing that
was kind of
cool also kind of crazy to think about
but cool still they made it work
somehow I mean normal louison fans were
probably confused as
[\h__\h] but it was kind of nice it looked
nice light thing was
[Music]
beautiful
yeah
uh oh yeah so SP time kiss for your cat
please kiss
kiss I'm glad you're enjoying the long
jpg streams they're going to get my
streaming hours back up again let's
go H Adam D will'll get to that at some
point space waterfall d g d
millennium
come and as I said fighting you can do
it and don't worry about it you'll find
your own path I'm sure of it don't put
too much pressure on yourself please
delstar thanks for the pinky narissa you
got to put your foot down you can't show
up every time you're summon words of
advice from someone in the usual room
don't listen to him what the hell you
got nothing to say
here yeah it's
it's she's happy to be there when she's
happy when I'm calling for her in the
first
place
so
yeah
[Music]
yeah there is no toxicity in our
relationship
yet she's my oi
too well and are you showing up whenever
I ask you to if no then that's a problem
that's a
problem we'll have to fix
it
yes no for now I can't see
it you know it's it's everything is
Heavenly and peaceful at the
moment and uh you know
I think I'm
done thank you for the
congratulations so still planning other
vacations like the B Trip and stuff will
happen next
year
um yeah I mean I shouldn't over plan cuz
like
realistically
it's not easy to squeeze so many trips
in but I I want to I want to do fun
trips with uh my
colleagues and we can always turn it
into content at the same time so why the
hell
not would be nice for real if I could go
back to Korea next year cuz I didn't go
this year in the
end
uh
[Music]
yeah what else
maybe maybe I have a reason to go to
America at some point but who
knows
oh I do need to go to the north of
Europe at some
[Music]
point that was kind of something I was
hoping to do this
year just like some nor
countries
visitation yeah
Scandinavia yeah Finland Norway that
kind of
area I want to go come to Brazil I've
been there two times now you come to
me yeah
Aurora the trip that was with another
member earlier yeah that was was like we
were going to do like two kind or two
two places like one uh like
coldish trip to the North and then maybe
uh like a short amount of time in Greece
or
whatever or Spain or Italy like get like
two types of vacations in
one we'll make it work next year
hopefully
I got to I got to stay on top of
[Music]
that grease round two you know you want
to Greece was really fine if it wasn't
for me breaking my [\h__\h]
[Music]
neck yeah Iceland geopal Springs and
cool
rocks all right all
[Music]
right you've been to La yeah I've been
to LA but I haven't seen much of
[Music]
it that was rough show the ID girl some
snow I mean they got to come over here
if they want to see
it they're welcome
anytime no more neck cracking in
grease it's
cursed
Hawaii oh Hawaii sounds nice
[Music]
damn New York right I got to check out
New York at some
point but it's so touristy like one of
the most touristy cities in the world
right so that really turns me
off
scares
me and
also I feel like there's so much
pickpocketing probably scares me
too it was already like the past times
when I was in America I also felt like
kind of like nervous all the
time America just makes me
nervous I feel like I have to like be
like a horse and only look straight not
not look at anything around me like not
not meet eyes of anybody cuz I don't
want to like insult anyone just by
looking at them or like get them in a
like what do you want huh what do you
want kind of
[Laughter]
mood this so scary that's understandable
thank
you that's how you ride the
subway I do remember riding Subway and
or like some train in America and then
yeah my I did my best like even like
when it was not so crowded it was no
problem I could just stare at a window
across me or a
chair but when it got crowded people
were sitting everywhere and standing
everywhere it's like uh [\h__\h] where do I
look cuz like I don't even have Internet
on my phone so I can't look at my phone
there's nothing
there and I'm getting dizzy looking too
much outside cuz it's like passing by so
fast w w wo wo W wo w
W and then especially when it gets
dark when it's like under a tunnel or
something then there's nothing to look
at at all it's like awkward looking
outside even cuz then people will assume
that you're looking at them for the
reflection on the Windows because it's
dark because you can see everybody
clearly every time I do this here too
when it gets dark like I look outside as
long as we're outside when we're in a
tunnel I stare at the floor or something
else cuz I don't want people to think
I'm like looking at them for the
reflection overthinking you say but like
I feel
like people find when I look at them a
little bit or like even when I'm just
looking like like past
them no I'm not over fing in
no no I'm
[Music]
not it's a thing
no
no I've had moments before where that
happened and our eyes would meet and
they look like they want to kill me and
I'm like well why are you looking at me
in the first place too I want to kill
you too but I I'm the first one to look
away
[Music]
I'm going to go now I think I'm making
pizza after
all [\h__\h] I'm so useless these days at
least I made the goulash the other
day I should make goulash again that was
good that was so
easy I think I'm going to cancel my
hellofresh subscription I've been with
hellofresh so much and they still don't
sponsor
me it's time to break up with
them I have plenty
of
recipes what that's what they
get for not rewarding me for the amount
of advertisement I've given to
them I literally just watched the video
two days ago about these meal
services uh losing like 9 90% of their
customers immed like immediately after
the first box or second or third
box they have like a hard time keeping
their customers and I've been a loyal
customer for such a long time
man yeah they do it for the initial
discounts and like I'm you know what
really triggers me is like every time I
get a box it always comes with like uh
one paper of like four or six discount
cards that I can give to friends and
every time I'm like when do you ever
send out disc discounts for your loyal
[Music]
customers in like how many years 2 years
it's never
happened I never got a single discount
for just being loyal I've heard when you
leave them they send you a letter
possibly with a returning
customer discount but why do you only
offer it as long as I'm not a customer
like ah I want like it's like they
dangling they're dangling these
discounts in front of me every time I
open a box but it's never for me so it's
like you can waste so much time so much
money on non-existing customers who
going to leave you right away anyway but
this loyal customer like I would it
would be nice after a certain amount of
time to get some like whatever 10%
whatever doesn't have to be
much
H so
[Music]
sad if you pause long enough they send
you 25%
[Music]
really
no no that's also the thing like I would
maybe send out more discounts if I was
getting anything for that too cuz like I
feel like a lot of other places when you
bring new customers in you get something
for bringing a new one in like you get a
little discount as
well yeah that's not a thing with hello
beep so there's not really a motivation
for me to really bring in
someone that's weird that they don't do
that maybe not like every customer you
bring in you could do like every fifth
customer you bring in or whatever I
don't know you get like maybe 10% off or
so well well well
well yeah some services do that so mhm
successful
referrals
no that's not motivating so anyway yeah
8.5 hours that is true let's
go I'm going to go now I had a lot of
fun with you guys
today so I hope that I'll see you
again on Tuesday I think I'll make my
schedule tomorrow now it's already too
late but you already know like a bunch
of it
anyway
on
thank you guys for watching I'll be on
Tuesday well currently I have slay a
Spire in there but just because I
couldn't think of anything else but if
you have an
idea let me
know let me
know H and I have a member stream
planned oh Hotline
Miami uh okay
maybe maybe I'll do a SL SL fire or
Hotline Miami thing and then on the day
I'll decide if I feel like Hotline Miami
and if I don't then I do slatest sp or
so yeah yeah oh fzero oh that would be
fun
too yeah
maybe true cuz I wanted to check out the
new tracks I wanted to do the same for
Mario
[Music]
Kart okay maybe up zero
F
[Music]
zero all
right all right
then uh I am logged in
again I love you guys I love you I love
you I love
you
e
e byebye my beautiful chickens you're
the
best ch ch ch
ch p
p in say
[Music]
in
or to kind
[Music]
SU