foreign
[Music]
hello
hello that was a that was in-game cat
not real cat
hello
um
yeah yeah yeah no that was not my cat I
know Minecraft cats are so realistic
wait maybe the sword should be
a bit lower I don't know oh
I I I know there's nobody not yet not
yet if I look to the front
maybe like that I'll get it
how are you all uh
I I played I've played Tales of arise
today
yeah a test version so we might talk a
little bit about that today uh actually
you know what let me write a list
um mama
um
I left my I left my phone in a different
room God damn it uh oh well for now for
now it's fine
what did I just say oh yeah tail of a
rise
for my homo okay so
um we are Gavin here today
to find Ellie tries I like trash
whatever you want to call them I
personally always tend to call them
elitras because of the Japanese
pronunciation I guess because they say
so I just automatically assumed that it
would be
elytra's but I guess it's not whatever I
was already fixed in my brain so I can't
do much about it
foreign
no well I mean you know did and the
person in the video uh that I watched
did too
Elite Track
wings
you could call him that and here here's
some bgmo
is that too loud
[Music]
I turn it down a tiny bit what do you
think
what a little out still really
[Music]
fine with me
okay
um now it should be good oh oh wait
[Music]
maybe 37 okay there we go also
I have with me
uh Oreo shake from Burger King that
stuff is stuff is so
good who agrees with me
[Music]
like I'm not even
I'm not even that big of a fan of Oreos
but the Oreo shank oh my God
[Music]
I can't stop drinking it it's almost
almost empty anyway
um so I watched a video about how to get
early trash
[Music]
from
how was your channel called
something with OMG
[Music]
um
he has a cat
[Music]
um
no I know that you know did not get one
she only got a horse
yeah OMG craft I think that was it
and what I have learned is
[Music]
um
something about North and South and West
and East
um supposedly apparently
according to that person although he
also said he cannot 100 guarantee it
he says that
um they spawn in a line so if you start
out and everything generates in front of
you in the end because it's not already
generated different different to the
Overworld where the seed uh already has
everything generated different to that
in the end if I understand correctly
while you're moving everything that you
start seeing that is not loading in no
that is actually currently generating in
each each block that pops up in your
vision is uh currently generating so
when you first start start out in the
end of the world city in the world and
the same then
huh you shall decide where is North
where is South and where is east and
west
and they once you go in One Direction
[Music]
um let's say you go let's say you go
east or west and you go in one of the
directions and you find the city then
from there on they supposedly tend to
spawn in their cities in a line
because apparently there's a lot of like
cases where that was true now I don't
know if that is true
um but we'll just I think we'll just go
into the diff into uh the opposite
direction of Ina's Direction
because where you know when they were
it seemed like the very unlucky side of
things like and kind of like cursed
cursed Direction
uh
I saw some itsy and bitsies from her
stream it was very painful
hmm
[Music]
she does not deserve that like then
she finally fine finds
an Ender city with a ship because for
the people who don't know
when you find an inner city it's like a
um you know you walk in the end and then
sometimes you find little cities
and that City only has an elytra if on
top of the city there's like one thing
with a boat
[Music]
it but like how talking hi is the
percentage that that happens the ship
was broken
I I did not know that that is even
possible
but her six percent that is actually
pretty high surprisingly High
um but yeah that happened
um I have some ender pearls uh but I'm
just planning to get some more by
killing the Enderman uh I got those in
Phoenix then yeah
quickly before the stream also another
thing I I already prepared I prepared
some things because okay I'll tell you
my list of what I wrote down what I need
number one building blocks number two
lots of food
number three
wood blankets
number four water bucket number five
feather falling boots I got new ones
because my old ones are gone
and I got them before the stream in
Phoenix them and number four well I lost
count of the numbers but sir touch
pickaxe I got a new one or an accident
that was an old one
[Music]
yes trap door maybe if I don't want to
waste one end of pearl to go into the
portal uh but I don't really care much
about that I guess then
um maybe maybe mending Unbreaking
and an anvil if I want to put it on the
elytra immediately
um I think I can probably get mending
uh before we go into the end if I wanted
to and
I don't know why I made two
I thought
I understand the concept of the energy
and the chest generally as in if there's
one Ender Chest I open it up
um I don't see the same thing that Ina
would see if she would open it I mean if
they're empty then they're empty but if
she put something in and I open it up
it's not there see I get that I get that
idea and I also get the idea that if I
mine it with a sick touch that's why we
need a silk touch if I manage with a
sick touch pickaxe
um then uh I have it in my inventory I
guess and uh then let's say I jump off
of the Void
I I lose that one that I have in my
inventory right but I will still have it
if I open up any other Ender Chest right
so I guess maybe it makes sense that I
made two but it would probably be
preferable if I didn't lose it
if I would just leave it somewhere in
the end but
I guess now that I'm a two we're fine if
I just jump off the void into the void
with one in the chest in my inventory
that would still be fine right okay
so
stream I got a lot of paper I got a lot
of gunpowder and I got made a lot of
firework Rockets
yeah let's go so I'll take one of that
oh see I take one of those
into the end right but actually you know
let me put that there again because I
don't know maybe I want to put some more
things in here
maybe the end of Peru
[Music]
um
and some food
I don't know not it doesn't necessarily
have to be in there I guess but uh so I
also prepared some new food see this is
a bit more organized than before I think
we'll take this stack
and maybe the baked potatoes that should
be enough then we'll take some water
buckets
we don't really let's just stick to we
don't
we don't need that money do we
[Music]
um
yes yes I'm prepared yes yes yes yes yes
I also have some things in my brain that
I remembered from the video for example
if I am grab it gravitating every I
don't know when I'm flying because one
of those shulker enemies hits me when
I'm levitating not gravity levitating
when I'm levitating and then I come to
the point where I fall down
once I'm falling down I want to use my
end of pearl throw it to the ground and
then it will teleport me to the ground
and I will take
um supposedly less damage than if I
would just wait until I fall down uh
normally
understand
um
yes yes yes yes also I I learned how to
be faster with uh
block placement let me try that out
though I'm not actually sure
yeah we need building blocks we can take
whatever uh
except sand what the hell I would put I
would take those I guess and those and
those
and those we will need more probably but
then we'll just mine whatever whatever
is in the end
uh oh wait we can dig Blackstone
we're gonna take a die right yeah we'll
need a lot
uh Carey another pickaxe you mean silk
touch or normal one because uh oh yeah
my question is
does anyone know who watched ama's
stream until the end where she put it in
the end because I looked into all my
chests and I looked also into all of the
chests and the and the and near the
ender portal but I did not find my it's
in your in my
so maybe she put it into the new house
this is the only place where I didn't
look
so guys in here
[Music]
oh nice what else do I have in here
I don't even I'm not even aware of what
Avenue nothing nothing special that's
the only thing I know
okay my house my house is amazing look
at this beautiful house of this
beautiful TV wow riveting content
no it's a nice house but
unfortunately it's not being used
but the head is missing oh yeah
oh yeah that why why are they here one
if I heard that happened they were
standing here
here I didn't move those
why is there no pickaxe oh never mind I
already have a pickaxe
I didn't realize I had some more stuff
here but those are I guess without
minions
yeah no I don't really I don't really
need any of this stuff
but good to have that in mind I guess
I'll take the Torches
ah
[Music]
sorry stupid question
mending I just need to get some levels
to repair the pickaxe right shall we do
that because we're not gonna really
be able to farm levels
in the end right or can I do that with
Enderman
but
um yeah no we should probably go to the
PPP
[Music]
because it there's not really much
way to get my pickaxe repaired once I am
in the end right
oh my God
it's so good
the Oreo shake is so good
um
okay yeah so I have wait let me let me
let me see we have food uh let me check
everything in my list food yes
uh wait
food yes burning blocks yes and the
chest yes although I still have to put
in my inventory wood blankets that's
right
um uh that was for building shulker
boxes when I get my first choco thingies
now I think I don't need that money well
let's just take one stack
um
so water buckets well yes wood blankets
yes better falling boots yes so touch
pickaxe yes and the pearls yes arrows
bow yes or do I
I has I just need them
uh yes yes I mean probably don't need
more than two stacks
yeah it's not that's not that important
anyway no I don't want I don't need the
pumpkin head nope I refuse to use it
oh
[Music]
I have learned one thing
um
and that is something that I
misunderstood
during the Ender fight and the dragonfly
which is when I have the aggrove one
ender men
uh it doesn't mean I have the ever of
all of them so well if one attacks me
whatever I'll kill one and that's all
all that needs to happen
um
Shield oh yeah where did my shoot go oh
yeah
where did I put my shield oh well I'll
take a new one
uh
[Music]
I don't usually use maps
why do we need Maps
[Music]
close the door when you leave you don't
seem to watch my Minecraft streams often
my house is my house is door it's pretty
much always open and I don't I don't
really care much about closing it
[Music]
um
not get lost but if I only go straight
into One Direction
[Music]
and in the end I just jump off of the
Void
foreign
[Music]
I used up all my paper
I think I have
[Music]
um
how much
[Music]
one is one enough what is what is this
again uh Redstone and iron
I
have no iron
[Music]
left
already started map or an empty map
it's okay we'll make our own ones
wait how much Redstone was that
[Music]
Tina has a map for me
she made a large one
but you mean the one that she already
used but I want to go in a different
direction and that map just like looks
like um
[Music]
I don't I know I want to go in a
different direction hers started like in
a corner
[Music]
she made a copy
yeah but doesn't it start like in the
corner I want to go the other way
she has an empty one too
and that's it
she left you Maps already for me well
okay
so you're telling me I don't I don't
need to make a map right now
is that what you're telling me
even in any case I wasn't really
planning on bringing a map anyway
originally okay well then let's just
take whatever she left me
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
excuse me
um
[Music]
yeah I can't get the rest okay
ma come on
[Music]
Okay so
let me go over my list one more time
uh oh yeah okay
[Music]
my secret Hideaway that I have never
really make use of
let's take one of those
and there are fireworks and and the
pearls
do I have it yeah okay
I'll get Papa hide out yeah you remember
nice
all right Daniel I think we're ready to
go back to the end and portal or was
there anything else I wanted to get from
Phoenix Suns
um
I think not
mending ah
what do I have one I don't have one
right now the line
knockback Riptide loyalty and okay
everything but mending of course in
order to get a book I need a book right
I put all my books in the downstairs now
what did I mean again a emerald and a
book right
[Music]
Infinity yeah I guess I could put
Infinity on my bow is that what you guys
are trying to tell me
rainbow power and breaking should we put
it on top of that one
[Music]
yeah how do we do this again I usually
don't do this is how it works
[Music]
okay
nope okay
could I put it on this one you sure
I guess so then I don't then I have more
space and don't need to bring two stacks
of arrows I just need one Arrow then
right
hmm
[Music]
um
ah
name
oh yeah we have stream heart Challenger
now we have stream spikes
okay
okay there we go uh
we don't need wait
emeralds uh we wanted to get the Manning
book
[Music]
um okay
quickly
what do I have don't have everything
that I need to get that I have some
emeralds I have a book and I have
oh yeah it wasn't it wasn't that
expensive was it
[Music]
love conqueror
pen books really was it 10 books
more emeralds
[Music]
oh yeah we're going to PPP too
yeah one book right would have surprised
me if it was 10.
[Applause]
Phoenix time Phoenix time Phoenix time I
have arrived
hello
hello my friends
hello I'm your lord and savior
who was the dude Again The Mending wait
do I still
infinity guy works here loyalty guy
works here did I not put up the sign
where The Mending guy works
wait Shawn Mendes that's his name right
wait what does he look like again Shawn
Mendes don't go to sleep no I arrive and
they go to sleep wow
how disappointing Shawn Mendes
what do you look like again doesn't he
sleep in here no
[Music]
bed
really sorry sorry well have you seen
them
my dude uh Shawn Mendes no
have you seen him
good morning
well he must be
somewhere here oh yeah hello lonely
alpaca
another one yeah I was here today
already to prepare a little bit and
there was a trade out here a merchant
trade-off thingy a traveler Trader dude
where is he now he's gone
only because alpacas are left and
they're kind of stuck in here nice
so Phoenix Sun now has alpacas where the
hell is this dude
no
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I didn't bring anything
18. it's great iron I don't have any oh
wait I have 19. wait wait wait but
that's still probably not enough
14.
okay
I can make a bookcase never mind I'll be
RB
yeah yeah
no problem
[Music]
yeah there was some more iron today when
I logged in
someone must have AFK
um
you always up
I just need a bit more I could be woo
honestly it could be anything
[Music]
mutton
uh did you guys watch our ender dragon
fight yesterday of course no one can say
no
everyone watched that didn't didn't
that was so dramatic so good
right
it was so good the scarf made it even
better
what the hell is this sound
is this like currently operating oh
I see I see
I never heard that actually operating
before that's a Golem dying oh no
is it do we have enough
that must be enough come on
wait I just need one book I just need a
Manning book and then I'm off to go
ready to go
home
Mickey Mouse
[Music]
okay bring Angel yeah yeah
gotta bring Anvil I don't have anyone
with Unbreaking books so we're not gonna
We're not gonna be able to put that on
right away
what
what wait I'm I'm around again
it makes me feel sick oh okay
ah is that is that both no they're
forever now
in the in the sky it through
foreign
a lot Shawn Mendes
oh wait I'm not ready for you yet
thank you now I'm getting ready
well fancy doing business with you again
that's it bye-bye enjoy this
is
I want the book back
[Music]
I don't know how what happened
but I got the boat back
my boat hmm
[Music]
ah good uh
wait I heard some I heard something
about that
good iron Taco Bell commercial
I did I did hear something about them
then watch it though
foreign
I don't remember it really
when I was like
Taco Bell
enough
right
I was just like you know you know we
have someone called you know
um
uh
all right we're ready to go aren't we
one second I know we wanted to go to PPP
okay we'll do that I'll put the book and
go
um
[Music]
okay
oh the path oh
laughs
okay Anvil PPP that's all that's all we
have left right
animal PPP right
right
maybe they didn't get to talk about it
oh you're funny my ammo broke oh that's
what that sound was
like an animal
I was wondering what's why did that
sound like that oh dear lord
oh
three blocks of
how much do I need for a block of iron
[Music]
okay
okay okay okay
things like these happen
31 iron
oh man
I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry I have to take so much
has so many friends it's
amazing
it's fascinating
31 you say
wait
okay thank you
[Music]
and I know she got it I know she got an
elitra I was watching her streams elytra
is this horse
man I feel so bad like I offered her um
to just go to sleep and I'll find two
one for her one for me but I feel like
she kind of wants to
[Music]
um
find it on her own
so I don't know if I like if that even
makes sense for me to do but but kind of
I kind of want like like once you have
an elytra then you can fly around and
then it will be so much easier
to find more once you have one elytra
the rest is just easy
foreign
we put that here do we need torches we
don't really need torches
and
tasty Anvil why do I need to place the
animal
[Music]
foreign
oh yeah that's right that's right
okay first we go to PPP
there is one happy I know
why am I bugging again so much I need a
cart please
now I'm taking the animal with me to the
end so that if I find the elitra in the
end I can immediately place the envelope
put the leech one and then put The
Mending book on it
that is the plan
uh and besides that thank you for
[Music]
eign
uh stream Sparks we can get rid of that
and getting rid of that
we can get rid of that
okay
wonderfully organized
I'm always on the chickening
[Music]
go get the extreme Challenge attention
that's literally what I'm about to do
that's why I am going to PPP
the more often I write this
the railway
the longer it feels
can we have a
Express version
maybe I should make um there's there's
always at least one block uh space here
maybe I should make my ice Railway right
next to it but then who's gonna
the express version
right
I I was watching on my stream after the
end of dragon fight and she was building
her Railways and then I said I said I
said I want I'm Israel I'm a real best
Rail and I still stand by that statement
but I also like uh takanasikiaga ice
highway
I like that too
we're almost there I think
here we are wonderful yes
let's see is it day or night day or
night must be night time time hello
oh my
oh wow that's
what's unfortunate
[Applause]
I used the horse as a shield
[Music]
hello
so wait how do we do this again
I I hold it in one hand right that
that's what uh how it works okay
well now I have to wait though
now I have to wait oh
[Music]
there we go
is this working this is how this is how
it works right go to the top
there's wait there's a top
is there more enemies
and how do I go how do I go to the top
[Music]
uh here
why do I want to do that
oh God so it's not I'm not sure if I can
do that
see I can't I can't
I can't
okay come on come on you can do it I
don't know I don't know how I don't know
how I don't know how
to just go straight
hello
what is the difference
[Music]
sleep spawn more
oh how
how even more higher
how do I go higher than that oh hello
how do I even reach you
go upstairs stairs stairs ah stairs
okay
it feels unsafe
has it always been this high
high today
space taxi to the sky
foreign
this
[Music]
why did I want to come here okay now go
back down why
just wait a minute can I sleep
or should I say a link
um because uh so they spawn more of them
spawned because I went up here
sleep hello
oh
okay now how do I go down can we just
jump
foreign
into that hole
this
[Music]
classic yellow
so scary me where do I go down here
[Music]
no
I enter man
how do I go down
I just I'll wait
um
wasn't there
wasn't there one ah
[Music]
okay
foreign
like the enemies Burn by now oh wait
there's a bunch
okay careful careful
I don't know how to do this correctly
but
there we are okay gosh
let's see what do we get
[Music]
holy
ah is is it is it healing is my yes it's
healing
incredible amazing
that's it that's the good stuff that's
the good stuff there it is Yo
okay
can we do one more
foreign
[Music]
my poor employee
wow that one died immediately
hello
from my my pickaxe is almost
full now
I don't want to do the going up thing
again
I'm just gonna
do it like this yeah come on come on
zombie
okay
one more one more
yeah I got ESP what are you talking
about
what are you talking about
nothing
[Music]
oh yeah no more
okay yeah I went into the pickaxe I'm
fine with that we don't need more doing
[Music]
oh yeah
some people are just not listening
that's incredible
it's an ending
[Music]
I was looking for safety you want to go
home with me I don't have any saddlers
though with me I'm sorry
[Music]
go
I missed circles you have to forget
about circles
okay we're ready to go guys we are so
freaking ready let's go
let's go
and put some water in my glass
ES
okay
we're going to the end and we're going
to kill a few Enderman so that we get
some more pearls
we want a few more pearls probably
this might be a long long long long
journey
yeah but the good thing is we have an
under chest
so whenever we are like
we just fall into the void
yeah I don't know yeah
I don't I watched like once how it works
but I think it's not
really necessary it's just one end of
pearl that I have to throw through the
portal right so
um
tractors are safer
think
I want to go once you get back
ah oh no I don't need one to get back
because I'm just gonna fall into the
void
in case I miss
um
okay
okay I'll do the trapdoor thing but
I'm not 100 sure how to do that we will
have to try on Arrow how did Eno get in
with the end the pro
yeah in a pearls stop curled thrill
I see
yeah
okay this I will put back
let's go
one more time back home and now and then
we have to first of all find our way
back to the end
in the world portal whatever
these words confuse me
[Music]
the books then
put the arrows in
put the Torches in
okay ready to go let's go
I know I haven't made a path where did
it start
ah there okay that's those stairs right
okay
you need a bed there's beds in at the
portal
uh a lot of it so I just put my save
points there
and if I die then I respawn
outside the Ender Portal
all right
Under the Stairs
oh
[Music]
below the stairs
oh yeah
what are those stairs for
I don't see a path here
where does it start I already came back
once
um but at some point I lost the path
on my Skype what exactly is the sky
Temple though and why I mean for a while
I can follow the sky Temple where
where is it
[Music]
must be somewhere here
you'll see it when you hit what is that
is that it
oh that must be it
political
for me it ended somewhere else though
funnily enough there was a fork or
something
but
and I asked you know like yo we know did
you also like some get lost somewhere
and she was like no hmm
how is that possible
[Music]
she's gonna build rails all over that
amazing
[Music]
ah by the time we saw her she was
started in town ah you guys didn't even
see her walking back okay
I see
by the way the the boat thingy I mean I
guess I could build a boat once I'm
there but I don't really know how the
boat thingy works
fighting Enderman in a boat I only know
the strategy with the like three blocks
to block
thingy stop popping
why am I bumping there we go don't Bop
anymore please like making me go crazy
I should have brought a bed just for
traveling oops
oh well I am a professional
part-time Warrior
this is not a challenge to me fighting a
few enemies in the night
[Music]
strike all right
huh
straight
what what is it what is it was the other
password
[Music]
did she find something
it's a dead end let's see stop bopping
stop
oh and left we go
it was a mistake
um she made it she made a bad turn oh
laughs
but I'm really grateful she made this
path to begin with right after the Ender
Dragon Hunt
she just continued she ditched Super
Mario haha can't hit me she ditched
Super Mario in order to build this which
I was like super grateful for because
this way I can easily find back
to the portal and back to the to our
headquarters in the first place
did she play Mario afterwards
what I thought this one already took her
so long that she might just not do Mario
at all afterwards I I have I had to go
to bed
at some point
the Ender Dragon thingy for me started
at midnight
yesterday
it is currently by the way half past 9
p.m oh I see you
oh my God a lot of skeletons
well that was maybe not so smart to stop
here
leave it alone trust me you don't want
to fight me
[Music]
okay
oh my God
rally really wrongly
is that
is it because I turned like that and
then I got in
[Music]
eh
I flip with him
I guess I did
ah it happens
it happens hello
yeah yeah shoot each other idiots
oh
[Music]
yes
so this is where it gets interesting
everyone
this is where it gets interesting
actually before the stream When I Was
preparing a little bit I also ran around
like I tried to find this exit
because I logged in and I was I was
standing here
and I didn't see that
so I thought oh I wonder where imma
build the the you know the exit
I was running around I couldn't find it
and I was getting lost in here but I
found some other things I found the
second library that Library didn't have
any Treasures though but I also find
found some from treasure chests I didn't
have anything special in it but it was
interesting to see that there was more I
thought it would only be you know oh but
oh Kusa look there's my stuff in here as
well
funny funny
I wouldn't even have needed to make my
own Ender Chest
oh yeah asleep yeah
that's Ina's chest
oh
so
we probably want pearls uh oh I want
hero
trapdoor
let's try it out
[Music]
do you guys think I'll be fine with
feather falling free alone in the in the
pearls
bring it
[Music]
um
no harm in bringing it okay uh
I'm a bit scared
um
but
uh yeah okay let's go
you need a lot of something yeah I don't
need it no
I'll be fine
bring frame well I only have one
there's only one
put more stuff and then the chest
Rockets I have rocks how many times do I
have to show this this is the fifth
stand that I'm showing is here here they
are and mending
foreign
no more comments about Rockets it's not
rocket science for God's sake
say touch
[Music]
hello
you lack arrows are you joking
foreign
if I didn't have Infinity
yeah I chose not to use a pumpkin head I
don't need that
gosh okay it was somewhere where was it
you know I must have already oh there we
go you almost have already built up to
it
um
foreign
[Music]
can we try this first
wait a second
let me try
oh
foreign
[Music]
add a map oh where was it
no map two blocks high at any
how do I get it oh wait
[Music]
no that they can get me when I'm here no
will this work
oh
okay we have to try that works okay hi
[Music]
you didn't give me anything
that's okay there's many many more look
at me oh I didn't I looked at the back
of his head and he still saw me there
aha easy
that's gonna feel
hello
[Music]
I love how they get so mad oh she don't
need to make upside down do they have
eyes Under A Bank
on their back of their heads it seems so
in the pearl what the hell
yeah
yeah the noise freaks me out too oh
hello you teleported huh you couldn't
wait to get to me huh meet and greet
with takanasikiana and don't call me in
Dusseldorf very soon please uh where are
your finest clothes just kidding I don't
care what you're gonna wear I really
don't care it's it's gonna be a hot
summer
a hot hot summer
hot thoughts gonna be a hot summer hello
let me see
no one here
[Music]
okay someone
who wants to find I'll do it somewhere
else
[Music]
and then
wait
[Music]
um
hmm
hello welcome to my shop everyone
I saw
oh baked potatoes and oh yeah oh my God
you guys really want those baked
potatoes vegetables
[Music]
lamb chops or whatever that is oh my God
die already
dad
here we go one death Wonder
and finally and then the Pearl I think
the other ones didn't drop any
what is that music
what was that music guys
I think you might have not heard it but
why was there music
[Music]
and music
it was like
ambient noise
oh
cute
remind me they are like simply they're
simplicity
of design kind of reminds me
a little bit
[Music]
um
it's poopy a little bit of
no one reacts to me of that no face dude
from
you know you know what I mean
and no face dude
I feel like I might run out of food
well those those mushrooms by the way
that teleport you back to the ground do
they also fill up Hunger
oh there they come they're coming
foreign
[Music]
do you see me no
do you must see me come on
no
oh
hello
fight me
[Music]
that makes my heart go doggy doggy
just anything Eva
these guys I thought they dropped way
more what the hell is going on
you see me
hello
[Music]
you don't need a I don't need a wall
really
oh it feels nice to have a wall
protecting me
hello
one more
[Music]
they sound like an airplane
hello
[Music]
I got one
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay for now let's go
it sword what what do you mean
X have looting
one
don't stop it unlucky for teeth
what do you mean looting
[Music]
five what
uh-huh
fifty percent I mean if I had looting
then uh
I would have a higher chance
one of them
[Music]
okay uh trapdoor how does this work
I need to look at the video I think it
was something like here and then uh the
other way around right but wait block ah
I think I think I know
uh
[Music]
this and now
oh
ah
I think I got it
oh now I'm flying right oh
that genius
genius
hi
Sophie
let's go I'm scared I'm scared
big brain
remote Gateway I didn't I didn't
bring the map right but that's okay so
you guys just have to tell me I guess
you know went in that direction huh I
see the path we're going to the other
direction although I see absolutely
nothing there
I guess I'll go I'm over to those small
Islands
uh I had a court ah
um yeah okay so there's this thing
with no no way okay so North here
oh
no up here
South here is here West here
I don't 100 understand that Fury well
strategy
[Music]
well
uh
[Music]
that I was watching when she made the
house on the dirt and the Enderman kept
on taking the Dirt away that was funny
okay so empty map
should I take 201
[Music]
we're going the other way then Nina is
going
the other way from inal
one okay and oh dear is wait once I open
it oh wait how does it work
eh I should take this one too but I
don't want to go in the same direction
oh well
how does this work make a copy
I never use maps
ah
[Music]
oh
hello
but can I make it bigger
well she started here right
she went like this this is this
but I wanna therefore with the dog and
it's only the biggest
I want to go the other way that I guess
that way
because
she found uh
she started East Side she started
uh
she started in the middle ah
wait
[Music]
ah
I see him
and did she first go up or down where
did she find the first Fortress
[Music]
foreign
she found it that she found The Fortress
in the north
[Music]
I see therefore I will go south
even though she probably found
absolutely nothing in South huh go east
um
[Music]
I mean that's an option too
go east
all right we better find something there
but if the fury is correct but go east
they say go east today say go east
well
[Music]
I'm trying to drink water don't look at
me
well
foreign
um made the blocks can I make
cobblestone into like
like slabs
I guess not
okay
wait how do I do it
[Music]
I can make thyroid slabs
and not Cobblestone clubs
oh there are so many
[Music]
that's a lot of slabs
I know I need to find a ship
okay
let's go that way
is this a joke
ah Southeast
um
[Music]
I already seen some stuff there
is
uh
well she went there
well if I how about I first go all the
way down south
the path that she already built
[Music]
no I don't need night vision
okay yeah should I do it
but that's where she found nothing right
that's where she found nothing and then
went back
[Music]
oh dear
oh
[Music]
wait where am I facing
but do we really have nothing here
come on there must be something
like she already was up here right there
is
she must have no wait you know what she
probably was not up here
she wasn't
all right that's pretty far away
pretty far away
I'm scared
quit
okay
[Music]
let's go
foreign
[Music]
that was fast
one small but we were trying to go to ah
that didn't render before right we were
trying to go over there that's okay I'll
go here
oh
no problem something above me all right
we'll go we'll go we'll go to unchan
Uncharted lands guys this is so scary
it's like being in the freaking universe
[Music]
I'm so scared
I thought it was falling
I was playing
[Music]
I can't fall I am in this position okay
I mean I can't fall when I'm in this
position
[Music]
okay
I hate this I hate this I hate this I
hate this I hate this I hate this I hate
this I hate this I hate this do a flip
yeah yeah yeah
ah
we'll get used to it we have to get
views
the handstand I can't that literally
can't
I wish I knew how to do a handstand
where where are we
okay
keep on going that way
yes keep on going that way
ah
I have I have like um toggle shift on
toggle so I don't have to press the
button thankfully unless I push it again
um
yeah otherwise I would probably already
have fallen down
[Music]
I have let's go
as if there's like a Subway here a trail
around
I mean the ambient noise yeah but that
just doesn't sound right
[Music]
guess you can toggle yeah yeah
help me
[Music]
I'm almost there
Wally
are you coming to welcome me huh don't
worry I don't have background don't
worry
hello
foreign
[Music]
let's see what we have
it's a family big one family Big Island
what if I am done with this map though
can I use this one
I'm not sure how to use maps and I don't
really need them out but
[Music]
I can okay
well there's nothing really here
[Music]
oh
that's I already found another city
probably not one with a ship but that's
okay we need to learn how
we need to learn how to fight against
those shulker babies first
that seems like just one tiny single
time
foreign
or is it just that rendering
oh it looks like a single one
all right let's go that way
let's check it out
tiny baby in City
[Music]
okay
we are doing fine guys
[Music]
we're doing just fine
I'll go from here
okay
uh
I guess this way yeah
[Music]
feel essential yeah yeah I totally feels
anyway so guys by the way I was I was
playing
um
trying to uh
get my mind off of this oh I was one I
was
I was playing Tales of our eyes uh a
test build of tales of our eyes
privately before the stream actually
that test build I think is um
one that has been shown already anyway
and has been given out to like media
outlets and whatever like literally it's
just the the one where you run around
suddenly with a full party full grip of
party full party of one full grip of
your party
um
and you you yeah you run around and then
there's someone stopping you from going
into the big city and then he tells you
yup there with you there's this big
monster so that's why you can't go into
the city which is just
um that that is not a thing in the real
game that is just for the test version
so that you don't get into the City and
then it leads you to fighting that
um
tiny boss and so that's what I did um
nothing super super new but it was very
nice to play it by myself because
oh originally I uh
um only saw some footage of that test
build okay we are here let's learn how
to fight those and then we continue uh
talking about it
at the coordinated but this is not
really any anything special but okay I
got it uh wait I got it okay
um yeah get me let me get some some of
the food
food thingies here one second not where
there's so many other men here
foreign
[Music]
I don't like that noise
I don't like it at all
I I know that it will always teleport me
to some ground
okay it heals too
okay
well good to know
okay but it can't teleport me too far
away right
[Music]
okay
let me eat one more
yeah I know it's a random teleport but I
I it can't be that far
so let's put that here
we need that we
I don't know maybe need a water bucket
maybe I would be too panicky to use it
anyway probably but I will
[Music]
uh yeah that's all I need
okay
when I land if I put a water bucket or I
pulled another Pearl
screams box everyone
baby I don't know I don't know how to
fight you guys
oh
[Music]
yeah okay what can I no no no no let me
go down
[Music]
this is gonna be chaotic
this is gonna be chaotic okay
[Music]
okay let's stop here also I need those
fingers
give me give me give me
with those things what can you do of
those things there was a bunch of things
that you could do with end rods well I
was like oh I wish I had an Android
black left Shield oh yeah right okay
let's get some end round I like sauce oh
yeah
oh I wanted them for interior design for
like lamps because they the ones that I
was looking at people were using lamps
uh using those for lamps okay I want to
kill them I want to kill them
foreign
[Music]
there's a drop right not that high
okay okay okay okay
there's not much here
okay and now
[Music]
I'm glad we're gonna go up
we go up we go up we go up
and there's probably nothing up there
except oh you guys
thoughtful
you're helping me to come up well thank
you
yeah I don't mind you guys telling me
flying
whatever the hell you want to do
fight me
yeah oh
[Music]
one for you one for you one for you one
I'm sorry
[Music]
hi
shut up
okay well did anyone drop anything ouch
no traps
[Music]
well now I have to
oh wait is there still one up there no
oh
no handyman are you okay I wish there
was one there's nothing up there right
should I just should I just go down
there's nothing up there I I assume
[Music]
was there a chest oh well then I have to
go out oh
[Music]
use end of pearl ah oh oh oh oh
I shall do that eventually
okay let's try to get up there
[Music]
it's gonna be a pain in the ass
oh beautiful blocks
oh
I want those blocks
[Music]
huh no
I can't it can't be that hard to get up
there
[Music]
and I can I can make these from the
trees those beautiful blocks I can make
from the trees but what if all I get is
the fruit
would I have to mine it with a with a
sub touch pickaxe
[Music]
I cook you cook the fruit and what the
block comes out of it
yo it's such a pretty block
aqua affinity I'm breaking fruit
[Music]
no space
put in another chest
[Music]
oh wait nothing call me
I'm breaking depth Strider
I didn't really expect much from this
towel anyway I just wanted it to for
practice
I'm happy
[Music]
okay
the boots
these ones are nice what does deaths try
to do again
[Music]
swim faster ah wait
I'm breaking
and Aquafina wow very much water uh
equipment underwater equipment
so
if we take the box
is still anything
or is that the end of course it's the
end
it was definitely the end I'm not
looking at you
that looks like
that
[Music]
I'll take those with me
thank you okay
we'll find the next Ender City guys
[Music]
ouch
I should be more careful of taking
damage I also love this beautiful glass
oh wait I was doing that with myself
touch oh well hello I'll be more careful
I want the classic
meal but no space probably in my
inventory I need to resist
all right uh
now let's take a look at the map
in the same which direction I have to go
that way
so oops uh
[Music]
we saw from that one always go east
we'll go only in One Direction
that is
my strategy
wherever you want it like it or not
[Music]
okay
uh it's a good one yeah I mean if you
only go into One Direction in Fury you
would eventually find something but
you know people say that
ends it is only uh generate in One
Direction now I don't know if that is
true
but
there is no way to know
so we can only walk but but she Ina went
in all kinds of directions right
there's a lot of land here
I appreciate that
makes it easier to walk around should we
try the new map
how how but how does how do I use it
it's
it's so tiny
no
it's all it's so tiny
why is it so tiny
it's so tiny
meanwhile paper I have no more people
all right then it's useless we just got
used to it
that's all right
it's so small
I should have brought more paper
so much land
foreign
[Music]
like um
because it was a test test build I was
playing like how do you call it remotely
like through parsec
so
that's kind of one of the reasons why it
wasn't really recommended to stream
because obviously the quality would not
be the best
and possibility that it would be lagging
but it wasn't lagging it actually went
super well it was really smooth
um the fighting was so much fun you know
I will not tell you anything
to like
detailed because I don't know if I'm
even allowed to but I can I get I can
tell you roughly I was having a ton
of fun I went down I was I was really
um
um uh brain not working I was I was
really uh had to say
I haven't told you
I I had I had this mood this this hunger
for adventure so even though it was a
fairly small
um test build
[Music]
um
I
uh
was I can't speak English right now
I was exploring a lot and I found a lot
of treasures
sorry my throat is really not doing well
right now
I found a lot of treasures
and a lot of equipment and stuff that
was cool
in the in the test play like the same
test play but played by someone else
would I have seen they didn't find those
Treasures like I really spent a lot of
time just walking around instead of
following the path like you were
supposed to it was I was looking in
every corner for uh oh yeah I should eat
when I'm when I'm over on the other side
I was looking at every corner for for
like materials and treasures and I found
so many Treasures
hmm
[Music]
don't tell me that there's a ship there
oh so young
okay
is that are you are you kidding me
that looks pretty big
[Music]
[Laughter]
phoenix look let's go
oh
okay
I'm so nervous
okay focus just talk about Tales of our
eyes talk about Tales of all rise
up my hands are sweaty
um
[Music]
uh yeah yeah uh I was actually quite
excited about for example the swimming
uh
I'm so sorry
foreign
[Music]
looks fine looks intact oh my God
imagine it
ah
all right
let me take a little cough drop
uh so anyway in terms of her eyes I
actually I I tried to play a couple of
characters because I think I mentioned
this before but when I whenever I play
tails off games
um no matter who my favorite character
character is uh
I will usually always play
um fights with the main character
um which would usually be a sword finder
oopsie I got them
um because I just always felt the
smoothest and the easiest and um
mark this one so that people know that I
was here
how do I mark it
[Music]
well I'll just put here a few slabs and
then people should know right or I could
put a sign I have Spruce blanks
oh well
here I was I was I was here
[Music]
vandalize it okay I mean you will see
once you get in anyway
let's go now my mission is just to not
die
do I need anything
[Music]
is sword better now
does sword have a better reach
[Music]
why did it teleport away what the hell
the way they can teleport
oh
[Music]
right
open your heart for me let's be friends
come on these monsters are so weird
[Music]
yeah
oh
there we go and dropping nothing okay
I'm not very lucky with chocolate boxes
oh there's something flying from where
I wanna find you shoot me I want to get
up to you
Oreo
I'm inviting you to shoot me and yes you
refuse
all right I'll go inside
wait actually we could just go straight
for the ship uh but I don't really have
that many blocks anyway is there a path
oh wait there is no path
wait wait wait
oh
oh well
I was on the wrong one oh well we only
use one now
and I want to mine some blocks
[Music]
what what
to me
[Music]
fly to it that's dangerous no way
no no no that that flying debuff doesn't
hold on that long
now what I've seen from the video that I
watched the dude basically he just went
straight under it and built all the way
up because then you know why the hell
why now but I want the loots from from
inside as well
um we'll go inside normally and then
build a bridge I guess
well I'm so lucky what the hell
why was Eno so unlocking that's not fair
she was looking for hours
and first of all she didn't even find
any Ender cities right that was the
first problem then she finds one but it
didn't have a ship and then she finds
another one but that one had a broken
ship and they she went up anyway to
check if it maybe still has anything
but it didn't
my neck's just sad
but you know what now that we have the
elite trap probably and I have the
Rockets you know what I I could totally
fly around and get her one too but
I don't know like she probably wants to
get it herself
so yeah I wanna I wanna like you know
the Journey of finding one is fun too
right and the excitement of finding it
yourself so I but however one day I want
to find one for myself and also
um for other purposes I might want to
get a few more
uh keep one for gift for example that's
that's or selling
selling I'm I'm not thinking about
gifting I'm thinking about selling
[Music]
sorry what's wrong with me
laughs
I broke I freaking broke
right now
okay let's get half a stack
I was talking about uh Tales over rice
okay
um
where was I oh yeah normally I would
always play the the main character which
would usually be a sword finder but I
wanted to for the sake of you know doing
a test play and wanting to learn more
about the game I tried out the others I
tried
um I tried uh
obviously because she has almost the
same name as me
obviously alphan
did I try for a moment I tried rain well
but
um Magic
[Music]
as uh like being as the as the one
playing the game using the Magic
character is
not
the I don't know it just doesn't feel
right
um because it doesn't feel like you're
really like the the one that leads the
battle
but I have to say from the brief moment
when I played renwell the magic user of
the group
um it was oh
it was surprising how
like
there was like I didn't notice any
casting time for her skills
I don't know I don't know man but I
didn't notice any casting time
weirdly enough uh
so I could like really bang out those uh
casts those skills
but the fights were so flashy and so
fast and smooth that I could barely tell
how much damage I was making as the
Caster I really didn't know what I was
doing as roomless I I quickly switched
back to
um whoever I was playing at that moment
normally okay okay that's fine with me
that's fine that's fine okay that's fine
with me that's fine with me
um
oh
[Music]
my God is this a good idea
I'll hide a chance okay let's stay here
let's stay here let's stay
oh my God oh my God
oh my god let's just go to the top let's
oh my god oh let's go here let's go here
let's go here let's go here
okay
[Music]
let's just oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God okay
ah
can I stay here help
sorry Panic move oh my God there's too
many oh so cute
[Music]
what's with all those curses mending
ombre Irish
foreign
[Music]
boxes though
foreign
above my head
why does it not hit him
[Music]
it never hits this dude
break the game I would like to say
no no
no no no no no no no no no no no
Shakira Shakira
Bonita
oh baby
[Music]
so be wise and keep on reading the signs
oh drop something on the one maybe then
come on tonight and my hips don't lie
I'm starting to feel oh there we go okay
starting to feel it boy
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait
okay I got one
yeah
oh I killed one
okay
[Music]
sorry this is the it's too much
for me
huh
where are you where are you I hear you
anyway
I started blasting
yeah
we need to go down again though to see
what they dropped but I don't really see
anything except for EXP
okay that's one that's one
[Music]
no no
no no please no
no
[Music]
I'm stupid okay let's uh let's get that
one let's get that one
a bucket yeah I have it but I don't even
think of using it
[Music]
all right
okay okay downwards is maybe a bit
easier
[Music]
give me that thank you
did I pick it up yes
[Music]
I could have used water there
I chose not to
wow there's still one left I don't know
[Music]
where is it
okay let's try to get up again it would
have been easier with those monsters to
go up again because then I could fly up
but okay
uh we're current gorgeous
[Music]
huh
where is it not in here right they're
outside right now
[Music]
how to place underneath there you go
am I hallucinating or
hang around here though
that's it
over there
it's outside right okay is it is it over
there I lost uh my sense of direction
[Music]
clear the top of the uh should I go to
the very top all right I was already at
the top
I didn't I didn't did I take no I didn't
take the treasure ah
sorry I'm really slow
all right
sorry for being so slow
my brain is not working
go top pool water I will try that next
[Music]
I wanna go up there
we go okay
okay
hi hi hi
nice stairs
why is this Tower
ing
why so big is that really necessary
[Music]
like a completely new environment
it's super exciting
okay thank you I'll use that thank you
thank you I want to go all the way up
there please pick thank you thank you
thank you thank you
okay okay okay okay
that was 100 planned
that is exactly what I wanted to happen
so we'll take that
although I mean of course I'm Vanishing
on the moment
diamonds
gold
[Music]
this and this
oh wait we can make a showcase
which means we need a crafting table
okay
how many two two right two I need
foreign
I could if I make one more chest I
have another box how'd you make them all
you can dye them right can you dine with
normal dye
this is so exciting
[Music]
that is so nice eat I mean I like the
color I like purple I like it I have no
problem with it
all right let's put it in
ah if I have the soccer box in my
inventory and I want to go like I want
this block now and but this block is in
the Shocker box will it choose like when
I do the the middle wheel Mouse wheel
thingy will it choose that one even if
it's in the shulker Box does anyone know
no it will not goddammit okay
okay I see well we can put the Anvil in
we can put the map in
we're gonna put
the gold
I can put all of that
um
[Music]
we can put that oh wait why is that oh
okay okay we can put
put this in this
[Music]
shoes ah thank you thank you and the
emeralds and the Diamonds
oh yeah I mean I'm not really struggling
that much with
face right now anyway but
looking good let's put some more blocks
here
so we have one row of building material
we have a bit more food we have an arrow
we have a water bugger with food ah this
part this pickaxe keep that here down
here uh these boots
box
it's oh it's not possible oh
no should I bring those I guess why the
hell not
why the hell not much
okay
well then I don't have to mine this one
with one do I have to
put chocolate blocks into it yeah yeah
that was my plan
do I have to mine this one with uh the
clutch no
[Music]
sorry
oh okay
oh
okay so now this wait do we go even
higher is there something nice
[Music]
no
oh
my God
chill Kiana chill
okay bolt is where
both is there
do we do you want me to go in all of
these hours
[Music]
wait should I maybe get the wings first
and then put them into the in the chest
you know just in case you know then I
can die in any of these towers
can we go first into the into the ship
so I just wanna I just want to make sure
that I don't die in any of the other
toys okay okay so we have to go over
there is that connected no okay
[Music]
okay let's fight this
okay oh I got one
okay
foreign
[Music]
ha sorry I still don't know what I'm
doing but if yeah I was thinking about
eating a fruit but I was wondering if
that means it teleports me too the this
ground or it can it also be this ground
like what the hell where is it gonna
just gonna teleport me to one of the
closest grounds randomly or does it
always have to be that ground
that's what I wasn't sure about
uh
we still have so many ender pearls too
oh yeah I should I should just use the
end of pearls
foreign
[Music]
okay okay uh but I'm kind of scared like
if I go there this one will already be
attacking me from a fire so I should can
I shoot him from here
ah a bit too far away
ah okay
but once we get a bit closer I will try
to snipe them down
when you think about that
you think I can from here all right
let's see
hmm
they're quite follow oh that one went
above I think
[Music]
and I don't really know how when I use
the zoom like how far I I can't really
I don't I don't know I can't tell
is this too high I don't know
[Music]
mmm
I don't know let's just get closer
[Music]
until until they start shooting me
that's when I panic
it's just just a little bit closer
oh I guess I could use the underground
so
um use the portion should I use it now
oh they have not really seen me yet
[Music]
come on and
this is so scary
yeah I'm thinking about the slow falling
potion and thinking about it
I can't get him oh I got him
oh all right I got it but I said falling
down oh well we already have a bunch
a bit too high
uh still a bit too high
huh
[Music]
ah there we go that's it that's the spot
where is it
get him tiger there we go
okay
cool
now I don't think there's anything
dangerous for us when we when we're on
the way there nothing should be hitting
me right
we're safe to go
foreign
[Music]
that's just like the second Ender City
like the first one was just a tower and
the second inner city not only
immediately found already has a boat
damn
[Music]
it's pretty big I want to see what's
like does every one of these towers have
like a treasure
Oh I wanna see it
now that's the lack of the Phoenix I'm
I'm so sorry you know honestly I feel
like the game was rigged on her side but
oh that was fast but it's really just
the fact that you know
Phoenix block it exists how do I get in
there
uh wait maybe from the side
[Music]
like from here
you're giving me anxiety yeah I'm giving
anxiety to myself as well
um
[Music]
here I'm gonna make it a bit safer
that's better for my heart too okay
oh obsidian oops
oh yeah let's go with that
Moshi Moshi
awesome
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
this is oh
this one is good good stuff
how how do I take it oh my God
[Music]
put it in the Box put it in the Box put
oh should I put it I could also put it
on but
when I put it in the Box
yeah
ah
been second on me uh put that into the
Soca box
um
[Music]
take a photo
we're not done I think I don't know this
was too short
[Music]
I thought it would need more time I want
to do more I mean we're definitely gonna
see the other Towers but okay so because
we're gonna check out the other towers
for now for safety we're gonna put the
links right in the in the end in the
chest and then afterwards we fly home
move the ender chest uh with the with
the only try I guess
um I mean we haven't been so far so we
could even walk but yeah
[Music]
um
right that's actually so good this is
perfect for like
a dragon head oh yeah this is perfect
for being hit by those projectiles right
because it had oh my let me put those on
am I dead
[Music]
regular protection is better oh well but
this one only has feather falling cream
this is already better
let me put mending on my elytra we can
name my elytra
[Music]
there's this
how it works
first
right
it was the first real Ender City that we
found the other one was just a tower can
we call it first and we try
is it is it okay hot wings would be good
too ah
but we can get a second electron called
that hot wings but this one must be the
first early try
ah
the second one I'll get I'll call Hot
Wings
okay
[Laughter]
I'll do it
I like I like hot wings too a phoenix
links
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm going to but I think this is a
nickname that you guys gave me with all
your love
oh my God
[Music]
okay okay
we did it
[Music]
that was that was so fast I didn't even
use my end of girls
man
oh I got oh I got all those thingies oh
I just realized the flight duration won
huh there's a
H those don't fly very long huh oh well
that's my my first time making fireworks
so I didn't really pay attention to that
okay let's put that
in here
and mine that
if this
creation one is good control
okay ah this one as well
okay
what's next oh
it's here instant health potions
[Music]
oh should I take this thing too and we
can use it in Phoenix then
ah
let's take it
wait a second
[Music]
let's put this in here this heals me
right the dragon head yes yes okay wait
I'll just keep that the dragon head must
be where
there oh I see it
I'll do
wait this bothers me
I need safety
I don't want this above me
how do I how do I mine it so it doesn't
fall down
[Music]
pull the platform around it but if I
mine it right here it should pick it up
pick it up though no
wow
[Music]
safe safe
oh scary actually it's not even that
scary
you look like a toy
[Music]
toy not the real head
okay do I mind it with a normal pickaxe
[Music]
yeah okay I'm scared
I'm just kidding
[Music]
oh
dragon head
you know what that just makes sense
because that was actually I don't know
if you guys noticed I didn't even notice
until people told me but I was the one
who did the last hit on the Ender Dragon
yesterday
is there something up there
Mr
hello
no nothing oh my God that's so scary
that's so scary
[Music]
if I ended up I left it there on purpose
okay
because that was the dragon slayer
yeah all right all right all right
um
[Music]
okay I'll put you back inside
try the helmet we can take it we can put
it on for the picture
there's a picture in the end so now that
we have been here
we want to go you
oh
I guess here
or where we are no we were not there yet
right we went from down here up here and
then
I guess Primo over there one here and
then here so now we check out the right
one first
get more shulkers yeah I guess you can
never have enough let's just wanted an
elite Trail
that's all I really want oh I hear them
shooting
so is there a treasure everywhere for
real
foreign
[Music]
oh that's new material oh my God
foreign
[Music]
oh so well you know what you know what I
prefer being here
I hate you so much okay worst case yours
are in the real worst case use on the
real voice kids just use the in
the pool
thank you
just go inside
[Music]
I love it
is so chaotic
okay I got I got I got I got health
okay okay
oh oh and the chest
I don't really need that energy okay
okay okay okay okay we're good we're
good now
[Music]
let's build a pop
oops
let's go over to that little friends we
have take it anyway yeah
Raja
oh
laughs
[Music]
how dare you
girls are so useful here against these
Buddies
[Music]
look to me you like me that much huh
[Applause]
[Music]
cookie
oh
I got it give it to me give it to me
give it to me give it to me thank you
okay
um
[Music]
let's see what's in here
leave me the hell alone
[Music]
that's so confusing that is so confusing
I thought I thought there was a random
one
that is so confusing okay
oh wait huh I I can't put interest in
the interest
but but oh wait before we do anything
let's take a shocker box
[Music]
put some stuff in there
um I could have taken the other one oh
well uh five reduction I'm breaking
mending
this is my stuff this is my stuff we can
put that in Unbreaking cream ending uh
pick that one up or a bunch a while ago
right
okay
[Music]
I wanna kill those in
chocolates you're so noisy
I will make them quiet
[Music]
let's order me I don't know we got the
treasure in here is there any more
Treasures
should I where am I
just go to the next Tower
we'll still find them way more way more
Shockers in the other towers as well
yeah
because very important next hour kill
shulker chokers are treasure all right
all right all right but I hate this this
is such a pain in the ass
does it go down
oh dude
[Music]
there are many more right
so I don't know
good day I would have to go down
there is no down okay well just this is
just we're done with this Tower we'll go
to the next one
[Music]
we'll go to the next one next one wow
okay
[Music]
okay we haven't been in this one right
I'm going
straight for you
[Music]
but we're still fine we're still fine
calm down okay
I was ready to select
the ender pearl but I'm good I'm oh
another one so many free and their chest
[Music]
hold on
welcome to the party
okay one down
[Applause]
[Music]
okay just kind of stay calm in this
situation
oh
hi I'm
trying I call my only trap I got I got
my wings they're called hot wings
when are you gonna get yours are you
gonna look for them soon
I got the elytra
if you're going to the same direction
where I went I think you'll find
something to
the direction that Ina went to is cursed
I'm telling you it's freaking cursed
you can detectives fly oh I see are you
are you suggesting that you might refuse
to fly at all because you want to you
know be the rail girl
[Music]
where the hell
up
I'm about to fall down
okay let's stay here okay
this is quite challenging
oh it died okay
let's get those
air
oh it's calm now I think I killed them
all
I think I killed them off
my my bow is doing a really good job yes
yes
you sure
I think I missed the last message that
I'm around what did she say
did you say anything about
the thing that I said
Infinity bow MVP for real for real Souls
[Music]
okay I got it what's in here that was
the most recent okay
[Music]
oh well I'm happy about the emeralds
silk touch iron shovel when do you need
a silk touch iron shovel
I guess I should take one of the rods
too
for grass
can we just put that in here for now
I'll I'll organize it later
let me take those
oh God damn it
[Music]
okay I want the free and the chest I
guess for someone else yeah I guess
Callie I don't know if she ever wants to
go on this journey herself but
uh it is quite a challenging journey I
did tell her though that she if she
wants to go I will go with her but if
she decides not to go I'll just give her
an Ender Chest I mean you will you will
need one
anyway when you go to the end so it
would be useful to have one before going
in here
yeah I'm ready to help her whenever she
wants
okay oh nothing at the top right so
let's go to the next one
I want bear Treasures
we went we went to that one did we no
did we
we went to this one we went to the ship
um
we did go to that one
I want you to go that direction maybe
was this what a ship was that was what a
ship was okay so now we go back to the
middle we did this part I guess
[Music]
drop me drop it now thank you
don't do that it fell down yeah
that was very stupid of me
I did not see where I was going what the
hell is going on here
huh did I oh wait I didn't check that
one out yet
[Music]
all right I'll do it manually
let's have fun here
there we go there it is
what do you want
I want Justice
and silence in this place oh am I
shooting the projectile
that's a way to block them too huh okay
shocker one two where are the rest
outside okay
cool maybe I'm breaking efficiency
that's a nice shovel efficiency ombre
come on
watching free
not bad I don't need so many shovels
though wait
let's take chocolate box
huh
it's almost maxed right
okay so tools oh that's mine I don't
really need an ax here but
you know what for safety because I don't
really need these two left at the moment
at all
put them inside
[Music]
rods
um yeah
[Music]
take it and put it inside
and here we go another free Ender Chest
my luck is insane really is this good
stuff
[Music]
is there usually not so much good stuff
here
put the NHS in the end of chaser
oh
oh wait
I see I see I see okay
[Music]
and their chests in the Ender Chest
foreign
it does really seem like I'm quite lucky
I mean me finding this inner city so
early on in the first place was
surprising hi zombies
I am
interception I want those please
okay uh I guess we did that tower now
when which Tower was that yeah
so many projects
I was on the wrong thing damage
stop it already
Ken has joined the stream yeah
[Music]
uh ah I wanna go straight to the other
side I suppose
[Music]
okay I'll stay here was I here before
I think not a lot of stuff moving in
there okay
okay no no no not again not again
[Music]
foreign
where is it
oh am I yes
this is so much fun and so stressful
okay okay chill chill relax
we have to analyze the situation look
carefully at what we got what we're
dealing with
another shirt
we stopped laughing oh you hit yourself
huh what an idiot you are
foreign
I don't even mind flying it doesn't even
do that much damage but I guess because
I have diamond armor
okay pretty much clear
ER oh
okay okay it's calm
I think thumbs down
[Music]
we have yet to fly with our Elite Shadow
I'm excited for that when we will fly
back to the portal
hopefully we will find it and hopefully
we will not die because I don't know
I've never flown with ah actually I have
I guess an uh Senpai let me use hers
before but I'm not wearing practice with
it I just hope I don't fall into the
void
uh let's see
oh diamonds Diamonds Are a Girl's Best
Friend
ah who the hell was that
is
I see you I don't see you
well
I don't even need an Italy and their
chest
no eh
[Music]
come on
don't fly in the end I've seen people
fly up flying the end
okay
I want that one
[Music]
okay
wow for the first time that I ever did
that
first time in my life
[Music]
that was friendly fire huh
okay uh this one is clear
don't get that
that one
thank you
oh which one do we go to next
uh I don't know it's kind of hard to
tell which one I went to before
um what do you guys think left or right
we're straight I love it
oh yeah
[Music]
oh no oh no
Mark the paths of clearance it's true
at all
probably been there before
[Music]
what what is it what do you want
it
oh it fell all the way to the ground
guys I almost I don't know if I'll go
get that one
oh let's clear this Tower so it doesn't
annoy me anymore this is the middle one
isn't it
kind of lost sense of direction
use one of like a true true true but
didn't one drop but there now it didn't
fall down as well I forgot already
but then I don't have to go
up again I don't want to go back up just
yet
it's okay I don't want I don't need
those
I don't need those let me try to make ah
but we can get that one that one is not
so far down
ah
[Music]
Hello friends
yes I was here before right because
otherwise this thing wouldn't be there
yeah yeah
okay okay I was here before
okay
[Music]
oh he did
okay
I'm
um I don't have many more yeah
[Music]
while I'm here pick those up
I don't know what to do I don't know
where to go let me go here let me go
here
water bucket I know but I don't want to
go all the way down just yet
was that here was that here I just want
to see hi hi
I'm gonna die
[Music]
oh my God
okay this is really dangerous right now
this is really dangerous right now I
need to get under something
to get under something
oh my God can you guys stop for once
where the hell am I no
[Music]
chill chill chill chill chill
y for trying
[Music]
was I not in here before
let's find out
[Music]
seems new methadone
oh no oh no
where are you
[Music]
thank you for the start guys thank you
oh wait I think this time it worked
okay let's just get into it let's just
wait let me can I eat one
[Music]
okay I'm going in
oh
[Music]
go
okay
[Music]
I don't know
this one didn't grab it special
oh this one dropped
let me go down let me go down
[Music]
I will never go down
going down there's no option we only go
up higher
only the sky is that limit
there we go thank you
one here and one above me
[Music]
you were trying to pose as a real soccer
box but you're the enemy you are the
enemy whoa where did you go
stop bullying me I think I cleared it
here now let me go let me go up there
thank you thank you thank you collected
it
okay
um it's it's still very noisy here but I
think we're done inside
[Music]
could you please
please that would be nice
okay make the same platform just because
[Music]
oh fire protection Unbreaking efficiency
I'm breaking we could put if you put
mending on this one that would be nice
hey
you know all those Armory things that I
don't need I'll put them into the
community chest I think
now we put
dad and wait does that make sense yes we
put that in there and then mine this one
right yeah uh
is this is this full is this full yet
let me see what's inside
oh we could make another choker box
put this in put this in
let me see the other choker box
should I make another one I'll need
another table
boxes wait is there a chocolate ah there
is a shocker box oh
box
I don't see any sugar blocks in Ashoka
blocks
of shells and yeah yeah shells I know I
know I know I know we have shells in
this show because sugar boxes
wait let me let me okay let me try to
organize this so let's let's say we put
um done uh armor and and weapons in one
and all the rest like building materials
and and bras and emeralds and gold in
the other how about that
okay so uh oops that one that goes here
that goes here that goes here
that is probably much better uh let's
put dads and dads in there as well on
this one and blacks on an iron that goes
here here here
I'll keep the black stone I'll put this
here it is here it is here and keep that
put that in look take that thing
that's again
and put in this
put in that
wonderful and now here we put armor
parts and
we're still probably gonna make another
one yes yes don't worry don't worry guys
don't worry
um this one and this one and this one
and this one and I guess this one can go
in this one and this one and this one
and this one
[Music]
and this one and this one
and
this one and we still don't use that I
told you guys I don't need it I don't
need such a thing
[Music]
you guys were like Kiana you need a you
need to you need a map and I didn't need
a map you guys were like yeah you need a
personal slow falling and I was like I
didn't need a slow potion following and
you guys were like yeah you need a night
vision potion I was like I don't need
that and I didn't need it
[Music]
don't worry
oh Pro Gamer girl you know
um take that
you know
okay now we make new chocolate box
I mean things could be a little bit
easier with those things but not
necessary sorry for doubting like a fan
yeah
don't say it don't say that
uh
oopsie
okay
what do I even put in there
um let's say
let's say
this stuff we put in here all right so
freaking nice
thank you
and let's just keep some build building
material in here I guess we won't
actually we don't really need much more
of the building material because we're
not gonna really go to look for another
Ender City today
I think
uh By the way when is my stream tomorrow
what am I streaming tomorrow
does someone know wait I think I only
have a members only stream tomorrow
right
sorry guys I still didn't tell you what
we're doing because I don't even know
what we're doing
members members oh I kind of I don't
know it's been a stressful week and next
week gonna be stressful too do you guys
mind if we watch a movie
is that okay you guys can choose the
movie
if you wanna are we streaming we're
always streaming spots
movie okay let's talk about what movie
We want to watch uh maybe during the
Super Chat reading
um portion of healing pushing the
feeling
okay well
so we have one chest with a few more
building materials
we have this
and I guess let's put the shulka shells
in there as well
[Music]
named oh I can name them how do I name
them
do
I need the Anvil can I just but I don't
need a name tag
I have a turn
of the animal
okay we can put that into items
[Music]
oh
that one well
[Music]
um
um uh what do I call it uh what was that
we put like at Wars
or is it and stuff
okay now this one is
that's what you meant thank you
this one is building material and more
shulker shells which I guess also comes
as building material
[Music]
it's mine very very good to organize
build building
okay
yeah I'm building stuff
and this one is all kinds of
uh I'm wearing stuff
I can dye them I know but I don't have a
I don't have dye currently wow this is
so cool
oh
[Music]
my God
okay and now we put those in honestly I
couldn't even leave them here I'm a bit
and we have enough space right now
let's put
yeah whatever let's put it all there
okay
we're continuing our search
full valuable stuff oh hello
[Music]
did you drop something no okay
can I come down please
this is me talking to you chickens when
you when you chickens find out you can
fly you constantly fly around and then
and then Kiara mama is like calm down
Oliver come down now enough playing I
want you to come get your dinner
normal playing around now calm down
it's not funny
do I have to come and get you now
you know I am already exhausted from a
long day of work I don't want to fly up
to go get you now
of it come down Oliver
we can fly yes we can't fly but don't
even don't around with me now
[Music]
what's up oh that's so annoying
okay I'm so sick and tired of this
above me
let me go down
okay
Escape
where do I go where do I go where do I
go where do I go where do I go next we
download that one
and uh we went we came from that one
I guess we can go down
I have an absolutely my kids my camera
it's kind of marked
[Music]
oh
okay
yeah
went there been there I probably have
been there too
way more yes time to go home now
oh no not yet
hi happy
[Music]
stupid slams come on
oh yeah
a lavender
it's kind of flat
what's here my friend
would you mind telling me what you're
protecting
nothing
back home why do you want to go home so
much
okay wait I'm gonna wait here I'm gonna
wait here until I am down on the ground
again I missed the top up you mean out
there
okay
[Music]
there's nothing up there
up there
[Music]
you wanna fight
oh yeah but this is dangerous dangerous
[Music]
calm the hell down now my friend
yeah let's go in here
yeah this is my hope
I made that hole
oh yeah yeah yeah already been here okay
marking marking my territory
oh yeah it was my
okay
now
have I been here quick check
oh yeah we might have not been here
I always try to get those at the
entrance but they're always like really
annoy the hell out of me after a while
then I just go inside but I got this one
yeah it's always the same thing but you
know what it's helpful it's helpful I
don't have to climb that much then
I oh this one is new okay okay okay okay
can I eat something first before we do
this again
[Music]
get down from the ceiling in an instant
or out we'll ground you for one month
your stupid little brat
it's giraffe oh did you die by your
friend hitting you I am not sorry
something is still hitting us
where is it
me and I
it's coming from above
you want that I want it
I want it
no
I refuse rejected
no okay
got it okay calm down you don't even see
me
[Music]
okay let's see what's inside
um
I'll take one in case we want to go back
home with us with a horsey
but I want that
oh wait uh
and their chest in here
and then take the under chest strike yes
yes yes
quick
[Music]
I'm going to kill you now
I am going to destroy you
[Music]
there we go that was easy
foreign
[Music]
make a safe ground here safe platform
wonderful
and then take this goddamn and the chest
you missed top of last Tower yeah which
one was the last
but there's also topped this tower now
which probably has a treasure
okay bye bye well well well well well
yeah
where the hell would you come from
nice Professional Building here I'm in
creative mode right now
foreign
hit me right now
no when I when I ask you for it you
won't do it okay
[Music]
I'm too stupid to go up a ladder
food
[Music]
spoke too soon
I'll just make my own kind of lettuce
make stairs this is what you call stairs
understand stupid ladder no one needs
you on it okay
[Music]
oh damn it I was asking
you're too late
you made me wait for too long and now
this happens God damn it
okay
[Music]
don't ever stop
Phoenix High School Musical
they had some great songs oh hello hello
hello hello you and me only us two
I like me I like this privacy that we
have is there anything up here no
I went to the top of the tower is there
no pressure
nothing okay
well
I mean they got some nice Flags
should I take the flags
foreign
[Music]
I am now no more sword and shield
fighter I am sniper
[Music]
oh no
so bad
so we went there I think there was
nothing but you guys are saying I
probably didn't go up here that's okay
but where else did I not go
I I went there I probably I definitely
probably went there
I probably went there I think we're
pretty much almost cleared it
[Music]
uh Clara got enough why I've only
streamed for three hours this is nothing
we found what we wanted the most that we
try yes yes but that doesn't mean I have
to cool it immediately
are you guys worrying because there's
like is this is this newcomers speaking
they're and they're like yo Kiana I'm so
worried about you know I don't want your
streams originally but you've been
streaming for three hours are you good
and all I can say to that is I am good
this is standard
but I mean of course we want to be safe
but everything's in the NHS so we're
safe
this is a short stream
but yeah I mean don't worry I'll I'll
end it sometime soon when we're done
with this stupid Talent okay we've been
here and we've been there and we've been
there so go down
go down
[Music]
down there
okay
that's a bit too late I need to learn
how to do that
did I go there
I think I did
who probably did but we can check to
make sure
let's make sure
[Music]
wait we might not have been here
oh letters not much going on in here
first up
[Music]
in here in here already cleared all
right uh cleared
cleared
let's go down
you guys think we did it all we should
do another two hour Spark Street
you wanna hear more spiders then open
your Spotify or whatever
oh this was smart nice open your Spotify
or whatever music service you're using
and then look for specs
that's how you listen to it for two
hours or open the music video
I guess we're going down
[Music]
okay that's a lot of water
waiting waiting there's bags this is
okay if I bought it on of course
wherever thank you for the support it
doesn't matter where you got it it
doesn't matter
thank you for listening to my music and
supporting me
[Music]
well
we got the only trunk
did I really check on everything I mean
I'm personally I am satisfied oh
do they not despawn after five minutes
oh my oh no
okay okay now I'm I'm used to you now so
you don't scare me anymore oh there that
was easy
oh
[Music]
oh hello Enderman
someone's still hitting me you should
build a statue for funny electronic wine
give me give me did I pick it up
yes now
but you know what I would like to have
some more of this beautiful purple stuff
but I guess I can just get these right
which one makes more sense to mine this
stuff
well I'm mining it
I'll just mind the whole thing
the flowers do they make more sense
I'll Take Everything home I still have a
lot of space in my shoulders
[Music]
the plants grow oh I can grow them
oh do I just have to put this one in the
ground
[Music]
thank you
I need the flower
[Music]
let me take some of those then
we'll put them into the shocker
by the way I wanted to tell you guys I
don't know if you guys are following my
Twitter but my mommy
my mommy was watching yesterday it was
uh and the dragon fight
that's that's pretty cute
because my mom is not the type like
she's not like I'm not saying she's old
but
he doesn't stay up long at night anymore
she's just not that young anymore
you know uh I think she usually goes to
bed before midnight
definitely
but our collapse started at midnight and
my mom is just she's really into
Minecraft
so I guess she just really wanted to
watch that she could have watched your
archive but she just wanted to watch it
live I guess
uh so that's pretty cute
and
and she wrote me a whole WhatsApp
message
uh this morning with her thoughts about
it
that's why I wanted to bring my phone
over but it's in the other room but I
wanted to tell you guys what she thought
about it I'll tell you in the Super Chat
reading but also
um a few days ago I think on Monday
this week yeah this week on Monday
wait wait did am I doing this wrong
you guys are saying flower
wait how do I get the flower
shoot the top block
ah
[Music]
okay so my mom
oh I'm pretty
oh it's so it's Sophia when I use that
as
a oh come on
oh cute decoration
okay so my mom my mom
on Monday I visited her actually
and she moved recently
and I visited her at her new place
the shop
because I don't need the stupid fruit
but with the fruit with the fruit I can
what was that
what was that with the fruit I can build
those blocks right
but only with the flower I can I can
grow them
okay
that was my own how did I did I hit
myself with no how is that possible
okay I was saying I was saying I visited
my mom
and um
and uh well
um we did we grilled we grilled for the
first time in a million years I
participated in grilling that was fun
and although we all didn't eat very much
oh my God are those are my animals
hitting me what the
at that time
and uh what would I say
uh yeah so we grilled and then yeah we
ate and my mom showed me her new place
where we proudly
um oh my God oh my God oh my God
and she showed me some some of the area
nearby
and yeah we had some ice cream
also then
she
went to her PC because she really wanted
to show me her Minecraft world she's
been playing Minecraft alone
and she built cool quite a lot
even though she's alone on her own serve
like it's not a server it's just so low
she she really wanted to show me and I
have to say I was quite impressed she
has quite the
like aesthetic
uh I
for building
I I I don't know if she like copied
something like she just built that out
of nowhere but yeah she it had a lot of
thoughts in it as well like she had her
own uh villager Merchant trading center
but like they had like each each one had
like their own little tiny dorm uh so it
was not it was not a free range trading
center like mine
it's still quite nice quite nice I must
say
I don't
and yeah it was just really pretty and
really big like it was huge she also
built like a boat docking area like a
ship ship boat stocking area and it was
pretty big too
um and yeah she built very uh uh various
houses for herself
uh
they were all pretty big and then she
also tried rebuilding her own house that
she currently lives in
she was really proud of it she was
giving me a tour and talking a lot about
this and that and oh she by the way of
course had full never right armor
my mom has full never ride armor and
super awesome Enchanted stuff
she's like really really Advanced
Minecraft plan she was like I already
did everything so I got bored and I got
bored so I built that house but you know
I already did everything
yeah that was funny
um so yeah my mom if you haven't heard
that story yet my mom is just a gamer
mom and that's yeah what I grew up with
and that's the reason why I started
playing games and all that very early on
um
and finally now I've seen her world
I thought that was lovely
quite impressive she she has a good
sense for building I kind of wanna
uh get her over to our server ASAP
so let's put some stuff into the
building shulker chest
it's put in this and that in this
and this is the beautiful chorus file
just put in all the fruits
and uh
um
this one this one
should I ask her to send me screenshots
of her home and uh and you guys can take
a look at it
you guys want to see
what hair Minecraft looks like we can do
a tour through screenshot although a
video would be better
I don't know if she knows how to take
like a video she's probably watching
this right now hi Mom
she's probably watching it and she was
probably laughing at me for uh the way I
handled this whole situation
so everyone says foreign
Anthony
[Music]
he's a Minecraft
professional
yeah
all right oh my God you guys we have to
try uh we have to take a photo
of the elytra first first align first
it's right what what did we say I mean
we called it hot wings but still I want
to try it
[Music]
but you guys are gonna be mad if I do it
in the end right but it's it's a big
area here I can just fly like a tiny bit
and then go to the ground right away I
don't wanna I'm not gonna fly over over
Islands okay can I just can
I just no
[Music]
you do it like that right all right
let's let's just take a photo oh my God
my pants
oh my armor
so pretty
it's sparkling
okay let's do let's let's take a nice
picture
I wanted to take I wanted to put this
one on
this doesn't look so cute
and now
we take it in front of
a bit more distance so we see this in
the background don't worry I won't fly
I'll just take the picture
[Music]
I don't know this is difficult
the head is the thing
can I somehow move the camera but not
move my body
I don't want my head to look straight at
the camera the whole time
okay can I do that somehow
[Music]
you head to this
ah it's not possible
[Music]
I would have to get someone else to take
a picture of me
well
okay hmm I want to take a nice picture
well okay let's go a little bit more
over here
[Music]
good
night
[Music]
the elytra no normally doesn't look like
this is it's like mixing with my um
OptiFine
uh
Cape like normally uh it looks
my Cape looks like this
that which is so funny because that kind
of looks like a phoenix although like I
didn't do anything this is this just
comes normally with my OptiFine mod or
my shaders I guess but then you put the
hot wings on top
and it looks like that that's oh my God
that's dope because normally
they're really dark right they only
turns are pretty dark
I mean they're still kind of shiny but
pretty dark
yeah
okay
[Music]
it's so weird because the horns or the
nose horns or whatever those are keep
covering up the eyes from the from the
dragon thingy
[Music]
ah change the oh
ah
oh I mean that's
not looking don't look at me when I'm in
this uh angle
when would they consider me looking at
them I wonder
[Music]
okay whatever
we probably got one picture
yourself yeah
[Music]
so I can only fly with fireworks right
but what if I for example fall down from
Aura fall down from a high place
uh will that like for or if if those
projectiles hit me like can I fly with
that
a no dragon head picture yeah I'll take
those
oh wait I don't have to shoot
follow me stop following me
[Music]
I don't need a fireworks wait am I
gliding now no
[Music]
okay okay okay let's take a picture
without the head
oh wait if I have a dragon head on does
it today sorry do they also not consider
me looking at them
I wonder if it looks like a like a like
a pumpkin head
double tap space to fly oh
oh helpful thank you
but it has ah normally without The
Mending it has quite the low durability
and goes off quite quickly that's why
you need to mending on it
okay uh one more photo oh
here
foreign
[Music]
I'm like fully embarrassed in
photography mode right now
all right all right all right
I like to have my fov pretty high
normally
sorry guys if that's triggering you
let's go home I guess I mean I kind of
feel like
um
[Music]
kind of want to go further but
you know the explore the mood
the thing for I just really want to
explore it but but but but I'll go home
I'll go home but I just wonder if I go
if I keep on going
in Shin where I was going to will there
be more interesting
or not
anyway yes I put my stuff in a yeah yeah
calm down come
down calm down guys I was just jumping
around for fun
you guys Panic too much
much panicking
foreign
[Music]
Let's see we are going home
all right that was mine and the city
it's looted
[Music]
no more no more dragon head
I'm really glad we found it so early on
we were really lucky I think I came from
that direction pretty sure about that or
or the exact opposite
let's see is there any
uh yep that's my bridge okay we really
didn't go that far so
[Music]
yeah it's easy to go back from here
all right we just have to be careful not
to fall down should I should I do the
whole
I wanna I wanna Crouch the whole way but
it might be really slow
I just don't want to fall down now wait
I can fall into the void
foreign
we're really close I don't really
we could put everything into the chest
and then jump into the void
oh yeah I don't really care about the
EXP
o okay
I'm so scared no Crouch
yeah I'll use I'll lose one chance
I have a million I have one more bag at
home and yeah a lot of them in here did
we really
how many are there
I feel like yeah we might have really
seen everything in there
why are people so planning because I
don't know they're they're chickens what
do you expect from chickens
are you a goodie
oh boy I could just I could just jump
I mean that would be enough wouldn't
that be another achievement
um dying from jumping into the void I
don't have that achievement yet
I don't want to try
you could do a flip
you don't know how right well I know the
leech was rare but it's in the it's in
the freaking uh
standard chest
I won't I won't even be losing anything
except for one Ender Chest but I have
like 10 other ended chest
do a flip
yeah I have one more in the chest at
home
so if I open the one at home then I have
uh yeah all the chests but okay we're
already halfway through I feel like I
only built like two Bridges didn't I two
or three
oh one one Bridge
one Bridge next Bridge next virtual as
well
[Music]
do it should I do it um
the portal is pretty close all right
guys yeah we already started vlogging we
wouldn't have minded just jumping into
the void
hmm
use the map oh yeah maybe now we can see
already uh
[Music]
where's my where's my next Bridge
is it over there
don't call
I'm off the map I know I know I know I
know
here
is this who I need to go
[Music]
it was quite The Big Field
yeah this seems familiar
[Music]
I came down like right I have been only
pretty much walking straight
die double
[Music]
I'm surprised I still have so many Endo
pearls and stuff I didn't use the potion
I was kind of like scared to use the end
of pearls I was scared to use anything
at all like I'm not really scared but
like I don't know hesitant
that's the that's the first tower that
we checked out where we did have a
little warm-up session
[Music]
that was uh totally calculated we needed
something to warm up
otherwise it would have been too easy
you absolutely nailed it I'm on the road
guys I'm on the roll
on the Minecraft world
makes sense since you're a day off as
you play oh my God for real though when
I play like for example today's laugh
games I tend to not use my healing items
because I'm like what if I run out of
them so yeah I I rarely ever use those
apple gloomies and Peach gummies and all
that stuff
[Music]
and then but in the beginning they're
really kind of like lacking like you
don't intense off games in the beginning
you really like money
a lot of the times in the beginning
there is a bridge
oh yeah I'm moving on the map now okay
Evie
yeah so I think in tails off games you
really gotta be careful with with money
and items in the beginning
maybe I should give I don't know if I'm
is planning on going to the end soon but
I want to give Amel
ender chest or shoulder blocks what you
think is more useful for her
definitely can make use of a shulker box
oh yeah
I think she would love that
[Music]
both
what's it those Endermans up there
I want to give her a chocolate box
I'm in Santa Claus mood again remember
last time when I was giving everyone
presents
hey
I feel like giving presents again
[Music]
Santa Clara is back
soon of course but I'll be coming back
anyway I'll be coming back I wanna I
wanna uh
check out some more understudies and one
thing that I was really looking forward
to was exploring the Overworld with the
with the elytra I was really looking
forward to that
because now traveling
will be so much
so much it will be such a game changer
so next Minecraft stream will probably
be
something like that
me just going on another adventure I
prefer going on adventures rather than
building stuff in Minecraft anyway
don't forget I'm breaking free oh yeah
uh
I hope I can get that
mmm
[Music]
don't tell Iris what why
oh because she doesn't like Santa oh
yeah what the hell was that
who's what
all right didn't you say that in her
debut stream
[Music]
what did make I didn't make a bunch of
foreign this one is my bridge right
find some creepy well there's uh there's
there's sexy Santas
they're sexy Santas too
sexy Stannis
[Music]
sexy Santa
when I give you presents I'm sexy Santa
[Music]
isn't scary what the hell
what do you mean
breaking into houses is creepy oh well
maybe maybe she would like um
you know in in my country we don't
really have Santa
although I mean we all know about Santa
and often we refer to Santa but we also
we have the crystal because
yeah
uh when I grew up they told me about the
Christians and not about the Santa
and Christian is supposed to be an angel
angel girl
that comes on the Christmas night
evening evening we open presents in the
evening of the 24th
the campus is uh Nicholas and Campos is
a few weeks earlier that's not on
Christmas
that's another different holiday
yeah it's basically like an angel child
girl that comes down to bring you
presents
or fulfills your wishes I don't know
I remember that like when I was younger
my mom for Christmas
um like in the uh in the early evening
she would tell us
to go outside in the park and play in
the snow
because back then we still had snow
for Christmas now that's not a thing
anymore unfortunately why is there no
more snow
uh but yeah we would make like snow
angels and uh
we would make snow angels
I'm so scared to look at someone right
now
we would make snow angels in the in the
snow
and look at the beautiful evenings night
sky
and then we would go really excitedly we
would go back home and uh open up our
presents usually just the tree would
already be lit up
with
um like bringing candles and my cat from
back then I had one cat back then solo
cat she would like play Under we arrived
by the way Hallelujah she would play
Under the
on the Christmas tree and almost take it
apart
remember back in the day when I started
off Minecraft and I kept on dying and
losing my but that hasn't happened
for a while
like like going on an adventure and then
losing my I usually make it home
safely these days
you're down
[Music]
okay so did I leave something here
should I put the
[Music]
this the chest and the wait a second
I could
should I leave my tiny
a map and so someone else can make it
bigger and go on with that one
should I do that or is it Anyway
[Music]
where did I put it my map is broken what
do you mean
when did I put it
I don't remember which one it is
yeah there's paper to make it bigger but
I don't need it to be bigger right now
anyway
no I mean the new map that I made not
the not the I opened it up so close to
31. oh
oh I'll leave it there anyway and well
if anyone wants to
[Music]
use that I guess I don't know if you can
even use it now if I open it up too
close
is it in here no
okay that pushed me away
[Music]
there it is
wait it's 42 though if it were the same
wouldn't it be 41 I Don't Know
foreign
let's try to make it bigger I guess oh
let's see what happens
[Music]
this is the tiny mount
why nothing
why is it because it's too small
it's tackled again a new map huh again
I don't understand much
keep it keep on really because I'm not
that real
on the right
[Music]
it is a new one I have to fill it okay
how much bigger can it get no more okay
[Music]
uh well then if anyone wants to go into
the direction where I went tell them to
use this map if they wanna
and the first and they're saying that
they will find is already taken care of
bye
really
rename it
with my Anvil or what
uh
[Music]
that's possible
Kiana map nah but then they might think
they can't use it oh
uh Kiana used this
I don't know
he he ran the town
East End ah because we went East
end map Maybe
maybe broken oh we can make such a long
one maybe
[Music]
yeah that's the name
please please test it out guys I don't
know if it works
[Music]
use this one please
and see if it works I don't know I can't
tell right now uh okay and then we put
in this and this and this and we go back
home
chipped Anvil
oh I didn't I didn't even use all of my
belly material so
and then once we're outside we're gonna
fly back with the hot wings
[Music]
leave one in the chest ah for the others
ah for me if I come back
oh
[Music]
take one when I have one at home I have
one at home though
makes it easier true
I have one at home but I would just have
to take my uh
[Music]
should I
um
I know I know I know they will just see
an empty one I don't know
[Music]
I always carry one okay
all right then let's go oh where is it
here
oh
I guess I'll build some stairs
do I have to do the trapdoor thing again
damn it
well then I do need a chapter for going
on
well I still have one
somewhere in a chest
probably in building material
I mean I could just jump into the void
using in the pearl
yeah but it's like easy
knowing the other says wow yeah it's
really not it's really not in here huh
foreign
[Music]
all right all right
okay
[Music]
how do we build this
I will do I
all right
[Music]
I'm gonna try to figure this out
oh
[Music]
I hate building stairs upwards and
downwards
away from the void
[Music]
oh
yeah now we can make beacons
like going faster because that's a brand
or how does that work
I actually don't understand how that
works
you need to Kill ah no we need to kill
him
that was something else
I mixed something up there now the hotel
okay let's let's surround this a little
bit
[Music]
just you know to make it prettier
um a tiny little tiny little bit safer
oh sure okay
that's fine blah blah blah
okay
now we did it
like that and close it and I'll go in
wait does it still work when
am I flying nope not flying just
crouching okay it has to be a full block
underneath
that's it
what I have
found out we have one more black so
let's use that then
[Music]
oh that would have to be here
wow scary
okay
we Captain the pills I only used what
one ender pearl
why did I get so many
didn't need them at all
yes and we go back home for this mess
what the hell is this such a mess what
[Music]
yay
I've seen
what a relief
okay and now we get out this and we get
out of this
[Music]
and then we fly
freedom
Freedom safely
oh it's raining
oh come on
yeah
that's not nice for my first flight can
it go into the water no
I'm very confident in my shooting skills
now I feel oh
like normally I would have never really
used
the
the bow that much of my own
all right
go how do we do this
oh
how do I do it
wait how does
I'm gonna put another hint
oh
[Music]
sorry the cape made me think I already
had the clip though OptiFine cape
blah blah blah
be calm become
[Applause]
easy
another one
no
did they drop yes I got one
morning
they didn't drop to the ground today
the second one there was no second one I
suppose all right let's go sleep once
okay okay
[Music]
well I took so many pictures
okay it's time
I wanted better weather to fly anyway
our first flight has to be beautiful
first off
[Music]
it's better
by the way no shaders today but I'll
turn them on again next time uh okay
okay so how
I don't understand jump twice look up to
use
foreign
[Music]
hi
everybody have I been here before
[Music]
this makes it so much easier
okay
[Music]
hello
don't worry don't don't mind me just the
Phoenix casually flying through your
village to check out what's going on
here do you have some Treasures
you have something interesting
is this new this place
Emma has been here uh okay then probably
nothing no Treasures
temples and pulls it up from now
onion mama
oh wait
no thank you but I'll jump off from here
that's okay guys uh where we came from
where are we going
[Music]
uh wait
all right screenshot
wow
those are just taking cute screenshots
right now
[Music]
okay where are we going
oh is this where I came from
am I going that way
I think y'all should be that way
hold it
up
Sky Temple
no wait that's where I started off okay
follow the path
[Music]
uh
uh ah this way
going so fast I gotta get used to this
it has been a long time since since I uh
yeah use my wings you know it's been a
while so it's actually putting in
trouble
tonight
oh well of course this is not the first
time I'm flying in my life no no no no
no no
this is okay we're gonna go home do we
have to go home we already home
where
fly like a butterfly I know that they
were built he kind of scares me
[Music]
oh
has someone been here before
probably yellow
that's probably
yeah that there must have been something
here before right
use um yeah I want Unbreaking I guess
okay okay explore Another Time explore
another time
I know I know it's hard to hold back but
now I kind of lost track of where it
came from
ah
from here
mending and Unbreaking oh
Thomas
where do I go other way
[Music]
yummy
uh check coordinates
um do you guys know
you guys know the whole 300 minus 400.
oh
okay
[Music]
this
is getting closer
yeah yeah this is the right way
it's okay it's okay don't worry don't
worry
does it only go down when I use the
firework or even when I'm gliding
[Music]
must be somewhere here
no wait ah wait minus 400 but plus 300
oh hello Village
oops hard left okay okay let me check
this out because I don't think anyone
has ever been here before
[Music]
oh
good I was here before really
a donkey
where's Shrek egg trick hello
somebody once told me
you look you look like Shrek
you got a blacksmith oh
oh it's what a nice house
[Music]
looks kind of untouched
I feel so untouched right now near you
so much somehow
untouched
[Music]
untouched I got emeralds
a bell hmm
I need to sing that again at some
oh it's um foreign
because that one time I sang it was
really fun but I sang it at the very
beginning so I think some people missed
it
[Music]
okay
I think that's pretty much about it here
huh oh
I'm fine thank you I'll take that and
the bread thank you I'm leaving
I'm leaving
nice nice place though
nice untouched area so now we go to um
free Plus 300.
maybe we walk a little bit
just walk a little bit
uh 300 300 300
um wait
um this is not
this is not it this is this way okay
[Music]
let's let's just walk a little bit
foreign
[Music]
good we have a mostly flat area that's
nice we're taking a little bit of a walk
in the parking I feel a little bit dizzy
after flying so much
I can't kill everything nearby to fix it
later
there's not really anything nearby
[Music]
this way this way
foreign
[Music]
that works right so
yeah
stop moving
how are you not dead yet so did that do
something a little bit yeah actually
quite a bit
[Music]
um
maybe that was my imagination
[Music]
sorry about that sorry oh no I don't
want to kill them mama no no no
not gonna kill the mama in front of his
children and it's Daddy
no no no
I am not that cold-hearted
contrary to your belief everyone
[Music]
don't worry I'm careful I'm I'm a
careful
[Music]
you have no idea how much I love you yes
okay uh still like 600 blocks
[Music]
so I just ride this bike oh God it's
turning night
yeah
I just wanna go home
we could even use the end of pearls to
move
but it's okay we have time guys
[Music]
I'mma made a Pap yeah but I've
unfortunately left that path
[Music]
where's my shield
um it's not going up much
[Music]
but I'll fly a tiny bit okay A tiny bit
well we're pretty close already
uh 300 plus and 400 minus right okay
[Music]
oh
I can't be
happy
or maybe not will be hard to get down
land on my house wait wait wait Smooth
Move yeah
ouch
[Music]
[Applause]
uh we have landed safely Phoenix has
landed
[Music]
keep
I got the first Elite trap
okay it's time
uh
what the hell I thought you were some
kind of weird ghost
sleep once
I think I'm
gonna opened it privately the elytra
off stream
no no Ina got a horse
which is fine till she'll get it
eventually she was really not treated
well by the Ender cities
that was not fair
but
if we go down down down down down down
you will see I have an interest here too
I didn't even need to bring mine like
this
um
I can see them eventually going there on
their own
probably pretty soon so I don't really
think they need mine as a present
what do you think
[Music]
I don't know man
I feel like they don't need it
did you get Unbreaking it no we can try
to see it but with level 16 I might not
get that much
yeah they're probably fine
I already have so much diamond armor and
stuff put it in the dragon fight
they don't get it they'll get a ton
of Ender chest once they go into the end
anyway
um
and Calia when she wants to go to the
end she'll she'll uh
she'll tell me I will help her out there
but we can put some of this stuff into
the community chest
and people can take stuff if they want
to
and yeah I guess that's what I'll do
[Music]
if in a rocket why
she doesn't have an elitra
I also I need rockets for myself
I think she probably has more than
enough paper and gunpowder on her own
she can probably make a ton of
uh rockets on your own I don't think she
really needs mine
let's be real she has the most materials
and stuff from all of this
[Music]
she doesn't need my donations
you know what I'll put one in the chest
uh
uh here for everyone to use
uh Okay so
I'll take
my sugar boxes
and then put some stuff into the
community chest what do we have here aha
yes yes
all the iron yes all the iron can go
mmm
armor what's this all for me
[Applause]
feel free to take this stuff
[Music]
more donations from takanasi Kiana
well infinity and Unbreaking free is
actually a pretty good helmet and this
one is mending even
nice
hmm
[Music]
wanna keep those
I'm gonna put those in
uh I don't know what I'm gonna keep this
one
I'm breaking free mending
[Music]
this is sticky call me Gonna Keep that
mending on breaking efficiency keeping
that one
um efficiency on breaking mending
I'll keep that I'll put that in
and put that in oh wait no I'll put that
in I'll put that in
keep the curse of binding for pranks
but what exactly does that do
they can't can they never take it out of
their uh handle
it's gonna affect every item in that
person
[Music]
you cannot it's unequip unless they die
ah
I see
iron Shuffle
this is pretty this is a damn good iron
shovel
[Music]
this gives you five mending
well I have a
actually wait it's one better than this
one
is the iron still an iron okay
[Music]
uh I'll keep those boots for now I'll
keep that so all of this I want to put
I know by the falling
oh no wait am I wearing in front of yes
I am okay then they can have these ones
[Music]
okay
hmm
do we have a toolbox
building materials
[Music]
um
not not really
oh
I put it
it says food for the upper one but
that's not food
if we put a lower one
put in the weapons but there's not much
all right all right and Fortune
but not not stream hard challenge this
one curse of Vanishing diamond shovel
mending that's nice
[Music]
oh here we're gonna put in this
efficiency
pickaxe to soup no way that's mine
that's mine right I was I was using that
one
this one curse of Vanishing Unbreaking
free efficiency free
this one Cruise Adventures silk touch
efficiency for
uh-huh wonderful
Santa Claus is here jingle bells jingle
bells jingle all the way oh
damn nice shovel
[Music]
okay uh now
uh keep all of that
[Music]
hold on
this one you guys want me to throw away
should I really
did I really
yes yes I have the electron
no yes
[Music]
smelled it
I'll I'll keep it
I'll put it in here for now now think
about what to do with it
here I can have some
Billy material should I put in the
bottom
I'll put those in here
feel free to use it for your
understanding
you Adventures
these ones I keep
but you know what I'll give
ah wait
you're sure
I'll make that I'll make a chest
one and two
and
[Music]
push up
McDonald's
[Music]
present
s
[Music]
my beloved
what are you guys doing are you mine
have you traveled so far because I
Unleashed you you I unleash your full
power
attack
[Music]
ones here
oh I cannot understand them on the
grindstone oh leash
what the hell look I guess the merchant
died
[Music]
come with me I'm starting a new family
ah yeah yeah follow me
I already lost so many friends
not gonna lose you
not this time how about I could keep
them under my house
[Music]
are you connected there okay
nah so you can do that herself
[Music]
I gave her a chance she can die whatever
color she wants she can decide it
doesn't necessarily have to be blue who
knows maybe she doesn't like blue
surprise maybe she never likes blue I'm
wearing my sugar boxes uh wait wait
do I have a offense five
[Music]
how do I make a elephant skin
this concept
I give you presents fun spots
don't get used to it
[Music]
oh
okay oh wait that's enough
[Music]
let me put that stuff in here
for now
um
mm-hmm
[Music]
so I mean this place is maybe not the
nicest I'll make it nicer I will like
I'll replace the stone with dirt and
stuff and make it grow grass and
how about that
you guys just have to come in here once
and you'll like it I promise you oh
should we yeah for now make it
relatively small
[Music]
don't worry I'll take care of you
I won't I won't lose you no more
[Music]
not tall enough really
you think so
is it not gonna be tall enough
and they will see the sun of course
they're outside
of course they'll see it
[Music]
yeah there's a ceiling
but there's still they will see the sun
when it's like at this at this level
hahaha
okay how do we
how do I take that
[Music]
okay follow me
okay come on come on come on babies yeah
yeah that's right come on in here
um okay
wonderful and now oh so I actually kind
of needed oh you know what
and you like that and then I can take
the leash back right
[Music]
you can keep the least one now
big success
put the look back
and
I'll put the fireworks uh here
uh get my sugar boxes
yes I got my Elisha I got it really
early on today
if you missed that moment you're welcome
to watch the archive if you wanna see
the moment where I found it
it was quite exciting and very uh scary
on the way to the inner city but
you didn't have to go to fire
[Music]
we will read some Read Super chats after
this by the way
and uh wait I want to see how we dye it
though we have some dye here I have
yellow dye orange dye red dye
let's try does it work like how does it
work how does it work
[Music]
how do I how do I entitle them everyone
help
[Music]
crafting table just add the Donut oh
oh
I'm orange stealth is now yellow oh
origin stuff is no
orange oh
wonders
[Music]
wow that's really easy
where do we put them
[Music]
ah cute
oh oh I can't open that one God damn it
because it's like because of the carpet
huh
all right that's kind of annoying
oh well I'll get around the carpet I can
play
a wall block there
I don't even have white Wool with me
right now
oh that's better that's better that
works right
[Music]
anyways
we have to Target the wall
it's facing up oh
really
after aiming at the wall
[Music]
could have killed myself just now
wait what what other way there's no
block
s okay
[Music]
okay okay
would that have worked with a carpet
no okay
battle holder thank you for your help
I appreciate it
this is cute could have put it into my
new house but no as always I put
everything
everywhere but into the new house
put that Hill put that there a little
bit of cleaning up
so you can put that in here although I
don't know if I'll ever use it outside
of the under City
put some food back in here I didn't even
use up my food
nice
some more of that solo pumpkin pie yummy
saddle
more Saddles we have so many Saddles now
all right I think I think that's pretty
much it I'm really excited to have
gotten the elytra that I've been hoping
to get for such a long time
and really successful lots of treasures
yay here tomorrow we'll have a members
only stream but we will
read the projects now so the stream is
not over just yet
um
so if you want to stay welcome stay I'll
take a like free three minutes break
until we read the super chats Tool uh
called my voice in a tiny little bit I
hope you guys had fun today I had fun it
was very very exciting an exciting
Adventure but there's many many more
Adventures ahead of us now especially
now with Billy trunk next Minecraft
stream will be a
finding new places
I wanna see some some some some temples
and stuff some sand desert temples
and oh fly over the over the ocean and
see what islands we haven't seen yet we
still have barely seen anything from
this seed so
oh silent voice and your name is oh good
idea yeah we talked about that before
that's a good idea we could watch that
for with the members the double feature
that's what you guys meant with double
feature I remember now
[Music]
Avatar is something I would want to
watch with Ina
okay
then I'll see you in a few minutes guys
thank you thank you thank you thank you
for today
[Music]
see you in two minutes thanks for the
memberships thank you
[Music]
foreign
oopsie
I'm back thank you for waiting
no that was denied and approved so
it cancels itself out
[Music]
well that went well
I think one of the reasons why it went
so well is because I was well prepared
for going into the inner city
the end City no Museum yeah what should
we listen to
um
I guess we'll just listen to Lo-Fi whole
life music
oh wait no I had a different loofah
music previously right I I got some um
[Music]
was it that
was no that was something else
what's that
oh
that must be it
oh yeah
oh there we go got some of our own Lo-Fi
going
okay
we will be reading super chats
and I got my phone although it's on five
percent
I brought my phone over trying to charge
it right now
uh but it's not really going up at all
I'm charging it for my PC but it doesn't
really work it out
but I just checked my phone and I
completely missed it because I didn't
check my phone for hours and I was
playing Tales of horizon before but my
mom actually
wrote me a whole paragraph about advice
on how to uh go around getting the at
least my wings in the end City she wrote
me a whole paragraph about that as well
[Music]
I was able to do it just fine
I need to drink more water I want some
chocolate but I need to buy more snacks
I don't have any more snacks I'm running
out of snacks at home isn't that
unbelievable I can't believe it even
chocolate what the hell is
I know
[Music]
Indo City
foreign
before
Minecraft before that oh and the dragon
didn't read that one and also didn't
read the takotori drawing collab Eva but
before that
I read it I think
so we start from the hoodle doodle I
think
hey friends please I did read I think
okay okay okay
you know it was so sweet to draw you
know a little bit of a
um
illustration for us for the thumbnail uh
for the hoodoo
this one so cute I love it
and I made the thumbnail but she made
the drawing it's so cute foreign
[Music]
adorable
she's so talented
ah and I'm glad I was able to do that
one with someone else
and
because
if I would have done that all alone I
know it might have been a bit a bit
boring
although I'm almost
always ready to entertain but of course
more fun with Ina together
um
[Music]
I know
foreign
ended up uh be they were exclusive
uh they they uploaded them on their own
Twitter and so on afterwards but at the
moment when I showed them those were
exclusive
once again they've sent me footage that
has never been shown before anywhere
um
pretty cool
yeah all right some of the in the
beginning
in the beginning and in the end
there is some super chats mixed in that
are from the Minecraft stream
uh should I copy those and put them in
the yes let's do it
let's do it let's put them
into that uh wait a second into the into
the
my brain isn't working anymore what it
would happen
into the Excel file thingy whatever
one second let me try to find
ah
realize that uhu is green hoodle green
green
[Music]
is not green
get a spreadsheet yep yep oh
file
[Music]
okay
Immortal screen is rising I've heard of
that a while ago and especially because
it has the word phoenix in its name even
though it's written with f I've always
been a little bit curious about it
oh man sorry should we should we just
decide now
um
what to watch tomorrow because and I
know there is some of you waiting for
that I guess let's uh like what time do
we start
is there enough time for a double
feature
[Music]
don't don't we start at like 10 p.m my
time
or earlier Terminator
I've seen that one before I mean
foreign
well I mean they're both not that long
so if you watch if we watch both of them
I guess it wouldn't take much longer
than three hours
[Music]
hey should we watch both or just one
what do you guys think do you guys have
time to watch two of them is
just one book please
uh it's the weekend I'll be there
we have time summer break
[Music]
for the safe service I don't know man I
have no idea I didn't look it up yet
Paul oh yeah Paul okay
and should we watch both movies sorry
sorry non-members this is unrelated to
you guys
or it's just one
both
just one
[Music]
okay
foreign
well both you guys just want to spend
more time you just want longer hours
you just what movies uh your name
and uh silent voice both anime movies
they are not that long like one of them
is like one and a half hours
I think the other one also something
around that
one more time
uh it seems like people want both okay
sorry for the people who just want one
you can I guess just jump out after the
first one
hold up
challenge voice makes you cry that's
okay
that's okay
your name seems cool never seen before
really I thought I was the only one who
hasn't seen that one before that one was
so famous
even overseas
[Music]
okay
whatever you have a decision
thank you guys for participating
[Music]
tomorrow we watch two movies
sound voice and your name is I think
let's watch your name your name first
and then silent voice second yeah
foreign
[Music]
is any of those on Netflix
otherwise I'll just get them on Amazon
foreign
[Music]
I actually was able to clean my
apartment a little bit today and I think
yesterday although I don't know it's
been so blurry I don't know if yesterday
and today is the same day
from what I've been doing or or I might
have just been I'm not sure anymore
[Music]
I know yesterday yesterday and today
yeah both yesterday and today have been
cleaning up my apartment a little bit
your voice is on Netflix I I feel like
I've seen it yeah like the existing on
on there time is an illusion for real
has it been a long a good thing uh today
yeah yeah
I feel excited I got it uh to to play a
Tesla variety that was that was awesome
yeah
[Music]
in your voice
what
what what did I say
ah your name and sounds
yeah whatever
it's too similar
can't wait for a Skyward Sword yeah
that's uh exciting too
looking forward to playing that finally
a Zelda game on my channel finally
of her eyes looks beautiful it really is
um
the scenery was absolutely beautiful
thank you oh my god thank you guys for
the memberships you guys want to watch
the movie so what
welcome welcome
I hope the story looks great I'm sure
it's gonna be amazing
[Music]
from what I from what we already know
it seems to be a great story and the
characters already are amazing oh my God
kisara is so hot
[Music]
no been here since your debut
now finally able to afford membership oh
welcome
you're so glad thank you welcome please
enjoy the members only content
tell us more about how hot she is
oh man she has the prettiest face the
way her hair flows over her face also so
elegant ah she got a nice butt and you
know what I really appreciate though is
that she's in a full armor like legit
full armor
normally in video games women
who are supposed to be an armor are not
really an armor which is fine to me too
honestly I like that too like from an
aesthetic point of view and design
character design point of view that's
fine too but seeing a character in like
legit full armor and that huge Shield
uh I really appreciate that I think
that's dope her backside yeah her back
side isn't fully covered up but
they need to show me you know her assets
that's important that's that's good they
understand and what's important
no but I think it's really cool to have
some uh lizard armor there
really no I'm serious about that
acids
that one was on purpose
oh my God next week is already the end
of July
oh my God
August will be starting
more
[Music]
thank you guys for the memberships thank
you
[Music]
why was July so fast I don't want it to
be so fast
by the way next week I kind of want to
try the gothic Arctic phone the game
at some point sometime next week also I
might be doing a few more streams next
week at an earlier time
um so maybe not so good for any time
zones
they'll probably be like really early in
the morning for you all
not all of them some of them
but yeah I wanna because because uh like
from what I see Ina will be streaming
every day uh in the evening so I kind of
don't want to overlap with her that much
but so then I decided to just
stream a bit more in the earlier hours
next week
although it's impossible to not
um overlap at some point but
fine for us yeah I know I know like this
week it was kind of
bad for sea time zones
so next week will be a bit better I hope
so I mean it can never be like perfect
um but I'm trying
okay I'm gonna start a few streams a bit
earlier than today
yeah yeah
it's lighter than so
um
kind of song
yeah someone's always working
well a lot of you guys watch my streams
during their work hours though so that
works fine oh yeah oh my God I just
realized tomorrow oh
very busy tomorrow
okay let's get the Super Chat reading
started because I need to do stuff
afterwards
uh okay
[Music]
I felt like talking a little bit I need
to do something off stream tomorrow
something important very important I'm
nervous
okay Patrick
has been standing
uh Peterson thank you for the Minecraft
Super Chat thank you soon
[Music]
also for the Minecraft Super Chat and
the afterwards after this one there
should be mostly Hulu super chats Nate
zero five six zero Duncan Trevor t thank
you for the red super chat Duncan
oh you changed your name to schnoohoo
which must be a joke uh a combination of
Schneider and uhu because of snow and oh
that is so cute I feel like that might
be actually a a word that they use in
German to describe maybe a crossover of
a snow owl and the woohoo that probably
is actually something to use it's so
cute it's new
is
a is a a German name for
a specific owl race
[Music]
cute
so thank you it says so I love okay fear
owls today huh I hope everybody
is jihood what was being partially
colorblind for the art stream oh
I could
be hoopier and
about this
you look paintering uh and I'm Talon
yeah
tell me y'all
I'm so cool by Randy food also fun oh my
God
now to duck owls of work how who could I
miss this on
[Music]
were you drunk with riding this one
oh
thank you
[Music]
thank you I I underst I understood 80 of
that
[Music]
that street must have been great for you
so many owls so much owl content that
baby owl who
it's so cute though isn't it it's so
adorable oh my God
[Music]
hey so small baby small baby
shut up
that just sounds like something else and
I don't know why it sounds nice it
sounds wrong gravity
it doesn't sound right
bless you super chance
what you guys roasted me on switch swiss
cheese dad I was I was you guys have no
idea I don't know why I was so roasted
about the Swiss cheese swiss cheese it's
not like
you guys need to Google you know you
guys need to Google
yeah I was right about the trees thank
you
oh the whole chat was like oh you're so
stupid
ah I was right
some of you guys have changed your mind
interesting all right all right try
everything again
you should work in Hooters
uh thank you for the pinky
thank you thanks for converting me into
an outfit today
oh I go on to say is how oh dear
who who incredible and inspiration
no I like that one
Eli and Dove there are hard times is
that supposed to mean dough
I'll love you for you is
equal
for your love for to your love for us
you're the coolest most
incredibly
talented girl I've ever met this is so
stupid
and all I want is more exciting exciting
adventures with you smile for years you
kind of gave up there and then couldn't
figure out anything new huh
P.S please
foreign
[Music]
the legal eagle yeah even you became an
owl for the day
kitten
[Music]
what why did you change your name like
that why are you a fairy now
why are you a furry now
could have turned into you know an owl
kitten
wait what
the hell I'm not yeah you are what the
hell
thank you soon
Alexian
uh wait I need my translator
[Music]
no no no no
thank you
where was I
said residence
is not the drugs Extinction residences
in darkness 2101
is probably talking about the North
American Swiss cheese which is kind of
like in the metallic but not actually
any of the any not actually any of the
over 450 kinds of real twisties exactly
like basically like when
um the cheese that you guys call Swiss
cheese
we probably in most cases we probably
that would probably be an emmentala in
our country in our language we call it
emmentalo
yeah so that's why you know and there's
more cheeses with holes inside that's
why that always like for me like oops
what swiss cheese equals that one cheese
with the whole inside and there's more
than that and there's more Swiss cheeses
that come from Switzerland so that's why
I was like what do you mean
but not only towards Ina more like
towards the chat yeah
thank you Chief education and now I'm
not even that much of a cheese eater but
um you know Switzerland is neighboring
country we have a lot of
cheese culture
in Europe and in Australia and
Switzerland in that area
there's a ton of cheeses here
probably way more than over there in
America I would say
cheese education she's she's ducation
cheese cross-pollination
[Music]
yeah so anyway
um one of the cats two names
uh uh chunkies and smoothie down the
orange Dorito cat is chunkers and the
um radioactive green cat is movie
oh
TD bankerson
Magnus boy sent action
ordinary donation Elvis thank you for
the pinky yeah what Kiana also doesn't
know the difference between
the water and the Avatar and the blue
Avatar don't I mean I know I mean I know
[Music]
different kinds of average but I was
just why was that so funny just because
the first one I think of is the most
famous One the blue Avatar movie The CG
movie huh
so what so what did I didn't think of
The Last Airbender first
[Music]
that one like like I see pictures of
that before and
I understand why you guys made such a
big deal out of that
[Music]
she said a lot of vendors whatever
as controversial to say
foreign
it's the way I said it I I rewatched a
clip of that and I don't understand what
was so funny in that moment I really
don't get it thank you for the
membership thank you welcome
[Music]
yeah and isn't it more like mainstream
more well-known so I thought of that one
first but I'm very well aware of the
existence of that anime series
huh
the movie based on the anime was
horrible okay but that's not really the
topic here that's not what we're talking
about
[Music]
yeah you're not funny we're talking
about the Airbender movie
which sucks then she realized she meant
the blue people one
oh
[Music]
oh how is that funny
oh well I guess it's just something I
will never understand
uh that's okay
oh oh the misunderstanding was fun the
funny part oh
lion videos
foreign
debut stream reaction video
uh yeah I'm planning to do it eventually
probably at the one year anniversary Ram
is Danish and Sanders resident
distinction
from the slap 21 yellow Duncan coryard
action
laughs
[Music]
um
the noise I I've didn't I've done that
before this stream is amazing also if
noises aren't going through Discord try
turning off the noise suppression noise
reduction that helped for me yeah I've
tried all those kind of settings before
turning them off and on
um and like for official streams the the
cup the whole life staff always tells us
to
um turn off the noise reduction and put
the
um noise uh the the microphone
sensitivity to the very left
and stuff like that and I still have
that right now
um and it supposedly makes it better it
makes it pick up more but it's still not
picking up a lot of stuff
even though my my mixer is picking it up
because I hear the I hear the feedback
in my headphones but it just doesn't go
for Discord it's kind of lame
[Music]
thank you for the membership welcome
I actually off and on and on and off
I've done both of that
Windows does strange stuff with Disco
I think that's a Windows Discord thing
happy belated birthday
your birthday was yesterday noise
I hope you celebrated well
[Music]
you would be excited to see you being
drawn as an owl
sorry if I kind of butchered you
okay
um
randallus Doncaster also read sorry it's
not Mothership it's called Flagship
title okay okay
what no that's actually I was also right
with that one because specifically that
I was wondering why I kept on saying
Mothership
but that was just something that was
burned into my brain for years now
because that is a tales of series term
that they use for specific games for
example Tales of Symphonia is a
Mothership title and base area I think
is a man now
actually not sure
I'm not sure but for example the new one
has the Horizon will be a Mothership
Tower it's kind of like the leading no
viseria must have been one too
it's like a leading a new universe
leading title that kind of like yeah
everything that comes like off of that
is like a like kind of like a spin-off
but not exactly but they call it
Mothership title
that's why I keep on thinking of what
Flagship Mothership Flagship partnership
like I guess normally that's called
Flagship but for some reason in the 10th
Life Community they call it Mothership
and I've been I've been so confused
about it and I've been saying that every
once in a while and then you guys are
like no no that's Flagship and I'm like
oh
why do I always say mothers
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
now I finally am confident about what
I'm talking about
now whenever people tell me again about
that I'll be like no
need to tell zombies they call it
Mothership yeah it is what it is
yeah it's like a main series uh I mean I
I think wait let me let me look it up
tails off Mothership titles
um
okay that just shows me ah there you go
uh terminal terminology unique
terminology is used when referring to
games within the Series in 2007
yoshizumi announced two classes of Tails
games Mothership titles and escort
titles monoship essentially means main
series whereas escort essentially means
spin-off exactly one of the recurring
differences between the two game times
internally is that escort titles don't
support inspiration for main entries in
the series but throughout the most
popular elements from them uh the game
games are also frequently given what is
called a characteristic genre name which
is essentially a short subtitle or a
phrase that outlines the game's overall
theme which I think for Tales of arise
was the one that the the fates that
binds uh you together or something like
that I mentioned that yesterday
um yeah blah blah blah blah blah uh
wait can I have an example for
for
a escort titles
tells off escort
titles
ophony and Dawn of the new world yeah
that's the
sequel because of the world random
mythology oh that makes sense she has a
fantastic dungeon external that's all
yeah those are definitely escort titles
yeah that makes a lot of sense
well I knew that
and
then
okay I should just never doubt myself
ever again
[Music]
Celia too
I would say that's an escort because
I would say but
because it's a sequel
should be an escort
but it could kind of actually actually
it could be a Mothership towel because
cilia 2 is so different from cilia one
because it brings in completely new
um
like game mechanics
uh completely new world and all that so
I think that yeah I think it might be
considered a Mothership even though it's
a sequel
I think Celia too also has its own
um like
you know those those phrases like the
wait let me tell you sounds off so it
definitely has its own uh what was that
what was it
[Music]
and I pretty where your choices spin the
future
foreign
that is that phrase the central theme
they always have this one phrase
does it say Mothership here
no it doesn't say it in the wiki
well whatever you guys probably don't
care about this at all
okay okay
yes
[Music]
Ohio
it's interesting is it
a few mathematics
thematic title yes
yes
[Music]
I'll take your word over a Wiki
maybe you shouldn't I think
more than me
um
[Music]
are there any Tales of fans here right
now like legit Tails offense
foreign
[Music]
I want to ask something
foreign
if you happy
uh if
[Laughter]
um
if you could
[Music]
if you could ask
uh if you could if you could
uh
[Music]
now I'm not leaking anything no but
uh if you could ask
something about Tales of our eyes
to someone who knows their stuff about
it
would there be like a big question that
you could think of
if yes
don't ride into the into the comments
here rather until the uh as a Twitter
reply to me
evil right now or after the stream right
away after the Stream
Tales authorized related questions
[Music]
but like not beginner's questions more
like from the point of view of a fan
[Music]
why is kisara so damn hard
no can kiss on a step on me no
[Music]
okay
uh yes okay let's continue
uh
wait oh where's Minecraft though
starting from Chris dumps where am I oh
yeah okay
days
[Music]
look at those funny Comic Sans foreign
foreign
Fontana
I hate Comic sense yes I do but I'm
honestly using it here as a stylistic
choice to make a make a meme out of it
that's the only kind of situation where
I would use comic sense
did my phone charge at all well what the
I charged ten percent okay so wait
okay my mom wrote to me I actually
didn't fully read it yet so let's read
uh so my mom writes to me at 2AM
congrats
after killing the ender dragon
and I'm like what the you stayed up
oh my God and she wrote back to me this
morning
and let me read it first I didn't really
read it yet uh
[Music]
okay she's like okay here are a few
thoughts and I knew that you would be
very chaotic oh and she knew it
beforehand uh
what ah you went you went well you were
well prepared uh you know as well
uh you were lucky to find the for the
stronghold that uh fast
[Music]
oh oh yeah and she's a
she's laughing about with a crazy
laughing emoji about the moment when
Callie jumped into the void with my
equipment
and then she's like
uh
you should have you should have built
the bridge faster
um just by one person one person should
have just built it faster
oh and then she's like with heart I
heart eye emoji she's like but then you
ran out there and became the tower
sniper perfect
I knew that you would
huh
I know that you would if you had to kill
him all alone
[Music]
now no one can how do I translate this
it was foreign
[Music]
in your description you can finally get
rid of that my Majestic chicken excuse
me
excuse my mom
and greet your fans from me and thank
them for giving you so much love and
support they are really great she really
wrote that and she added a kissy Emoji
so you gotta I guess uh I can't say for
my mommy
[Music]
oh and then you know today today before
the before the
um stream from today she wrote me this
whole paragraph on how to do the elytra
and City stuff she actually wrote in
there uh
you don't need diamond armor but you
need a good sword and a bow and arrow is
pretty useless because there it only
works when they're open but turns out
that I guess you know my mom right now
there's different ways to do that to
fight those and and to go through those
Ender cities I think you know
different strategies like for for me the
boat totally worked out and I definitely
needed the diamond armor because I was
panicking too much and flying around all
the time getting hit all the time I
needed the diamond armor I needed the
feather falling on my bootsies and I
needed the bow the bow was for me way
more useful while flying around then a
sword
but I think like she can she did it her
own way previously
and but yeah by doing it in a different
kind of style
um
my Approach was similar to yours I think
that's the Panic approach
at least one point the boots absolutely
saved you from death
yeah
when are you two getting never right
over now honestly we gotta do it soon
now um I'm gonna I'm gonna
ask
my staff first of all if I can't even
let her out I don't even know if it's
allowed yet but they'll I don't I can't
imagine him saying no to that because
she won't even be on voice chat and do
Japanese girls had their mothers and
fathers on stream before already so what
the hell she's not even gonna be on
voice chat
now should be fine she'll be fine she'll
leave the server afterwards but of
course I'll get permission proper
permission first of all morning
foreign hello mom she can collab with
paper mama no
[Music]
no
no boys
yeah my mom you know I would maybe even
do the voice chat thingy if it was only
like a short thing of five minutes or
whatever like on the Japanese girls did
sometimes but in my case we're doing a
gaming stream so she'll be on the stream
for I don't know one hour two hours who
knows so the potential of her saying
something yummy is much higher
than if it was only for like five
minutes
[Music]
yeah but don't worry she'll she'll be in
the chat in the in-game chat
I think it's better that way
it will be my real mom though don't
worry
I'm not faking anything that will be my
real mom should we get her like a like a
cute skin I wonder actually I don't know
if she uses any skin for her Minecraft
character
well she's playing solo so I feel like
probably maybe not
we should make her like a cute skin with
orange hair
y skin is there anyone in the chat who
can make that
I don't really know how to make that I
wouldn't even know how to make it look
like maybe maybe very similar to mine
but like in a in a simple dress
give her a design
yeah
just put her in a cute simple dress with
an apron or whatever
I'll leave that to you
oh yeah hook up a good uh probably do it
but I know I'm not gonna hook it up with
that but he made uh his own
um BlackRock shooter design uh skin
previously are you one hooky Papa to
make the mama design
well that's gonna be expensive that's
gonna be quite expensive
survival mom deserves survival outfit
true true
foreign
it looks to me like Mama Loni
very confusing in my brain now
um
very confusing again that was on purpose
wasn't it
oh okay let's go
Phoenix is the superior mythical
creature
12 words have never been spoken before
Jesus you know what's up a famous could
have never lost against a stupid Ender
Dragon
it was meant to be
just like how it was meant to be that
the Phoenix gets the first elitra I'm
really sorry I'm actually so surprised I
was so sure that Ina was gonna get one
it took her hours and she didn't get one
yes but that is that is that is probably
fate
that is that must be Faith the game
wanted takanasi Kiana
the Phoenix to get the first Wings it
was just the game wanted it
it's Destiny
I'm sorry
it had to be like that
[Music]
yeah she will find one soon she uh she
at least seems to be handling the end
cities pretty well
foreign
[Music]
too quietly my people don't hear it
she answers me but it doesn't pick it up
now
[Music]
I heard that one
oh man ah belly fats still ones belly
fats
[Music]
foreign
because actually it improved
I think I think she's fine without a
death
she's she doesn't smell bad anymore
Chuck has heard the story about me
wanting to give her a bath and she was
like oh yeah this
I better clean myself
no more stinkers no no
no only tonkers no stinky only chunkers
[Music]
foreign
thank you
okay she's leaving she left
um
foreign
[Music]
at all
Ali Ali thank you Lexington the lion
dancing
I'm freaking impressed by all your prep
dancer being a MF boss good luck brother
employee thank you
recently it's been very fun again to do
stuff to be prepared to
um do stuff well in Minecraft so I've
had a blast and I want to play more
Minecraft I want to fly and have
Adventures now
and I want to explore the end at the end
a bit more as well
thank you
dark the eagle dancing
and again thank you he can have Kim
dungeon
my name is
but some people call me Health such as
gura and Iris should I change my
nickname oh they've been reading your uh
name Brown in the super chants
[Music]
sorry about that uh
huh well I don't even know how to say it
I'm not saying I'm not reading it as
health but I'm still not sure if it's
Heath or hey I guess it should probably
be Heath I guess if it's where if it
were to be pronounced in a correct
English way where I am absolutely the
professional expert in
foreign
like Health but without the L don't
worry I won't read your name wrong but I
don't know if you want to change it why
not change it but uh hmm
you could add after the heat came you
can't could add uh
um uh what do you call what do you call
the
[Music]
parenthesis
is that what I'm looking for you could
add parenthesis
yeah and then write in not health
because if they read the Super Chat and
they read Heath or like Health Kim
uh parenthesis not health and then
they'll be like oh sorry oh and then
look at it again and they'll be like ah
give him oh sorry yeah there you go
thank you
[Music]
for being there to support your mama
on her ender dragon fight
a brackets brackets a brackets are the
edgy ones
[Music]
thanks for wishing you all the best
thank you
besides the beginning I think it went
quite well
the beginning was scruffed but the whole
platform thing it was just yummy and
then yeah you know me not being able to
log into the game and then uh them
having to wait for me
and then them being attacked right away
I don't know is it normal then you get
attacked right away when you already
said when you're only standing on the
platform
is that normal
that you get attacked there already
no not none of me
it was a bad SpongeBob oh yes yes it's
normal
if you aren't quick
uh your guys's opinions seem to be split
never made it that far let's go and the
dragon kill him
you gotta be fast
yeah but we couldn't be fast because you
know
uh
pretty smile again crashed
wasn't Cali's game also crashing because
yeah she also had to turn out the
shaders
um
[Music]
and that was troublesome
yeah unfortunate beginning but after
that I think it's because of that
chaotic beginning it continued to be a
tiny bit chaotic afterwards but in the
end it worked well uh the towers were
taken care of pretty quickly some of the
girls went up uh to the towers that had
the cages that was really good I didn't
I didn't have to tell them to do
anything they knew what they had to do
and I just shut down every other
of those Towers
[Music]
yeah
oh thank you
[Music]
now this is epic entertainment and the
boob has no chance
I wanna at one time you wrote that
did you write down when we were already
in I mean I have I I wrote this to Cali
too
afterwards I was like you know things
might have been very scuffed but uh
you're gonna see it that way that if
that was that was what made it funny
that was what made it into entertainment
and I think the people and enjoyed it
way more than they would have enjoyed it
if everything would have been perfect
and smooth like going uh fruit butter
with a butter knife
so uh yeah all of that all of the fails
were also just
good stuff good content yeah
Peak Peak content
so I agree with that
um
that's what I mean I I was I was also
panicking and all that at that moment
but
I I still felt like I'm super excited
about everything and just you know hyped
up the adrenaline was rushing through my
veins
[Music]
another game crashing though
or something that was not really
necessary I would say
um
Grand Island
the struggle made the victory feel more
worthwhile exactly
very true
also I can't believe I can't believe we
would have we were so close to just
literally digging through my house and
through the surroundings of my house
foreign
they were legit about to do it me too
though I was like what do we really have
to do this what the hell
oh it must be here then no it is
under my house
I'm so glad we were able to stop that
oh man
you don't use it no no I use that house
they could have they could have checked
under the other house but none of them I
would still use the old house
foreign
[Music]
that was a big grass moment
thank you for the support I hope you
enjoyed it
cryptomax 8536 Foundation opportunity
101 Duncan Sam Cruise dancing crazy 101
thank you for the pinkies
let's go oh yes yes we have gone we have
went Gone Going Gone everything don't
miss a thing
going that's a really old blackout peace
song right
do you know that song anyone who knows
the song
[Music]
I love that song back in the day am I
the only one who knows that song Come On
Come On
yup you know it yes I know oh
oh yeah yeah oh
okay
shut up
you're you're probably much more of a
boomer than me
okay thank you need to go to work with
you slay dad and the bird Victory final
thank you thank you thank you for
supporting us even though you were busy
thank you so much I appreciate it thanks
to thanks for the pinky
bronx819 thank you for the ransom
offer up your flash potential fellow kfp
employees
foreign
chickens was I yesterday
what happened what made you write that
Bronx
ah when I used up the chicken The
Roasted Chicken ah
oh yeah the food toys
um
Ah that's right oh I get it now
it was for a good cause
you guys gave me power no just kidding
it wasn't you guys it was vegan chicken
shut up I'll put you into the usual room
if you guys make a drama about it again
did she make sure it was big I'm pretty
sure that probably the chicken that she
had was probably just my chicken
that she got like picked up from the
ground probably when I dropped it
probably
not sure but probably just my vegan
chicken
you ate my cousin no I did not
[Music]
the reason why your cousin is not
answering your calls it's just because
your cousin doesn't like you
[Music]
pranks thank you so much I hope you had
fun yesterday
for Pinky as expected of our amazing
boss and part-time Warrior oh this is
when we hit them already this was when
he died
thank you for the support not Lu
IGI and Jackson FB baggage and sweet
victory to sniper Kiana
I've really I have a awoken awakened
mm-hmm
I'm I am indeed somewhat of a sniper
neighbor maybe one of my previous
Phoenix lives I chose the weapon uh of a
bow and uh not sword and shield
it could be you know I might just not
remember it well because it's been such
a long time but I still have it in my in
my veins and in my arms
[Music]
sniper Awakening I will still not play
FPS games though
at least not for now thank you Jackson
Christina
[Music]
videos
foreign
the moments when I hit the towers
because I said yesterday I was like oh I
was just luck but I was so excited
yesterday I rewatched some parts of that
fight
and I think honestly
[Music]
it might not necessarily have good luck
I think it was a Feeling
I felt it
it was it was um surprising yes
oh but
it it could not possibly yeah it's
Instinct it could not possibly be luck
because it's not like I aimed into like
with closed eyes or whatever I had my
eyes open I knew exactly what I was
doing
I just underestimated myself and my
feeling
for the AIM
yes I became the bull
yeah even today with the shows up yeah
yeah I guess so
a lot a lot of times when the shots
today didn't hit I guess it was because
they weren't like actually hitting the
projectiles that they were shooting at
me and I was like why is it not hitting
the chocolate box
[Music]
I'm gonna take one more
uh
foreign
[Music]
and I don't want to let anyone tell me
otherwise I have sharp verb eyes exactly
thank you and if you're still doubting
me then what will you watch that and
rewatch today's stream as well and
re-watch that one moment when in the
that's talent you know what it's not
luck it's Talent rewatch that time when
in the Summer Festival I did my first
hit in a million the first time I used a
bow in Minecraft in a million years I
don't really have practice with it but I
shot my first shot and it went into the
Bull's Eye not bullets eye Bullseye that
one we learn from that
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
enough of praising myself
foreign foreign
[Music]
whoa
I missed Minecraft did you find an
electricity of course pretty early on
um
that's a good one
foreign
[Music]
tell me I need to know where we're going
you probably already left since you sent
that super chat yesterday but I still
don't know where we're going I'm sorry
to keep you waiting
where are we going dog
a victory
are you here totally and are you in the
chat if yes tell me where we're going to
I don't think you're here he already
left he's he's at the destination I will
never hear from up she's here wait is
the destination to chat
am I supposed to go into the chat okay
oh wait
I am here
I have arrived polian nice to see you
again
sorry I'm stupid
thank you for the support
[Music]
um
Jacob 47 dinosaurs
thank you for the thinking Phoenix
Landing yeah
I guess it is congratulations thank you
mission accomplished great work thank
you thank you
wait a second let me do something here
because I'm sick of that song
let's repeat this one
thank you sorry
for watching this even though it must
have been all Supreme late in the night
for you as well
but
I think you're also here right now so I
guess I guess you don't really mind
staying up late for takanashi Kiana
a very new Fox spicy I'll get to you
soon
thank you for the red super chat
thank you Mama MVP good job you do a lot
you know I I have to
uh remember
yesterday I I tried to kind of remind
myself of
how shitty I was in Minecraft uh a few
months ago
and now
I know what I'm doing so it's it's
really fun is a very
um rewarding
um
I hope you know I hope that for a Cali
at some point it can be the same but I
think what the problem is for Cali is
that there's too much time in between
her Minecraft Let's Plays uh and also
most of the time she's just uh either
fishing or building something so of
course you're she's not really learning
the basics of the game or learning how
to fight and all that so
um I think that's absolutely normal
but the game can be so much more fun and
so much more rewarding if you first
grasp the basics and all that so I feel
like you know we started out together in
Minecraft a long time ago
um and then we both got really busy so
we couldn't really do it together that
much anymore I guess but uh I told her I
told her that if if she wants to uh if
she would like to do another Minecraft
collab sometime soon and I'll take her
on a journey and then you know I I'll
kind of like softly try to get those
Basics into her head again because I can
understand like she might have like got
learned the basics in the beginning in
the first couple of Minecraft series but
honestly you forget all that kind of
after a while if you don't play the
game very often
that's that's I totally get that that
happened to me too uh I think in the
beginning I would forget things
sometimes and
um
yeah yeah but it can be so much more fun
and
um
no she just needs to kind of like have a
general
understanding of it and then it will be
much easier
um
sorry I'm kind of tangenting into
completely different matter has nothing
to do with me but
I just I just um I mean if she does want
to play the game that's totally fine but
she seems to wanna play the game somehow
because she has like these collabs with
Kuda every now and then so
yeah I don't want to force her to play
the game of course no one has to play
Minecraft if they don't wanna
but yeah even for someone like me um
both
I guess I would say I'm a bit more of a
gamer than Cali is but generally I'm
also not much of a Pro Gamer
um
but I got used to Minecraft and now I'm
enjoying it so I think Cali could do the
same
yeah I understand it can be very
overwhelming yeah
especially you know after doing that
building and that fishing and then being
thrown into an ender dragon fight
yeah that's a very sudden and very
frightening
but she did great nonetheless
once we were on that Island she
did great
I mean I I didn't see what exactly she
was doing all the time because I was
focused on Surviving myself but you know
once once we were all of that Island it
was good
she tried to help with her shovel I
think from what I've heard
yeah
she did great
in the beginning was scuffed for all of
us
it was not her not her fault
so I hope she feels better
about it now
better than yesterday
foreign
I think that will like clear itself up
once you play a little bit of Minecraft
then you will be able to recognize
what's
something that someone built and what's
something that is uh generated naturally
what belongs to someone and what doesn't
belong to someone I think that'll be
much easier to recognize because
um yeah
I mean you will you will see the
difference between a tree that has been
built by someone manually and a tree
that is a normal tree
so I think that will come soon soon
after a bit more of a general
understanding yeah she is too hard on
herself no no I don't think any I I
think the only people who cared about
the tree thing were the chat
because the chant always goes absolutely
insane even if like one piece of a
stairwell has been
you know destroyed or you today today
when I placed a block on a path and the
path was unpacked
I I saw the chat going like
[Applause]
but I ignored it
worked whatever but Cali needs to
understand that she doesn't need to give
a about that and that it's mostly
the chats is panicking for no reason
ah every time when I leave the door open
uh even at my place or other people's
places okay I get it a bit more in other
people's places but but my own place
come on come on and for leaving the door
open in one second it's not like the
whole place is gonna blow up and go up
in Flames ourselves people like
[Music]
wow
yeah a may or may have not
entered my home and that is okay I have
no regrets
that is fine to me it was fun getting
rid of them and again that was content
maybe I'm just keeping the doors open so
that we all can have a bit more funny
content
maybe I'm thinking a few steps ahead of
you
okay see for you gotta continue
thank you for the pinky congrats weld on
hot wings TGs Kiara video I got I got an
elytra called hot wings now who was the
one that created hot wings originally
was it 3D
or am I going crazy
who originated the hot wings uh nickname
it was you you say yes I feel like it
was you yeah
I love it
was wasn't that like at a moment where I
was like uh I wonder I want a nickname
and then people were like throwing out
ideas and then there was hot wings I was
like I like that
foreign
thank you thank you that name is now
being used to name the legendary first
elytra of the Halloween server yeah hey
oh yeah and don't remind me of that
Mystic has been Sanderson
[Music]
Jesus Morales thank you soon I don't
remember this
guy thank you for the pinky
congratulations to this for defeating
the Ender Dragon I will always trust you
well done Kiana you guys from the what
was it 1500 members Discord or 2005 2500
I think very much Discord I so
sweet and so like
supportive you guys are not tsundere you
are only yeah 2009 was it you guys only
did it while my well my other chickens
who are not from the 2005 on a Discord
are quite soon
you guys are very dead and I like that
thank you us when always
always
feel attacked
hahaha
I uh you guys are trying to tell me that
you guys are not Sunday as to me
I've always did it maybe some of you
will definitely
good sheep
I don't know why you guys know sheep but
sorry I mean good chicken
[Music]
I was thinking uh of a German
the phrase I guess
are you did you ask me if I'm drunk or
if I'm duck druck druck did you mix it
up
drunk and
whatever uh looking for the top fashion
Daisy thank you thank you for the red
super shed and all the way to the egg
picked egg
we still don't really know what to do
with that huh
but I guess I I didn't even know about
that but I guess that's how you
um Can summon the Ender Dragon again I
don't want to summon that boy anymore I
don't need them anymore but I don't want
to see his face anymore I already have
his head
that's that's the only way I want to see
his face anymore
on a spike
[Music]
maybe I'll cook his egg into fried eggs
oh
will she make fried eggs out of it
it's brutal hey
and the dragon doesn't deserve Bella
and his Dragon deserves to be on a spike
thank you Daisy love you
just
[Music]
congratulations on defeating the Ender
Dragon girls congratulations for the
last hit boss yeah thank you I wouldn't
have realized if it wasn't you for you
guys on Twitter telling me about it I it
was it happened too fast I was too
stressed out because I wanted to take a
screenshot
so I didn't even realize that was so
good because I was I was yielded Away by
the Ender Dragon I was like oh my God
he's so low on the HP I gotta run I got
it right I gotta run I gotta get the
last hit or like at least one more hit
in there and I I ran I ran as if
my life depended on it
and I did it did it
I freed the end
[Music]
honestly
such a Daenerys move
uh uh what was the breakout of chains
Daenerys freed a lot of people too I
freed the end however I feel like that's
a bit more impressive
wow the confidence today is immeasurable
yeah sorry I Love Game of Thrones so
much
you're much cooler than her
nah she's pretty cool
not spoilers in the chat guys
Elvis
thank you for the pinky rats bus finally
beat the game you did superb
preparations I'm so glad you all did it
together I think you even got the last
hit apparently I did anyway now you can
finally try to get wings I got the wings
it also can't wait for Ian Japan
connection is going to be awesome thank
you
thank you
[Music]
boss go take our fellow egg that was not
our fellow like that is an imposter egg
assessing don't trust that egg we can
cook it but we cannot let it hatch
in no situation can we let it hatch
danger danger we want we want
medicine tea thank you for the rest of
the chat
wow thank you for the generous support I
appreciate it next time write a message
okay
thank you
bad egg exactly disgusting egg
huh
what um
how how how why would why would me
getting confident
result in me playing Mario 64 gorilla hi
[Music]
you know she was just walking towards my
room slowly and I saw it and looked at
her and I was like chocolate and the
moon I started talking she ran into my
room so cute she was like that was her
feet
oh baby in the Box
foreign
[Music]
make yourself comfortable I know you're
gonna run away right away
but chill for a moment stay forward and
listen
baby
yeah
stay for a while listen
tip her to me no way
no my baby
no baby
he's speaking baby talk with my cats
foreign
do you wanna hear Thumpers
okay
she sniffed you guys
no
no you know
you good baby
I'm good baby
she got scared of the microphone
sorry no stay here
you should neck scratches
you had a hair in your eye I took it out
not the eye took off the hair
you know so okay she's turning away from
the microphone you can't
really listening anymore
[Music]
hmm
no
oh
yeah cuddles from Mama
hmm
Rachel
okay microphone sorry
what is its movie
[Music]
a baby
one second
you're sure okay cat gone
now I shall Read Super chats wait
oh
I changed my microphone uh fresh
threshold again uh I don't even I don't
know how it was before
uh
[Music]
ah okay
now
stop okay
okay
okay yeah
medicine tea I already read like I mean
there's no text but I already read that
Super Chat didn't I
oh yeah anyway chickens monkey thank you
soon Jackson FB thank you for your
thinking Canada loves you Kiana
sorry for doubting it actually wow
there's a yeah there are the Canadians
sorry for doubting you
foreign
[Music]
I love that song it's really cute
I love mid cm
foreign
thank you for the red super chat
now from Canada
thank you for showing your support thank
you very much very generous of you thank
you soon I appreciate it
SpongeBob 51 thanks
fire thank you for the pinkies
so many Canadians now
thank you I appreciate it Kristoff thank
you George from Texas
I don't waste my translator
oh yeah yeah she
yeah
[Music]
it's very difficult to read your name
what the hell
thank you
[Music]
thank you for the thinking
you have some hidden skills I swear if
you were to give one of those kinds of
games a shot you'd be decent with no
prior experience
I'm sure I would love to hang out with
you and collab with it oh my
um then you gotta stop you gotta stop
because
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
oh these ones are nice Callie uses those
I think
[Music]
yeah
ah maybe not the best shape for my eyes
but you know what if I move too much
and it doesn't like fit my face and how
that would just make it bigger then no
matter how much I move
it will always be on my face
okay that's good just comments
[Music]
okay well then uh thank you for that
question I agree well thank you you're
so sweet of you I'm sure I would love to
hang out with with you and collab if you
did try one
you know with all that praise you you
make me start thinking about it I can't
help it now thank you Kiana she's like
oh my God thank you
Jamestown donkey some black kitchen oh
another Pinky Okay now wait you sent the
same oof that must have been uh did you
oh
you accidentally sent the red one huh
because it's a double pinky with the
same text
uh black friction
oh no
but I will read the same thing again for
you
yeah you have some hidden skills as well
if you want to give one of those games a
shot you'd be decent with no fire
experience
I'm sure Emma would love to hang out
with you and collab if you did try one
um
I agree it's the first time I ever heard
that one damn thank you no wonder I'm so
smug about it thank you
wow your case is what your voice is
accidentally setting a red one I I uh
stunks that's the only thing I can say
about that one
thank you
Sam Cruise dancing oh we're done with
those weights I need to take down my
glasses yes this one
only those from today I left I suppose
oh
I'm seeing from which I have so many
Minecraft films in my folder
uh
well oh is it
wait didn't I name the elite draft from
terrible
cute
nice thumbnail attack
it's graphic design your passion well oh
yes it is
haha
and again smug I mean I have my own
glasses but they're just not as smug as
those ones
I have I have some a pair that's like
rigged to my body okay
[Music]
Mama almost finished baby
almost finished chunkers
please wait for me
[Music]
do what wheel glasses oh
true maybe true
[Music]
oh
glasses still glasses glasses still
glasses glasses no glasses glasses still
glasses glasses still glasses glasses
still glasses
glasses
still glasses glasses still glasses
glasses still glasses glasses Sunglasses
glasses School classes
oh my God
[Music]
laughs
gotta
reads
that smile is so smug
without the glasses smoothie doesn't
look that smunk but with the glasses and
that smile it just looks like a perfect
smug smile okay
foreign
they're having a conversation in the
Super Chat skin
silver one especially Cali um Kelly you
love for your fans and your content I
wanted to say it in Yakuza when I
struggled toward this oh you're an
awesome Majestic Phoenix and I
appreciate that you exist in our lives
oh
I don't understand how you struggled
because you said it so perfectly thank
you so much
very very sweet I'm very flattered very
kind-hearted wholesome Super Chat thank
you for your words your feedback and
your love and your time and your
generosity I appreciate it
oh wait that's a rainbow is it a rainbow
no that's just a pinky following up okay
okay
followed up by a pinky
oh as fangs free times and have you seen
season 3 of railgun
this isn't
he oh wait that's the one that came out
like what last year
no there's not another one that came out
right it's really cute and the
soundtrack is lovely just like the ones
you're saying karaoke I really recommend
it and can't help but think of misaka
and kuroka takamuri it fits too well
kind of does
um yeah last year I I tried to start
watching it I watched I think the first
episode
um even though it was a huge fan of uh
railgun previously
oh the time that they took between the
second and the third season to release
the third season and that time I've
really kind of grown out of anime that's
why I kind of didn't feel like watching
more but I I don't know I guess I still
want to give it a try
I kind of wanna thank you for the
membership
yeah I I'm not giving it up completely
at some point I want to watch that
season fully
feel a bit bad for not having watched it
yet but I just
railgun is very comedic
uh especially because of Kuroko
and not only kunaka but especially and I
just kind of grew out of that style of
anime or like anime in general too
um
but I don't wanna I don't wanna grow out
of anime it says Channel
I mean
I get your point but
I didn't get noise
I don't know how to say that
taste change your time yup
grab anime became anime
or not
well I'll give it a try at some point so
thank you m don't
I'm glad you share my interest in real
gun though Royal gun one and two we're
definitely dope uh and indexed as well
and the movies they had the movies I
think there's one movie
um they had was also insanely good
but there was a movie right
if a index or a relevant movement there
was a movie right there was a movie I'm
not going crazy right I'm not mixing up
things right
one movie
I remember it being good
yeah
index of it Mexican
so much wonderful content to pass
both days provided Oodles of Hooters and
with all the Hoots it
got me hoping he was saying fukuro
someday I love this goofy hug hug world
that's a new one and can never thank you
enough for always brightening my days
thank you
what would I do without your tragedy
uh
I must have heard that song before
somewhere
haven't you already received enough I
will love love verses
what happened to you already gotten too
much out of this
no
was it not enough that Tiana has a pet
that's an owl huh it's not enough that
tons of her eyes mascot is an owl and I
am being the Ambassador for that is that
not enough for you
lastly you want more owl content huh
what about the chickens though huh
the majority of people here are chickens
you are the minority tragedy I have to
cater to the majority and at some point
as well not only to the minority
chickens are cute and owls
um
sure
now I'm gonna retreating with my hula oh
my God which one
wait Banda nango us
oh dear let me see it
oh my God I go on Twitter and I see baby
in a swimsuit moving her hips dear Lord
okay that is not a swimsuit that is
underwear
oh nice hips
anyway I wanted to go to Bandai Namco
uh us let's see the hoodledoodle
wait I'm not saying which one was a
different one
[Music]
has a tails
of our eyes that makes more sense
oh they were tweeting a lot oh not a lot
oh
yeah a couple of them oh
oh oh that one's cute
nice little Doodles but every time I say
hoodle now I feel like I'm a turkey
[Music]
I know
foreign
voice uh recording collection
by the way I think the name for a hoodle
in Japanese is
foreign
I've seen it somewhere
it seems to be the case kind of similar
to hoodle yeah
and there's there's snatch Ben
Jacob's monkey dancing soon putting
Channel thank you
[Music]
you understand
Girls Generation baby
[Music]
yeah okay
meat popsicle function it's a very cute
induction
and there's no Spanish and also trapped
cake with chocolate conduction thank you
for the red super chat yes yes
attention last week I turned into a
chicken and that much closer to my fate
in kfp
and just a thought to not get eaten by
you can't I just restart my membership
to turn into an egg again that means I'm
a phoenix too being reborn again PS4 not
or Stat membership
[Music]
whatever try it out I guess
um that's cheating
[Music]
doesn't work does it not
does it start off again it does not
reset even if you have like months in
between
oh that's interesting well there you go
downstairs you cannot cheat the system
[Music]
it's her point you will be you will be
uh you will
be hugged and buffed and kissed
eventually
yeah
thank you for the pinky it's my birthday
today birthdays feel less special as I
get older but I'm glad to spread this
one with you and can't feed us here yay
I'm stuck at work right now but I want a
milkshake too
I hope you got one by now it's cool
sharing a birthday month with my orcie
you're a cancer then right oh happy
birthday God of amiibo
go get that Oreo uh Oreo shake from
Burger King go get it so yummy oh my God
I did get one did you get the same one
or a different one
I mean any Shake is good but
that Oreo shake though damn
well well well I hope you have a lovely
birthday I agree like for me as well
birthdays haven't been feeling that
special at all the past years but yeah
it is what it is
I think there's still people who care
about you and me every day
um
no matter if it's your birthday or not
so I think at some point people are just
like no no another year but it doesn't
matter I love you no matter what day it
is
I don't only love you on your birthday I
love you and every day
um
but also for me like I am oh is that not
cancer anymore is that Leo oh
for me
um like I I feel like if if I were to
have a party like a birthday party it
would feel much more like a birthday or
you know like having people there in
person uh in person eating cake together
in person giving presents and
I guess that ultimately makes it feel
more like a birthday but I haven't been
doing that for years and partially
because I don't want to be around so
many people it just makes me feel
awkward and uh the other reason just me
being too lazy to organize that
yeah
maybe next year
also kind of feels childish
[Applause]
childish nah I wouldn't say so
that also depends on how you how you
organize your birthday party you could
have it in a really adult Fame
you could I don't know do some adult
stuff together whatever that means thank
you God have a meal and happy birthday
much love from me
[Laughter]
the Divine Teddy thank you
I like that Watson Industries doesn't
believe in efficiency yeah that we
believe that the only correct way to do
things is the Amway that's fine I I like
that but I have to say I'm as I'm just
going to do things are efficient though
so even though you don't believe in
efficiency it is what she does is
efficient
mostly
and Oliver Sorensen Duncan free circles
2021 who is this
action
[Music]
ah oh
now that I have an elytra
and I do still have the
boy that's for sure goes somewhere right
at least in a stream
I could indeed get circles
oh is that cats because cats is very
excited and he's like yes
our the horse our horse
note is circles in the upcoming streams
after getting an elytra it's been far
too long he deserves love about Phoenix
cannot put a hoist into a circle box
or into an Ender Chest can I please do
that instant please please Minecraft
like getting there is easy but then
going back
um
[Music]
well okay he hasn't even heard hot
challenge yet now that is a good
argument
okay I think that is one of the things
that we can do mentally
it's a possibility
[Music]
um
XXX
function pathetic rodent Duncan rice
I'm a big fan of tense of respiria it's
my personal favorite abrigee of all time
do you think arise will be enjoyable for
someone like me
um
I don't know if you skipped all of the
undertales of games until now after the
Experian if you did then I don't know
because I think Tesla rice has a very
different atmosphere a way more mature
atmosphere but it is still very much a
typical Tales of uh game I think the the
reason why it seems like such a
different atmosphere is mostly because
of the graphics and the character
designs but I think in the heart it is
still uh yes definitely the core and
more more than just the chord it still a
tails off game today playing it I I
um definitely did get that like tails on
five from it even though the graphics
are very improved the style is a bit
more mature and all that but still yes
yeah uh water I'm running out of water
soon
yeah yeah
[Music]
first Italy try I thought that was
really good
yeah
the great building
[Music]
uh Taco Tuesday
which is
foreign
Trident the first time you killed the
drought
and you weren't even trying it's no
surprise it will be the same thing in
the end honestly
content thank you destiny
it is so true
it's it's amazing
place my glasses
life comes easy to for this lucky
Phoenix it does it does
it have the same luck with blue actually
the thing is I don't really care about
axolotls yet who knows maybe I will in
the future
but honest like I don't see how
the color even matters like what the
hell like why
I guess people just get so obsessed
about it because it's the one color that
is the rarest but like I don't
I don't know like I don't really
care about collecting those colors
but if I would get started with it I
don't know maybe I'll start caring about
it
[Music]
um
it's like a challenge yeah
who gets the first blue axolotl
I don't see how why why
how that can be such a big deal
maybe it's like getting a shiny but that
that's the thing I don't really care
about getting shinies in Pokemon at all
so much that I gave my shiny away to
someone
so yeah
I don't see myself really caring about
that
yeah
at least not personally
I
saw you finally got the he finally after
what three thousand tries he got the
blue axel
nice good for him
Pizza dead
X of the Titans dinosaur thank you for
the pinky and in terms of a kfp in the
end oh yeah right someone already
suggested that to me yeah
let's do it next time we uh go for the
understanding maybe let's do that maybe
let's build it on the main
uh main island although it's gonna be
difficult with all those Endermen uh
walking through the whole time
but they could work at the kfb no
the end Brands uh care Supino
foreign
[Music]
it's gonna go
the gentle chainsaw that is
walking virus Spanish
[Music]
uh wait name
read as uh
[Music]
huh
yes
thank you will you be following the
Olympics
no I don't have a TV I guess it's
somewhere online as well but I don't
really
I I
they didn't let me be the torch you know
if if they would have let me be the
torch
which how it was obviously originally
planned
yeah
they kind of ditched me so
ah difficult difficult situation here
midnight dinosaur Slavic fellow thank
you to satisfied Angus and tricks and
follow his donation kind of salty about
that I gotta be real
yeah
pillow Nexus thank you thank you
a little late uh birthday gift little
bit Dragon defeat celebration a little
bit tells ambassadorship appreciation
little bit and later finding success
recognition a little bit just because
doing great piano keep it up thank you
that is very sweet there's a lot of
things always to celebrate indeed thank
you thank you for your sweet support and
for
um watching over me throughout all of
these happenings thank you thank you
all Channel thank you for the pinkies
would you like to host a shareholders
meet
why
Channel this meeting why why why Yakuza
out of nowhere what happened
uh the inside of my mouth is hurting
your streams and music always help me
for the work day
it has been a wonderful experience
watching you grow gaining confidence
gaining confidence as a veto board Idol
and streamer I await your future
projects and Adventures with great
fantasy patient
why were the dots in between
what does that mean is that a secret
code what else could there have been not
instead of entity patient
what
other word does start with anticipate
anticip it's a reference
is it me oh I feel so old again
[Music]
what is the joke Rocky Horror Picture
Show
oh oh
what the hell is that never heard of it
especially never heard of that
foreign
thank you so much
I'm so happy you listen to my music into
my streams
thank you thank you from the bottom of
my heart thank you for spending your
time with me hmm
I will continue to grill
continue to improve myself and my skills
so please continue to Watch Over Me
[Music]
Skye thank you for the pinky
mother of kfp Savior Phoenix and hot
wings dragon slayer yeah
Yo's title
I'm getting closer to being Daenerys
Daenerys also has a ton of titles
I think you did that on purpose Sky
didn't you try to make it sound more
like Daenerys I like it I like it give
me all those titles
and ggs yeah you forgot ggs
en Ryan
um
I like how you stopped changing your
name because I just won't read it I'll
just censor it and you just accepted it
you I guess you're happy with that
solution so you don't have to change
your name anymore
you stopped trying I see Kev beat unseen
dancing
thank you Jackson FB thank you for the
pinky sorry I can't watch the whole
stream today because of work no problem
I hope you had the best luck in the end
I I did my movie votes are Avatar or
Kimi no Nava if you're still deciding
see you tomorrow thank you yeah we're
actually watching that together with
silent voice was it
was that was that the name
look forward to you can join us when
we're watching that thank you Jackson
yes yes okay that was great okay
not silent name or or your voice
yeah I'm not gonna say that
I am say so
um
and
I would like to apply for the position
of fry cook I have four months of
experience let's go add it to your name
you're welcome to add the title and
whatever title you want to add that's
fine with me you are hired
oh no no I am the Lord and savior
not mad Queen who the hell is mad Queen
um
closer
because
[Music]
Santa dancing
Anderson
um
foreign
[Music]
and now I finally get to refresh
old
I said so
and don't
recognization thank you thank you soon
all right does let's let's let's see
American Swiss cheese is the only real
swiss cheese I refuse to see it any
other way so in my mind I'll always be
right you said you were saying
I see hello meow
no way that went into the English way
thank you soon
the thing is for some reason I cannot do
one of those accents without also
changing my voice
I don't know why
I don't know why I don't know why
foreign
[Music]
uh with our thanks soon
thank you
Sam Cruise Danish and alcohol
oh
thank you soon hello this is my first
live stream of you oh welcome is that
right haha I don't know is it oh are you
asking if the English is Right chocolate
what are you what are you nibbling on
chunkers
yeah
did you hear that
when she goes like
foreign
[Music]
cute
so I don't fully understand English yet
so I'll probably spend a lot of time
listening for a while but it's nice to
meet you anyway
thank you that's so cool there's so many
newcomers uh recently thank you very
much I appreciate it but your English
seems really good for now
please enjoy your time here
soon
and love a Korean name
thank you
I don't know if I can deliver the
message accurately using a translator a
while ago I saw Kiana wondering why
Korean people like Kiana I'm not a
Korean representative but I think many
people were fascinated but yes positive
and cheerful personality efforts to make
a good broadcast and childness that
satisfy the audience you know at least I
am on of course chicken is love
thank you
[Music]
very happy to have all of you watching
my stream thank you so much for the
support chicken is love indeed yes yes I
love my chickens I am not the chicken
though I'm a phoenix remember it
is
looking for the top dinosaur looking for
the duckish and crispy chicken nugget
shrimp crispy chicken nuggets and crispy
chicken tacos and Mr kitchen
um
let's open chat with no text though why
why why
[Music]
why you do that thank you though wow big
kissy to you thank you for watching
today's stream I hope you enjoyed it
hope you had a great time
thank you for spending your time with me
ah I'm shy oh
um okay then good luck warming up
to the Phoenix
and maybe one day you can say a bit more
just whatever you're thinking
anything is good you can ask me
questions in the Civil Jazz you can ask
you can tell me something about yourself
you can tell me what you like about my
streams whatever doesn't matter or how
you got to know me I always like to hear
that one
I'll melt away you shine is exactly
turkey
I don't know what you're trying to say
with that but you know what I I am 100
sure that the CH dot in your name stands
for turkey chicken you chicken I mean
you already know that you're a chicken
brown boy but yeah just trying to roast
you make you into roasted chicken
foreign
for Channel or anything that stands for
chicken
you got him
oh no reverse
[Music]
yes
thank you for the pinky hey thank you
since you're going to be streaming
Skyward Sword are you thinking about
going back and trying to stream other
load set titles also from Zelda games
you've played which one's very famous
and yeah yeah I definitely want to up
until now I just didn't really have the
time for it and there was no new game
that where I would feel like oh now it
really is that would be a good time to
play it and there was no pressure like
that no time pressure so yeah up until
now we didn't play it but I definitely
want to play more Zelda games on my
stream
thank you so next up is Skyward Sword
let's girl
thank you for the pinky as well
good day my Aussie
congrats on getting electron GTS Kiana
thank you love to hang out more but
gotta head to work oh
you're still on the chat
um
and give give some more Collins love to
the kids I will oh as soon as the stream
is over I'm gonna tackle them
Pikachu tackle
that was 40 minutes ago oh treating no
more no more GT is dead though
rip rip around me
too bad spangenon thank you also for
Pinky what's with all these pinkies
chickens rise up we can beat the owls
overlords
we are definitely the majority again
there's only one uh yeah one or two one
owl I think there's only one owl
in KFC so
I think you know
they they will definitely just like
prefer to not fight so
um
let's just be nice to the owl and maybe
get them to I don't know do something
for us
in exchange we're not attacking the owl
[Music]
um
it is
what Korean name need to translate
[Music]
spy who gets on spy
uh-huh
hi hello
German spy translated
oh wait you even the Super Chat
ohion in Korea
and let's head to somewhere for like
nice for Arkansas and so evenly for a
thousand information the Korean fans
are so cute and adorable
Kim fire chicken and rice you guys
what's up
um
[Music]
hmm
okay
I'll found this Spring Village
[Music]
is it high for you oh I guess I said
okay yes it's already half past three am
here oh someone reminded me thank
you
Domingo language
ghost Phantom Ghost Phantom
thank you
soon and
refresh click
on
video chicken you changed it thank you
Andrew Padilla thank you thank you
thank you sorry my throat hurts congrats
only forget you luck in Minecraft makes
me worry for when the other shoe drops
what does that mean but I believe you
can overcome thank you you mean like
when the lock is over
now that will never happen
thank you for the support that's it guys
uh stream is over I slept actually I
still have to eat a bit more because I
only ate a little bit uh
seven hours ago
seven hours
oh my
God
[Applause]
what's wrong with me
foreign
of course after seven hours I'm hungry
again dear Lord
[Music]
it's half past three am here but I'm
hungry because I streamed for seven
hours and I ate my dinner before that
God damn it I'll eat something small
yesterday actually before going to sleep
I I made some soup
yeah I I got some I made myself some
soup I guess I'll do it again now I have
some more soup
thank you don't stop
so anyway I hope you guys had fun and
both in the elytra hunt and in the Super
Chat reading guys I love you we're
watching some movies tomorrow with the
members I'm excited to chill a little
bit and most oh my God I just
remembered
[Music]
I love you love you
foreign
[Music]