[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
Kenny King
yeah
um
[Music]
recognize that
that's mine upcoming song In album no
no
you did right you just don't know what
it's called that's because it's from my
album no
ah how you feeling ah it's [\h__\h] hot
it's hot
it's too hot soy
um yeah what tweet
what tweet did I see I don't know what
tweet I saw
thank you for coming to Link's address
but I love it
mmm
well it's fitting that it's hot today
because we're going to the the place of
the rock people
I heard they like ah they listen to a
lot of rock music
um
[Laughter]
on one day of this week I played
some
I played some of this game
is
only one day
yeah uh well let's see what I did
where where do we even where is uh what
is it where is it ah here
okay I found a recipe that I want to
cook sometime now maybe that was on
stream
um that is for reference
but I mean I guess you really don't need
it because it's all on this big map down
here
yeah yeah yeah
but I was like
oh oh I activated
oh
I think two maybe three but no I think
two two
viewing Towers
two
yeah
I found this somewhere I dedicate this
Monument to the memory of the souls lost
to the Calamity Zelda
well
mysterious
oh
and I picked up the sound pretty I
thought this was really special but then
I saw in I think I think I saw in Tom
tando's episode somewhere when he was on
the sky island that on some Sky Island
you get like a lot of those
so not so special I guess ah here's an
apple pie recipe I want to make that
sometime
it sounds like I'm saying I want to make
it in real life but no I sound like a
train whistle
oh
and then I made something funny again
I stopped this had like two holes yeah
in in in the in the wood so I put one
through it but it wasn't enough to stop
it so I was genius and I used the the
the wheels to stop it on the side
actually genius but it still gave it a
lot of support on the bottom too
I don't know if that was necessary then
I visited kakariko Village
just a little bit I didn't even talk to
many people because I didn't want to
like spoiler myself too much but I did
the shrine that's there so when we need
to go here then we will have easy access
and
um
I did one side quest the one that you
get right away when you enter from some
old woman they're they're from a shop
and you probably yeah you get shitty
prices unless you do the side quest
apparently
um
and uh for for that though I needed of
course again rice I was like no I'm not
gonna do this anytime soon huh because I
still I can't find rice but then I just
instead of like finding free rice I
ended up buying rice and then I made the
uh what's it called uh
what is it called the rice thing the
soft rice
what do you call it again porridge yeah
the healing porridge exactly oh yeah
Highland vice president Walgreens I did
this one
ah this is probably just me looking for
at the at another geoglyph
but don't worry I'm I didn't go to it I
didn't want to spoil myself you know
don't tendo it's so stupid man
yeah so he gets the normal the first one
yeah and he talks to impa and uh they
obviously tell him let's look for more
but on his way because he has to 100
everything he he looks at everything and
then finds the eighth the Geo Cliff of
the eighth memory
unknowingly of course because he didn't
proceed with the quest yet thus not
knowing that there's a proper order but
you could kind of guess that it's you're
not supposed to look at that one because
it's like you're not supposed to be
there storyline was
and then he does I didn't I didn't watch
it I was like are you really gonna watch
this now the eighth member for real dude
so that's when I turned it all off
that's when I turned off his his video
and then later on I continued watching
after he was done
um but yeah yeah he must have gotten
really spoiled
stupid
um he doesn't know yet that there's an
order
um
spoiler averted real tuba what the [\h__\h]
are you doing flash tuba
yeah no you have to unlock it in the
right order and I'm scared that he will
continue doing this randomly because
he's very far from going to the to the
side to the quest and and he's like oh
my God
so many different paths as then he
should be going finally now he arrives
in in the orny area unbelievable
unbelievable it was triggering me so
hard
ah
but probably only it wouldn't trigger me
so much if I wasn't playing a game
myself
now there's just
he's doing too many caves and clocks and
all that [\h__\h]
great cat but I forgot to one his name
is Rufus 50 Scottish world but I don't
know what the other health is last time
again doesn't expect you to find them in
order
I mean even I did it like naturally
because you find the first one yeah
usually if you like follow
request logically you know and go go to
the hints they tell you to go to the icy
region then you find the first one on
the way I did that too naturally yeah
yeah and then and then and then and then
and then you know
you know you know
and then after that it's kind of obvious
you know they make you go to you know
you know
I guess you only get that hint of going
with them to that place where they show
you the order after you save the ornies
right because I was I was trying to
remember when I got that Quest and I
think it's in the ornery Village after
you finish them right that's when they
show up there
um
no no you have to you have to do it in
the right order it's
it's it makes no sense otherwise
but whatever
whatever I'm just gonna skip those parts
no I didn't I didn't tell him anything
I'm just like seething quietly
uh here in this picture I just took this
picture because I found the cool cave uh
I don't know where the [\h__\h] that is but
I found a cool cave where you have to
shoot through that hole
uh you see that hole there's a little
little book there with two spares I
think
and the book tells you about some
traveler who tried throwing the space
through the hole but he failed because
they don't go that far and genius me I
immediately knew
I immediately knew what to do so I
attached the the thingy the the wing the
wing that lets you shoot further yeah
and no the Gloom hands I've met in a
stream once and haven't since and don't
tendo met them too finally but he didn't
manage to kill them so he didn't he
didn't see he doesn't know yet that
there will be Phantom gun on once you
kill them but he was already terrified
very funny noon
yeah so I shot through and then uh I
think a shrine opened
I think
I'll have a picture of it but I think a
shrine opened afterwards
was this uh oh just a cool funny verb
statue that I thought I wanted to show
you guys
[Laughter]
doesn't it look funny
looks like a funny bird statue but
um I think this might have meaning later
because there's something like an altar
down there but enough no no function yet
for me
um
yeah funny actually it looks like a mix
of a Kappa and the bird
oh and then we have another recipe I
want to cook
ah then I found my first uh what are
they called again uh in German at least
they're called IGA
um
was that was annoying I I I I didn't
know they were in this game too but like
this lady she it was a side quest where
you have to go from spot a to spot B Etc
like you go up you go through the whole
valley of uh enemies then you go up the
mountain then you go they fly over to
the other Mountain because she's testing
you she's testing and she's hinting at
the fact that you know oh someone with
with blonde hair you need to prove
yourself you know she's trying to find
out if you're if you link yeah and then
they are like okay your link let's fight
and that was actually stressful because
it was three of them it was free this
one turned into free it was a bit
difficult to fight them holy [\h__\h] it was
rough my first Giga was free
um
yeah oh and then uh
I guess I was back in the orney region
yeah I was trying to do
something uh
ah I was trying to fulfill all my side
quests and my Shrine quests and I did
indeed uh I did
um like some stall uh
stable stable Quest and Francis and uh I
did the one in the morning village where
you found where you find a
a cave by looking at uh down at the
mountain from the top of the ornie
village and you find like a
University is free and you find this
cave by looking at the mountain from far
away remember
um
yeah and then this I was I found this
guy it was a weird there's no Quest or
so but there's this random guy drawing
a sky island that's like really far far
away I don't think you can even I I know
which one he means because it shows you
afterwards but like what
and you see the progress of him painting
it yeah
quotes
he's from Bradford the wild oh he helps
with the locations of the memories oh
oh so now he does nothing just paints
maybe he'll be in more places
and we'll see what else he paints or
maybe it's a hint that on this Sky
Island specifically
there is something I definitely want to
see
huh
I know I know
yeah
is that actually the island that has a
flower shape or is it a different one
I don't think it's the flower sheep one
maybe
oh well okay let's remember him after
all maybe he's work he used to work or
something ah this is the bird cave it
took me a while because I'm gonna be
honest I I tried to skip the part of
going to the very top of the horny
Village
um and I just went I looked at a guide
of how to do this Quest and it said you
know it showed the map location
uh pretty accurately uh and I've walked
around this mountain
a million times
uh to find this bird I was like it can't
be so difficult I'll find the cave this
sure shouldn't be too difficult but I
just I looked so much and I couldn't
find the cave
um because it is very well hidden it
really is like behind you see that the
beak of that bird
and it's like behind so it's really
hidden
yeah I finally found it ah then I
then I did this Quest nah I did two
quests here I did the stake Quest I
brought the restaurant the steak
for that I had to make myself some
medicine
um I first made the wrong medicine I
thought heat resistance was enough then
I made really good heat resistance and
it didn't work so I had to collect all
those little little geckos and I made
the fire resistance yeah
and then I brought the
the meat over there but I I already I
already noticed what's going on because
I thought the meat in that cave looked
really weird
uh like similar to the what are the
stones called that we collect in the
underground
um so nanium and then the overground in
the sky I guess yeah but this one I feel
like it kind of looked funky like that I
don't know it just looked like like so
purple and and scary you know but that
was weird
um
so I think yeah they're they're Rock
meat is currently kind of like poisoned
toxic that's why they are
um like the ones with the red eyes there
is gorons that have red eyes
and there's some that don't have red
eyes right
[Music]
um
oh yeah they're all kind of like
so we saved them today as I did that
Quest and then this guy is another Quest
look at his hair
and he wants you to bring him 20 fire
stones
and apparently there's some fire stones
that are extra ripe yeah but you won't
know until you eat them but if you do
get it right and he gives you a lot of
money
okay
I had
uh uh four
39 I thought I would have more but I had
39 so I first gave him 20. and it failed
it wasn't right then I had 19 only left
but I wanted to try one more time so I
got a bit more a bit more Firestone and
gave him the rest of my Firestone all of
it because I I guess normally I don't
use it anyway so it should be okay uh
Flint I mean
you got it first time with 24. I I hear
from so many people that they give it to
him the like the first time they get uh
the reward but then afterwards like even
after 10 tries it never hits again
so I was really unlucky I didn't even
get it on the first try
and also not on the second try and now
I'm out of Flint so that was not worth
it I should have done safe scumming
because I I saw on the guide later on
that you can escape save scum
foreign
like first he's like oh my God whoa what
is this what is this like he gets you
really excited and you he makes you
think you got it but then he's like oh
no man no it's just the usual [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] man anyway I've been trying to
document more for you guys what I've
been doing so that's what I've been
doing I got like two Skyview towels I
was just traveling because most lives
I was looking for the rice I wasn't sure
which which area and this for some
reason I could have just looked this up
but I didn't look up uh where hateno is
because I hear all the time that at
hateno Village is where the rice is and
I just random I thought it might be here
might be here and I just randomly went
to some Skyview Towers and it wasn't it
wasn't there ah
okay
yeah
but at least
um whenever I did the Skyview Towers I
did like close by I did some shrines and
stuff and I traveled a bit
so and I got materials and I did some I
did uh all the stable quests that I had
and all the shrine quests that I had
vacations
foreign
travel vlog
yeah I wanted to make some progress
switch audio or I don't hear anything
ever it's okay it will come now
see
Shrine uh yeah I did that and then I
ended it
yeah but it wasn't even I didn't even
play a whole day because that was
actually on the day where I had a collab
with gura
uh and I I got really tired you know
after like I don't know how long did I
play maybe five hours my eyes
so tired yeah yeah I went towards the
actual Village and I walked in a little
bit
and I found the shrines I was like let's
do the shrine and then continue
after that but yeah I'm already here so
well I didn't even notice that they have
an opening right there
maybe that's at fault
uh all right I need to
did I do this
no no no that wasn't me oh I'll
orientate myself
ah yeah yeah yeah okay are you hearing a
big Jam guys at the bgm or the game
sound
talk to like some NPCs but mostly I just
rushed up to the
up there to the shrine yeah okay good
well then today hopefully I mean I
wonder how long it'll take
but hopefully we can help them which
would mean
we will have to
do the their their
[Music]
um
let's see
I mean I don't remember what this stuff
looked like in breath of the wild but
I can't imagine it was like freakishly
glowing like this and look it looks
otherworldly don't you think and
obviously the eyes are glowing and
they're crazy but when I was told
and I checked but I'm not convinced
I was told that in the shops not this
one but what do you have no I I bought
some spice so I can make curry
uh that the the the jewels the gems
yeah they are the same as as the enemies
have yeah
but I was told that they're cheaper now
cheaper than ever because they're crazy
like fun okay maybe I should buy some
and then resell
but where where is this shop now I can't
find it
this is their their hat uh the hotel
is this restaurant no this is close ah
oh I was like oh my God it looks the
same as the breath of the wild one
isn't this the same one
but it's good that I find it now because
I thought I will have to buy at least
one piece if not two
it is the same wow yeah
where's the wait there's signs there's
clothes there's a moon for slipping over
there is just that was a general store
that I already walked in walk day with
why can't I not ah wait it's outside one
is outside the diamonds one thousand
I don't know
they say it's way cheaper now would you
guys say it's worth it
I have to buy one
I mean the clothes right at least one
okay okay yeah both the winter clothes
it also works to just have the pants so
I'm hoping I don't have to buy
everything I bet you get an extra bonus
if you wear all of them right
useful to construct crazy strong diamond
is worth but
are they lying to me
because some of them the ones at the
entrance definitely lied to me they
wanted to buy my my
Jewels for like five bucks
oh they're ripped oh they are ripping me
up oh
oh I I at least believed them about the
fact
paper but I guess that was a lie too
[Music]
there was one that was selling sapphires
too I think but that was somewhere
inside
okay well thank God I didn't buy I
thought that was kind of not really that
cheap
oh wait what about this place did I look
in there
man run a rip off
gonna rip up man how dare you
I know I was in here too
and I saw oh this looks like uh the
boss's place but they're not here
[Music]
's Moana looks
wanna looks so good we have to do the
color remember this is
oh
why why
they're so strong
this little game is this like
tic-tac-toe
it must be
they just gave up
I just think I know
cute Goron's build sturdy seems so yeah
unbreakable pot what the [\h__\h] I mean you
can probably break it with like a proper
weapon
let me put the chat here
yeah guys I'm I'm very happy to be
playing tltk today
but they'll probably be
playing
uh very long and only trying probably
because it will take a lot of time we
will only be able to do the dungeon can
I take this without you getting mad
[Music]
what
you loving in living in your mind rent
for you after all what's living in my
mind runs free you saying Tio tigayla
just something what
but I don't think so
I think the thing the reason why you
think it's silly is because b-o-t-w
obviously just doesn't roll off the
tongue tongue in in English it does in
german though Bill TV because W is just
V
so it's easier to say so I think then
also with totk we just say it okay
shortly like that
[Music]
resistance to the cult
d
a
Beauty
that's it oh my God this water is almost
cooking there's like bubbles does it get
hotter over there
stamina
oh I think I'm
a shrine thing is to get an extension
something
ah this used to be filled with lava
oh
I hope I won't return to
Lava afterwards
okay we'll just change the rock
situation
don't swim away you little [\h__\h] okay
what let's go back to the uh this one
this was the one I was talking about 300
that's the one I saw and I was like
and this lady I talked to her I think
it's her she wants to buy them off of me
um more expensive than what the shops
would buy them for normally
um I think it's her
you again
it seems most everyone's into Marvel
Brock roast not much else not a great
time to procure or since you're speaking
to me again I assume you have order to
sell me
she wants 10 pieces of Amber for 200 do
I even have that
but but she's like not scamming me right
[Music]
if you have fun with the secret post
girl song yeah
um we stayed for long time afterwards
yeah yeah we were just chatting
[Music]
um
eventually gurus
internet internet kind of died that's
how she left us
and me and roommate just continued for a
while that's a good deal do I have it oh
yeah I don't I don't okay I'll save up
now to find her again sometime
I wasn't trying to fool you lady I
wasn't
poor gubia
okay when I want to sell I'll find her
is she always in this Village though
will she be elsewhere this is 1200 700
or why is the main armor the cheapest
interesting
maybe I'll get the main armor then
[Music]
yeah for now because one is enough right
now oh
we probably need it if we want to go to
the dungeon thing
Rangers starting
here
are you are you talking about the girls
talk stuff
where did I where did I talk about that
hmm
yes this will be very useful when I want
to look into those caves again as well
all right
it looks stupid but okay
um for pants
guess we can wear this
because it has free at least
yeah
you look stupid
okay then uh let's try to do the main
cause maybe there what you're the Elder
aren't you
crazy
all my warnings about the marbled rocker
so he knows what's going on but he can't
control his people huh
so everyone's acting funny because of
them are about rock rose that the
president you know who is mining you
know boy you little [\h__\h]
over there
you know Paul
nothing
[Music]
it's only here
oh he's making [\h__\h] to the money huh he
looks like a wrestler
that mask
[Music]
s
I don't know about his voice
but he's still a child right
yeah I guess so from breath of the Wild
close on Japanese that [\h__\h] yeah
because he's supposed to be a child
that's why he's got a high voice I guess
but in English does he have a lower
voice
yeah yeah he was a very wimpy character
I remember yeah
is
he's just he's just still wimpy he's
just like feeling more confident because
of all this bling bling that he got
print uh clothing oh my God
[Music]
um
yeah I have the voice uh voices in
German because
um Zelda sounds a million times better
and people were interested in what it
sounds like anyway
and there's not so many cutscenes where
they speak German anyway
yeah
so
yeah yeah
[Laughter]
leopards leopards yeah indeed we haven't
seen a leopard
um
what sorry I didn't read it
or talking like that I always steamed
two hours same guess
these days
foreign
what happened to him
you hear that blue dog you're not needed
around here anymore
you don't think I'm just going to sit
here and some link what's your business
in government City huh
[Music]
and you're wondering about strange
goings on
we're interested I thought you'd gone
missing but you're telling me she's
still missing I mean it's Artemis those
lovely blonde locks of hers after all
Knox does that mean hair
oh oh the lady with hair like that she's
the same one president unable talks to
about marble rock Rose
wait a second
is he
did he make himself a fake Zelda to talk
to because
he needed he wanted like a girl and
yeah
Massacre
has he gone absolutely because he he
might have fallen in love with her but
he was too young now he's like he's like
older and he has all this money he wants
to impress her but you know she's still
you know all into link so what he does
is He makes himself a fake Zelda
stop cooking but wait wait wait wait
wait
the way this sentence first I thought it
was just to know that he just saw her
once like for
um you know one of those hallucinations
but this sounds more like he talks to
her all the time
about marbled Rockdale toast Rose
and yeah
the money like maybe changed him into a
really creepy dude
[Music]
you'll keep your traps shut if you know
what's good for you see he's sensitive
about it too
as you can see is the picture of peace
and we can't have Princess Zelda so you
better shove up yeah
I'm gonna go get more marbled round
roast can't afford to keep her reading
see
Scott like effect Zelda in his place
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
oh my God
you don't know the I swear if you bring
any more of that stuff
thinking back
that's surely the right story
HQ
and they be rolling
is this the main quest guys
surely that's right yeah you know both
of Golden City
just a kid following me around crying
boss and this and that blah blah blah it
was all business as usual around here
and he created Universal a group of
codons who worked their minds once they
start digging up that marbled Rock Rose
you're gonna blowing all youngsters
changed
hmm you heard me changed all due to that
strange modeled Rock Rose
now all the youngsters to sit around
eating it instead of working why some of
them are even running scams trying to
get you to get more bubbled rock rolls
yeah I actually helped someone get
something
there's no way he can't see what a mess
we're in a little bit but he keeps
playing dumb
because for the money it doesn't for the
money if it weren't for my darn spine
I'd marched right into unable cause HQ
give you unable a piece of my mind
what HQ is in the pain in the neck
location you'll see for starters I'd
have to go through the Norfolk mining
side
that's what my back sounds like in the
morning when I get up
oh
in this condition I can't even write a
card what do I want to do
okay I'll do it they went this way right
put it down there
[Music]
and somebody must be on my map oh okay
let's follow this path
over there
cute
oh
[Music]
my neck my neck is still like that I
just I guess I
don't do it as much anymore on stream
maybe I'm doing it generally a bit less
but it's still very very
um disturbing
I'm still very concerning
yeah don't do it much on stream Nanny uh
damn
uh even if I wanted to move the card it
won't be happening with the safety
officers so preoccupied
um
didn't get any work done today thanks to
them wait
it's the biggest dungeon nah it's not in
the volcano right because that just
leads wait maybe
it does maybe it's there
and we jump inside
oh
I thought it's just a hole to the
underground but probably it is their
thing because like what else could it be
it's probably there yeah okay
that's why we need the heat resistance
um
good morning Cali
OT kids
good morning Callie
but you guys are disturbed about the
Super Chat I'm confused about this
I got this message
Cali how could you make this mistake you
can't possibly think you're on Cali's
channel can you
hmm what wait I'm half asleep I'm sorry
you're a little [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
God my name is Kiana
oh
I wish it was Cali
I wish I had her body
um
but I'm kiwawa deal with it
[Laughter]
wake the [\h__\h] up
drink some coffee or something
yeah maybe maybe it's
um someone who mostly really really
watches Cali and the thing is like she
mentions my name a lot right so
they get like brainwashed
and my name just lives rent free in
their head
[Laughter]
um
I think it's called ever since president
unit we started mining this stuff
everyone's been too busy with it to care
about work I don't need it so I'm doing
fine I get the sense that stuff's just
not great for you
yeah you get in okay oh wait we're
supposed to ride
which one
oh no
left ah Maybe look at that
oh yeah that's it yeah look at that it
looks like a Ninja Turtle
wait you know who looks like a ninja
turtle wannabe
okay
oh here we go
give it to me
[Music]
someone said that you can get the end of
the tracks if you get in this Minecart
but how do you make it move
I bet the ancient city of garontia is
over there
oh grandia sounds like something from
Lord of the Rings
well if you're wondering is the
legendary place where the golden Revolt
used to live I heard there's an amazing
transfer stored there too maybe that's
where the other track leads to
and Gondor
they had even more advanced technology
than we do now and I heard they used to
ride in strange vehicles
[Music]
I want to use this Minecraft to search
for the treasure but I can't get it to
budge anyway you better not tell anyone
all my secrets okay
oh
where's cool
okay but I really can't have it or what
you little [\h__\h]
and now I can have it okay they just
really wanted me to get the side quests
okay
that won't be enough I suppose is there
ah here
how
look why do they have
so nice stuff here huh
weird
okay
what's that weapon I have
oh
sure ah I bought this girl Garland in
kakaniko
uh because it was cheap and I thought
maybe I have to do something with it but
ah
how can
[Music]
how caring is moving
a lot Sims yeah
well
and I say where other cards do I can
just get one of those
[Music]
but I get back
my turbine okay
yeah there's some down there and there's
some more here can I use those
ah okay why why you gotta be so specific
anyway is the Garland you still don't
know what to do with the garland either
is there is there
a quest for it or like a specific use or
what does it do on the weapon anyway I
found that to be very mysterious
hmm
[Music]
Minecraft
oh
there's a lot of
that [\h__\h] where they mine
okay
wait let's read this
[Music]
and those are Highlander workers when
entering a sizzling hot cave Remember to
prepare yourself Bumble skin
that sounds like they're describing
chicken skin
okay no problem
Doug B's card from Mario Kart DLC
that would be cute
they're they're all feeling so bad hey
it's you again the one who knows
president you know Paul ah he's talking
about marbled wrong so if the blonde
lady
see I'm telling you guys
I'm telling if I am right yo I don't
like that lineup one there's definitely
a marbled around course that's fault
that makes everyone funny yeah
is
the mass
it's always so nice but as soon as he
starts wearing it he got real mean oh
your friends are present you know aren't
you you know how he created you know
book called for mining it was supposed
to be helpful for people who needed
orange stuff but now it's just making
things weird around here if we let you
pass will you convince president yunoble
to make unable cost up buying marbled
Rock roast
okay let me
let me on they let me go okay I want to
see that Zelda puppet
[\h__\h]
wait it is
that the blood moon Zone
everybody let's just happen uh
cut it out already
we want you to take off the weight
Master you can go back to the president
you know but we know and love boys
thank you
is she gonna disappear yeah
and she can stay longer than the other
oh
yeah Zelda that would keep on saying
it's not just like you know the one that
we saw or maybe maybe that is I wonder
if that's the same Zelda the one that we
saw but she always disappears so fast
oh well this one's evil and she gave him
a mask
and make some evil that's so mysterious
I I'm excited to learn more about what
what's wrong with that
thank you grayman gaming thank you
that's why am I weird
Zelda evil
mother Rock Rose good makes everyone
happy
are we gonna find oh oh dear uh what
clearly
um
okay
oh I have I have no no good bunking
sticks uh maybe this one's this one
[Music]
this one wait this one's the jumping one
isn't it oh
that's okay this one's fine
[Music]
uh
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
it makes no damage
please
I don't want to waste I don't really
have five bombs I don't know if that
will do something oh wait ah oh wait
easy
right how did one only the maybe from
behind I don't know because now we're
stuck from behind
and it works
why do the arrows work so well
or is it only when he's dazed okay
I'll wait for him to do it again
unbelievable
okay I thought this would be like a more
exciting battle
um
[Music]
it's so bad
at all
what happened
oh
but yeah snow go off Rick I don't
understand
everything's a blade ever since I put on
the mask from points of Zelda I need to
talk to her maybe she can tell me what
the story is
hey where is she anyway
oh
is it imposter like someone who's making
use nah then she wouldn't look exactly
like her
so it must be some
ghost evil ghost version I don't know
manipulated by Ganon
or or the the the shitty stuff from the
underground who knows or yiga yeah I
guess yeah because yinga can
but I don't know if they would
yeah yiga can change the form but still
would they would they do this like Diego
aren't supposed to be like the main
thing of the main storyline I feel like
you know what I mean
I feel like
they should only be Side Story stuff not
like participating in this main story
like that like what's their business
[\h__\h] she's she trying to bury Us in this
cave
but only me
oh
yeah it obviously looks freaky
they were the main bad guys in Hyrule
Warriors well Hyrule Warriors is
Hyrum Warriors
is everyone all right nobody's injured
[Music]
wait is leopards uh armor is gone too
thank God
so that and a lot of us bling bling has
gone to that had to do with the musk him
trying to be like a
like a I don't know
what you call it
the game had a lot of fans first I saw
some scenes where like Pura they were
comparing PIRA how she changed from
Hyrule Warriors to the current one yeah
yeah yeah I guess you get a lot of Side
Story thanks to Hyrule Warriors yeah
douchebag massive pimp that's that's
what I'm thinking of yeah
[Music]
right now princess sounds outside the
cave oh that blonde lady was pretty
Zelda yeah yeah and I need to ask her
about that mask and the marbled Rock
roast we gotta hurry and go talk to her
the only way to break those Red Rocks is
with my charge attack oh right will we
learn that but I can't really say where
I'm going when I charge yeah link read
my eyes and guide me Coral
whoa power fire when you know those
areas chat she can be aimed in any
direction for a very fiery of rolling
attack
that's what we'll be getting
yo then I don't need bombs anymore to
like break you know you know like big
cave
opening
ah and this will be very useful in the
underground with mining the bigger
collections of you know
yeah thank God because I thought it's
really hard to get a big amount of bombs
Bryant
I I I'm always lacking bombs
foreign
that's amazing that feels more useful to
me than the other one already
although I've been using the other one
like in the sky
to move forward quite a bit yeah cool
okay okay nice I'm Gonna Save so many
bombs yeah nice
great come on boys let's go after the
prince Zelda
all right
we already did something very helpful we
we already got unable back to normal
oh you didn't notice
spin like this all the time what's that
red Haze battling from the Death
Mountain Gordo oh
you don't remember princess you know
Prince
president
or he would love to be a princess for
sure
laughs
you told us the red Haze is dangerous
and that we shouldn't go near it oh
let's be cute cute cute
it showed up at the same time how a
class started floating and the upheaval
happened the crown was super rambly and
you were worried that mountain lion
erupted again so you went to check it
out
oh was she there and when you came back
from the mountain you were wearing that
mask I
don't know I saw
I saw there she talked to me and gave me
that mask to wear
[Music]
does that mean princess Ella lives
inside Death Mountain which is
definitely not there not here maybe if
we go out there we'll find her
she's scary
I'm gonna go look for her I can't be
having you too long but I'll sort this
out I'll ask her how to get everyone
back to normal yeah yeah so went back
home for me everything is gonna be okay
okay
[Music]
maybe Zelda also ate uh too much of that
rock meat
yeah okay I'll come with you no problem
easy cards are sure useful I believe you
[Music]
um
where's my armor there
[Music]
is it more expensive here
was that same price and he only got the
top
[Music]
is it say it okay
I was gonna be mad if it was cheaper
really mad
shall we
[Music]
do something here or
so it goes straight to the Death
Mountain oh
oh the cherry trees over there
oh
is he already following me oh okay I'll
look around just a little bit because
I'm a bit curious
oh
no way
no go up go up
oh [\h__\h] run run run run run
bye
[Music]
okay at least I'm busy with him
so I don't have to oh there oh what the
[\h__\h]
children's game yeah
yeah I would only meet them randomly in
some of those caves
look how fast though
sky is moving hello can they stop please
oh my God okay
push it
welcome man
[Music]
are you okay
wait
I left some stuff
can I take it dark Clump an unusual
substance is cold to the touch and it
seems as though it's filled with pitch
black darkness use it in cooking again a
Gloom resistant effect
so they dropped that and if we get lots
of it we can just run for the bloom and
probably it won't be much of a
difficulty anymore to fight them
once we get a couple of it so just a
couple times we just gotta bait them
and run away go back pick it up
until we have plenty of it
make some Gloom resistant medicine
and fight those
also whenever you kill them you also
gonna got a fight every time
[Music]
okay I wonder so like what is that like
do they want
like early game players to attempt that
feels like
quite a challenge
I wouldn't want to attempt that now
what do you get out of it
well out of the hands you get that
material and out of Ghana maybe some
some more like glue maybe Gloom
resistance
weapons I don't know I don't know I
don't know but weird that's so scary
there's someone to the gardens and
breath of the world I'll dealt with them
by spamming bombs at the hands and
during the fight afterwards normally
yeah it seems like you know I I watched
uh someone deal with the hands like the
Dom tando actually in the cave
that the same cave that I was in
um
didn't really I don't think he
understood was the best way to fight
them but then I think I saw elsewhere
some comment or some guide or so saying
that the best thing to do is just throw
AOE damage bombs at him
so because apparently this I didn't
notice this because I was also using
bombs but when you kill one you can kill
them you can you can stun them pretty
easily if you shoot their their eyes the
eyes on their hands
uh with an arrow but the thing is if you
kill one only one by one then they will
regrow apparently
so you do want to use the bomb strategy
get somewhere high up throw the bombs at
them get them all down at the same time
um
[Music]
mm-hmm
see I'm like so
I'm so I I informed myself a lot about
this game
yeah
okay
so what where are we going
the biggest mountain what's the best way
to get there there's like a rail here
so probably gotta take that one
although there's also from the hot
springs
a path to the
Dove Mountain but from our current
situation this one would be easier okay
eh
get rid of my card
what why
do we have another
uh no
[Music]
now I'm scared to go down I wonder if
it's like everywhere
don't go down
[Music]
oh
they're supposed to be used here
no Steel
look like
let's go I don't know how you're gonna
follow me but I'll see you there up
it's not
yeah I'll go I was gonna follow me just
like teleporting oh
what what
when I'm in a cart I can like shoot him
at things
oh
that might be useful and some situations
that we haven't met yet
oh
no hold on
okay so we want to take the other one
is this path yeah yeah yeah oh but it
goes It goes up quite a bit
no way that's that's that's a different
one it's it's that one
down there I don't think one turbine is
gonna be enough
also not not enough a battery anyway
probably
but we can try I can take some of my
capsules out
make it stronger
we'll find out I guess I'll I'll put one
here
I'll get one out because I'm already
guessing it won't work maybe it will but
I mean why not I'm never using this
stuff anyway
card has momentum to keep it moving
really do I not need to
my shield makes the last one of what why
do I not have to do this there was
another fan back there
really
where's my boy where's he
what's he doing
I'm down here
uh okay weirdo I'm going without you
then bye-bye
[Music]
or maybe here we have to shoot something
who knows
there's like
um maybe maybe a deep space
rolls like that
they're still kind of same thing I
thought we shoot him
oh it's going up just fine
um I will run out of batteries though
but now at least now
stop here okay okay that's it I thought
it would go up even higher
okay then we good we're good okay stop
eating that that's not healthy
a car
okay
let's go up the mountain
Death Mountain West Side
is that a muscle car
should we go in here check out what's
inside is it worth it
oh there it is
oh scary look at his eyes
we could check out
what we can find there
wait we'll come here
yeah whatever
um
I'll just checked out this one see if
it's worth checking out and if not then
that was that
but if all the like stones in there are
infected I wonder if you should visit
them after you're done instead
oh yeah
oh dear
this happened before and the first time
we streamed this
and yeah at least I I survived holy [\h__\h]
I was dangerous or maybe this will lead
to a chest or so
oh
[Music]
I guess now I will never need fire
resistance anymore will I
because I have the oh it's okay
[Music]
the rocket floor
what could they be for
eign
I was not listening
the dude has a quest
oh maybe it has to do with them
they're torpedoes
let's go
is that it in this cave
that's it
why isn't anyone coming okay okay I'm
coming
just when I thought help was finally on
the way it's a piddly highly that
stinking track broke and now I'm stuck
here none of the other workers even
noticed great just great at this rate I
won't be able to go buy any more bubble
background this is my last one
you gotta figure out a way to get me out
of here okay
uh let me know when I can get into the
cartons and it's fine okay okay okay
let's do that quickly bro doesn't
deserve to be saved yeah honestly I'm
just
supporting his addiction
right now
must be good
is it this specific car
uh where is the front I guess the front
is the front right
like so
thank you
treasure chest
you see a treasure chest
next to the Rockets
come on
Look Around Blind you
I never see those that are like ah
that are like blending in I've already
noticed I missed a couple
thanks to dontendo stream uh video a
cobble Crusher
hmm
drop this
no
okay
yeah okay besides that I would put
a turbine on it but I don't know if we
need any more I hope not
double fee for that employee this month
rocket the hammer for a rock of power
hammer I know that you can attach rocket
and all of those things uh to Shields so
you can probably also attach any of
these things to a
a
um
weapon yes I would assume so
maybe the other ones are just for me to
make my own and get back
the other materials
are you on it properly
you don't have a good feeling about this
creation
well the wind turbine is a little bit
looking to the left yeah we can fix that
I don't think it would have really
been a problem
it's gonna hit the ceiling
I was thinking you know they need some
time to really get going
so I thought it would be fine but okay
I'll do it a little bit diagonally
uh try it
see if we got a first try
oh
I should have gotten on it too wait I
should have gotten on it too
why did I not get only two
I'll talk to him in a moment
of course it worked yeah
German always works
I mean I can I can go the same scruffy
way as before
and just climb up once I land in the
lava button
I guess I'll do the same creations
no no as I said it needs some time
Torpedoes usually need some time
to really get going so
this is gonna be okay but I think I saw
it uh scratch that magma a little bit of
course the MPC didn't mind but I will
maybe mind a little bit oops let's see
[Laughter]
why
we can't even pick it up
well
uh I still made it out to save blue so I
would say this was a success how does he
did he over there
I made the same thing and I failed
miserably
hmm
[Music]
ever in my design
it was scripted nah
he did he did not go completely straight
but he didn't fail as miserably as I did
no oh
no oh okay thank you
okay bye bye
we did decide quiz
the abandoned laborer complete okay
so there's a lot of materials here to
build myself something
um
angry can you hit that
yeah
okay I see there's gonna be more of that
[Music]
yo he looks like a phoenix
oh
my God okay how did that fail huh can
you just go straight in here thank you
oh some meat oh no
I don't know
I don't need this this is useless to me
you know
okay this [\h__\h] gets a headshot
or not
um
he doesn't see me still
wow
he saw me
oh no go away go away go away
[Music]
yeah
now he's got nothing oh the monkey's
still got the street left
more
yeah there is more
and now does he also help fighting
oh [\h__\h] yeah
uh
oh one thing I forgot to do is like cook
a lot beforehand oh well
[Music]
just go get him go get him unicorn and
my other buddy forgot his name already
what was his name
link yes that's my name
we got him tumbling out
[\h__\h] hell
what is this far
[Music]
sheesh
that one had a lot of armor on him
um
can't carry these
armor shark Shield
so we'll just claim them hmm
any more of my arrows here no oh and a
cobble Crusher hmm
I'm gonna look at my weapon lineup
um
don't think we need a flame weather
around here do we
so let's combine
Soul just Claymore
with the Cobble Crusher
try blunt weapons on Armored guys what
does blunt mean
[Music]
combination
looks stupid
that almost looks stupid but what can
you do
ah not Sharp
I thought that was kind of not sharp
looking though
oh
it broke
ah you know what I've learned a life
hack
um I watched a video how to get
overpowered in totk in early game yeah
and
um I have learned
some ways of doing it not that I will
attempt on doing it but
um
so there is apparently those lionels
in the underground too there's like a oh
a whole
um
what's it called
Arena to fight them in
yeah
and the materials they give you yo
very good for getting overpowered but
then what I mean what I've learned what
I what I find very useful for the future
is that when you combine something some
material that you know you find
very very very
valuable and you don't really want to
lose it
Well
turns out
when it's when a weapon says it's about
to break the best thing to do and I know
that I mean we already could have known
that but
um
before breaking
you put it away and then later on I
guess you can only do this until later
on when you find the pla shooting star
when you find the place
that can de-attach the materials that
you attached to the diffused weapons
then you bring it there and then I would
only mostly do that for Lionel stuff or
maybe to construct the real construct
the really strong construct things
is it over there
Terry Town
um yeah so for that I would do that in
the future I think before destroying my
my Lionel uh uh materials I would go
there
and uh get back or maybe also you have
gemstones on top of uh some weapons yeah
yeah
I would get that back and use it
endlessly because the weapon that you
merge it to will be damaged but the
material is not and you can use them
again and again and again endlessly
yeah
breaking them apart
basically kind of low-key repairs the
thing that you've used not the base
thing though okay let's wrap this car
look at it I guess we're saying sockets
to mine cards but let's see how far we
even get with this
the elevator trick moving objects up and
down oh yeah I know about it but I guess
I haven't been really making use of it
maybe we should take the mine cards on
the left track actually
if we want to get some problems
um
where is it
ah still there
my nose is so fuzzy with cat Harris
scars like people's watching it
trying to get rid of it
where'd it go
ah here
come to me
don't run
[Music]
clean your home you little [\h__\h]
with two long hair cats
I clean my home but the hair is they're
just like you know part of it
my bookable broke
you little [\h__\h]
give me my arrows back too
ball
there's a solution for that what don't
say shave my cats
that is the most ridiculous thing
that you could ever suggest why would I
do that take all that comfy fluff away
from my cats never
no
I want to ban everyone who who suggests
something like that like ridiculous
absolutely ridiculous
that's the best thing about cats they're
fur that's the best thing about them you
know how many nights I've been healed
therapeutically healed by their
fluffiness
huh every night every single night
so I will not
ever even consider such a stupid thing
why is that thing
why is that rolling
randomly okay
let's go
oh let's see how far we get
oh he's saying ah I'm coming now
what are we gonna charge up
I didn't even see him
she's Pro Gamer skills
I remember in breath of the wild getting
up the mountain was kind of rough
wasn't that
[Music]
should have cooked
foreign
[Applause]
I can't see it go away
[Music]
I can't sleep with you nice
are we gonna stop here
oh thank God okay here it stops um
we should be fine let's just stop
stopping there
okay
[Music]
that one's taken care of
it
don't roll down don't roll down we need
yourself
[Music]
okay
did we kill all the enemies you know I
might wanna
get rid of all these
suspicious openings nothing here only
the rock roasts well I don't need that
[\h__\h]
and obviously the one right in front of
us actually came with a perfect time
they know I don't have enough battery
yet to keep on going straight
done
oh
that place is interesting
[Music]
um
I've never noticed that before
what is that
wait
these look like geckos what's that
that's not what I looked at right
now
come on
Gekko legs
horrible
okay
we continue
those uh Fire Bats actually
pose a surprising threat for me
oh
[Music]
oh okay
so in the way I keep on hitting things
that I can't see
I didn't kill that one because he was
hiding
yeah
that wasn't yeah
oh oh keep on going keep on going keep
on going
why does he fly so high yeah
yeah good one good one
this feels easier going up than going up
the wind
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
okay
and we stop
I don't mind walking a little bit
two birds one stone yeah one stone for
real but not really Birds
remind us for Highland workers the red
substance that spouts from cracks in the
ground is called Bloom avoided at all
costs
coming into contact with Gloom drains
Your vitality if you touch it get away
from an Amelia and rest
resting Ayah if you rest outside
it heals back pretty quickly unlike when
you're down in the underground because
there's no sunlight
oh this is sundalian
because there's no sunlight it will not
heal back up I love oh
link over there
yeah yeah
okay
um I was gonna go there anyway
it's this way
okay are you gonna show me a cutscene or
why is this necessary
there's a shrine down there okay now
here have a seekers in order
for here
you lost [\h__\h]
oh no
Nani is it erupting
session die
die oh
what
is that that's not the gloomy stuff
though
wait what we're not getting a dungeon
not always just like foreplay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] how
um
the dancing is coming to me
what that thing broke out of the Cradle
like it was nothing I don't know
nah this is probably a foreplay and
we're going in afterwards aren't we
is that marble rock is it still alive
and there's three of those things hang
on no those are heads
so big how could something like that
appear out of nowhere like that I've
never seen anything like this on Death
Mountain Guru
if we don't take that thing out who
knows what will happen to Princess Zelda
but I can't exactly charge it from down
here any ideas no
ideas
can you know
oh there's a there's a shrine let's do
the shrine
[Music]
I've got better things to do it seems
this Shrine is sitting uh it sits some
it sits on the mountain
[Applause]
let's regroup yeah okay I have to I have
to fight it
what ah this thing
[Music]
it's got oh two batteries and still I
wonder
can we really use this properly
um we have to go up it has no torpedoes
when
anyway they're trailing for now
yeah it has a steering wheel but it's
legal how do we even take off
it has wheels
tonight
go down again
oh no try it okay
oh dear okay interesting uh the battery
is better whole wait are they endless
right now
because it doesn't show me
let's go up high
oh
[\h__\h] almost I felt like okay yeah
okay
okay one broken
oh mine
where's the other one here
okay wait we got this one down we should
be good let's fly it down can you hit us
yeah baby
oh
okay then that was sweet results there
must be more after that
must be more where that came from
I was gaming yeah
we can go in now can we
press f for faster
we did it I think what was that thing
anyway
if one person sound I walked up
somewhere around here
yeah
so I want to throw my rings in
you don't suppose you fell into that
hole wait is it on the ground after all
[Music]
thank you blank thanks for those 50
memberships by the way the other day I
saw that
that would be awful come on link let's
hurry let's turn there
[Music]
yeah
it's is he sure about this like there's
a lot of Gloom here
foreign
is
that what you're saying
oh
I mean it's a mountain maybe we're not
going that low discovery
ah Death Mountain Chasm I heard it's not
Chasm it's a parallel Chasm that's so
stupid I'll call it Saturn
study I don't know
oh God that's stupid
can I land on that what is this I can't
see oh
[Music]
uh where is he anyway
am I not supposed to join him I see a
blue light there oh another one
um we probably should oh what no
[\h__\h]
[Music]
we should probably go straight
okay to the big light
where are we
oh
okay
what is that
inside is that crying no it's just light
food okay it looked weird to me
examine more like a generic support
message that than one dedicated to you
what
why
why I want to dedicate it to me
[Music]
I I I I I need to understand
um the anatomy of volcanoes right now
because the lava comes from somewhere
right
but are you telling me that
like
how did the opening go deeper into TK
or was it always this deep lava always
came from down here or
i i i i what hmm
where does hmm
should I not think about it
the Caldera was deep but
only as deep as the mountain was tall
mm-hmm
and Earth it comes from the magma layer
oh yeah but there doesn't seem to be
such a thing now
I mean maybe there's a lava pool around
it
but
that makes does that I don't think that
makes sense
oh there's another different statue a
headless one
and okay
where did we lose him
and we have to find him oh but those
could be wrongs right
the other ones I was kind of questioning
but this one
I'm guessing it was a groan
oh there's another one pretty close over
there
oh [\h__\h]
yeah I guess it
when it erupts it goes it jumps up like
that but does that really it makes sense
oh wait he's there oh
history of the death didn't used to be
the surface I don't think this was ever
the surface no but
people back in the day knew about this
stuff and used it more and then somehow
it became forgotten that's weird right
you wouldn't forget about something like
this normally
um interesting though
who knew it would look like this inside
the Death Mountain you have no idea
now they look closer I see a whole lot
of those Red Rocks
I would princess download be down here
with all this marbled Rock Rose she's
really into it
she's just really into it she wants to
start a restaurant as well probably oh
oh we've had this before
okay
I'll be on my way
although I don't like that we're doing
this on the ground
I'm hearing things again but I mean you
heard that too all right link because I
definitely heard someone speaking just
now let's see I think I think it was
coming from that away
okay
maybe this has to do with Zelda yeah
I've got a heaping pile of questions for
him let's hurry where she is she
probably won't be there will she
pixel machine
okay well thank god
um I can use a lot of my bright Bloom
seeds
once we get over there
can I touch this stuff yeah okay
can I also break it
my fire alarm voice
[Music]
thank you
what
are those
I've noticed that they brought a lot of
like uh enemies
from oh
older Zelda games back
uh which is really cool because I I
found out those hands where also in all
the Zelda games so I'm assuming these
were also an old hotel games before
and those hands um when you in all the
Zelda games when you were in a dungeon
they would show up and if they catch you
you bring you you are normally brought
back to the beginning of the dungeon
remember
um
I think it's cool that they brought back
so many familiar ones
in tltk
you're saying that's just a different
answer I think those are at least
similar hands connected
you don't think those hands are wall
Masters I think so they're just like a
diff a little bit different version of
them
um
this stuff right
I mean if we find one here might as well
get something they might have new stuff
for us
okay batteries
nice I've seen those before
steering stick okay
a big wheel
okay okay
that's some good stuff for now
um
uh what am I doing
I want the scenes where are they
[Music]
wrong direction Maybe
nope not wrong direction
man
it's hard to find this [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
did I miss them I missed them
you can't blame me though man
nice butt
wanna get those pose
[Music]
well I hope the magma doesn't hurt you
but
when you run right into me
and you make it so that it activates
with a
well this stuff just is bound to happen
sometimes
um
I need more normal food I want to cook
maybe with my portable cooking pot maybe
I'll cook something
maybe I will
okay I will
does the portable cooking pot work
without fire or do we have to put fire
under it as well
see I have so many I should use it oh it
works on its own
then I have to eat so many and you know
you know
you know I want to do my my tomato
things you know they're really easy to
make
I collected more tomatoes one two three
four
I think I always did four maybe what did
I do three
oh okay there's too many that's too many
I didn't realize
what
the hell
it's single use
oh man goodbye okay I'll do it a few
more times I have so many anyway
[Music]
emergency cooking yeah it's okay like
when when will I
use this normally I don't use these
capsules much
so I don't need to be so stinky stingy
with them right
um
they were very wasteful nah I don't
think them the other things aren't
really one time use only
but just because of the game
how it works it disappears when you go
too far away and all that
I think I really need to wash my nose a
set in a second because like it's making
me go crazy so
it's so it's yeah
[Music]
okay I'll make one more
poof
uh
yeah keep on rubbing it it doesn't it
doesn't do [\h__\h] oh was that critical
was it a cooking crit
oh there's a lava Eva Rock mini baby
baby
okay
okay what's uh what's the best way to
get to where we want to go it's up there
right
I'm gonna climb
there's no ticklish
okay we can go up there
let's go watch it
okay one second I'll wash my nose I'll
be back in like five seconds or ten one
two three
foreign
[Laughter]
you heard me counting yeah yeah yeah it
was 10 seconds
okay hopefully that will help my nose
I find this very interesting
I wonder if that means that there are
more dungeons down here
or if this is like a
one-time only case
because I guess it kind of fits when you
go down the volcano
I guess it was not her legant
it was just you know it was just right
there like oh why not why not then
use this opportunity to make use of the
huge [\h__\h] underground that we have
created
um
straight
do I have to
go around these enemies or
uh
yes
it looks so dangerous
you can't go out
I'll try to climb
or should I
let me try
if we get in one hit then it would help
no
oh
okay now's your time
your bae
if they hit me
will I get the the heart problem
[Music]
oh then I should have cooked some things
that restore the hearts but I have like
this one at least at least one yes okay
so
so we do not want to be hit okay
don't touch me
okay
okay okay it's always gonna be careful
you know
[Music]
once we cleared the enemy camp without
taking damage
I am proud
um
oh there's one left there
uh
-huh he's kind of hiding
okay yes come here
eh nothing
no no no no no no no
you do it again
sometimes he just gets heated into
nothingness
hmm
wait wait
run away
[Music]
there we go but why does it not drop
anything is it because I shouldn't be
hitting it like this
thank you
oh the arrows shoot through my friend's
home
that's probably good oh no way
it took one
higher
that is silly
yeah I think if you break these things
maybe because it's too close up or just
because they don't like to be broken
like this
but it will unfortunately got rid of the
materials sometimes at least
um gonna rest now good night thank you
for coming by
and did it break
oh no it broke
soldiers brought sword
um
oh oh did the materials just fly over
here because it seems like
hmm
I'll get rid of this I guess because
it's burning anyway
unfortunate there's this little girl
that makes these
in kakariko
those are materials from the enemies
okay
guys
yesterday
I felt like I was a [\h__\h] teenager
again
like back in school
I don't go outside much you know that
but yesterday I went outside and I took
public transport
and on a train
something happened that I thought I
wouldn't have to experience anymore
I guess
um
where do we go straight can you break
this
try yes
you can we broke my flower
yeah
um
we're gonna cutscene or something or can
I talk
sheesh
no no no no no no they didn't ask before
I do no
uh what happened is
um
I was on the train I sat down behind
like two teenagers
thank you
uh
they were maybe I'm really bad at
guessing age of people oh [\h__\h]
but maybe like 15 16 or so none probably
not even 16
15. yeah around that age
and I sat behind them and I was looking
pretty on that day you know
yesterday
I did my makeup for once and I put on
cuticles and all that you know I was
feeling good you know I I knew I knew I
was looking pretty cute
and I think those little boys oh [\h__\h]
knew that as well
bye bye
um but they did a thing that I only
really experienced in in school back in
the day I noticed I was just looking at
my phone you know
but I noticed like pretty quickly soon
after I sat down
I think came flying over to me little
little like
rolled up pieces of paper really tiny
really tiny
to me and I knew exactly from what
direction that came I didn't see him
throwing it but like Through the Windows
reflection I saw them and their faces
you know
yeah it's so old yeah it is it's so
childish I thought okay if you do it
once and I didn't see it directly that
it was you I'll give you the benefit of
the doubt that you won't do it again
then they did it several times more
after the third time I took one
and I threw it back at them and I always
gave them like like really evil looks
like I'm gonna strangle you if you don't
stop I'm a [\h__\h] adult don't do this
[\h__\h] to me
don't be such a [\h__\h] childish
teenager
um yeah they contain it even after I
proved they had they act as if like
nothing happens
like I kept on I tried to pay attention
to catch them in the very moment they do
it but they always wait until I look
back down on my phone
eventually
I was like pissed off they were annoying
me I was like I don't wanna feel like
I'm back in school again
I'm out of this age
this shouldn't be something I have to
deal with anymore
so I said something I spoke up
I was like
hey you little shits can you stop doing
it that like how old are you
and they're like doing what and I said
you hit me with those little pieces of
paper at least five times and they're
like
well I don't know where that came from
do you know who did who did it yo you
did at least five times and they're like
what we also someone shot us two of it
too I'm like yeah I threw it back
because you did it and then they're like
oh we have to get off here anyway and
then they just get off the train
but
those little shits
hmm
so childish so annoying oh man at least
they weren't like oh you know wet
because I I remember in school time uh
these tiny pieces of paper they would
shoot it through
um
uh little I don't know rolls of paper
and make them wet first yeah spit balls
oh thank God it wasn't that
um
yeah even they would make their own roll
of paper or they would use some
straws but I think mostly they did it
themselves so it's like bigger and fits
for you
disgusting right
I know
little little shits those like literally
little shits right those bullets
harmless but it's not
it's not do it once okay don't do it
five times during the whole time I'm
behind you I will [\h__\h] you up
I'll call your parents
yeah so annoying
the light with the spell the darkness
[Music]
but only the Broken Heart
oh it's one of those Warriors up there
that freaked me out the first time I saw
them there's a lot of those
see another one over there
there's a lot of those around here
elastics uh shooting elastics boys
will be boys it's always the boys and
all that [\h__\h] boys will be boys you you
boys did that too probably a little bit
in school didn't ya
I know I know what you're up to
[Music]
um
let me get that
laughs
music
ocean what I do about this should I
fight them they look strong
only elastics
I was what Kiara I was
a weeb yeah okay I think those were
mostly holding back when it came to
those things
one thing that I always did was sending
messages with little pieces of paper
I am guilty of doing that but that's
harmless like I'm just trying to
communicate
okay
Don't Panic Don't Panic dude don't run
away I need you
guys
this is so useful right the holy [\h__\h]
yeah
if I go underneath the flower do I
do I get healed again even though I
already activated it does it always work
like that I wonder
[Music]
has no HP
yo
let me activate you
let's do it again
oh get up get up
[Music]
I was trying to dodge
I'll die okay okay he dies okay I was
saying that to myself yo exciting hey
it's nice to have like buddies to fight
with me
okay let's test out what I was just
asking
if I can go back to heal those hearts
I can't pick up any
of anything okay
lots of loot yay indeed
oh it does heal okay wonderful it just
takes some time
the Allies are great yeah
curious about what the others are gonna
do
oh
the the water one especially the one
other one and breakfast the wild you
could go up waterfalls right oh oh
there's oh
it noticed me from so far away
oh dear stop it
[Music]
just kill it once
okay the next uh Arrow hits you into the
trick though
do it do it
be careful
follow my leads oh [\h__\h] oh I should
probably heal myself
Yahoo
I'm down oh no he's dead
oh yeah they always drop a chest so
these ones are also uh Rob schleimer in
German
and I've also found out that these ones
you also had in previous
Zelda games
and I probably even met them
also I wonder why these are like the
only type of enemies that are not
infected by the stuff down here
that is mysterious to me too yeah
multiple Zella games right they they eat
you up and I think they steal your money
most elegant yeah and they store Shields
these little [\h__\h] are the big ones
so what am I doing
money and shields ah the help Slimer
yeah
it's a horror one in corrupted version
yeah but why do the small those little
babies why do they not get corrupted
foreign
collection of
materials here
that one could use
it's a 20 minute Laura video explaining
it explaining the house climber or or
why these ones are not corrupted
thank God I have these bows man
the frogs they're native animals and not
Ganon monsters negative to the
underground huh okay
yeah it makes sense because all the
other ones I can see they wouldn't be
native yeah
okay
sounds as long as they're not touching
all that Gloom they're probably fine so
it seems like they're smart enough to
not do that
they eat the flowers but hopefully they
don't eat the ones that I'm throwing
around here I need those guide me
Big Boy of rocks ah there's a big
version of them
okay where do we go next this way
I feel like we gotta go that way
but I want those pose over there pose
before hoes
doesn't that sound perfect
are you
was this place like a hot spring almost
but I don't think
I don't think uh I can touch the water
right
another light red really close
yeah I've been seeing them here and
there
oh whoa whoa
it's scary scary
there's quite a lot of them are in this
area
probably purposefully placed so many I
mean I know they're connected with the
shrines but I still feel like they're
purposefully
scattered so well in this area
come down here I want you to destroy
this
okay
maybe underneath some of those there's
something useful no
yeah game design thing I think they
purposefully
like paid attention to where they're
placing them although this area is just
generally bright Maybe
[Music]
anyway
remember my pizza friends
the one who helped me out with the pizza
[Music]
yeah so turns out he's now working
at a newly opened pizza restaurant
and it opened yesterday so I went there
to support my friend and his girlfriend
was there too so we sat together and ate
the pizza
fish
it was so good like it was like legit
um I think some of the stuff on the menu
wasn't like 100 percent
something you would see in Italy but
most things were
and they like are really really paying
attention to make things authentic you
know
yeah the pizza was so juicy like so um
so hydrated
it was so good
the dessert was really good so I had
like some kind of like cinnamon
chocolate like pizza dough
uh
um
agate
eat the dough fried fried pizza dough
but like it was kind of hollow inside
um
and those are like dipped rolled in
cinnamon and then sprinkled some
chocolate sauce Nutella and the white
sauce what do you call that again
top of it so yummy like churros I guess
so
it's a little bit comparable to churros
in some way
that was really yummy and I had
bruschetta as a starter
that was really good too
almost as good as the one I made no just
kidding it was it it tasted very um
professional
I hate how they are so they're so ah
Campbell
come flying at you very funny
that's so funny
[Music]
does it have garlic what no I mean there
must there probably was garlic somewhere
oh my gosh
but
that's that's what I was going
really yummy pizza but I don't think
I'll be going there much
[Music]
my friend isn't even working often there
anyway
I'm lazy
I know I know tracks are gonna throw you
off [\h__\h] hell
is that what I'm cleaning it up for
I mean oh yeah there's like a lot of
connections via tracks up there I see it
now oh at the entrance I see the
entrance let's go to the entrance
into the entrance we can go normally
although uh
yeah
more or less
[Music]
so I think it had no take away yeah
that's kind of weird they don't seem
like they wanted to take away although
you can take
the rest of your order if you don't uh
eat it all
you can take it with you but they don't
seem to do takeaways from like the
get-go you can't just go there and say I
want this forget for takeaway I don't
know why it seems kind of like a weird
business decision but okay
thank you
yeah maybe because they just opened who
knows what they will do in the future
oh yeah it was really yummy I still
actually have some leftover
so probably gonna eat it today after the
Stream
because I wanted to try as much as
possible from the menu normally I know
that if I eat like one pizza from a
restaurant
be full
I won't have space for a starter or
dessert
but
I wanted to eat the biscuit though and I
wanted to try the dessert too
so I already planned ahead I said I'm
gonna eat only half of this pizza and
then bring the rest back home yeah
officially we have reached it which
already seems like we were faster in
reaching the fire temple than we were
enriching the wind Temple
but maybe this Temple is even bigger
than the other one
is this why I heard the voice coming
from
I think so yes
yeah lots of tracks
the fight will probably happen with me
on a track won't it
Fire temple first floor
temple built up took a while but it was
great yeah that was good it was good all
right Temple's a nightmare oh no it's a
very disorienting Temple oh no okay
annoying to figure out this is the
longest dungeon by afar oh okay and good
that we saved some time in coming up
here
um
you guys better help me
what is this place why is it something
why is something like this inside that
mountain huh
There She is again yeah she wants the
big
Rock mate
please
[Music]
she's gone already
using my stream as a guide
okay okay
where did she go
stop rolling yes come in and open this
door
I mean
he doesn't even realize that we're not
only inside the volcano
we are also like in the underground I
don't think he knows about it yet does
he or he realizes
they're sapping up a head photo
oh yeah
oh it has like six head five heads
so I'm assuming when we do five things
activate five things in the dungeon this
will open up
I'm genius I'm genius
love you so much thank you you know boys
not the smartest fella yeah
cutscene worthy apparently oh [\h__\h]
did she get smashed
is that where the fight will happen
um
stuck in there we gotta hurry and help
her but how do we get in there
um well we have to solve five puzzles it
seems what is this
teleportation or oh yeah I guess so we
had this on the Wind Temple too
wait I should
Maybe
no don't open okay only a little bit
number one it closes again
what
did you say that the gate it moved like
oh just a little bit cooler
okay it will probably move only and like
more and more the more I
solve hear that there it is
foreign foreign
[Music]
no denying I heard it loud and clear
this time but who could it be and what
did I mean by Young Little Rock and in
German they literally say like
um
my my uh Offspring basically
they make it clearer and driven
I guess so they did tell us how to open
the gate so they can't be all bad right
so all we gotta do is unlock the five
blocks and then we get in there
you already said that
um
let's look at the map oh
we have five floors and in four of them
are these marks scattered throughout one
is pretty close we should get that first
if we can
ah and one over here
oh wait okay two are on this floor
one is over here
nothing's really here
just connecting
oh the tracks are also all on different
floors
okay well then while we're here let's
see if we can enter these two first
spooky music
holy Godly spooky music
[Music]
well I could see how this one
will be not accessible for me at first
um
okay two hours to finish okay well we've
played two and a half until now
thank you
so okay time wise I think will be fun
but that doesn't look like I can access
it yet so let's try
to take these tracks
that look like a trumpet
over here
is that
oh that's so nice are down here
oh okay
and I can get some more of those bows
that don't burn
but because of my
because of my burp friend I lost the
rest this will probably happen a lot
guys
foreign
sorry guys
for for needing some time with this
where is Flowing towards is this is it
okay here
it's not gonna move
no problem ah [\h__\h] can I make one in
between
really oh God
I don't think I can jump with this yeah
I see my biggest enemy in this dungeon
will be the lava
[Laughter]
YouTuber
I want to pick it up again
[Music]
up again
let me do a differently
ah okay yeah I can walk over that but
over that no I will have to jump
probably okay
all right
oh I left my friend behind
what is this
what
it turned the track
eh but does this one even matter maybe
it's just supposed to show me that these
things exist here okay
all right
there's already one prepared for us very
nice
and this one would go right we wanna go
basically just straight
this circle
How can I
I don't see where it continues but let's
try
no
I mean I feel like maybe he could but oh
there we go perfect
okay I want to get off here thank you
let's try
why is it bathing the cart
yeah he probably can yeah
another one of those
oh but they all get blocked off
[Music]
why can I not switch weapons all right I
guess not
oh we didn't even go for a second round
of throwing the balls
it's gonna stand here in case everything
falls down
genius
doing well yeah I'm doing well
thank you for asking I must I've cooled
down a little bit I feel like it was
hotter yes for me in the beginning
[Music]
can you do this now
okay we need some
platform for you to roll over or
or it was just an angle problem
was it an angle problem
[Music]
normally when he Bonks against something
he'll fly up
what if we Bonk you against
you can't no okay that backfired and the
treasure chest is gone
wait maybe here
[Music]
no need for a road maybe Road need for
me Ah that's why they were high trends
I mean
I could just
make the jump with the paragraph but I
don't want to risk any more of these
embarrassing situations anymore I solved
that by making platforms ah you mean
making it explode first of all
well
seems like a reasonable thing to do to
me
you're gonna make one here or not
oh made one on top
[Music]
okay okay we're good
okay so first seal huh yeah
yay oh a gun
I know exactly what to do with that
wow
okay first one was easy
think
yes
they talk uh when we're in the in the
temple
indeed there's lots to do
what are those oh can I pick them up oh
hi trans capsules
let's go
okay I wonder which one we should go
next Sports
come on I wanted to look at that item
this is still there
I think it's gone
okay
sad magma died
which one should we go to next oh wait I
went to the wrong direction [\h__\h]
we would go back apparently
Eva breaks off or it goes down it
probably goes down but wait we don't go
anymore down
also it goes up
okay now let's go to the second floor
I think that the other one that we saw
on the first floor is just not
something we can
oh there we go
we can fix right now
that will be for later
foreign
well let me look at the map again
because I want to pay attention to
no no
don't think we'll have to switch
anything there
maybe maybe here no probably not we go
down
the middle path
and maybe we can get off somewhere here
or worst case here
and explore a little bit okay
oh
why can we do that now yes
before we get going
[Music]
also the second
floor Zona riding the cars
well not on my track
[Music]
I have not even died
thanks for picking them up again
we've made it I think I hear sound
crackling let me fix that
um
nice shot right
well he's got a pretty big hitbox after
all
okay
yeah we are as expected here and
the thing should be up here we have to
go with a cart
we could
we could take the car that goes this way
jump off
and run over to this one because it
doesn't seem like it's
like kind of stops here but that's ah
because it's turned it's turned around
[Music]
I wonder what this place is for because
there is not a single of those locks on
that island
trying to deliver a Subway the cipher
subway map kind of yeah
okay so currently it would go to the
left side we want to go to the right
side
shouldn't be too much of a problem
you just have to oh
turn it around they can do it for us
[Music]
no
uh
wait
turn it off it always everything turns
on at the same time huh
thank you
no this time it didn't actually okay I
guess the wind turbine was still on
can you hit this please
and then
yeah we already want to get off here
I wonder
should I just jump off
uh
oh it stops okay
laughs
uh uh wait I have these these ice
thingies
okay
I never use this I've been like that's
the only thing I feel like I've been
Hoarding in this game so far
because I'm like oh this must be like
really really useful and and unvaluable
so let's not use it too much but then I
actually I threw away my fire uh sword
I think because I was like well
haven't been using this at all
so I guess I don't need it
you can pick up in front of rock guys
wow
I guess so yeah I remember that come
back for the wild true true
aha
oh so far I'm I'm feeling like I'm
making better progress than in the wind
Temple
police
foreign
gotta go you're creative and I see you a
plus this one thank you
[Music]
you know you're stacked to the teeth
when you're throwing away the yeah the
the elements or yeah
I feel bad about it but I guess you can
always make it yourself or you can get a
new one so
but when you kill the Mages does it um
do they respawn to make the majors too
they do right at least by the latest
that blood moon
they should respawn them yes come here
[Music]
I I thought I still had some space
mean
s
[Music]
okay oh
don't even have to make my own platforms
oh I could time reverse status
get over there that way
right
where are we going oh just over that
little Lake of magma and then it should
be there
yeah I did something like this in a
dungeon in a shrine I might have done
that Shrine uh
off screen
on my day off or it wasn't even a day
off oh
ah
these are more effective right against
the soldiers so I want to always switch
because I've also noticed they're really
not effective against normal enemies
always keeping a donut sword or spare in
case I need one of these
oh still alive
you did one on stream which was oh
really horror
oh oh really is that so
let's use the Zone I feel it's so nice
here
there you go
doubles on my shield
and this
activate and with that we got the second
one
[Music]
on stream Oh I thought maybe it happened
offstream the lava baths last time
[Music]
it's basically just a spy experience
guys
it almost happened again almost I saved
myself time oh
I made that on stream too tonight it
looks so good doesn't it
I want to make more special dishes
this is the porridge that you get from
the side quest by the way
um one two three four
yeah I jumped away I saved myself for
once
normally in these situations I always
panic and then it's over
okay we did that so
we are the only we want to go up to the
third floor
I wonder
where we could do that
[Music]
uh-huh
there's tracks here
ah
um
oh
we have
uh we have
this one that leads to this island ah
and if we stop here we can jump on this
one
I would hope
I mean
should work maybe
you had to brute force it why so far I
cannot relate so far I haven't been
feeling
I've been having so much troubles with
it
am I on the right track
yeah okay
we just got off right we don't have to
switch anything
or
wait can we switch right here
no wait never mind it's fine it's
probably fine
let me test it
ah yeah okay
then we want to take that path okay
we turn it around
yeah it looks pretty straightforward
thank God I returned to rails before I
went back
good thinking good thinking
why can I not read
thank you
Eagles are
um
[Music]
what are we gonna do about that my track
my my car is gone
there's no cart here
are you all right you can Shield
surfings I've seen
yeah that's so [\h__\h] is there another
card over there yeah I see one
that's so [\h__\h] um now I have to learn
how to shoot can you do it even with
double Shields
well desperate situation is called for
desperate measures right
is it not gonna work if it's straight
but
um when you have the momentum to do it
here yeah
if you run it works
okay I thought I was falling down but he
kind of linked into it
okay thank God
don't think I can do an upwards though
but uh
we'll change the track from a distance
because if I do it from too close I
guess it just gets all wobbly and crows
me off
I think it's possible but
um
I better not risk it again
now we go up
and when we go up
we just get off here and then find our
connection
the one that leads to here okay
always gonna be aware of where we are
and where we're going and as long as we
do that there shouldn't be too
Troublesome huh
easy easy
I like it so far
oh
are you selling Minecarts and stuff
yes
but normally not you don't want to sell
so highly in fact wait wait
Tim I should have stopped him
yeah help me help me out here oh no
[Music]
why are you
guys
oh come on
okay we get his weapon it seems like it
uh Captain can start with porn
[\h__\h] off I win
well I'll drop it
okay
rockets and hydrants
15 fuse attack oh didn't have that much
well
nice
so we're not buying we're stealing
where are we going
for now we'll just go this way
and hopefully from a distance we can
deal with the track okay
probably behind you
what are you gonna do about that huh
try again I still believe we do it from
here
I don't know if we can do it
yes come in come on yeah there we go
thank you Daniel birthday
oh wait you also sent a super chat okay
I'll cook then I'll wait until I read it
but for now you get a happy birthday
[Music]
okay
and we just want to activate it from a
distance again to be safe because I'm
scared
very scared
wonderful
[Music]
huh
and then where do we get off uh
we wanna get off before it turns like
when it turns
then we'll lose the card though
maybe we can time reverse it
when that happens
okay
uh I will jump up now
okay and
stop it this way we don't lose our car
to The Voice
it would have gone
over there and fallen down no we don't
want that oh
can we open that with you
wait a second can I not enter here yet
maybe you have to enter From Below
we might have to enter from below with
Ascension because I already see there's
like a lot of this
is that even possible I'm I'm seeing a
big open
there's a shrine in there
is that a shrine
twisting
that means I made it to this place for
nothing
and I climbed
climb I could fall down here no will I
regret it
if if I go down here and I it turns out
I can't Ascend up then we're kind of
lost here because there's no rails that
go away from that platform
well we'll see
leap of faith
[Music]
but it's close wait this is just
am I going down to the first floor I am
ah only the
only the walls are like considered
second floor [\h__\h]
[Music]
and thus I am back on the first oh [\h__\h]
that was that that's a big setback
ah damn it climb back
and look that's possible
and it would be too easy if I could have
sent here
um
no way
[Music]
there's an elevator to the third floor
an elevator
what
elevator like maybe
like we were already here right
and did the one that's there
because there were two
after activated that's activated from
the top or so ah
you guys should have told me to not go
down
a cheese it somehow
[Music]
oh man
foreign
how high can we climb
where would we want to climb
maybe up that yeah
update
dreaming for
uh
supporting walls
oh Rockets well I guess so
I'll try climbing up here I might have
to eat some stamina food but
we're fit
wait let's change but I can't change it
I only have the top of the climbing gear
they'll [\h__\h] me up
[Music]
can you I think you might be able to
stand here
do we want to risk it
what busy
[Music]
cheese
resting
ah is that possible
can you climb like that
sheesh
okay
okay where's this elevator that you have
to uh activate I would think over here
or here
they're not even connected with the
first Florida though behind me
I suddenly lost my confidence in this
Shrine
I'll go
I'll go here and then wait wow we came
from here
um
can I not do anything on the third floor
yet anything meaningful
I mean we can activate the elevator
right I just don't know where it is
I'll go
oh no I'll go this way
because the other one I think we would
lose our heart
let's go
I said let's go
[Music]
huh
saved
safe space
and then
we're just circling back though
[Music]
is there an elevator here actually and I
missed it
that would make sense because this one's
connected at at least
more or less
maybe it's like
this thing
yes
ah okay
currently the track is connected right
okay I think so it looks like it's gonna
happen yes it better be
actually that one goes up
that gonna Circle it
huh
but the other way
huh cause like is this path
so but we just went this way so if we go
back
does it go up this way I think
so we didn't necessarily make a mistake
ah
down now so if we'll fall down or
something we can go up
yeah yeah no problem we can change the
tracks here I see the connection now
thank you
okay it is the other way would that make
some sense
that makes no sense
I'm supposed to connect
those rails
uh-huh
[Music]
and then then it's the fourth floor
ah and then it turns around and brings
me to the Middle Island on the fourth
floor okay
now I'm cooking it can rotate even more
I want to rotate too
and why Allen I want it to be
oh
wait that makes sense too
depending on where we want to go
where should I go first
one even is there
a connection I guess the Middle Island
to on the fourth floor then go to this
point
but the way we have it now
sorry leads to this island where then we
can go this way no no no wait what at
least this end where we can go to this
one okay so both make sense I think
you didn't realize it could fully rotate
oh
oh no
closest
is a classic what do you mean
am I safe to go
[Music]
I hope so
I hope I hope there's not a proper order
that I should be doing this in
where I can't get this one verse but the
other one
we gonna make a full circle
or I jump off here but I guess
we should maybe
do the circle
ah and shoot something oh
are we going down hopefully not
only a little bit
can we stop here
put the weight
bring me back at least one of those
[Music]
why no why no cancel
why can't I not cancel uh-huh
okay
I'm so confused I thought you canceled
this uh rewind with Al
been working
weird
perfectly prepared for us
okay
[Music]
is it for me to climb up
let me look around
[Music]
there's not much to look around
uh but I'm guessing I can't do it from
the bottom but let's stand in there
again
can we
angle
why why are we making those
oops
cheese
oh
whatever try
[Laughter]
does it attach
oh it does
well then wait we can turn the bottom
one too can we
oh
yeah
why
yeah okay
dad
maybe that already works
[Music]
what
eh
um
okay he goes up way too high
ah
custody
just saw the same height
maybe wait maybe in that case we don't
even have to lean it onto the Rock
if that's already enough momentum enough
height
I probably don't have to agree
[Music]
ment will work
maybe a bit further behind
um we'll see on now let's see
again
no now he goes over it again oh okay
then maybe closer is actually
before he gets before he gains too much
height
makes sense
peace
[Music]
left okay and one is also
um
no as on the fifth floor I looked like
it was there too
[Music]
um
but
it seems like
sorry there are no tracks that lead to
it unless I can still change something
but
no but this day they go to the fourth
floor maybe I can raise those two I'm
confused
it's changed here too
ah wait wait wait wait wait wait use my
ramp
[Music]
okay sometimes it shall be mine
yeah that's exactly what they wanted me
to do
it's so interesting
can I build myself
a
bridge is that what they want
foreign
I guess I'll I'll stick one for the sake
of weight
it's probably a minecart could do the
trick too
[Music]
we can no one ever gets you there you
did the same but it's super finicky
I'll prove you wrong
[Music]
you're scared me
will it fall over
probably too steep
it doesn't fall over yet but it's
already like wobbly
we build it on the flat ground and move
the whole thing at one time
and move down let me add one more here
oh my God the bgm
already gives me gun on vibes
scary
you didn't build a bridge
nothing you have two and you can skip
most gaps yeah
[Music]
let's see that's already pretty high
uh
hard to see but
okay
I try please don't feel good something
[\h__\h] I can't climb that
[Music]
going back abort Mission needs bigger
Bridge
[Music]
how could I have extended there
can I have stand here
you have any steaks tonight's devices
please hold it down
oh what steaks no I don't think so you
mean in Pillars no
come on Arceus which sounds sucks
I'll add one more and I should be enough
[Music]
oh wait maybe
goodness
um wait I'll I'll check in a moment
where it is
it's not too late because like
it's limited but you can rewind ah there
it is
laughs
ah it did it separate
no okay
[Music]
I could probably try to be quick and run
over it while it's doing this but
but holding it
also
works for time reversal just holding it
[Music]
oh
okay
cheese cheese
[Music]
I hope we don't ever have to use that
again
hey can I grab it
[Music]
well
well if if we have to then we'll even do
it a different way or we build a new one
oh but
ah we get to the first one
nice wait should we look at the top
first what what they have at the top
here
thank you
it works
hey yo
wait no I thought it would be open and
we could uh wait
we'll find a way we'll find a way we'll
find the way we'll find a way
seems like
it's closed off here
and where are we
can we not just fly in I think we can
probably just fly in
right right
look if we jump down here uh
that's where we made the connection
right yeah okay
I didn't [\h__\h] up I didn't [\h__\h] up I
didn't [\h__\h] up see we're good we're good
I just wanted to save maybe you know
since there's a hole here too maybe if I
do it uh
here
should be good
ah I know it would be worth going up for
something even if it's just a chest a
hat
[Music]
was there something there was that the
floor that I was looking at oh yeah
[Music]
yay we made it to this one then we'll
we'll uh maybe oh use the Ascension to
go back up or we will have to use the
um
[Music]
oh we have to use the elevator we'll see
yeah so far I mean I don't feel
like it's been so difficult maybe the
boss is really difficult
oh my God only one left yes
why does he not say good all come on
say it's pickle
have confidence
you gotta have confidence
okay can we
[Music]
that's too high is it
what about these doors ah
does he say it in English
[Music]
okay of course it doesn't work
he does
okay that's the first time where I have
to say German VA lame because they have
it in the script but they don't say it
but they forget
why is it video so scary please stop
which is scary
okay before I go
and continue since I'm already here
um I will
I want to go to a goddess statue
somewhere else
because I think where do I see it
um
I think I have enough for something
where do I stand
[Music]
I'll be here
ah wait maybe the key items
seven
I could get at least one
[Music]
okay I wanna do that
I only remember like two goddess statues
I think and one I really remember is
here
I'll be back
[Music]
yeah I'll be back don't worry
there was one in golden Freddy I didn't
find it
his VA is just some guy and not cute in
English really
so the godo seems unfitting as well
next to the chief's home
I didn't find it
oh well it doesn't matter where we go
um
should I get a heart or heart or stamina
guys
foreign
you guys are so Pro stamina man
I don't get it
[Music]
there's so many hearts I need to get
ah one question for the clocks let's
assume there's 900 again I think in
breath of the wild wasn't it a a thing
that
um
after a certain amount of upgrades
you
uh don't get
the bag upgrades anymore right
and you got what did you get money or so
I wonder if that's the case again
I know how to fight I don't need Hearts
don't need Heights if you don't get it
cheeky cheeky chickens
uh there's a thousand oh my God
you only need 450 in the last game
so I will talk but that is the case
one more for four wheel yeah I only need
uh one more shrine
to get that anyway I'll cook a little
bit while I'm here
wait I should be able to make the curry
I think
let me look at my recipe
uh this one no that's not it that's the
crap I don't even think I have a crab
is it this
no
okay
that maybe I didn't uh save it like that
wait how do you make her I need rice
maybe I can make this too honey sugar
butter Apple wheat
honey sugar butter Apple
honey
wheat butter
maybe I don't have sugar
ah
sugar an apple
apple pie
energl
okay how do I make
wait do I still have rice
wheat
the rice looks like the wheat
I Hylian rice
is it just the spice
and the rice
I want to look it up if you guys can
tell me
meat salt and rice for udon
wait how do you make curry
only spice and rice
tutk curry recipe
um
any vegetable hanging rice and go okay
we still need a vegetable
any vegetable says
carrot or pumpkin
does it have to be that because the
online it just had anything
but I do have a enduring carrot
okay it's a meatless
meatless Curry and
them oil it looks like there's a pumpkin
there but it would probably work with
tomatoes because there's also tomatoes
on on the picture
mmm
I think that was a something with stamp
bulbs that I wanted to make but I forgot
what it was
wait
what else
was there the crap I don't have a crab
but this one I think maybe I can make
the the shoe so it's uh the meat that
looks like a steak
the pepper the wheat the butter and the
milk
and butter
[Music]
gold on this one
the milk
wait
as we read okay and a Pepper please
the babyloni
spicy Meats too cold this isn't so
needed but you know I want to make those
recipes can I look at my recipe
somewhere
I'm here
the ones that I do know I made this by
accident
apple pie
um
these are the things I made wait I never
made this
did I
ah maybe I got it from yeah I don't
remember getting it either
it's rock salt
it's not made it before
[Music]
rock salt and meat
oh
ah she said no that's not it
God this would look so good
aren't you guys getting hungry too
looking at this
oh they also show the the potions
oh yeah the fairy tonic that I have I
got as a present I think
okay I make some more things with the
tomatoes just so that we're covered
mm-hmm
I should mention
hold hope
okay I just want the four Hearts ones I
think I I need those a lot
I'm making breakfast
um
today because it was Sunday I was
thinking yesterday already when I was in
the supermarket like I don't know
whether I should eat for breakfast
tomorrow because I've been going like
almost daily to get like croissants or
other things
but I was like well if I don't get it
fresh I don't want to eat it so I bought
those pancakes again okay but I'm only
gonna eat it you know only ate it today
and I might eat it again
tomorrow until you know it's gone did
you just
oh look who it is I recognize that face
anywhere any and any face I know is the
face of a friend please link help
yourself to anything don't you want to
like give me a quest you should probably
avoid this area in particular something
I hear sometimes I hear a creepy voice
coming from this hole sounds like a
demon growling no one else clams to hear
it but I certainly do I kind of already
awaken some Demon when I busted up this
wall my and my even bigger worries that
the demon has it out for me now
hmm
I'm very curious about this now
you don't need to justify pancakes thank
you I felt like I needed to a little bit
but you know
okay you give me
confidence
let me sleep a little bit
[Music]
I'll check it out privately probably
because it's a side quest
frozen raw croissants
oh Benders blood Moon's list great
shell out Zelda
does that mean in the temple everyone's
back too
prefer waffles waffles are good too you
know but the waffles that you can like
Buy
um
like already finished the supermarket
are are not good
not what I would want to eat for
breakfast
but yeah
the pancakes are just easy difficult to
get it wrong
oh here I suppose
let's go back
and so far I haven't been
that much disturbed by the blood moon in
critical situations
only one seal left and for that we have
to go up very high
sorry for the wait buddy
uh Which floor was it we did the one on
the first floor we only have one left on
the fifth floor
um
we'll probably figure it out if we go
with the elevator
if I find where I put the L word
oh yeah the enemies are back happy happy
there it is
[Music]
oh there's some
armor here in case you're not oh really
dire situation how did I not see the
chest
[Music]
who knows I always welcome arrows now
is the boss hide guys you guys told me
that
oh it constantly moves
you guys told me that you some of you
had troubles with the
dungeon itself but with the boss no
okay
I'll probably just smack unable at him
several times
oh that dude is back
oh he will he will can we stop him
I dare you so do not do that
no no no I need that
iPhone fuse for a good use
since this one's like the strong one he
gives me his strong materials again
okay
uh but since I left does that mean that
certain things that I prepared are gone
wow wow wow we have to get up
there but then yeah my question was even
if I go up to the fourth floor here
and maybe here I can actually use
Ascension
Maybe
I yeah I refuse his views Fusion
because it is an intrusion
of my quest
[Music]
um
I guess I'll just try to go first up
here
there's why is there three different
parts
why
why do three different paths all leader
this one's broken I don't know if I can
fix it this one I can definitely take
this one's also kind of broken
should I take the middle one first then
that one's broken for sure
that one's also broken
can I even fix that
[Music]
what
this ah
[Music]
okay
that's what we gotta do
[Music]
and this one has no
wind turbine
smart good eye really it's no big deal
no big deal
some things look a little bit confusing
but it's manageable
back up to the fourth floor
uh
uh I still have the spare
he didn't drop a normal weapon
now I want to pick up the other one
ah
I've played with stuff like this in the
dungeon with these Bridges you know
there was like this dungeon with the
with the with the car
I don't know if you guys know which one
I mean
[Music]
can you do that a little bit higher or
let me just attach the bridge first
how
[Music]
is it even long enough it doesn't look
like
how do I
eh it's not long enough even though I
had a really smart idea here to help
myself out
I thought why doesn't that let me cancel
anymore
I could use the cards to connect it even
more but that seems oh but this looks
obviously like that's what they want
I find that stupid
swapped oh that's why okay
you don't need to connect this do I want
to so that he rolls over
and destroys the
what is the The Rock properly
is that how I want it anymore
that's not how I wanted it's still
hanging
maybe he'll roll down and then up
are you so slow yes come here
he went all the way up but even the
stone was kind of used as a ramp but I
guess I can go there
I can just go straight up
we're gonna do it or what you know Bob
[Applause]
[Music]
why not come here
can you not climb
[Music]
[\h__\h] l
uck
I can't jump when I'm in this
time rewind
no that sounds too stupid too
complicated like why
why I know I don't think so
um
if we get it out of that
okay what
[Music]
maybe a lake and now attach this
oh
look what happened
what the [\h__\h]
it's attached itself again
don't want this
the angle actually might be helpful
are you seeing what I'm seeing
but maybe he will fly too high again
you know
[Music]
finally yes
I mean at least he's not going
put it all the way using himself
now he explodes against that
[Laughter]
pain gonna come here come here
[Music]
you can't it's just it's just stupid but
this works no no no no no no no
no no no
I want you
yes
he'll only do it for my pillows
[Music]
I feel like these bangs are so obviously
for you to connect it
that's why they had these hooks on them
don't you think
oh it's actually already nicely
straightened out
oh [\h__\h] hell
I hate this solution and what did I even
do that for I thought there would be
something there
[Music]
what did I do that for
is it to trick me
Monty did oh
what are all these random capsules doing
here
[Music]
uh-huh
wow okay that was perfect what is that
we're still on the fourth floor
[Music]
and
the thing is right there
but obviously
we won't be able to just simply Ascend
up to that but what is that box for
[Music]
really
but it only goes like this high
should I rewind you know ball and climb
on
I can't even do that
[Music]
hold down
what happens if because eventually what
if you mess up like me
and it loses its memory from falling up
from there
um
uh
[Music]
that maybe it comes back you you just
climb
or maybe it comes back when when you
throw it into the library so sometimes
these items respawn when you really need
it
okay we're climbing
maybe that's why they made this wall
like this in case you [\h__\h] up
uh
[Music]
I have no patience right now for this
um foreign
[Music]
that restores eight hearts
I don't want to okay I can't make it
but can I stand on there no no way ah no
I
have it let's go back down and stand a
little bit longer
[Music]
okay chill
why so forgiving unbelievable
okay where are we this is scary
you know can you make it up here
okay again yeah
[Music]
oh the last one has been opened and now
all there's left is foreign
[Music]
I don't think it's even been two hours
has it
don't think so
is there a shortcut
isn't it this thing
huh
there's like a lot of holes
could have gone through those windows
let me peek
a little sneak peek
I don't know
oh further than expected you think so
yummy I'm so scared going in here though
spot is easy
[Music]
I don't know like magma bosses lava
bosses fire bosses they always scare me
it opened oh my God smash those red
rocks and rescues that dude
it's not the right Zelda
I don't think she's even she's like a
ghost so she probably didn't get smashed
she probably just you know
okay oh wait oh
why does that remind me of Metroid
[Music]
she's not our Channel
dollar stores
she just disappeared into like air
oh
I guess we'll continue doing what I just
did a lot of times oh
oh oh
maybe not maybe it goes up there
sometimes and that's when we have to do
that to hit it
it repeats
down here
we just hit it the legs
last minute goes up to five and then we
have to shoot it when it's up there
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
pulling
I did not say the corner the dwarf the
fairy by the way out of Interest
it's one Theory
ah
okay get up get up
okay
I don't know but uh whatever I'm doing
it works I did a lot of things
I was trying to switch weapons but as
long as I'm like in here
no okay
it's too easy
um let's get a strong weapon 15 18.
should be good
still stage one
good good good
ah no I wonder if we can
drop it on him hello
hello come here come where are you where
are you
you are still rolling up oh okay
man there's so much to do but so far I'm
like handling as well
okay no no time will be stopping right
now but that's okay
I understood the assignment we all do
I stumbled
but no problemo
is he different now or still doing this
everyone is very powerful yeah
mm-hmm
I'm on my way that took some time
[Music]
oh okay thanks too
we surely parachute it down right
before he's doing that okay now you're
up there that now is now
what
bring it bring it back up
what am I doing what are we doing
what are we doing
uh
where are you oh my God what's happening
baby
[Music]
ah
that's why I couldn't shoot
yeah okay I thought maybe I had a chance
to hit him like normally
now there was a chance indeed but I
missed the window
pass out
he'll be
is it happening where is
he'll be better to have like a an
overview
um
go this way baby
almost used it so that we can make it
explode
in his uh on his leg at least
came on
whoa what what does he do when I when I
do when I do that nothing in particular
uh no it hit one of my rocks
she just gets angry
come on you know ball we have to
oh we have to hit him we have to get a
hit yeah
so well
[Music]
right up here maybe
uh
come on damage
[Music]
some shots in okay
okay okay good stuff I'm still chilling
ah it doesn't count
fulfill teams are what
else
do your thing you know boy I hope you
hit I don't
know
yeah that doesn't work
oh wait run run run run run
run run run hi
hi
send them out the door maybe
let's go
let's go shot
nice
okay I wait I I I did it for a little
bit too long
maybe just I don't know randomly sending
you there now I was close
it's a fun fight though I gotta say
hello can't see
okay
pray for him
[Music]
we missed we missed
go go
[Music]
I believe I believe I believe I believe
hey he went through
his leg
s
where are you right now okay
um
okay next time next time
next time
[Laughter]
oh
[\h__\h]
get up get up oh we'll explode on him
[Music]
a lot of time
I feel like a few
a few shots of an arrow would do the
trick though
um
[Music]
what's right there you think
guys that was a little fun boss I mean a
bit okay I think you could probably do
it better than me but
did the one thing that we definitely
wanted to do this time
help the groans
will we see Zelda though
[Music]
after this what I'd like to do is get
another memory from the geoflips Maybe
what are you playing here's a king I
mean a girl and asked him on the ceiling
so Jackie
right
it's mostly a luck thing and I was
thinking maybe I was doing it wrong with
the whole sending the Rocks back is it
really only to open your path because I
was hoping that maybe if they're up
there they can explode where he is but
then he moves around so and you have to
look at so many things like where where
you send the grown Ball
but it could probably work right
to blow those up too oh
oh
but aren't they kind of like in the way
and then you would explode too because
you're right there I don't know
no but not anyway and how I did it
worked oh and we get a high tier where
the [\h__\h] up keep on forgetting you get a
heart from the bosses nice
I know where I am because I know where I
am no I didn't really know you climbed
over them
my way was better yeah I can imagine
climbing on top of them would take a lot
of time and stamina basically best way
is move them away and already run
and then immediately either send
uh him away before they land or right
after your your you have the path open
no but they're fun fun fun I was cooking
with everyone really
I feel like we don't use the rewind
Bunch so far
um for this at least it helped um
can I take oh you want to take oh yeah
right they take it
your free airpod
only one though but it should be enough
yeah you have to wait for him to
recharge if you use him to destroy those
bombs
I I first thought it was a mole on the
side of his face but I realized now it's
uh his ears
does he also look at it on his ankle oh
yeah memory time
you know
ghost oh
foreign
oh
you guys yesterday
[Music]
Asylum go home and get seemed
Ishmael
is
your test the mysterian style
um
[Music]
High rule
foreign
[Music]
on the left foreign
oh
I guess the one on the left was the same
as Ronaldo like the same race but with
the ears upwards and it was better
no I know I know this is
laughs
[Music]
maybe her coming here
a seeing that was a vision too
well she seemed evil
[Music]
holy stuff
muffled again
foreign
[Music]
we get it on the Belt as well
oh he got that rope
oh man
[Music]
foreign
Airport
second one baby
hey
and he gets the wrestler belt after all
oh this one's better this one's cool
yeah
it is for the hair
[Music]
yeah
no problem guys I got a keyboard
[Music]
thank you
brofist
[Music]
you know who devised it is
no
[Music]
ble no
hot my arm feels hot
oh and your ring things
[Music]
yeah
we're not getting 10 right
there's 10 fingers but I can't imagine
doing this 10 times
[Music]
only on one hand
yeah and then together we're six
like them
um Fire Emblem engage copy
good stuff
very successful today so far and it's
only been four hours
there is the option that we ended and
read super chance
or we continue
at least maybe getting the memory would
be nice
oh
back into normal meets at least
[Music]
we keep rolling cause I can't stop
yeah so far I really like the story I
like it
no
this is very moving and satisfying
amazing one of root for all those kids
all those descendants
yeah
yeah very interested to learn more
it's so good right so far
nice
well are they selling at normal prices
now
I don't know if I would buy it anyway
though
is it worth it now
how can hardly believe you're making me
worry like that
please don't be mad at president
it's okay it's Lego I'm the one who made
such a mess of things after all if I had
just been more careful
you said you'd put corn City back to
normal and you did
oh you're the hero of current singing
you are when you made your noodlecon
you're still now
it was his Destiny he had to do that
with me
does the old guy not understand what
fate and destiny is he should he looks
like a guy who gets it
he won 50 plus weapons you can get one
right in this Village a hole
ah
and we have to thank you to link you got
rid of the marbled Rock Rose then Smiles
are coming back to go around city I keep
imagining what might have happened if
you hadn't broken that mask I can't even
think about it
Princess Zelda wasn't angry we ruined
the mask machine oh
actually weren't able to catch up with
her it was also strange now that I think
about it it seemed like she was walking
toward that giant monster by choice
after that we didn't see her again
oh president you know do you think that
maybe Princess Zelda is one of the bad
guys oh [\h__\h] they're starting to doubt
princess salad this is bad this is
really damaging her reputation
thank you
Belden
you definitely learned how to be bolder
bold for this dungeon despite some rocky
patches I lava I love to watch but thank
you
like maybe the Dan monster was
pretending to be Princess Zelda
no way
hang on come to think of it my ancestor
was talking about the stage of time and
that Sage looked a whole lot like
Princess Zelda so maybe she is the Royal
Zelda but my ancestor lived a really
really long time ago so that would be
weird but if it is true then that means
that was the real tell that we were
following
um don't think about it anymore it's
gonna break your Rocky head my answers
just said oh but that was so long ago
and Princess Zelda could she have been
the railing or not or maybe I feel
confused go to real or not we need to
find Princess Zelda and ask her
ourselves
yes I agree
last week is a funeral code to search
the area around the city for any leans
on the princess even if you're not here
with me we'll still be connected link
You Can Count On Me
[Music]
yeah
we got the bow of uniball
enthusiasm great and oh but let's not go
digging up any more weird rocks you got
that
hmm
so I wonder if the caves with all that
stuff have something different now
um
lizard legs
I remembered something about that other
Zelda when we were mining marbled Rock
rose on the north side of the Death
Mountain she said something kind of
funny she told me not to go the lizard
licks that's a go there I don't know why
a bit surprised to hear the words lizard
Lakes coming out of your crawl don't
much hear about them legs these days but
I still wait is the it's the next memory
and ideally next memory there
because I don't remember seeing the pure
pad memory anywhere so far
oh nice hidden content so maybe it's not
there
this will be water temple that's what
I'm thinking yeah
one brother hunts what the other brother
hides two lizards fighting over what's
inside
not everyone knows this but the laser
Lakes are also called The Lizard
Brothers I searched high and low for
them back in my younger years always
thought the treasure must be there
somewhere then all might hunt Death
Mountain blue is top it was covered in
lava before you say boom boy I forgot to
know about my switch
um
halfway up the Death Mountain
back on me to the north side
ah
that's a side quest I don't know if I'll
do it
on stream
but if I do I'll report to you guys how
it was 300 I think it was uh 500 before
and these ones I think they were a
thousand no they were more and now
they're a thousand
what
[Music]
weren't they a thousand before
or more
the prices didn't even change
hey y'all
a [\h__\h]
yes okay now they'll tell me where it is
huh oh wait they don't have to tell me I
already know
after hearing there may be some out here
like I've been wondering have you found
a jail group in the South and Alden yet
cell phone
I don't know oh
the map in the Forgotten Temple that
looks like a stone there we go that's
the one I need
we intend to investigate that geograph
as well okay perfect south of Belden
how did I not see it though Elden
what is the whole region is called Alden
right so South look here
that would be rid of Skyview Towers so
we could just go there now
we should be hopefully accessible from
there
I feel like I haven't seen it yet
I should check my map
get a better idea of that
um
yeah I mean roughly
um it's
well
oh
somewhere South
and it looks like there may be like a
body of water close by
oh that one that one probably I should
be right there
[Music]
okay
let's go up
oh I can't see it meaning
foreign
looked like it was like here
connected to the lake Verona
am I blind
let's switch gloves
[Music]
easy easy easy they're probably all
pretty easily accessible with Skyview
Towers
maybe with some simple exceptions to
couple
there's a tower
okay
so can I only equip one of the time of
these dudes
oh no it looks like baby both
stupid doesn't work like that
I can use both won't that be like
scrambling uh maybe then they will be on
different buttons
he's an a the other one will be a
different button so I don't accidentally
do something wait
um there's a stone probably a Croc up
there but
[Music]
ah there
what is the info somewhere here
[Music]
oh
you know as well as granny you know
power yeah I know I go up to the crack
first
impa not here this time this time or
that oh
little tree
there was actually one on the other one
as well and I didn't
I didn't even attempt to lift the stone
I have to do that sometime
does she not want to check it out this
time with me
is she not gonna be there all the time
I guess I watch it alone
oh no he's not here
okay
I'll I'll text her
why is this one a whole pyramid eh
let's look at the memory
Thanks for the Memories even though they
weren't so great
[Music]
okay
oh
yeah oh
isn't it is
foreign
[Music]
oh they're like
doing stuff with them
endless Alice this is
[Music]
contest
videos
I'm charging it
is
[Music]
um
foreign
scarf
[Music]
Ace
nah
into ascent
Horizon we don't want her to become
something
[Music]
foreign
so not literally a dragon
so convenient
oh no it could even this is
[Music]
good either it's literally or not
literally if it's not literally it would
explain why she's acting up you know she
lost her soul for the sake of being able
to travel and give us hints
that's why we've been seeing her doing
weird things
that wouldn't make sense
it's literal while we did see a big ass
Dragon right in the beginning in the sky
but I can why would that be her then you
could go straight up to her now
more or less
cable here instead
does this work can I see if it's
connected by cable
okay now it's charging
yes hmm curious
very curious isn't it
I was fast we did so many big things so
fast today
damn I'm maybe it's because I'm doing my
homework so well
what do we do next
again
we can make our way
already to the next area
oh no
should I
crazy bird
oh man
maybe I should ask that bird to join
horotori
um then you can progress on Joshua's
Quest Joshua Joshua
yeah I mean there's more main quests
than those two so yeah we can check out
a different one
um joshia mean
hmm
yeah yeah we can spend some time on the
Underground stuff
sure
was that an emu
emu emu for Ian free let's go
all right
that makes sense
the mystery one is important wait which
one the one I just uh selected
um
great fairies ah yeah but for the great
fairies you have to do this like stable
side quest I think
I think they'll just do that off stream
can I get something from the Kodak boss
let's see
[Music]
okay yeah mystery okay okay
you have more clothes than usual
you're selling the flame breaker one
I found the full set of this in kakaliko
I think was this radiant shirt
show a glowing bone pattern
s are stacking each layer to routine
oh
should I get more rice
ah
all of them
thank you maybe some milk too
just two for now
armor upgrades to be safer than Siri
what's the shop too
yeah
what should we expand I think the main
weapon thing if we can
[Music]
okay there you go
down
yeah
he makes me happy
it makes me so happy
[Music]
Maybe
cute
should be illegal
[Music]
thank you that's it for now
I love how you're referencing a meme
that I love
this is new too I think the [\h__\h] yeah I
think I've seen this before
Don't Tell Me based on your stature
frizzy you can distinctive right arm you
must be linked am I right Pierre has
told me so much about you I'm words with
my word is worth it you know my research
specialty is ancient hyrulean and la and
by ancient Hyrule and I don't mean the
text found in the ring ruins but
something different it's what we call
the language used at the time of
hyrule's founding traces of it are still
present in our speech time I think
that's what I found
uh ancient hyrulean and isn't that on
the on what's on the flower Islands
I think I remember it saying something
about ancient hyrulean that I can't read
okay maybe that's connected
you see the difference I trust
the stone tablet that fell from the sky
is inscribed of ancient hyrulean if I
can manage translated text it may be a
key to understanding the moment in time
from ancient Hyrule
oh I can translate this from ancient
High ruling and but my notes are back at
the research lab in kakariko so I'll be
heading there oh perfect I already have
a teleportation Port there
I've already copied down with inscribed
here so I'll be getting back uh to the
Village if that picks your interest link
you should come to kakariko Village so I
can share what I've translated so far
this inscription has tremendous
archaeological value it's a bridge
connecting us to the distant past I aim
to unravel its Mysteries and the sooner
I get started the better side quest
side Adventure
okay interesting
I wonder if I
go I wonder if I maybe have to show him
pictures
I go up take a picture and then bring it
to him
possibly
[Music]
um
nice nice nice
he's just chilling he's just rolling
okay
uh let's talk to you guys
we could investigate oh yeah I need to
do this thing
I found more fragments among the things
that server team brought back from the
devs and guess what they fit together
yeah you already filmed this right
I'm supposed to follow the path and then
find the middle thing
um
no
follow the case of each of those statues
down there you'll erase the structure
okay
but it's specifically those of the arm
up except for one that looks different
foreign
[Music]
I am I am one who returns pose to the
afterlife where they belong
at 177. oh proposed me their spirits
that ought to return to afterlife
holes are pitiful beings who have lost
their way home and wanted the deaths of
this land good evil test a futile
perspective of a never-minded being
there is no such distinction in
wandering Spirits you have already
obtained both
[Music]
what what
surely only the first one is one by one
right
oh this is indeed a poem
I have returned the Lost Spirit to the
afterlife where it belongs since I've I
was brought here to the surface I've
been unable to return post to after life
because of you I can assist him once
again you should take this
oh
if you offer me more pose I will give
you suitable compensation
but dark tunic Dark Link
oh but it's just like for looks it
doesn't actually do anything against the
glue
oh
I can afford it
sheesh
bomb flowers
one flower 16 pounds
I am always low on bone flowers
[Music]
hmm
yeah it surely would look good on me but
I should hmm
if you find more statues of this guy on
the ground you can get kulum resistant
armor this one okay
don't buy it
[Music]
you can find bomb blowers in the depth
I've been running around there and I
haven't fine I found so many
and the ones I found I was using on
those big chunks of uh whatever that
stuff was but now I at least for that I
can use my new friend
[Music]
um okay I'll buy this
and then maybe later as you guys said
I'll get other stuff to buy if I find
more of these statues
those will probably also be expensive
uh where are they wait would you tell me
where
I just need fitting pants
but I look pretty cool
[Music]
temples for location hmm
I'm not that desperate about it yet okay
[Music]
um
how many are there
as well
I can dye the pants nothing see I still
didn't make it to hathino I want to go
to hatino but oh well we will now go in
the underground because we've done
everything else I wanted to accomplish
today already
earlier than I thought
so yeah let's go to the underground
ah you know what I've been wondering
about those mystery mysterious dudes
that give you weapons in the underground
right
and I've noticed one thing I think
pretty sure every time they give you a
weapon it has like the sparkle symbol to
it and domtendo was asking you know so I
thought about it
the Nintendo was wondering like what
does that sparkle mean is it stronger it
didn't seem particularly stronger so
what could it be for and I have come to
a conclusion it's because those weapons
that they give to you if you look
closely yeah they're not the Kate and
the sparkle means that they're stop
saying
[Music]
hmm
okay where's the best place to start my
search for those should I just go down
here
[Music]
I should Mark
wait was this like
one of them how are they shown on the
map
would that make sense because like we're
probably
yeah we started out here and then we
walked right and activated another one
down here and then close by we found
this one
right
yeah
it says it in the description don't ruin
it from
oh man
[Music]
yeah I'm almost
no no one told me no
but that's I guess the only place to get
an undecayed weapons clean weapons
you didn't realize it you learned from
me
let's go okay
welcome to the underground baby
because while we're here we should be
wearing this
looks stupid
okay the
statue is there okay and I see another
one so we just follow them okay is this
the very first one does it just still
happen
hmm
wait they're not marking the map the way
I thought they were okay but I'll mark
them so I know
I can look at the pattern and see where
I am Maybe
hope this will not be too difficult of a
path
I put stamps on the map too whenever I
met the statue see that's a smart thing
to do don't you think
maybe we'll find
wait what is he looking at
maybe we'll find some more
this way
some more
um
big
uh light thingies
uh what
oh are those the big versions of the
small one
not friend no no
no it hasn't seen me though
[Applause]
it's made is that are they difficult to
fight
[Music]
uh
hey
there's something up there
oh God it's gonna throw me up
oh he's like one of those Rock people
thank you
open your eyes oh that worked didn't it
[Music]
he wants to suck me
oh you're fun one little guy aren't you
my friends but not me
okay my friends
gaming
excuse me
[Music]
hey he's good he's cute
oh yeah okay
nothing to hit
yo come on come on come on yeah
[Music]
I'm better at shooting his eye than you
his eye is pretty small
so yeah that's difficult to shoot
we needed to kill him though because
otherwise
he would keep on eating my flowers huh
frogs Fang frog tea infused attack power
hmm
cute
I'm getting hungry Fox fingernail
flat oh flat cracked fingernail
10 attack fusion that's fine thank you
that was pretty smooth don't you think
I only got like damage once I think
so not bad not bad
now however I I lost orientation
of uh where the statue was looking
towards
um
there it is
we were walking around it
oh that that went really far
we don't want it to go that far
oh
wait is that the next one
ah it might just be
right it is
it will make it smell better
noise aim don't you think
[Music]
Apple
oh I always want to know where we're
going
to be careful in the on the ground this
I I keep on getting like surprised by
new things off screen to offstream of
stream of screen
there's always new things to discover oh
there's another one like new enemies
that I did not expect to meet down there
as already taking shape
and we could even build something here
if we wanted to but I kind of like most
of the time I like going by foot
Alex no stop
Alex
please
what is that is that Wheels
those are wheels right oh no maybe not
oh where's your arrows you can just
throw the flowers how many do I have 87
okay I'm Gonna Save now
I'm Gonna Save where is it show where's
it looking that way
uh uh wait uh
fun
get him oh yeah there's actually right
there anything we gotta hit the head
and the body can wait for the long I
guess
I panicked I thought this was gonna be
more difficult
eh
the arms what
okay I did pick it up as a weapon
[Music]
tomorrow
then I would prefer to fuse it
bro
next one right here oh there's bomb
flowers
okay
you know the reason why I uh
delayed the stream today sorry about
that what was I doing is
because yeah okay I was awake pretty
late but that wouldn't have a loan
resulted in me delaying the Stream
I oh fairy [\h__\h] no no there's not
fairies
yeah
I
um I was awakened by a smoothie second
day in a row she just would not stop
meowing for the food it was pretty early
and eventually I gave in like yesterday
the problem is when I get up to give her
food and then go back to sleep
all the time it doesn't it doesn't just
work like that
it's not that easy
last movie is in control these days
but so I was I was so very tired so I
lay back down after giving him food
horses
they're trilling
hmm
um I lay back down I tried to sleep
again but
uh I made a mistake
for one moment
for just one moment I
looked at my phone I think I was trying
I was gonna like change my alarm to be a
little bit later to make up for the time
that it will take me to fall asleep
again
and then I looked at this chord uh and
that
there was some stuff going on so I was
like what
and I I couldn't I couldn't just sleep
yeah and then I
please don't
no did they hear me this one didn't
and then so it took me two hours to fall
asleep again
again whoa whoa
it's not really working okay pretty
chill uh oh
can you throw ah
while you're on a horse Let's see we can
shoot right so we control maybe two
yeah because of that
I delayed because I thought I need more
sleep if I'm gonna do a long ass stream
I will need more sleep I'm sorry
sorry guys
thanks for understanding I want to pick
that up
if I if I go off this horse will it stay
a little bit
only a little bit okay
yes
a good horse who's a good horse
I would have slept and woke when you
started oh nice
you overslept but just in time
for my stream
uh where are we going
so far it's been a pretty straight line
these horses can walk over the Gloom
right
what is this plant
oh
you're scared nothing
huh I'm scared where am I going should
be this way over there there should be
something logically thinking
are you guys protecting the statue or so
surprise it's a flower in your face
where is it
[Music]
ah I found it
let me just mark it around here
is like completely straight except for
here there's a curve I could probably
already like guess where it would be
but I will continue
the proper way
that's the next one
huh
keep the Jokers on the clip what does
that mean
Jokers
ah now we are
we took a curve I can't I didn't realize
what the [\h__\h] is that
what are those lanterns huh
they scare me
oh
just a broken camp
are the Sages
Jokers you mean the stages
what is this
according to the cool
cool this location will be destroyed
oh no I said you guys are going to show
up right now after I'm done reading this
no
okay
I saw on film tando's video I was
spoilered that there's uh the yiga have
camps down here
oh hi
and they're pretty big and they got some
cool I mean okay the one that we saw it
wasn't that big
actually it looks big but then once you
conquer it you realize it's not that big
sorry a lot of domitano mentions these
days because
it's related to the game was my horse
still there
where did I leave my horse
took on
oh there it is oh it's cute it's waiting
for me he's cute
wait wait wait wait wait
don't wander around
I need you really helpful
where's my Kami Oshi
I feel like
I don't think I have like something or
someone someone
recently that I feel like
I
I so actively support at the moment
yeah
this way kind of
I haven't been watching pecora sample
for a long time because
no time
huh
and it's kind of different now you know
being in the same company it's just it
it's some it feels weird
um
[Music]
honestly you could do this without a
horse too
[Music]
growth of time oh have we arrived
already or so poor thing
foreign
why would it break
yeah
uh it doesn't want to grow on trees
okay why is why is this called growth of
time
yeah
why
Chloe sketches around she on tomato
stitch for real
hmm
I mean
I know
thanks Patsy
wait there's a bomb
[\h__\h] trees
where
where did uh
this way
am I going backwards
oh
you [\h__\h] trees
[Music]
uh it's like kind of uh there I think
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
stop running
nice you
are the best horse ever
that beats course let's go let's go oh
it's close uh
my my markings are getting very wildly
wait there's a there's a big see whether
that I haven't activated
keep on running keep on running uh what
are we looking at over there
oh I see something interesting is that
the structure that I am looking for
wait why is the next one Not So Close by
they're all normally so close by
what was that
[Music]
you need some love
that's a tree
there it is
the [\h__\h] is this shape
let me know
[Music]
ah I think
we're looking at the left side maybe and
we're now close to the bottom middle
that's it
yeah yeah if we go over here here should
it should be right I think so
hey and the Snapchats I don't even do
them in game I don't know why hmm
okay so I'm actually already looking
into the direction
yeah scary
oh but it's so confusing to me
Maybe
maybe wait I said is this isn't that
no but that would be a different
direction
I feel like that makes sense or
[Music]
um
can I go a bit further
let me get a big one
stone is just a depiction not
necessarily the same shape but it looks
so important in this place what is this
uh there's another one of those statues
though
um
does this one even have anything to do
with this at that point
this this one's this one's looking
right there
foreign
I'm Gonna Leave My Horse behind now
because
I have to go down anyway to collect
materials
let's Market
I'll continue
for a bit more because who knows
maybe I'm not where I think I am
but I feel like now I should make my way
down
okay
should I check what he has no really
care
ow
I don't know why I did that
don't know
okay we have some gaps now but we don't
need all of it
hmm
should we go
what is this a big pool Maybe
a grandpa 20.
yeah um what is this place
great abandoned Central mine
scary
why
but it kind of looks toward that
direction doesn't it
yeah yeah
this is the place I thought so
I know it like look at this big ass
thing obviously that's the thing we're
looking for
we've packed night vision potions isn't
that Minecraft
oh
[Music]
that makes no sense they don't have
shrines there's a person
hi
oh
it's creating it can I talk to them
first look oh I just think we'd see
anybody else down here though I imagine
you could say the same to us right yeah
you're here to investigate too right you
know since you took the
[Music]
yeah
yeah yeah I know yeah
yeah I won't even listen to you oh even
good yeah yeah
let me kill you
they're gonna activate themselves maybe
after I activate it
I'm already attracting them because I
trust my guts you can't fool me
trying to fool me guys I'm not going
crazy right
I know what I'm thinking I know what I
know
you're the way to suck that was way too
fast if that's not a temple then what is
that uh wait maybe there's a Temple
no
very bad
hi it's me comparing all the Bell to oh
ah
[Music]
please utilize it as you explore and
excavate The Depths for tonight
now we get out of build
ER
basically whatever you create if you
have the materials for it
then it will build itself
I saw a video
where that happened with the Mecca
big robots
all of build instantly recreate your
Ultra hand projects using nearby items
and zonite all the build records your
previous creations
starting from now or also what I had
before
yeah yeah you want to fight me now
no
no I will not demonstrate I want to kill
you
disability will allow you to commit any
structure you create to a memory any
object committed to truth memory can be
instantly reproduced oh I know just what
to use it on
yeah yeah cause you guys want to use
this stuff too right both of your
vehicles just broke and we've been
struggling to put them back together
again no I want to kill them oh
they're not good people
what
the one on the round who doesn't want
the wheel
[Music]
if you put the lid back onto the first
one you should be able to use your power
and repair the second in no time for aha
are they eager helping me figure this
out just because they want to steal from
me or so
[Music]
oh
I don't trust them
that looks so creepy
those hands look so creepy
they're gonna use it and then run off
with it
whoa look at that where's the boy
now do it there
uh-huh
well what if I don't have this exact
real piece of metal or wood or so the
thing in the middle
then it's a different build right
yeah okay that helps for sure
do you want to fight me now
text her right after him I'll say that
power's incredible oh Master no there we
go she mm-hmm
big one
nah no problem right is that cool guy
great work both of you you too stranger
credit what creditors do
yes created with credities
if there's one farewell never forget
it's the man who cast me from my Gerudo
dancing hideout
no you like when you kill him he falls
down into this big ass hole right
that's why they're down here
[Music]
I remember
were you able to follow him into that
hole when that happens
or did it close itself or so
I did this
that's so funny but we only sent him
down there how to did the rest just
decide to follow him
we just moved on hmm you can't follow
him
Obama's pit in the original ah well you
just falling and you're like ah and then
you could spawn back up
that's funny it was you no a little
Vengeance both upon that no good job and
upon my sworn enemy that means
we beat again
try to tell me you've forgotten me we
are bound by thank you Renee hear my
name my trembling fear I am the leader
of the yiga clang they're strong they're
flying From the Ashes Rising Like a
Phoenix
monster cooker
I'm sorry though
I saw the moment you obtained the
ancient power it would start for so long
see John 10 in the wrong order again he
should have had this cutscene before
meeting any Giga ideally
because that explains why they are down
there
to highlight of all the musco texts we
found in this land it remembers objects
we've assembled and can instantly
reproduce them
that introduction though was a very
pokemon-like introduction
a long lost ability from the distant
past so you you
you're Trading
here we are working on shops to the Bone
to build things by hand and you can just
whip them up
and stand that's not fair you know who
could have used that power the one we
worship and review the Magnificent one
we feel afford it to him he would have
crushed you and Zelda both but you just
want right up and snatched it away now
I'm gonna snatch it back
hey yo
okay
we just shoot him off
[Music]
wait aim to go
what if I drive it
okay
I wanted to steal his car
ah
you're resting back your car
what if I just take apart the car
[Music]
okay
I can't reverse it either but it's
obviously
[Music]
you can't do the striped turns can you
I love the music that plays by the way
all right what do we got maybe this one
[Music]
I love the soundtrack
he's too easy to hit but I like to fight
anyway
[Music]
oh
yeah
wait he improved the car
you're gonna do it again
but where are you gonna go
okay I have to let him go oh
no is he gonna rain
position it
[Music]
okay
I'm on my way
that's so funny I like this
I love this scene
we did it and we tried entering his car
in the beginning but
he doesn't he wants he wants to do it
differently right you pesky little
pissed why won't you just stand still
let me squish you
well fine I suppose I can let you up
easy for today you think you're so smart
but I've already found a whole bunch of
runes down here
I saw you a little trick there use your
right hand to get the construct going
I'll grab the power you treated me out
for myself off that at the Southwest in
abandoned mine mine what then the
Magnificent one and I will guide this
world to its miserable end and there's
nothing you can do to stop us
what does he tell me where to meet him
again or what
thank you
but you you just summoned that out of
nowhere you don't need my power
logic
logic.com
don't follow me
I caught them two more times oh it's a
side Adventure
this is a side Adventure but the finding
the structure is for the main class no
huge specialized charge oh a hundred
yeah you told me the place where to find
him again then he probably will prepare
it more
their people they can't Auto build
excuse me
thank you for repelling the trespassers
I hope you will pardon me for listening
on in in your conversation the man
mentioned an abandoned mine in the
southwest I suppose suspect that he is
referring to the former Gerudo mine that
plays florist with activity long ago
like this one one or one is constantly
Unearthed and refined there are statues
that point away to the abandoned
ah wait so also the different statues
that have different looks point at
something specific
follow them to WeChat destination
[Music]
I recommend you begin by making your way
to the light you see over there
[Music]
they all point to Big Minds ah
one more thing before you set out on
your journey
there is something I would like you to
have please speak with my associate when
possible that you associate
I didn't notice he was Associated all
thank you for driving out the
trespassers I will no longer need to
hide in order to avoid detection there
is another reason that it's good that
you have come I see that you have the
ability to Auto build that means this
game Stone schema Stone I carry is for
you
these stone slabs to pay schematic skin
schemes of things such as solar Vehicles
audible saves the schematic and builds
it on command
oh like you've given me a recipe now or
for a different one oh thank you
um I know that the the smaller eager
eager camps
not the one that he's invited me to
probably but different one have like
these kind of things schemes they just
don't know what to do with them
but they are there and you can pick them
up there
so then we don't even have to build it
ourselves
you don't have to come up with it
ourselves and these are like I guess the
most ideal builds
that are not going to be scuffed like my
own
the new design has been registered with
other build you should now be able to
Auto build an additional design please
wait why not prepare to the necessary
parts for you to test this schema Stone
oh Should I fly off the same way that he
did over to the flower
schema Stones can help you to build
things you have never before imagined I
hope that you find this one useful
you have to choose it though what if you
make like a hundred
oh and it takes three of those stones
nice though oh right here's a little one
of those shops
[Music]
that is precious mineral which is
already slated for processing it would
pose difficulties for me if you took it
for yourself there are examples of
processed materials available on the
nearby shelves I encourage you to
examine them to see if there are any you
want
um
which ones are the ones that I need to
collect a million of these ones right
right
like even the big ones are the small
ones
okay
does it make a difference
[Music]
is this like do I get cheaper prices
somewhere else or is this like all the
same I'm grateful to you for driving out
to trespasses it was necessary that
actually to avoid detection and speak no
more of that
I mean I won't need it for anything else
right
the
The Zone Knight
except for when I drop it
no way that's the the charges
let's just get all of it
you will need to ah
I do need them for building true so as
long as I just keep a couple
the last one is just for these okay
[Music]
I'll process more okay
um okay
oh 30 for now
[Music]
and what was the number that we wanted
in the end 900 or what what was that 9
000 or
I don't remember
100 per upgrade how many do I have now
oh I could do two upgrades
but the upgrade itself
was only up on that one sky island
what's that
and then I will have like always more
battery is that what what I get from
that I think so
yeah yeah yeah yeah
only a third
100 is only a third
there's one outside Lookout Landing oh
okay
let's go to the flower
or should I just fly with my
[Music]
I want to see a little bit
only a little bit
[Music]
uh-huh
that is a different statue
foreign
and there's tracks down there
um
oh okay that didn't go so far
[Music]
no
I wanted it to just drop down
yeah
okay
I guess we'll fly over to the flower
oh yeah I just wanted to see a little
bit of what I'm when I'm flying over you
know for safety
let's go
is that
um
what am I trying to ask oh dear
oh dear
still flying we're still flying
what am I trying to ask
I could have landed on some [\h__\h] man
God
[Music]
why did I jump down because I wanted to
land here anyway
this is right underneath the great
Plateau ah you mean where you start out
in breath of the Wild
[Music]
mm-hmm
oh nothing to heal because I'm a pro
oh
those could just be humans
find them interesting so I take a
picture
for reference
we should already Mark those Maybe
should I mark them
oh
humans
looks like the queen
I mean it gives me Zelda Vibes yes
I mean I know Dallas was a princess but
oh
there's this place
we're basically done right with that
Quest we can report back but now I I'm
very curious about what down there
I can't help it
I need to look at it
good stuff there good all right baby
it is one of those things that they
point at
oh
those paws
and you can make some more stuff here
I would just try to fly over
that's still the arm lifting ones
interesting
okay no I might need a card for this
let me get one
follow your Wanderlust
ciao what do you mean I'm the hero of
the story
this is all for me to use freely
that should be enough
what is that a box
and my guys too far for you guys
in the game should I go take it easy
well don't worry next week
I will play once on Sunday and then
maybe sometime in between the week as
well
um or not only or only once there's a
chance maybe I'll only do it once and
you guys can catch up
even more
I I I I I wanted to check what's here
this is where I wanted to go right is it
it is where I have one of those
come back maybe
it's gone where I have one of those
marks
but it's okay I'll go here because I can
is there an enemy here
[Music]
schedule today or tomorrow
maybe today because I also I think I'll
stream tomorrow
are we doing more story if so why are we
headed minus Charles
they look funny
wait they do remind you of um like
Japanese
um what they wear uh Japanese workers at
uh like um
Minds I guess too but
they have these
funky pants always
they don't glow but they have the same
shape
yeah yeah
um
wait did I activate the flower that I
was supposed to activate I did right
yeah yeah
uh oh wait that's already the what the X
was supposed to show me huh
okay
I ain't got so mine some stuff here
oh wait but
I'm so not sure if we're I don't think
we are losing materials oh it just flies
really far I suppose
um
one
two no
maybe it fell down oh yeah
no I have like one hammer let me use it
a little bit
for the small ones at least
and then this is what I was hoping for
for the big ones
we'll use our friend warranty
where is she
who lives tonight
uh I recall to see what I went oh I
guess I could do that where did he go
one more one more
the only thing that's like not super
transparent on him is that tear
interesting
hey perfect
yes this is how you're supposed to mind
this stuff
very good
is that all or
can we possibly find more
supposed to be a whole mine
hylia Canyon mine
I feel like that would be more
[Music]
is that my Minecart
that could be my Minecraft wait
wait
do I want to ride it
let me in let me in let me in mm-hmm
okay okay
I'm in
let's go where are we going
we're going to a cave
[\h__\h] scary
did I not turn it on huh
oh
you mean Indiana Jones yo I can't
[\h__\h] see
I hope I won't regret this
ah
don't need more
I can't do it now
you just gotta
yeah yeah yeah wait wait
oh
nice
maybe I bonked it by accident
we are away from the canyon mine
why does it sound like there's an enemy
here
it's not Marcus for whatever reason
um
is this just the pap to like from you
would find it from a different location
it's just another path to the mine
what What's following me yeah
[Music]
there goes it ends now
elevator
can you help this place
is
like Gloom Deluxe
can't get much more gloomy than this
I am my own enemy well that is often
very true isn't it
really we just like go up is there
nothing here except a [\h__\h] ton of Gloom
yeah seems so
maybe it would be more interesting once
I'm able to touch the Gloom
I don't know
there's a Chasm above oh really
ah
well we're already in here
yeah I guess we should go back and
deliver our Quest and see what she says
what next what next she has for us in
store but this means we failed up the
tools
there is nothing more
is that activated or not
I'm not sure how it's supposed to look
like anymore
it's only Loki right oh it is okay
let me climb a little bit
just curious
bombs
[Music]
dinosaurs
half past nine the good thing is I don't
have to cook because I have half of the
pizza and
something I cooked like two days ago
sorry guys recently I haven't been
showing you my cooking but
it's been some some repetitions as well
some things I'm just cooking again I
ordered the same recipe again as I did
before
because just because I know it's decent
what pizza was it tunnel
it was tunnel yeah
I know you guys sometimes when I talk
about tono Pizza you're like
okay I'm leaving this place anyway
but
tondo is legit
I'm telling you
it deserves
recognition and it's legit yeah tuna
Pizza is legit something they have in in
Italy
as like one of their basic menu pizzas
it was with red onions
unfortunately no corn because corn on a
tunnel Pizza is
not so normal anymore
I'm just gonna collect these pose and
then I'll go back
um
imagine if there were codecs down here
huh
that is
granny not the case
okay no I don't I don't need it right
now
unless I dropped something else
[Music]
yes normalized corn corn has to be on
everything
why are you
just climb up
thanks how much damage does that do
I want to fuse it onto something though
I guess I'll just refuse to do this
[Music]
corn on schnitzel Okay I lied corn
doesn't have to be on everything I take
it back
take it back
oh
[Music]
look what the [\h__\h] was that
those pop shrooms
are so good guys I'm telling you nice
moves but
I already killed your leader you should
run away and warn the others
but you don't have the brains for that
[Music]
thank you for starting the work for me
okay now now they're all dead
no Witnesses
just gonna clear this on my own without
my friend's help
um so much so nice you
little mind they got going there can you
only get tonight out of this stuff is
there absolutely no choice to get
diamonds or so probably not
oh
so nice monster yeah
[Music]
a large one too
okay
I think I got it all
for myself to
[Music]
back to the
OG back to my roots
I will
go for real now I won't go I won't go I
said I would go back give back my quest
don't keep them waiting
foreign
mountains I don't want to check out that
building didn't I do that already it
wasn't that the building I saw already
I got some new stuff yeah oh you know
what I will have to snack on mine
send Bay now
and I think I will read super chats
after this
at least some I can't I promise I will
read all of them
but at least some
because I've been neglecting them
because of very long long days of gaming
and other days where it was collapsed
movie
[Music]
I'm not done yet
um sorry
this movie entered the room
[Music]
foreign
but she's already escaping
hmm
goodbye
soft child
okay
[Music]
swordsman what is it you look very
pleased with yourself I do look pleased
don't die
even holding the belt of my clothes does
he
he doesn't always stand like this right
is it the pants
wait he does
okay never mind
oh I didn't know this
could it could it be
oh
talk about what the ability to instantly
replicate things you've built
schema Stones so they're really animals
it's only Temple housing a mysterious
power down in the depths
that may also mean that some of the
things collected from the devs may give
us other Clues wait here just a second
[Music]
um
here we go
eh
what's next here's what's men
I found one of those
nice okay yeah we got the basics now hot
air balloon oh and it saved my my
Minecart
um
those are in different categories the
ones that you got from schema stones and
the ones you built yourself
this is a schema stone for a balloon
right so if you use this water build you
could replicate a balloon right I'm
thinking
yeah and that one you had out there for
a while that balloon over there belongs
to goggles but it's broken right now do
you think you might be able to fix it I
could have fixed it without that too but
sure
I'll go prepare really quick
I gotta unchain it please there we go
please demonstrate how all the
replicates things okay Robbie you want
to see this trust me
[Music]
look at this
hot air balloon
but this is costing me stuff you guys
better give that back to me
[Music]
believe that you rebuilt the balloon an
instant now that's pretty cool thank God
that exists
I'm so done
building everything on my own this this
mysterious power goes beyond scientific
explanation
yo they also got a safe [\h__\h] like you
know those super scuffed Bridges uh the
bridge I made for example the super
scuffed one in the dungeon in the temple
that I will never need again but they're
gonna save that too aren't they
can I delete uh certain ones I wonder so
it doesn't get like too much
it only costs
what I can make like stuff out of thin
air
with those stones I didn't realize I
thought you have to have everything
close by oh
history is only 40. ah
I think goggles
oh
what are you like yelling about Joshua
inconceivable my balloon is fixed this
must be the mysterious power that's all
I had I never thought I'd see such a
Marvel with my very own eyes thank you
for making this a reality please take
this I've been saving it for a special
occasion thank you
hmm
inconceivable isn't that what um
that dude says in the in the movie that
we watched
right it's a meme
I still haven't been able to figure out
what that is
by judging from that light it's gonna be
Zona in origin since you can use domain
Powers I think it would be better for
you to have it there was an incredible
power lying hidden in the depths after
all I think I'll keep researching The
Depths going forward who knows I just
might find a clue about Princess Zella
hopefully
we can make any new discoveries in the
devs please let me know Swordsman
oh yeah nice nice nice
yes did you need something she's
she she asks me right away did I find
something
ah to know about Koga
oh God the leader of the year
oh this is dangerous I've gotta regain
my composure okay come this way ooh will
that be part of the main quest too
um
yeah yeah the watch along where I had a
laughing fit
he's not really dangerous
so you faced cooler in the devs
um what's the leader of the yoga Clan up
to down there from what I know the Higa
Clan is a super dangerous group that
schemes against the kingdom of Hyrule
and Coca has had it out for you and
Princess Zelda for a long time he'd do
anything to put an end to your lives
despite everything we're looking into
already we just can't take our eyes off
this bread besides know what's happened
to the princess that would make a lot of
sense if you do go after him keep in
mind that I'll be continuing my research
for the deaths from right here oh by the
way do you know about the force of time
it didn't didn't I find the Forest of
time like also underground with south of
Hyrule Field there's a chance in there
and I've gotten reports of another
series of statues found at the bottom of
it these tattoos are different from the
one you showed me using the camera they
seem to point the way did I take a
picture that I'm gonna show her right
away
I found the growth of time oh
well you got the other build ability but
they don't stop there these statues lead
farther south west Into the Depths where
they go as anyone's guess but I bet
there's a destination far beyond the
building worth seeing Oh
wait
the is it for real a picture I took it
was it worth it oh
so reference thank God it's like this
picture
okay
I didn't think that I could use it right
away
there's so many different statues I
found different ones too different from
this one but this was exactly the one
she wanted
Giga brain
um
yeah good that I use the actual photo
function for once because normally I
just take screenshots
It's gotta be it appears just like it
was described in the report and of
course you already found it you're
amazing Jake
I'll keep Gathering info about what's in
the depth so be sure to stop by and
check with me soon okay from now on I'll
take a photo of every statue I find
seems like she wants that
so what's the current Quest you have for
me what exactly you want me to do
she's not pure she's Joshua
nothing ah
I don't have to wait okay oh wait what I
have more
I said what about them
oh no wait never mind
um
okay okay so you want me to follow those
and then report to you what I found
but why is it not part of a quest
or is it
you're from Josh Young
side quest
wait it should be one of those
no
hmm
it only was main quest the first because
of the other build oh okay but now it's
only like cyclists on adventures okay
is it an adventure
okay the Koga one yeah
but that's the one we already got like
down there
[Music]
are these like
should I keep at least some of these
first streams like
um I mean this one I'm like constantly
doing these I think until the very end
it doesn't really I should just do it
off screen
but I wonder are there some you want me
to do maybe a Koga
the whole Koga thing I can do like a
whole stream about the yiga
[Music]
that's stone tablets that's curious too
but you know I think I'll do those on my
own
well that would be rad to see on stream
okay and the hero clip you mean
those ancient texts I was thinking just
going to get them and then taking
pictures
I mean I have to take pictures anyway
right so maybe getting them I'll do on
my own and then reporting them I'll go
on stream
[Music]
you want to find the whole house okay
I'll do it off screen too
oh problem I'll do it for you me chorus
gentle beige coat
grain dappling
okay high places
the Dragon Tears huh
oh that's what you meant where which one
is the next one by the way O'Connell
because they're kind of music is good
maybe everyone can do one more you know
or should I
should I wait for
because it seems like you know after you
finish a temple impa will show up we've
noticed that and she will tell you about
the next one but is it worth waiting for
her
maybe just one more you know
um it's
what is that something curved
um
ah it's um somewhere in the middle there
uh I think
I think I can find that
if I have the map for it
uh
it's hard to tell
it's under like a U-shaped
River
with a Snake River leaning up to it and
stopping right in front of right in
front of it
uh
so I should be like here
but I have
ah I have the Skype your Tower I wonder
if we can reach
I wanna I wanna find that
[Music]
can we reach it
the sound looks right up ah that maybe
that's what I marked
um
probably
at the stamp yeah I marked something
when I was flying around that's one of
the towers I think that I did offstream
oh yeah yeah that was interesting
because you had to go through the well
and they closed the doors
[Music]
go in there from Below
I should change my clothes
okay first of all
sorry I can't stop myself I think it
would be nice to finish off with a
little memory don't you think
I think so
ah
foreign
this way
good time to activate tooling again
wait longer [\h__\h] help
there's one of the flowers
I'll go flower Island while I'm here
might as well
just to take a photo I guess or we could
already report that
you cannot read it exactly so I shall
take a picture
[Music]
is that good enough
from here just I want to build a hot air
balloon to get back into the sky
[Music]
should I really
do we need that height probably
um okay
sure
[Music]
yeah
uh does it need fire
it does need fire huh
so ah I need one of my
one of my fire emitters I guess
I don't have so many
you don't fall down please
why does it not come with a flame
emitter
what the hell
[Music]
it doesn't it doesn't go for very long
maybe a bit more
foreign
interesting
okay
yeah
that should do the trick the whirlpool
man that's a different kind of Whirlpool
normally you would like to get on a
Whirlpool oh yeah and another Dragon
yeah scary scary I've been seeing a lot
of those
three-headed dragons
hmm
well I want to see where it is
it's here left up like middle left left
on the very left you know what I mean
you know what I mean
and there's a Chasm there I suppose
the church
is that the great plateau
it doesn't feel as familiar to me
because I never played it I just I just
watched five times
it is
just eating my apple pie maybe or this
that's good
mm-hmm
we're getting there we're almost there
maybe one more time
Come on Come on load faster
[Music]
we'd have to climb a little bit
and it's raining oh no
at least I landed in water but [\h__\h] I
think it's raining
foreign
guys I have it all under control
don't you worry
close one
oh wait it's not raining it just looks a
little bit like it
okay
no we couldn't reach out is there a
crack here too it doesn't seem like it
um I'm just so curious about the lower
so I I have to I have to find out more
which one is it
no
oh
oh how late that's one of the last I
don't want to see it maybe if I end the
game now I'll be um
somewhere else
no
no no no no no
I can skip it and we watch later ah true
I'm killing yourself
[Music]
why why did we go to this one
I thought it's the this one
how did I make a mistake
don't worry we will not watch
no no I'm not looking I'm not looking
I'm not I'm not looking
but it saves it is
I know
wait what you are meant to watch them
out of order
so
oh God but we
we
didn't we go to the one that was like
next
appear a pad and then some like weird no
that's something else
I accidentally went to the one that I
confused I went to that one and I should
have gone to that one
[\h__\h] but we might be able to reach that
one too from the same Tower
it's hmm
it's it's uh underneath is three legs
and on top is like it's covering a leg
too
[Music]
I don't know I don't I don't want to
read or say anything
[Music]
Green Lakes underneath
Nabi it was probably here right
foreign
near here okay and we can
[Music]
should I go from this Tower yeah
okay
you got that one already okay then you
will not be spoiled
I got you
I got you guys
but if we ever need to check this one
I'll just wear out then we just gotta
re-watch our memories
there's a bunny leading to a cave that I
didn't check out yet well I still will
not do it
we will watch these in order or is it
what that doesn't look like an even
though
that doesn't look like it either
but
location wise it's kind of there that's
the one
for real
oh because it's covered in trees
all right then that will be the last
thing for today for real for real
it's been six hours I could go longer
but
it's a good time to read super chats I
guess because we got so far today
[Music]
please
is that down there
wait do I see it
no so it's probably behind the trees
[\h__\h] weather [\h__\h]
I suspect
oh there's enemies
I hope it's not there
the nice child suspected to be here
hidden right
anyway
I have a feeling for it you know
natural feeling
good guess
[Music]
your let's watch this that's the last
thing today you spent 25 minutes it's a
women's intuition you know
and the jrpg experience in me
oh
is this one he's still like somewhat
normal
early days
well
I was a Mia Linda
I wouldn't say
cause he still got them that's why I'm
thinking he's still like somewhat
considered normal
[Music]
here
that looks familiar
oh
[Music]
well that is a [\h__\h] Hyper Beam if
I've ever seen one no I don't know
[Music]
well we learn about like when
they I'm mysterious
and they're like [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] yeah
cool
I mean I've always heard about it you
know but if this is the first time I
think I've like seen
something like this in a Zelda game
where he actually is with them
um
very cool
if you like the voice acting I'm happy
about that is the cat nobody oh no she
left again
um
oh you see it in Ocarina of Time
I don't remember that
but it's a rare thing that's for sure
cool
oh wait this is probably yeah
yeah this is one of those
hmm
Shrine up there
I should stop shouldn't I
help
oh I can't stop when that one's moving
says
ah but I can't stop running in this open
world game you just can never stop
running it's impossible
blue Nightshade pretty which lake is
this
is that a stable over there
the one I have found before yeah okay
I should go
I need to go okay I go I'll go I'll go I
can I can stop myself I have control
over myself I I am I am an adult
I can do this
I'm not addicted
I know how to stop myself
no no I'm not going anywhere this is it
for today we did a whole Temple
we did the underground main quest
we did two memories
we did plenty
I would love to do the glyphs just like
one after another and you could probably
just
speed one the gloves right
[Music]
unless maybe the last one is like not
easily accessible in the early game
something like that you did that
um
but well well well well
intervention Kiara and The Legend of
Zelda oh is that what gets me on Hall of
engine after all
okay saved my progress we are good to go
I think I'll just go to let uh Idol
meeting
and then I'll see you maybe in my my new
room ah because I actually have it with
a desk and all that too so I'll see you
there in a moment
[Music]
is this happy GM oh yes
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
together
don't care
haven't used this screen in a long time
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm ready in one moment
[Music]
almost almost perfect
appearance
the chair is huge oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
the girls talk room but with gamer girl
chair
should I take off yes I should take off
my things ah don't look
[\h__\h]
don't look
get rid of this you're not seeing
anything right yeah yeah okay
okay
now you can look
so oh wait the microphone the microphone
here there we go now now you can look at
it properly
I wonder is the chair like dimensionally
too big
double mic
we have my chair
and oh no not very much I don't use this
one anymore but I used to have a chair
like this I guess it has a it has a kfp
logo wow
um and the The Dana keyboard yeah
special keyboards not just any keyboard
and the the cute basketball
and the buckets and all that
you know
some some logos logo stickers and a
wireless mouse which is really
unrealistic I don't use wireless mouse
I would never do that
I only use cable Mouse
um
not wearing shorts well I'm wearing a
completely different outfit today so of
course of course do you want to see like
the clean background ones though
oopsie yeah it's kind of like this
[Music]
I love the rug I love the rug it's so
cute
um
and the Plus in the big chicken plushie
or I killed all right let's bring it
back
chair there we go
ah wait chat where is chat
I thought I had it set up
oh it's just not working I'm gonna go
oh there it is
[Music]
yeah I don't really know where to put
you guys
um
because it's like you know there's no no
real space
for you it's hard to read probably
proper prop probably over here
but if I put like something underneath
you maybe
um
see what I got
I should have some kind of chat box for
you guys or something
young girl said no no I was hoping to
use this uh sometimes
um
even outside of girls talk not all the
time because then the specialness of
girls talk
uh I guess would be
not there anymore
um
some things that I could use
made me
ah this one
could go here
right and then you guys
go there
but on top of it
undone
and make you a bit higher and a bit less
wide
skinny chat yeah did you lose some
weight
what diet are you guys doing
how to make the chat look prettier yeah
some people sent me
um
some creators coffee thing where you can
buy like cute chat boxes I'm thinking
about it I'm considering it
[Music]
like this there we go you got your own
chat box nice
yeah they look cute maybe I'll get some
of those maybe maybe
you're skinnier now but it's okay you
don't have to you know you don't have to
do a diet or anything which
you look fine the way you are
I'm not on a diet I just have a fast
metabolism you're saying me too
I'm never on a diet
but it's not like I oh hairstyle change
it's not like I
really feel the need for it personally
um
actually next week I have to
do some shorter streams because I need
to
[Music]
um
I need to learn choreography
for the
at least one song that I'll be recording
I don't think in the end because we're
still kind of like fixing the first
songs choreography
I what I wanted to do two and then
record two to make two and beans
but I don't know if uh
we can do it because the choreo is not
ready we're still working on the first
one
so only six hours a day nah I for real
gotta do some shorter ones I think I'll
do one Korean study stream next week
because there's like so much I need to
kind of take some time to repeat
everything anyway so you guys might as
well watch Me While I do that
um
good luck boss thank you
thank you Slade Aspire passport tutu
yeah yeah yeah
I could do that stuff although even
passport 22 tends to be a bit longer
often
um
I can keep it short I guess
we'll see we'll see remember no no I
think was it this week
did I said no member stream no we
already did one this week so I said next
week no members stream
um
10 hours dancing at Amazon I don't think
so Ava doesn't think so either because
the reason why everything was like so
scuffed last time is like I would uh we
would like you know set everything up
then we test a little bit it doesn't
work then we think okay maybe it works
now so we start recording and then of
course it wasn't usable so restart again
then we do it like Parts by Parts by
Parts like we split the song into
sections and then even then you know we
had to record everything double and
there were so many songs we had to do
um
and there was so much uh like scuff-ness
and like limbs flying away and twitching
and all that so but Emma says Now is
better
I mean she used it in her uh birthday
stream in February
and it was already pretty stable it was
very stable then I mean she doesn't
Dance AS
like Extreme as me
but
I should handle it
and the good thing is still I'm doing an
MV so
the the problem with the recording the
birthday concert I guess was that I
needed like the full choreo to be
like something that I can show
presentable but for
uh the MV whatever looks really scuffed
we can always just you know do a
different scene do a close-up or
something or like a lip sync or a
Running Scene or whatever yeah yeah we
can cherry pick the good parts exactly
so it shouldn't be like too much of an
issue but really I I would appreciate
though if we can get one one clean cut
of the full dance so that maybe I can
also upload a dance version or so you
know
um
[Music]
that would be nice oh we need some bgm
here
[Music]
you know what I should put here
he's slapping the desk
I don't know why
wait I have no idea ah that one's just
that one's white background white can't
use that
if I could get that one in transparent
that would be cool
oh well
on the keyboard
this is not how you use the keyboard
little simkin
ah okay we'll just let him do his thing
he's happy
he's in his element
Bongo he's playing bongo boom boom boom
boom boom
I'm checking if I have anything else
that's useful nah okay although maybe a
drink uh Chihuahua drink
one that was specifically for me
oh God I have so much
stuff
[Music]
ah
from yuminix
hot cocoa with marshmallows
[Music]
yeah let's put that down here although I
would I think I wanna
mirror it
there we go
a little bit bigger like this
looks good
I could even put down
golden Yago somewhere
okay
go put them up here oh but the angle
makes no sense
here could work
oh that's it actually Blends in nicely
oh nice nice nice nice
[Music]
it's about it what I have useful things
right now at hand
at least
what's that what else do I have in it no
I didn't have it hit in the nope yes I
just had it you know uh I'm looking at
my resources folder this is one of my
favorites I actually I have the and the
mated version somewhere
I don't know where it is
um
animated
animated and animated
okay
okay wait I was actually looking for bgm
um
music
[Music]
what do we want
foreign
[Music]
don't question my outfits in the
background
now there's bgm
[Music]
what's this remind you of
does this give you valibimes or Animal
Crossing vibes
[Music]
Animal Crossing Final Fantasy Animal
Crossing old FF games oh
sound music
[Music]
Harvest Moon valves hi this is really
nice isn't it okay let's do this one
let's play this one okay
I know I know it might make you sleepy
but don't fall asleep yet where do I
need to start reading super trumps does
anyone have any idea
foreign
she just started half an hour ago
she's also addicted
amazing astounding
Animal Crossing on the yes it does feel
like no sounds like doesn't it
first tmtk stream
oh really
no no no I don't need too much I'm in
the problem
I think afterwards I'll continue
watching uh at least one episode of the
great I've watched uh I think two so far
last night I watched two
and I cannot really comfort yeah that's
what I saw if any of it at all even like
roughly like that happened in in actual
history
I cannot really tell yet
Maybe
maybe none of them maybe it's a whole
stretch
turn it down okay
how about now
I have to hit the wiki article Zoom but
it has been very interesting so fine
it's so nice to see that actress again
she's so pretty she's so cute and she's
such a boss lady now
because she's the empress and she just
in the previous season she just
basically demoted uh the husband the guy
the dude
the Russian dude yeah and now she's yeah
a girl boss basically
and
in in the end of the previous season she
like thought she killed him
because that was the plan but then she
accidentally killed someone else because
he was just wearing the same clothes
and
yeah turns out she didn't and then she
realizes and then and then he sees it
too how she regrets it
which makes him feel better about her
trying to kill him in theory
[Music]
yeah and then she gives up on killing
him because she realizes that she
actually like somewhere deep down she
has feelings for him even though he's a
[\h__\h] idiot douchebag [\h__\h] who
had
um
intercourse with her mother and then
killed her by doing into course throwing
her out of the window which was very
funny
um I don't know if that's historically
accurate
at all if we have any proof that he you
know
nailed her
um
it's so it's so fun it's so so it is
really funny yeah
they were like doing it on the window on
the open window and then she fell down
basically
[Music]
and then she's dead and then you know
she finds out that her husband
the emperor
killed her mom doing that
[Music]
it's uh yeah crazy crazy show
I'm so funny because they swear so much
they swear double as much as me no trust
me it's funny when you watch it it's
really funny the whole show is like they
make fun out of like misery and and and
they make fun of history and all that I
don't know it's funny
um
the show I'm talking about is
um the great on Amazon Prime you can get
it there
no for real but um it's uh it's a a bit
embarrassing if you guys watch it then
you know what I watched and and there's
a lot of yeah scenes
a lot of them
very many happy scenes
yeah there's many eggs
many eggs eggs
zing zing
I heard High Praise from other people
too that's because it's like really
really good quality
um
it's very entertaining
okay
[Music]
I closed my eyes yes of course yes
smoothie and Congress covered my eyes
with one paw each
and they were like Mommy you can't
launch this we also don't want to watch
they're right next to me this movie
covered my left eye and chunkers covered
my right eye with their cute paws
[Music]
okay let me read the super chats Jacob
thank you soon
oh you want to do Seinfeld I've been
watching it like only to fall asleep
these days like always immediately fall
asleep after like during the first
episode that I'm watching
so good to fall asleep and then the next
day when I do that again I noticed that
I skipped like four episodes while I was
sleeping like I went through
it ran through five four episodes I
always go back and I repeat again and I
go back and I repeat again
Seinfeld my beloved yeah it's funny
sunfeld's also so funny yeah
my dad does the same
there's no problem in the end I mean I'm
just putting it on to fall asleep you
know
at this point I watched it properly once
and maybe I wasn't properly again
sometime but
um
and you guys on Twitter
with your arguments that you weren't
alive or you whatever you know when
Seinfeld was a Fame I wasn't here but I
I was in Seinfeld was really unknown I
think in Austria it wasn't very common
don't think people knew about Seinfeld
here
I just picked it up I think partially it
was your guys's recommendation
then I started it it was really good
hey happy birthday
[Music]
22nd May
congratulations Gingy oh
almost and my country is still the 21st
but congratulations happy birthday
[Music]
okay Patsy donkey
for the red super chat oh it's Japanese
name but an English text I would love to
watch you play
Rhythm Festival on stream somehow live
songs have been added please consider it
incidentally the newly Written song
has the same composer as the bgm of ssbu
Super Smash Brothers Final Destination
there is a Thai Kono touching fan here
live songs have been added when was that
Guna should play it not me Kura is good
at that game and then I think she would
be happy if there were whole life songs
in there did she
PlayStation when there were whole life
songs
already she has oh okay
well I don't know
I don't know
[Music]
um Rhythm games I'm so bad at them
I actually was sponsored good for her
[Music]
Desiring
Riven games from me is
dangerous I don't I'm not like as
against it as I am of like horror games
because at least Rhythm games are cute
but I don't know
maybe someday once
if there's like
two
two two what do you call them Bongos
that you hit
uh taikos
can like gouda hold one and I hold the
other one
is that possible
we can make it into an off collab
[Music]
but it would probably make it more
difficult even
it's one Taiko but one drumstick for you
okay we'll see we can just share
drumsticks Maybe
[Music]
it's like super super hard challenge
even for gouda because she has to focus
on only doing one
or is that easier I don't know hmm
but thank you um
[Music]
for the pinky
oh this is my second birthday to
celebrate with you oh I'm already glad
to be okay for chicken thank you for
always caring about us you're the best
time to ever love you
thank you love ooVoo you too happy
belated birthday sorry I'm so late oh my
God I'm like 10 days later but
congratulations
hopefully your birthday was nice and you
had some people to celebrate with
you you treated yourselves or something
hopefully
thank you for being here on your second
birthday hopefully your third one will
also be spent at kfp remember how you
could have birthday parties at like
McDonald's and so on I never had my own
birthday party in the McDonald's I
always wanted to but I was only once
invited to one
and that's it but it was always
something I wanted to do imagine you
guys are basically having your birthday
parties at kfp whenever you sent me
something like this
oh I wonder I think it's still a thing
nowadays I would think so for kids
[Music]
yeah
so this is birthday
kfp
very cute that's depressing no why kids
want to have their birthday party there
because they love the food there
it's not depressing
maybe for an adult
a Nifty birthday crown yeah we can make
a kfb birthday crown it's it's basically
an eggshell hat
[Music]
don't know if the kids are still into
that or maybe at least you know I don't
know the seven or eight year olds I
don't know how big are even eight year
olds I can't imagine
you think it's not a thing anymore
[Music]
oh
ball pit of course we have a ball pit
and we have a slide outside
oh good night thank you for watching
at 27 I still have my birthdays at
McDonald's no way you mean you just go
there right and get some McDonald's
you don't use the birthday room do you
know your favorite food or so on your
birthday is I think totally fine and if
your favorite food is fast food then
what the hell go for it if you don't
treat yourself on your birthday then
when are you gonna treat yourself
basically
no
jungle things
for the ride can't do sadly a couple
days late but here's my birthday bonus
to go with this mom's salary oh well you
were late but I'm also late so are we
good
happy birthday
birthday
you can also celebrate together
with the others in the birthday room
I'll send you guys a clown or something
to entertain you and endless endless
fries
[Music]
I wish you all the best yes thank you
for supporting me this isn't this like
your third birthday already in here
[Music]
no clown
you're scared no really oh no I already
ordered him he's coming and I paid for
him so I'm not gonna no he's gonna do
his job
I'm not gonna waste my money he's on his
way
unless it's polka well who knows who
they're sending we'll see
do you think you also for a red Super
Chat Auntie how you doing thank you so
much for the support hope you're doing
well I want a kiss for you to take away
thank you
chocolate insomnia shouldn't come in
rather than question blank you crazy
chicken thank you for the rest of the
chat recently you've been very very very
supportive thank you so much for being
so generous I appreciate it thank you so
much
a broken man down soon
fire the elements thank you thank you
Chad today marks the second anniversary
of my kfp career oh I want to thank you
our thank you for being here and
creating all the content for us to enjoy
I'm looking forward to what the future
holds for us as always I'll keep
supporting you until the end well guys
again
thank you I recognize
um an oldie an old chicken when they use
hashtag workout
thank you for still being here two years
very long time I'm glad you're still
here
thank you soon for the big big
long-lasting loyal support hope you will
continue
[Music]
um
did you see the new studio oh yeah I
think I answered this
because I remember answering something
like this looks spacious and cozy with
this new Improvement I hope everyone
will be more comfortable with the
recording
[Music]
it looks looks special did you guys see
huh
why did you guys see and is there a
picture of the inside or what
[Music]
they were pictures I didn't see that
I wanna see
was I supposed to look at the article
I need a special invitation to it from
staff yo obviously I'm gonna miss that
um
fake Hollow fan
[Music]
well I've only heard it's big I don't
know anything else about it
there's the milk Club area in some
hallways
why aren't they showing it off weird
flex but okay
maybe to be like hey this is what we're
doing with your money thank you very
much or what what
is
yeah because it's the biggest one okay
cool flags
uh it's not about being comfortable
though that's what I wanted to say Jeff
some about being comfortable that wasn't
the problem we just need
um
says to it more staff to work it
yeah but also like for me for me it's
also just being far away but you know
look forward to your stories and
feelings the first time you experience
it
um I think
I mean yeah I should be able to
experience it at least once this year
I'll tell you guys
how it was yeah
[Music]
yeah I think we're always hiring always
always but just we don't just take
anyone obviously
[Music]
well I hope they hire more directors
because I think that's the problem
Brandy RJ Duncan 723 Duncan
black which is
twice thank you Phil weasel Duncan oh
and again Richard G thank you thank you
oh he did answer me he did watch the
episode of holds okay
good noise
here's what you do oh my God I'll get to
you eventually zero nine one one two
thank you thank you
zero nine one one two thank you
[Music]
thank you and congratulations on two
years thank supporting me for so long
love love love love love
[Music]
happy belated birthday
Richard I am a tea
presidency
[Music]
five years watching your stream and two
years in kfp anniversary
oh it's a fun journey and I met a lot of
cave peeps without kfb and you I would
be so lonely and lost by Saturday from
studying in a foreign Place alone in the
past two years thank you intention kfp I
find it very courageous of you
yeah I'm very proud of you thank you for
staying with me I will I'm glad I could
like help out a little bit
by being there for you
um
thank you for the support Captain meow
are you you're still in the Forum place
or not anymore
[Music]
Phil
oh how long how long are you gonna be in
Germany
that's a long time already
you missed most of this dream oh no well
you have an archive to watch what were
you doing on a Sunday huh
as long as you can oh well enjoy it
please enjoy your time in Germany
I think it's a decent country to be in
you know
and you should use the time to visit
like neighboring countries too
I pre-ordered new Zelda for 100 bucks or
price in Brazil what store I add this
story this is unbelievable
story sand will take between one day to
two months to deliver just my luck glad
to be able to watch you play while I
suffering wait I thought it was one
month or two months wait wait the
minimum was one day the maximum two
months have you got and by now maybe
full Chuck
are you here
hopefully you got it by now at least
it's been like what two weeks one week
one and a half two weeks
or so maybe
don't see him anywhere guess he's not
here but
I hope you got your game recently or get
it soon
that's really rough that's why you don't
come to Brazil
yeah I mean
I know things on the pinky love whatever
unconditionally always and forever thank
you
I'm happy that you love me
unconditionally I really do feel that
thank you so much
for your sweet sweet caring support
always thank you
that's how it should be
Ryan dungeon Richard Richard
that was from the first
Zelda stream
now we can read the super chats from
Pico niku stream
[Music]
um
two pinkies thank you I remember two
years ago I just finished getting my
shot for the same thing and I was
watching you play Yakuza 7 while resting
and was that the first one you saw
you were gonna do a rebroad because of a
members karaoke that weekend and I
really wanted to see it but I wasn't a
member yet oh the rest is history I love
being a part of kfb and supporting a
wonderful person like you Kiana I hope
I'll be able to do it for many more
years to come
even if life makes me less active
someday I'll always be cheering you I
love you advice
was that just a day where you became a
member was it does Yakuza stream
kind of the first stream you watch I'm
guessing it was just a day you
remembered right
you didn't like watch me and I
immediately remember right
before the karaoke yeah yeah
well you remember you have a good memory
ma'am
um thank you so much for the long
lasting support you're the best
love you too thank you for being part of
kfp
and always being there no matter when no
matter what day what time I mean you say
say maybe sometimes you're less active
future you mean
but for now I always see you so thanks
for always being there
Darien
[Music]
uh Avril Helm thank you for the pinkies
a blushing helmet cute have to be bought
gang for this so here's my prepaid
cuteness tax oh
this is
I'm Gonna Take It
I'm gonna take it it might be for good
but I'm gonna take it it's mine now
belongs to me I was cute too I'm cute
too by default okay
[Music]
no no mean
and evidence look at me look at me
hey
[Music]
what's there not to be cute about that
huh huh
[Music]
you got my super special card wow thank
you
congratulations
lucky
very lucky
um
[Music]
rice over reduction
kicking the key glad to catch you again
I missed you where were you huh it's
good to see you collaborating with
friends too I hope everything keeps
going smoothly I had a birthday on
Monday to visit your super chat but I've
been listening at work kfp and Kiana
always make work go easier
um busy at work
you're gonna do what you're gonna do you
know can't do anything are you here hi
well it's a weekend weekend may be
easier thank you no problem pain bill I
should pay my bills too
been ignoring my bills again I don't
like paying them
I need to pay another
year of taxes actually right now
[Music]
why why why why why is adulting like
this why can't we just live our life
hmm
the whole year no I think actually I
think she said it's prepayment
yeah but
just reminded me miss kiwama you have to
pay your taxes and update me please with
some
documents please
I feel like it
when you buy games on Steam
how do you get the receipt
[Music]
and even get the receipt
email what I never got done before I
think
[Music]
really
is there like somewhere where I can look
at them again
View
purchases or soldiers or something like
that
um
[Music]
you can look at them on your account
page
it's a record on your Steam account page
[Music]
foreign
I will have to
find that because I can't find it now
or account purchase history
and counts for love is it my team is
actually English
count purchase history
account
I'm looking at a different account I
guess there's no purchase history here
[Music]
ah Account Details and then
purchases there it is
it a problem that I always paid with
Steam prepaid cards I also have the
receipts to the Steam prepaid cards
though
here it is here it is I sneeze
did I click on it and then okay can I
get this look as a PDF or so
maybe I gotta go find the emails
yeah thank you oh well back to Super
chats thank you
eating Mike Tyson's ass Duncan
thanks for the recipe Chad
but
stinky to think a timeline exists where
I can confess my love uh undying loyalty
to both of you at the same time
oh wait you're calling her stinky
live life is pretty goop
wait I know I meant good love your group
both of your big heads take up two
tenths of the screen
excluding Dev okay
thank you you think you can test your
undying loyalty to both of us at the
same time but I'm the one reading this
super chat so I think it's not working
but
as long as I know
on Mike Tyson's booty you stinky is that
the stinky thing
wow thank you Sanji Sean For Your Love
loyalty right no love you don't love me
you don't love me
I think you do
kiss for you
[Music]
did you get some Abdullah there's
actually a a syrup as well but it's not
as good as long as you had the real
thing at least once I think
that's all all you needed to do
[Music]
oh
your birthday during your eel trip oh
[Music]
hi why did you not tell me
was it during the trip or right before
so you forgot to tell me
could you
I need to be informed of your soup of
your birthdays in some way or another
[Music]
but
I hope you had a great time you're back
home now what
if you enjoyed Europe
to its maximum
as much as he could made the most out of
it it's my birthday today happy birthday
Abby
well congratulations is it really really
really
[Music]
looking for the top decision
Evil Genius
thank you for the recipe chat at
delightfully chaotic experience
collab
that was fun we had uh interesting
conversations I had fun playing that
game in the game
with her making up weird stories
um
yeah the the nuts I I wish I could uh
undo that whole composition to be honest
I feel
I think it wouldn't have uh
gone that yabby
if could I would have just ignored what
I said
I just you know looked past it like you
guys do
something you know
just ignore me
[Music]
sometimes you just have to ignore me
sometimes
[Music]
she doesn't let things slide yeah
anyway I'll have as much fun as much of
this as I can get things
is what you call her the [\h__\h] her name
is but okay you don't call her like that
that's okay um I think it's okay if only
I call her that
my birthday was two weeks ago
yes
yes it's three happy belated birthday
why did you not tell me what the hell
congratulations
thanks for telling me now spending time
here's the keys when you catch it
um
this certainly is a stream you two are
hilarious thing you you know yo I had
fun with her I had to hold myself back
do not ask gouda for another collab
for the coming week
I hold myself back I was like okay we
had two in a row
maybe we're good for now because I'll
also be a little bit busy coming week
with learning choreography so
what's up sub Channel
she's welcome to stream alone on my
channel too if she wants to
[Music]
I know chumbas are hungry oh I know but
you can't always rely on me
I don't wanna
I don't think she's annoyed but I don't
want to risk annoying her
we'll give her a week off and then
and then maybe I'll bring her in again
in terms of collaborations
we should do a Minecraft cool I'm doing
we kind of work on that stuff that we we
said we would do
um
I think I can get that talk going again
maybe it will be not just not just
samitori but like the whole group
stunk yeah stunk let's go stunk
[Music]
you're welcome oh oh the weather has
been so nice recently I want to do a
real pikuniku
I was talking to my friend about it we
should do real pikuniku and both of us
make something maybe I make muffins she
makes something else something savory
and then we have pikuniku it'll be nice
I only had I I bought a picnic basket
and I only had a picnic
once I think
last year I think I think it was last
year or even the year before
it's it's difficult to tell time
so this year I want to have at least two
picnics cool
with my picnic basket
[Music]
the chicken is typing BBB
it could be cbbn
some
[Music]
I think
wait which way which way
one two three four one two three four
okay one is Bean
and then the other one is ah it really
is
it might really be a comma
[Music]
uh comma B comma B comma what's comma in
English
comma
comma B comma B comma B comma
comma is just comma oh okay
in German we say but coma is like a
cooler way of saying it
with Kato
Zen yes yes yes yes before you even
start
[Music]
no a comma or none of it doesn't come on
it's like directly translated
um
stroke
like at stroke stroke right at you know
where you put it at Stroke by
[Music]
you say I think maybe in the trail you
use it
I would say comma in like a mathematical
situation
but then Bachelor is more in like German
class and so on
[Music]
mm-hmm
does it sound awesome really
[Music]
I am
Skylanders
[Music]
actually a bit less than even the one we
just read
oh God that will be the last one though
Cause I'm lazy I'm so lazy I'll wait
wrong one
tada
[Music]
I admit it finally it is true Cruz
action happy Mother's Day young that was
a Mother's Day Jacob 47 aldecution type
induction
mean foreign
[Music]
thank you for the pinky happy Mother's
Day you've always done so much to raise
and nurture the chickens in your care
grounding us when we misbehave consoling
us when we're sad inspiring us and even
changing our diapers hope Mama today has
a Happy Mother's Day too thank you very
oh and I hope you had a good Mother's
Day I think
uh from
maybe for me wanted
you're close with your mother aren't you
I feel like I saw something like that
maybe maybe I'm imagining
no we don't consent about the diaper
changing we should just wanna
keep the dirty diaper all day or what
[Music]
hmm
okay you'll be stinky stinky chicken
there is no diapers
hmm
and then you're just gonna poop
everywhere and then we have the problem
that nourishama will be angry with us
I don't know man
foreign
that's where that came from after all
[Music]
okay I poured some more water I need
water
[Music]
or Evans out
you
[Music]
Heaven's L feels the need to immediately
rectify
himself
is that the right word correct himself
and Loki apologize
don't worry I wasn't I wasn't gonna like
take it in a bad way or so
[Music]
cute
gives up so fast
ah
[Music]
Not Unusual room enjoyer I wasn't gonna
put him there anyway
[Music]
oh it would be cool yeah playing like a
Lord of the Rings related game at some
point yeah maybe why not JoJo thanks for
the pinky hey my first Super Chat feels
weird being able to do this anyways the
point of this is that today is my very
good friend moza's birthday and she'd
really love it if you sang her Happy
Birthday also give my shoe to her please
she deserves it oh you have a friend
called moza who likes me too is that so
happy birthday to you happy birthday in
your shoe happy birthday in your pants
too happy birthday
there's no two because you sent the
pinky sorry Jojo
you miscalculated but you got a song at
least
yay a little bit late though hope you're
able to pick this one up somewhere
you know how my birthday song goes by
now
it's in your shoes it's in your pants
it's everywhere
you should you shouldn't be shocked
about it anymore
oh
I didn't consider that
well okay I'll rethink my song for next
time
and the only one like
the window here and I didn't it's not
Mother's Day until October I still want
to celebrate with the one that who
hatched me and took care of me and all
of us since we were little eggs eggs
mama
[Music]
you guys are cute for considering me a
mother
a little bit of a stretch but thank you
very much hope you had a lovely Mother's
Day and you know congratulated your
actual mom too please
thank you so much
the last Hazard one thank you soon
[Music]
rabbit hole
wow
hi I thought you went well okay I'm
happy about that wow Brandon now
induction
[Music]
a small list of most visited countries
places in your opinion for someone who
might want to make a newer trip
it's it's difficult because I haven't
visited every place in Europe yet and
I'm sure there's like many
um more great countries that I can't
really judge yet
[Music]
um I would however definitely say Italy
capital and there's some other
[Music]
um
cities in Italy that are worth it as
well I would say Switzerland although I
mean
it's in the continent but not in the EU
but I mean while you're there you might
as well go to Switzerland because it's
[\h__\h] beautiful no matter where you go
and
for once I guess you could check Paris
but I I don't know yeah it's all right
are you I mean you should see those
famous cities at least once right
um
in Spain I haven't been anywhere besides
Valencia I think but I I think for a
city trip
Madrid and Barcelona would probably be
cool places but especially Madrid I
think
[Music]
well mostly you can just go by going to
the capitals most of the time I would
say
um
I have
I don't know ah
see I haven't really been to Poland
before
check I just went to a casino but you
have to see Prague in Czech
that is
100 you have to
um
I think Amsterdam
also
have to go
oh yeah and all the north Fern ones I
can't really say I'm sure they're
beautiful
[Music]
and and worth looking up I I can't judge
it yet
yeah Prague however like everyone in
Europe and everyone who went there too I
think will tell you Prague is incredible
like the architecture is just incredible
I think even though I haven't seen it I
would put Prague like up there on a
similar level with Rome I mean Rome has
all that like historic
um ruins and all that but Prague I I
don't think it has Bruins like that but
it's just incredible architecture
people in Prague very nice
really I don't I don't know about that
either but
oh yeah
I've been watching like videos from my
YouTube channel I think it's they're
they're from Czech
um and they make videos about mostly in
Czech but also in general in Europe
about scams and all that and in Prague
there's a lot of scammers
I think it was Prague
yeah probably
yeah a lot of tourist traps so be
careful like there's this one trap scam
that happens a lot it's like uh when you
go to an ATM and you take out your money
sometimes there will be another guy
close by or right next to you on the ATM
and they will then ask you to change his
own money
with your bills because he only has two
big bills they're too big and and uh you
you have so many smaller bills can you
please exchange and then he gives you
something that's like not usable anymore
um
apparently very common there but also
seen in some other European countries
never happened to me I never saw it
either but I saw it in this YouTube uh
YouTube channel that it happens a lot
and this this YouTube channel they like
go up to them and they stop them and
they try to follow them and you know
bring them to the police and all that
but it really doesn't help much
solution never talk to anyone ever
oh and also that there's like this Bank
dad is like everywhere
and uh like a change bank and it's an
absolute scam but so many people fall
into it because they see it everywhere
and sometimes you just gotta change your
money I guess the exchange rate said
absolutely crazy because okay The
Exchange rate's okay but what they don't
tell you or don't make too clear it is
written there but they don't make it too
clear and I probably wouldn't really
look at it either I wouldn't know this
either
um is that they their interest rates is
it interest
they have just crazy fees on top of it
yeah
that are Unthinkable and
they don't take it back after you gave
them the money like if even if in the
same moment you change your mind they
won't
they won't give you back your money
[Music]
so as you logged in there's Randy
account what the [\h__\h]
careful scary
I've seen like this this thing where
like the ATMs like behind it is an
actual ATM and the front is like fake or
so like what the [\h__\h]
I don't get it that's scary though
similar things we're just the the the
key thing is fake or the key thing has
like something that like saves your key
that you just entered
on top of it what the [\h__\h] oh your card
skimmers what oh I'm glad I probably
never ran into something like that
um
[Music]
my partner was grabbed by one of the
scammers trying to put a bracelet on her
hair that was scary got him to back up
yo yo yo yo yo yo yeah especially after
those videos that I've been watching I
realized because one of the scams they
also introduced was those bracelet scams
and I realized oh
remember my trip to Rome and I think I
told you guys about this dude giving us
bracelets
um and and like little little like tiny
elephant sculptures and all that and
first you know I was just taking
pictures of doves I think and then my
mom was standing around so he started
talking to us and and wanted to like you
know ask us some questions
uh and then gives us one bracelet and
it's
same thing gives you one person for free
and my mom also normally is like
skeptical of this kind of thing
but fell for it too
and we're like oh thank you wow free
really really really we were like really
really booties like yeah yeah
so this is for you
and then the more he adds eventually
he'll be like okay this one's for free
but the rest you have to pay for
and then at that point like I felt bad
so I was like okay don't really need
this stuff the bracelets where the
bracelets okay I guess with the other
the sculptures like I don't need this
[\h__\h]
but yeah so apparently this is also
super common
in Europe in general
yeah that's how they get ill well next
time I'll know next time someone says
this to me if I'm a tourist on vacation
somewhere I'll be like nah I don't want
to get scammed thanks I like say it
clearly like [\h__\h] you
in downtown L.A they hand out free
mixtapes really
is that what they have instead of
bracelets here's my main tape we want
another one another next one is not for
you though really
no apparently
you could like they don't seem too
aggressive if you want to give it back
they will take it back I've seen from
like some footage where they tested it
out they will take it back if you're
like oh okay then I don't want it if you
want money for it then no thank you and
they'll take it back but also if you
like if you're really good walking away
without listening to them you get the
first free thing and just quickly you're
like okay bye
bye then run away I should work too
and if they run after you and they're
like okay no no no no no no no no no
then I mean in the end you can still
give the bag
dumpster fire mixtapes
scam scammers it's not worth it
yeah I mean it won't happen to me
anymore I think generally this kind of
stuff it happens to you once
and then hopefully never again
[Music]
ignore them yeah but I feel still bad
like about other people who fall for it
and also they kind of I feel like they
ruin the image
I don't want people to go for example to
Austria or other European countries and
have this kind of [\h__\h] happen to them a
feeling when Brewing the image
oh there was this other actually funny
scam
apparently there's some scammers who
will like be in an alley way
um and have they're like supposedly
artists but all of the artist printers
just just printed on paper and they put
it on the ground you know some artists
they actually do this and sell try to
sell their art on the street but then
there's some who are like just printing
[\h__\h] on paper and then if you step on it
by accident because it's like a crowded
Alleyway they'll be like I have to pay
for that 50 bucks even though it's just
printed [\h__\h] aren't they they
probably stole it from somewhere yeah
but you might step on it and then
they'll ask you because and then you
know a lot of people actually probably
it seems like it works quite well
because they feel bad for stepping on
the art because first look it might look
like they actually painted this and
they're trying to sell it and you
stepped on it yeah yeah
that works quite well when it does
happen apparently but I don't think you
would step on it I I could just easily
walk around
you've seen it at anime cons
what like as an actual scam or
oh so they wouldn't do that right
they're just
not with the same intention right
yeah but for real that's ridiculous like
if you put it on the ground of a
business busy alley
um I think I would still be able to walk
around it but still
[\h__\h]
I would look at it and be like yo you
didn't even paint this did you I don't
feel any brush strokes this is pain this
is printed
printed again
so many scams
um
well I would hope to be like that but I
don't think I have the courage in such a
situation either let's be real that I
just this wouldn't even happen to me
though this would not happen to me I
think
where was I foreign
[Music]
thank you now I'll find it
I think
oh
I hear thank you thank you
foreign
[Music]
ER can you even bring that in a plane I
don't think so are you sending a
proposed
mail because nine leaders
you can't bring 9 liters did you put it
in your luggage
hope it didn't explode
we must have really light down doodle if
you guys don't know I'm doodling is like
an herbal
um fuzzy drink from Austria that's
actually really good
[Music]
has um I think a lot of uh people would
compare its taste to elderflower but
it's like not only elderflower the
elderflower is strong yeah but yeah
fizzy fizzy
[Music]
um
Milly spread thank you soon for the
pinky High bars enjoying the mostly calm
and comfy Dallas dream perfect for lazy
Sundays or today's also Lazy Sunday
haven't received replacement ski gloves
for the ones I lost in Austria I'm
staying home and Chris the mailman has
problems fitting them in the Meadows
[Music]
has been very busy
maybe wait a couple more days or months
or
no
the syrup but I tried the syrup and
if you tried the real deal once okay but
if you have never then don't try the
syrup because I think it will give you
wrong uh impression
and it's difficult to
figure out how much syrup you should
actually use to get the right taste if
you never had the OG
you just put in a little bit but it's
not enough
[Music]
and
um that 1999.
[Music]
give me 13 thank you
thank you blank thanks for the pinky
time to bet for me good luck and have
fun Dental thank you very much
sleepy time for me as well soon
hopefully although they said I was gonna
make a schedule
I'm gonna eat food and then think but
let me look at my schedule I don't
really I don't even have it planned out
well just yet
[Music]
I am going to
I think my Korean lesson should be on
Thursday normally just coming wink
[Music]
so let's do
an early Korean stream on Wednesday
[Music]
gosh I don't know what to do I don't
know maybe
Friday and Sunday
yeah
just casually started scheduling things
what is this
Phoenix social when's my return do you
say only one two yeah I'm looking if I
can
I think I have space for it
here again
um
passport two on Tuesday
and something even shorter what could I
do that's even shorter
tomorrow
I'm gonna do something short tomorrow
Hotline Miami too
for chat reading I don't know if
I don't know if nah it's not that much
nah
[Music]
it's not but it would be short
trying to put us tax evasion
oh I saw that somewhere
Star Fox 64 is two hours if you do two
rats what so short
y'all have some proper way I still need
to record that other song [\h__\h]
um
I said I would record it this week
I recorded one not two two songs this
week but I should have recorded another
one
now the detective from games I'm keeping
those for if I you know if froggy wobble
escapes again
ah broke like
right I forgot about let's play the
spider
we could do slay the spiral run but it
might not be as short as I'm hoping it
to be but okay maybe tomorrow then
let's fire
um
Maybe
maybe 6 p.m
um
now wait I'll do Korean stream on
Tuesday passport two on Wednesday
evening
maybe oh I have a recording at 7 00 am
on Tuesday
[Music]
that will apparently end until 9 00 A.M
so I'm probably recently awake at that
point maybe I'll have the Korean stream
really early like at 10 A.M or so
foreign
that'll be really shitty for EST and PST
though
yeah I I might need a nap if I take too
much time in between but if I do it
right away after
hard to say
[Music]
okay okay now let's do it
um
later now I can take a nap
so like 2 p.m 2 p.m 2 p.m is still good
time for Korean Bros
[Music]
ah tomorrow they released that video
right right they just go did you guys
see they always announced those videos
like three days early that was the thing
[Music]
that was the thing where I said I have
no idea and I don't want to do it but
then they were like please kiwawa
that was the thing guys
the program where I was very uncertain
[Music]
it's uh this one
is about calories
but this made me look up a little bit
um roughly what calories foods have
generally speaking that was still
Bamboozled so many times I don't know
what they were referencing
a lot of times I think you know you will
see you will see I think a lot of it is
just guessing from their side as well
hmm
so this will be uh tomorrow uh 6 p.m jst
I think
pretty early for me
a little video on the official program I
think on the same day right after or
right before we recorded another program
that will probably follow a while after
[Music]
um
looks full of confidence I didn't do too
bad I think but you will see
foreign
[Music]
and I will just put up my schedule
probably tomorrow but 6 p.m play the
Spire is I think pretty certain
um
little skit videos are always great yeah
but like we record them so far in the in
the past that it's like like I
completely forgot about them
but it's good because then suddenly
and
[Music]
blank I think I read that one right good
luck and headphone ninja thank you for
the pinky and Brandon insulin
uh
Crimson Phoenix
[Music]
this is the one where I got really
addicted huh
[Music]
thanks for the long stream bus it was
really really nice and comfy you're
welcome
I will continue providing you guys with
really long tutk streams whether you
like it or not I cannot do anything
about it but I think so far we've done
good progress
we have the second temple finished I'm
guessing even though after even after
you finish all the temples
you're probably only like one third
through the game in terms of like main
storyline I would assume it's always a
big twist after that and I'm I'm
guessing there's a little bit more than
just one twist for this game
so
I'm faster than the viewers for once
you're doing the courage
all of them I'm not planning to do all
of them no [\h__\h] no [\h__\h] no I'm just
doing the ones that I see and that I
feel like doing
yeah
hopefully plenty to at least make my
backs feel comfortably spacious
no hundred percent run for me
[Music]
[\h__\h] no
Over My Dead Body which will never
happen because I always rest from my
ashes there will be no dead body
thank you Ray Ghana leave my dog looking
for the top down kitchen
um
[Music]
the pizza from yesterday I'm gonna make
it warm in the oven and then I will also
eat the rest of my food
thank you guys I'm tired
thank you for your support today hope
you enjoyed the stream you gotta play
okay you have until Friday
to get ahead of me
you know how much progress I make in one
stream
so you know and even outside of my
you have homework to do unless you don't
play the game at all then whatever
foreign
[Music]
like immediately went over to the fire
temple so I mean I did some some side
quests in between
but you can just go there immediately
thank you 've been playing in other
parts and there's no overlap and put it
eventually it will overlap
sample do you want to do next whichever
is like the recommended one
other one
Doras
bought the game two days ago oh dear
good luck
okay we'll do the Zoras next wherever
they are no way to go
hmm
I can't stop yawning God damn it
probably is it in the gorilla one you
think so but we don't know for sure well
yeah probably the longer one
um
you did water before gorans Oh
thanks for the orange the potato the
lake Elida okay oh
[Music]
oh
yeah
Gerudo is fun too
let's go little drinking
stop hitting the keyboard you're gonna
break it
let's go
let's go now
I love you guys
a little bit a little only a little bit
[Music]
my my
no
maybe more than a little
bye -bye I'm gonna lie in my bed now
um
[Music]
good night guys I like sleeping uh
diagonally on top of my bed good night
[Music]
you
can you guys turn the PC off for me I I
forgot
fresh fresh batting
no hairs yet where are my cats though
there's no space for my cats on this bed
it's a one-person bed
the hell
[Music]
can you turn it off of a combo of being
commas I'm not sure
I keep on pressing the same which one I
mean I don't know is there even any
combination at all that you could press
on the keyboard
that would work
because I don't know of any
[Music]
just press everything
that surely will work I feel it
happening and during recently nothing
good night
so my head is hanging up all the blood
is the blood is
ah flooding my head
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]