[Music]
e
C
K it's takiar from Hol life English myth
and we have a very special announcement
for Hol life English today so let's
introduce the cute girls who are joining
me today starting from
cie everybody Mory kipy from H live
English here maybe I should do my
greeting hold on me in the song it's me
Mory kipy from H live English thank you
so much for having me today and it's I
pyrus is it's Iris from H life English
as well I am so happy to be here let's
go let's go and of course we have the
legendary
fu
I'm together
we nice this is our lineup today and we
are going to have a big announcement so
any assumptions of what it possibly
could be girl oh my I wonder what it
could be maybe it might not have
anything to do with Ian who
knows maybe a JP
thing we might be Shilling JP stuff
today I don't know maybe maybe it could
be some
snacks snacks everyone together connect
the world yes everyone needs to
eatting yeah well pretty good uh that
those are some good guesses yeah but I
guess we should make it clear from the
beginning so you know what you're
getting yourselves into so let's let's
announce
it the announcement
is the Blu-ray for the whole life
English first ever concert connect the
world that was held in July is going to
be
[Applause]
[Music]
released W yes as you can see here the
sales begin this year November 30th
jst yeah nice it's so soon oh my god
let's go that's right that's right after
this what yeah oh yeah the pre-order uh
will be available right after this uh
from the whole life production official
shop uh from 12:00 p.m. p.m. p.m. is it
p.m. noon. is 1200 p.m. I always get
confused by that I think it's 12 p.m.
yes 12 p.m. 1200 p.m. noon onwards so
first will take a look at the album
jacket
art oo it's pink and
purple I like it I love the logo a the
logo is so
nice it's gorgeous it's like what do you
call this kind of um coloring there's
like fluffy yeah fluffy oh yeah you can
tell it's definitely a very cute package
like there's definitely some a really
cute concert inside
there
inside so true yeah and then if we look
to the next slide we have the set
list
W I finally know what some of the songs
are
called oh you didn't know no like you
know like how there was like a couple
songs that were like that were revealed
that day that
was and they don't show the song title
over there I'm pretty sure so like true
so I'm just like what was that song
called and now I know oh let's go oh
yeah like goodas good new yeah both of
those yeah so this this is the set list
with 18 songs looking really packed mhm
and inside it even comes with a booklet
with a lot of pretty photos from our
performances
t
everybody looks good so
pretty like all of our Idol dreams came
true I know it's very colorful yeah very
pretty nice memories so the pre-orders
start from today 30 of November up to
December
25th 6:00 p.m. jst so that's not even a
full month so hurry hurry hurry let's go
get it yeah grab it yes don't forget it
don't for get it you have to have this
on your shelves on your bookshelves
forever for one to watch one to to keep
in your room one to also put in your
closet and maybe want to gift to Future
whole live English fans who missed out
on the sale right so basically buy 10 of
them that good yeah so be sure to get
your hands on the Blu-ray to relive your
memories of whole life english's first
concert connect the world the first ever
overseas concert by whole life
English yeah please support us thank you
yeah so well since we're all here today
I think we want to look a little bit
inside the DVD maybe maybe some sneak PE
let's go we can show it we can just show
it to people yes but only maybe only the
moments that we personally chose that we
want to show up how well those are the
best parts though oh my God we're so
generous well you know you got to show
the best not everything's the best but
you know it's hard to choose right I
think everything's the best everything
was great
amazing we're going to call this section
your favorite moments C ski from connect
the world C
[Music]
ski yeah for the non-japanese
understanding viewers uh it C SK it
means what girls I like this I love it
love it like this this part is what I
like this is the good part exactly so
before the stream um we actually had
everyone in here fill a questionnaire
about their favorite moments from
connect the world so next we will be
looking what everybody answered and
we'll share the footage with you guys we
watch it together and it will be the
same footage as the footage that will be
on the Blu-Ray so
hi yes yes as for for you girls were not
part of the concert were you even you
you weren't even members official yet
right
no watch you waiting right we watching
live but along with everyone yeah we
still we were still pre-debut then and
we had lots of lots of very complex
feelings but we were just so happy to to
see our so
fun that was the concert where we like
they did the sneak peek door slam
uh yeah the door the door like what what
is this
door guessing people were guessing from
the beginning and we were right we
thought you guys were going to be like
super evil creatures or something yeah
we were guessing like villains or
something we're de dogs
okay I'm so scared take
me so even though you weren't in the
concert you still like happily picked
out your favorite moments I think
and actually it might be like an
interesting point of view to have it
from someone who wasn't actually on the
stage
right what it looks like from you so
we'll be we'll be going through all of
that so let's start the segment we'll
take a look at the first answer for the
Cocos ski favorite moments and the first
one will be from oh I think from
me yes what did you choose my favorite I
have I chose a lot of different ones but
the one that was chosen to Showcase is
from Amelia Watson solo
[Music]
song cute excellent choice we cute yeah
let's watch it shall we watch
it a
dozle so
cute look at those high kicks she's
going off a cape is so flowing
[Music]
so it's to stay quiet I know right it
just makes you want to yell and Shout so
hard where's my pen light G
me she
TL she's so bouncy yeah you can't help
it bounce along with
[Music]
it it's so Ganky I love it all right
yeah the energy is just off the turn
right I love
[Music]
youy it's difficult to control
[Laughter]
ourselves wow look at her flap when her
arms on she could
joinor she looks like a
bird she yeah flapping slapping I
remember how this was also a game too
yeah they made a game for it oh yeah so
fun they made a game classic going above
and beyond
yay so I think I think I personally uh
chose this one because while I am I'm
number one I'm a gosling but
also uh you know I feel like she just
has this really cute charm Amelia Watson
she's just just you know she just has
fun she bounces around the stage and you
know she just makes everyone in the room
happy with her energy and with her cute
personality so I love her so much
everyone loves the gremlin she's so cute
yes yes and it wasn't shown in this cut
right now but at the end do you remember
when she went
like so good
yeah good am moments my favorite am
moment
so uh next up let's check out uh the
suggestion from Fu what do you got from
me we have B by
psycho oh yes a Prime Choice right it
was so
powerful you know just like the emotion
the emotion that Bas
had it's
hard dance right the dance her
expression mood that was like the
opening that was like the opening solo
act right everyone excited right off the
bat everybody was ready to go fire right
yeah and was after too
so like the gap between the two of them
M very very nice both very energetic but
in different ways right exactly Well
everybody's super different in Holan so
everybody gets to shine in their own
way so shall we check it out
watch it Doo Oh God it's it's already
they're dropping the Beats already oh
it's really nice being able to see all
the choreography so close up too I know
thigh we've had so many good thighs so
far in I know but they're so thick let's
go just b control and the power the stop
and
start her skirt is so
short you're
looking look forever I like the shortest
skirt I don't know I mean it's good
though I like it oh god I've already
said this but this is my favorite Holo
Yen song so it was very exciting to
watch the VOD and be hyped by it you
know
wow wonder
between
is oh that camera work that camera work
was great that was solid good it pierces
your
[Music]
heart crazy yeah yeah yeah oh yeah yeah
yeah choreography yes wow those kicks
that was
wacky my K is so
cool no don't stop playing it
what that was that was not psyo but in
Japanese psycho right
py I love that double meaning mhm so
good you can use it in so many ways you
already Shar like a couple of your
thoughts but yeah why why did you choose
this one ah well it really it stands out
you know because like uh in whole life
there's a lot of different Idols right
but Bas is like so just it's so intense
and so RW we really like all the the
expression that they should put into it
especially the choreography too and just
also the facial expressions as well at
the course there too yeah yeah now the
choreograph out the chart yeah and she
made the choreo
herself I want to hear
more like making your own
Coro I can confirm is a pretty difficult
it's it's a crazy skill to have so
amazing absolutely talented individual
so thank you for your
choice next up we shall go to Callie
Choice what do you have for me wow I
really it seems like I phoned it in but
I was very broad with this one what I
chose was it's basically the equivalent
of saying everything everything is great
hear me out showing everything then yes
here's the whole Blu-ray you don't even
need to buy it n the way that I kind of
explained it though is that I think
everybody chose songs that were perfect
for them if that makes any sense that
was my favorite part of the whole
concert I think doing live shows it's
really important to Showcase like what
you are best at especially in this kind
of situation where it's not just your
show but it's the entire group's show
right so if you're going to be given
that opportunity you need to choose like
what is going to make you stand out what
are what are you the most proud of what
is what is you like the essence of you
what can you show like as in that part
of yourself in the show basically I'm
going to ramble on forever and ever but
basically I feel like I mean I just feel
like that's the most important like when
I chose wanted wasted I felt like I
really wanted to kind of shine a light
on like I guess screamy edgy vocals that
I try to kind of accentuate my work and
you know fauna chose something that was
very perfect for her you know soft and
Angelic and and M chose a song that
could really show off her vocal prowess
she's a fantastic singer too but she
chose a song that was perfect that I
remember right I was blown away by her
Goosebumps Goosebumps I guess we can
take a look at the compil they had to
make because you said everybody I don't
think we can cover everybody but let's
take a look at the the M compilation
compilation that's
me I really expect
that I really wanted a guitar I really
wanted a
guitar so cool I'm pretty happy with how
it turned out lights are so cool too
yeah was pretty neat they got my jump
they got my jump in there it it's I
don't think they're going to show it
here but if you want to see the jump
make sure that you get it the you really
like the
jump oh
yeah I'm really proud of this
song it's my favorite one I love the
chorus this is great thank you very
happy with that it looks like everybody
excited the visuals are so neat Love
thej is Great oh yeah that was solid
yeah so cool oh my God oh my God I don't
usually look at something like this and
say kak but maybe it's a little cool I
don't know you can't explain this in any
other way it's kind of
cool
maybe go that's this s this song is so
cute
it's so
funky I love the city poop perfect for
her that's another thing that's what I'm
talking about she chose a song that's
perfect for
her yeah this is like revealed this is
the first time she she saying this yeah
y
ever I love
[Music]
it it fits her voice so
well so cute so gentle
so pretty I love her singing voice yeah
she really excels in this kind of like
City poop poppy environment soft singing
Beautiful let's
go cute
shark
[Music]
refrain cute the dance is so cute
too the little PES I love the little
fishies in the back too it's hard not to
be ch by that little the little smile
that just pops out of
nowhere ah the little Japanese line I
like it yeah I
know
wow that's right that's right hip
s slightly robotic is dance move on that
part yeah it really fits it works you
know
yay we are both very very different but
but sell at different things
that's I mean it would be weird if H Yen
was full of people that were exactly the
same right
yeah good good song actually I also that
was one of my choices too yeah nice
solid it was a solid she revealed that
song on that day but she since hasn't
released it I know I'm waiting I'm
waiting for the right time yeah I asked
her the other day good up when are you
releasing the song I'm waiting for It Go
go go is it coming with an MV
oh maybe what
she yeah we're waiting for it good but
okay uh we have another another choice
or like two choices perhaps from is
right what do you yes yes so first the
first choice that we will probably
introduce is cron Solo solo ten Mayu
which is also a song that was um
performed for the first time or shown to
the for the first time in that conert
just like G yeah I was like so surprised
when it when it showed up I was like
what is this what is this bop that's
just playing right now and then you
start hearing like the rap and I'm just
I'm just going in Heaven from the crony
rap cuz she has such a cool voice and
when you hear her go rapping with the
the cool dance moves and like the I love
the guitar riff in this
song so like anyways that's I really
wanted to show that to you guys that was
my first choice uh we're not going to
talk about my second choice yet let's
talk about that after watch this let's
watch
Cody starts with the ra let's
go
oh oh
god oh the Y I love that part Y is so
cute cool so cool her
legs looking at her legs I'm looking at
her face oh yeah you're not looking at
her ribbon there's many things to look
at here a her thigh I think she has like
no spats they couldn't give her spats
yeah they couldn't give her too short
too skirt is too short
yeah this is also when is she going to
release this song man oh she also hasn't
released this yeah I know she hasn't I'm
pretty darn sure what's going on so
powerful bless the public with the
release
please
wow yeah she's
[Music]
awesome Wow Let's Go cron
go beautiful oh it's so blue so pretty
blue is heror this this is perfect for
her she's amazing w w w that was good
that was
great and then my second choice was I
think a choice for a lot of us one of
the choices for it was just it was so
Godly because they're from such Godly
mythical creature I mean a
talents the the myth group song
nonfiction performance was off the chart
like I know you guys performed it you
guys performed it in your 3D collab but
the way you guys performed it in this
concert like with the VJ and with the
crowd and everything it was just chef
kiss I definely did not you worked
really hard on it no tears No Cry it's
like like no wonder you guys like the
first gen you guys are like the the
legend the legend of H you're very sweet
Iris let check it out
yeah I also really like the choreography
too oh yes oh the
wave I still remember all of us
practicing this together yeah I can
imagine how much work it
[Music]
took say oh my God the VJ with the solo
it fits perfectly just like the MV yeah
yeah we put a lot of emotion into I know
I love like the expression it's like
slightly sad but like not not def
definitely not sad but it's just it's
just so much emotion powerful yeah
powerful yeah
yay my forever let's go really it just
makes it that much more emotional and S
of hits you right
yes a look at as girl all of your hard
work
yeah everybody's so special I know it's
like every every one of you guys like
put your own like charm into this like
you definitely need to watch like a
whole thing like buy the Blue-ray for
this performance
please thank you oh actually I I also
suggested this I can I even have my my
um description explanation as to why and
I I want to I want to say it so I I
wrote so happy to perform together with
my girls and I'm so proud of how far
we've come the practice and performances
we've done for our showcase and this
concert this year strengthened our bond
so this was a really special performance
for all of us that we are really proud
of I think and everyone's personality
shines through while we tell the legend
that is
M that sums it
up I know that is that sums it up pretty
much that's pretty much what I wrote to
oh God yeah but been through a lot
definitely this was one of the
highlights yes but there's so many
there's so
manys true every every song was amazing
in this concert but oh God it was really
hard to about Chad how about Chad what
is your favorite moment what
tell us in the live chat or in the
comments of the Vault afterwards us we
watching you we're totally live right
now we're totally live yes comments oh
oh your favorite was Iris oh oh yeah
yeah too my favorite always
Iris AG great oh yes your favorite was
uh M oh yeah me too me too yeah M's
ghost oh oh do I hear Sparks oh yes
solid I didn't want to go right after
that let's go it was good very very
solid en was amazing yeah I know Ena was
also
amazing ena's voice is so Angelic so
many cultured opinions in the chat thank
you you guys are right you're all right
everybody's
right okay so that's all of the answers
for the Kos ski favorite moments from
the concert thank you everybody it was
really really nice
nostalgic to relive everything
right Nostalgia so before we end why
don't we share a few more details of the
Blu-ray one more time for all the
viewers to make it uh easy and clear
Cali can we start with you okay sure
thing so guys listen up the Blu-ray will
be available after the program ends
starting from 12:00 noon on the dot
onwards don't miss it don't miss it and
don't miss it also pre-orders will start
from today November 30th all the way up
to December 25th 8 uh not 18 p.m. um
6:00 p.m. jst so don't miss it buy it
during that time frame let's
go and finally it'll only be available
for pre-order on the whole live official
shop so please don't miss out on this
channel you'll get to enjoy all the
memories of the first ever overseas
concert by H life English all over again
with us please make sure to get it don't
don't miss it
now yeah thank you girls so we actually
have one last surprise for
everyone what what is this surprise what
what do we have what do we have any
ideas for
M more snacks something yummy yeah more
snacks yum
yummy donuts can we eat it donuts donuts
oh no okay I'm sorry it's nothing to eat
but uh to celebrate the Blu-ray release
we're going to make the live performance
part of the theme song for the concert
connect the world free to everyone after
the stream so you can watch the exact
same footage as available on the Blu-ray
but I think we're also going to watch it
together let's do it let's go okay so
much sharing sharing is car the world
Doo here we
go look at that we're all here oh God
for what a cute song it looks so
Wow Let's go I love the shape of the VJ
in the back too
yeah you turn around you know
choreography so much because you want to
dance along too yeah the rainbow pen
lights and like I don't know this
performance also help it really reminds
me of like the first like JP um concert
too yeah but now it's like our time to
shine you know yeah it's like you know
we know that you know hen is going to
grow right now like in this footage it's
like 10 of us but now we have 15 of us
and it's going to become even bigger and
there's going to be more on the stage oh
I'm so excited for that
too would that be
amazing I want to see where it goes you
know yeah picture is
bright Miracle to
life
I think
amazing I love that you can hear people
cheer as everybody sings yeah no it
features everyone the support is
[Music]
amazing I really like this
song I know I didn't think the song
would also be called the connect the
world and the lyrics really represent
each every remembers like unique person
so it's really I love that everyone's
personality gets across the song know MH
I never thought that when they asked us
like for like suggestions on what we
wanted to name the concert that it would
end up being like the name for
everything oh yeah connect the world I
they were like oh we're using your
suggestion IR was like let's go
perect
Iris I have a confession I also
requested the exact same oh shoot was it
just me it wasn't but I mean me laugh I
guess I know we had the exact same
thought the synchronization yeah the
synchronization and why did stop not
tell me then
huh they're like oh we using your
suggestion I was like oh but that makes
so much sense
then yeah know that was great I mean I
did give a bunch of suggestions but that
was the first one yeah know that was
like the only suggestion I gave I think
I mean it fits so perfectly though don't
you think yeah this part is so good
because you know there's the other songs
in
it oh so cute oh yeah the SSS
callback dream even the Coro is actually
like it is basically yep lot of
references
MH respect to the
S always
respect
man step by step so
cute part
two you just want that's you know it's
so happy and like contagious right right
it's just so idly so idly yeah idle
dreams come
true I also this is my favorite part oh
yes the rainbow the rainbow's so pretty
I especially love the ending yes I like
the harmony for
it
Contin it will continue of
course kind of feel feels musical to me
feels like a musical number at the end I
love that whole live English musical
connect the world let's make it let's
make
it
come that was
great it's so
nostalgic can we do it again I want to
do it
again we talked over so much of it
true well it's fine they'll get to see
it afterward themselves yeah and if you
buy the blue right hey maybe we can do
another one of these That's why you
should support us and buy the Blu-ray
yeah yeah might even be a bigger bigger
concert who knows if we ever join again
we know we we reach for the stars
right our new friends can join should we
do one in space to reach for the SP
Stars SP a space full of pen lights it's
like millions of headlights you cannot
count them the Stars just like the stars
imag English stage is already kind of in
the space anyway so we're on a
spaceship yeah we're looking for the
aliens where yes
intergalactical so yeah that was
beautiful it's going to be up on our
Channel separately as its own video as
well after this Stream So if you want to
you know watch it without our voices
interjecting right you can look at it uh
on your own and cheer on your own for us
thank you so much for joining us today
on this uh stream stream video where
we video where promoting our Blu-Ray so
at the end I would like to ask everybody
how did you like it did you enjoy
reminiscing in these memories how was it
let's start with Callie yeah I mean it's
a really important
Milestone I think for Ian as a whole in
the beginning there was just five of us
and doing this kind of show would be
impossible um and we've made so many new
friends along the way that I keep
feeling like um I really hope that more
of these kinds of things happen and so
it's a really important memory I think
and I'll always look back really fondly
on it um and I hope I hope it can
Inspire the future Generations too uh to
keep having fun with us in h live for as
long as we can make you guys smile
yeah I guess that's
it beautiful thank you thank you thank
you let's move over to Iris what what do
you have to say well like this concert
itself it still feels like like
yesterday when we were all like you know
performing and like Kelly said this is
like you know such it's a milestone it
is a very very important day for holo
live and it was like the the first
really official big 3D event for all of
us and you know I think it is just a
start for many more to come hopefully
and even bigger you know bigger places
like I said reach for the stars and like
it's just you just how do I say this
like um including all the you know
Advent girls that have just joined and
like you know also future Generations
like Callie said you know eventually
this I'm just hoping that this will
become as big as like you know even like
Fest you know like the Fest that happens
every year but for like so this is a
start of something beautiful and New Y
so true so true a good cause to
celebrate I would like to hear from F
separately so let's hear
from
separately well I I think M you feel the
same way too of course they feel the
same way but we
just we're happy to really be included
the the newbies and I you know it meant
a lot to us to be able to see our sen by
dancing and singing on stage and you
know it was it was really emotional for
us cuz we are still just you know puppy
dreaming of TR to yeah you know and you
know oh you guys were still in jail
yeah we didn't have Wi-Fi so oh wow what
a beautiful jail cell to let you watch
it yes condition yeah but you know just
watching you all on stage it really made
us want to work hard and hopefully like
dream of maybe one day we could be on
that stage to all together I believe it
the idol
dream I think at that time for us we
still hadn't really processed that maybe
things would be like that potentially
maybe one day so we're going to work
hard so that it can come true right
seeing the audience also like emotional
passionate too it was it was an amazing
experience definitely did not cry yeah
like
you know all together all together with
Senai and other ADV MERS so that
hopefully one day all together we can
connect the world even further
too connect the
Galaxy connect all dimensions of space
and time and existence and reality and
space w that's so ambitious but we
should stay ambitious it's good yeah is
always good hunger
okay thank you thank you girls for your
opinions oh everybody's so passionate
about it I love it d d so that's it for
today thank you everyone and please look
forward to the H life English first
concert connect the world Blu-ray
release D for watching and the German we
say if he doesn't byebye see
you bye everybody byee catch you
later the blay blay BL
go byebye
by