[Music]
oh
a
[Music]
[Applause]
are you
ready for some
[Music]
CH it's to M
time to
[Music]
time
K hello I've combined my gorgeous
outfits please
look it looks like I'm naked
underneath
K uh
oh oh the under Bo the under oh wait
here there you go that's the perfect
that's the perfect angle just for
looking at the under Boop
though
nice oh oh oh this view too like you can
see nothing on my shoulder nothing on my
upper
arm nothing on my
oh my uh below the
Poncho oh
man Shenanigans
Shenanigans I shall become
small
okay should I show this part of my body
I look so ah there's so many things
going on on my body right right
now I can't I can't we have to cut it
here that's it's too
ridiculous it's too
ridiculous okay okay I have calibrated
my body you know like every other human
has to do when when they get to work
they have to calibrate their body holy
[\h__\h] this spoon is piping hot Mama
[Music]
Mia okay
B sorry for the little delay I actually
I was doing so many things before the
stream I finally emptied my suitcases
from the Japan trip then I cleaned the
kitchen like deep cleaning
I even cleaned like the the walls you
know because of the the oil going
everywhere cleaned the sink and
everything I cleaned out the fridge I
throw away the threw away the trash I
cleaned the duvet of my bed uh I made my
bed I uh did the the laundry I hung up
the stuff that was lying around so like
I was cleaning so much uh and oh yeah I
found found I was looking for and found
my cookie cutout thingies
because I don't know if this is like a
negative thing for you guys but I was a
bit disappointed so for me it's like
maybe slightly negative but actually
it's not I'm looking forward to it um
for tomorrow change of plans instead of
uh doing um a Christmas Reef of DIY
stream uh we're doing uh we're doing
cookie B Bing Christmas cookies so
that's why I looked for some stuff and I
looked up recipe and I went out to buy
ingredients for the cookies tomorrow
they're going to be pretty basic cookies
but I don't think I ever made those
basic cookies before so you know we got
to start from zero and become a hero of
cookies
M yes and the good thing is I can eat
those when I made them I can eat them
let's go yeah so lots of things have
been done and
uh yeah I I I have been busy before the
stream cleaning and all that and then I
had needed a little I forgot that I
didn't need anything before the stream
and this is was this was going to be
like a little bit lengthy so I quickly
made myself a salad and here we are
Christmas p this show and then like the
plan is maybe uh starting from the
baking stream that is possibly tomorrow
unless I don't finish Super Mario RPG
today then we'll finish it
tomorrow um but if we do it tomorrow
then every week I want to do one
Christmas cookie baking stream until
Christmas
and then we're going to get good cuz I
I've made cookies before the vanilla uh
qu shape
cookies um but besides those I don't
really have much baking cookies
experience
yeah
so that is the plan let's let's go let's
go let's get into this
[Music]
now and I have a Coca-Cola and a green
tea to keep me energized cuz recently
remember I've been
like I've been just such a blob when
I've been playing this game like it it
takes so much energy from me
man the winter
debuff
uh let's
go that was a cute
remix all right guys H there was
something that someone mentioned to me
yesterday what was
[Music]
that sign me up you can join you can
make cookies
[Music]
too
moleville fireworks okay what the what
am I supposed to
do go to
mville oh wait how do I play this game
again
uh I
should I have to go to the map through
here oh wait what I wait no I have to
leave the
town moleville
town
mville was that that that that one right
this
one and then there's some fireworks or
something and I I have to watch the
fireworks or so or make fireworks and
then I get something cool so what I do
know there's a dude in the mob in the
back house higher up
okay thank
[Music]
you
now in the in the house in the back ah
this one maybe
that's not higher up
though said higher up in the
back
house there's no house
here maybe this is all like maybe maybe
this one to the left okay what about
this
guy yes you like you look fireworks I'm
working on my very old invention right
now I've only got the sparkly St but I a
giving up want to buy one for 500 500
how much do I have let me
K oh okay that's half of my money
sheesh you guys say this is worth
[Music]
it
okay than I just want wait for my
masterpiece come back with more coins
buy my all my inventions all right wait
eh there's more I got the fireworks you
saw the mole hiding behind the boxes
with pink
bow what is what's the next
step a mole hiding behind boxes with a
pink
bow that's the next step why can I not
jump down
here I want more freedom I passed her ah
there she is
cute welcome to my pant store would you
like a shiny
store no tra we're trading
okay thank you please come again
uu she literally talking in uu language
okay Shiny Stone hold it for
later also for now I'm done because I ah
I think I remember they said that if I
don't do this now I can't do it later
this one's so cute
[Music]
okay for later okay okay okay
okay oh it's for secret
boss M okay what are we doing next
what's our current uh
thing ah we got to go to this town where
we were
anyway what's my goal
here can I see it in the
journal maybe in the
Scrapbook no that's memories how do I
see my current
[Music]
goal I got a start taken
away I don't I don't remember
that
but in the main screen it still showed
that I have them all I
think so that's
ironic so what do I do where did they go
did you see where they went which
direction did they go this
way ah yeah
okay the Blade's late what's taking it
so long we need to get out out of
here this is just great Mario caught up
with us oh it's the same person only
only one thing we can do now although we
may rest a little we'll have to swim for
[Music]
it oh my Shark friends are protecting
oh
Chad I don't remember what voice I did M
no it's so faster that star is a gift to
me mate Mario ah to me mate Mario you
spineless bloody dunks have no code of
honor will make you walk to
plank Johnny maybe we should leave Mario
the pleasure of wrapping things up
[Music]
here I guess we'll have to take our
disguises off now oh are they going to
be shy guys
what will it be
what oh one
person oh you're saying this is your
true
form wow I was right I I I ended right
like in front before uh uh a [\h__\h]
boss
battle what the hell I hope I have the
right characters for this
one press a prior car let's try this
let's get a critical hit uh priority to
contact uh I don't even remember what
this looks
like okay now hold on I don't think I've
ever seen it
before uh I need P probably
[Music]
soon he's using
no wait he used water I feel like fire
is not going to be
very
yeah you know let's try it
jumps wow
17 at least he wasn't uh immune to
[Music]
it
M oh I want to try the Shocker hit a
just as the bolt L I will most likely
fail this let's
go wait did I say weakness oh [\h__\h]
uh that scream was
partially me being scared and partially
the like anger
and
tenseness of me not hitting the right
timing
um should I keep in Gino I can't switch
out Mario right so let's switch out
Gino for a nice little heel heal g
p yeah let's do that
and then we'll continue shocking with
mow uhoh oh I blocked even though I
didn't know the timing let's
go oh visiting oh miss you she got you K
merch oh my God best sister let's go hey
sister go
sister
sister nice that's better than my other
attempts with Mario even though it's
just a basic jump
ah oh I did it I did it I think I did it
I did it right because last time it was
double can I make him
sleep
Nice N
with resistance okay well then she's
really just here for
healing let me try super jump
again ah
[\h__\h] I saw like videos of people getting
hundreds man I suck oh should have just
used Mario to give me the
[Music]
item oh well let's do this
then lightning okay
1,148
wow uh yeah [\h__\h] I would like to heal
you Mario
but I can't
uh let's use one maple
syrup oh oh yeah regular I forgot
regular attacks were a thing what he
became
two so did the HP
[Music]
split
so then I if it's two people then now I
should do fun the
bold a a come
on it only did two on the left one but
way more on the right one so does that
mean the right one is
real cuz somebody just said only one is
real
okay so do I ignore the fake
[Music]
one
Mario oh [\h__\h]
what
130 you [\h__\h] kidding
me30
damage 130 from the supposedly fake
[Music]
one uh what the
[\h__\h] how like you couldn't even
withstand
that anyway how do I get rid of the fake
one oh oh my
God how do I get do I have to kill them
both
anyway I'm going to guess that I have to
kill both anyway so
I don't know I don't think it really
matters hey but how do you kill him if
it's like 2 Hp that's all it does to
him maybe I can sleepy time him cuz he
does so much [\h__\h]
damage please cuz the other one has
resistance but I don't know maybe the
fake one n
okay oh God thank God good block good
block
[Music]
M I don't know if I'm try supposed to
try to do damage on the left one barely
Does
anything go for the real one
okay oh [\h__\h] but at least it did 92 oh
[\h__\h] no [\h__\h] don't die
again just as the bolt lands
ha yes oh 27 five oh and he's coming
back together all right uh let's switch
I guess at least now he's back to one
dude let's terrorize
him oh [\h__\h] I forgot oh oh it's still
okay okay okay it was not too late to
terrorize
him Bowser normal attack good oh [\h__\h]
okay uh well we're running out of FP
again
so one
more and another
shocker yes yeah okay I got this one
down this time it did way less damage
though like
half hey I'm pretty sure I had the
timing right holy [\h__\h]
Mario holy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
come
on ah
ah yo am I
underleveled because the fake one got
hit
oh
Ohi m
[Music]
27 I've never ever done so many ever
before that's what you give me I was so
proud I was so proud and it only for 27
damage is so
ridiculous it's ridiculous another pick
me up for M am I underleveled guys is
this fight really this
difficult it's the first tough fight
that's what it feels like man
sh e it that should have been
timed a not
[Music]
again weak ass
mushroom I know Mario's just going to be
healing now let's poison these
bastards what a cute poison
Cloud they resisted but okay wait so
poison would that normally be doing
damage every round is it like supposed
to be dot damage but they resist it so
it doesn't or or or
no too I was too uh oh too early but
that's
fine now I again don't know which one to
attack go for left
[Music]
one well like I can't kill him I'll just
try to continue do AOE attacks so I
don't have to think about who to
attack uh uh FP
that's my only that's my only FP thing
wait I can get Yoshi to help me but
maybe I should do that only
when when he's one dude
again maybe mow can check for the real
one I would prefer to do damage with him
cuz mow is the only one who who can
attack
effectively the Ron takes less damage
since he has higher stats but why does
he take even less damage now that he's
separated what the
[\h__\h] anyway I guess I'll use the Royal
[Music]
syrup
damn
[Music]
a I'll tear no wait you guys you guys
said I should attack normally so the
left one really
it's not too bad that's not too
bad should have been double what the
hell
[Music]
nice oh what's that cute that's kind of
cute there's so many attacks that you
can't
block oh double double
throw oh
okay and he's going
back uhoh someone's going to die
Mario we almost wiped the
party oh sh
holy [\h__\h] I hope he's dead
[Music]
soon [\h__\h]
um holy
[\h__\h] water blast is the main thing that
can make this F difficult holy [\h__\h]
man uh um I have to do damage I have
[Music]
to
um ATT should I attack normally or with
a
special safe if people mow yeah
okay I should heal him though no
yeah let's keep him
alive me
please I couldn't block it I
panicked mow must survive at all
costs he's our Golden Boy
n
missed oh
[\h__\h] what do you think about healing do
I have a item that heals
everybody party party recover oh not bad
I like this item right now very much
dun hey
AOE
heal okay
okay got a
[Music]
double die uhoh water blast no
no uh oh my [\h__\h]
god that's
ridiculous that is ridicul
ridiculous oh my God maybe it would be
worth to nah even even if I bring Peach
into the team oh that recovered my FP
too like for Peach's healing she's going
to use up the FP the whole time we we
want it for
mow but yeah
okay my channel got taken over what some
and that was a double oh we did it oh my
God then I shouldn't I didn't need to
heal so much right at the end feel kind
of stupid for that but
okay
M Mario is now 13 years
old and already has a banger mustache
holy
macaroni m
six why do this game continuously force
me to go for
HP the Boost is always on
HP
five ah yeah we can go for attack for
peach if we want
but does that make sense for
peach I'd say HP or magic but her magic
is not getting boosted very
much there's a specific order for each
character
oh you only got HP for
peach well I would maybe at least go for
HP cuz cuz at least that
one's like seemingly a little bit
boosted she's just support just healing
she does get a strong weapon at the end
game oh for real okay thank you for
telling me that then I don't
feel like bad if I put at least one time
only into
physical and hopefully next time magic
will be
boosted yay star is back
[Music]
Smithy is now in the race for the star
pieces what horrible surprises might he
have in store for
Mario
yay the fight was
intense oh a key and to Mario knowing
you it must have been Bree a breeze
knocking down SP eh by the way my
Pirates say they saw a huge axe flying
across the sky it's probably one of
smiffy's nasty friends go get him pal
well my gills are failing on me so I'll
be heading back down drop in whenever
you have time is this what who's who's
writing this Johnny your true mate
[Music]
it he really found a liing in me
huh what
[Music]
didn't think he would like me that much
cuz at the end when I was like still in
the room after everything he was like
better get out of here faster before I
changed my mind you know so I thought
okay well he's he's following his
promises but he's not necessarily a fan
of me but
now seems like he really likes me sheh
it's a dude thing respect
him usually ha a surface dweller so it's
to be
expected fish people um excuse me
they're called
fish don't call them fish
people uh well what's
next what's
next what did the game tell me guess I
got to go to the map to
see uh oh still here H why is so so
confusing to me I can unlock the shed
now the shed where was there a
[Music]
shed a shed which one is the
shed bottom
left ah oh this
[Music]
place
ah right they're still in here
[Music]
soon you get a very powerful AOE attack
Regino pairs well with the flowering you
can buy from the frog in Seaside town
for 50 frog coins also you can get some
extra FP at the booster
[Music]
Hill you thanks so much you thanks so
much enough of crap dirty old places
like
this hey fella you got us out of a bind
peace brother
swag it was my G and pleasant in here
thanks for helping us out thank you yeah
thanks a lot we should just stop by yeah
stop by
bye thank you for freeing us I've got to
get back to work now but stop by and see
you
there he Mario thank you for saving our
little town of Seaside you're exposed to
fake Town's people and gave up your star
to save us please take this with our
thanks I'm so relieved that all of the
town's people were all right in the
end can you believe he didn't just
kidnap them had the nerve to lock him up
too me and my minions would never pull a
stunt like
that really you seem to recall a certain
someone kidnapping me not too long
ago uh but no one got hurt right all
well that ends
well come on let's scramble ready the
mold in here is bad for my sensitive
nostrils here here we should see the
sights and tell down that it's back to
normal maybe someone here can point us
toward the next star
piece yeah I'm glad that they are
pointing out the
obvious issues with having those two in
one team working side by
[Music]
side strange shop looking for
beetles I'm the mushroom boy did you
know that hidden amongst the regular
mushrooms there are some special ones
and real huh I'll give you items in
return for those special mushrooms but I
forgot to taste them to find out what
kind they are so I'll take a nible first
I'm hoping for a special mushroom but
even if it isn't at least I'll get a
meal out of it you have any mushrooms
ah far out Munch Munch that was just a
regular mushroom thanks for the snack
this is exactly like the tears of the
kingdom stone dude who wants you to
bring him special kind of stone
meat and like it could be like it's so
Random you bring him 90 and you could
get one or zero it's like the same
thing he but this game exists way longer
so did they get like the idea from
here I can just like open the door and
Trigger them like this it's like hello
somebody open the door are you coming in
hello hello are they even just stay open
can you close the door because like the
wind that's coming in is like really
uncomfortable it's making me
sick no all I can do is open the door I
can't close
it wait so did my mushroom disappear the
one that I gave him hello there you were
so brave to rescue us and I'm so
thankful but listen maybe it's time you
thought a little more about what you
wear accessorizing is a big business
these days is see anything you like
[Music]
here
no it went so I gave him like one of my
basic mushrooms or did he cuz I have
these different mushrooms I would hope
he takes takes the the worst one
[Music]
first regular mushroom
so okay yeah he took the the normal one
oh you can have them hoping that I'll
get something out of it
[Music]
regular what if I run out of them does
he then go for the other ones the the
more valuable ones
no they're all they're all
lame I have one
more only regular oh okay and now he
didn't like any of these so
[Music]
far I guess it's a way to get rid of
your regular mushrooms
but H got a lot got a lot of he Foods in
our store you got to treat your body
right M okay um oh there they're really
cheap sheesh you can get more if you
want to get lucky over
there uh so we
need a lot of new Maple
syrups that's a lot of
money
[Music]
M maybe a couple of
these can I sell some
stuff oh can I just sell
this is that what you meant to do with
this to max
out
just you can max out your Feer
[Music]
yes it only gives you one coin in battle
imagine I would have used it in [\h__\h]
battle and then you guys were going to
tell me um kiaha dot dot if you would
have sold this you would have gotten 555
coins you wasted this so
bad oh it gives one
H it doesn't disappear either way but I
will have to use it like constantly to
get like the same amount no that's not
really rord I would prefer to sell it
then you what about the
wallet where did I get that wallet from
I don't remember this
wallet I'll keep it I'll keep it for a
while
[Music]
longer please come Bros okay armor shop
I me anything
[Music]
new
no
weapons oh the Ribbit
stick oh okay well we have a few things
uh that are a bit
better
[Music]
and the
parasol damn I'm going to be broke again
this game really like the
economy they use up so
much money so fast so you at least you
don't like end up having way too much
money at least
now why the [\h__\h] is there a shy guy here
ah this is the beetle guy that you guys
mentioned welcome to beetles our ass we
run a beetle business here want an
explanation I'll explain the
system uh so that you can also be part
of it first you need to purchase a
beetle box which will cost you 50 coins
then go to booster Hill where there are
many Beetles if you bring back the
beetle box full with beetles you can
trade them in for coins and frog coins
check the menu list for more information
uh should I do
this
what male 50 coins female one coin
why are male beetles so much more
valuable like in reality
too E I need to pay an Initiation fee
too what the
[\h__\h] cuz they have
horns
okay h
[Music]
but like this is such a
scam do I have to do
this oh thanks for the memberships oh my
God thank you optional just a mini game
oh you guys don't think it's so
important then okay ain't worth it it's
a
scam okay
wait what's next did I oh wait I didn't
do
uh okay I'm still not
done
oops they told me to go to the
Inn
so let's say hi Mario how nice of you to
stop by it's quite a track from your
place isn't it out there there aren't
many people passing through please rest
up before you go
no uh
why did you want me to come
[Music]
here them telling me to go to the Inn
was just an
ad in the end this one mov here for
[Music]
good why am I
stuck why am I
stuck Mario if it's a star that you're
looking for I may be able to help you at
the far side of L xand is a town made up
of reformed monsters reformed monsters a
mouse came by the other day and I
overheard him boasting about a star of
theirs I don't know exactly where this
town is located but if you follow the
road
okay I think this gave us a new
[Music]
goal monster town
oh oh maybe this has been here for a
while and I just didn't see it cuz it's
cut
off
h
what is
this oh oh I can
choose oh oh
ooh but why when there's this way of
getting up as oh can't can't really get
up
there
oh H
sus
ah but then there still should be one
here
right jump North from the platform
North where is
North
[Music]
h
okay so the middle of the screen at the
top okay yeah that that I thought that's
what what you meant with uh North
possibly did I get what a flower thingy
F
FP tell me these are reformed monsters
right they're not going to attack me H
H shun
wow it's an ant but it's also like one
of those Samurai Warriors
shees um oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] still plenty of damage but I forgot
how it it
works2 what the
[\h__\h] uh
huh please be effective n n vaker up you
don't need to get stronger you're
already [\h__\h]
strong
[Music]
yeah more
more let's bring in
Bowser oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] y not bad more
power he wants so much
power he is a
[Music]
coward hey 93
m what's with him like what he gets to
attack after buffing himself come
on that's it right no not
yet but now
now hey squashed the ant go back to your
ant
hill Oh wait I have to oh the others are
still there I thought that counted as
one
enemy
[Music]
n maybe I I maybe it has to do something
with m M maybe
not how do I get
there there's a hidden platform you got
to unlock first where the dogos
are oh wait they're gone now oh but
they're back now
[Music]
[\h__\h] ah I really have to fight them all
come
[Music]
on here then platform do
go I found
it maybe I can land on
[Music]
it
y well I did get the Frog
[Music]
coin nah now the now the doggo is the
special
enemy h on the level okay I'll try not
to run away from them
all sorry that was kind of
weak oh oh oh yeah right there was that
part at least that one's pretty easy to
fulfill they resist
it
nah
oh oh car kiss you try to kiss me I
don't kiss
ants you kiss my
butt mow is scared poor
mow
no FP no now I'll try to get out of this
battle without using any more
FP I mean I want to use a flower box
nice nice actually nice after the
[Music]
battle yeah yeah see wasn't
necessary maybe maybe fire ants were the
cause of my butt
problem I mean the the tear in the pant
[Music]
so ah oh no I wanted to see if there's
like something else over
there can I not get there yeah here
nothing else
huh okay a [\h__\h] I forgot to take the
FP ah
M but they're both normal enemies so
let's
gamb nice nice there is a chest up there
I mean it oh I do still have a
notification oh W I didn't
realize
ow okay then let me look again is it
again on top of the other chest
[\h__\h] no strong one okay
[Music]
easy
oh on the very left okay did you guys
see in case you didn't see here's me
telling you to go see it h i was in too
sensei's live
today that song was so difficult
but it was a lot of fun and I'm so happy
you know Cho sansi and Like Me
Senpai they invite me to these things
I'm like really honored and happy to be
part of it oh nice there's so sweet why
are they so
sweet of course you didn't know I was
going to be there actually I mean there
was an a little announcement but yeah
it's usually a surprise until it
happens oh cute they can jump back up
there that's
[Music]
funny
oh yeah dance with Ollie and CI and CH
s it's pretty pretty difficult song they
use cannons
oh I was going
to right you do
this nice five
FP and
then
uh heal up heal
everybody
nice oh I was I was ready to fight you
guys what's that
healing are they doing damage they're
confused
why cuz they keep on shooting each other
through the the the
canons I'm not
surprised I would get really dizzy
too oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] I'll have to watch it later yeah go
watch it
later
oh wow that's a lot of damage but the
spider is
still up on its many many
fies they're permanently confused oh
that's kind of funny I welcome
that cuz then I don't have to concern
myself with them too
much sleep sauce no
no why would you do that you little
[\h__\h] good spot to grind he are they
endlessly spawning out of the cannon no
no
right
oh I was trying to attack the spider
what the
hell
nice gsh up
oh should we switch I guess we should
[Music]
switch nice double fist
attack I haven't seen the end of them
yet you don't really really you don't
really need to grind on this game h i
mean the previous boss battle is telling
me a different
story
oh self-destruction so cute I love
it ah have you guys seen oh 34 months
thank you L Ru love love have you guys
seen uh day two of the Advent calendar
was indeed
me indeed it was
me
whatever
we need to get up
there how do I get
up
what can I
not you're no race made it extra comfy
thank you I thought I mean I know a lot
of people know what these markets are
like but I also know a lot of people
don't really know so I thought I wanted
to show you guys um you know in a little
mini Vlog kind of way if you don't know
what I'm talking about we have begun the
Advent calendar for this year again and
I was in day one and day
two mhm and for day two I basically come
on get in there no I can't I really
can't I went to Christmas Market and
bought a lot of yummy food and like
filmed everything m and then I edited
into a small cute video that I hope you
guys
enjoyed I really like Christmas markets
but they they're so overpriced like for
real for real for that kaar the pancakes
a small relatively small uh serving of
it and like one tiny cup of uh children
punch I
paid minus the you know giving back the
cup 15 15
bucks if you don't give back the cup
then you can keep it and then it costs
bucks
H well it can be worse because the
children punch is at least generally a
little bit cheaper than the alcoholic
one so if you want to get the alcoholic
ones which are the bump because there's
more
variations
then it costs a bit
more so now you understand maybe a
little bit more when I talked about it
the other day that I I asked my friends
to go to the Christmas Market with me
and they were all like uh I don't want
to because so
expensive
shees I have
to so how what the [\h__\h] how do I get up
there
ah
to maybe I have to do it with a jump
Stam
[Music]
probably got to make their money somehow
I can only
imagine how much
money the people who are doing those
stalls are making during this Christmas
Market season I think they're making
absolute
bank but it's only once year so I wonder
what they're doing the rest of the
year like some I I didn't show uh that
much oh this one's empty
huh actually I
show or I missed showing a lot of things
too there's like a lot of like handmade
soap or handmade wooden products oh [\h__\h]
or handmade this and that so I'm
assuming that they have like their own
shops or like online shops or
so why am I so
[Music]
stupid the stall cost oh yeah I'm pretty
sure that the stall also costs quite a
bit of money to rent because damn you
know you're going to make
bank that is
[Music]
certain
nice nice
Gino
but yeah if if there's like a lot of
these Christmas markets
close after Christmas like after the
25th or
so I
screen um but I hope that uh I can find
one that's still running
beginning of January cuz I I want to
show some
girls the
market there are some exceptions that
are still running like longer so I'm
sure it will be
fine well yeah plural but not they're
not as I said before they're not going
to be
overlapping sorry I forgot how to jump I
legit thought it was a that's what I was
like
hesitating before the fight as
well why am I so confused oh but I feel
like the the enemies is kind of stopped
coming in there's like h less now so
they don't spawn endlessly I
think girl forgets how to jump in Mario
game
I'm
ashamed there's a hidden treasure here
surprise oh these are bouncy flowers and
this
one nothing
special F
flower it's
like how I say the word
think
why would you miss you little [\h__\h] oh
Mario resists that
she what are they thinking about 15
damage but it's their weakness
n sometimes these things don't make
sense
you thought I was saying
think what the [\h__\h] you little
[\h__\h]
die Bonk
Bonk
no I'm
scarecrow CR scarecrow scare crow
scarecrow
Crow these don't do anything where could
this treasure be no no no no go
[Music]
back B
bam between the two what okay
sheh ah let's go six what the actual
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] I don't
[Music]
understand
huh explain
Min Noto oh my God on what you little
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] that's it oh well Mario's dead so I
can't M no no no no
uh
unbelievable
unbelievable get up Mario you lazy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I am out of patience all right this is
an AOE attack even
better oh have I seen this
before
probably but it's very impressive oh
yeah good damage yeah yeah and yet this
shitty ass thinking flower is still
standing there won't be much more
thinking after this
hope you think it's really worth
it that 220 damage was pretty
sick
[Music]
nice five random attacks
oh
what we got a l
love come
back probably tells that
Mario every night when he leaves to buy
out mil
milk leaves to buy milk revive a pal you
learned that now good
timing
it
9 well I have to holy
[Music]
[\h__\h] hm did you troll me there's no
treasure
[Music]
here between maybe when I jump from one
to
another
[Music]
ah go away
B
[Music]
why are you so stupid I hate you so much
you little [\h__\h] get out of the way you
are in the way get out of the way what
do I
[Music]
do what should we use are any of them
strong no then I'll save my
FP
mhm uhhuh once again Gino Gino the boy
who can go
twice or even price if you let
him holy
macaroni Mario can't do that
M Gino performs with
triples o baby is literally what you're
going to say
when oh baby a
triple yep y Ultra
jump for repeat jump oh that's cool
that's like low key and AOE low
key
um free okay I think it's finally time
we get uh some magic going nice finally
something else is being
buffed oh why am I so
[Music]
stupid and down we go wow
really we jump down I mean I did say I
wanted to jump down in the previous map
no
oh I was supposed to talk to him
no oh Power
Point wait wait let me go back up
hello this
SK can you set me back up skim me up
Bobby
yeah I really just need to let myself
talk because I say things like skim me
up Bobby that's even worse than what I
did before I said it different before
Scot me up beam me but I said skem me up
poy what's the actual phrase beam me up
Scotty skem me
up
Bobby
Bobby then now we have free versions
[Music]
free I do not know
English SK me SK me up
B SK SK get or something like that oh
beat me up yeah next one will be that
beat me up Scotty beat me up Scotty I'm
masochistic as
[Music]
[\h__\h]
I have no idea what that means I learned
it from narissa who learned it from
beimu and I'm not aware of its
implications uh you will actually beat
me up Scotty thank you
wowy thank you oh and then you
disappear welcome to the sky Bridge it's
a big tourist attraction here
Yahoo
hold want to challenge
it okay I'll need five coins from you oh
dear well just jumping from one to
another no oh if you fall anytime you
lose on the normal coaster blocks won't
fall for oh you can jump to the next
block by
tilting thank you for basic
explanation mhm
okay
m m m okay I'll try it
once no I mean normal will already be
difficult for me
what I didn't expect something like that
[\h__\h] wait
what oh wait ah I'm kind of uh oh oh I
feel like it kind of like yeah yeah yeah
yeah
ah wait wait wait
uhoh if they get me while I'm like in
the middle of the platforms it's
probably not going to let me stay yeah
yeah please beam me up
Scotty they actually let me I thought it
was over when I fell
down
he's back probably means it's
over so one more
time just one more
[Music]
time
I had the the timing like usually it's
like you jump and then immediately you
jump over the bullet sometimes I think
every third or every fourth it it's uh
coming at you a little bit slower or a
little bit later
actually yeah no but it's not because I
lost the Rhythm it's because generally
the B button wasn't really uh
activating kind of stuck think I need a
new
controller you can you could probably if
you turn up the volume even hear that I
was pressing the B button several
times one more time Bobby one more
[Music]
time [\h__\h] oh yeah it's more like the the
direction too like I
pressed I pressed the direction stick
but it it's not going where I
want I'm going to lose all my money
[Music]
here
o one last
try not my
[Music]
specialty
I spr I I jumped too
late I jumped too
late
[\h__\h] I want to win it
once just once but I'm wasting so much
money
[Music]
M I can afford
it what's in the cave I can't get in
there right now but maybe it's like
connected to the mini game you have
to maybe go with the mode that uh where
the blocks fall down if you stand on
them and then go like with the last
block you go to the height of the cave
and then you jump in from there maybe I
don't
[Music]
know [\h__\h] Direction
stick
careful oh [\h__\h] didn't didn't work
[Music]
again
cool
[Music]
I couldn't save
myself one last time for real for real
please I cannot just give up here I need
a
win ah a
[Music]
wait I I swear to God I swear to God
a
[Music]
[\h__\h] controller why is this
controller so
[\h__\h] the buttons are like barely
[Music]
reacting
[Laughter]
[Music]
it felt
ticklish it's quite
[Music]
ticklish
no I can't believe it I can't believe it
I'm stuck here forever seems like we're
doing a Mario stream tomorrow oh I just
realized I forgot to buy one of the
ingredients anyway I forgot to buy the
butter the worst case I can buy it from
the um tank Stella tank
Stella [\h__\h] my [\h__\h]
throat [\h__\h] what's like going on this
can't like is is everybody who's trying
this like having these issues and and
and making this into into a wa into a
huge entertainment
[Music]
Source I a gas station yeah yeah that's
what I mean oh my God Kelly did this for
an hour e but surely not just the normal
course right like surely she spent more
time because she was trying them all and
it's not as [\h__\h] as I am
right just jump forward while jumping
over the bullets not
separately
what oh
H jump forward only not straight up
oh
oh oh
[Music]
okay not
hold
ah well it doesn't always
work because of this Joy sck being a
little [\h__\h] no it's not working please
let me thank
[Music]
you
that was close again but this way it's
definitely easier I didn't realize that
was a
thing want to double your winnings no
get double the coins if you make it
across on the same course in one
attempt the course is harder and if you
fall you won't get any
coins I mean I definitely already lost
money anyway um I don't know not worth
it
okay okay five coins but I lost like
maybe
damn
unbelievable oh oh is this a nice
Mouse I haven't been here in a while
I've been busy TR
Casper traveling around nice
Mouse it's
[Music]
Casper why are you heading is it Monster
town by any
chance Hey listen up look for the well
where the ant pops up and proceed after
it keep following and you'll find your
way on the ground once there monster TS
just around the corner I'll see you
there Casper I miss him bless your hard
work thank you so
much hick hickey hick hecky
hick where there's no ant here there's
no ant here so but I want to see what's
there anyway right should I enter
nonetheless
[Music]
wowy oh there's the end proceed after
it it it won't let me oh there we go
there we
go I made it what now or do I keep on
following it oh it's not just once oh
now I have to fight it okay that's
[Music]
fine Amelia I
am
materializing my inner Amelia
Watson
I'm
[Music]
oh if I ever do like a whole life
English quiz or something like that
again either for the members or for
viewers if it's for the members the
newer members like promise and Advent I
should ask where did the amoko meme come
from because it started from that
cooking stream right where she didn't
show show up right but even now it's
like very fitting very suitable in my
opinion every so often I ask myself I'm
a
doco but that is quite the trivia to
know where that came
from I'm oh yeah and I'm a muted ah yeah
yeah yeah I'm a
muted oh
wait was that I'm a muted and not am a
where did amoko come from is it from the
same
thing she had K I was probably sleeping
snowman FS FS oh
oh
Magic it's both Alma was always m al
does tend to be low
volume not necessarily low volume but
like she's just uh doesn't talk much in
collapse unless it's like a one-on-one
collab then she's kind of forced to H
but uh yeah if it's more than oneon-one
or even like a free people collab you
know like the one with wait which one
was it [\h__\h] I didn't look I
forgot
[\h__\h] um but yeah the like if it's like
one with GDA and me for example you know
that's just uh that's kind of like
there's an obvious Focus
there where we you it's also I I think
it also depends on the
game if she enjoys the game
then no let me in there we
go my game skills are very unique mhm
they truly
are
yes I must agree with
that it's
moving now it's showing up in
both
you want to
[Music]
fight
nice oh my God that
hurts y
oh my God he's
dead
well Daisy want to have some fun the
girls just want to have
fun oh girls they're weak against ice oh
I don't care I if there's not a special
enemy there I I currently don't feel
like using up my FP oh nice it pick me
up okay it's it was in here so let's
does it still count as me following the
ant I think it did
okay is there anything else
to
[\h__\h] oh was it fine was that what I was
supposed to do I thought I still had to
follow the the ant but I just messed up
by leaving the
area but there's a Casper here hello
again isn't this incredible it really
does look like the end of the world
doesn't it no it's to Spooky for me I'm
heading back to monster Town see
you follow once more okay but what about
this place though oh oh can't even maybe
I need a super
jump not a okay so I do have to follow
the ant once more
okay oh you can get c a
[\h__\h] no way you did that you little
[\h__\h]
ah I want to get more coins more coins
please more
coins I'm no no
no no
no I can't believe
it yeah tomorrow Super Mario RPG
[\h__\h] not wasting my time with you guys
mm-
[Music]
no
no finally part one
hey got a coin do you get one coin or
more coins and it just looks like you're
getting one coin oh there's so many shy
guys yeah come
here
okay
one you could make endless money if
you're good at
jumping
[Music]
for some reason until now I thought I
had to jump into the
wildwind well I can just walk
in oh I got a
coin one more no
no that little
[Music]
[\h__\h] yay y
yay
baited yeah this shitty
ant baiting ant B
no little shitty an
hole
no I walked over it NY the
[\h__\h] get in there get in there there now
why am I struggling with this it's
unbelievable none there none
[Music]
there get in there see it's not that
hard oh my God okay this is the last one
though this is the hard one oh oh does
that
count oh I think I did there's a cloud
here that's new do I
touch oh
do I have to like corner it
oh
formless it looks like it's a
relative of mow to be
honest can I even attack this
thing no probably not an this is an
optional
boss exp
[Music]
Farm special attack
okay ah there it is cute gaso
stinky stinky
[Music]
stinky do I still have to use special
attacks only I wonder
[Music]
oh no
nice only before it becomes the cloud
that it is what the
[Music]
hell I wanted to refill my FP
but Mario being dead doesn't look so
good
so let's do now it misses
again I don't always miss
so okay so now I want to fill up the
FP with a maple syrup I guess
t
nice
H I'll try a super
[Music]
jump W but so little damage I hate this
attack I never want to use it again such
that like all of Mario's [\h__\h] attacks
are so useless like the fireball too
like what effective but then there's
like 12 damage are you kidding me like
what is this scam all his attacks are
[\h__\h] scams scam you that should be
his name mhm
[Music]
mhm that's also scam cuz I'm telling you
I got the timing
right
Peach don't
[Music]
die
Mara you're just you're just better off
being a weapon for Bowser just stop
fighting on your
own weakness but F that's what I'm
talking about that's what I'm talking
[Music]
about
M oh really
mhm you [\h__\h] killed Bowser he just
entered the
battle Yeah Mario needs more magic
then how much HP does this dude have if
it's a boss then he probably has a
lot prior to
[Music]
contact should I
boost Okay so his physical attacks are
boosted oh almost down oh
[Music]
M don't kill
me no
way what did I boost
[Music]
for
uh-oh
is this boosted too still 15 only so
probably
not okay whatever I have killed the blob
The Blob that was mallow's father
probably 30 XP hm okay uh we're not
doing so
well everyone needs a big
heal nice uh f he is fine okay you
shitty ant stop doing this oh my
God it's so
fast we killed malo's father malo's
father let's go oh now I'm here uhhuh oh
no I hate
everything you little
[\h__\h]
okay
no why why is this so
[Music]
shitty let me
in let me in let
me let me in let me in now you want to
fight now you want to
fight what if I don't want to
[Music]
fight I am losing my sanity that is a
correct
observation but I'm still very Ganky and
my throat is okayish I've recovered from
the screams so
far did you guys see my Spotify wrapped
up thingy for
artists I know it's like probably
compared to
others it's really not much like others
like C and I don't know I didn't see Su
say senis but yeah can't compare myself
to them so I will not I'm I was was
personally very proud of it you know I
feel like that th those are huge
numbers and actually I didn't think so
many people were listening to my music
so which one was it which one was it the
bigger one right what was
it I have to follow but which one was it
God damn
it you guys
know was it the smaller one or the
bigger one he's not coming
back this one's the bigger one the
bottom one oh [\h__\h] now I lost track of
it I think it's this
one please oh thank
God need the
[\h__\h] oh my
God
[Music]
no more ants and sand [\h__\h] all my homies
hate sand
oh
no oh well oh my God
no not ideal yo let's
go hey I feel I gave me like two level
UPS holy
[\h__\h] did I miss the quality
chest you had over 2,000 minutes
listening thank you so much yeah so for
real for real everybody who listen to my
music on Spotify and also other services
I just the only one I got is for like
Spotify I don't know if other services
do this but yeah thank you so
much for using your precious time to
listen to my music I'm I'm really
honored I feel like that was is quite
the
accomplishment I'm I'm happy very happy
with it
thank
you ooh nice everybody's getting magic
attack you earned it yay oh my God I
wish I still had the star what the
[\h__\h] if I wasn't like running around so
stupidly Maybe I would still have it oh
but they're not even moving why
why wh
why it's
creepy let's kill
one there's a guy behind the boxes
there's one here too go behind the
boxes
[Music]
what
then I figured it it's because I listen
to your YouTube instead oh yeah I mean
that would make sense feel like a lot of
people also just use something else
that's not Spotify so those are of
course not the like final numbers of
who's
listening hello you're looking for a
star
what 400
coins oh he disappears I wanted to check
how much money I have
400 should I have should I say yeah
worth it [\h__\h] will I get the chance
again should I reload my
[Music]
save I wanted to check my money cuz it
doesn't show how much money you have for
some reason it's kind of
stupid reload or like maybe just like
this see here again what the he's not
[Music]
here yeah poor game design for real for
real like every time I have to go back
to my inventory to see how much money I
have wasn't there you guys were saying
there's another location where he
there's a person behind the boxes or is
it like he's either there or he's there
and if I miss
him then it's
over
go to world map you can reload the save
okay how do
[Music]
I
yes we'll also let you retri the initial
star what do you
mean
he has unique dialogue if you below oh
what do you mean that's an initial
star there's a star in the first chest
so you can get more free
kills hey you mean this
one yeah let's go get
more so already way
faster
no no why is it over
already I was way faster than last
time is it
scripted so you can't have the star in
the next room because you would be
getting too much H from the Next
Room the
hell
oh wait a
second oh big
misunderstanding I
thought I thought you guys were saying
with the star that I can buy also
because of the price I thought it maybe
made sense that I'm getting one of the
story
Stars not
a
star
but that makes more sense because of the
the way the room is set
up uh well 400 I would have
paid for for like a story
start you're telling me this is
a
star I guess I'll still get it because
you guys say it's worth but she
that is quite the misunderstanding it's
purposely designed to be oh really like
he like it's a scam like but I mean what
you get out of it is still a lot of exp
so I guess it's not the worst but I'm
not wrong for being
misled was that their intention all
along
Maga all right then give me that star
cuz that looks like a lot of
exp you guys say it's worth it
right they chose to use star for du
purpose in this game that's so
scammy what a rip
off
ah I mean yeah I could kill the manually
but
like
oh
[\h__\h] A almost all almost all of
them time saving I guess oh
wow that's more than
10 I got to go for
HP
okay should I kill you
[Music]
manually that was free Oh
Oh I thought it
was uh like
13 okay I my
brain I
[Music]
can't please forgive me
the [\h__\h] are you doing
here for 100 coins the shortcut will get
you back to the surface no you already
scammed me too
much what's with these
[Music]
scammers my fortune I'm kind of
interested in that for 50 coins that's
not too
[Music]
bad should
I it's probably going to be something
funny
happening see the free faces on the wall
hit them in any order and you'll receive
your
fortune oh would I have gotten that
without like even if I wouldn't have
asked
[Music]
you
oh
H if you proceed for the pipe next door
you'll have many friends in the future I
already have so many friends I don't
want any more
friends if I proceed for the next pipe
I'll have lots of
friends did it matter which
pipe
you can do it in a specific order to get
a big
treasure I once again have failed the
system are these my friends are you
saying these are my friends what the
[\h__\h]
what
what I was I was supposed to have
friends here
huh
[Music]
n exp
friends well I did say I don't want
anymore oh this is
confusing oh oh but that's a lot of
damage on both of
them hey that's so confusing when he
switches that like kind of like easily
breaks your rhythm
H not bad
though all right that enemy didn't feel
that strong but hey we got a frog coin
actually I realized something was really
weird in my last stream of Super Mario
RPG and comparing it
to my first stream and the current
stream and also to dendo
playthrough I even more realized how
weird it was last time I got Yoshi like
every second sometime honestly
every every almost
second uh fight I got the Yoshi thing
now I haven't gotten it a single time so
far
today something was crazy like maybe
bugged even last time for me it was
normal last time I that was
normal oh this doesn't open until I kill
them
huh think I
must W nice one
hit attack
up
ouch
[Music]
resistance I think Fireballs have high
chance of dropping it she appeared so
much that it made your eyes tired yeah
maybe yeah yeah that may have been the
reason wow the attack up is very
effective
[Music]
oh no mow don't go to sleepy land
no
Yun in
Japanese Disneyland is like when people
don't want to say the name of Disney
they call it the the land the country
the land of
dreams
wow Japanese members use that all the
time I I I I don't know why why we're so
careful about saying Disneyland it's not
illegal to say Disney or Disneyland yeah
we got to be careful of like you know
singing their songs or showing their
Graphics or whatever but besides that
saying your
name I don't know why everybody's so
careful about
it Crush
Earth eruption hit a right after the
rock pokes out oh okay AOE that's the
AOE you guys were mentioning
right
oh it's just a thing in Japanese talk
about Brands oh
maybe I I feel like they're like they
don't follow that that often though then
only when it comes to
Disney no actually never mind like some
sometimes with holot talk uh you know
the question where I ask them like which
restaurant which convenience store Etc
and then sometimes they're like really
concerned about answering it a few a
very very small amount of them but um
somewh like I don't know if I should
answer this because of sponsorships
Etc I mean we do have like sponsorships
with like convenience stores so I I get
it but it's just one question in in a
little stream so I don't think it's
really going to affect your sponsorships
like you should still be able to freely
say which one is your favorite uh
convenience
store but maybe if you if you're looking
at things from a business POV really
seriously and you personally want to get
more more uh sponsorships with one of
the convenience stores then I guess you
don't want to you know ruin your options
but yeah
I don't know I personally just really
don't mind but if they say they don't
want to answer it of course I don't mind
like usually beforehand they would tell
me I don't want to answer this so then I
get rid of that speed
question so where are my
friends I've been
bamboozled ah nice SC I guess this is
the way
back those were my friends and I killed
them oh
no oh you get
faster W I never got so many coins out
of these things
[Music]
before
oh big brain wa I did I didn't really
expect it but I
oh I just wanted to try it out oh my god
I didn't even realize there was still
Treasures in here he
[Music]
free but there's no more right now now
there's no more
surely oh my God damn girl I'm a
genius
sorry I'm not accepting visitors past my
bedtime is this like a matter of talking
to him and bribing him the yellow Tower
will get you to the Next Room your
fortune determines which room you'll
arrive at if you're lucky you'll run
into bom and monster town will be just
beyond
[Music]
him
okay let's
go I'm
confused
uh give me the key and I'll let you pass
through I I can't I I I have a key right
then how do I give it to
you
huh do I have to go into my
inventory oh wait where is that key that
I had ah that was for the sh the shed
the key is Monster T you don't go back
into the gcha
[Music]
again what the frog
coins your fortune
deter wait
so AR into the room okay okay okay okay
okay I thought I had to go back all the
way to where I got my
fortune oh now it's a different one I'm
so hungry I wish I had something to eat
all right let's go I wonder if that's
the right
one there it is
okay there is a pipe maybe ah that's
what they meant with the my friends are
beyond the pipe
cuz with this pipe I will get to monster
town and those those are the friends
they meant I
suppose oh
bom you
again I have to fight
you Shan I
know no don't eat me unless that will
take me to Monster
Town bom didn't we fight him
before Oh we can do a triple move but
the one that peach is just healing right
The Shining real protects the whole oh
from anyone attack what
once now we got to switch out peach in a
[Music]
moment I don't know the timing of this
man I feel like I'll figure it out next
time
maybe
M okay let's switch to
ooh what is uh what was effective for
this boss I Wonder World doesn't work on
bosses except
one Oh you mean the the
crit oh okay okay okay let's go for
Bowser I guess and then do our shoot oh
that's actually the AOE one right wasn't
even necessary but let's
[Music]
go take damage
please no that's okay that's all
[Music]
right
a why did it have to end there I was so
going to
go
[Music]
why pretty solid yeah at least I can get
more than two or three these
days in my last streams I never got more
than two
three that was quite
[Music]
embarrassing oh too early that was way
too early but
[Music]
okay boo
surprise I never forget a taste in fact
after this once SL I can clone someone
watch no don't clone
Gino are do you taste
but not
bad there we
[Music]
are
well it can't fool me cuz I know it's
the fake one it's even even tells me
it's the fake one but we have to kill it
before it it kills
us
wow yeah nice good job W pet myself on
the back thank you thank
you I'm guessing he's uh he has a
weakness for
fire so let's
go let's start blasting
oh
[Music]
what Japanese
bro
[Music]
for
[Laughter]
yeah Japanese bro is going to a wedding
and it's saying that there will only be
uh like like there's so many doctors as
guests apparently so he can get really
really drunk and I said no that's not a
good reason to get
drunk and also ask if uh
overseas um
if uh it's like like in Japan where you
give money to the wedding couple I said
No at least like in Europe you give
presents not direct money well it
depends probably depends I don't know
I've never been to a wedding here
so what do I
know let's try this
again no my timing was perfect what the
hell
scam ski
[Music]
scam and you always give money now e for
real well okay time times have changed I
guess we have money in hungry at the
bright dance
[Music]
what we give a tree of bills I've seen
that before
so depends on what the Yeah Yeah Yeah
cuz like some have like Registries right
of like certain things that they
[Music]
want
H money as a gift is becoming more and
more popular honestly
personally I I also think it's like
better that
way because then the couple can use it
not to buy shitty things like mixers and
you know any other kitchen supplies and
laundery and that kind of stuff no they
can just use it to yeah like balance out
the money they spent on the wedding m
yeah like toasters and [\h__\h]
like cuz those those are really common
wedding gifts right like stuff that you
you think they might need in their life
but they probably have so
yeah all those all those
things so I guess that's
better with
money but I wonder what's the
expectation in Europe for European
wedding how much money you're expected
to give them cuz in Japan to me it felt
kind of
[Music]
expensive a gift money to a pool or they
make a wish list of item yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah you already have mus yeah yeah
yeah y yep weren't we here before and
did all of this this is such a
Deja
[Music]
hello again the pipe is sh got to my
home monster town I'll see you
there all right let's
go
oh
[Music]
I I I just just checking if it
works just
checking I like this wow this music
wants
the starts pretty
dope Monster Mama oh I travel from a far
welcome to monster town where many
monsters mingle I'm the land lady
Monster
Mama but you're not a monster a star you
say oh you're here to see our star she's
up a
person feel free to go and take a look
for yourself what the [\h__\h] is this airf
flow set a
it's
what what does it do though if I make it
stronger do I get something out of
it is it going to
explode
H that's
weird mama
you oh oh it's a [\h__\h] sea
star I've been all around the world but
the strangest person I met this is old
Jer in Ros toown he really is weird but
definitely worth
meeting times if you jump at the right
places a treasure box will pop out of f
air anything like this happened to you
these treasure boxes are known as hiden
Treasures because they appear out of
nowhere you think you found them all but
you still have 21 Hidden Treasures left
oh that's not that
bad so this your star I got scammed
again nice dance still are you'll keep
on dancing when I talk to you you're
just going to
ignore like the situation that I got
scammed I I came here to see and receive
a
star and you're just going to dance to
ignore your
surroundings but
wait there was a sheet of music next to
him maybe U I need to remember this
m so Talent is she's so talented too
folks come to see her from
afar why am I moving this fast oh yeah I
want a real star star bees oh star pce
no not familiar with them so you came
all the way out here to search for a
star piece it must be really important
this is the last place on land if you
can't find it here the only place left
is
up Mama
Mia so you want to go there H you're an
open book okay here's what you need to
do there's a secret passage to the sky
at Bean Valley the first you must scale
the cliff beyond the desert desert to go
there since you're such a nice guy I'll
introduce you to someone that can help
you power Troopers I need
you oh here they come
Flying S and flutter
aw what R our flying time
troops 8.52 second
sergeant pirate Troopers reporting for
Duty ma'am
we're 52 seconds late I hold myself
personally accountable for the delay
ma'am still as rigid as ever about your
rules and regulations no need to bother
with a protocol around me unless blue
protocol the mmrpg I've been waiting for
6 years or something like that I've got
a favor to ask of you yes ma'am should
we hijack the servers of blue
Protocol
no maybe next time this fellow here
really wants to get to Bean Valley could
you help him scale the
cliff understood ma'am the orders are
get mustache over the cliff we will
succeed we will now deploy ourselves to
the cliff at Land End per us keep a
tight
formation we have a lift off
swoosh they're odd but trustworthy good
luck with you search yeah thank you I
actually I'm going up to your room one
more
[Music]
time I shall take a picture I don't know
if the melody is more important than
the visuals of
[Music]
this something like
that I took a screenshot
so
yeah we
good you going just read it ah
oh well oh there's a
key I don't have to remember the hip
movements do
I he'll give me a priz if I manage to
jump 30
times what's the
price grent you're quiet an accomplished
jumper oh they're all about jumping
here oh seven times in a row
[Music]
okay don't you dig these
Vibes
[Music]
no he he says the same thing
now
doesn't seem like anything's
happening always mumbling about a
crystal this un evil that isn't a
crystal some kind of shiny rock or
something I know I've seen those
somewhere that the guy next door
oh
ah that's why I needed to jump seven
times cuz otherwise probably just with
one jump the key wouldn't have fallen
down n hold
sealed the shiny stor is reacting oh the
seal has been broken hey yo hey yo who's
in
here what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] it's a
pixel
thing what the [\h__\h] is this Ultima
Ultima why are you in this game [\h__\h] off
I was done with you save let's go l
f
RP save your game how could I can I will
they give me
a what how how was I supposed to know
the hardest boss I forgot to save no
come on who's so
young can I still
leave I've crossed into this Dimension
to fight for the dark Mage you who stand
before me where does your death come
from why you rendered so
deepen the evil bar that gave me life
mapped out this flat plane as my
form why is this dude in
here you're formed from a power unknown
to me I wish to gain the secret of your
three dimensional world no no
no you wise to hesitate mm my chat told
me if I had any weapon or armor you have
no chance but I do have a weapon and
armor I do I do
though so even if I save
I'll probably lose right
[Music]
so where where is safe Point here in
here
right a goom Hilda go Hilda what are you
doing here Bower it's been ages hasn't
it sorry about going a wall on you I R
away because I was scared to fight
Smithy a lot has happened since then but
look how far I've come I'm managing this
store
now
you have betrayed Bowser you lord and
savior and look here my little ones come
on you have little
ones a they're cute hi Uncle
Bowser although I can fight for you I
still have some items you you can
use maybe you'll find it in your heart
to forgive me I can help you get
equipped I guess if you are bribing me
like this and also showing me your
children that's not fair Fair Play
That's Foul
Play don't worry I'm not angry with you
I got my I got new minions now and we're
going to reclaim my castle you go on
with your life here I wish you the best
but still give me those items
though give me the items for
[Music]
free
woo she has an item only for
Bowser interesting oh this one
too
[Music]
nice talk to the kids too oh
okay I have to please can we
oh it recovers 30 HP
but but what should I get
this unique
mushrooms do you also have mushrooms why
you
do I get more makes me smaller that
would be so
[Music]
cute
h
yeah I wonder can I give those to the
[Music]
dude
ah M
nuts nice to meet you I'm G
hi I'm
Boo and I'm dry bones we are the free
musty
fear
no don't give me nightmares he's
sleeping ohy he sure he
is check those bubbles coming out of his
nose don't pop him maybe he can still
hear us while he's asleep hey you we
want to play around of find the
flag
mhm you'll hide a flag somewhere around
the world
okay final for Flags you got an awesome
prize okay
byebye they'll be back why you going to
tell me
that it's like you're in it together
with them I'm back I hit my flag behind
a wooden
flower doesn't really doesn't really
make click in my brain right
now green
bed between o and
a our flags are invisible so search very
carefully when you think you found the
spot you guys will have to help me with
those Mario
Mario
H I have a feeling one at least should
be maybe in Mario's home do I have a
green bed
maybe
wait if I want to
leave do I leave for here do I get to
the map
[Music]
or
no
[Music]
h ah I can save there okay I was looking
for a safe
spot oh
what why is this one so particularly
hidden why why what are you trying to
[Music]
hide thanks for coming by
wait I have the key for the treasure
room guess we got to go back there too
oh hold this is the accent ah well well
well I'm not done exploring this town
There's A J
here do you have the moves like Jagger
by any chance who isn't sorry but the
Sensi isn't in oh my
gosh oh it's another one of Bowser's old
minions Bowser I haven't seen you for so
long I've been sitting here at the do
you under the Sensei Jinx because uh to
tell you the truth I I knew I couldn't
beat Smithy that's why I'm here now
someday I'm going to return and make you
proud H well he he has like a like his
his his plan is to come back to me to
Bowser I mean thanks for the
membership don't worry about me I've got
new minions now we're going back to my
castle eventually so stick to your guns
train like there's no
tomorrow
[Music]
okay a challenge oh all right what kind
of challenge is
it you know that I'm not going to make
it easy for you
right oh it's a fight let's
go holy [\h__\h]
oh let's do a super
[Music]
jump no
what scam scam scam scam scam scam scam
scam
this whole game is a huge
[Music]
scam I will find out what is your
weakness cuz I have no
[Music]
patience uh fear sleep and mute what so
I can indeed make him fall asleep all
right then maybe I'll switch to PE te
[Music]
them [\h__\h] I'm so
bad I guess he resists like everything
let's give him a normal hit oh
[\h__\h] uh search like
this sleepy
time
recently it's so crazy like for the past
what do you mean resistance
huh I'm confused for the past
while couple of weeks now I've been able
to fall asleep
like so fast like almost immediately
which is so crazy cuz like a few years
back it would take me like 5 hours to
fall asleep no joke
H yeah if only there wasn't a little
little Daredevil evil cat waking me up
so much then I would have the best sleep
of my life
[Music]
[\h__\h]
nice nice
thanes your
[Music]
tough bless movie no she's
evil but I love
her can't help
it I love her so
much she's also the one that helps me to
fall asleep with her
[Music]
fluffiness oh oh the Sensei is back
oh
s have you been here all
along you found my key didn't you not
bad for
noice is this a
Pikman your fighting style it isn't as
full Prof as you think I looks up the CH
any
day
wait thank you guys
T I'm going to go to fight oh did I get
healed then we shall
fight oh right
cuz this game came up before Pikmin
right right R I'm just making jokes
don't take it so
seriously ah holy [\h__\h] I was not ready
for
[Music]
that
so is he also going to be resistant to
special attacks I
[Music]
wonder yeah he did resist it oh my God W
he got the moves like Jagger and his
name isn't even Jagger why is not his
name Jagger his name should be Jagger
but do you think he jinxed his fight
with me by saying like claiming how
amazing he is should I not try any of
these at
[Music]
all [\h__\h] ow ow ow ow ow
ow you just got a old school damage okay
no
weakness ooh I got the timing red ow
ouch then I'll just use up all my FP to
continuously heal
[Music]
us nice I did it again ah damn he's so
fast veiler up so you're what you're
even faster
down
free Peach's damage is like
non-existent Peach You Keep On
Healing if I feel oh a bit more
safer oh my God I'll switch out Peach
for someone else but that time is not
now one more group
[Music]
huh why is it so
unstable the damage that I do have you
considered blocking oh my God maybe I'll
block
you oh my
god oh that's defense
up you think I'm not [\h__\h] trying
[Music]
oh nine oh my
god well I can't get the timing right
I'm trying
though
ah
[Music]
this is so
fast shouldn't actually be that hard
well it
is this dude is so
fast
[Music]
H see I can get other timings right just
not his from Jinx oh that was it
actually
oh oh you only need to block the last of
his
attack I thought you have to block
like the moment before he
attacks well
uh I guess I underestimated you you pack
quite a punch but don't let it go to
your head because I let you have that
round let's have a
rematch well I don't know man it didn't
give me anything just now is this just
an exp
Farm or how many times do I have to
fight with
him three rounds
what do I
[Music]
get the next Bight gives me
something
H I'll consider it after doing
[Music]
this uh was it
here and I need to leave this room again
[Music]
okay hungry no that's not what we
want
no I want the one that I got the first
[Music]
time this
one you will accept
visitation I will put this key into your
butt and you will open yourself up to me
yeah yeah take the key enjoy a golden
key for a Golden Boy and I get all the
green fro coins
yo
yo yo you have to come here like damn
this is so worth it m
m
lots of brw coins and
flowers
nice you never got this
what did you not know because you like
were lucky and immediately got the one
that leads you to the monster
Town didn't know that there were other
options like
this ah oof oof o That's so how many
frog coins you missing out
on couldn't get a good pull
what
ow that was pure sugar
[Music]
again
yeah he why did you need to figure out
that the key went there you do see the I
feel like pretty easily you see the key
up
there but I
mean I didn't
know how to get it either I don't know
if I would probably wouldn't have
figured it out that it's to do with the
jumping probably wouldn't have
known yeah when you're young this kind
of stuff is even less clear that's why
you got to go to game FAQs and
[\h__\h] let's start with attack up right
away I'm guessing he still has like all
the same oh my God ah that
one all the same weaknesses and all that
[Music]
so
[\h__\h] missed it yeah
by let's do one more uh boost for Mario
too
okay oh let's go I didn't even
look should I heal I'll try
about 18 what I got attack up and I'm
doing less damage now
amazing amazing and I miss
wow okay ow wow what's going on yeah
that's fine kill him I I'll bring
someone else in but what the [\h__\h] is
that what what's going
on
[Music]
what
what what do you mean bad luck how much
bad luck could I
[Music]
have he did get significantly stronger
since the last battle holy
[\h__\h] malo's heal was not an AOE heal
[Music]
right oh thank God
okay ah
[Music]
[\h__\h] block probably
there
[Music]
H yeah I know there's one more so that
one will be maybe too much for me now I
don't know uh what was I going to do I
yeah HP rain for H maybe
myself
ah what did I heal myself for 115 damage
mow only has 118
HP Mama
Mia oh my
[Music]
God ah ah
[\h__\h] uh
I'm guessing when he dies the the buff
is
gone so that's kind of sad more veiler
no great uh great uh
[Music]
wow H oh wait I have the super special
move wait so if I switch someone for
peach and they're already dead do they
come back with one HP or do they come
back with zero HP can I heal them from
here no
okay what the actual
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh my
God please
survive please is he going to is he
going to attack
now
[Music]
okay now I can do the triple
move oh my
[Music]
God please obliterate him what are these
numbers oh
my
I even pressed block and I would say
that was quite a good
timing but apparently not the right one
what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] what is this
fight how much more does he have I
wonder like if there's if he's dead soon
then I don't mind like holding on to
Hope a bit longer
should I use my Yoshi
cookie Yosi what are you going to
[Music]
do
no
no y didn't do [\h__\h]
we waste of my Yoshi
[Music]
cookie should I give
up I mean I could heal and I could like
BR force it but if I wipe then I I lose
all the items do I or do I go back to
before the fight with my
items give up might want to reload I
healed right before didn't
I I did right didn't think he would get
that much stronger holy
[\h__\h] yeah I'll come back
[Music]
later h
like I feel like a lot of players like
first time players will attempt the
Second Battle right away and then be be
surprised by how much stronger he
is
um
here looks like it's before the battle
right before so I'm out of here one
battle is enough m M this
way
yeah get the shiny Crystal what I
already I thought that enemy is also way
too strong for
me Mario hesty I just got it because it
was like really cheap and I thought I
heard it's like one of the best ever
Mario games 3D Mario games so I just got
it for the future sure just in
case wasn't I here before I was here
before but the flag is here
right if I ever feel like playing
another Mario
game if I ever feel like I don't have
anything else to
play then I might pick up Super Mario
Odyssey there's another exit
[Music]
I do not have the time for four
enemies Mario St
no oh my God
[Music]
please
okay where is this other
[Music]
exit hits all foes let's try this build
power and energize hold a release at Max
easy B you're missing aim do well pretty
good nice damage though holy [\h__\h] that's
a strong AOE best move in the game mhm
[Music]
M
CID oh you're right there's a thing in
inside I
[Music]
forgot he has one Ave move that's even
stronger than that
what let do it right away
again Channel
BL
[Music]
she nice
block I should bring out my tangents I
think it's time for tangents
tangerines very Orange tangents you know
tangents were named after me because I'm
orange and I tangent a
lot so tangerines were named after me
because they also tangent a lot
yeah
yeah yeah believe me trust me
[Music]
bro boom
shop thanks for the super thank
you new Tangerine Lord just drop you
know winter time is the time of
tangerines though at least in Japan
Everybody Eats
tangerines eating eating tangerines
under the kotu peach L
mute old magic
attack
five
three let's go
[Music]
HP so is there a different exit
here I don't
remember don't touch me don't touch me
stupid be ah this one
maybe did I take this
one oh wait no that's just this one with
the game that made me lose my
[Music]
[\h__\h] looks cozy it is really cozy I used
to have a KATU of my own when I first
lived in Japan
I was like in living in a student
dorm with like high school
students jump when you ah okay okay
okay and even though like the room was
so tiny I still really wanted a KATU cuz
it was it was my first time like living
in Japan and I had my room where I
thought I was going to be there long
term relatively long term so I thought
now I have to get aotu and I I got
myself a pink KATU or like the the
blanket is pink at
least and I was so excited like I barely
had room to move in the apartment
literally the KATU was blocking
everything the room was so tiny so
freaking tiny but it was worth it cuz I
just really wanted that Catu I made my
dream come true my my [\h__\h] weoo
dream when I I think of kotus I think of
mamik please tell me somebody
understands somebody here watched mamik
right
yeah yo minam is so good still to this
day I have to rewatch it I have to
rewatch minam that's like my favorite um
Slice of Life
anime you finished watching the Advent
calendar videos there's only two there's
still going to be so much more so check
every day
[Music]
okay oh not difficult jump there we go
not so
difficult hosaka I love hosaka too yeah
so
[Music]
funny m never seen it oh my
God you
are missing out I mean it's pretty old
at this point I
guess I guess it came out like when
maybe 10 years ago even at this
point but it's about these three
sisters one of them the youngest one she
goes to junior high school and she's
really cute but she's like the this the
T
type kind of serious and
shy kind of tund actually very
tund and then the middle sister she's
just the dorky silly funny one the B
yeah tiaki is the youngest one and then
the the oldest one they live together so
the oldest one kind of becomes the mommy
of the sister group and cooks for them
and all that and takes care of
them and that's like that creates really
wholesome T moments and she also
sometimes has to you
know what's the word
uh be like you know bad bad bad Chucky
bad bad
Ka
2007 that
is six
six
16 16 years ago is that 16 years
ago it it's 2007 16 years
[Music]
ago
16 16 [\h__\h]
GE 16 [\h__\h]
years but but that's still in the 2000s
how can how can any year before the
current one in the 2000s be longer
ago than 5 years you know what I mean
you know what I
mean how could it have been 23 years
since we entered the 2000s anyway like
how
how how
it's [\h__\h]
insane yeah like I remember when we
entered the 2000s and like I don't know
people were like really like any anybody
who was born after 2000s for the coming
years was like a [\h__\h] baby and now
these 2000s babies are like way past
adults what's why to
what you're to ah you're too
F huh that's what you call your y
[Music]
2K I I I I do not want to live in this
world where people that were born after
2000s are adults
that is insanity can you
imagine like let's say somebody who
maybe born like
1980 or something like that or 1970 even
they're still alive right yeah or 1960
even also also still alive
partially and to
them writing the year down as 19
something and just generally like this
whole
how to say
like consciousness of it being the like
the
19,000 was just
so I suppose like just so normal like
entering the 2000s and now being already
in 2023 must be so
surreal
crazy
[\h__\h]
1900s
whatever how is the why why you not dead
yet what the
[Music]
hell m
m
[Music]
what do you mean drop the S what oh up
19,000 guys almost [\h__\h] shut up don't
tell me no I don't want to I don't want
to think about time
passing time isn't real time is imagin
ation crony is a pigmentation of my
imagination wait a
pigmentation I don't
know crony isn't
real at least not to
[Music]
me
there's still treasure
here
treasure ah there it is there is where
you are
wo you know I felt
really
BCT what's BCT confirmed no m
[\h__\h]
nuts what's the
word validate
today when I saw an Instagram re real of
Ariana
grander she was
doing like some sort of ASMR but like
kind of
sarcastically and she even said it like
herself like I don't understand what
this does for
people like like
she herself said like she doesn't get it
and then kept on making
like really bad ASMR
sounds and I I could really relate to
that you
know why is that
here what
where is that here
[Music]
now yeah hearing that from someone like
Ariana
Grande and the the ASMR mic that she had
was so cute though I kind of want to get
the same if I ever do ASMR if I get my
own ASMR mic I want that one I don't
know if it's really suitable for it but
it's so cute it was like a tiny mic like
one of those from the videos where
there's like a person um with a tiny
tiny tiny tiny
microphone uh uh oh my God interviewing
tiny
animals cricet Jam Cricket oh Cricket
Jam wait haven't we been here before is
this the same
[Music]
place uh another
okay
why are we in the sewers
again a freey yeah let's
go
[Music]
ow H mellow
congratulations
um four five
six
yeah why are we here let me
save wait we only have two stars
left no come on I slipped I slippery
sloped a this right h i I don't know I
don't know what I'm supposed to do why
why am I
here why why am I
here where ah wait I wanted to go can I
go to my home
yeah let me go to Mario's
pad want to check
something it's
green under the bed they said a
[Music]
yeah
okay that's one could they all be here
no way right between between a and o or
something like that like there could be
one here between the
letters but probably not they're
probably not here
anymore like the rest of
[Music]
them
okay wooden flower green bed wooden
flower I wonder if I can find it like
naturally um
um
between
an H
um wait did I have a reason to come back
because like what about the cricket Jam
for
example yeah yeah yeah
yeah the the big boy wanted right the
frog the frog of all
frogs
[Music]
mhm thank
you a little allowance as if I'm like
your
child thank
you okay going back maybe we can buy
something interesting of the frog
[Music]
coins
not we
have oh wait oh you don't
even uh use frog coins with this
one some of us from the 1960s are still
alive are are you from the
1960s no judgment I mean I know I know
someone from 1960s now
is
60 60
yeah yeah so there's many 1960 people
still alive so okay if you're one of
them didn't it feel weird as [\h__\h] to you
when it became
2000 for someone who already spent 40
years in the
1900s at that point I imagine it must
have been
insane like unreal like you're in in a
different
[Music]
uh Century I don't know
oh there's someone who's
76 oh we're being uh uh uh uh uh uh
raided wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
answer oh things change slowly enough so
you don't
notice that is not the answer I have
been
anticipating I am not happy with
that I don't really want to buy any of
these things what am I supposed to do
with my frog
coins is there anything
else what do you
have a yeah you're just the the guy who
spoilers the game
thingy get the flower ring in Seaside
Town sheide Town shop for better fr okay
Seaside Town Seaside
town
was why is my shin so
scratchy or not scratchy I
mean wait seide down seide down seide
down seide down
itchy did something bite me let me check
no no nothing nothing
there uh someone here wants my frog
[Music]
coins
no Elder house second floor
oh Elder house is this the Elder house
this is the Inn but does that also mean
it's the Elder
house no probably
[Music]
not also remember if there's a wooden
flower or something with a and
[Music]
o just want to keep that in my in the
back of my
mind
[Music]
ah frog my frog
friend frog
bird my beloved I have accumulated some
stuff actually plenty we can buy these
run from battles e no I don't like this
the flowering you guys said I need to
get the flower ring Cuts FP used in half
during battle
h
everybody wants me to get it so I guess
I'm getting it we'll put it
on it's it's for everybody right
everybody in the team has less ofp uh uh
usage or like uh it uses up less or just
the one who's wearing
[Music]
it oh just a user oh okay let's give it
to
[Music]
Gino ah Peach is wearing no
accessory
NY didn't realize yeah she can have the
signal ring cuz I want somebody to have
it for
sure okay what else is there to do I I
got lost actually before coming here uh
so let me look at the map where is the
flag where where does it tell me to
go here after all did I go through the
wrong
exit and Peach is not wearing
anything she's wearing the
work she's wearing wearing a saor
dress well she's
fine Warp to the dessert
desert where where was there a warp
pit no I don't want to get into the hole
again I don't want to no
no on my
map
oh
ah oh I fought from here cuz the
the the thing is here
the it the the flag is
here the beach why are we going to the
beach
why are we going to the
beach why are we here are you sure
[Music]
guys a the desert why uh not the well
sand is sand the beach is just a desert
with lots of
[Music]
water oh oh wait
H what what what I do go for L and but
if I go like
this uh bone Temple
maybe
okay
no or or yes do we want to then leave
don't
leave
oh why is this so confusing to
me I love how they attack each
other the spider must be like what the
[\h__\h] why did I take you guys on this
journey you guys
suck always so
confused
was that dude there again the star
guy I paid him before feel like I saw
him
again should I do it
[Music]
again yeah he's here again a better
Star oh you come back later you'll find
it what you are you actually getting me
the kind of star that I really
want my super chump timing is [\h__\h] I
mean I'm better than last time at
[Music]
least I can't go back this way what the
[\h__\h] what the the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what do you mean I can't
run let me
run oh come
on go to the go to the temple pay the
guy on the spring to go back to the
surface
[Music]
Temple this take the spring in this room
keep going okay I'm so confused it's
frustrating
me
[Music]
oh nice jump nice jump It's almost like
I've played a Million Mario games before
this and like I'm a pro
jumper
ah this way or is it this way the one
where I have to climb supposedly ah now
they helped me to go
up
ah mention this a scale of close by
jumping sh all
right ah you guys should have just said
go to the cliff where you thought you
need a super jump in the future the one
you couldn't
climb nice jump one one nice
jump oh it's okay I I I I'm I'm not
missing it anymore why is there a
timer or something that seems like a
timer can I miss these jumps yep it
almost felt like I couldn't because my
jumps were just so
good rewards for Speed
oh first jump is the most difficult
one shoot
[Music]
you hey why did I slip did you put oil
or butter on these shells or
what
scam I saw myself slipping that's why I
went forward
but
wait for
me you can still get back up on that at
that point
huh kind of want to redo yeah at least I
don't have to pay money for this
one just had wax yeah I guess it's just
general shell body care or paraca body
care
ha
hygienic
procedures he says slow and steady does
it but he doesn't tell you that there's
a reward if you're
fast so much for slow and steady you
just don't want to give me the reward
greedy little piece of
[\h__\h] what is this what is this View
the camera angle is like H misleading as
[Applause]
[\h__\h] I'm
in
isometric what I'm not in school anymore
isometric I don't want to hear these
words they don't matter to me
and
then why did I move I thought I had to
adjust my step but no it was perfect the
way it
was
bye this time this time
[Music]
no I want to make that jump early shut
up you don't have to tell me all the
time
at least I'm better at this than the
other jumping
game although the other jumping game
once I you know knew that I should just
jump
over the
Torpedoes everything was fine after
that oh you can just walk over at that
point Mama
Mia I was like wondering can I just walk
over if they get really close there it
is 20 seconds do I have to be under 20
seconds to get you kidding me let me
redo what is also here right
now under
11 I'm I'm never going to do under
11 you can't
redo what do you mean I I am redoing it
right now but
11 maybe you can jump up
there skip that one that I can you skip
a
[Music]
couple you don't the just drop down and
do it again I
did you can't get rewards during this
part of the
story H okay whatever I mean I feel like
11 seconds is kind of impossible anyway
at least for
me well then you don't even have to jump
if you if you don't aim for 11 seconds
then you can just wait
all of this
out this was even under my previous
[Music]
record I felt slower
though all right here we are finally in
the bean
Valley oh that nice music
oh testing you're testing my
patience oh
no no problem I was going to heal Mario
anyway and with peach we also get rid of
the
debuffs let's let's let's let's go
go let's not talk about the scams
anymore in this game
it's
[Music]
ridiculous these
flowers I hate these
flowers I hate
them cuz he has no magic stat I mean I
gave him a few did I not
also I got to kind of go for whatever
the game is recommending Me by buffing
certain stats you
know what can I
do okay is this like uh you can go
either left or right and then you may go
wrong you may possibly go
wrong
[Music]
nice let's affect them all so that they
stop healing each other and
stop I
missed
unbelievable oh yo that damage is legit
though why did I miss even though I got
a perfect I guess it's just the enemies
being overpowered
[Music]
cool two wrongs don't make a right but
three rights make a left so are you
saying I should go right three
times there's a treasure
here don't jump on the
be maybe it's
uh
where is
it let's kill the bee
[Music]
first oh come
on Nice
Shot lower left
corner Gino keeps on getting those
double attacks
wow
okay there it is a frog
coin oh
[\h__\h] wait was there treasure here too no
I guess I'll go to the left side but I
wonder if there was something on the
right side too but this looks kind of
interesting oh he's growing them stop
stop stop
stop
[Music]
chewy cute name
nice no
no so
annoying oh
wow Santa Mario CH yes I am two things
actually three I'm three characters at
once I am normal Teno I am Mario Cho and
I am Santa Cho
oh Mario resists it
[Music]
amazing
so oh wait what that was
a am I the
SE please
no is the is the chess saying that or am
I saying that a pawn looking at
it that's a cute name
I never saw that mimic before so it must
be my first time
here why are you so
cute wait you know what I bought that
was for a moment from Toy
Story
the there's one toy that has the exact
same skin color and like black uh uh uh
mustache right and yeah Mr Potato Head
and I really like the first millisecond
registered it as Mr Potato
Head why is there a
genie
[Music]
why a genie excuse
me oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
hm ouch holy
[\h__\h] ah nice though nice it's both of
their weakness oh Mario almost
died
da oh a
triple no no no no
Mario
Mario perfect
score ah
y yab y
[Music]
no he brings the Jenny back again come
on come
[Music]
on
please let's end this
[Music]
now okay only the geni is
left
ow let's do normal attacks already used
so many
FP I need to heal after
this okay
so me coming here was this basically a
fail like did I basically go through the
wrong so to say
pipe I mean there is a hidden treasure
so you want to go here eventually I
found it no wait that was one of
[Music]
them red
Essence just extra
goodies he was dooming
no let me go I don't want
[Music]
to Great Vine rare
item where does this bring
me oh more fancy cool stuff a frine all
right but I have to go back I
guess and
then back
here do I have to wait for him to water
the plants so that I can fight them let
me save
once he
SpongeBob Peter Riven which
one oh my
God so many
enemies
[Music]
nice now we can focus on this
one sneeze
CH Let's Dance everybody let's dance
Everybody Let's Dance everybody Dance
uh
Maga eh I mean none of these are boosted
really this three seems pretty normal
for the HP
one
phical okay
and what's behind this one never
surprise
ooh
what are
[Music]
you
uh can I fight that he looks like he's
made out of
wood
cute ah so cute golden chops honestly
they don't look like they don't look
like real gold they're just spray
painted I'm telling you trust me I have
the perfect attack saved up just for
this three times next to the wall where
Trump is
okay three times tsue fun thank you I'm
fine though I don't need tissues right
now he did only one die at least at
least one my gu
e how about
Fireball yeah okay not really strong I
might so on a CH
jump oh nice
block nice good fight good
fight
I have
[Music]
to that's like super
secret
is this what I just
opened
Casino
gamble front of the house looks like
a
face let me in members only how do I
become a member
what
I need a card from booster tower all
right I'll come back when I have
that tot and Suits there really
suits it looks good on
them now I have to do this
again God damn it this is why gambling
is bad for
[Music]
you let me go
no gamble only mini games I mean that's
fine too
[Music]
no
so I'm
sure that wasn't the only exit I want to
go there again let me in let me in water
this
[\h__\h] come on shy
guy I want to go there again but then
doesn't mean I have to fight the chomp
jumps
[Music]
again was that all was that all I could
find in there then I'm good maybe let's
go here
[Music]
then uh [\h__\h]
uh he's just
gardening he has such a peaceful nice
job
damn 21 diamonds to
himself all you could find okay
[Music]
okay ah goodbye ah
[Applause]
what
at least I got a kill yeah
still
ah ah takes him so much time I press it
way too
early nice but I don't really need those
Buffs cuz the fight is over
soon
only
[Music]
free I haven't used this new move yet no
I didn't really feel like it was
necessary
yet
oo oh oh
Casino
MAA do I get all of
them oh okay
fine your flow flower these
[Music]
please Doom shall be upon you now
kaboom
Victory
y what's in here well it's like
Christmas oh this one's the same
[Music]
oh I don't know I'm bad at this kind of
stuff
flower the flower comes
after uh I can't tell after the
mushroom
no I jump when I see the star
maybe maybe I don't I don't know
what's should I jump when I see the
star oh God I I don't have this kind of
reaction
time no that was pure luck I just jumped
whenever please but if I already have
two like last time I had too much
mushrooms and something else and it gave
me a mushroom so do I get the flower for
sure
[Music]
now yes okay then we're
good pi oh no wait there's one more okay
come here come here please please shy
guy I need your help over here please if
you want to be friendly and don't want
me to kill you then
please thank
you
[Music]
yeah is Aura still
here
[Music]
oh w
if I DM her she would show up for
sure I know you guys don't like me going
for so much HP but like what choice do I
have but for this time I went for
something else or Not
Here Again
logical well this one's kind of slower I
feel oh maybe it gets faster later yeah
yeah
[\h__\h]
whatever whatever I don't care
a you know the reason I wanted to oh
[\h__\h] no I got to go back no no no no no
no
no uh she showed me something really
interesting the other day that I even
though I'm a long-term hello project
fan I didn't know about
[Music]
this
oh oh nice we just like were're talking
about hello project like so randomly oh
because because there is a member that
graduated from morning musim after being
in there for so many years like she that
member um she was like the leader for
like the longest like you know Morning
musim has been around for how many years
like several tens of years and they keep
on getting new members and graduate
members and new members and so on just
to keep the the group alive so there's
like no original members anymore in that
group right
and like I haven't been really following
the group anymore for a a long
time cuz my favorite group wasn't
morning with anyway from that company
from that agency it was a Betty's coobo
and like smileage and so on and you know
all my favorite members are pretty much
gone there's like one member in morning
musim and the current one that I I do
like a lot because she's a great singer
the Oda
Sakura but yeah you know I don't really
keep up with them anymore
um
so that one member graduated and I was
like damn it feels like she graduated
like 10 times cuz I feel like I I've
been hearing about her graduation since
like a year ago and I'm like
I I thought you already graduated but
then I keep on seeing her in new music
videos and photos and all that and I'm
like oh she's still in the group
huh and it was like so confusing to me
but yeah turns out she just graduated
after so many years of
service
Mizuki
and uh boss is this a boss so tiny
that's not a boss l are you gonna you
gonna make him grow again shower time
that's kind of cute what a cute
boss what a cute boss he hold them wait
it's more now it's two H oh and I can
only Attack
One
H so she graduated graduated and then I
I told AA like oh my God like it feels
so weird to me I feel like she graduated
a million times already I have this
weird phenomenon going on in my
brain and then she showed me something
like we talked a little bit about uh
like how we don't keep up we both don't
keep up that much
anymore and then she shows me a picture
of some merchandise that she has from
long long time ago
nice uh and I've I I I I back in the day
I used to also buy a lot of merchandise
so I was surprised not to know this item
of
merchandise but she had
like a a really interesting piece of
merchandise basically these hello
project Idols for every concert they do
they have like a new
outfit so cool I love all their outfits
I wish we could have a new outfit for
every life that we do but 3D takes more
time to create an outfit and more money
I
guess
so
apparently there once was a merchandise
where it's basically like kind of like
an envelope a picture of the member on
top of it and then there's a window in
the envelope and there's a piece of the
fabric of the outfit that the an uh Idol
was
wearing on that
picture in that window and you can touch
it so it's like the same fabric and
they're like you know stage outfits so
they're all like cool fancy Fabrics not
just normal fabrics and that's such a
sweet idea I don't think they depending
on how much they sell oh [\h__\h] why did I
skip oh
well uh I don't think they only cut it
off the outfit I think they just buy the
same fabric and then produce like a lot
of those things just so you can have the
same fabric but the outfit probably
doesn't get cut up is what I would think
but I guess they make you think that you
have a piece of that very outfit that
the idol
wore and I love that idea it's so cute
and maybe it's limited maybe it's a
really limited item the thing is I never
saw that when I was an active fan so I
was really surprised and then there's
they have it for like normal uh outfits
just like normal performance outfits but
then there's like graduation specials
where it's from the graduation outfit
and those are obviously like the ones
you want the most it's like the last
Memoir of your idol your OSI the last
outfit you ever saw her on stage with
and all that you know oh my God can you
imagine I I wish I had one of those
pieces of merchandise but I never saw
one of them
around but it's such a great idea and I
was thinking could we apply something
like this to to uh our to us basically
but I I I can't really think of a way I
have to think about it
harder h
[Music]
um you want the tiny
hat a piece of my
beard yeah but it's like so sentimental
right it's such an original idea I've
never saw seen that before I was quite
fascinated by that
[Music]
that's where it ends but good job
me next
round they do have those outfit replica
yeah yeah outfit replicas yeah that that
was quite cool I I like the idea of uh
basically putting cosplays
there I like that hit a right after the
Rock right after the rock which rock
let's see first time ah oh okay well too
late no
Gino ah [\h__\h] hell
no no I'll I'll keep
[Music]
him it's
okay in wrestling they do sports card
with a piece of the mat from the
wrestling
r a wrestling ring you mean you don't
mean a ring you mean like a
belt those big belts that they have or
oh no wait you mean the mat I was
thinking mats like resources you mean
the mat that they fought on
what that
ring also not the the original meaning
of ring so I wasn't too far
off what what they destroy the
mat
what after a wrestling match is the mat
like
useless do they always buy new
mats first and collectible what she C
going to do that send out SD cards of an
orange
PNG I don't know I feel like we could
somehow make our own version of
something like that somehow but I don't
know yet
how m
[Music]
oh nice oh but they resisted it did a
lot of damage though
surprisingly thanks for waking me
[Music]
up nice okay is that it I don't see any
more buds I added some nutrients a
more
really where are you getting those from
oh okay yeah that's the biggest so far
and I'm guessing that's the last one
Mega Smile X now it's time to crush him
but I do not have uh much more FP let me
try first with a terrorize and then
Mario or orino can use
the the FP
item
oh but they resisted oh oh
well
[Music]
oh I can't block that Mama Mia let's
bring in
Peach ah but
wait okay it's fine I can only heal I
actually only need heal for Mario right
now anyway so that actually works out
well now I would like to to bring in
some FP yes please I need
them yeah I can't block the AOE that's a
lot of damage that I can't block
sheh let's
see that was not it
really that was not it how how come I'm
not blocking
it what the
hell
[Music]
h i could try to donon the smaller ones
I'm sure I can do that
right let me
try I'm sure it doesn't work on the big
one but maybe the smaller ones no
[\h__\h] man let's do ultra
[Music]
gem
oh this one's really difficult cuz
they're different heights and like if we
jumps on the middle one suddenly then
it's going to be like shorter reaction
time
shees
[Music]
shees God damn it I can't get it right
d
[Music]
ah he's back to
normal H I guess we need FP again how
did I use up 40 FP so
fast we live in a society man freebie
though let's go I appreciate the
freebie I don't know even when I do
earth
eruption because I can't get the timing
right it doesn't do that much damage
maybe not worth it
I did get it the last two times e what
do you mean the crush
really we're talking about the same
[Music]
thing yeah it just doesn't do that much
damage here oh really cuz I feel like I
didn't hear the melody so I thought I
didn't didn't do
[Music]
it yeah let's just do normal attacks cuz
166 is very
satisfying
yeah even D is
fine seems like he's uh
uh weak to just normal physical
attacks oh
yeah flame wall that's fine I'll hit you
with n I'll switch cuz I want it to be a
different kind of
attack clown car
barrage big attack let's go I'll destroy
you take this and that and this and that
and this too
yeah oh and it is his weakness of course
because something in there will surely
be his weakness 462
Shee don't know how much HP he had left
but he was obliterated he had no
chance look what you did my look's been
wack I feel so bad I'm going to get it
Queen Valentina told me to keep everyone
out of nimus land what should I
do I I'll run away he's he has such cute
Wings
what the way that fell down they must
have animated it like that on purpose
like lackluster
animation
like unrealistic just to like yeah keep
it the same way as the
OG cuz that on its own was very comical
to me just falling down
[Music]
straight wait do I have to enter here
have I seen the inside or is it do I
want to enter let me read this
though H what's this it's a seat let's
take
it oh Oh I thought it was like a message
[Music]
okay oh
I did not expect that even though that's
a very Super Mario game kind of
thing a magical Bean hit the block once
more to climb it
o I was thinking I feel like I can't
reach
in oh a clown it's like a kobo's fredd
stage the clouds look so
funny wait is this melo's home
maybe how to climb the vines climb and
circle around Vines
ah jump to NE Vine by tilting l in the
direction you want to go oh no here's
Shadows below you as a
guide in a
circle what do you mean Circle I just
can go up straight
though
what
[Music]
huh what what do you mean use the shadow
I have no idea where this thing is I
don't see a shadow of the next
one and like I'm getting the directions
wrong this time it worked but still took
me free tries Mama
Mia frog
[Music]
coin wait I want the Frog
coin yes
ah
no can you fight those people by the
way well I guess we'll see oh that's a
cute fighting area and what the [\h__\h] is
that big fat
chunkers wow birdie
cute oh wait oh I thought I was uh doing
the alra jump where I can jump on both
of them
oopsie what did he eat did he eat one of
those
birdies that's what he looks
like big guy ready
to he needs to charge cuz he's so slow
but when he gets to you he's is going to
leave an
[Music]
impact well he didn't get to
it what did
he ah living his best
life looks like he ate everything well
now the enem is out of the way so I feel
a bit
safer oh nice
jump
wait
I swear to
[Music]
God I got up from here before there we
go oh that's it there's surely more
yeah nice flower thank you left or right
let's go
left right
choice went left but it was the right
choice
haa
looks like some kind of kids
park uh you're kind of in the way dude
thank you
[\h__\h] oh that's going to take a
while oh okay yeah the Shadows look like
they're pretty much in a straight line
even though it doesn't look like here
really
um
oh give me the
[Music]
coins the Cloud's faces are so [\h__\h]
cute hot
springs I mean what where also which
trampoline do I
[Music]
use you do it like nothing
well sometimes I have to show you guys
that I am not one to be messed
[Music]
with down the hole ah for the hot
springs down the hole I guess so yeah
but what about these trampolines do I
want to go for them
first if I go for the hole can I come
back here
easily the one on the right takes me to
the Overworld ah
okay let's
go
oh these are mow
people they're definitely here his
family and they're show they're not
showing their faces purposefully I feel
like but we already know what this is
but only royalty can B there and you
don't look so
Royal I am very Royal excuse me I'm
Royal
Jo my wife is waya who is Royal te so
come on they don't know got to teach
them got to bring
way wow the cloud
people oh my
God
there's so many we need malo's reaction
like is he going to notice that they
look like him are we going to notice
that they look like
him all right everyone listen
up e what the hell is that Valentino
she's
evil she's got like a tropical bird on
her
head and some pretty big frontal
Arrangements shut
up King Nim's condition is growing worse
this means we'll be losing our
magnificent
ruler
oh they always smile but it just so
happens that I have found the missing
prince prince mow that is it's going to
be a fake one isn't it who who do you
claim is Prince mow wait mow is a
prince prince come on get over here you
little [\h__\h]
where is Prince mow where's Prince Malo
well it seems that our little prince has
a mild case of stage fight excuse
me all little B come over here I'm going
to rip your arms up snappy
snap are you too
fat oh my
God what a cutie
P big fat chunky bird
a he looks so soft
too oh Lord Oh
Lord that is not mellow introducing
Prince
mellow welcome back Prince you got prins
looking fruit
prins yes what is it
dear what you're asking me to uh Gra
ious you're serious aren't you my I
don't know what to say dear me I've made
my decision at the request of the prince
I agree to become his
queen queen Valentina it just makes me
shiver well that's that back to your
business
everyone what the [\h__\h] is she like she
has very froggy eyes but her body is
very human but also pink has a bird on
her head what is she supposed to
be hurry up
willia the way he squeezes
through
Den as
F uh I forgot what he hasn't talked in
so long I don't remember his voice can
you believe was it was U voice can you
believe it what a coincidence there's a
prin a prince with the same name as me
don't we have anything better to do than
hang around here come on let's go and
find the rest of the star
pieces dude no reaction to these people
looking like
you Valentina lost her bounc the bounce
in the REM e were they
bouncing can't make the letter move
realistically but the seat package but
they make her boobies bounce really
really
a lot what oh there was a patch today
that there was a patch today that undid
it
today today today today
today
today today
today no was it not even there one guy
did I get one
[Music]
guy uh 30 coins I I'll just do it to see
what's if there's something special
there I guess cuz they seem to always
have something special a dream C A this
is like such a scam again but I guess
I'll see something
funny don't try to sell me anything else
though good dreams of fun entertainment
mm will I dream of
Valentina
wow that looks
comfortable he was I supposed to jump
out wait was I supposed to jump out and
climb
[Music]
up
I saved
right that's it
it there's a chance to sleep when to
appears I thought I literally missed
like to jump
out you look for the toad
dream
oh
let me try
again can you safe scum
[Music]
this let's
see oh
Yi I win I
win I don't care about toad who wants to
see toad in their dreams I'm happy with
Yoshi
[Music]
sleep
gaja the way it bounces I like it
w okay I'm happy thank
[Music]
you hidden
treasure yeah
F what do you have
M oh look at my money
[Music]
um
n what is this ooh okay I'll be using up
all my money here it seems H oops no
accident War fan wow mysterious battle
fan
um okay fluffy shirt are we going to be
made out of
clouds fluffy
pants for our resident cloud and fluffy
dress okay let me uh give Mario his I
think it was a weapon
right Mega glove
[Music]
me come
Sita okay should I sell some
stuff let's see can I sell something um
can sell this this
[Music]
yep that too that too and that as
well
[Music]
okay how is your Korean [\h__\h] I wish it
was better but I haven't been practicing
for like 3 months now
oh is that a statue of the prince mow
what a coincidence looks like
me guys maybe people will notice that I
am the prince AKA Mel is the prince look
it's
me oh you me that that's K when he was a
young lad oh
really huh looks just like me uh huh
what the who are
you my name is
mar this is my friend
Mario
so it it's you my boy it's been so long
M you've become a splendid Young
[Laughter]
Prince that was a big jump mellow what
I'm really a
point [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
Mario it is story
time I don't even
I don't even know what's going
on he going
bananas he's like holy [\h__\h] let me tell
you Story
Time Mario is becoming a storytime
[Music]
YouTuber
G yes inde I understand so you are
raised by the the Frog Sage there's no
question about it you are without adopt
Prince
marel that was easy to convince them now
we should be able to convince everyone
else Mario look at at Mar look at me I'm
points what was that
[Music]
reaction Mario best Zan vtuber oh we're
getting raided waited we're getting
waited thank you
I knew Valentina was up to something I
just didn't know what that must mean
that the king isn't really grave
wheel W I've never seen mow so angry and
intense
qu now let's go inside the castle and
save my mother and
[Music]
father yeah let's do that right away
okay yeah hey who are are you you can't
just barge in
here what didn't what do you mean barge
in here didn't he just go
outside oh he went to the castle is what
we heard like him entering the palace or
whatever wait I have an oh wait I have
an excellent idea come over here
disguise like a super
true are you got put armor on me do
[Music]
it the cloud is getting smaller oh no
it's not it's just
moving oh I'm becoming a statue do I
have to walk like a statue are we going
sneaky sneaky NY NY NY NY sneaking like
a
snake hey don't move I look I Look
Marvelous I look amazing in
gold
you're going to be in statue for a while
okay let's get going
now oh are you like acting as if you're
transporting me into the building ah
well thank God I already bought all the
items that I needed I'm delivering
valentina's latest order to her why does
she want a Mario
statue how tool goes
there hey this doesn't look like valtina
at all
oh that's because the statue of
valentina's nephew
[Music]
Mariota oh yeah I totally knew that
sorry I was just uh testing your
knowledge Nar waa so many statues really
loves herself
she you can hear her laughing in the
back
oh my God she's laughing
constantly all all around
me she's asserting dominance with her
lady
love
Ohama that's just what she does all day
all day she looks at her statues and
goes
like that was close I didn't think we
could get through that one there's no
such person named
Mariota yeah yeah yeah yeah oh oh oh
[\h__\h] oh she's here she's not laughing
though oh no this is lovely my beauty
simply shines forth like the sun only
you can make something this
stunning thank you your majesty I'll be
on my way now H what the [\h__\h] is
this uh my my latest Masterpiece I I
created it just for you it's called In
Search of Lost Brother come
on wait
wait lost part who's in Sur Mario is
looking for Luigi or what first I
thought it was implying something about
malow what does this imply it's about
Luigi
right observe the fake mustache with it
I depict His Kind feelings for his
younger brother oh
oh Luigi where the [\h__\h] are
you this was different in the old game
oh
really what was he oh just a name but he
was still like looking for his brother
supposedly and The Sideburns conveying
his strength of the heart yeah yeah yeah
and the legs well the fine strong legs
that can leap any distances in a single
bound is it to you like King you should
say yes because there's King in the word
liking you know it'll make yourself more
like a queen like
royalty ah well that makes a lot of
sense so it is to my light king or may I
say to my like Queen uhuh I'm such a
genius so
go I'll go
[Music]
now
spectacular do do don't just sit there
like a roast hurry and carry these in is
it going to be the prince the
prce it's called
Doo cute step on it what what do you
mean oh like Fast just go faster you're
not going to step on the statues
[Music]
right oh he's cute what is he
doing what why did he oh did he let out
his anger just
now oh okay uh should probably yeah wait
for him to
leave can I jump up now
oh I feel like I should be hearing the
the music the soundtrack of Super Mario
64 when I become
steel I know I'm not steel or like iron
right now but you know it's kind of
similar I want to hear
that yeah metal cap m
mental you guys think I'm ready for a
boss fight do we even get a boss fight
right away seems kind of
easy did you display the statues
properly fine no polish them to fine
luster and make them a tribute to my
beauty thanks for the membership
gift the
[Music]
nuts
ah
pay attention to me hurry up and don't
let me catch you dozing
again why am I running
away cuz he has to polish
me Donald's in a pretty bad mood is he
going to poke me like he poked
Valentina keep up your statue disguise
and jump to avoid getting packed but
then he's going to but then he'll know
I'm not a
statue
[Music]
[Laughter]
he's so
cute
[Music]
oh
cute I I didn't know when I didn't know
when no no no no let me do it
again I didn't know when I'm guessing
that just like the the mini game uh
where I was behind the curtains mini
game The the thing where I was behind
the curtains I have more than one chance
hopefully what you saw the statue move
don't be ridiculous you're just stalling
so you won't have to polish them so now
he comes back and I get another try [\h__\h]
when am I supposed to jump that's so
confusing for like if you do it for the
first
time it's still jump
[Music]
okay he looked away so that was okay I
thought he was going to poke
now hold okay okay so the fake outs are
really nothing I don't have to
worry no [\h__\h]
I I was I I literally pressed B but like
it was like a tiny tiny millisecond too
late
[Music]
[\h__\h] can I fight
him H oh okay that's fine do you have
the option to not fight him either like
in the in the game Tower
[Music]
thingy should I
reload should I is he to
[Music]
strong you got a really good accessory
oh okay okay okay okay I do feel like I
can do
it this is significantly more difficult
than the the one with the curtains
[Music]
though that's okay I'll probably is that
the right one do it in the next try
should be
fine better to do the win the mini game
okay okay
[Music]
okay okay okay okay go let's go let's go
let's go let's
go yeah yeah I saw the head going back
and I knew it was coming there because
there was also still kind of a like a
rhythm that I felt but I was a little
bit too late on the J
[Music]
jump so
slow for real for
[Music]
real nothing happening
here m-
[Music]
m- going to the other
one and coming back to me
again oh that was a really bad timing
but it didn't matter it was
[Music]
fine was that okay was that okay I I
jumped so early but I think it was okay
where did he go he went like under the
floor
my my rhythm was pretty bad there but it
was
forgivable I have been
forgiven I like the way he lets out his
anger man we should even oh for the sake
of him mow shall become the real Prince
so that bird Dole can just go back to
being
Doo I like
him
H I like him so this feather is that the
item but what does it do can I equip it
I can't open the inventory right now
interesting oh I'm absolutely exhausted
jump up there go go go
go oh is it them talking I hate being a
god R only gives us the most boring job
to
do but I guess this beats Doo's job
to has to polish Valentina strates every
day here's how I do it
no no no no don't poke me
dickles let's just kill them quickly oh
I'm not gold anymore m m a good night
Skye thank you for
watching I like big round burps I
do hey tell me sop do statues move no
statues don't move then explain this
one of those high-tech lifelike
realistic ones let's get out of here oh
you don't want to fight oh
really
okay what about what about the other
[Music]
directions I want to
check
oh
flower damn this Valentina what is it
that she's is like being uh surrounded
by a lot of like fat flying
things how come like when does she
attract these fatties huh these chunky
wonks oh it's uh the punch uh glove now
right I
forgot
[Music]
sheesh feather good for the slowest
ready to
[Music]
launch yeah my slowest one
is Bowser maybe I don't
know
Bowser has ah that one yeah we can get
rid of that
one oo defense up speed up by a lot and
Magic defense a little bit okay yeah
that's fine I think that makes
sense oh oh it's the it's oh I can fight
it here
ah I still follow it as a as a fan and I
thought maybe I can change the strength
and then blow away the other enemy in
the
room that was not the
case booze are so freaking adorable I
[Music]
can't
oh how can you miss I saw it Landing in
his face
please be
efficient please do some damage don't
resist it
please imagine me doing 100 and
then being so happy that I did 100 and
it would be like so legendary and then
it does zero damage
resistant that would be
amazing
well that is not really
cool oh come
[Music]
on uh you still would get the reward
yeah I guess so but
um I wasn't doubting
that I'll do it
[Music]
again H that's
fine heal yourself
melow be your own
hero rescue yourself oh my God not again
all right
[Music]
fro green triy
go don't want to fight
them oh we're in this room now this was
like one of the beginning rooms right my
payday was recently
Tassimo thank you
[Music]
yeah there was another path wasn't there
so or wait is this the same
room okay I'm getting confused about how
it's connected so I'll just go this way
what what's what's what's the matter
with
them this one I'll
fight not all of them just
[Music]
some
to stream in the background to play a
new game oh what were you
[Music]
playing
strong he was looking at the spinning
guy so he got dizzy oh that's pretty
[Music]
cute
a [\h__\h] oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my
[Music]
God the distance is so
different depending on where I would
jump so holy
macaroni no time to register anything in
my
brain not bad not bad concer uh
considering the situation
oh they resistance oh man oh wait
Bowser's dead Bowser when did you die
and now Mario is dead let's
go thank God that
[Music]
missed let's see if you can resist
this
Gino beam let's
[Music]
go Gino Beam ginina Beam Gino
[Applause]
Beam for
Mario uh his magic is kind of boosted
here so I'll go for that
[Music]
one let's do the GP hog I
guess I was going this way right
yeah oh oh he was also a fake Statue ah
let's
[Music]
fight thanks for the membership
gift
[Music]
let's do a
jump wa for the
44 I was like I kind of got this Rhythm
down maybe I I can go to 100 I feel like
I
could but why risk my sanity you
know if it's not
necessary use him like a
trampoline hell yeah I did that's what
he gets for underestimating me oh it's
kind of funny how they make the oh what
is that
tomato jawel sleeping who
is who is
jawel oh the
Tomato
H is that a dangerous enemy he has a
huge
Fork oh is awake now do you just have to
do some damage and he wakes
up m
what do tomatoes not like I feel like
they wouldn't like to be jumped
on cuz they probably
explode oh wait they're almost down
never mind
then I want to see him attack I don't
want to kill him no we didn't see him in
action at
all he has above average HP but not that
dangerous oh okay okay
okay fat fat fat
fat oh oh no somehow I thought there was
more
no have I been in that room like that
room looks so familiar
but so
confusing
[Music]
wait did I give Gino the half H uh FP
thing I didn't did
I remind me to give it to him if I
didn't give it to him yet okay thank you
everybody
ah I did oh okay okay
he's ready to launch oh no take cover
everybody it's dangerous
here uhoh wait he's actually launching
yeah bye yeah bye ah wow okay so when
you when he actually gets to do it it is
pretty
powerful I I just wanted to give him
some time to to show it at least
once just once you know would have felt
bad if I didn't let him do it
once oh L coming he's launching again
but he's been like almost dead for so
many times
now
die all
right should I continue that path or
should I go
back oh no I've been
here I'll go this
[Music]
way cden
treasure
[Music]
tomato go back really
what what should I go I mean I I was
going to go there eventually cuz I'm
thinking I probably have to go through
the door where the big fat chunk is in
front
of oh they poke each other
cute I missed too come
on
don't anger
me no need to go back this is right chat
is laging oh okay okay ah you meant ah
okay the
latency oh oh that one's special
though I
no I hope that's at least somewhat
effective oh yeah it is she
I mean not effective but
powerful so where is
this it's not up there is it maybe it's
where the tomato is or here let's
[Music]
fight yeah I don't know eventually I
want to try out Ultra l see again but
I'm kind of scared to do it like now at
any time now without knowing for sure
that it's going to be fine it scares
[Music]
me yay let's
go follow the open path
have yeah but I first want the chest the
treasure chest that I have been teased
about I miss ultra low latency oh what
the [\h__\h] happened
no
what
what go back where
is it for the
door yeah okay where is the treasure ah
there it is and
then oh cuz there's another treasure
oh let's save
again I mean yeah that path was kind of
obvious because of the lack of a
wall did you know that there are Hot
Springs around
here ah you're no fun I want to be the
first to tell you that how about you be
the first to give me a membership to go
to the hot
springs I used to be a guard here until
Valentin sted away all my keys and gave
me the boot I guess I won't be needing
this master key anymore would you like
it yeah hell yeah all right there you go
you just don't tell me what you want to
do with it tell you okay go on take this
oh wow I'm being like presented with so
many things
here another one who loves the hot
springs did you know valentina's got a
huge egg in the middle of room it spits
out eggs from time to time and sometimes
when you Shield yourself the eggs will
Ricochet off of you now hold a hint for
how to combat that I
guess now back to the other room where
there's the three doors I
guess
[Music]
X I feel like I I made the right choice
with the door that I went
through oopsie I didn't hit the
thing
lucky w w w w w how did I get lucky what
what happened to me though
it said lucky but I don't know what it
did oh we're also lucky I should be so
lucky lucky lucky
lucky I should be so lucky
alone a Yosi what what's up Yoshi did I
get a Yoshi
egg Ah that's that's how I always
trigger that I don't know our first y
hey are there like certain enemies that
are more likely to give you a lucky buff
or is it really
random
middle just
random h
oh there are really only specific
enemies oh
really doesn't seem to be common
knowledge uh
ooh
magic
[Music]
really
uh
[Music]
nice why why would you run away after I
put so much effort into those jumps you
little [\h__\h] die
your friend dies because you ran away if
you stayed maybe just maybe it would
have survived so I hope you have
survivors Guild after this you little
[\h__\h] oh what a nice
[Music]
pot so we're here now again um I
wonder oh
that was uh waste a little bit
[Music]
um did I I didn't enter this door before
either did
I oh treasure woohoo y we got a flower
how do I get up there oh maybe I can't
but there's still a hidden treasure here
probably
upstairs seems like I missed an
opportunity Aura now you're here I was
asking for you and and I was hoping you
would be here cuz I wanted to tell the
thing that you told me that fascinated
me about the the the Fabrics of the idol
outfits being sold as
merchandise I have to go for the middle
door okay I'm going to go ah
[Music]
sausy G what you ate sausages or
what ah sausages really
sausages all right I don't think that's
how you write sausages I may not
be like the best English speaker of the
world but I am after all the myth
speaker
ofm
sounds good though right now sausages I
would love some
sausages sa no not even
that I'm really [\h__\h] hungry right now
man I'm so
hungry maybe it's time for a
cookie m j Flash oh that must be his
last attack that he
gets
don't I hate
[Music]
you sorry about the
screams is that a Yoshi egg will there
be also a giant [\h__\h] chunky wonky
Yoshi out of coming out of there like
all the other chunky things that you
have or another chunky
Dole maybe that's why the doo is so fat
because it came out of an egg like this
and it was like over
[Music]
nutrient
oh it won't open it's
[Music]
locked is is the egg
laughing why why is why is the egg
mocking
me should I
[Music]
look I'm lonely I didn't want to talk to
to you I was going to give you the key
to the Next Room sure uh I will take up
that offer but I just wanted to
see oh wait God damn it the flower jar
we're just going to use that thank you
now we can play is it a fight you're
kind of playing seems like it's Shelly
Shelly is your name cuz you're in the
Shell what if you come out of the shell
will it still be Shelly maybe we crush a
shell how about that that that has to be
effective but it's a boss so oh I got
the right timing I think even yeah yeah
I did it it did make the boo
[Music]
sound
nice nice should we is it a waste if I
use my triple move now maybe I should
use it after it
cracked
[Music]
maybe hold for now okay
okay let's see this egg crack oh [\h__\h]
only twice but it does a lot of
[Music]
damage
hey everything does a lot of damage
right now
[Music]
nice as long as it doesn't fight back
yeah we should maybe safe
[Music]
FP
I'm
speechless I never thought I would see
bero in this
game was this game the OG the first ever
appearance of
bero I'm so bum Boozled that's not what
I I mean I said it could be a Yoshi but
I didn't expect
Berto not even close oh
[Music]
oh well I don't
know I'm too young for that you know no
but hey
burto which why why does she have an egg
while she's in the
egg is she PL while in egg what
explain hey wasn't there something about
eggs like some NPC said something about
eggs and dodging them is she going to
shoot at
[Music]
me damn
it cor exception
yeah makes no
sense guess she just is that her default
like just always has an
egg wait how much damage did that do I
didn't
look wow this is like our fourth rate
today hello
girlies I wonder if jumping is still
that
effective no I'm so
stupid you're hurting me now it's my
turn get while it's
hot
[\h__\h] did she just shoot out an egg out
of her
toot toot
[Music]
mouth is this where I was supposed to
jump did I terrorize no it probably
doesn't work on her
anyway damn
[Music]
it
M [\h__\h] I'm stupid
a
EG how did I never think of that kind of
name for you
guys wow thanks for the membership gift
is is the one who be became the member
egg bird this same this very same
[Music]
egg egg
bird is is it going to hatch at some
point let's not risk it waa oh it's like
a bomb Oh and it hurts her
too I say her but wasn't there some L
that Berto is not a lady how is it not a
lady she's bfing
eggs I'm so confused by
Dan it's complicated
not well well
well
[Music]
[\h__\h] still so little oh my
God kab I mean that is decent
damage I thought you know having to
focus on a minion is going to be
Troublesome but it's like as if as if
I'm attacking her directly what you just
returned to egg understandable sometimes
I also just feel like returning to
egg just want to be left alone I wonder
if we're going to fight her again at
some
point let's go we were
healed there's more no
no no no no no
no no no no
no is it because we have to fight it
otherwise it's going to blow me
off okay fine then fine with
[Music]
me his new weapons timing I'm so used to
the old one I can't get it right
now oh wasn't this one resistant to
jumps [\h__\h] I think he
was on no no he's not but it doesn't
really care much about it okay physical
attacks it is yeah okay resistant to
thunder Bowser special aren't really
usually good for damage yeah but I
thought his terrorized was like pretty
decent also right there's a treasure
here right is it in the corner maybe no
maybe it's where the tomato is
[Music]
again let's try this
one how much does this do again oh
pretty
good good decent
AOE and they shall all be dead yeah I
love the look of the Tomato guys
[Music]
too they're
adorable they could be a Pokemon
honestly okay it was not there U maybe I
have to jump on this treasure chest and
it's on top of it
yeah
okay I'm glad I made the jump I'm glad I
didn't fall down I I registered where
the shadow is otherwise it would have
looked to me like it's more of a
diagonal jump but it's really just a
straight
jump almost Bamboozled what is this king
nimus is resting in bed absolutely no
running in the Halls
oh
Mario this can only mean that my mom and
dad
here what the
[\h__\h] it's
locked ah thank you Bowser I was going
to say like why do we have to open
everything with keys let's just break
everything do it do it go go away mow go
away make way oh do we have to help him
again wellit wait a minute if my dad's
really B we didn't we shouldn't make so
much noise we need a another class
H now I think someone who stick can take
a little bit of a kaboom of an a door
being forcefully
opened I guess we should find Valentina
and force truth out of her yeah okay I
like that idea
too oh you going to break that though
what what listen you never ever talk to
the leader of Bowsers minions like that
oh I hate that I'll ignore it this time
but it don't don't let it happen
again a
[Music]
oh another Chun
car
H all
right no trouble for
[Music]
me
stink attack followed up by a Geno
blast I love
[Music]
AOE doesn't kill
them that is
unfortunate I'll just attack them way a
[Music]
[\h__\h]
ready to launch oh no what should I do
I'm so
scared y bab protect me kfp come to my
rescue
please I'm scared pick me
[Music]
up AOE too yeah I mean I never played
AOE can only judge AOE
too five oh that one's pretty
good thank you I feel so protected I
feel so secure thanks to you
guys oh she's there que Valentina the
mar creature who beat up SMX is
here Mario what does a Mario look like
it has a bushy mustache long sideburns
and a pair of mean looking legs uh or
eggs was it eggs or legs I'm not sure
well both look mean probably
um I have a feeling I've seen this Mario
before somewhere oh yeah right that was
something like
[Music]
that I thought that was a statue of
uh what was it again I don't remember
well what are we going to do what are we
going to do
Valentina well we certainly aren't going
to listen to your partless chatter
Frankly Speaking I'm not going to worry
without this KY the king can't go
anywhere
Hold the
[Music]
Line Pablo my man I'm going to call him
Pablo now is he going to let out his
anger finally and become his own
bird poke the [\h__\h] out of here yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah go go Pablo I said shut
up already
no listen to him he's a bird Bird's
opinions are very
valuable what the that isn't a statue
that's
Mario Valentina head over to K
now how utterly rude Who in places are
you
anyway me I'm the real Prince that's
who
braki how dare you listen in on the
private
conversation private private everyone in
the 10 m radio could hear
you why do they have to look back to say
that to each other why aren't you saying
it directly to
her her if you're going to be this rude
I simply am going to
leave
coward chicken she's a chicken but not
the good
kind and fly to the CP too C they have a
c wait let me see the coup oh Pablo it's
okay you can be my friends no Pablo
don't go I think we kind of missed the
boat here we better get moving to let's
go
[Music]
okay oh
safe but I'm guessing there's still a
lot more dungeon to
go or is the fight coming up
that feels like a lot more dungeon they
always have like this safe point where I
feel
[Music]
like I feel like it's
like wa what the [\h__\h]
no no
I can you reach
him I feel like you
can
but yeah these safe points have bum
Boozled me plenty of times now I just
felt like oh there's a safe point then I
would think that that's the end of the
dungeon and there's a boss fight and
then so many times it's just like kind
of like a like a middle of the dungeon
safe point but I feel like at that point
it's already like the dungeon is big
enough so it makes sense to me that it's
over there
and the boss fight is coming
up but
[Music]
no let me
go
no can you not that's a lot of damage I
don't want that
please that's so rude that is so rude
let me
go
[Music]
are you forcing me to
stay for
real going to use this one for the first
time
[Music]
then
what that seems a bit
crazy [\h__\h] you killed
Dino cuz I hesitated too much because I
thought I could leave but they didn't
let
me I am
[Music]
shooked I need some levels anyway
I guess I mean I'm not dodging all
fights
uh do I have
[Music]
no wait I shouldn't use those
up
and
[Music]
okay I know I have this Maple syrups
but come on again
no
no I know I know I know I have Peach's
hug I know I know I just wanted to do it
differently
why do I even bother to try to run
[Music]
away
man here we
go
no it's because they're like not in the
middle I don't want to do it again
[Music]
whatever
no can I aim
[Music]
no
it's here where the entrance to the onon
was prin m is in the hot springs no he's
not just going to jump over you and go
there why why why can I
not so this is scripted right what the
[Music]
hell wait why do
I oh
[Music]
but
oh okay Queen Valentina Queen valtina is
the king showing up showing any
Improvement how how is his wife the old
Queen prin I see well no what I think I
think not only that
but F more uh but
then shut the up up I don't want to
listen to you
peasants ugly bastards I have better
things to do than listen to your half
Wi-Fi opinions and look while I've been
wasting my time listening to your
endless
chatter Mario has managed to f find
me
Pao that bird has a permanent brain
cramp don't look can you hear me get
over here now I need some
help move it come
now bam bam
[Music]
oh she
looks so
different optical illusion or what he
hey what separate
fight it's
like like in the
battle
she she has all her filters
on or not really I don't
know her face face is like so much
more never not never I don't know like
lengthy looks like Sith from Ice Age oh
my God I can kind of see
[Music]
it let me take that that cookie let me
eat the cookie that I was talking
about
[Music]
let's try
this
ah no what what
no it's going to [\h__\h] die
[Music]
can I
win is it a scripted
death I'm trying to
[Music]
block it's not as easy as in the mini
game
[Music]
yummy I need help no no B God
okay I don't even have much FP
[Music]
left what are we working with
here fire fear poison
79 I don't have fire fear
poison oh thank God I
[Music]
up and like it's hard to tell which Peck
he's going for the theun or the
immediate Peck yeah
it okay we can do
it
[Music]
uh that's
it I was
worried just [\h__\h] slaps Mario well
should we bring peach in here and have a
slap
battle oh my
God
I wonder what she's weak uh for I don't
know maybe
[Music]
jumps
oopsie wasn't too bad
though pretty
flowers
ah uh I guess I'll switch to Gino that's
fine that's
[Music]
fine oh
oh I kind of thought it was the charging
attack
[Music]
oopsie can't block can't do [\h__\h] Mario
don't die Mario Mario Mario Mario
the AOE attacks yeah I
I I I assume that it does more but at
one like on one side I want to save some
FP and on the other side I feel like
it's a
waste I know I know I know I know RPG
brain I only want to use AOE attacks
when there's more than one enemy
but also
this damn they're so expensive
too I mean down to 50% but still I'll
try this one
then maybe the damage will convince
me it's all
right oops see Crystal oh no I hate the
crystal attack ah he's
dead why can't I not instead of like uh
where mow is supposed to stand bring in
one of my other characters like
Peach why why why
why I'm the peach you can
what
no no I
cannot
mm- I cannot have a third member in this
fight for
now
should we jump
[Music]
again that's really
bad not worth
[Music]
it [\h__\h] why do I keep on missing now ah
Pablo is back don't you think Pablo is
really suitable for him as a
name so
cute mow is back as well oh my
[Music]
God
swear let's check her out too
t no not not not and now
weakness not known or not there are no
weaknesses which
one are there no or do I does not want
to tell
[Music]
me not
available here's a small man who puts on
a big friend who
Mario
I haven't seen a attack in a long time
so I didn't know the timing
[Music]
anymore all right let's
go so anyway Gino started
blasting
[Music]
how much
damage I didn't see
[Music]
again
M 1880 each oh that's
[Music]
good
I've never tried this one
before
oh oh please be
no right back at you
it worked well on
[Music]
Pablo okay let's do some Ur to
jump oh ah the height difference
[\h__\h] yeah it's okay though it's okay
decent damage to
[Music]
everybody I don't
know should I try
some electricity
attack Thunder attack
[Music]
only down to 20 FP again let's do a
normal
one uh-oh
oh
[Music]
ah oh we see a pretty fan now it's so
nice I like
[Music]
it what a fancy
fan is is Pablo dead like considered to
be dead or what's going on why is he
[Music]
sitting how about jumping on Pablo for
once we're doing
the I did the ultra one right you maybe
Pablo is considered
dead is he taking a
break a I feel bad for him he's so cute
[Music]
oh yeah I can't choose him okay oh
[\h__\h] okay so we're only fighting the
lady
now oh no Peach turned into the
mushroom not looking so good
[Music]
here let's switch to Bowser uh and
then heal him I
[Music]
guess I guess the cleansing
JS yes okay
okay
do I have much more left of the game by
the
way asking for a
[Music]
friend uh-oh one and two a I can never I
do what do you think in terms of
[Music]
time two more major one more
major area at least three more hours
three more
dungeons three dungeons including end
game H you did very little don't say it
like that I did very
much try my best here
[Music]
okay yeah okay then I feel like we might
continue
tomorrow after this dungeon is
[Music]
over yeah but at the same time I don't
want to
do like
a a fre hour only
stream only three hours of gamepl is
kind of lame
[Music]
too I don't know
not sure what to
[Music]
do I could finish but I'll be I would be
probably done after
midnight
[Music]
yeah yum
it uh
well this one heals debuffs too right
let's do
[Music]
it yeah it won't be what do you mean it
won't be for us you think it will be
longer wait it didn't heal their
mushroom status what the [\h__\h] man do
they turn back on their
own
longer okay yeah then I'll probably do
that I'll read super chats and then end
it
um how long does it take until they turn
back on their own to their original
forms I don't want to have to heal them
[Music]
both eh so long oh my god let's do peach
then and she going to heal
mellow looking cute as a mushroom
[Music]
though what what do you mean you think
it'll take 6 to 7 hours tomorrow what
there's no
way I'll show you I'll show you
specifically you that I can do it in
maximum 4 hours tomorrow I don't even
know how much there is left but no I
will
not it will not take 6 to 7 hours no no
no wait why is peach a [\h__\h] mushroom
again H what's going
[Music]
on did I use the wrong item on her or
or
Mario needs some help
here oh oh that's it
[Music]
okay I guess the the Sakura attack turns
them into
mushrooms bye-bye
Pablo
oh
what he was carrying her
huh first it looked like he was going to
crush her out of
Revenge when I was at 99% I could have
almost used my special oh man what a
pain in the
ass wait they're
gone so can we go to your parents now
let's go after her I know she but mow
don't you want to oh I guess because of
the key oh there it
is
let's go to your
[Music]
parents take back our rank our title is
royalty let's go go go Mario why are
you oh was he
waiting oh I didn't
understand
Bo oh it's cuz mow cried they wanted to
show that he was
crying I don't know why we waited
outside like this whole time we do
everything
together and now we had to give him some
privacy or
what Mom Dad I'd like you to meet Mario
um because I'm going to marry him I love
him oh oh also these people I say how
can we ever thank you enough I'm M's
father King nush hello everyone thank
you so much for looking up to my dear
child allow me to introduce
everyone
Peach oh I've heard so much about you
may I have your
autograph don't embarrass Junior dear oh
never mind and who is the sh man
here
Mario oh my God the Mario
she's okay then how about showing me
just a little jump a tiny hop that was
more than a tiny he even
flipped that way they celebrate him and
he asks to be
celebrated
SK it's
[Music]
Bowser uh should I be scared oh my God I
also need your autograph I guess not not
even a little oh man
Gino well he's a real
[Music]
boy speaking of stars a little while ago
a large star fell into the Vol
volcano well I probably melted
[Music]
away God damn it we'll never make
people's dreams come true ever again
it's over it's gen
over I bet that's one of the star
pieces but a try star dragon inhabits
the volcano it's going to be tough
getting a star out of there perhaps all
of you working together could handle the
Beast why when I was young I yes dear
now once at the volcano find Cinder toad
he'll be able to help you
time to just give up and go home exactly
before you go to the volcano you ought
to take a dip in our oh finally are you
going to give me a members card
please you're you're not you're just
going to tell me go to the onone even
though I need a member's card or do I
not need it anymore
now okay but we probably won't come back
until we find the
star he seems
not as like I don't know I feel like
there's something
missing like
emotionally there should have been
more emotions about you know him being
back from them and from him I feel like
that could have been a bit more you
know was
a a little bit brushed over in my
opinion
is there anything new here now that
the oh do I always get the star oh no
now it's a flow okay it was worth
getting back into
here
[\h__\h] can I no no no let me land no maybe
it can I am I even able to stop on that
platform and then like jump the other
direction I
wonder [\h__\h] let me
in I the real prins oh my God sorry
about that you don't need a members card
of
[Music]
course thank
you what
volcano you reach it from an AB oh okay
maybe from here why are there these
statues with the king oh I guess just as
fancy decoration it's kind of weird
though
like what if I don't want to be watched
by Four Kings as a lady and during the
hot
spring I'm guessing that healed me
danger Bey on this Edge is the volcano
o
really really
though wow I am so
lucky I jump straight into the middle of
the volcano and I'm so lucky to land on
a platform like
this oh nice
music I like this music but I would also
like to save and perhaps leave
[\h__\h] you know I'm not good with lava and
Mario games especially in free was
a oh
oh
oh yay get this over with yeah bye I'm
leaving there was nothing else there
right
no is this taking HP from
me h
this is like one of the major areas like
like a long dungeon
right nimas Town nimas
land just sends you back no HP l oh okay
okay okay
okay
is there something new to do here can I
go to that those platforms from here I
[Music]
wonder bottom right is this bottom
right oh what about
here let's
go oh
[Music]
that was not
it the right wall this is left no I mean
depending on how you look at it cuz this
is top right uh for me so then that
would be bottom right down
there run against the wall on the right
oh oh beo is
here
yeah B I'll give you this fertilizer if
you let me go
okay Pizza is so cute with those cute
little wings oh my
God that was
adorable uh
[Music]
okay now go to Flower
Town okay the M I've never been here oh
my God what are you doing in here
haven't seen you in a while
tomorrow here we read again this here
land is Rich I've got tons to loot and I
want it all but hey I'm not sweating
this device will tell me where the
treasure aen rest of them are mine oh
mine adios
amigos H don't I already have this
signal ring no it's an echo signal ring
if you equip it it will tell you the
locations nah I don't even want to put
that on I want to keep my OG signal ring
and find it
myself
this is where you got the single ring in
the original game oh until then you
wouldn't even have had
[Music]
it Rose what where am I going where do
we say I'm going uh
uh nothing sounds like the thing you
said I should go
to oh wait here they are Roseway Rose
town or
Roseway Rose
[Music]
Town yeah I think uh that was a good
change they didn't make many changes so
that everything would be you know like
the good old
times but the few changes that they did
make I would say are good changes uh why
am I what am I looking
for wooden flower there's a wooden
flower here oh I guess this
one oh is this a a Wen flower Bo oh
there it
is one of the
flags okay what about the A and the O I
want to find it myself but but I feel
like I would have to visit every single
map just tell me which map to go to go
to the back of the town or for for
something
different related to
the to the thing the
fertilizer never been here
before I
think hi am the gardener see that huge
planter I've spent many years seeking
the legendary seed and fertilizer to
fill it with but had no luck if I could
only find them I have
both oh my God I se My
imin
all as Garder that's why I have most
importance it's like me he's like
me he's going to steal it from
me while I'm out dead hey I haven't
finished yet
oh that's my story say will you give me
the scene
yeah finally have it this is
extraordinary oh I can't believe that's
a acting for the last I've been seeking
for forever I thought was barely R
searching high and low on the wall never
came close to finding made it
call change
tactics formulated myself fulfill my
life on dream as a GU I really cannot
enough the
part
[Music]
short attention
span that's what I should say to you
guys when you're like not following me
when I talk really fast excitedly about
something
amateurs
[Music]
no
[Applause]
no he's so
excited oh it's going to completely
destroy his
[Music]
house
so my long dream has become if I were to
attempt milon to one against you no that
sound quiet if nothing's more this is
that acally close to certain that the
truth of it is that no one would be able
to suppress this came into possession of
this planter it was not easy to believe
that a plant big enough I this a plant
with my own eyes and once again reminded
of the it's good to be a gardener wait
until my body's Over Happy Garden
monthly hear about this you think I
could use a little more
fertilizer
ah maybe not
M N M so if I climb up there do I get to
those
clouds no way no
[Music]
way was that
overlapping m
but can we get much higher because there
was
[Music]
more what was
that no wait what's
[Music]
we got some
shell and was it the lazy
shell a as a Mario
weapon
ah why did we get two here's a laser
shell and I
guess there's laser shell for him too
but it's oh wait wait his defense
though
his defense she oh his magical attack
goes down like
crazy it's for everyone
oh give it to D to
Peach best on Peach oh uh I guess but
isn't her healing affected I guess not
not
really by the magic attack I was going
to say but I guess not
really yeah that's that's seems like a
good
idea oh give her the FED to cancel it
[Music]
out well maybe not necessary
but
is mar Mario going to be doing good
damage
now unkillable healer and yes a potency
of heal is lowered but not enough to be
[Music]
harmful
okay yeah I think that's fine um but can
we like give him more fertilizer so that
this grows even
bigger I
[Music]
wonder
where is safe
[Music]
point he'll be dealing huge damage oh
look at
[Music]
them now to Yoshi's aisle oh what do I
have to do at Yoshi's
aisle let's
see why
[Music]
uh where was your shoes oh there it
is the last
[Music]
flag he and
oh maybe it's their
names oh I probably we got to get on
the on you yes is there someone
H with oh oh wait they don't have
names wait
goal ah I just
noticed I no this myself it's okay yay I
got the flags what do I do with all the
Flags again Yoshi you're coming with me
no come with
me I I didn't think it would be like
that
okay
uh look take him back to Monstra okay
okay okay
okay sleep in more oh yeah right cuz
they came to me in a
dream they were revealed to me in a
dream wait where was Monster
Town
where's what which
one I know I could go differently but
wait is it uh down here yeah okay it
doesn't look like a town cuz it's so
hidden good morning hello uh in wait not
here where is the one with the
star was it second floor
[Music]
no
what ah it's not an in It's just in
[Music]
here let's see what happens I am
curious uh good job you found your free
Flags hey you're not how
band you did pretty
well we had a great time too thanks for
playing our
game now the grand prize
giveaway what better be something
good so that sounded like a flower
[Music]
thing what what did I
get did I have 71 before check your
equipment oh is it
this doubles defense during
battle is it worth putting that
[Music]
on on
him
should I keep it on
him even more defense
item yeah
okay what does this do
again at this one
ah uh that's pretty
good what this one prevents
M I don't know should
[Music]
I give him the safety badge then I
guess remind me before like the final
final final final Final Fight maybe to
change the signal ring to something else
because then we definitely don't need it
[Music]
anymore
okay uh is there a safe Point here at
the beginning right no oh here
maybe face the 2D bus do you think I
could
now save to go oh wait the the the hole
was a safe right
right why did they hide hi it like that
so
[Music]
stupid the new items you think I can
okay we can attempt it and then fail
miserably no no I'll start with
uh
Gino oh wait
wrong you will die but it will be worth
an
attempt some people believe in me I
guess you're not one of
them oh he remembers
me why does he remember me can I save
scum
whoa oh no I didn't say I just left I
didn't even have to fight him I am the
antim I can see your past I can see your
future I consume time yummy yummy and I
will consume
you everything's
Mixel hey blast them it's so dark in
here I think I should turn on the
[Music]
light
h y y
y
y yeah it yeah it yeah yeah it's fine
it's fine did someone resist couldn't
see so
well how about the Snowman so far he
hasn't been resisting
anything Do You Want to Build a
Snowman ah oh they have the crystals
have different resistances
[Music]
ah
goodbye
[\h__\h]
uh I switch out for peach
anyway
oh but no one resists that wait I I'm at
100% yeah maybe I should uh switch
[Music]
ah as a mushroom can I still do the the
garge
move if I switch to
Bowser now can I do
[Music]
ites more
no okay then let's not use it yet
[Music]
okay
mhm no
[Music]
Mario
so this attack is insane and very very
necessary for this
[Music]
fight
y oh does she like resist all elements
I has a problemo because
[Music]
uh peach is
Immortal what does it do when you uh
maybe a full heal
uh-oh let's switch Gino
out
is it worth a terrorize or a poison or
should I go for
crush or
revive
[Music]
Mario but then what's Peach going to do
in her
[Music]
turn let's leave it to
Peach let still
poison actually want to see how much
that
does it's all right oh oh
oh
[\h__\h] W no BOS is going to die BOS going
to
die come
on D the
[Music]
sandstorm
[\h__\h] was so nice of you to welcome him
back
[Music]
out if I fail this fight I'm going to
save
scum oh oh thank God it went on
Peach oh yeah keep on going on Peach I
don't care yeah thank you thank
you that's what you guys mean with
uh her being Immortal
not it's basically brute forcing it if
you have peach in your team and insist
on Surviving uh-oh oh oh wait what does
the shredder
[Music]
do the triple move is
just Oh I thought if you have Peach on
your team it's always a healing thing
but it's all enemies I should do it now
right let's do it I've never seen it
before I
think or have
I
[Music]
oh yeah let's go
that one makes me want to play the the
soccer game from Super Mario please go
and Peach no not again Bowser down Mario
down
uh
uh maybe I can get the timing right I
can't why don't they show the
exclamation mark a second
before
everyone's dead right
[Music]
yeah why don't I show it so
late why oh this is actually doing some
damage to
[Music]
her showing when I should have done it
well I would have appreciated
if it showed it a little bit
earlier oh thank God um I think we
should help her with Revival work
maybe
maybe the one for switch sucks oh no
really I was wondering if I could do a
stream a collab stream with Mario
Strikers
K Crystal are are they any almost dead
ones no not
really yeah D gr pun yeah that's kind of
my plan but I don't know if they will
let me if I keep on
dying but he gets full HP thanks to
[Music]
that
oh I could not block it so what can I
do that's also not blockable
oh my [\h__\h]
God I'll just group hug for now and I'll
let I'll let him use a Revival item on
Mario Bowser will use
it wait why was group hog so did I use
the wrong thing why was that so
weak
[Music]
okay we're back in the game kind
of let's try some Ultra
[Music]
jumping I
suck oh man yeah I don't know I'm not
ready for this kind of
fight oh the heal does feel weaker maybe
it's because of the
[Music]
accessory I want him to be fully healed
that's why I'm using the
item at least I'm getting freebies all
the time so
far Mario please
Mario which one annoys me the most which
one do I want to get out of the way
maybe the fire
[Music]
one yes we did we got some AOE at
least come on come on
Wawa
why what's happening why can I not jump
properly anymore Mario don't die
no
yikes the green one has the lowest HP
oh as long as I'm getting the freebies I
think it's okay to go for that one the
item Dark Star one
two
[Music]
yes a
[\h__\h] one I mean I missed the timing but
[Music]
one
okay he's gone
[Music]
yes Bowser no
Bowser come back
please making progress yeah I wonder if
he'll get more minions once these are
gone but they're so strong that I would
hope
that he will not spawn any more minions
after
that I want Mario to
survive if we can't block I don't want
him to die
[Music]
again
so maybe even this
one
no spawning
[Music]
okay
oh [\h__\h] 19 holy [\h__\h] no Bowser I feel
like I was so close to the timing ah man
what the
hell I almost had the timing but I guess
that those stones would have killed us
any anyway oh no because we couldn't
block anyway right cuz we had the the
debuff I couldn't have blocked could
I
you
man another attack I can't block wow
great thank you there's a little bit too
many attacks that you can't block in
this game honestly
a little bit messed up in my
[Music]
opinion [\h__\h] I missed who is he going
for yeah okay okay okay Peach is fine
Mara Bowser Why Did You Have To
Die stupid let's bring Mario back his
normal attack does a lot of good damage
[Music]
[\h__\h] usually really weak uh
not not to my
[Music]
experience N I didn't make it this
time bye-bye
Mario now almost still
alive
[Music]
okay I think I know the timing now for
next
[Music]
time nice okay this one too when he
kicks it up bye-bye Mario it's okay
we'll keep on repeating that that's fine
that's
fine
I can repeat that Reviving you only
costs 2 FP ah wait a little bit early a
little bit early
still next time oh dark start one two
three
yes I'm making improvements okay I can
block some
[Music]
things yes this one I'm nailing
too so that's all of that is fine is
like whatever oh wait we don't
oh let's focus on healing Mario for now
maybe nice
69 what level is my team no idea do you
guys know extra block is the most
important mhm focus on the crystals yeah
okay can you mute them I don't know can
I hey I thought that was timed
well
[Music]
ouch yes finally did something right
can't block
uh okay anyway uh water
crystal
nice
ouch there he goes again there he goes
[Music]
again uh come back Mario save me Mario I
totally need saving right now ah too
early again
[\h__\h] it's when when it arrives right
when the star touches Mario basically is
[Music]
it
yikes sometimes I legit don't know like
most of the time I legit don't know are
they attacking peach or Mario it's hard
to tell
[Music]
uh ah [\h__\h] well 69 is quite nice
honestly Dark Star one two
three you got nothing on
me why is peach so tanky good question
she's I don't know why
honestly just before it ends the but
yeah yeah I mean I mean I I know that
but somehow I'm I'm so old always a
little bit
early uh
yeah still not dead got
B uh Mario Mario stand strong stand
strong
[Music]
Mario
oh his FP is
gone that is funny I mean he hasn't been
even using that much but I guess his
black star thingy costs him a
lot uh
oopsie what's with these
[\h__\h] uh-oh yeah B that's that's
cutting it close Earth crystals FP is
gone to can they attack normally I I
don't want to win like this where I just
styled it until the
end I don't want to win like
this no that's that
[Music]
sucks his noral attack is also really
strong and it it's like out of
[Music]
nowhere oh finally one is
gone so is a legit strategy and RPGs are
all about
strategy valid Strat restart the fight
no I will
not well we got rid of uh
two I got it does he get full heal he
does let's go
let's
go let's
go then it's time to revive
Bowser yes yes
yes one cannot say that I am not uh
improving during this fight quite
forcefully but uh I am
[Music]
yeah wa I'm getting all those AOE hits
too beat him with all you got of course
of course I'm not restarting the game
it's okay it's okay I mean it's not very
satisfying way to win but it's
okay
oh don't
die can't block that [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
Bowser has so much defense and it still
did 145 on him time for a group hug
everybody hug I love you so
much so that's not a lot of HP on
Bowser I'm just relying on these normal
attacks cuz they're pretty
good yeah
300 oh bye-bye Bowser it's okay I can
revive you with full HP again I think I
figured it out
Jinx totally a valid strategy I mean
yeah history has
proven this as well like in the Medieval
ages stalling someone like by
surrounding their Castle endlessly and
cutting off their food sources yeah I
mean it's been done many times before
been there done that ah [\h__\h] I
missed Shin Mami tensei 3 fre I played
one Shin Mami tensei for one sponsored
stream do you
know that did happen in the past
uh-oh I played five oh oh my God
ruthless attacks
here
yosina I
missed thanks for reminding me each time
that his um FP are
[Music]
gone
oh should I use it on coolx I would say
right I mean it hits everybody anyway so
whatever Let's Go full power full
[Music]
frontal I wish it was longer actually
that damage isn't even that impressive
when you look at my normal attack damage
when I time it
correctly that's not even that
good like look at that
222 what do you mean the this is a
normal game Boss what what do you
mean
[Music]
it's over buddy I don't know what this
Final Fantasy character is doing in here
but it's
over I'm destroying your fantasy
[Music]
world it's time to stop
dreaming maybe then you can become 3D h
join whole life and then maybe you get a
chance at becoming 3D if you really want
to become 3D so
badly you might not get much studio time
but you you could become 3D and you can
use home 3D all you want every
[Music]
day Home Free is quite funny too you
know quite
[Music]
entertaining oh my god dude
chill a pix actually that sounds kind of
funny in
pixel whole life or like give someone a
pixel form like like like just like in
the same sense of like how kodon has
looked that tree form for example give
someone pixel forms like really
small yeah Cordon could actually be a
good
[Music]
candidate H thanks for the membership
gift you're gifting so much today are
you celebrating something are we
celebrating
something oh
[\h__\h] that's
[Music]
fine what was that peach what was
that can we try like something else for
once nah not worth it
[Music]
nice alino and
mow H I don't need them
anymore do they get exp even when
they're dead at the end of the fight
because in other games uh often you
don't get exp then and it feels really
painful when that happens they don't
okay then I'll keep them dead oh he's
dying that took ridiculously long but oh
that 244 exp she how many level up is
that was I 17 before
or did I get two level UPS I wish I
could would have gotten two ultra
viable
what is this Banger music
suddenly wait it is a wait is it a Final
Fantasy
character I was just
[Music]
joking a Square Enix Nintendo TI
staring I love
this hey
[Music]
hey Square made this
game so they self-inserted them into the
game I mean if you can then why not
[Music]
right they weren't squaresoft back then
they were just
Square
really
it's an original character oh this very
Square Enix
see Meta Koopa
stomp oh mea mea Koopa not
[Music]
me so I mean I'll just say it again you
should just audition to Whole Life
become frd in her life how about
that this like legendary strength is the
power of that third dimension it is far
mightier than the forces of malevolence
could dream I will treasure this momento
of my journey here perhaps in another
time another game we may have been
mortal enemies someday I will gain the
power of this third dimension and those
forces will visit a land not yet mapped
until that time take this treasure as a
keep sake of our
fight what does this do
[Music]
this music is funky farewell Champion
KN slowly
backing like a car again the door is
gone
what I did it I brute forced it let's
go did he ever show if this is an
original character did he ever show up
in any other
game would have been nice if he was
implemented in a future Final Fantasy
game as an a villain and enemy or
so double
save no what that's so sad let him
become 3D why is he forever stuck in his
2D form or at least let him show up in
2D and one of other Square Enix games
doesn't have to be doesn't have to be
you know what what is what did we just
get and this is better than what we
currently have shining stour
of I thought I would maybe as a gimmick
become pixel because it doesn't do
anything it it doesn't do
anything no you're not telling me it
doesn't do
[Music]
anything
I do 50% more damage and
[Music]
oo all right so there's no downside to
it
right it's worth using okay then then
[Music]
then
um who do I give the ghost
one maybe to mow I have so many good
[Music]
accessories oh thank God it was a good
reward for a moment I thought they were
messing with
me give it to Peach no no that doesn't
pay off my student loans nothing nothing
will do that
except maybe his sugar mommy or
daddy you can totally wipe Jinx
now
oh maybe another thing we shall do now
did I get healed and all that
yes Mommy Kiana I'm not that kind of
Mommy
all right then let's do it you little
[\h__\h] I just fought a big [\h__\h] now I'm
going to fight
you Bowser's Ultimate
Weapon going to fail
oh oh my finger is not so
fast
ow still only
one uh didn't he just uh like normal
physical attacks
I think that was the
[Music]
thing should I leave peach in this fight
maybe for now let's see how much damage
we're taking if we need peach in
[Music]
here oh yeah still has that weapon ow
[\h__\h] da
da we will kill this one before he runs
out of FP I promise
you I'm obviously dominating I mean
look oh [\h__\h]
oopsie I can miss once let's
switch yes oh that does little very
little
maybe just for Gino I can use uh his
special
[Music]
attacks he become so good no I really
haven't but thank you ah he does not
have a he just SP spams physical attacks
yeah but now he uses an attack called
Quicksilver 69 really really oh cuz ah
his defense is up isn't it
I want to debuff him or or we'll boost
it let's boost
[Music]
ourselves oh bye bye
Gino your time is over
here back to the good
damage oh that's
it that's it
I thought we were still like going on
for a while let's do the third battle
yeah yeah yeah let's do it but I want to
be
healed I did get healed okay let's go
number
three the final
[Music]
one uh okay here we
go but he already starts off with so
much
[Music]
defense not quite not quite the timing
oh wait did I do it cuz now he got
defense up too so I guess I did do
it
[Music]
whoa what what what why was Mario's
damage Mario's damage so high but Bowser
is so low and holy [\h__\h] he does a lot of
damage I have to focus on blocking but
wait my triple move is almost
ready Let's boost Mario before we
[Music]
die yeah yeah yeah yeah that's what I'm
talking about H super special time
[Music]
now oh it's quartz charm oh yeah yeah
yeah that's like 400 damage that we did
I think
[Music]
roughly you oh I would have not dodged
de I'm telling you I would have
died yeah oh that's it that's it oh what
a loser what a city loser give me a
title give me your dojo it's mine I am
the champion for sure my reputation was
sted on oh wait his voice was more
higher my reputation was sted on this
last fight so I've lost the title of
Sensei and today you are the Sensei of
this Doo L there please take this belt
which only the highest ranking fighter
in the dojo can
wear a jinx belt another accessory that
I don't know who to put on we will
rename the dojo Mario Style dojo and
incorporate your jump technique into the
training
y give be take over
woo oh T we'll start our training
immediately what why did he run outside
did he change a sign in the
front one fast and warm jump ups jumps
up warm up jumps ready to
begin can't jump on
them they should have implemented a
secret treasure here that you can only
uh get once you made Jump by jumping on
top of them also why is
his why does his shadow follow him and
his doesn't I don't
know yeah it's say Mario let's go let's
go let's
go
M brilliant right that would have been
so good
man that would have felt so so intuitive
to me too cuz that was my first idea my
first idea of doing that even though I
didn't even have a sign that there would
be a secret treasure just feel like
doing it anyway okay then we've done
like two side bosses that I didn't
wouldn't have had to do
obviously that used up some time but
I've become very powerful thanks to that
which maybe will make
tomorrow much more com able and
[Music]
easier ah
oopsie ah the accessory that we just got
oh yeah what is this one I mean I don't
know I doubt it's better than the quartz
charm uh well that's pretty good
pretty good emblem of power I mean yeah
I wouldn't say that would be better than
the 50% that I currently have to put it
on
Bowser already replacing the
feather man
27 I don't necessarily need him to be
Speedy anyway that's what I was thinking
like we all get a turn anyway I don't
really feel like I need Bowser to be
first
so that's fine 31 94 that's fine that's
that's good
so okay all right then Super Chat
reading time Super Chat reading time and
I'm sorry guys uh I'll do the cooking
baking stream
on Tuesday probably cuz I have some um
business meeting on Monday like in the
middle of the
day
and
I don't know if I want to bake cookies
like after 700 p.m. you
know that would be cookies for
dinner and no I was just drinking that
was the
bottle yeah stream tomorrow to finish
the
game uh but yeah Monday would probably
be a day off or a short stream in the
late evening maybe I'll do a Koke or
something like that I feel like
celebrating my Spotify wrapped up by
doing uh unarchived K or so maybe maybe
maybe
maybe H sounds
good would be fun would you enjoy
that although I I there's some songs
that I've been hoping to learn and then
I keep on forgetting about it feel like
there's something I wanted to learn and
now I really don't
no let me put it in my
schedule so that I don't forget that I
want to do a k maybe maybe one ah wait
ah another
H H my other plan for Monday I had like
two plans so this is
[Music]
uh that one thing that I have to do I
was planning on trying to get my accents
motion cap suit to work on Monday like
just like looking if I can get it to
work just going to spend some time on
like getting it
[Music]
usable just please take a day off
sometime next week oh just like this
week I will probably take
two oh next week is Anime Frontier too
in Texas I'll be
there I do want to do K but uh maybe on
the weekend is
better once we finish Super Mario RPG
this
weekend what the [\h__\h] uh then we don't
have anything currently long running
right I gave up on
gt8 wait did I finish the
GTA or did I give up on it I don't
remember
anymore oh we we are not finished indeed
it feels like I finished it but it's the
DLC that I'm not finished with
right maybe I can schedule
uh GTA
day
uh okay maybe on Sunday I can do like
GTA and I think maybe after anime
Frontier
in the evening I could probably do K
maybe so a full
[Music]
weekend tra oh
yeah
true how's it can I can we watch it can
we react
together house house house of the Dragon
new trailers can we watch it together
did you guys watch it you don't want to
watch it no you will watch it you little
[\h__\h]
okay I want to watch it came out uh 3
hours ago oh my God it's just one 1
minute and 25
seconds don't skip
it okay let me just watch it's just one
minute one and a half minutes
uh my my chat crashed why why why why is
it pinned
no it crashed cuz I wanted to pin
it well another gifted membership thank
you got you got it
ready when I say zero we click on the
play button
okay 3 2 1 zero oh wait you hear us stop
stop stop stop stop stop I need to mute
the test of audio one more okay one more
one one more one more 3 2 1
zero
oh who was
that who's
Victor oh what's that
scene oh
oh oh right she looks like Fiona in the
green dress that Queen whatever her name
was I actually like her cuz she has
reddish hair too she looks like
Fiona from
Shrek how of the
dragon dragon
D thing never
mind oh okay not not really um like to
me I think I would have to watch it
again uh CU that that was like a lot
happening very fast I don't really
understand what's going on
um but yeah cool cool trailer uh now we
have to wait another half year for
[\h__\h]
sake It's the funniest thing you've ever
said I'm crying
laugh the funniest thing I have ever
said in three
years I know it was a joke I know it
means the
winner I know I I I I heard it and I was
like this is my chance let's say who is
Victor I want to make more jokes like
that but normally my reaction time is
not that
fast I don't believe that Dragon was
actually able to fly what do you mean
what what
what
[Music]
of course it was a joke who's Victor but
actually we should be asking who's
Frank why there was no Frank mentioned
you little
[\h__\h] oh just because I see it in my
recommendations right now you know the
other day when I was in the airplane for
the first first time of my life I
watched an episode of Saturday Night
Live never seen it
before I made the same joke and tell R
brother Frank I did I did but the victor
one hit way
better it's bad these days that's what I
hear I liked the one though that they
had in the airplane there was like one
episode of SNL New or Old I'm guessing
it was new relatively new as new as
things are on the airplane but
um
yeah I think yeah they made pretty
recent
jokes something about I think it was
something about Biden they kept on
saying something about
Biden what did you think it well
generally I thought it was uh pretty
entertaining I think I mean no it's not
like the
worst no
anyway I know what episode you you
do do they only talk about Biden once in
the whole Saturday night life uh
history
remember you told cie she should be on
Saturday Night Live during Shark Tank
and everybody in chat so it is an
[Laughter]
insult I mean I just thought it would be
funny to name any kind of comedy show
and then that's the one I had in my
memory in that moment probably
because I may have seen
it close to that date because I started
in an airplane maybe I saw it on my
flight to Japan that's why it was in my
recent memories maybe maybe
most people don't like
it
interesting or actually it might not
even have been dead just a while before
I watched like a kind of like a deep
dive about someone who was on
SNL where the focus wasn't necessarily
about him a yeah yeah it was about James
Cordon I think was
it how he kind of made his was it James
Cordon he made his career for Saturday
Night Live and then left it behind and
everybody hates him now what was was was
that it was James cordin on Saturday
Night
Live was
[Music]
it no it was about col
O'Brian sorry I'm mixing up too many
things now yeah it was about Conan
O'Brien it was a deep dive about Conan
O'Brien I think and and yeah yeah
yeah and how he came to like who he is
or so maybe maybe maybe maybe that was I
I don't even know anymore I'm so
confused
whatever I don't know anything anymore
he was a writer for SNL
oh huh okay whatever completely cancel
that that conversation because I'm so
deep in confusion that I'm mixing up
everything uh let's let's let's let's
read the Super
Chat
uh let's actually also go to a room
that's nicer than this
one sorry this is members only content
please don't look
[Music]
cuz I had a I had a 4our members only
stream
yesterday in case you
remember I've been doing weekly members
only
streams but yeah there may be like some
uh exceptions every once in a while a
week where I don't do the members only
stream but so far it's been going quite
smoothly
H maybe this week the coming week you'll
actually will get a short members only
stream 20 memberships
motion ho [\h__\h] ho
[\h__\h] 20 thank
you one of these days oh next the next
next time yeah yeah yeah
yeah
uh
no just write a
message uh on
Discord
bgm
more memberships thank you come watch my
weekly membership streams yesterday was
fun I did a handcam stream where I built
some fake
[Music]
Legos
little oh yeah we were having a comfy
tea drinking Sy ceremony didn't
we hey can you guys remind me at the end
of the stream that I need to upload uh
something to a drive for someone
else cuz they just sent it to me
directly and I have to upload it to a
folder thank you more
gifts
more thank
you
it's good music
right a more man thank
you wow T the season of gift giving it's
the season of giving and being
[Music]
Jolly so
nice what what super chats are we
reading guys
are we done with the wa waiting room we
are right then
origami I thought I was done with the
waiting room
yeah ho ho ho ho ho
ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho
[Music]
ho
E I didn't finish
it what
so what I
didn't
huh
okay but did I read the one from
honu feel like I must have right did
I may I pinch This
[Music]
Woman's what did I do what did I do is
it like out of affection unn thank you
oh my God so many memberships to
crazy I did read it so
[Music]
okay why did I not finish this
SW H Tracy
thanks for the pinky on Thanksgiving I'm
giving thanks to the best 10 he I read
this
[Applause]
you who who said I stopped there who was
that who told me to continue reading at
Honolulu H raise your
hand GD G what
happened I don't want to send you to the
usual room but I must I
must
unfortunately this is the first time I'm
sending
you
GD no they said that it was them one
month go
on I'm
disappointed I thought I could Rel on
you I trusted you one mon FAL
room you have to do better not the first
time
oh well then
enjoy just for this season there's a
special author so to say usual room has
no Legos at the moment to step on so a
little bit less painful than usual
[Music]
okay Jacob for7 D I want a 20 W
lightning cable D Justin Reinhard D
thank you
oh I understand I understand why she's
so cute chocolate
insomia how merciful it's a Christmas
miracle it is it really is I am so
merciful chocolate insomnia D Monkey D
br br jell Le
D donate blood and watch me D the James
reloaded
D oh it is food expensive in New Zealand
really Marcus Mac
[Applause]
[Music]
danan simply d h origami oh someone with
origami in their name
dun Marcus menes dun thank
you yeah the origami frogs I remember
when I was in school I also made the
origami frogs and I feel like I Knew by
heart how to make
them not
[Music]
anymore yes I show benevolence to you
guys because T the season that was what
in my list I was trying to keep track no
no don't make me feel
bad now I feel bad I feel like I'm too
mean you were just trying your best to
be helpful
uh bmed
and
e thank you thanks it's over a year that
I watch t streaming During the period is
so much fun and many things were
happened when I saw my birthday passing
by last week I could feel that time went
fast but
hung oh oh
H
[Music]
so so
so
[Music]
H oh something about me studying Korean
come thank you thank you thank you happy
belated
[Music]
birthday yay yay y y y y y
yay y t d and py
d yeah it's it's good practice it's
actually shocking how I'm really unsure
about how to read this
partially but thank you it is
helpful and next is oh Mario
Mario let me get the
thumbnail B
[Applause]
[Music]
Mario RPG the first
episode it's been over a years since she
became my Kam was she tell me more how
did you watch whole life before what
made you want to you know support me
more what made you fall in love love
with me tell me tell me tell me tell me
Michael tell me Michael tell me Michael
tell me Michael tell me Michael tell me
more tell me more how did you find me
tell me more tell me more why did you
choose
me Michael Michael Michael Michael
Michael Michael Michael Michael Michael
Michael
Michael Michael Michael
M
M M
Mel I don't see his answer did he
answer is he still
[Music]
[Laughter]
typing hey you tell me too for a look
tell me tell me tell me tell me ah There
It Is I've been in the whole life rabbit
H for a long time oh a 2020 when I was
getting over a breakup but it was during
your GTA 5 streams when you hooked me
with your love and care a that makes me
really happy I feel like uh like um GTA
5 was really good for me like in terms
of like I think GTA 5 may have been my
best
running uh long playthrough on my
channel my long it's it even even though
it was also so a really long
one even at the end it was still
performing relatively
well yeah so I I felt pretty happy and
satisfied with how well it was
performing and how well liked it was by
you guys and I was really having a blast
too I wish I could recreate that I feel
like uh GTA 4
[Music]
did not quite reach that did not quite
get there also
because I don't know I guess it's not
like the most popular one and GTA 5 was
just uh I guess pretty popular at the
time GJ 6 yeah I think
although if I play GTA 6 when it comes
out I feel like everybody's going to be
playing it
so I might not be People's First Choice
you know at the the
time so I don't know if it's really
going to perform that well but even if
other people pick it up you know how it
goes with a lot of the other girls they
maybe start streaming it but they don't
stream it until the end but I will I
certainly
[Music]
will oh I'm excited for it when is it
coming out again please remind me
[Music]
again when I finished GTA 5 and even a
while later I was still like doubting
that GTA 6 will be out anytime
soon no date oh but trailer soon so I
guess we'll know with the coming trailer
I was watching whole life mostly cor on
it for about 6 months when Ian came I
was watching a debut debut and I feel I
fell in love with you in positive energy
right away even I even like your old mic
hey thank you thank you I don't even
want to think about
my old self
anymore but thank you I'm happy that
you've been around for so
long you're the
best you can play cyber Punk until GTA
nah I don't know I'm not really
interested in that
one I've heard that it finally is like
playable that was a game right that's
like was like really buggy and stuff and
it got a [\h__\h] ton of
patches just a real trailer probably not
going to give us a release
[Music]
it I don't even want to make any guesses
now space Channel 5 what's Space Channel
[Music]
5 mostly broken on consoles
H well I didn't really hear good things
at the time and and I was not I was not
interested anyway to begin with so it's
like
[Music]
whatever cyber Punk
GTA
[Music]
[Applause]
just explain to Japanese
bro what's so funny or great about GTA I
said I feel like you could compare it
with Yakuza and say it's like American
[Music]
Yakuza
you guys keep on thinking that my
Coca-Cola bottle is me cracking
something it's just me opening the
[Applause]
[Music]
bottle kind of fair right like in terms
of the
humor I feel
like it's comparable the atmosphere and
the
humor
[Music]
the wackiness
yeah the amount of side
quests and also like generally like the
visual
quality both games have like actually
really good great quality of visuals of
graphics and
and like you play in big cities that you
can explore
[Music]
freely well more or less
freely you prefer yaka yako sisters you
know that's funny because my mom she she
likes GTA right so she really enjoyed me
waa watching me play GTA but remember
she did not like Yakuza she did not
enjoy the humor of Yakuza which is
actually funny now that I now that I
talk about how similar those two games
actually
are I guess for y
you know what adds on to it is like
Japanese uh wacky culture not that she
has a problem with Japanese culture I
feel like I have forced her to get used
to it enough
now but
still yeah it's just a different kind of
humor more Western humor is going to
resonate more with my Mommy I suppose
like I feel like what will forever be
stuck in her brain is the the the
scene with the grown ass man and diapers
rolling around on the ground acting like
[Applause]
babies I don't think we can get that out
of her
mind she will never give G uh Yakuza a
[Music]
chance
what are we talking about Yak yeah like
I mean we were mostly talking about GTA
but then saying how Yakuza is kind of a
good comparison to to say it's like a
Japanese GTA more or less in some
ways assassin
screen H I would not say no to that it's
not something I would want to to pick up
like immediately in the upcoming half
year but I could see myself play it at
some
point maybe but yeah maybe maybe if we
want to uh if GTA 6 is still far far far
away we could play Red Dead Redemption
before GTA
6 you guys keep on asking about it and I
I don't uh mind it either I've been like
eyeing It
[Music]
Anyway a it's horse
GTA are there muscle
horses I mean usually horses are pretty
muscular but can I go straight to Red
Dead Redemption too
[Music]
I mentioned in the past superat that I L
mainly during the first year but like
do what my aqu by whole talk she yeah I
can I can okay okay okay okay
okay maybe that will be something for
spring anyway let's go super chats take
a 47 D morally immoral
D this game was going to have a sequel
but legal issues caused that not to
happen so they created the Paper Mario
series which the first one was
originally called Super Mario rpg2
uhuh it even though legal issues arose
they still called it Super Mario rpg2
kind of like a
successor a certain character in your
party if set up right will be the most
broken character in the game but I
wonder if you learn who it
is Gino I
suppose
imagine Gino's beam attacks with the 50%
damage
increase they were going to call it that
but they didn't oh okay okay
okay I think we got to that point yeah
right now like everybody's pretty
powerful
[Music]
peach peach I mean she was broken in
that fight where she wasn't taking
damage
[Music]
yeah Kingdom Come Deliverance never
heard of
it square and Nintendo got salty at each
other over the square taking final
fantasy series to
PlayStation
really is that where their breakup
happened you wouldn't like the game
yes
really take damage from op
extra yeah for real hey what did I do to
make her so powerful isn't didn't she do
it
herself bit more
[Applause]
complicated maybe we should do an
intervention for them a the lazy shell
oh
laser
shell I gave her laser shell armor did I
I guess I
did I don't remember that
anymore I don't know who I gave it to uh
SM dushin Lu with danin reach
[Music]
tashin ooh actually that does sound dope
reach H maybe in the future Ricky da
thanks to the the
pinky why do I feel like I haven't heard
from you in a while huh and still you
don't even write a
message in your
pinky
n hope you're doing well though chat is
gone oh oh oh oh oh I didn't
[Music]
realize
I want nintend to CD drivers in their
next
conso one with
cartridges oh so because of the
cartridges the next Final Fantasy game
wouldn't have been able to fit on
[Music]
it oh another all too much data maybe
they should have downloaded more RAM at
Nintendo I don't
know why did they not think of
that
[Applause]
Al
[Music]
it's
birthday but Japanese bro already went
to bed I think ah even though he's
always trying his best to stay
around ah you're still
here happy birthday to
you in the H happy birthday to
you
[Music]
time
congratulations it's early in the
morning now
[Music]
thank
you CH UT become
CH k
d Studio Rob D wait Kon wants to uh
recommend me a
RPG oh that looks
cute which spring
r that does look really
cute is that for the phone oh no it's on
Steam I mean I might play it
privately character looks like she could
be in ging impact
TBH but
cute well she's an alchemist is
she it was initially for phones that's
why it looks like
that but I don't know I like it I like
the
visuals is that a criticism I don't
know not
[Music]
[Applause]
necessarily but okay
continuing
uh
all so Studio T Al thank for the pinky
again and again and again thank
you surprised he didn't play the little
wi game that Ian friends for
no well no
comment I lost interest oh there she
goes in comments even though she said no
comment Mama Mia and the do be 1,000
d m d Lord evok D Anthony D black d Mr
kasik
dun skum
dun I oh I I know oh skellum you must be
new here we did use tur duckin more or
less as a unit name when we were just
free
mhm John Noble dun Daisy thank you for
the ride chat and even nowadays if we
collab with just us three then it's also
tur
ducking H fun fact H the original Mario
RPG was developed by the final fantasy
team and this remake was developed by
one of the Dragon Quest teams so this is
kind of your second Final Fantasy and
first Dragon Quest uh not really but
okay Big Stretch so stretchy you might
be getting stretch marks Daisy you
better check out your body for some
stretch marks and put some lotion on
there Mama
m a kiss on your stretch marks because
you're beautiful no matter if you have
them or
not you're beautiful the way you are but
then I
mean you're causing this yourself with
these stretches Mama
Mia
hey
did you did I inflict emotional damage
upon
you no it's okay I also have like like
something like I don't know if it's you
know I mean you know I have a few
stretchy Marys here and there you
know we all have it we're all you
know I mean you guys are covered in
feathers so you might not even see it
but you probably have some we all we all
got them here and
[Music]
there
mhm
yeah no it doesn't even mean that you're
chubby
like
[Music]
yeah just a skin thing
M just a thing that happens it's just
it's
natural
[Music]
huh
so anyway Daisy I
I I had to I mean how could I not roast
you for that spider me d m d donate
blood D JK d thank you for listening to
POV you are one of the reasons why my
Spotify WRA looked like that thank you
unless you didn't listen to it on
Spotify then I guess not probably not
were you did you put in the CD in your
album in in your car because you say it
was on a long drive maybe it wasn't on
Spotify at all maybe it was the CD oh
well still
still same
sentiment black FR
dun j d space waterfall d a rer nine Dan
r n Dan Bo 73 Dan yuk Mike thanks for
the pinky we had lots of snow during our
vacation no way last week didn't expect
the same for Austria though is snow
really common for Austria's winter
hopefully you're feeling better after
Japan trip by the way welcome back thank
you um I feel like
it most snow here is always in this past
years it's always been in January
February
but it has been snowing a lot in Austria
these in this past week one or two
weeks
surprisingly much
snow Yeah
e and even sticking to the ground not
disappearing
snow so that is uh nice to see H but
earlier than
expected
mhm humic effort closed until tomorrow
what munic aort has been surprised by
snow Munich Airport
snow top stories Munich Airport suspense
flights amid heavy every
snowfall why why did they not
really
really Munich Airport is a pretty big
airport like couldn't you have like done
something
like get rid of the
snow heavy snowfall has brought chaos to
parts of Southern Germany with air and
rail traffic blocked in the Bavarian
state capital Munich after first
suspending flights until noon on
Saturday so today Munich ort later said
it would be remain closed until 6:00
a.m. oh so a whole
day spokesperson said 760 flights were
affected more than 40 cm 16 in of snow
fell overnight on Friday into Saturday
according to Weather Services oh so in
the night from Friday to Saturday
because the airport is closed during the
night and then they woke up to an insane
amount of snow m
but like I
mean yeah I mean I feel like you you
kind of know on the evening before that
there's going to be snow in the night
and then maybe for something as
important as a huge airport shouldn't
you be like ready for it with like what
do you call the snow flowing machines
plowing
machines 50
cm I mean
[Music]
surprised you can't counter that
somehow oh even the even the
trains the main Munich station cannot be
served it said Travelers should expect
delays and cancellations for the reach
oh my God okay uh Bavaria AKA Munich has
been
[\h__\h]
[Music]
holy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
damn
well
damn good luck to anybody who has to fly
to or from
[Applause]
[Music]
Munich a rare event I mean in January
February it wouldn't even be that rare
though during like the the more common
snowing month so there has to be some
[Music]
[Applause]
solution yeah
oh Looney I can't do that I can't play
Nintendo games in member
streams I don't need a quick first
impression I'll just play it at some
point I'm I'm pretty sure that at least
for one stream I already bought it so
even if it's just one stream I'll play
it
[Music]
eventually I don't need the first
impression I kind of already have a
first impression from watching I think
at some point I watch dendo play it a
little bit at
[Music]
least although playing Mario games for
me playing Mario games is very different
than watching Mario games everything
looks so easy when dendo plays Mario
games he's like you know he had years
and years and years of
training and I play it and everything's
so [\h__\h] difficult everything that
looks so easy is so
difficult
man anyway ah thank you yukar that's the
story lots of snow everywhere in Europe
it seems yeah for the past one or two
weeks I thought when the first snow fell
that was a onetime
thing the funny thing
is
uh a day before the first snow
fell I
uh oh like I mean not the first maybe
not even the first snow but like the the
first snow that I witnessed since I came
back from Japan I was sitting in Uber
and I was like oh damn it's like really
cold would kind of feels like maybe it
could snow tomorrow and then the Uber
driver was like nah no way n it's not
going to snow until like January
February whatever and I'm like H I guess
or maybe it will be a oneoff snow at
least yeah but then it jinxed
it oh it's more like him who jinxed it
the Uber
driver cuz for me it it got so cold I
thought this is kind of like snow levels
of
cold I'm
Forecastle for
Castle he jinxed it said nah ain't
happening
believe in the forecast CH I am the most
reliable forecast
ever but you know what was really
cute I saw when it was snowing I saw
like one morning I I wake up and I'm
like wakey Wy and then
I normally chunky wonky she's like
always until I actually really get out
of bed she's like always like waiting in
bed with me but this one time I see her
like in uh at the bedroom
window behind the curtains with her tail
and her butt sticking out I'm like oh
what is she looking
at what what's so normally she doesn't
look out the
window what's she like sitting there I'm
like chunky wonky chuny wonky and she
just ignores me I'm trying to get her to
react to me but she just doesn't react
and then I finally get up and I look and
I'm like holy
[\h__\h] there is so much
snow now I understand why she was
looking so
interestedly so cute I I love the
thought of her just looking at the snow
and being fat fascinated by
[Music]
it ever touched
snow not sure if I made her touch it a
little bit before but I don't think
I
[Music]
ever like maybe like I gave her a little
bit of like snow from the what do you
call it window
sill maybe uh but I don't think I like
actually had her walk in snow or
anything like that
before I
think no maybe it did on the balcony
when there was a a little bit of snow
maybe but yeah that's not much H and she
didn't really like it I think I don't
know I'm not sure got to try
again first
time don't know if this the first time
at this point she's already like 5 years
or so so probably happened
before but it's rare it's rare that she
really like sits at the window and
stares outside the only other time when
that happens is like when she notices a
bird and is trying to talk to the bird
like I sound exactly like cats when they
look at
Birds the
twittering She's Always a bird yeah yeah
that's how she looks at
me when allowed to roam free outside and
they carry so much now
inside whole belly full of little
snowballs oh I can
imagine oh I
I I hope I can get my cats to play in
the snow sometime but I wonder when
they're already this
old they might never accept it we'll see
we'll
[Music]
see
well chunky wony definitely has a lot of
fur to protect her from the cold so it
shouldn't be so
[Music]
bad yeah yeah that's exactly what they
sound like when they see
birds like I mean when they're register
registering them as a hunting prey you
know look it up on YouTube there's it's
so cute there's videos of it
hundreds sheel the G thanks for the
pinky MTG heck yeah expensive cardboard
is the best oh this is when I talked
about Pokemon cards with
GMA expensive cardboard yeah I don't
know if you can even call those cards
cardboard because they're still so thin
don't I don't think they qualify as
cardboard just yet something in between
paper and
cardboard I
guess that's why it's called a
card not quite bored just a card card
stuck oh there's an actual word for that
w w w what I never heard that
[Applause]
before you know there's a nice uh uh
cardboard
song that I think every German speaking
person knows and loves
unless maybe not if you're Zoomer
but it's
addicting and it comes from like a
commercial uh I think like an e
economical commercial about paper and
trees and all that and I love it it's so
[Music]
cute
recycling why why did people saying I
never heard it before maybe it's an
Austrian
thing my rmt uh my old roommate she
definitely knew it we we sometimes we
would remember it and jam to
it basically it's like uh
cardboard uh comes from the trees and
trees grow back again through proper
cycling cardboard becomes cardboard
comes from the trees that's where it
repeats and trees grow back again
through proper
recycling cardboard becomes cardboard
comes from the
trees yeah
yeah yeah it Loops so nicely I love the
melody yeah just uh recycle cardboard
and make more cardboard yeah but uh
yeah that's literally what they're
saying yeah for proper recycling you can
make cardboard out of cardboard and gain
cardboard yeah but cardboard is
good because it comes from an I guess a
renewable
source cardboard make cardboard into
cardboard
is so
good nice Jingles jingle bell jingle
bell yog is so my leing yog
[Music]
is
chips yeah yeah we're talking about
yogurt German yogurt
m
[Music]
there's a really good German yogurt that
we seem to connect on in the chat with
the
German it's the bomb yeah sometimes they
have special collaboration
yogurt it's called yogurt with the
corner because in the corner there's
like chocolate balls or depending on the
version of this yogurt there there there
could be chocolate corn flakes and
whatever and you you're like crack it
and then you pour it into the yogurt I
could imagine that they have other
yogurts like this all over the world
where you just like crack it over and
then pour it
[Music]
in the jam you like the jam ones I don't
really like the jam ones so much I
prefer the ones with the crunchy stuff
crunchy
chocolate like Muller cor yeah yeah the
mow ones yeah oh do you guys have the
German brand over there in
America the merer one when I'll show
you you good meat
there oh I'll show you my favorite
ones why are we talking about
yogurt I do not
know okay
so this one really good do you guys have
this in
America maybe at least in the UK you
have it
right oop
see and then I like this one really much
too really much very much cuz this one
has banana
flavor with the chocolate
[Music]
flakes sponsor
me yeah this is fromer they're from
Miller skin
I'm sure yeah something similar must
exist everywhere in the
world wait what is this I've never seen
this
before there's a Mozart cougar yogurt
with the
corner yogurt with the
corner s f syphony m yogurt to stat
pistachio yo the green color and this
like really luxurious
design with chocolate
maripan balls I've never seen this
before
what oh my
God hey
y' that's
crazy oh what they have American New
York style
cookie version of oh my God okay why am
I looking so much at
yogurt okay let's let's let's get out of
here let's let's get out
all now I have to try it I've never seen
them in the shops before
ever H where was I yeah
uh thank you Jesus you got me on a weird
tangent
from cardboard to cart to the
Jingle somehow to the yogurt why did we
get to the yogurt m a dang L and dang ah
because the jingle was apparently also
used for This
Yogurt that's how we got
there try D Evel thank you for the pinky
hey K was bot frag birthday on the 20th
I was wondering if he could get a
special happy birthday from his oi has
become real actual great friend of mine
a and he really deserves it he's a huge
fan thany shanky than
[Music]
shank thany
shanky thank you
shanky oh my God that's like so
[Applause]
American that that was
painful happy belated birthday bottom
frager
congratulations yay let's get older
let's grow all together bottom frer
let's go let's go congratulations hope
you had a lovely birthday sorry I'm a
bit late but I wish you all the best and
much
love you got a free kiss how about that
M I want to be old I mean NE but what
can we do besides holding each other's
hands while getting old
and then and
then rocking in our rocking chairs
H I'm timeless yeah but like let's not
tell them let's not remind them let's
act as if I'm
[Music]
not yeah
Coca-Cola make me
[Music]
burp farming life for
short yeah uh Brandon d g d Rob easy D
oh thank you thank you for the coins can
you stamp St shocking rine thanks for
the pinky greetings T I'm late but
welcome back I hope you get uh you got a
good rest and and feel better now from
your long trip how is small Wawa liking
the Square Enix
Classics I do definitely not see it as a
Square Enix game it's way too
Nintendo but damn it's it's crazy to
think about how after that they left did
their own thing and became such
a
strong different
thing they went in a pretty different
direction
damn it's
like not saying they were held back not
saying that you know what Nintendo is
creating is like worse than what's
Square Enix creates no it's really
different that's the thing but just
makes me think maybe is that is that
really what Square Enix wanted to create
back then were they like made to create
some stuff like that but actually they
were trying to create other
[Music]
things I guess they did definitely want
to do
jrpgs
and that's what they went on to do
afterwards but as you can see Jes are
not quite Nintendo's thing that's why
it's not their main thing it is square
enix's main thing
[Music]
H very interesting there are many
documentaries about Nintendo and Square
Enix it's the more I learn about this
the more it feels like two ex
lovers but every now and then they still
like get back together because of all
the children they made together and and
you know they just do the parent thing
that they got to do they won't you know
like properly be together anymore but
every once in a while you
know
that's really how it is it's so
[Music]
weird it's so
funny Nintendo has Ceno blade Ceno blade
to
Nintendo is
basically it's Nintendo's child that
reminds them so much of their past
relationship with Square Enix that it
even hurts them to look at Cel blade but
it's still their child so they're still
raising
it but it kind of hurts you know they
don't want to admit it they won't tell
it to xblade like you remind me of your
father and that's why I don't like you
that much I don't like you as much as my
other children
like Legend of Zelda or Super
Mario I will not tell you
that but deep down in your heart you
know that's how it is and that won't
ever
change oh it also orig well then I me
yeah that's basically then that makes a
lot of sense though like Nintendo has
custody but looks at that game and feels
like this
is this this this child maybe our child
but it has way more genes
of it it shows like the the structure
the facial the visual structure shows
that it took over rainow jeans of Square
[Music]
Enix
uh it
[Music]
hurts video game fraternity test what
are you talking about I I I what what do
you mean you
understand it has its eyes exactly and
its smile and its
nose sees cooking okay they were on a
break we were not on a
break
DL
KIRO than julan or Julian Vargas than
moral Brandon py Anon m g or than J
thank you for the pinky another
birthday another one reported by someone
else though it's B Bast birthday today
might I request a birthday song from his
talented oi I mean
I'm not going to sing like you know the
the like to the Melody I sang before
because first of all these are pinkies
and I've been doing that for red ones
but also at the same time those take up
a lot of time and I feel bad if I don't
nail it as well so those are
over he's always telling me about how
much he loves you and the community for
brightening his days he's a true loyal
chimpin I know he is b b happy birthday
happy birthday to you Birthday to aisb
oooo happy happy birthday to you B best
B best birthday
oo you're the best k no
you best best best best best B best best
best
best yes best is best best in the
biggest world bir bird B best bird best
best birthday bird bis best happy
birthday free kiss birthday
kiss no
[Music]
you
this music is such a bob
[Music]
[Applause]
now don't talk about
that it's embarrassing Bruce jedy Lee
d space waterfall
D Nathan coton thanks for the pinky this
sounds like kfp needs to do our own part
ah yeah this this Super Chat start
bringing our own tanes to help our Tanto
out you provide so much for us so we
should at least bring like a desert or
something to the Chann yeah like a
casserole or something like that or Mac
and jeans I don't
know but yeah I
thought you guys could bring me tangents
and I can claim them as my own and tell
them on stream as if they're my own and
we'll see we'll see if people believe me
and if
they get good uh
reviews I kind of like the
idea
I
will claim copyright to your
tangents oh we can make it like into
whole game my tangent or your tangent
but you guys know my tangents already so
well and I don't even that's the problem
I don't even have so many tangents left
anymore in my life that I could share
that I could say are new and could be
compared like that so maybe not maybe
not for you guys at least maybe not a
game for you maybe for someone
else
H that was a stream year year one stream
idea did I actually bring this up again
before is that what you're
saying repeat old ones first new viewers
you're not even that new
anymore but then I I don't know I need
to remember what all the things I've
told
before that would be interesting again
to talk about
I remember a few of the big ones but I
feel like there's like so many smallers
small small smaller smaller tangents
scattered in between my old streams that
I don't even remember anymore but they
were
gold thanks for the membership
[Music]
renewal annual tangent
tracking oh yeah I was going to bring up
the scooter right now
that was crazy that was I felt
like I felt like I was in this crazy
adventure doing illegal stuff driving
that scooter over a mountain out of its
[Laughter]
range so funny I remember didn't I tell
this during Wind Waker the story I did I
remember I was in the water
dungeon
[Music]
good times is this a dream you had no it
was
reality I used one of those electric
scooters to get somewhere to an
important um thing
and I used Google Maps but apparently I
used a route that was supposed to be on
foot and it led me into a really really
muddy uh
hill side but it was really difficult to
get through but I kind of committed cuz
I was already in
there and then I got the scooter really
really messy and
dirty and also it went out of the like
range where it's allowed to be
at yeah there's a there's a clip about
it and holy B ping ping D ping I
did you stop clipping me because you're
now like being paid to clip sh ODI full
time is that what's
[Music]
[Applause]
happening I feel like that happened
before many such
cases
H at least he stayed in Hollow yeah I
guess yeah certain someone went to
n
man my all my resident Clippers
[Music]
man I have I legit have PTSD I legit
have PTSD from like creators like you
know going
elsewhere should i p him first well I
mean I did pay him
occasionally
right I did not for everything but like
sometimes for my own projects I I
occasionally offered
money but I guess she only like
permanently hired him like just always
do uh stuff for me I guess maybe that's
the the kind of deal they have
[Music]
going yeah I mean you
know I thought I
thought whatever I don't
care I just really liked his clips and
now I don't get these anymore you know
there was a certain pudding
charm this like
cursed absolute
cursedness
[Music]
H I still clip you when I have time
thank you maybe I should poach you from
cie since cie poached chy From
Me Maybe I should poach Elsie
Lain poaching
[Music]
battle EXT
changing exchange
student oh
[Music]
man it's okay I don't
[Applause]
care Holo poach
Wars It's a jerk not going to do that of
course
not no c car Stay Stay Stay
Stay I don't need
you yeah CI has been blasting out the
shorts
like I I think she's like really focused
on shorts right
now so I guess she banned
skirts huh I don't know
[Music]
man
seems like she has a problem with skirts
boo boo boo
you as shorts team is stack I've noticed
like they they're all different styles
and all
[Music]
that oh they're funny though I like
them those CU those are just Industrial
rather than focusing on one
[Music]
oi W awake past it's
[Applause]
bye and in sorry i'm Cinderella I'm I'm
turning into a pumpkin now
[Music]
bye you can't see me as a
pumpkin oh tomorrow Super Mario right
yeah just to make it
[Music]
clear I'll end Advent calendar in 1
hour
[Music]
oh thanks for the
reminder thank
you thank
[Music]
you
I will do it now now now
[Music]
now
oh let's
go thank
you