[Music]
do
so
[Music]
my dear
okay all right
let's do this
oh hello everybody
hello
oh my
there are so many visitors
[Music]
oh my
oh i don't know
what to do
all right all right now calm down
otherwise i'm not gonna show myself
press the button which button are you
talking about
i'm pressing all the buttons
all right all right
okay are you are you quite ready
[Music]
finally my age matches the subscribe
excuse me
how proud of you
when you hear me don't you
yes okay
[Music]
come here
come on over
but don't be surprised we haven't seen
each other in a while and
i am i am a bit self-conscious about my
looks nowadays so don't
don't you know
don't give me any weird looks or
be respectful okay
i've gone through many many things over
the past
many many years
okay be respectful
[Music]
okay
ah
let me sit down comfortably come on
smoothie jonkers come on to my lap
mouth
okay
all right
all right here we go
comfy
[Music]
oh well
isn't this lovely
hello everybody
nice to see you again
haven't seen you in such a long long
time i missed you
hello
oh yeah that's right i used to say
something back in the day i remember
do you guys remember
[Music]
i still got it after all these years i
still got it
after all these years
i still have it in me
yes
yeah my smile of course has never
changed
welcome everybody
it's been a long time
i've missed you
i've missed you a little bit but you
guys are
very noisy today oh dear haven't had so
much trouble before like a long long
long time
anyway you you came here
for
whatever reason i don't really know
why you came here
but alright
while you're here
i'll tell you
a few stories because you know
we haven't seen each other in a while
yes
who are you guys anyway
i are you from uh
from kfp
i thought
i thought that kfp
after
after i gave my ceo position to someone
else
eventually
was taken down because of all these
problems that have come up totally after
after i've left this uh tax fraud and
and uh
abuse of chickens and poisoning of
customers
but that all happened
after i've given my position to someone
else but what do i see you guys still
call yourselves kfb
[Music]
oh that's wonderful
that's wonderful
oh you seem to be proud of what you have
done in your past that is beautiful
well yes all of that is pish-posh
indeed
indeed oh well okay if you are all from
kfp then i would like to welcome you
guys
here have some have some of grandma's uh
grand monkey baba's best cookies here
take them
here i'll make them small for you
there you go
oh wait oh dear mom
yes
i'll eat them all up because
oh i've got plenty i think oh i'm not
sure
did i really bake enough cookies for all
of you
well i
for now you must share okay sharing is
caring they like to say that even
nowadays
oh well anyway maybe there are some new
people who don't actually know me so oh
i i all forgot who i am so let me
introduce myself
yes
my name is uh
but nowadays people like to call me
kibaba
yes well you go ahead and call me
whatever the hell you want okay
as long as you are being respectful
that is very important
yeah younglings these days
they always forget to be respectful
it is quite sad you know to look at that
you like the cookies oh that's wonderful
all right yes so yes and uh
how old i am
are you seriously asking that
you shouldn't be asking something like
that to a
lady
well let's just say
i am still a phoenix and
well while
while i age
a little bit slower than you humans do
i do
eventually
um
uh come to this point where i look like
this
but then eventually
i will go up in flames and i will be
reborn and i will look just like i did
in the old days
yes
yes i will look
wonderful and charming and fresh again
i mean
i
i oops upset
all the technical things i forgot how to
use them
you
you won't be mad at me today if i make
some problem mistakes uh
in terms of the technicalities
right are they they used to call it back
in my days they used to call it the
whole live english curse
yes oh apparently there was a curse
casted upon us i don't i still up until
this day i don't know who did that
but anyway
apparently it's still following me
yeah the e and curse
they called it that
oh that to be honest i always said back
then
this is tonebook
this is so unhomebook
no but
it seems to be true after all
i mean after all these years
it's still following me so there must be
something behind it
anyway anyway so yes so don't ask about
my age all right
yes good
uh um what else i only told you my name
and my
age
what else do you need to know oh yeah
maybe it is important to mention
that
back in
the good old glorious golden days of the
2020s
yes
remember in those times
during those times i was part of this
sometimes they like to call them idols
but i would say it was just a talent
agency for streamers
yes and it was called
hollow live
oh low live
yes i joined that company
and that's when i got to know most of
you
it's a
yeah entertainment agency
unfortunately
it's been about
3 000 years
and uh
it doesn't seem to exist anymore
i don't know what happened
that is so for you to decide there are
some conspiracy theories out there
that uh
um it has been taken over
by some secret secret
people who have like one eye and a
triangle as their logo
oh but i don't wanna talk too much about
that because um previously when i talked
about it
they came to my door
and they yelled at me and i
you know i i live here alone with my
cats and i was pretty scared
oh yes that was a terrifying situation
oh
so you guys better not think too much
deeply about what happened don't don't
question it or i have to be worried
about you guys too
yeah
so anyway
ah
oh yeah where was i where was i
let me collect my thoughts oh
i
oh
all right wait i didn't give you guys
cookies yet let me give you some cookies
here you cute cute beloved chickens
you look very hungry you forgot i forgot
i forgot to give you some cookies here
there you go
yeah you must eat
you must eat
yeah you look so thin have you not been
eating properly
you take all these cookies but make sure
to share them i'm not sure if i have
enough of them for all of you
yes
go on go on and eat my dear younglings
yeah all right
all right that is a grandma kibaba's
secret recipe which
yes it is totally my secret recipe i did
not steal that at all no no no no no i
did not take that from that hotel
there is no absolutely no evidence of
that whatsoever
is my my original cookies you don't
believe me
[Music]
what what do you mean archives
what no no no i don't remember such a
thing and that is impossible
that is my original recipe
yes chocolate chip cookies chunky very
big ones yes beautiful anyway oh where
was i where was i oh yes i was talking
about
uh uh my time
in hololive
unfortunately that company doesn't exist
anymore but don't ask me why it's a
dangerous topic
um
oh yeah
oh i was in this group called hollow lie
of english myth
and we were actually the first ones the
first english-speaking
girls in the company yes it was quite an
outrage or
it was just a legendary legendary
happening back then yes back in my days
yes it was we were pretty big i must say
i mean
we did not expect it back then
but yes we ended up being all quite
successful i must say
that's probably why you all guys know me
um
so
yes we consisted of
let me tell you about these girls five
five girls including me
yes
um
yeah i mean
uh okay
baba nowadays
and uh
besides that there was a
a girl called
ninomaya inanis
and
amelia watson
gouda
and indeed clio p rory
[Music]
yes those were the girls that i shared
so just all of this with
oh
oh my favorite memory of my time in
whole life
um
let me try to think
to be honest i think it was probably
that time when we first met in japan
finally
after waiting so long for it
yes
we had a great time at karaoke
we sang a lot of songs together and cut
out
and watching movies before going to
sleep in the cute pajamas
yes we had oak we bought cute matching
pajamas
actually
that was my idea
nowadays that pajama has been eaten up
by moths so i don't
i can't wear it anymore it's all holes
nowadays
absolutely ruined
but i still have it in the back of my
closet in the the
uh in my underground storage system yes
maybe i should fix it one day
oh guys you look so hungry may i offer
you some cookies you look so hungry
little chickens i've totally forgot to
give you some oh cookies there you go
now eat up my dears
my lovely younglings oh i wish i was as
young as you
oh but i'll get back to that when i am
revived so in the end it doesn't even
matter
that was a good song for back in the
days yes um
so yeah um yeah and we went to shopping
and took cute booty cuda and all that
kind of stuff but what what was even
greater than our first time meeting
in uh
in japan
was um a concert
a myth only
concert
years years no not years it felt like
years so you know it felt like a journey
of a thousand years honestly oh but yes
we had a concert for myth only
eventually
yeah
do you guys remember that
i remember like it was just yesterday
we had these lovely charming idol
outfits on
i couldn't wear that anymore today oh
yes um
well i wish i could but nowadays
i think it wouldn't quite suit me so
well anymore what do you guys think do
you think i would still suit that cute
idol outfit
[Music]
i wonder
maybe i should try it on again
ah and baby go on stage again oh well
anyway we all um we all performed duets
and solo songs of course uh because at
that time i already had my first solo
album out there
yes it was a big success actually i
remember
i remember it very well
my first album
yes it had a
9 or 10 tracks in it
um and i also eventually had my own solo
concert in 3d yes
but that's a long time ago
but yes so
when we perform together i would say
that's the concert that was my favorite
memory and perhaps our biggest bonding
experience
oh
bonkers [\h__\h] get off the
table no monkeys
oh dear wait a second wait a second
one guys
it's my new cat one second
no that fake is for ela later no it's
bad for you to eat
[Music]
yes i i have um i have another house
uh close by where i keep 231
cats and after after this session i have
to go and pick up five more cats um i
cannot keep all of them in here because
they don't get along but i have a
smoothie and chalkers on my lap as you
can see by phoenix cats they live
forever just like me
and bonkers is running around in the
kitchen and bought his things i cannot
hear
what it is doing over there but i know i
can even smell it the moment it sets its
paws on top of that kitchen table i used
to allow it but
i cannot allow it anymore bonkers likes
to eat the
the cakes and whatever i prepare i i
like to get up at 4am these days i all
back in the days i used to oh i used to
stay awake until 4am
isn't that unbelievable
i can't do that anymore no no nowadays i
get up at 4am and then i bake some
cookies and some cakes and um yes i
prepared some other things maybe i'll
tell you about that but oh
oh dear oh dear
i'm
tangenting off again excuse me
where was i
oh yeah i wish i wish we could do it
again
the concert and all that
yeah
oh
i'll never bite actually
i think
i think i forgot something important
more important than that
you have some cookies my dear chickens
you look so hungry i forgot i am so rude
that is so rude of me
that i did not offer you any cookies
i apologize deeply
oh my dear i made so many for you and
then i forgot to give you the cookies
how rude of me
oh oh yeah i was i was talking about uh
how i wake up so early in the morning
and then i prepare so many things well
one of the things that i do
is i i cook some um extra lunch dinner
for uh ina
yes you know why
because inna actually
she lives uh
almost like next doors yes either
she um she moved out of her
parents home long long long time ago and
then she tried living on her own but uh
she
she thought she was okay but i told her
ina this is not a good life that you're
living when you always sleep on the
floor because you fall asleep
and then and then you only eat those cup
noodles unbelievable no no no so what
did i do i
see this is a picture i took a picture
of her just this morning
just this morning i took a picture of
her
in her nowadays
natural habited
see her lying on the floor there
yeah
unbelievable she's still drawing to this
day
she picked up violin as well she was a
bit bored after whole life was taken
down by the shh
better not say it okay
oh but so i go there and i i look
through her fridge and hold her storage
in the check that she didn't advise
those cup those goddamn cop noodles
again
and then i'd bring her some hot soup and
some lunch and some dinner so that she
kinda you know have some proper
nutrition
of course i also bring her my world
famous cookies do you guys know about my
world famous cookies
she really likes those but sometimes she
complains that i'm bringing her too many
and i'm like there's never enough
cookies here let me give you some of my
world famous cookies
i think i didn't tell you about those
cookies yet let me give them to you here
there you go
oh they are so
yummy i actually won an award for my
world famous cookies
but then they
after i won the war they took it away
from me a few months later claiming that
it was not even my own recipe i tell you
those people they have no respect for
the aged ones
no respect this is my original recipe i
worked very hard on it
i want my award back
i want my god damn i'm a ward back
unbelievable they treat this lady
so badly oh well anyway so this is
either yes yes a photo of ina on the
floor
but at least i am feeding her well it's
basically like i am her caretaker
nowadays yes
she needs someone to take care of her
[Music]
well the live stream is just
probably going to uh
die on the floor if i if it wasn't for
me
oh oh
only i remember you is that really you i
can't believe my eyes
my back oh
oh don't even ask about my back
please don't ask about it i just just
yesterday
oh i went to the doctors again
it was
really really exhausting because i threw
my back out yes
and but that happens literally every
week
and know what i take care of eno but no
one takes care of me and my back
but it's okay i have my cats after all
so anyway ollie you should come by uh
one day i i
i miss the way we played
back in the day
we had some fun when we played monopoly
you do you remember when we played
monopoly and i won
[Laughter]
the good old times i remember like it
was just uh
a week away or something like that
coming soon tm oh anyway yes a lovely
memory where did she go where did that
girl go
i saw her but my eyes are not as fast
anymore as they used to be where did she
go
where did she go
ollie my dear where did you go come on
these girls eat
no one listens to me anymore nowadays
back in the days they listened to me for
hours and hours and hours i was actually
in whole life english i used to always
be the one with the longest streaming
hours
yeah i'm quite proud of that
oh anyway do you wonder what the other
girls have been up to
i am
i don't besides ena i don't have that
much contact with all of them anymore
but i do check up on them every once in
a while
yes
who who would you like to hear about
besides eda so you already know what
happened with eda she's close by don't
worry i'm taking care of her
i'm sure sure so the thing with ahmed is
last time i met her she's been quite
busy
she actually after after um close to the
end before hollow life was taken down
she was actually part of the management
um
she was part of the management and she
was she was uh bringing a whole alive to
a completely new
sparkle and beauty and uh yes she
actually really changed up a lot of
things and um
yeah gave it some refresher that it
really desperately needed yeah i was
very very proud of her
but then it got taken down and ahmed was
like oh she had nothing to do she was
bored so she went back uh uh to what she
used to do before her whole life and she
started to time traveling again honestly
it really messes with her skin
but um she brings me fun souvenirs so
that's okay with me the other day she
brought me um a present it was a alien
baby cat kitten
yes look at her go
this is her she has actually a whole
group of ufos and people she travels
with sometimes
and um
yes she brings me presents for that that
baby uh alien kitten was indeed she sat
from mars
so i tried putting that cat together
with all my other cats
in that other house
but the alien cat started eating
trying to eat my other cats
so
i put her into a pot and made some yummy
stew out of that cat
it was pretty yummy i fed it to ena
she didn't know what was in it but
she said it was really yummy and it
tasted like a
beef it was like a beef stew
yes
so i told admire
thank you
but
no more
no more i said all those aliens they are
quite troublesome but they've been
trying to take over the world but
they've been so far failing
because we try we hold on if we still
try to
help the world a little bit with our
powers
that of course council
council is trying as well but um they
whatever i oh dear
let's just say situation with them the
other day so i i don't really want to
talk about them right now
these younglings i'm telling you and
they think they think they have all the
control and they can mess around with
the world but however they want they
kind of have started
some kind of evil
evil evil
um propaganda yes
the thing is with council that they have
kind of turned against us
you thought that they would be with us
but they are now against us
yes yes
they had too much power i told i told
omega
and back in the day
council is just too powerful you cannot
give someone so much power and accept
them to only do good
because that is just unrealistic
expectations yes
oh big alpha i forgot the name i haven't
heard from dead
youngling in a long long long time even
when i was still in myth active i
haven't i have barely heard anything
from that
whatever that is
is not a person i don't know what that
was i haven't heard anything for so long
so i forgot the name almost oh [\h__\h]
forgive me
let me drink some water
[Music]
oh wonderful
all right so that is zombie for you she
is still very active and happy and
brings me presents and souvenirs in
exchange for cookies as well everybody
wants my world famous cookies of course
oh and then and then and then there is
gouda
do you want to know what gouda has been
up to
actually i am quite proud of gouda
you know when oh back in myth how old
was she
nine thousand years old or what was it
but she looked like a child didn't she
yes well actually nowadays
um she has aged
properly
yes
finally she has aged properly and looks
like an adult and oh oh yes she actually
became the president of atlantis
yes it is now also way more fitting with
her adult looks i mean she still looks a
little bit too young in her face but
that's just the
other shark dna in her
body
yes so she oh she ditched her hat i i
took it away from her and then burnt it
because i was like
good
your hat is so
stinky
we need to get rid of that and now make
something proper out of yourself
so yes she became the president of
atlantis isn't that amazing but that
means she has been so busy that she has
never been calling me anymore or
visiting me
unbelievable
yes it's like she forgot about me
completely
she forgot about me completely
i thought that we had something special
i mean
we do
but she doesn't come by anymore she says
i talk too much and she does not have
the time for it she must do whatever in
atlanta is controlled the fish and the
shrimps and i don't know what all of
that means that she marriabies yeah
these younglings
she is very very busy but okay
you know i still love her i forgive her
uh
i must invite her to come by again
i will tell her that i have some of my
world famous cookies and then she'll
probably come right i'm sure of it
but i am so proud of her look at her
this is this was a picture of her uh
inauguration
i took a picture i was in the front row
and i was like oh good eyes girl
i was so proud of her i'd always i
always knew she was smart people said
she wasn't smart but
that was all just
these kids you know they were so mean to
her sometimes you did not deserve such
treatment
she was very smart and i think she
proved everybody wrong by becoming the
the president of atlantis
[Music]
yes so anyway that was good
and then uh last but not least
let me tell you what cali has been up to
now this one is actually perhaps pretty
pretty surprising because she did a 180
or 360 or whatever you younglings like
to say
and back in my days if you remember
oh
callie she was uh
she was a reaper
dressed in black and uh
yes she was very fond of the underworld
and all that she is kind of edgy
um but but nowadays she did a 360 or a
1080 or 30 60 or whatever
and uh
she ditched hell and underground and
instead became an angel in heaven to
greet the people in heaven instead of
the hell yeah she even has that halo and
the cute little angel wings and all that
yes
she said it's really refreshing up there
the air is really really good and i
think that all of this matches and suits
uh
complements her skin tone and her hair
perfectly
yes i always thought you know she looked
pretty uh drop dead gorgeous dead
in her black clothes back then but she
was always so edgy you know
always so edgy
nowadays she has completely changed i
honestly don't know what went through
her head
um but she said that
after whole life was taken down
she needed to
you know she said it was like a breakup
and she needed some change on her life
and she said that it opened her eyes
and
she didn't want to see all these people
in hell anymore not around if you wanted
to uh see what kind of people
go to heaven
yes
oh did you know
did you know that um
who was it again
uh that uh
that actor
who uh
who voiced so many characters
what was his name again that famous
actor
oh
no not adam sandler chris pratt yes but
adam sandler as well they both went to
heaven
yago
oh yago
he is somewhere in between like one day
he is in heaven and one day he is in
hell i don't know what's going on there
there might be a glitch in the matrix as
they used to say
oh do you guys remember that the movie
matrix
yes it's very very old
very old yeah yeah maybe he is uh
looking for someone but
that is
another story for another day to tell
genma
oh don't worry about genma
because i gave her one of my uh
phoenix feathers to keep her alive
forever
yes i will never let her go
i love my genma
she was
she was gonna go to heaven obviously but
i could not let that happen because she
is just
too precious and i cannot live without
her
[Music]
so yeah that was kelly
uh she's very oopsy dammit she was she's
very
busy
sorry technical difficulties she's very
busy up there in heaven so
um i
just like gouda
we don't talk that much anymore but
sometimes i just hear some voices
some voices in my head and it's like
echoing and it's like
kibaba
what you up to
yo
and i'm like is that you callie can't
you use a goddamn phone it's creeping me
out when you talk to me like that from
heaven okay
just use a goddamn phone it makes me go
crazy i'm like i'm losing my mind i have
reached a certain age you know and stuff
like that it's just i cannot keep it
apart anymore if it is voices in my head
or if it is cali
it is just all mixing up in my head
but if if if there is uh some edgy
language involved then it's probably
cali that's how i like to uh
make
the
seed
decide which one it is
yes anyway so that's kelly cute little
angel she has become don't you think
she looks so cute i actually
i s so soon sold i made that dress for
her
yes i haven't spoken english in a long
time so forget forgive me for making
some mistakes you guys are also making
me a little bit nervous
yes but that dress i made it for her
because you know why
before she was wearing a way more
revealing dress
at the moment people
would die and go to heaven and were
greeted by kawaii maury with those boing
boings
they were going crazy and immediately
catapulted to hell for how they were
looking at callie's boing boings and i
said you can't do your job like that
everybody will be catapulted to hell
once they see you for
for sinning by looking at your boing
boing so i made her a dress that covers
up her
more voluptuous areas properly
as it should be in heaven
yes
i do
you have to be respectful
so yeah that was the myth girls they're
all still alive and doing fine
but i kind of missed the time when we
were on stage together
and
oh oh yeah there was this one time in
our concert where we sang a slow
arranged version of journey of a
thousand years on stage and
i think not only us but all of the
audience was crying
i suddenly feel like singing that song
again
i don't have the arranged version but
i have did the original version
oh let's see if i can still do it
one second
oh yeah
do i remember the lyrics i wonder
oh i will try
okay
let's see if you guys hear this i hope
you do one second
take off and fly the longer we wait the
longer it makes us as we fight every
fate
strength to finally defeat this journey
a thousand years to meet
hey
yeah
is it okay
i barely hear things nowadays i hear
nothing
a song in snow enchanted by rhyme
painted in wishes granted by time our
longest hopes connecting yet those feel
like echoes of ages goodbye
obey the splash but found of that free a
fish out of water about to the sea then
a reckless high tide brought you right
by my side i bet this moment's a wave we
could ride
connecting songs across the sky
let's go take off and fly the longer we
wait the stronger it makes us as we find
every fight strength to find little feet
this journey a thousand years to me here
comes my part yeah
witness to fire in our minds burning
inside rising again from the ashes yo
every bruise and he scratches makes us
feel more alive but never give up never
give it no matter what's ahead it's that
will crush your worries aside
the world for us to touch or to see
we'll make it ourselves and make
memories
there ain't a mystery our brains cannot
solve
we just shine brighter grow tight or
evolve
the longer we wait the stronger it makes
us as we fight every phase strength to
finally defeat this journey a thousand
years to meet
[Music]
at the end of this world war is a
fighting chance
nothing's changing it's always the same
story stage with a different dance
seek out a happy end for me and my
friends and those who loved us up till
now
i wanna see your smile
find my way to you
somehow
take off and fly the longer we wait the
stronger it makes us says we find
everywhere
[Music]
strength is all that we'll need i won't
wait a thousand here's to me
come visit me
[Music]
my precious ones
oh
[Music]
yes that reminded me of the good old
times very much
huh you remember that song guys
i still
i still got it don't i though
it may have been a little bit emotional
but i think i still got it after all
these years
oh technical difficulties there we go
[Music]
all right
well you know what
this was so wonderful i feel so
revitalized just by singing that
maybe
maybe i'll call ami
to bring us back to the old times
i do miss it
maybe she can use her
time traveling thingy
that she still has
under control
to bring me back to the old times i
really miss it
all right let's
let's give it a try people people people
people people people
oh hello
mrs what said you stinky cutie pie
ah oh no no no this is not about dinner
tomorrow
no no ah the dinner party is still
happening but i was thinking you could
uh
you could maybe bring me
to the year
2021 were 22 because
yes yes
what do you mean you just brought me
there
yesterday on the day trip
no no no no
that's impossible
no i haven't been there in a long time
oh that is nonsense just bring me to
2022 for god's sake i want to go back
and meet my beautiful kfb chickens and
the empire that i have built with my kfb
and then i want to be on stage with you
guys again in 3d is that too much to ask
garmin just don't make it so complicated
yes
okay
you pick me up right and uh yes give me
some time i will give my kitty cats some
extra food or is it okay to bring them
yes i know i know i know they're very
hairy but
come on it's very fluffy
you know how it is with pets
you know what you used to wear to aren't
you
yes come on let me bring my cats it
would save me
no no no no not all 200 fruity whatever
of them
just smoothie chunkers and bonkers okay
yes the rest of i have a caretaker
called the needle bye that as you know
yes okay then i'll see you in about 10
minutes later and then you'll bring me
there in the good old days and yes
okay sounds good to me thank you very
much my dear how about how do you do it
how do you not age
i thought you were the only human among
us
oh yes yes okay okay i was just trying
to have a little bit of a conversation
but
i understand okay okay
all right i will be quiet now i'll just
sit here quietly and wait for you dead
yay but please hurry up okay i am really
really uh
missing those times i had a few lovely
guests at my house and
yes okay okay okay
no it's not those that i was not going
on a tangent amelia
oh
all right i'm waiting for you
all right goodbye
all right
all right guys uh then
thank you for coming
um
i i i
i i i'm gonna leave you guys i don't i
don't care what you guys are going to do
just leave my house properly and don't
leave anything here okay
take care of your belongings
thank you very much for watching it was
so nice to see you guys again to be
honest i
i really missed you but i'll see the uh
past version of you i suppose in a few
minutes
all right then um thank you for coming
by don't forget to tell people about my
world famous uh cookies
critically acclaimed cookies there is
some cookies uh in in a gift uh bag for
all of you guys next to the entrance
door so when you leave please take a bag
of my world famous critically acclaimed
award-winning cookies and then share it
with your friends and tell them about
takanashikiyada also known as
takadashikibaba
okay
also thank you to also the overseas
guests
i never ended up mastering korean
well anyway
and uh what was it again
i think we used to say back in my days
we used to say uh and in german we say
of
vedazine
yes yes is that right
i think yes that was what we used to say
haven't heard that in a while but oh
it's beautiful to see all of you
repeated again you like little parrots
even though you're chickens
you act like parrots it's really funny
oh thank you thank you thank you i am
gonna go now and meet ame and meet the
old versions of the girls
or the young versions whatever it is
it's kind of confusing it's like a
schrodinger's cat
oh thank you well then auf wiedersehen
indeed scottish somebody goes on
oh
oh wait uh one more thing i didn't say
it yet because i wanted to um
uh wait until the proper reveal
um but i want to give proper thank you i
said i had no one to take care of me
nowadays but
actually um there is this this uh
person this cute person who comes to my
house
and does my makeup
um to make me look
pretty
and this person did my makeup
let me show
you who was in charge of
uh the way i look today
am i not looking fabulous
yes this person is really charming
so here there it is
thank you very much
um i suppose i think i remember you
speak korean don't you come sanita for
doing my makeup today
donkey shirt indeed
you did such a great job oh please
everybody follow them on twitter
yes they still use twitter instagram has
been taken down
um and all those other stupid services
like snapchat and tick tock i never
understood those
but twitter is still striving and being
strong as ever i told you but you know
why that is it is only because kfp
eventually took over twitter and turned
that blue stupid burp into an orange
smart burb yes
if you look at the logo from twitter now
you will see it's been taken over by an
orange burb called kotoli
yes that's but that is by the way by the
way where kotori went
now managing twitter and that is the
only reason why twitter still exists to
be honest without us
it would have been lost forever just
like tick tock and snapchat and all
those stupid services
yes
alright anyway goodbye everybody thank
you very much uh i'll see you in the
past or the future or whatever it is
thank you sure end of vid thank you
thank you don't forget those cookies
alright i made them with love
goodbye
[Music]
you