foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
this is
foreign
thank you
Kitty
uh
I'm in come here
uh hello hi you have to go there oh my
God
[Laughter]
oh man here I can
um can you read the Jazz oh it's very
small but if I go in there
well guys
um so we we tried but uh
it's it's
too many things running on one left of
we are out of ram please donate us more
RAM
um uh everything's lagging and it was
impossible to get Emma to work I mean
look at her she's yellow she's a person
she's totally amazing
she knows she already had a fine body
I'm a skeleton I I I was so happy when I
saw her I was so excited that when I
hugged her I accidentally scratched off
like all of her skin and clothes
oh I think my my movement is mirrored so
I'm pointing at her
um yeah sorry guys
um you know I mean
yes uh so what happened is uh I'm not
using my my PC right now and I thought
maybe my laptop could handle running
um like six or eight programs but the my
laptop CPU is not that great and I have
a 1060 and like 16 gigs of RAM which is
good but not enough
TV
oh my God what has time traveling though
nice hips new average yeah it's just one
of your many different animals
I mistakes
it's just another
sorry guys for kind of um ClickBank but
doesn't she look so nice look at me oh
wow yeah I mean don't have a finger
tracking right now but besides that
besides that
um
my skirt physics uh sometimes yeah bye
but besides that all good ah
[Laughter]
I'm a very
it's collect them oh yeah
um the the switch might also possibly be
lagging guys
um let's see
right now
we're gonna play for the OBS screen
we're gonna play Nintendo switch Sports
um
good luck to us
this must be what the oh wait did I
did I I may have
um
chat delay on very very strong again or
or it's just you know the laptop like
I'm just gonna close that out window and
make the other one bigger if that's okay
okay but uh you know this this one we're
not using it for anything yeah okay
okay
[Laughter]
oh yeah an OBS it's also
uh it loads like a twitch chat to us
I've noticed on Twitch and everything's
like
coming in like little brackets anyway
how am I looking guys I mean I'm still
honestly if it weren't for the lag
everything here is pretty cool you know
it's like a pretty professional yeah and
I'm gonna put the trackers on me with no
issues
everything's sticking nicely
and looking nicely mostly yeah
and you could have had
um you guys know the the song uh what
was it
[Music]
that one or get done no wait that's a
song Yes you know that song that's
basically what I was doing
when we had her in her OG body she was
making like really fast
movements okay all right she was out of
control yes somebody was messed up I
know what it was but I can't fix it
right now but we're here and
um we're gonna we're gonna do a better
one tomorrow right yeah I mean tomorrow
you'll be a puppet but that's an upgrade
from this you'll be a different puppet
you look like
um like this like wooden puppet that I
used
um oh the art school yeah yeah the
figure drawing one yeah can you do like
a nice pose and I'll draw you like a
French wooden puppet
wow wow she looks so beautiful oh yes
hmm
you have YouTube app on this uh
uh yeah he's not gonna play Ed we'll
just leave it I've never used a thing
before okay
um you can kind of see the chat right
it's a little small on the screen I'll
have to squint but if I come here then I
see it
have you shown it before yeah oh oh hold
on
well oh wait before I get started yeah
yeah I saw Papa
his new haircut Bubba's new cut it's
fresh right it's definitely
um fresh and and I I can see that it was
self-made
I I cut my own hair a lot do you cut
your own sometimes because like you
can't just you know straight because
when I when I cut my bangs you can't
just like cut straight you know you have
to like cut upwards you know like that
and I would I would think like with dogs
it's like more or less the same but yeah
and then I tried to give him some more
pets
um I tried I tried what do you think was
it yeah he likes you he's always liked
you
in me though cause and they have a boy
in the dogs I guess they're a little
scared they're they're still scared yeah
this is where are you
[Music]
on you one day oh my God
maybe if I if I think about it really
hard I can put a tracker on one of them
yeah
yeah I'll bring my cats over too and
will the cat
um off collab all the encants can't play
date vocab cat play date
okay yeah I'm besides that
cause you guys told me that I miss you
bring me to Mexican place I may had me
eat some Mexican food yeah
uh I ate boyo not Polo
I never had it before either and uh it
was it was good it was I think it did
have chocolate in it I'm tasting only
the mole was meh but when mixed with the
other things like because I made like a
little burrito style thing that was good
that was
that was pretty good yeah if you guys
don't know what mole is I think it's
just like a sauce with a chili stuff and
nuts and seeds and chocolate and other
stuff and it's like a thick dark sauce
that uh you eat with chicken or I guess
other stuff I don't know uh and with
rice and the mashed beans that you told
me about oh yeah refried beans it's like
mashed potatoes
and some salad and and and and the
tortilla and yes
but it was getting really messy
but that's good though it was good it
was good it was good and I had to drink
apparently uh Mexican drink what was it
called I called it Doritos but that's
not how you say and you today even
flexed at me again that you can speak
Spanish
sounds really cool but I guess
it was good that was yummy I want to
drink another one actually I placed it
somewhere I forgot about it
oh it's in my living room dry pozole
oh I think it's like a stew with beans
like garbanzo beans I was actually
surprised it wasn't a spicy because I
thought oh my God okay
it wasn't so spicy actually I thought
everything would be spicy but I just
ordered something random and it wasn't
spicy very good what did you have and
enchilada enchilada
yeah it was good yummy yeah okay okay
okay
let's try to play this game I've never
played it before you never played this
yeah really no oh I was waiting for a
collab partner to play this with me but
you played it before did you yeah I've
played it before but it was mad life 2G
yes it was a lot today that's true this
is Frankie
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
our emotions are a little bit delayed by
the way guys mine's I think yours is
kind of okay yeah it's like a little
yeah yours is worse
okay let's try to sync up maybe we can
see how wait
oh let me know
oh beautiful but wait before we start is
there anything wrong I'll check I'll
pull up the chat is there anything wrong
with the stream right now besides me
look at this lens everything
uh sticks in
uh
[Music]
uh me esposaame
what's Esposa
uh I'm gonna do too much time lunch
this is what happens
okay
so at least you have a name tag above
your head I don't have that how would
people know who I am that's true man
because I'm not blocking anything here I
will see I guess
play online one to two players let's go
let's go go let's go well okay
here we go by the way tomorrow we'll
stream also a 3D stream but it should
lag less because yeah we'll fix it even
if I have to move my computer I usually
don't like moving it but I don't mind
we'll fix it okay I have a little
is this
uh oh should I hold it like this
we're all
right let me look again I'm confused if
I was Globe oh yeah look local local
look I'm local
[Laughter]
oh man
who are
okay so we have some games when we have
we have volleyball badminton bowling
golf football
chamberra Canberra what 10 a sword
fighting one oh okay we'll play all of
them oh all of them okay yes
she have to make use of this we are two
players and the sport is played with one
controller run oh yeah one each right
one reconfiguring The Joint concrete
okay couldn't reconfigure it please
but uh lrr press L or R
okay I did first huh
okay slagging player one huh no you
didn't they tried that before and it
didn't work but okay try again is it
because you're not
um they're updating only the controllers
is it because it you gotta be connected
to Wi-Fi or something
it was wasn't it it was I think it was
maybe all right because otherwise it
wouldn't be doing this right now
connected
it's nice yeah it's working I think I
think the controllers work via Bluetooth
anyways I'm ready to see my tweet about
arriving in America
I think so when I wrote I have arrived
in the connected lens yeah why'd you say
that okay why did you say it like that I
wanted to
um rename
the USA because it's like connected
United you know land States it's just
synonyms I was just using synonyms I
honestly had no idea what you meant when
you said that
yeah you guys understood it right that I
was just trying to be funny I was making
a joke
oh my controller vibrated
let's go
oh okay press select player one ah we
have to use the
the the profiles no ah never mind what
no no we have to quickly make a
character random random and you're
standing in the character I am the
character oh okay you're gonna do it
really quickly
um or uh let's uh hair no wait this this
eye
I feel like I'm making an animal
crossing character it looks like it
uh this do we have to make yours too
why I think you could just give me a
guess one I'm so pretty yeah
well okay I browse I don't give a [\h__\h]
about the eyebrows here give me these
fix them anyways oh
I'll probably never play this again
anyway no what's a good collab game oh
wait is that it where's the what do I do
okay
how did I finish it
am I in the way
what do I press
earned okay
okay but okay it's just like selecting
things
Where'd I go
guys what do I push I've been getting
his squats and she's gonna be a
squatting I don't know if I'm blocking
something she's like a frog Emma has a
frog no I heard a frog for like a while
I guess not when you were here last time
probably wait I saw it it's cute but
it's too thin it needs to eat more yeah
it's probably just that kind of wait
maybe B oh and this B
uh look that's those clothes look so
lame I want to be orange wow
what the [\h__\h] you have to earn them
don't you think if I wouldn't have
earned it wouldn't I I wouldn't be
wearing two hats right now maybe if you
went in a duel against me oh body can I
get a badonka dunk no okay
uh wait no uh no I'm done oh there we go
then there's some Chatters on there okay
ah and then you have to press
the button to select
what are these
am I got a whole zoo yeah oh you can use
parasite that's my old um roommate
this one yeah it's okay yeah yeah yeah
she doesn't use my switch anymore she
got her own switch
do you want to look like that okay
who is she oh
there we go oh
yeah yeah oh pause
wait what are we what is this this is
like the arm stretching pose
why can't I
like do it as if this arm helps you push
back the other arm
yeah
[Music]
uh what why is it sleepy ah we both have
a CPU as our partner okay okay first
volleyball okay select the hand to serve
and oh I'm left-handed let's go they
don't discriminate left-handed people
you'll be right-handed
yeah even though I have the left
controller which we should have opposite
well we can switch
no because then we'll have the wrong
avatars on the screen oh it's okay we
both have a handicap it's okay yeah I
mean it's laggy and we can barely see
the screen
uh play with one joy-con control upset r
one
let's just say should I shrink the game
no no no no no this is good that then it
will be even smaller what am I so should
I press this okay
I didn't do that
um
okay parasite don't stand too close to
the television okay but did we have no
TV there is no TV oh my God okay how to
play volleyball tell me tell me tell me
I I know I know it's like it's like this
let's learn the basics of volleyball
Bring It On bump set and Spike return
the ball to your opponent's side while
switching off rolls with your teammate
teammate I
[Music]
then swing it up at the right time
to hit the ball okay
I used to suck at volleyball
try it now okay
oh man this would be better if we heard
the ball I want to hear the ball oh yeah
Lily although
let's go and well oh a bit early oh okay
over anticipated it wow I did Dan
so good they were okay next would be the
upload wait do you not have to test it
am I the only one testing everything wow
I don't even get to live but you played
it before
when I'm just trying to fix uh the audio
so that we actually hear something
because the truth is we don't hear
anything
but might be okay oh
hi
Windows oh
oh yeah wait is the audio laggy
is that what you guys are hearing
no way they would have told us right
yeah I think it's just the output
oh [\h__\h] are you guys like
is this well you guys are hearing the
audio is like really [\h__\h] on our side
guys
yes yes
okay
oh my God
guys
what didn't you tell us
is it cutting out now is it crumbly now
[Music]
um
uh there was no audio before now oh
there was no audio before now
oh we didn't hear the game until now
okay
um
we only heard it it was fine early but
because there was no money okay what
about now
what about now do you hear it
it's cutting out it's cutting out bad
crunchy
yes
[Laughter]
uh we didn't want to inconvenience
oh just wonder if this is like even
watchable
wait but you should be hearing audio now
guys are you not hearing anything wait
no they are but it's crunchy
okay I don't think I have any way to fix
this
oh it might be my HDMI cable oh
oh have you tried to replace it really
quick I have another one okay she'll
replace it really quick she has another
HDMI cable she fittings maybe maybe it's
an HDMI cable
honestly love the scope really
oh man it's okay I didn't come all the
way to America for the streams anyway
the streams are like a side product look
at she's walking
um but um I was
I came here to record something for an
upcoming music video For an upcoming
album slash EPA whatever it is I don't
know
she knows and I can see
uh she looks like she's humping a little
bit and she has
injured her leg
I saw you celebrate
bye
yeah yeah so if you guys curious about
the outcome of my actual objective why I
came here you gotta wait
um it will not be out before or on my
birthday so it will still take some time
we're checking our time I thought it
would be good to not stress as much as I
did for do you because do you I feel
like doing you everything and and
birthday things were kind of like
last minute I'm stressing oh
I see the game again oh she switched
HDMI cable how is the sound now gosh
[Music]
honestly if if the flight wouldn't be
expensive in so long then I would come
here every weekend to do collaborations
out here
yeah oh that sounded crunchy better
better really like better like it's
still crunchy but better or no crunch no
weirdness no it sounded worse crunchy
because I was looking into it we're
listening to it from the can we listen
to it
except look she gave me
like like I just broke her hopes and
dreams
oh
okay that's good that's good that's good
okay I will swing it Upward at the right
hand okay okay
over in there
yes okay why not
okay oh
oh
oh boy that didn't count all right
I'm always the second one I think
yeah
this is fun
you should put a volleyball net up here
can you cut the space maybe one day
swing the joycon up to jump my turn no
no
swing wait what did you do
what what did you do when you just went
back oh I just moved you over a little
bit oh but when you step closer your
feet disappear
I'll I'll put it uh
this is all you know
Emma likes this kind of technical
solution finding stuff surely she likes
you okay uh swingers Jam swing The Joker
and down to spike you know okay
first swing the joycon up show me Lady
okay which will cause you to face the
ball and jump
okay I don't understand show me
oh apparently it counted but I failed
whoa
is that like a super hit you spiked it
well well I did it correctly once I'll
never use this move ever again swing the
draycon down to spike
next after jumping try executing a spot
what okay up and down oh okay okay
okay
as soon as I have a little quicker to
jump swing this one okay okay okay okay
yeah
[Music]
I'd help you but I want to win so
people will never get faster
let's go
okay oh
huh
[Music]
what
what maybe more clear a little quicker
to smell
[Music]
it
you know why because we have we have a
delay yeah because we're playing through
OBS right now oh I wasn't so bad with
the other moves
oh well
um okay
swing the joy-con up to block oh try it
now but it does all the same movement no
what
uh-huh
I'm looking
I'll just I'll just
I'll just move and play on my arms as if
I'm playing in real life yeah
yeah I'm up looking pretty good
we're not playing this in life today
what we're playing it in 3D so you
better use your whole body like your
legs do yeah I'm gonna show it to me
um bum said Spike and block
um remember the teamwork is the key to
Victory
a rat do you get the same tutorial now
okay okay but you can maybe do it faster
because you've done it before I'm a
parasite
huh my my my roommate used to call
herself parasite because she was using
my um
[Music]
all right empty swing at the right time
to hit the ball try it now okay first
try watch
yeah I'll Stand away yeah
it's
do I really have to actually do it I
could just swing the thing yeah
okay easy
boom
[Music]
was that me very early no yeah
here it goes again
oh it's still so early it looks like
you're on my team are you on my team no
they're just trying to confuse you how
nice
okay
we're balling we're balling
okay now you gotta do the up down thing
okay
I'm ready
I practice by watching a master I'll
make myself small
I was looking at the other one yeah
when it reaches its peak
so the up is the jump and then the down
is this pipe yeah I see feel free to
like actually jump why he doesn't even
show that I'm jumping because because
the Avatar is down there no it's not
they're not even jumping on it
is the example of the weed yeah right
there that's like for lazy people that's
how you're supposed to put lazy people
you look you can role play you're
actually playing
there it's
oh yeah no oh I think I was just too
slow on the come down
swing I am now they're blocking just
it's like who's this again raise the
roof but how is the blocking different
from like the second thing that we
learned
she knows
I play volleyball in school well I did
too really yeah I guess that's pretty
common everybody does
not I think everybody does but that was
not good
all right okay we've mastered the basics
of volleyball
[Music]
oh
okay I don't think you have to push the
button okay we're ready to actually play
oh
[Music]
versus oh Stephanie and Jake all right
Jake so Martin all right actually I'm on
that side on the other side should I
move it yes but not that okay oh I'm the
server uh thank you for telling me okay
oh
so small it's so small
what's up are you guys
wait
[Laughter]
um
it was behind you this badass
keep on looking at my ass I know you
like it I'm serving you my ass now you
plugged it
go kick those butts
uh
come on [\h__\h] yeah no
oh God
didn't I bounce
yeah that's it I'm moving you out
are you going to the other side
you can make me know
okay okay
here's my best model walk okay look guys
[Applause]
I'm winning what's going on
what's it
like I think oh we're supposed to switch
oh I'm okay you're serving still okay
wow
it's like I'm a waitress that came up
oops wow
sorry man don't sleep you're distracting
me
match Pawn this is the one
[Music]
hey
oh
[Music]
well I was in it with my whole body to
see how I like
you actually did the diving game oh it's
my turn now I guess you're serving when
I can come on I can't see
too bad that you're static
laughs
do whatever comes natural okay
oh
let's go do whatever comes natural loses
[Music]
the only one because you have the you
have a real body and I don't
it's like you're saying things like
Pinocchio
too
I'll make you real
I think if we play more games and make
you win you'll transform into a
beautiful young lady you think so yes
hold on let me fix something all right
I'll I'll
maybe I should just I saw I know okay
can you put me in the middle again
are you mad no we're playing different
game now I think
because we cannot keep on playing the
same game
okay
I just said different game and still
wants to tell me how to surf it's just a
tip I know how to surf
and also we have no straps that was a
tip for me zyloss what do you want to
play uh let's do this one the champion
you're asking to play a sword fighting
game against the one okay
I've actually played this one before so
I have the advantage this time but I
play it in real life you know I've
fought many Dragons and Knights and all
that [\h__\h] I didn't even know what this
one was
yeah but if it's with a sword then you
know it's just natural it's different
there's rules oh wait oh yeah Legends
okay
all right
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go
oh I just realized yeah
I was using the right hand the whole
time even though I saw myself
no okay I'll try to use my left hand now
a sword charge sword twins what
Do It shows uh it's it's whatever you
want your preference
wait what is a check filled up energy by
guarding oh [\h__\h] no
[Music]
yes
how do we do this enough space now okay
I don't have a bubble like that though
around me how to play chambara
Bring It On Point the joy-con at the
center of the screen press that okay
keep the web buttons facing you as you
hold down the control you don't know
what but anyway
okay uh yeah I mean yeah sure
when you move your joy-con up down let
the radius sword will move to move two
okay obviously swing The Joy come
quickly and attack okay
it looks like a big baguette is it
it's a big lights the only one looking
from afar okay you can let guard by
holding on that eye
oh
okay today you don't have the actual
sword prop for this yeah true you can
block attacks by gardening blocks so
that I get sword on your opponent's
sword cross
what ah
sure yes you gotta block my attacks I
wonder if we should face each other
we should but it asked me to point
towards the screen Ah that's true hmm oh
my God what
you're gonna die
you're about to get kicked off it's like
Sumo you get kicked off the range you
died
am I so aggressive It's gotta be the
yeah the shield okay next episode okay
yeah vertical baguettes versus
horizontal bucket okay yeah
okay uh a sneaky died
doesn't have to be the other day oh my
god oh that worked out too okay oh were
you holding something
can I move the chat
no okay attack without being blocked
what what does that mean when your
opponent is guarding vertical
swing the joycon vertically and attack
vertical vertical
oh
we don't know it's working so it does
take that
what happened clapping some more slap
him silly oh I got silly too uh when
you're pulling this gardener on attacks
you know the crossword huh
what diagonal now
I don't need too many instructions yeah
I might need this instructions I played
this game before your 10.
okay I have to stand here and be cute
both hands I'm not doing that
okay
you see that that's gonna be you that's
gonna be you huh
guard
[Music]
um
am I doing it okay I see it's just the
instructions okay
[Music]
all right is anybody timing this because
I'm pretty sure I'm doing it faster
I had to read everything wait for the
chat not to cover it
wait what does it say stop I can't see
wait next comes vertical strike guarding
horizontally oh okay
hi guys
is this is this this might be the old
version of you with this without the
shout out to fix oh my Butts oh true oh
hi all fat how you doing haven't seen
you in a while I mean there's nothing to
say really
where's the juice
right alcoholic Garden diagonally
I guess I did it
[Music]
beat them
be careful gonna get dizzy oh what does
it want now horizontal attack huh yeah
just like do the same direction and um
as long as it's not me
that's not you that's not me
I'm killer than that just beating them I
already made the story all right here we
go here we go oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
round one they're gonna be able to read
your movements
okay right
you can't read my movement yeah
[Applause]
wait what's cool am I oh
look at the platform I forgot I was
trying to do block motion but you have
to hold the button
you'll see there's three two rounds left
look at that she Esh going all in
go swimming
thank you
hi Lincoln okay
ready
foreign
it's a cam it's okay you you'll get your
old body back
surely well that's fun we should play
again yeah okay
if you think you got a chance
oh
[Music]
fine I'll go easy on you with my magical
bucket
do we have to do the thing again
ready
chill
hand cream
come on
yeah yeah whatever maybe I should go
full-time Warrior again round two it's
fun I forgot how much fun it was to beat
the [\h__\h] out of people you're you're
screen peeking what
she's not even she's just shaking it it
is too early she's just shaking it you
must find your inner true self to become
more like your
your what do you call the yodar you're
just famous
uh-huh
[Music]
haha
the game lets her spam
what you want to do it again
[Music]
let's do bowling
I'm gonna get water really quick because
your water oh chocolate you can drink my
water I don't have to take your water
and there's water right there right over
there
guys should I do something for you I
think the chat is oops oh [\h__\h] oh I
actually I accidentally started it again
do you want me to do something I can do
something I can do something
like the model walk
[Music]
you understand what the he really is it
not too scarf then you guys who came
with it I'm so sorry but I think it's
going pretty well now
[Music]
tomorrow I'm gonna do
um like a dancing karaoke
I tried to find some songs and know the
color of golf that I can do in an
archive stream
[Music]
um
we'll have to like move the model so
that because hers is like kind of static
mine you know moves around but hers is
like set to stay
it's better now now it's a push-up
[Music]
didn't we already do this in my brain
fit 3D stream I'm gonna do you want me
to do a push-up yeah
[Music]
um
your forms all messed up
that's it that's the tracking
[Applause]
so exhausting
who originally has been using my muscles
a lot you know because planning the
Aquario and it's just
it's just uh too too much my arms were
dead do a squat
um this thing is this a squat yeah my
heels are not going up not at all my
heels are they are I'm looking at them
let's spread your legs wider okay
there you go
that's better
gotta do it like those Instagram girls
right if you do it like that you have to
face the other way
oh
can you uh I just need to be plugged in
and unplugged
um the main one
unzip okay yeah
[Music]
Move Along
and zip back up
[Music]
oh oh oh
they reacted to the squad
[Music]
my boyfriend
I need to drink water
it's getting hot in here
so take your off your motion suit
foreign
[Music]
what do you want to do uh play okay but
uh my thing is frozen oh like for real
oh yeah I think it's because I'm not
sure why but usually if you disconnect
reconnect if this is it that is not
using it right now
um I don't know if you guys heard Ahmed
Bush she says um there's a technical
problem
which we can chat and play around in 3D
for a while
okay
let me try for like another one though
but I won't be on screen oh yeah
[Music]
foreign
Studio
okay give me a second
I'm gonna make up a dance to this music
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
I see on there
but she's so cute in life today
I personally don't mind it
[Music]
let me come back what I'm almost there I
miss you
I'm almost there Emma did you tell them
like I told you to tell them when we met
that when I gave you a hug our ears
intertwined oh no I forgot wait wait
wait
don't you tell them one thing and you
forget about it
[Applause]
no
no someone in your ear kind of like hugs
the other's ear too
and you and I just found a flap when I
moved away from here
important information she just left it
out that's when you guys have me guys I
almost tell you every single thing every
single thing hmm
like the fact that I'ma cleaned up so
much
so much to impress me
she cleaned her dog she cleaned her
place
cute oh I have the music oh
sorry
air hug yeah
ah getting here getting your earrings
yeah thankfully that doesn't happen to
me because I don't wear earrings but I
can imagine that being a struggle when
a girl with earrings big Hoops or
whatever hugs a girl with no more
earrings
yeah yeah
boom
you know I don't think you understand
what intertwined means well one would be
a better word there are entangled
entitled
what do you think of Bubba's new haircut
uh yeah he looks fresh he looks he was
very excited I was on the problem was I
wasn't wearing pants so when he was like
jumping on my legs
eh
what what you weren't wearing any pants
yeah I was wearing a dress
didn't you pay attention to what I was
wearing
oh my God I'm just kidding I'm so sad
what are you looking at when you see me
on the
[Music]
um
my dress was matching okay color wise to
you
[Music]
it's working out to The Omelette you
gotta downgrade to 2D but is it really a
downgrade
from from uh wooden stick person
[Music]
foreign
I'm warming up for tomorrow do you guys
want to see choreo for my secret new
song
yeah
[Music]
what is this hmm you will see something
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
I guess you could
just like the edges of the studio hey I
have a new hat
what your head is so big get out the
floor okay
well this will be kind of an excuse for
you to put less body movement
into this yeah nobody will be able to
tell now you want it to Bowl right yeah
let's go okay
oh there's a special in
neck standard yeah stand again take
turns or simultaneously uh
uh simultaneously I guess yes saves time
for all the scrubs that we already had
the reason of the delay Chad's having
fun
and what does I can't say what it says
but I guess it says let's go with us
yeah
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
there we go yeah I think bowling is just
you know just it's just like Wii Sports
yeah okay I have a little extra
I'll do some extra movement you gotta do
like oh like bowling they like run like
for my legs
okay then press press that button okay
hold what well joycon with the front
facing you to play
what so don't hold it sideways ah okay
okay is that is that English what it
feels felt weird okay are we already
doing it do I have to press something
when I throw
no I'm making rotate oh
hold it so I can control in front of
your chest and perform a rolling motion
while holding ZR ah okay
okay let's go middle
okay
oh
whoa
oh nice
you have how many
eight uh I don't know I didn't say I
wasn't looking it's so chill I made me
at the bowling alley I haven't been in
the bowling alley for a long time me
neither
okay [\h__\h] I missed it
so extra that's what you get
um
[Applause]
our father was European and couldn't go
straight but I guess I was wrong when I
don't get it
[Music]
it whoa it's just a replay ha I got a
spare you got the pins what does that
mean uh you didn't get all like terms
it's like bowling is like golf
all right all right
let's look at this they're the angle is
very important indeed and the energy
let's play baseball baseball
oh
that's not really a big oh no
so you get her twisted and turn it
around like crazy
oh Mommy fix me I'm fixing I'll fix it
this is terrifying
I'm standing in the t-pose
and being shot at by lasers from all
sides
oh no
oh no it didn't hurt turn around
okay
there we go I think that's fun yeah oh
sure
hi am I normal again I think so pretty
normal
however normal I could possibly be okay
now let me think about something
oh wait um
what are you doing wrong
correctly okay
stop bowling
nice
this is so much easier than bowling in
real life because in real life I always
have the problem with the bowling ball
even the smallest one is so heavy that
yeah it's hard to hold it like three
fingers too it hurts
put oh that was too normal how lame I
don't see it what what
mine disappeared too
okay oh because I didn't hold the button
yeah wait
no
what are you doing now on my way
oh [\h__\h] oh well that was my bad are you
holding the button oh yeah
it looks like you just laid an egg
oh yeah
oh
why why
you gotta hold it oh
nice
what did you do did you not get all of
them again
I missed I missed two
up to you I just I'm like somebody in
the chat just watching you maybe you
should make poses like me and then
you'll get them all they can't even
all right right it's about the spirit
the soul and the bowl
wow
more and more
[Music]
we're even now oh okay can you get that
one picture only you can get that one
that's easy easy she says yeah let's
look at her
oh
my eyesight is bad it's a small screen
that looks so close to it so far okay
did you wearing glasses no no how do you
do comic coming huh that's not really
cute though kind of honey that's pretty
cool though
um let's do a squat
You're Gonna Miss anyways
I did that for you
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah she did it
on purpose was that bad at 140 straight
yeah
who's winning I think you're still
winning of course I'm still winning
right
[Music]
um
what are you doing over there [\h__\h] I was
too far on the right side
two pins left oh no problem okay
okay
I keep throwing it round
I got two of the four what are you doing
um we still have a lot of turds left I
think it's the win
[\h__\h] go away
we got one you got one
oh you like you spun the ball but I
think it was by accident yeah because
there's like a there's a strategy to
spinning the ball like curving it you
can do that in this game yeah I think
you can damn wow
mm-hmm
[Music]
let's see I'll just imagine them being
chickens all right we're gonna beat them
give me a hug babies
[Music]
let me give you a spanking
as you can see I'm doing before are you
holding the button yeah I don't think so
maybe not really no oh don't let go of
it don't let go
what the [\h__\h] okay
[Music]
okay I'll get them all I'll get them all
what does it says
I said it's a good ball
is it in German no oh no I'm just not
making things up
happening
skills oh [\h__\h]
it's so happy
you're holding it
okay come on two hands
go back
you can cancel and if you're unsure like
this okay here we go they put
instructions on the screen for you again
hold the joycon in front of you
in front of your chest and form a
rolling motion while holding the button
the bumper um
maybe okay here
[Music]
here I come
what are you doing wrong do you need me
to take the controller I can yeah I
could do this one for you
it's good for you no I can choose a
strike
oh
[Music]
um
how did you get it this time
I just thought my life depends on it at
this point you're gonna kick me out
okay oh there's still so many happy
fruit okay okay let's do a few quickies
here
whoa nice where are you two you two
eight versus nine yeah yeah I can get it
though
[Music]
upstairs are you first spare I think so
spare
[Music]
I wanna I wanna see uh what do you call
it again when you get them all
strike a strike let's bring it on isn't
it a strike I think so I think oh wait
is that a baseball term yes it's right
oh [\h__\h] we're gonna get made fun of I
don't know it's a pretty short strike
because that's yeah oh okay okay right
right they share some terms I guess well
yeah but it's all the opposite I think
oh [\h__\h] huh oh maybe I should bowl with
my right hand
it worked last time
oh that was pretty cute
I'm already off for today
Victor dance yeah
I think I froze oh
all right oh okay okay I lost this game
whatever it was of course did you even
win that's so sad as you win the single
thing today
you're doing this because it's my
channel you're letting me win right yeah
yeah
let's go with that
oh my God
it's not even fair I got a space
[Music]
King almost
sweeping what sleeping what crap I'm
sweeping the game the bowling alley wait
I [\h__\h] up
why does it herbs
what what what what
um
[Applause]
okay okay what is grounded is is a
phoenix when you get it four times then
or what oh
no probably not
Ah that's bad that was really bad but
yeah did you do something
something put the lane no did you like
tilt it
I poured butter on it bother
you want to put butter on you what what
like a foreign cob because they're so
yellow yeah we're talking about eating
corn earlier yes
all right
for me yeah I'm gonna I bought some corn
oh yeah
I'm so proud I'm such a proud mommy
bowling Mommy oh yeah you know we should
try well after this game we didn't try
in Japan if I try to give you like a
piggyback ride if you like sit on me
while I walk around
okay okay I'm happy on the oh you want
to give me a picture I think we can if I
messed up though yeah I hope my markers
don't get stuck on you okay so I think
there's a possibly a win for me
yeah look you won by like 50. yeah yeah
or 60. and usually now I'm winning these
kind of games
like you know um Clubhouse games Club
Penguin no
[Music]
Mouse games oh the the 50s
right no those games I always lose
penguin yeah I beat you last time we
played no when we played chess and you
cheated
oh
[Laughter]
yeah
he lives in the chat
I was just trying to help us finish this
maybe I don't know let me drink some
water I don't forget
oh where were you when Club Penguin was
killed
I don't I don't remember I don't think I
had it all right I don't think I was on
the internet at the time and like I took
a break from the internet what
what one called penguin oh no no no I
remember
yeah it wasn't that long ago it was like
five or six years ago right
I don't know I mean I never really
played I played other games but um
like an anime mmorphages
a few that I tried this
oh Dolphus was cool yeah
those is cool I think it's still running
yeah it is they have two games
probably I think well how long have we
stream one and then okay I mean okay 20
minutes if that was loading screen no no
we just started late
the soccer one in this is oh yeah yeah
so then even the game says football and
not soccer
this one's pretty fun oh boy what we
don't have them like a strap I have tape
problems wait wait wait let's tape it I
can imagine we wouldn't eat it
okay
uh assault has the footballing prowess
control the ball and score I'll just
tape it to yours since you're the only
one that has
okay uh practice
shootout use your legs to score
well which one should we do never mind I
don't know should we do this
I'm gonna sound fun okay
but which one
is this not is this not a normal game I
guess not
okay
this sport is controlled I played with
two controls
per person
nah
um I'm just reconfiguring
um
all right
I'm holding the tape wait do we need two
each
oh yeah I think we need to
ouch but I think if you do the leg one
it does I don't think you need to eat
but there wasn't even a choice
oh
[Music]
it just told me like randomly in between
do see do one player and then we'll tape
one to your leg and I want to see it too
okay wait what does that say uh yeah a
solo test the footballing prowess
controllable score
so I guess to tape it to your leg I
guess so
um yeah
it'll be me
I totally have football and prowess easy
please easy easy not easy okay
oh to utilizer to change the control
mode oh you don't have to I don't I like
sharp mode
ah
so like where should I take it though
only one leg Yeah
okay what does my uh the other one okay
like with your right leg
[Music]
I I guess laughs that's why I have left
what can you and do soccer players have
to choose one
ah no oh it's half apparently up here
okay I called it underneath on my knee
here
I'm pretty sure I have the leg
strapsible
I also can't find mine anymore I think
for my last ringford stream I also use
something that was not the next dress I
put a cradle thing oh it works though I
think it's fine
oh
it's already okay and hold the joy-con r
and here we go
okay I'll play some soccer make sure you
have enough space on a standard bag do
you want to be my ball okay what my head
are you gonna
should I position my head like that over
there let me Triple you
yeah
oh can you make yourself bounce
can you make yourself bounce when I do
this oh okay okay and
[Music]
ha
hahaha oh
okay enough dribbling Ramen welcome to
Lex trap mode first up is kicking
practice slightly swing your leg to pick
what that's a football
it's my head too big oh
does it actually work when you kick hell
yeah
oh the action of the kick is set
automatically so just kick straight oh
okay
I'm gonna make myself a little smaller
and I don't know your character moves
automatically you can also move my hair
only using art oh
tracking and file when it gets close
okay
Charlie
whoa I shattered the glass why would
they make a gold out of glass what the
[\h__\h] a character will automatic jump uh
toward an airport ball watch a character
jump and time your kick so it hits the
ball oh YouTube is lagging apparently
what
whoa
holy [\h__\h] it looked like you actually
hit it
that was so cool perfectly lined up
let's try dashing okay they can Dash
toward the ball by swinging both arms as
if you're jogging in place oh okay
just
[Music]
oh
do we run towards it again no okay we're
done
okay try to try on real much versus at
NPC
on which side are you I'm
mentally chica
she's a ninja
are we reversing a real person
I don't think so because I could shoot
some difficulty oh
[Applause]
do you have no more I do
um
it's okay I do I don't want to stress
you okay let's go
I'm already running oh you're dashing
get it
[Music]
nice thank you thank you
I'm like Christine what's Cristiano
Ronaldo or something like that messy
I'm the first awesome
oh the first Austin to be good at soccer
because we suck we never make it
anywhere near or we make people mad it's
strong no lost friends no they all
wouldn't
we are very honest people you'll be the
first why am I blue haired oh cause I'm
a rookie uh because because your team
color oh look blue macroni okay okay
I was like playing with you
okay
um you you carry me piggyback now sure
she she wanted to do it
you say sure as if it was a mile of
course
why are they saying what does that even
mean what like
[Music]
are they spamming or something does it
mean something I don't know oh it might
be something that people say when you
win in a see you oh maybe it's
somebody's name
a a soccer player yeah
is that so
oh we got gift subs thank you hold on
let me change this really quick it'll be
super fast I'm just gonna put real pants
on okay okay there's a batteries back
here all right meanwhile I'm gonna
foreign
[Music]
you guys are fans of soccer
you know you know these kind of things I
don't know anything about soccer I
watched oh I remember when I was like
this small
um my family was watching some worldwide
cup yeah and it was I think at the end
it was Greece versus someone and my
whole family was against Greece and for
some reason I just as I was just small I
believed in Greece for some reason and I
made myself like I took like A4 paper
and I painted it
um in the in the grease flag and I put
it as a helmet over my face and over my
whole body
and then I was like
cheering for grace and day one oh it was
Euro European wow
yeah you know huh that doesn't say
anything about you know anything at all
you know anyway I was the only one
cheering for them not like I had any a
reason or like an idea why they should
win
you know I knew nothing about soccer but
because of me they won hi honey hello
are you sure you want to try this yeah
we'll try this you can like sit on
you on your back yeah and then you're
gonna go like stand up
no wait
[Music]
is it working yeah
[Laughter]
it actually works pretty well
you like it like a like a prop this is
like a horse prop or you wanted me to
test out the trampoline oh yeah I can
bring it up
I don't necessarily needed to jump on
we'll see how high I can jump
be careful not to roll your ankles since
you are wearing shoes oh okay
can you do any fancy jumps no you can do
spin do 360. okay and then I'm gonna
take should I
kind of hide change the screen or is
this okay oh yeah let's change the
screen
[Music]
is it okay if it's my background yeah
problem
hey I'm
saying
oh yeah
that's pink it's pink okay yeah
[Music]
please
oh look at those physics
do you guys hear the fancy sounds
oh
whoa
[Music]
I can't just spin maybe I'll fall off
yeah I'm scared
I never did a spring before
careful
[Music]
well
what else what else uh
I don't know what else is there
[Music]
the flip
I'm just kidding I
no no
you can't do flips I know this is so
cool it's what the chat would be asking
for
it but this is also a blue yeah it's a
horizontal flip
[Music]
you know uh jumping on trampoline like
Burns a ton of calories too it's just
like running my birds cardio
on the head
actually you know there's a there's a
thing that I really wanted to do
but I don't know if I should just let
the viewers
like edit it oh if I should do it to get
like a uh for my own and upload it as a
short but there's the tails off meme
yeah yeah you know those games oh yeah
yeah there's like a move where
um the dude he fights
and there's you know this move is that's
called demon Fang oh and he goes my
demon friend
oh I'm a genius double demon friend like
he just learns a new move and because he
says oh I'm gonna do this WOW double
even thing uh I think I get it yes yeah
that's it's funny like a like a short
video you'll make yeah good old zealous
he's such a genius wow
um
I think it it might I'll just do it off
screen but but just in case I forget
about it okay maybe can you get rid of
your thingy can you put on like a green
screen green screen I guess so I have
too many colors
and then you guys can you put a sword in
my hand what does it even look like when
he does that
I don't even remember
[Music]
oh
no not magenta I have Magenta in my eyes
[Music]
oh yeah
I'll be fine I'll move my head can you
take my phone that's like on your left I
think
take it yeah I want to check really
quickly to me
thank you
oh shiny can't have shiny things here
should be fun
um demon Bang
genius okay here
[Music]
double demon okay okay here
I actually have a sword but I can't use
it so you guys just put a sword in my
hand okay
Photoshop Photoshop
okay here we go
[Music]
I'm a genius double demon friend
yeah
Sonic fast no wait one more just in case
I did something
wrong okay here we go
oh
[Music]
cool
thanks guys I'm leaving the rest to you
yeah make it look good oh my gosh
so tomorrow
um around the same time we're gonna do
um
archived dancing hopefully it will go
well and pre-record I'm gonna be honest
I'm recording the the audio
because I want to focus on the dancing
if I remember the dances dancing takes a
lot of brain power
it's not quite like bicycle riding
Carmen I actually can't do a cart rooms
no I was wondering if I should ask you
to like hold my legs up I can't I guess
but
how do I even start in a wheelbarrow we
should do wheelbarrow what's available
it's like where you you kind of do like
a push-up and then I'll pick up your
legs and then you'll like walk your
hands
well I can do that
but my arms are so weak what you can do
it I'll you can do it
oh yeah so anyway guys be there tomorrow
Emma will be there too as you know sock
puppet she has no dance you were singing
for me and she'll just cheer me on
it'll be cute if I had little like light
sticks
[Music]
but if you use it via our app I think
you can put like six on the morning yeah
but it's not it's not in that okay
I try not to mess anything up so I'm
gonna hold you back
are you okay
they were kind of floating yeah you're
you didn't hurt yourself did you no okay
laughs
it's coming after me
I'm just taking a walk
so yeah anyway
[Music]
thank you guys
for watching oh oh The Trackers hurt in
my head
oh sorry don't look at that
oh close up all right
[Music]
oh I'm broken okay
ah all right let's take a screenshot for
tomorrow for I need to make a thumbnail
[Music]
um
I want to have like a cool angle
oh they told me I should covered on you
in here
oh yeah
[Music]
I'm scared why there's nothing to be
scared of your belly button is right in
my face smell it
I took a shower today
what was I saying I am opposed
I took a pose for a thumbnail
no Mr Beast hands Mr beastown nevermind
we don't have finger tracking oh what
the Mr bees beaten's hands look like
yeah really is it not more something
like uh wow that doesn't even work
um
oh maybe too close
isn't that something like this oh there
we go oh no that's something else
recently I've been getting so many Mr
Bean bees bees Beast recommendations in
my videos Everybody watches them
do you I've watched I watched the series
video the other day that's probably why
I got it in my recommendations
uh okay here's here's some cute poses ah
[Music]
oh
unfortunately nothing at tracking so all
I can do is
[Music]
back
oh nice ah I think you know language
when we do in the in the cover studio
and they do like a camera I know yeah we
need to do that
I mean like
are you are you technically capable of
the yeah
I just gotta work on a way but it's
possible
[Music]
um
okay I can't think of much in here just
a bit broken
[Music]
oh yeah should we say uh okay I think
it's okay to at least say
was that we're gonna watch the first
movie yeah yeah because I'm in wants to
go watch the new spider reverse movie
it's a spider-verse and I haven't
watched the first one
we haven't made her watch it it's okay
right now after this stream we're gonna
watch it you know together yeah and then
this one we'll watch here
and then the next one we'll watch with
some popcorn and nachos or whatever yeah
yeah on the big screen
are you guys jealous we're the teammates
where are the teammates oh you must be
some jelly well
number one teammate right here I mean
what do you think about you know my my
title your titles number one teammates
yeah I don't know I think you have
Fierce competition but to be fair you've
been able to do you know what no
teammate could do before what was that
you could get into that on my studio
that's true VIP VIP and eating animal
food I'm eating um drinks because I may
mix the great iced tea oh yeah I should
make some Nails I will I will drink I'm
gonna iced tea we're gonna actually
um I shouldn't even be reward okay you
know what I should be rewarded after the
shitty travel I had to go over to come
here but
but I mean
set this up for me so I can do my stupid
stream yeah thank you it's fun to set it
up so it's like a new challenge for me
so thank you for letting me and trusting
me to setting it up you know it's a
little scars at the start but look it's
something it's working now now you know
what you need
last year like we figured everything out
like at the spot on the day yeah right
there and then you know after I left it
was it was all like Smooth for using it
on your own yeah now we're here again to
you know like test out streaming
together two people in 3D at once now we
know what we need for a better next time
maybe I'll buy a new laptop more brand
more RAM more RAM I need a beast laptop
and now I regret not bringing mine I
don't think yours is better than mine
you might have a better grab this cut
because mine just has 1060. 10 16. my
viewers know what laptop I have
I don't know I have an Alienware from
like like last year I think or the the
two years ago it was the newest one yeah
it's probably better than mine because I
know the laptops graphic card is better
than my computer's graphic card yeah
it probably isn't it
I'm gonna get a better one I'll get a
laptop with a 460. oh someone said Kiara
is better
wow well I've had this laptop since
before I joined hello live oh I think
yeah okay 10 16 is eight years old
you're eight years old
everybody calm down oh [\h__\h] okay what I
said kfp
okay guys thank you for watching
everyone's on the chill now watch a
movie yeah um cuddles no no we're not
doing that okay
Bubba I will cuddle with the Kato when I
find the Kato I'm looking for cattle
yeah he's scared are you scared of her
no
he was obviously scared of the dogs
we are not me he's not used to meeting
new people some dogs wearing like I saw
them I saw them running and then and
then Henry ran like can we bring Bubba
in here you could pick Bubba up
oh you want to bring Bob on here okay
[Music]
oh no
uh
oh don't mess anything up hi okay he
doesn't he didn't look at me I'm not
interesting
[Music]
he's not invisible but uh
he likes you I think he likes the way
you smell oh I smell like sweat right
now it's salty very salty hi isn't it
cute it's better when you pick him up
because then he can't like jump on you
jump on me
oh
[Music]
yeah
come here
again
oh cute okay yeah that was Bubba
interaction one day he'll get his own
model yeah one day I mean he did get it
on my 3D Street
yes and if you figure that out
[Music]
[Applause]
all right I'm gonna go Fade Out the
Stream
see you tomorrow if you want to see
chihuahua dancing
and trust me you want to seek you out
dancing
[Music]
thank you