[Music]
what is
this I feel
wor R
is huh
everybody feels sort of
familiar
[Music]
but what are they trying to break
out what are we doing
here
why why
[Music]
remember what I want to remember it
who's that I don't
know three other four corners occupied
is that some sort of
[Music]
clue what
Happ oh I feel scared
[Music]
I'm not getting hurt
though of course I remember your
[Music]
rans
we looks familiar
[Music]
already that sound not
right Nissa seems like bad news
Nissa Nissa Raven c h who are you people
H what hello can you say that again
hello oh oh my
God there's a pretty Orange
lady yeah I'm kind of scared what's
happening oh my God my hand what
happened to my hands they're so blocky
where's why is it why is hold on hold on
a
second am I Beau
really am I square like that
you ow what happened where am I oh my
God what happened I think I hit my head
what happened who are all of you hello
yeah I that's what I want to know I
think you all have some explaining to do
what a coincidence I also hit my head
you hit your head too I I hit I just hit
my head wait I don't see any cracks
though are you sure I'm very durable but
it was trauma damage very
you look
famar are you guys also heroes from
another did
you did anyone see the lights I wonder
if you can people here did you see the
[Music]
lights I feel
I don't have guys are talking to each
other did you see where are you
[Music]
from
oh
oh ba
[Music]
you look you look Harless are you are
you a
human yes I
think what about you
what
happened I was remembering things
I yeah why you short huh what do you
mean
anyway what a she you know what you're
eny are you this is how the life ends I
don't want this anymore oh I don't need
this life it's all right I'm just
waiting to be kicked
from the conquest I could just go find a
little cabin in the corner in the middle
of the woods just about myself it's all
right I don't remember much about my old
life and you know it's fine you can't
miss what you don't
remember watching you feel bad if I say
that I do not no because I also don't
remember you okay
oh you know your name I don't even know
what my name is
yeah my name
is oh okay what if they like
[Music]
Li me
Li know what if I li about being what if
I no no I would never like I don't trust
you is this any better r
is everybody else too loud exactly I
don't trust
[Music]
Youk
I I feel lost
[Music]
stop ear seen you
somewhere she's going to leave my
[Music]
corner this is also a very nice
did I do something wrong
[Music]
your corner is safe the corner is safe
right the the
aure the aure
maen then
Cana Nissa
[Music]
you're pretty quiet
Nissa do you know who I
am I remember you
slightly let me make you louder
[Music]
though try talking
again okay I'll try talking okay you're
still quiet but that's the most I can
do smells like a
SM like a it's not bad
though I
see it feels
F yeah I feel I feel sort of scared
no
[Music]
h sneak key sneak key huh sneak key
sneak key
[Music]
sneak
what what and more than
[Music]
anything what
H more than
anything the people I hold most
dear faced with oil Oblivion I feel
empty
relieved don't know perhaps
destroyed I do not know what
huh and so much I don't know and
yet I don't know the bright light it
calls to
[Music]
ohy let's
go it's all bright light actually
there's a lot of lights oh the brightest
one yeah don't fall
there's oh wait
[Music]
oh this looks I can do this I can do
this what happens if we
fall go to the
light the
light we going to shoot up we shoot
up this is my
I like that me
up Pi me up take me wake me up many
voices I don't know why this so many
voices can we go up we go we don't go
up
my that that looks like an
egg octopus
egg EG it's like a broken egg octopus
egg but what came
first it's
not it looks so
icy come
[Applause]
[Music]
on what is this what is this
huh what are you doing here what are you
doing
here you have to look of Outsiders about
you
oh oh
quick somewh his majesty the GU have
arrived at the sanctuary the
sanctu of the heroes
[Music]
the king chamber audience
chamber welcome Heroes this is the
kingdom of the bestest and I am its king
the guards who brought you here have
informed me that you remember not but
your own
names a side effect of travel between
worlds No Doubt
[Music]
huh this must all come as a surprise to
you but here can well twice I who
summoned you
here you see an unprecedented Calamity
know threatens our world oh they so on
the earth with corruption and driven us
from our
homes oh the blade of land now gives
rise to creatures of Shadow known as St
St this Kingdom of lesto and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to us live best
[Music]
oh huh oh but should the Calamity be
left unchecked it is only a matter of
time before it consumes the entire world
oh what king
[Music]
he's tiny he is
Tiny the rual of hero
[Music]
suon you who ha from another world have
been summoned here by me to become the
saviors of
theor yeah
I
can only you have the power to save our
world and so I ask who
[Music]
you your magesty ver this ver this what
is
it stains has broken through our
defensive line
oh
no no
the def we are rushing the mountain of
Defense but the situation is
dire
oh what about us we help where are these
strangers
oh what's say you Heroes will you accept
this
Destiny there is a great power within
you will use it to save us to save this
[Music]
world oh he's
cute oh this
is I thank you for leting your Aid bra
you may call me V yeah I know
that the ancestors Celesta
Celesta is Celesta the ancestors
blessings upon you my name is
Celesta do not hesitate to call on me
and said you need my Aid let your heart
be your compass and I have faith we will
prevail you says
te facial
R the
rumoro name ate my special normally but
a fortune favors the don't
it
show
[Music]
Ru so you are the hero i s the
mysterious power within you well my name
is r
that's more like
behavor that's a pretty big gate there
oh best
oh oh lost you're still here sir
gentlemen you're still here H it's not
yet baby
L what
you can't what kind of soldier are you
H oh this is a
house oh I can't open
[Music]
it this must
be
what Li where are we it's wide are
those Graves
am I saying that forget it not
[Music]
Graves
my are you
[Music]
pouring excuse
me did I catch you
puring oh wow she P for
anyone I'll pet you with my sword
I like the Ping I like the
[Music]
Ping
fuzzy oh danger there is what are you
saying as iMagic no doubt explain to you
our kingdom faces an unprecedented
crisis that's not good Calamity the land
leaving it Breath of Life and invested
with monsters known
as not even the mighty lesto Castle can
be said to be safe
anymore mayhaps it is too late to save
this world from destruction nevertheless
[Music]
it is our duty to defend our King and
Countryman to the very and brave Heroes
From Another World let us go forth with
Valor and fight
together I can
fight let's get
him if I H at him oh there's mini ones
open
you yeah am I helping oh
you I took him down it was me I took him
down am I hitting him I took go
down oh no where the king go I jumped it
I jumped it okay King I'll take the king
I'll take the
king am I hitting him oh gosh oh go look
out for the king he's going for the
gate get the K he's going for the
gate
the where'd he go there he
is oh go there more them he'll keep on
spotting the
guys get the King get the
king where'd he go where's the king
there's
a for him here he comes there we
go you am I am I hitting them hey who
are
you oh no I'm going to how do I eat how
do I eat so
many oh right quick I
remember I'm going to
heal do we not make
it huh oh no shout Revelation hold your
weapon and left click
Revelation Revelation revelation
[Music]
Revelation
Revelation re how long does it have to
be
Revelation reation
[Music]
re
Revelation revelation
am I missing
something if I eat bread doesn't
work
well
[Music]
Revelation my
go oh did I do it well enough we'll be
back
[Music]
guys did you know we we failed to save
the world once that was that
was we're
back is this like
AES have turned back
[Music]
the maybe
we proposal you get me out of here
not tell to
[Music]
do but they're not the same oh God she's
approaching me I approached you are you
blushing me there's no need to blush
I'm it's nice to meet you
open you can call me Callie though
Callie okay I'm apparently a very strong
Reaper from a you're
what a Reaper a Reaper I thought you
heard a very sweaty Reaper
maybe nice to meet
you what about me and do I is what I
heard you
say nervous new people don't be nervous
I'm on the
yellow belly button
girl is that what I have to you I'm not
B but girl I'm
M it's nice to meet you well I think I
think my name
is is that what my
the last thing I remember is that I got
hit by a truck you got hit by a truck I
lost my
stop my memories are just sort of fuzzy
I'm glad I wasn't hit by a truck
H I'm glad that you it looks like you
have all your
limbs that's good
yeah all your CL a little I just lost my
memory I didn't lose my clothes
well I I feel like you need to go to the
shopping mall what do you want to take
me to the
mall I don't know if there malls in this
world you have money is but but we can
go shopping for
clothes I'm going shopping for
clothes
Oh e was a forgotten memories I feel
like I remember this
[Music]
though who am I
the world I live in the world I live
[Music]
in I'm more than
anything the people I hold most
[Music]
de face with Oblivion I feel
empty
relieved perhaps
distraught I feel like there's something
wrong I don't know what
[Music]
though so much I don't know
yet huh the bright light it CRS to
yet go toward the
light what if we don't go toward the
light what if we we
fell we here I feel something
reel
Rebel
Rebellion Rebellion
hello reell oh my goodness I'm so
Sor
excuse what
happen What happens if I go don't go to
the light huh huh oh I can't
it it makes me want to go to the
light H I
am
g
g nice to meet you g nice to meet you
nice friend what is your name I'm
M but my memor is a bit
fuzzy wait it says fuzzy above your head
perhaps how can you read
I thought I was the only
one I too can read go orang it says it
says dumb
ass who excuse me what does it say above
my head it
says you
are
D I don't think can read too well know
[Music]
wait wait did I did I miss
it
SL that
again what's going on
here what you okay
[Music]
my best Castle
again is this all because we
[Music]
failed why are you doing here oh we
heard them we heard them Outsiders about
you yeah I'm an
outsider I could it
be what the heroes arrived at the
sanctuary
wait is that us is that me huh the king
I like his mustache though huh it looks
very
[Music]
mustach
okay
Calamity I don't like the Calamity
part
[Music]
no yeah we have to fight the the
Calamity the ritual of hero
[Music]
summoning okay summoned here by him
yes we have the
power
you and then get him away
H H
this
things okay somewhere
safe we we we SE this already
rafin we talked to vus we talked to the
king king
bestto okay probably want to follow her
how do we break
it we need to kill someone do we need to
kill someone oh yeah let's kill
someone are you purple for me why do you
smell a
chicken for me offer bread and peace I
want you to
P do the
[Music]
paring help I'll pet you with my
hand it's cute when you
P you don't have to run away
I was going to make it why do you guys
look the
same I don't know it feels sort of weird
to me why are you trying to touch my
tail
[Music]
H checking
what I don't know it feels it a fun oh I
hurt myself I don't
know I know she was trying to be me up I
like
she I want her
to she needs the P it's
cute no no no no she needs the P have
you heard
it make make her
P Make Her
[Music]
P thank you I appreciate it hey she's
talking to me do get
away it's GL she
PRS two dogs are attacking me for no
reason two
dogs it's just it's GL she
[Music]
PS I I I don't think I have heard it but
I think you should leave her alone you
are
Al yeah don't be a bully I'm not
bullying her I'm just bully I just want
to hear the cing do do you look like you
might be a dog so do you bark hi do you
bark yeah bark me yeah bark for me yeah
bark for me come on come on puppy yeah
bark for me in a
tail for me too I B but I don't think
that's
barking C though Bow Bow Bow Bow yeah
she is barking you don't don't you hate
me I don't hate you I want you to
P okay you come CL I want I'm a little
oh there's danger wait the big guys are
talking who cares about danger there's
party oh you're that's
nice the don't don't hurt me anymore
wait I'm ready they were right here I
remember from my
are we friends now I'm happy thank
you you're
welcome
Ro you have the pr
Ro save the world from destruction but I
was busy with
puring you can't about destruction when
they puring
huh defeat this
St oh
[Music]
the heck why does he have a
laser excuse
me he has a laser he didn't have that I
don't remember a laser
before he has a
laser stay away from the
he has a laser don't
think I did it no I did not I did not do
it I
missed only
our stay away from me S stay away from
me oh
gosh I don't want to
die lose your
oh gosh I'll
you I feel s of sort of
[Music]
bad something about that doesn't make me
very
happy here's the vo beam I don't
remember what that is the king
[Music]
over here get the
r yeah I'm
scared this
then I
died oh
no where is everyone oh there they
are I can join the botle
[Music]
okay hold your weapon and left
click Revelation
Revelation
hi the stain host has been
routed reel
oh
hi you fought bravely CL Heroes I pray
you're not injured I died Papa I
did that Mighty armored one must be
their leader the stin king fascinating
Most Fascinating say from someone who
didn't fight well I see why they call
you Heroes we in a right pickle without
your
help please sustain minimal damage
thanks to your Valor our kingdom is in
your de thank
you I must hasten to inform His Majesty
of our Victory will you accompany
me you're going to you're going to show
me off
huh Royal audience chamber huh King are
you proud I heard the do you heard
it called upon you though it called upon
you suddenly you Rose to the occasion
you have my greatest attitude deepest
gratitude what interest me most however
is the strange power you manifested
during the battle with which you're able
to defeat the
stains the power May well be the key to
saving our world from
Annihilation according to the heroes the
power came to them like a forgotten
memory when they spoke the word reel
H but once they used it to Route the
stain horse it seems that the power
vanished Without a
Trace Orin wait oh Orin or did I talk to
Orin I can't remember so what are we
supposed to do the next time the stains
attack revelation we must uncover the
secrets of this phenomenon if we are
able I to Prevail against the
Calamity many questions remain but thing
is certain the kingdom of theal still
stands today thanks to you y me here
here here here here so heres I asked of
you once more will you lend us your
strength to save the Bessel from ruin I
guess I guess marvelous on behalf of all
the best friends I thank you you're
welcome we are blessed to have your
eight kind Heroes allow me to introduce
the four Great guilds which are
responsible for ensuring the Kingdom's
peace and
prosperity The Haven for the Curious
where knowledge and creativity are
valued above all Scarlet one knowledge
and creativity okay soela the home for
Glory Seekers with ambition and vision
where closest allies become fiercest
Rivals of Amber coin I ambition ambition
yeah the sanct of healing where the
spirit of empathy and devotion drives
the seruan
cup the beacon of the righteous and
loyal where great threats are faced with
even greater courage J sword sword huh
one of these guilds will become your
home during your time
here
[Music]
Guild oh Beyond the Door lies a room of
Truth the will of your ancestors shall
decide your
kill ruus fear not introspection is a
vital step to the road to Enlightenment
excels you as I always say even higher
time to roll the dice being seeing you
some of you at the Amber coin okay let's
save the world together so last St we
this okay okay oh oh oh oh
oh I save the world yeah
world the dice oh step on the platform
and receive the will of the
[Music]
ancestor I miss the raising Curr of the
heart seek the peaceful seruan flow
theing of the
heart J SW by
Dawn the coke Dawn the cloak Dawn the
cloak did I Dawn it Dawn the cloak how
do I Dawn the
cloak how do I do the
cloak D the cloak D the
[Music]
cloak right cck right
cooking hey
hey
inventory inventory
now
[Music]
hi e
button
it put it on body eat and then put it on
body okay armed with an unwavering will
seek to defend the soul of
Jade aing magic
[Music]
recollection
okay speak to your Guild Master oh
excuse me
oh the
blue I like mine better
[Music]
Elizabeth yes I'm
elizabth enemy
know an
[Music]
enemy I guess I I got to pick a name
hold on let me ask voes in my head
what's a good name you don't know your
[Music]
names are you also part of the Jade
sword and you
are Fu waa I see I see and you oh what's
your
name John Watson John Watson John
[Music]
I see John Watson is it one
name all of you I met that's a big knife
oh it's not a knife it's called a scythe
hi Callie has a big S
farmer uh farmer no I think Reaper so
yeah farmer but farmer of souls maybe a
sweaty Reaper sweaty hey I'm not sweaty
please cut it out
oh you always have really long
fingernails you they're perfect for
ripping into shreds oh wow oh I see so
they are your weapon I won't use
them
what I
dock oh it won't use again oh
[Music]
I that was a big sound
and this is Jonathan
uh this is your
weapon bubble blower or something who
are you going to hurt with that a bubble
uh I can smack people in the
head I
will
Heen it looks bloody I see and your name
is Reaper no my name is Mory K but you
can call me car that's what the bone
people in in my chat say the Kia people
yeah that's what they say Ka people stay
back though
why I'm I'm soft I'm
fuzzy should we talk to them
huh imagine it does once no never ceases
to M me but wa wa wa my not Skarlet
One D over any
challenge that was
cool where's be this yeah I have you
guys on my team are so
powerful
together you are also powerful
Jonathan the J
sword oh Arena
coordinator ah you can challenge your
friends to walk duels here at the arena
I don't want to fight
yet might be fun
could be T our strength against each
other very true we could we could
[Music]
train I suppose we're all in the same
since we're all here in okay we're going
to fight the stains yeah save the
world bestowed upon me the Jade sword oh
we have to do Quest together imagine
that is why you here too is Quest bo uh
yes uh kind of weird why would maybe uh
completed uh maybe they ran out green
swords maybe that is why I mean red
quite suits me I
think I guess if it was green it might
be
like look at that look at that look at
me you look
[Music]
nice this is our
home we live together now don't watch
Callie Elizabeth FL yes we live together
we live here this is our home yeah do we
have like a a place to rest maybe this
it's our home
wow wow where are the beds
though Quest boy
right AR
[Music]
run oh
H what's this way a big
door oh it's a
wall just the wall where did everybody
go
huh huh wait wait wait wait wait don't
leave me on my own don't leave me on my
own don't leave me don't leave me your
don't leave
me Elizabeth
[Music]
don't leave me I don't want to be on my
own I don't know what's wrong but I
don't I don't like it it makes me
upset do not worry Fair puppy I shall
protect you it hurts my tummy don't
leave
[Music]
me I will not leave you alone you won't
you just did
though oh you only but a few steps away
I don't want to be I want to be by your
side
okay okay here on out I will promise you
I will remain by your side yeah
[Music]
byebye okay what it's Ming wait where's
colie you find the oh do we find the
quest board I don't
know
best I can be a sheld if you want me too
I I don't have a shield yet so I might
come to depend on you bye good thing
that I have these guys with I do
[Music]
directions hi hi
hi what's his name
Ed
Ed I speak
Lees yeah oh this looks like a quest
board a good eye you have what is your
name sweet one
you can
[Music]
fly you got nails
too it's about how you use it of
course has been
kidnapped I've never felt special in my
entire
life why
okay
okay I thought he asked what color are
you so Jonathan you have spoken to
the okay
yeah tired of his prattle huh Quest away
okay quest
Quest off you go
now complete the side quest and then
speak speak to the quest
master I must go back to our Guild and
speak to the Guild
Master complete the side quest and then
speak to the quest Master
oh one are these the side
[Music]
quests this here looks like aect
job complete the
I don't know what the side quest where
is the side quest we need to go to side
quest I know I keep on looking to the
side of the board of
quest guess this is
[Music]
it I accepted it materials
as here as the guild Masters oh okay we
accepted the quest
[Music]
maybe we should go on the quest together
best
[Music]
of this looks like the perfect job best
of Lu
[Music]
Scarlet were we able to KCK out that can
I join the party Elizabeth
go
Elizabeth
Elizabeth don't leave
me don't leave
[Music]
you will leave me right Elizabeth left
me how did you get
a to the
party everyone is invited to my
party oh invited except except how do I
accept AA if you press T and then type
accept
I think
from it says you're in my party oh oh
yeah we can start a voice group that's a
good
[Music]
idea instead of typing accept you click
on accept is my how do I click on it how
do you click on it oh press T and then
hover over press
[Music]
it thank you Revelation a new revelation
Revelation our I want a horse
I shall be back
away why do I get a horse I don't know
but we can figure that do I have a horse
speed summoning
egg I got a
horse is he
cool is my horse cool how' you get that
he was in an egg he's a horse born from
an egg yes I have one too
wait for they're
fast egg horse wow that's frightening
[Music]
Steed how do we get off the
horse that's a great question shift
shift okay
hor voice oh wait every time I get a
different color
horse horse
get hor
hor I know you can get a different voice
until you're happy with the
color okay I guess I'll go with this
horse oh he changed color
now oh that was
cute how
I how do I go
name H
this way how do I go name do we do I not
need to accept a Quest from the board or
that we are I wonder because we all
accepted the
quest maybe you should go ahead and
accept the quest just in
case is
that I'm to turn
off I can't I cannot it opens up Social
menu for
train at the smiy
my master says we're running low on raw
materials
okay ah Quest accepted okay let's go to
the Smithy then yes right where is that
where we go um who's the one with the
map it's not
me yeah
map yeah I think John Watson was the one
with the map well we shall Venture forth
and
see leads us yes where is Jonathan
joh joh
want
[Music]
Jonathan let me see I can find over here
there's John
Watson you guys disappeared he went so
fast the horses are fast H oh here let's
put away the horse is this the
Smithy hello little guy I may look scary
but I'm chill you saw the quest yeah you
saw the quest I saw the quest an oak log
10 oak
logs okay okay 10 oak logs sure yes I
see oh we got 100 coins just for talking
to this I like getting money for talking
cool wow easiest cash I
ever Rich I'm sorry s do not worry about
the horse that just appeared in your
face what's this what's this what's
what's
this what' you find a
stook oh I used my claws whoa what does
that do you cannot use the enchantment
table right now I like it though it want
it wants to talk to me but I want to use
it I like
hello people scare big crowds
Jonathan I think me and Jonathan are
going to be good friends
then oh all right shall we go to the
forest to do
some that does look like the
exit where we
go what go to another location yes oh
yes oh yes oh oh oh we're outside now no
no I don't want to go to another
location now I'm
oh there enemies enemies enemies oh
boy was this correct oh
gosh use this he cries he
cries oh I got coins I got coins for
killing stuff I
like not sure I like the way they they
cry I get coins for killing stuff I get
coins the lands of the stain
the co you
no destroy the stains clean the stains
clean them yes we should not have
[Music]
stains yeah get get some
exp are we getting exp oh I guess we
need oh right oh my super attack is
powering up I
[Music]
think do it is it Oak is it Oak hey
you taste my claws yeah is that
good was tasty yeah it was tasty good
good
[Music]
good oh yeah I totally forgot about that
supposed to be what I need there is a
cool down yeah are these what I need
[Music]
wait am I being
attacked am I being attacked yeah I got
logs
yeah sword a tree these trees seem to
grow back very fast Fair
Maiden
tree I don't know where the logs are are
we getting
logs oh gosh he scared me what the
heck look out for him look out for him
let go go go go I got him it's
[Music]
okay the tree has consumed
me had consumed
you that's
[Music]
dangerous I will take the one the tree
will consume you be careful oh no
[Music]
okay I'm going to use my horse I'm going
to use my
horse 13 logs so I'm done get the logs I
only have five logs yeah I'm how do I
know how many logs I have oh if you e
you can check E I have nine I need one
more oh thank you he's not dead I'll
make him
dead what the
heck a now I'm dead they are strong
too are they strong or are we weak
time oh
my yeah get
them I really could use some
food right
F I got the L care about the stain
growing back I got the L
maybe use the sword while sc's on cool
down Scythe is still stronger I
feel done oh no what I'm sorry them all
at we well together I got
theall very nice
job well I I have 10 I have 10 to yes
where time
let's go finish this Quest
okay oh and go another
location wonderful
okay wait who is the to top
top to
top
to Hello whoa cool swords
is this the
Smithy
yeah I can't get through the door there
we
go great you brought the logs yeah oh
you want the master completed craft the
pickaxe at the
Smithy the way pickaxe at the Smithy
[Music]
I'm sorry about
the
hi hi hi
hi
[Music]
crafting I don't know party M this one
oh but you need a
certain planks into
sticks what do I
do um H oh oh oh maybe I can make the
sticks myself
now we can craft them from
[Music]
inventory did I make it
suppos
to what are we supposed to
make you bring over 10 oak logs there's
a bunch of trees not far outside the
town that you can
chop am I suppos to
make all right make a stick make a stick
okay uh well I have a crafting table if
we would wish crafting table you can
also do it in your inventory can you
well that's not a stick yeah make planks
first and then oh planks
first okay plank I made a plank I a
plank
[Music]
PL wow so they wanted us to make the the
axe and the shovel and
and does he want the
planks and sticks and stick you can make
sticks in your inventory by using two
planks yeah just stack them on top of
each other like one on top one on the
[Music]
bottom I don't think I can fight again
until I have something to eat though we
should definitely eat
something Tommy stinks I me stinks
they're very excited about making sticks
okay well they are puppies
[Music]
dogs do I I am a member of J after all
what does he
want does he
want well I don't know about my place I
like my pickaxe he wants the
pickaxe I gave him the
pickaxe that one's very oh I made
it wonder if she's alone did I do it I
hope we can be friends why do I
want craft the wooden pickaxe did I buy
it bought I SP qu to bought
it oh no I didn't want to spend my money
it's okay I also bought one I thought I
was making it what a scam he does it on
purpose H scam I think it is I feel like
you can actually use
it maybe we can make one how do I make
the pickaxe I have a pickax but when I
to this
maybe
not uh yes it seems we
cannot you got to buy things I have to
BU like normal hum I don't I'm
[Music]
not how I make the pickax should we
should we should we come back another
time to get the coins huh one second one
second the side quest and speak to the
quest master craft a wooden
pickaxe
cobone wait how do I make a
pickaxe you can't make one you have to
buy
one I mean mine was made immed have the
materals oh this is say
completed it says completed
[Music]
especially if you need coins them
to everybody have their
pickaxe
yes oh one second FL need
these how do I drop them oh you have to
trade
oh yeah make sure that you trade with
the the uh I sent a trading request
trade I thought we had to buy from him
we have to trade too yeah it's both you
trade your
coins so think about it every time you
buy something at the store you are
conducting a trade locked in a
TR
think I think okay good
byebye I have low confidence and self
we'll check with the quest but maybe we
need do another okay okay shall we
[Music]
go hello we did your quest
H off the quest look like the perfect
job for you best of luck off you go okay
I think we also need to collect
Cobblestone now
oh wait
what we need to collect Cobblestone oh I
don't it's not huh I don't think I
finished it either it's showing me a
blank page
so that's why we need that's why we need
the pickaxes got I don't think I
finished
it this John Watson character is
definitely the smart one
help help help I'm not I'm not done
you're not done talk to the quest master
I talked to him he just telling me to go
we're going to go get cobblestone no not
yet what happened you know pick okay I
don't know what's
wrong I have traded oh hello
hello I I'm supposed to get cobblestone
now no wait I still make AIG
puppies Fair puppies have
you have you been asked to get
cobblestone
no you have
not so you
Apprentice wait no he doesn't oh oh oh
speak to the blacksmith Apprentice oh
okay okay okay okay he gives me a new
Quest I've created the wooden pickaxe
yeah so it's time to go get cobblestone
okay I think
so I think so are you okay now fuzzy one
I think so I don't know though brandish
your pickaxe and let us see oh pickaxe
that's my
hor um now swing it from side to side
side side to side pickaxe
pickaxe pickaxe that's that's an
axe that is an ax it's a different
weapon of mass destruction what that is
an axe it is a different
weapon that is not one you pick your for
accept myquest quite
foul quite fou oh I don't he that but
you're not have to
pickaxe is it in your inventory I had
one but then it didn't work one
second there you
go what I haven't finished the yet you
have to talk to follow C to finish the
follow me follow
me follow
me H talk to
him not the horse get out the horse
get
him here all
right what do we
need come come here follow us talk to
talk to the
[Music]
blacksmith talk to him uh talk to my M
his
wees W you have a wooden
pickaxe fast here some materials use and
a bit of coin to show my excuse me who's
doing
that that
one wait John wson hey i' heard of your
kind before
johnon excuse me are you picking a fight
you must Spa if you would like to SP you
must come over to the Jade sword area
Okay g gone right know she doesn't have
enough walk I was getting excited I
thought they knew were going to
yeah some people can can talk a lot at s
word but they can't take
it I'm ready to mine whatever you guys
are is having issues I'm sorry oh that's
okay does have materials by chance she
can't open the trade box oh she can't
open it right do you know how to open
the trade box you should just right uh
let's see right click when you talk to
the quest or the blacksmith
person one the smiy where where you I
thought I heard a bow bow from
afar where is
she is guys the quest isn't done yet we
have to go get
cobblestone if you have I think it's
fine we just just go get
cobblestone I have I have
the what he will accept the stuff oh so
with the oak logs then you make Oak
planks
I did you buy it from
him you have the Pix my master you
should be able to make your stone tools
give
it yeah come talk to him okay come talk
to him
[Music]
Cobblestone and sticks okay I will to
them oh I
see oh I see now it makes sense from now
on when you find new material by here
and talk to my M the more different
materials you find the more things
you'll be able to
make now it's completed but my master
will make you some cool
stuff yeah I already got the stuff from
him
[Music]
I wonder what would suit you better
bring 10 Cobblestone next and probably
find some lying around in the same your
own planks did you buy did you buy it
from him and talk talk to the The
Apprentice again yeah you got to keep
talking to him until he mentions
Cobblestone talk to The Apprentice again
complete gain 50 exp talk to the
apprentices here him here I see figured
it out
nice thank you bone
people
people the princess is more important
pickax okay
Cobblestone yeah see your pickax let me
see that thing that's
no that's not a pickaxe it's a
horse can hardly tell the differ unless
the horse's name is pickaxe we're not
leaving until we see your pickaxe so the
pickaxe we not leaving until you show us
your pickax young
lady all right we're ready let's go get
okay the horses are so
fast
hor what you doing this hey is this we
got to Beware of the enemies though
because I haven't had a meal in a long
time okay oh I'll get off my horse I'll
protect you
seems like it isn't working oh that
stuff can't be
broken away with me ouch I thought you
died
already ouch they're they they're ging
up on me it doesn't up they up
[Music]
me get away get away get away
okay now I'll use my
pickaxe okay oo lots and lots of cobbly
stone how much cobbly Stone do we
need I think probably 10 once again 10
what the
heck we are
efficient have the stain as our Noble
Steed it is very
cute I do not like it when it cries nice
gosh how much do I have now 25 that's a
lot of not is it not right what's cob
stone that cob
Stone what why is Cobo
Stone it's it's war cry Jonathan it is
but it's war cry think of it that way
trying to attack us enemy okay I thought
it'd be a special one it was not the
special
one oh I got it see I knew that rabbit
was evil a
[Music]
rabbit okay horse
CL I'm good with the Cobblestone now oh
nice wait if I can I attack someone with
my horse
you no I
can't as long as I know how to love I
know I will stay alive I don't know why
that came to
mind maybe maybe a song that you heard a
long time ago first time oh all the
enemies are really gang up on us do we
want to go I'm going to go back
okay danger it's way too dangerous yeah
we got the Cobblestone though didn't we
yeah wait it says please wait for me oh
no it went away no waiting we're
good one she's probably still fighting
you seems to really like fighting oh no
not oh do you have do you have the about
the
Cobblestone okay that's what I got I got
coin completed objective material St
sword I think we completed the
[Music]
quest I go inside on my
horse I'm going to go
make let's wait for John
Watson John
Watson that's what a oh my
[Music]
go you seem to want to have a fight with
everyone you come across okay
oh do I look cool like
this thus far we have known each other
you have always seemed
cool did you guys turn in your quest
yeah oh wait no not the quest we have to
go to the quest board still oh okay you
talk to The Apprentice right
yeah cool then I guess let's go Quest
master
yes yes okay Quest done I feel pretty
good about about how fast we've been
going so you've gone and finished the
quest yeah land the help to the common
FK have a look around we can stop buy
and help to Common
F yeah yeah some food I could go for a
money
yeah okay so cute the item shop there's
a bit of a coin to get you started oh
cool 500 coins we're rich why he's very
shopkeeper that's nice I can retire now
on this yeah yeah we don't even have to
keep doing this
anymore
no is there another Quest we have the
shopkeeper we have to talk to next speak
to shopkeeper yeah that's true maybe we
should do that
first wait
where's where' she go
oh red one oh this is no oh that's a
different red
one we going that's a
one Lo
red H yes I I yes you got the M another
Quest got go to the shopkeeper but it
has to be after you've submitted the
quest Quest board then we're going to
get oh I see this new
[Music]
money B
no oh supposed to
[Music]
help
no did you pick up another Quest We Do
oopsie oh that's okay can you decline it
after accepting
it I was going to pick it up after
visiting the shop I want to buy bread
from
[Music]
him okay maybe the shopkeeper has
something for us though I'm a little
confused because it just gave me the
option of getting another Quest unless
it's oh the quest Master sorry why do
you have a ra port
sh I'm so proud of you go talk to the
quest leader
now we
waiting
hello hello hello there F my my mind was
up in the F and the fluff in the skies
oh FY that's
500 my name
is 500 smaron just did you get the 500
smackaroonies what a bit got the 500
smacko I'm rich
yeah have we got the
500 wait wait wait have we got 500 500
what 500 what
Co there where he
[Music]
go way on
again where you oh I'm on my own I'm
lost I'm lost excuse me small one stay
away from my guild
[Music]
member is this the
shop excuse me what are we doing excuse
me excuse excuse me
excuse is this the shoper talking to my
guild member
first that my guild member wanted to
hurt the king my gu member would never
want to hurt the king we are part with
the J sword salt Ander we are loyal wait
wait wait we can buy sweet vinyls at the
shop do records your father's a hamster
your mother of fire drop by here if you
ever want to listen to some sicks we
have tracks that are fire finals at the
shop he the other dope records we have
the fin scavenger Market scavenger
Market vinyls I don't know tenda if you
like to order something ask the barid
over this nice cut of stey some salt and
a pepper put it on a
[Music]
grill
Vis instant health I like that I'll get
one of those please I am from wait wait
wait what you guess 100 coins that's
expensive you stealing their
oven dang we should have slain some meat
outside Amber you are correct you are
correct I am from Amber yes Miss yes
disgusting I am from that
place where is the shopkeep disgusting
yes Amber is
disgusting do
not here not Amber I agree what a your H
do not shush me Fair ma
or else I will shush you in a moment
don't I know a way to shush you marus
and Brutus
Brutus maybe there's still
hope maybe there
maybe but I mean have you seen who's
here to save the
day will bring back P to
Li wait is the
shopkeeper it looks like there's just a
bar maid selling potions where's the
shopkeeper I
love my Stu not their
stuff I wanted to take their
stuff May that's illegal I want to take
their stuff but it was my stuff oh my
God
whoops she's crazy oh shop shop shop
oh his humble little
shop okay select what you want to buy
makes sense maybe it's not this one make
sure I have enough coin I have 700 80
Brave hero thank you for saving this
town in all of our Lives welcome to my
humble little shop on my body yeah sure
what do you what have you s i me I'll
show you I in stock isn't that easy yeah
I'm afraid I can't just give everything
for free make sure you have enough coin
okay pleas stop byy if you ever need
anything or if you just want to keep me
company I don't think I'll be stopping
by to do that Gardens children are
tending to the gardens
are they okay to work like that remember
to take care of the best child in the
gardens visiting the GU halls ofs for
instance each of them has an activity
you can participate in speak to the
child jealous of us I'll cut you
[Music]
down allies to stretch
further sometimes I feel like I could
stretch further too h Overjoyed to meet
a real hero such as
yourself sounds cool we have to go talk
to a child children is
O can I get something to
eat I know I want something to eat too's
so hungry maybe should
bimo
bimo here's an idea what if we go
hunting out instead outside and bring
the back instant Health there is an
instant Health there
is I was thinking maybe I bought
something have you seen what this barid
sells it is is amazing potion she sells
inant house so I bought
that oh well done I got
strength did you find the shop yeah the
shopkeeper is outside it makes sense H
together shall we I saw a bunch of them
out there y yeah he's here I wonder if
we have AER chest that we can store our
food in a chest in here I tried to steal
oh oh that's probably not a good idea
don't I'm sure I thought they had stuff
but then
I huh yeah they might kick us from the
kingdom to be honest huh but we're here
to protect them taking a couple things
is probably okay
[Music]
yeah probably continuing the
quest boy do we want to go to the the
child I mean do you think there will be
food there
maybe there will be food there Wow Let's
Go
small
oh where's the where did you want to go
Cy I I apologize let's go to the
gardens yes lead the way wish I had a
map to know where they are Watson was
the map holder oh I have a map but I'm
good at looking at it do we not oh yeah
I me that is
true I have to pull it out let me grab
it saving this town welcome to my shop
talk to the shopkeeper we
did what can we get what can we get all
right the child is in the garden the
child is
working why are they making them work in
the gardens it's kind
of I was
wondering why do have
to are you looking for the child so seem
a little far removed don't you like this
behind the
blacksmith are you looking for the
child oh you see the child blackith you
guys I'll follow who
then it feels
wrong I fallowing
FL oh no wait what hey found the same
way a to I'm
embarrassed you think they have any
venies here
oh all the best what the what the heck
is hurting me berries I think I hurt a
lot now golly you're one of the heroes
boy this must be my lucky day boss what
I could to die Gardens you're free to
come and use them whenever you like use
them for what child Aces is it doob is
to keep an eye on scare away birds and
stuff let me know if you need more one
of the heroes boy this is my lucky day
is that what the speak also
build build whatever you like
[Music]
bu I can't tell you a secret did you
know there's a place called The
[Music]
Pit you want to do building
secret did you know there's a place pit
is people I don't care what your mom say
kids aren't allowed to go but I can hear
F thank you I don't care about Mom
H hope to see you again okay sneak IED
to sneak the lested child to the pit
you're
hero what okay oh gosh child is speaking
to you
bread no I didn't get any bread I would
have loved to have some bread how did
you get bread y kid where's my bread huh
excuse
me can I have bread please someone El I
have more bread bread too I did I did
threatening violence does work this is
good you hit the child and got
bread do you see
this you see this look it look it look
it look it watch watch watch watch
watch I give you head child on it's the
best the best salad making skills ever
look look look look
look is it that
easy you don't see
anything what are you doing are you
destroying the bushes I thought we were
making a
salad wait was it really okay okay wait
you're getting the berries
salades what the
heck hey did someone take my berries I
don't get any berries I just get
infinite
salad
scavenger I want infinite I want berries
not infinite
salad hey the Sal's good for you viol
yeah maybe this isn't a great idea I'll
Attack fun it does seem kind of
fun right click it maybe it needs to not
be a
sword maybe my SI you right cck it is
normal this is definitely a
[Music]
harvester that's really
funny I like that I feel a little
silly ouch ouch
ouch they gave us the bread so that we
can get hurt by the bushes
huh I guess
so bushes are dangerous this is a
dangerous Garden huh yeah we all got to
be on our guard yeah guard in the
garden oh
oh are you guys being called Away by
something us do you want to try and go
to the pit first let's go to the pit
yeah Mom can't go there or was it the
child can't go there
okay oh no
Steve yes on
Horseback where's the pit I don't know
where we're going I think the pit is the
the Amber coin area I'm pretty
sure does it not on mine let's see I'll
pull it up follow me
I'm
following oh that's that's a
tile
Callie I think you
are this way here
right oh that's money doesn't look like
a pit looks like a mansion a super rich
person
mansion is this the pit how would they
call it the
[Music]
pit what ooh bookie here is it for
racing oh
hello got the game for you P dor
oh a new face I'm a new face I am a new
face yeah I'm a hero who are you this
guy want to get rich yeah we are
heroes I think don't go
right
nothing get rich you us to run with the
de sword that's usy why would he what is
good you can buy things you with money I
can't understand what he's saying but
it's
okay used to run with the Jade sword for
I joined the Amber we party
and yeah when
the some stains they also taught us how
to work as a team ex a CO
just point yourself at your mate add to
the party oh come here and play a around
or two to get money now you can
adventure together swap items and
coins see told you it was useful didn't
I you'll thank me for it when you're
adventuring oh be a lot easier point is
all I'm saying k Master oh don't
WatchON you appeared again hello come
down here to the pit and play around or
two
okay walking out of here pen don't worry
about it is this are they asking us to
do something
shady I don't know he said
[Music]
hey exp the
town I don't know fi Master wishes to
speak with you please meet him at the
Jade sword Guild
Hall that's where we're from right yeah
Jade
sword we know where to go then
what I don't
we're going to the Jade sword area V is
that
vus yeah oh oh those are you sure the
sharks can drown now that seems
confusing drown not something that
should happen to go I must go my own
path for a moment oh okay Elizabeth you
said you'd stay by my side forever
though maybe she's just a bit of a loner
I can kind of
relate I guess
but you guys I like hanging out with you
guys I don't know where I'm going are
you sure you do follow me okay I know
where we're going I don't know are was
going back to the same
place here no not here oh
gosh here
here no this is Quest Master wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait
wait I'm lost I'm lost
don't want to stay by my
side
[Music]
okay oh
no oh
[Music]
Callie if I go too far I can't see you
anymore honestly not the worst place to
wash up Eide where is up the stairs
oh no oh no oh no oh no
[Music]
no I'm lost I'm
lost I can't go in
there Hi H I'm stuck I can't go
there I'm lost
help
what what help
help I'm
lost it's somewhere down the stairs wait
wait you oh I I found you ruin I'm found
yeah wa over they observe from the ruin
of light reation used to repel the
staining
where SC from are already St for further
investigation I asked that you might
join it join them there go forth with
Valor no problem cool exit the town
headed the planes and speak to hus of
the Jade
sword so that's the next Quest Shen
suddenly find yourself another wood yes
yes I am shaken yes okay powers of
Revelation
okay
[Music]
yeah oh you guys are going away on a
different Journey
[Music]
huh okay well let's adventure together
when you guys come back shall
we well take
care Jade sword Jade sword
together trespass get out of
here with you we'll take you
[Music]