aah
[Music]
la
n
[Music]
la
for
[Music]
la
a
[Music]
la
a
[Music]
why are you
gayan what what does the AI description
say what does it
say what does it say
why are you
frog so do me so do
me no I didn't watch it again but you
guys I saw one person in the chat asking
me why are you gay and then I answered
to that person why are you gay
who is gay you are gay I am not gay no
one is gay you are
gay good
stuff wait is this ah wait I
disconnected it again oh no Mama Mia
wait wait
[Music]
okay
okay come on turn on it's on Yoo yippe
balers gay
B is
G
why why is B gay who is
B thank you
sorry sorry if people don't know it's a
meme it's a meme but it's also
reality aarion oh yeah he's G
sorry sorry sorry
sorry you think everybody knows I didn't
know until recently so I would have to
assume that you know not everybody
knows hello controllers please thank
you
no ah no now I can hear I thought I
wasn't hearing properly
yeah yeah yeah yeah after I watch I
watched like so many John Oliver like
episodes uh but I have never seen that
one I think but it was recommended to me
after I watched the full interview so I
was like oh my God crossover let's
go
yeah but the more you watch the
interview the more you realize the
interviewer
isn't like that that evil as it may seem
if you just watch the short version the
just the
clips um like and eventually he kind of
tries to help so I don't know but I
don't know I don't know what his real um
uh ideals and opinions are who knows I
mean oh well that's a long time ago
maybe by now he's maybe by now he's gay
uh
yeah he just wanted to know who was g to
make sure to to Really set everything
clear no
misunderstandings they got
[Laughter]
him
okay
uh my neck hurts I just got a massage
like two days
ago H but yeah my neck hurts a
lot massage was was pretty decent though
oh H Massage was nice because like
sometimes in some in some massage places
they like put your feet into like a
little foot bath first a hot bath and
then wash your feet or whatever
sometimes but um this one kind of had
that too but they had like this whole
almost like a
bar okay it's not a bar but it's like
bar
counters with like so many separate
little bathtubs for your
feet uh was was actually uh really
nicely set up and kind of
cool and you can just like chill
there and when you look outside you see
like cars and people going by a lot of
them yeah yeah yeah and you sit down
there and you get your
feet
wet time somebody to stand on you again
I don't know I I I I was so scared when
she said I'm going to stand on you now
is that okay I was
like well I hope this is going to go
well but she did it very differently she
didn't really seem to do it the same way
as they did it to me in
Thailand I don't know what exactly she
was trying to
do but generally the massage was fine
so
um let me check one
thing
Twitter
um out of context takik has already
posted my uh chat message Chat messages
always always dangerous people will use
them and out of context they will like
post them everywhere and it will seem
really
confusing really confusing but uh that's
funny it's
okay uh let me let
me okay so I woke up today to as always
a lot of messages and one of them was
really
long by
only it seems she has completed a
me a challenge of sending a love letter
so to say to a member and she chose
me now I'm thinking of reading this
before we get too
deep let me ah okay I just don't want
this to go away
um so I will I will read this now I
don't know if she I think she did this
on stream I don't know if she read it
out loud on stream but or did you choose
everyone no I think it's for me right
just for
me just for me so let's read ol's
message of love to me I haven't read it
yet so let's
go hello Hello Ki Senpai I'm writing
this to you today to clear a box from
the whole that's the has me bingo card
but honestly I've also been meaning to
send you something like this for a while
now and I'm so happy that whole life
Bingo finally gave me the push for me to
actually make you this cuz I've been
chickening out and remaking my love Ess
for you for a while now because I'm
always too scared that you'll think I'm
gross or just doing this for the sake of
content so well but now you are doing
this for the sake of content because
you're doing it for the bingo card as
you said yourself
but okay so to start off I just wanted
to say that I love
you I love you so much and I will always
do my best to help and support you in
ways that I'm capable
of if you were to tell me you were
thirsty I'll defy the laws of Earth and
gravity itself and fly myself to Neptune
to collect the freshest spring of water
then filter the dirty molecules and
destroy the physics of the water itself
making it waterier than ever just so
that you don't choke if you were to
drink
it then put it in the diamond Fus to
keep the drink nice and chill while
running back to Earth while I collect
Stars well she was not at Earth yet when
she was filtering the water she did all
of that in Neptune
[Music]
damn running back to Earth while I
collect stars and turn them into shiny
bouquets to decorate said fos serve it
to you in the champagne glass glass made
of all yaga's hopes and dreams decorated
with a small umbrella and a swirly
takanashi Fe straw for you to
drink what would that look like that is
if fate were to let me you're one of the
most honest upfront
sincere ambitious bewitching alluring
captivating tenacious this just looks
like a list of of
words amicable talented confident and
inspiring gorgeous beautiful prettiest
sexiest person I've ever met and that's
just scratching the surface though you
have your insecurities and doubt
yourself from time to time I can assure
you that you none of those negative
things that you have fought yourself to
be only cute you're basically the
perfect Idol and you always strive to be
better even though you're already the
best to put it simply you your own
magnum opus
bro what whoa I hope you have never ever
have to think uh that you're lesser than
anyone because you're already de great
takana I've mentioned all those
objectives earlier but I refrained
myself from typing the word kind because
that would make for a whole new
paragraph I Remember by the way this is
all one paragraph she has not used the
button to make a new paragraph a single
time I remember like it was yesterday it
was my third an and I was playing
Minecraft while being depresso espresso
and questioning my whole existence about
being a whole life member I remember
this since frankly during the time I
couldn't see myself as an equal to
everyone else but then you came and DM
me asking for a call even though it
wasn't a to M and you were there to slap
me with affection and made me get my
[\h__\h] back together yeah as you should as
you should ol you were there when I
needed to hear the words of emotion
affirmation the most and that meant so
much to to me if you weren't there I'd
probably break down on stream for the
whole world to see and ever since then I
try to remember your words when I feel
uh difficult and it gets me back to my
feet K Sena you're not just a Oshi
you're my hero I know my love seems like
a gimmick that I look like I'm just
doing for the sake of content but the
things I'm writing down are true and I
truly admire you for who you are and
what you do
a she's so sweet
I I wish I could like hug her right now
and say thank you in
person but there is oceans in between us
separating us only why why don't you get
rid of the ocean for me
huh OE yeah that's nice nice to receive
something like
that oh hello welcome to the dram kittyy
that was very very
long Ollie Ollie thank
you I want to send her one
back oh
man ah okay that was
wholesome that was sweet
[Music]
I really do think that Ollie I said it
back then I think but I really think
she's
like one of the best additions to whole
life and very very very unique and
entertaining and fun and like she always
adds some some energy that no one else
can bring to a group when she's with a
group and I think you know like that's
always something great to have
like you know you don't like when she's
around you don't really have to try to
make it entertaining it's like easy to
make something entertaining when she's
around yeah she always works so hard and
tries her best and I love that about her
yeah she yeah she's an ultimate hype
woman she's so sweet and supportive
like this kind of support that she
brought since day one and the love the
unconditional
love I think yeah it's just like anybody
any of the members like when they hear
that I think that alone is always
something nice to hear and and be told
when you're told like I love you so much
Senpai you're the best you're the best
like okay maybe sometimes it might seem
a little bit like oh she's saying that
everybody but she really genuinely loves
whole life and wants to support
everybody and that's so sweet and and I
feel like sharing so much love is
something we we need more
of like sharing it so openly and
directly I feel like we need more of
that not just in whole life but like
generally in the
world such positive people bringing
positivity into the room
yeah not being shy of doing that yeah
like yeah why are you okay and we need
more of
[Laughter]
[Music]
that so this okay
today we're going to continue Luigi's
Mansion 2 it's
11:20 a.m. for
me and I have almost the whole day until
I need to go for dinner although I
haven't decided yet where we're going to
dinner and I think the person is
probably relying on me to decide where
to
go so uh when she answers me what kind
of food she wants might have to ask uh
jenma
to find me a restaurant cuz I'm
busy which which whole life remember I'm
going to write it I didn't think about
that yet but there's so there's a couple
I would want to write something
to
yeah
but I think I think I know who I'm going
to write it
to but Ollie might just get you know an
extra one oh viewers are expressing
their gratitude for all's kind words and
encouragement they are responding with
messages of Love support and
encouragement and many are suggesting to
visit her
[Music]
yeah
I the problem is now like I'm so [\h__\h]
sick of traveling
and I think October is going to be like
the only month where I'm not traveling
and I don't want to change that at this
point
so not that not that Cali has any time
probably anyway
either um but yeah I I don't want to add
any more travel I think to my schedule
of this year I'm I'm like so [\h__\h] I'm
on I'm I feel the burnout coming not
just because of the traveling but
traveling is definitely a part of it it
it's it's reaching dangerous levels
right
now but I did dream about like I don't
know I think I was in Italy in my dream
or so some some kind of European beach
um for like 80% of my dream I was at
some beach doing weird things like
assembling furniture and then realizing
why did I do that I can't bring that
back home on my flight why did I just
assemble a whole [\h__\h]
closet
uh I don't know I don't I really don't
know not with that
attitude and then missing our flight and
blah blah blah but I do kind of want
another real chill vacation like you
know males but might just have to wait
for another Mal's vacation in like I
don't know January or so
again might just have to wait for that
again yeah World Tour and uh breaking
Dimensions is coming up in New
[Music]
York Bali do well yeah so I'm saying I
don't think Bali is going to happen this
year as much as I would like to go I
don't think it would be smart for me to
add another thing to the list because
then it would have to be October but I
want October to stay a month where I can
just stay at home with my cats and
stream normally but also rest and just
like not travel I don't want to get on a
airplane that I have to sit in for more
than 10
[Music]
hours I don't want that anymore and then
feel like guilty about you know missing
out on streaming uh and not creating
enough content and then having to catch
up before and after like doing the extra
amount of work to not feel guilty that's
not something I want to do in
[Music]
October yeah yeah yeah
so Kiana will be playing the game thank
you
yeah next
year next year for a real vacation where
I can chill at the beach and like really
just
relax perhaps males perhaps someone else
else some somewhere
else yes I'm still in Japan yes yes yes
are you getting horror games month of
October I don't know maybe one or two
but probably not the most Crazy
Ones all right let's do this guys let's
do this probably something that can
happen whenever you're feeling really a
Feeling all recovered yeah and ready for
it yeah I think so too I mean the
problem is like if we want to do it with
a lot of people we have to choose um a
time frame that works for a lot of
people and that's really difficult
um but might just have
to like make sacrifices somewhere and uh
uh
compromises y yum yum yum
I don't want to miss out on another like
Mal divs kind of vacation I got to do it
[Music]
again it's not even starting so late no
no
no okay guys Let's do let's go today
today I will I will do my best basting
some ghosts yeah
[Music]
you got dinner with a cute girl lat yep
that's true
yipp it's oui
time what you Lui um the new mansion
right wait that's
not that's the old mansion and that's
the that's the online thing no wait how
do I get to the new mansion are we not
going to the new mansion yet
[Music]
ah there we go we choose it from here
okay wait let me read that these
remarkable towers are built around a
colossal tree wo the original owners had
a liking for gardening and exotic plants
which are growing out of control oh oh
it's going to be like plant themed I
see probably similar to something that
we saw in um uh Lu Mansion free
too Forest Mansion mhm it's going to be
probably all like
overgrown a job for a plumber oh is
Mario coming the tower's Machinery isn't
active I'm guessing the ghost broke it
already let's
go Quest
is Quest is taking us to a new location
lady aren't you
excited he's like n no no no no
at least he's
honest come on where's your sent of
Adventure
son our work is right from done we need
to get a handle on these gold or who
knows how far they'll
spread and there's only one way to
fix if only we had a plumber yeah okay
I'm aware that Luigi is also a plumber I
know you see the haunted Towers feature
a complex water system that powers all
the
Machinery so the first thing on your
to-do list will be to check the
hydrogenerator send me
then let me find
out let's
go got to fix the water why don't I just
like go to Neptune and get the water
there like
OE no we got to do it this way we got to
do it this
way eh what bees Oh you mean from
plumber plumber I I know I know I guess
I know nothing you saying yeah I said it
wrong but um damn
it plumber plumber yeah yeah I've heard
plumber way more times than I
[Music]
plumber look at me hello look at me look
at
me look at me look at
me look at me look at me it's a twice
song of course of course my K-pop girl
is in the chat would know that oopsie my
aim I am still playing with the two
separated
joycons
so the controls are
janky janky
[Music]
janky
yeah I asked uh Gemma and she can bring
me one maybe for next time uh like the
the connection thing that connects to
joycons and makes it a proper
[Music]
controller there's a hole in the
tree he kicks thee rude poor tree don't
kick it honestly
like that would have hurt his leg
immensely I'm I'm surprised he didn't
scream out in
pain but okay
going
[Music]
in Luigi hates fauna even though they're
both green maybe he doesn't want like
green
um uh a green
rival maybe he wants to be the only
green in the
world that's why he sucks up the money
too hey yo what do I do with
[Music]
this how do I how do I shoot this by the
way like properly I know you can shoot
it wait now I kind of shot it but I
thought there was a way to like properly
aim it
[Music]
too oh well did you watch no I didn't
watch it I didn't watch it yet I was
kind kind of like waiting for dendle to
upload a reaction but I don't think he
did it yet I I would think he would
though
eventually I was hoping he would react
to it and I could watch his
[Music]
reaction well if you didn't if if you
w't do that even after my stream then
I'll just watch it on my
own wait wait wait wait no I'm too slow
my reaction time and the
controllers you can only aim at certain
op
[Music]
ah what is is this true oh what
[\h__\h] liquid water wait did I get him or
I'm confused I'm not sure I didn't
really see if I got him or not
okay so I'm kind
of
guessing the ball has to be shot
somewhere
um I feel like it has to do with the
with the wheel
but let's see if it lets me aim at it
though
no wait how did I just shoot it before
Oh not hold on wait can I not actually
ah yeah I can make it go
faster and what does that
do nothing oh oh there we
go
[Music]
yippee okay but I can't go up there it
was just to open it and get the money
it took a while I was close to giving
[Music]
up oh I can go into this room all right
nice
oh wait hey what he
left there's Liquid Gold down there too
and down there too
wa
okay I don't know what I'm doing I
thought that's how you do it
[Music]
no smart goes he looks exactly like that
emoji it's so
funny I got the
key I don't know what to
wear
but eventually oh oh oh oh what is that
stop I almost didn't get I almost didn't
get it in
time yippe
oh a one and a two and we all love
bamboo except for
you can we fight are we going to
fight wait he's certainly still in here
is he does he do the hiding ah ah wait
wait wait wait wait wait I
forgot wa
bamboo wait wait wait
wait I'm so
stupid ah did he go where'd he
go I [\h__\h] hate these controls right
now ah how do I do this
again oh there we go there we go I got
him H wait that's ah
so balloon
bamboo
cute we're doing it
again let me get the money
[Music]
first where'd he go
oh I feel so banned he's so
cute
a I don't think he does that like
fall um action in the other games does
he I don't remember him
like bouncing off everything in Lu's
Mansion
free not normally right
feel bad for him why what what happened
to him why did he get so
bouncy oh that's why I had to
go just stand right in front of this
MH in other Mario games you just destroy
them with stars
oh
Stars when I was first introduced all he
did was float towards you and if you
looked at him he covered his eyes oh
when you when the boo was first
introduced mhm M
mhm the hydrogenerator seems to be in
good condition so the water pump must be
closed why don't you check the water
supply on the
roof now why don't I do
that sounds like a perfect idea is the
door gone there why is it gone on the
left
side can you just like get rid of doors
while I'm still in the room
didn't I walk through that
door I thought that only kind of
happens when I'm
gone okay I think I wouldn't have been
able to go to the other for the other
doors right I guess the key was for
here aha
esy ghost claing to
pipe poison
frogs I watched a video about raising
those little dirt frogs not not raising
but like keeping
them uh and it apparently you know those
little dirt dirt tiny angry dirt frogs
the really tiny ones that look really
chubby but
tiny so they they are not supposed to be
meant uh supposed to be kept as uh pet
frogs but this one guy like all he does
is like keep frogs and do stuff with
them um make nice enclosures for them
and
stuff yeah the potato ones yeah
[Music]
what huh I can't proceed here can
I I don't think I
can yeah lot a lot of animals are not
supposed to be kept as pets M but
apparently they they are really hard to
be uh to keep as a pet because they're
really hard to like it's hard to make
them eat
food what he managed to do it it was
really interesting seeing those cute
tiny fat friendly shame
FR who the [\h__\h] was
[Music]
that you shook
me then I should have played this in
October then my once in in a year uh
horror
game what have been fulfilled
mama
mama no now it's happened three times
now I I know it's in here probably what
the [\h__\h] I'm not going to I know what
you're going to do I know what you're
going to do I I know what you going to
[Music]
do what the
hell okay wait I know I know this one
what shouldn't you get like bonked
shouldn't you Bonk yourself when you
like go towards me
[Music]
bro damn it
what oh I got him but I didn't
n oh oh wait he lost his stuff he did
lose hey hey what
the it can't St switching
position now there's two of
them they
[Music]
multip uhoh
uh-oh I'm not sure how I did it
before this is getting out of hand no
there's two of
[Music]
them you
suck okay got him got him got him got
him got
him
yeah need to try to get gold bars more
often I I I've I've I've I've um watched
like I don't pre-at it before I do it
but I I watched don't tend to play this
game like uh yesterday I watched the
archive of it the VOD um and saw how he
does things you know but uh I realized
uh like when you suck in two Gods two
Gods two ghosts at the same time for
example you get more gold and if you
do frog froggy waa friends actually no
froggy waa
foes um
yeah if you if you what was it if you
like you know there's like this this bar
when you suck you can like press a after
a little bit or you can wait and then
then you press a and then it's stronger
if you do that I guess you get more gold
and all that M Luigi's fighting Gods
yeah are we done with this room is this
okay I guess
so so I'll try to pay a little bit of
attention to that
oh oh there's something there a
door a door a dumble
[Music]
door and a
bat oh I got the
door I feel like that door isn't even on
the
map really
isn't
wow frogy wa fo these are evil evil
frogs red frogs are not nice um how do I
how do I get rid of these
Vines can I not
currently maybe it's not possible right
now is
it I think it might not be possible
okay this room is useless for now I
think I found the door too
early put a pin in
it finally able to I guess yeah I forgot
I'm wearing the the Frog cap right now
the Frog hoodie thingy forgot about
that I'm not exactly fing about
but I am embodying her a little bit I
guess how do you catch the the liqu with
gold it do I if I suck this up does it
actually count as getting
[Music]
money I don't think
so am I doing things
wrong how do you do
it Roi wa adjacent exactly what is these
what the do
is this how my garden is going to look
like when I come back
home
y can I fight
[Music]
them wait I probably have to do
something like
this oh the pump will
break what it's shaking up there but
it's not actually doing
anything oh it stopped shaking
anyway is this room a wait ah these
balls
[Music]
ah oh oh you like that oh that was fine
I thought I didn't get
you thought I actually didn't get
you n n n n
n you are the Oshi I'm glad that you
have only two oshis and and the other
one is basically me
[Music]
again it's just me it's all just me it's
the waa Universe the wa
verse that's how you do it that is
indeed how you do it wonder if there's
any other things to be collected here
no all my other she are just versions of
you beautiful I like
that what the
hell what is this a a flying
carpet what no do I
live okay is there even one of these
plants
here cuz there's the
ball maybe ah maybe the keys was for the
other side again the
key it's always for the opposite side
somehow so maybe this
door no not this door
okay wow a Cinematic
Universe my other a is another aan girl
bir too but you mean me
right just making sure
[Music]
it doesn't I don't think
I got to go back ah to from where I fell
okay okay
okay thank you
Jackson what you Tred to find another oi
huh huh no I know you didn't I know you
didn't but you're implying you did I
should be angry at you for
that why were you even on the
lookout was I not sufficient for
[Music]
you okay sorry I'm I'm yawning maybe a
lot it just feels like I'm never
finishing my
yawns okay we go here again
why why did they make me fall down when
they make me come back up again I fall
down and I get back up again they never
going to take me
[Music]
down
oh what the hell is with those
bats or
[Music]
birds why why are they what's still
malfunctioning am I just missing the
timing
or no I think I think it's actually not
possible
to you're just supposed to dodge them I
think it's a murder
y
ominous wait that reminds me of
something
what was
that I can't
remember [\h__\h] what was
[Music]
it I said a word weirdly the other
day I said it
[Music]
wrong I know there's that is a common
occurrence with me but um I think it was
C funny
[Music]
situation
oh I say words really all the
time um there was
um I I'll just say this now because I've
been waiting to say this there was a
moment where um I was in a uh I was in a
in a recording right you know I've been
recording a lot of things
[Music]
and
I I was in I was in a recording
and I said something I was thinking a
thing and I said something
else I
was I was trying to express
[Music]
my
this like for
something and so straight out of my
mouth came the
word with such a serious
face this is an
abortion
and
I the person I said that to
was a english- speaking person and she
looked at me shook at and
confused and was just silent and then it
like it was just like two or three 4
seconds of like moments where there was
silence and the clock in my brain was
ticking and then I realized and and I I
was like sorry
s and the other person also like started
laughing but like also like panicking
and you know Japanese staff did not know
what was going on and and why we might
want to cut now and I had to explain and
be like ah this notor I said something
really weird in in English um yeah just
uh I don't know maybe maybe cut it I was
trying to say I was trying to say
Abomination and then like later on I
realized I even said that wrong I always
say Abomination but it's
[Music]
[Laughter]
Abomination yeah show was
thetion and at that
moment I knew I [\h__\h] up that's not
where I was going but that's where I was
led to say that just now and in that
moment she knew she [\h__\h]
up um but
um I was thinking like okay I mean the
word itself it's not like I you know
said like a word that in itself is NG uh
like baned but yeah um I understand that
was weird
so we had to do it again
we had to do it again and yeah yeah that
reminds me so in another recording
I said
Abomination again and I realized oh wait
I think I'm saying that
[Music]
wrong wait the stuff it's not about the
abdomen is it
h yeah yeah yeah it's all connected all
these words are discombobulating
me yeah oopsie oh
the mouse the
[Music]
mouse how did I not get the mouse on the
first
time how did I not get it y why did I
not get it this time
[Music]
even wait I want to get them at the same
time ah they're [\h__\h] me over man
[Music]
ah it's
ridiculous just going to get this one
[Music]
now whatever one by one for the Wawa
this is all I can do this is me at my ah
you back ah now there's two of them
a Peak Performance takik what the
hell oh no oh no oh no I'm not going to
[\h__\h] die in here
okay I refuse I refuse I
ref got
[\h__\h] die
thank you for the heart oh my God oh my
God I got both I got both I hate you I
hate
you mouse please
Mouse uh-oh uhoh uhoh
uhoh okay I got that one I got that one
I got to
okay okay okay that's ridiculous holy
[\h__\h] he kept on interrupting me and they
the big ones they're so big there's like
no space to dodge so easily when you're
already sucking on one of the ghosts
man the shovel one I hate him so
much oh my God this is going to ruin my
score what is the shovel doing in there
by the way
oh look at that give me that give me
that what it is this
glass
H why how did I get these
things ah oh what the hell what is that
oh the flowers flower
[Music]
power oh
what what did I
[Music]
do I know it's weped up but it's like
not clearing up either and what is with
the
flowers I did the thing it's not
happening again they need water the
flashing definitely is not working
now yeah they look like they need water
um oh hey that was easy I thought it
would be like more stuck in
there can I crash this
glass
oopsy with the shovel
no uh what is this
[Music]
for what is the shovel
for got to be a friend shape around here
you mean a a
boo oh wait let's look for this
thing Let It Go Let It
Go ban Senai
lab wait should I looked around
more Oh you mean friendship as
an V is also friendship but uh you
mean you mean a v
right I don't see one maybe over
here I know these are balloons these are
water B oh I sucked it in though I open
please wait but
it's yeah thank you for calling me now
you little [\h__\h] hello
hello that substance stuck in the pust
5,000 why don't you try create a balloon
with it mhm mhm I I I no that R
and A coming out of the pust might just
be hot enough to let you lift off lift
off I was thinking of if I thought this
was filled with
water and that I could oh oh wait okay
give me one more I thought the purpose
was different but I see now ah wow
is this
realistic no definitely
not okay
Dodge that was difficult to dodge there
like I was trying to go to the
left okay now
no come on what the [\h__\h] I'm trying my
best to go left
but he barely moves to the
[Music]
left okay oh
finally
okay I still have the balloon I didn't
pop it this time I want to look through
it but I guess I can't when I have the
balloon now how would you go over there
when there's the spikes right
there no
nah well come
on now I'm back oh wait this is a like a
middle level ooh
[Music]
money shall we look through
here seedling
laboratory
oh what are they
doing this kind of gives me Fallout
value
okay wait no I sucked too too
much like the the vent that we went
to the vent that we went to how do you
go
there on purpose of course on purpose
need this thing after all
of course that was on purpose let let
me please let me out of here is there no
there's an opening there why can't I go
go out
[Music]
again excuse
me it's not getting bigger for now come
on how do I get out of here is it fcked
because I'm
i' it's barely oh there we go what the
hell what did I do wrong I'm going to
fall down again I don't know how to get
past the
spikes left left left left left oh
I'm it I think your balloon has to pop
there but it's so close you have to aim
to the to the left when you're
[Music]
falling
oh
okay look at those bats over there uh
crows my heart dropped and sunk to the
floor
[Music]
Liquid Gold
baby why the SS music why the SAU
music boo no not
boo no don't go away gold no I should
have sucked it
up oh wait that's the moment where you
take it off right a moment
do the NaNa again
[Music]
no
bucket I remember my love for buckets
somewhere deep in there it's still there
I will never forget what the buckets
have done for me in the past oh wait I
see what's going on I fill off the
bucket with the gold so that it's
heavier and then I put it on the button
wow I understood that I understood that
immediately without even standing on the
button first yeah Stanley
par really I talked about this um in the
off collab but I
really I really am kind of envious of
the new members who now still have all
these games that like the oneoff games
that they can play on stream cuz they
haven't yet they they just started I
already used so many of the one of games
I wish I could like experience Stanley's
Parable or poor and all that for the
first time again wait what now what did
that do
even wh what
what i is is that hint that I already
know that seems like hints that I
already know oh
money is there something there
[Music]
but at the same
time like who knows what games they
played in private before
and like wouldn't actually be playing
for the first time on stream
anyway but still still they have so much
to choose from I really hope more people
play cookie on me I don't know why they
didn't play that wait ah wait I think I
understand I have to switch it up
because if I stand on on this button
then I can't like flash him maybe I have
to flash
him but let let it down put it down
there why does he lift it there why does
he lift it
there why does he lift it when he stands
there is it not supposed to go there no
yeah yeah yeah okay and if I stand here
I don't know if that's something I have
to do but I I certainly now think so
there we go I have to stand on this one
smart I got it I understood
[Music]
it I hope you play thank goodness you're
here for an extremely British what's
that what's
that going to be anyone out there like
Liz who is playing under tale I never
played undertale before
I think a lot of people never played it
before W flowing through and flashing
out those shitty ghosts through the
drain let's go although I think they're
enjoying
it it's like in the water park for
them I think you'd like it yeah it's on
my list of games to play one day I
guess she did some dance in last oh
really oh I need to listen to
it opening Water
[Music]
B oh is this um is this a sports string
not sport string but um just like
sang it
twice twice in a row or
what oh well it was an archived one
actually
mhm if somehow if you somehow haven't
been spoiled on undertale I think you
would like it all I I don't think I was
spoiled H once in the beginning once at
the end oh W she really likes it huh
[Music]
H okay ni a job youngster the water flow
is slowely normalizing hold on I'll
pixelate you out of there in just a
minute
[Music]
wow she always sings the first song she
sang at the end ah for people who missed
it I guess
oh uhoh uh pixelate me out of here now
please before I get covered in gold and
die
oh
Jokers
well well this ghost better drop me a
lot of gold
ah immune immune what oh no not immune
but I guess you can slip on the
gold ah
okay ah he doesn't really get like swung
and flung around
ah you can do this pretty much endlessly
until you get
hit he just stays there cuz he's so fat
wow that's a way
of strengthening your
defense yellow Press B while sucking to
dodge oh okay might try that oh good job
dealing with that rather Ro round ghost
mhm just get rid of the tea and say it
how it
is I'm bringing you back hold on to your
head wait let me get the heart or do I
get I get fully healed anyway right oh
yes I did it oh yeah I did it mission
complete don't don't don't even
it was a long
Mission the health is well you know I
got
bullied okay
[Music]
whatever bronze chw forever but bronze
it kind of looks like my hair color
okay it's
nice nice
how you go
to yeah it's my first time
playing now we're going to clear two
Mansions
sure what ooh you already want to have
my stuff wow
okay what if I want to keep it he's just
using
me I want to keep this stuff what do I
get what I
it well I'll be I've never seen that
kind of ghost before and good job
restoring the water floor y y if this
whole ghost hunting thing doesn't work
out you may have a future as a
plumber I have a past as a plumber and
after this I have a future as a plumber
don't
worry I got the boo so the boo is
actually optional or what
germa using me an
EDF and said how useful I
am
really JMA is like a famous uh YouTuber
streamer twitcher I don't know
right what
oh God that's embarrassing I can't
already imagine like people cringing at
me in in the chat
there oh no oh
no isn't J F as oi e really the chat is
supportive really they liked me really
did he try all all of
us are we different do we function
differently germa likes
Miku germa you know I always want to
read it as
[Music]
JMA uh nor Lon as far as watching who
who is
that W okay well that's funny oh God I'm
embarrassed I'm embarrassed but I mean I
mean maybe
does does he does he know
what what that was that like what Hol
life is I wonder people probably
explained it to him if he didn't
know cuz like what you would think like
what is this anime girl doing but it's
not the first time if he knows EDF then
he would know that that's not even the
first
[Music]
time hasashi that is very embarassing oh
God oh
God spread the word yeah I
guess he's a silly guy he's not going to
be like what is this [\h__\h]
okay okay that's that's I'm glad if it
was not like that because you know
there's there's certainly other twitch
streamers where that would be the case
where both the streamer and the chat
would be like what the [\h__\h] is this
[Music]
uh cool okay I'm
glad still still kind of
embarrassing
okay I wonder if there's a clip of that
that I can
perceive I like that you use the Y
voice it's not not 100% % the
same not 100% the
same ger chat is only mean to
germa kind of like you guys are mean to
me
sometimes y remember
the the gay tree the dark moon piece
seems to be somewhere up there so we
know roughly where it is but the hard
part is getting there
y
[Music]
y the
what you need to cross the newly raised
bridge and explore the interior of the
Holo tree to find a way up the Holo
tree everyone that's able should join us
we need a lot of virus to protect the
planet's
CR wow I'm so motivated
now I am so
motivated ef ef I am now bucket
foot very common problem that people
have in the ghost hunting world oh
where' the bucket go I lost my bucket
no not my bucket okay there must be a
water stour
for this bucket for
[Music]
sure ah there's one in there but do I
not need to do anything else here
ah okay I have
water oh with X
okay yeah it's important to revive all
the flowers we need to
support the growth of nature
and now we flash
him thank you see nature thans you
back if you're nice to Nature you will
be rewarded this is what Luigi's Mansion
is teaching us that's actually kind of
wholesome isn't it like it's
subconsciously telling us that we want
to help nature and revive
nature and then we'll get money out of
it not really how it works IRL but um
you
know it can be manipulating Us in the
best
way maybe we don't get money out of it
but we get nice air from it
right weird how there's always just one
flower that's is still there and the
rest
is
dead random how did they die how did
that one survive what is the one flower
doing differently from the others maybe
it should share its wisdom and knowledge
to the other flowers I think that's it
is
that I think that's
[Music]
it he had a cloud
backup oh wait this FL too
hidden survival of the
fittest oh wait that's kind of an evil
one though what the hell ah no okay it
froze that thing yeah maybe we want that
or
something and weone that's a should join
us we need a lot of V
okay what does this do
again and now we get water from that oh
so I could have gotten it from
here what happens this time if I open
this up is there a point in doing that
[Music]
again oh
oh there was a
point the noodle
ghosts oh how many oh there's ah have
the wheels this time they're stealing
this and leaving one okay
bye have
fun guess I'll go home and leave this
Mansion like this can't be helped right
oh no too bad I can't work on this
Mansion anymore all right then next
Mansion please you think the ghost would
be disappointed if I just gave up on
this and just wouldn't play with them
anymore HH not you shitty play thing for
[\h__\h] sake why do I have four DMS again
is it from the ones I want the DMS
from oh yeah
[Music]
M when you ask someone what do you want
to eat and they say uh
anything
um
[Laughter]
uh I mean I'm also culprit of that
sometimes I'm that kind of person yeah
me too sometimes although no I usually
say anything but Sushi seafood and so on
I give them like a few things I don't
want to eat and that's at least helpful
[Music]
right
dma can you help me find a rest of
[Music]
yeah Jem also ask me what kind of food
I don't know mhm
[Music]
uh
mhm
[Music]
mhm she's listening J is listening J's
listening not germa JMA is listening
something with corn are there like corn
restaurants
MH no I don't think so although maybe
there could be because Japan loves corn
really I love ordering like corn side
dishes just simply like in family
restaurants there's like always like
corn soup and then uh like corn with
butter on like one of those like hot uh
uh iron plates they bring it in while
it's still kind of like sizzling um I I
love to order that and then you like mix
it with the butter that's on
top and then oh you just you just bite
into that beautiful mess of
buttery what did we what did we say
yesterday what sausages were Snappy not
Snappy
right nice nice coin
m not crunchy but snappy really does
that
fit I love Corin in Japan understands my
love for corn yeah Loki elotes but it's
just literally just butter and a little
bit of
[Music]
salt it does fit
okay thank you
jenma thank you she's going to make a
reservation for me and the
the the mystery person yeah yeah I saw
the fan art I wonder if JMA saw it
yeah the pin wheel is gone yeah look for
them
okay okay this looks like we got to go
this way what was this for though what
did I revive that one for wait wait ah
somebody was saying a stone plate was
missing indeed it is
missing but is that a button or what oh
it
is wait is it missing on the other side
too
is it missing on the other side
too no but I can't stand on this one
anyway what happens oh oh I see I see I
see now it all makes sense now wait
there's a ghost on this side but I think
I want to shoot the the
plant because that's what you usually do
with these spiky balls right big brain
and I have to stand on this one anyway
wait I don't I'm so bad at this I don't
really understand it
okay wait do I have to shoot the other
one
too it's still
there okay but in this case I don't have
to stand ah I guess it just only
activates one of them at a
time
oh oh I got wait wait wait can he
escape don't
escape I need the
money I need the
money I've been inviting my
coist for dinner it why did it go behind
wait what it's still there right okay
okay
okay I think we said something different
on stream you know because
um uh you know the other day with the uh
uh Quest only Iris
collab Iris forgot her wallet right so
then who was it I think crony said she
will pay for Iris and then I said okay
and I will pay for crony but in the end
I paid for
[Laughter]
everybody
yeah because splitting the build would
have been too complicated they they
don't seem to like to do that very much
in Japan um the
waiters and so I just I was like paying
for it and and figuring well I am the
most Senai in here I I could do a nice
thing for once and invite them all for
dinner I don't do that that often I
prefer to split the
bill but in that moment I felt like okay
I'll I'll do a nice thing we had a
really nice dinner and talked so
much we yapped so
much why
not what is oh oh that opens the door it
didn't do that before probably because
there was no water flowing
huh o Luigi why don't you react faster
like I was literally already pressing
the the
flashlight but he was just not doing
it if you would have done the command
that I'm giving you maybe they wouldn't
have escaped h
[Music]
what is
this just trying to find things but I oh
what
[Music]
what that's really the least the last
place where I expected something
oh that's like basically something like
this I got to look out for those kind of
tiles then
huh
oh wait was that a Japanese person
writing
that no most restaurants in America I
don't like it when you split the bill
either if you and if you do split the
build please tell them at the beginning
of the
oh I mean I think in Europe it's never
an issue to split the bill at the end
and even in Japan I do it sometimes but
like recently I've only like ever since
I'm here in this trip I've always made
the experience that they seem to have
issues with it more than ever
before oh no not the combination of this
big red guy again with the Shovel
Knight no oh but I sucked this one in in
one go
yippee okay
okay I thought I could maybe get
both okay but this goes way smoother
than before let's
go
yay waiters before ask before the bill
comes in US if you're playing the veil
oh that's smart thank you for
asking wait there's still something if
the doors aren't
opening
[Music]
no I hear a sound
what are you doing in
there do you have my wheel do you have
The Wheel of Time oh he has this yet
let's go
woo my group usually has one person the
rest play them yeah uh we did that a few
times in Italy
recently
but it's also annoying I don't like that
either then you have to run after some
people some people just
don't you know they forget about it or
they don't immediately follow up cuz
they don't have cash with them or
so so I rather just split the goddamn
Bill and also one thing I personally
really don't like is
when people like want to split the bill
but oh interesting but not in like the
fair way of Fair Way of uh paying what
you ordered for no like for example 5050
or uh whatever like everybody pays like
uh like split by five or so because I
usually order way less than the others
especially because like it's not decided
in the beginning that that's what's
going to happen that everybody plays
pays the same amount if I knew that
maybe I would order more but I usually
order just what I think I'll be eating
and sometimes I don't even order a drink
I just order water and then others order
wine and beer and stuff and then you
expect me to pay the same amount in the
end Bruh Bruh Bruh everybody ERS always
so much more than me so I really hate
that system I'm sorry to say but like I
I I I'm not going to pay for your Feast
nuh-uh yeah I hate that I hate
that like do they forget that I I I
basically order like nothing like half
of what they order do they not realize
that this is not fair for
me they did that joke at Park and wreck
that
situation
[Music]
really oh nice almost almost fell down
there stay up
here I want to capture you
[Music]
you order water they order gold en
crusted
Lobster and Perkins made your AR makes
your argument oh and Perkins that'sa and
Perkins I've been rewatching a little
bit of that because like uh it was on on
a lot of airplane rides that I've been
on and yeah I like watching um just
comedy shows that they have on the
airplanes but usually I've watched
them already or it's some something not
interesting to
[Music]
me with movies there's always so much
choice but I always have a hard time
choosing which one I should watch
because I'm I'm never sure is it going
to be a shitty movie or a decent
one hard choices hard choices I wonder
if you can look up before you get on the
plane if there's somewhere written down
uh all the movies they
have so you can like look up beforehand
and plan it out like if you really
travel a lot on longdistance airplanes
if you don't then it makes no sense to
do that but if you do travel a lot then
you might want to like think about first
like what what can I watch on this
15-hour flight it's 15 [\h__\h] hours
yeah like a catalog I wonder if that's
like available online
[Music]
okay I guess I could have known that
because this door is not marked on the
map okay I will look at that from now
on I'm just I'm just using the
flashlight to see if there's anything oh
he anything
interesting oh
[Music]
some do so bring my switch or download
show yeah I've been doing that
too bringing my iPad and then watching
on my
[Music]
iPad oh
bucket the return of the
bucket oh okay
water stopped working why why why
why is it not continuing to work it's
not that easy
huh thanks for the
membership and the Super
[Music]
Chat okay what am I
missing
maybe
oh that's not what I was missing but
it's certainly something nice to
find maybe I can't help but um only get
it for a moment maybe I already placed a
bucket
here oh where was the water coming out
of oh here
ah H like a moment of water could
already be enough you
know I don't know if that's how you're
supposed to do
it see it felted the bucket maybe it's
supposed to only be for a moment I can
do a few things with that
probably I actually can I'm I'm okay
with this
see what else do I need the water
for can I throw it into the middle is
that
open I'm not sure if there's a proper
opening oh it doesn't give me the X
prompt
[Music]
so not sure let me put this
down oh oh I didn't see that up
there the whole pump was missing not
pump let you call this again
uh metal thing
[Music]
so but I already have my bucket of water
what's going to happen is it going to
automatically put it in there huh okay
okay wait there's a there's going to be
an evil big plant coming out of there
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah oh wait maybe
not evil thought it was going to attack
me okay that needed a lot of
water is that everything in this room I
feel
like w Wait I have to
FL I thought I was about to say say I
feel like this room should have one of
these Jewels like there should be one in
almost every room and I I probably miss
a lot of
them
so I always feel like I'm looking pretty
furly but I guess I'm not I have hdms
again probably all from
JMA I have to
choose oh my God she sent me like 10
oh what is
this what is
this W that looks yummy sweet
[Music]
stuff wow
wow what is this what is this what is
this place what the
[\h__\h] what did you
find what is
this surprised the rating isn't even
that good because this looks
[Music]
insane oh my
God ah wait did she answer my question
ah I'm meeting waya by the
way I asked her can I say she said yes I
didn't see that I'm meeting waya does
way like sweet things she does right
probably this place has a lot lot of
sweet stuff wi w w I'm eating wi no I
said I'm meeting
wi I'm I'm meeting yeah it sounds like
I'm eating I'm eating I'm eating I'm
eating
when she likes sweet stuff this is
really
nice what about
this choosing restaurants now well they
all kind of have this kind of rating wao
what is this I got to go to there
another time
[Music]
maybe
shasco okay I'm not going to go there
but damn the shasco makes me think of
masar rasco uh experiences in
Brazil wow
wow
what why do they have this kind kind of
food
what this
[Music]
what there's some funny restaurants in
Japan like the the foods they choose to
to serve in
combination
F oh what's this
[Music]
oh hope they have
corn maybe in some
[Music]
way okay I think I think I made my
choice
[Music]
damn she found some nice looking
restaurants shall we disturb
them shall I go ahead and disturb them
they're not noticing me yet
wait he
was no what what do you mean that
doesn't work what do you mean that
doesn't
work why did they ignore oh because I'm
a not
like
wait now they now they
realize oh okay I got this one oh wait
I'm just getting his glasses give me
give me
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay kind of antil that that's also
weird I don't know do you say
anticlimactic or antil climatic is is
there a c or is there not a SE
oh I'm adding letters where there
shouldn't be any letters often there is
a see anticlimactic okay ity really wait
really no I think you're gaslighting me
now wa there is a seat but you probably
don't really pronounce it
[Music]
right what are all these things here oh
I don't pronounce it I do you do oh
really you do
oh
wait nothing
behind it's a common mispronunciation oh
you do say anticlimactic but a lot of
people
don't and they're saying it
wrong you guys are saying it
wrong what green Mouse wait it's well
will it come back because it's it's
carrying the
jewel you can't like I don't think
you're allowed to have me miss out on
that you have to come back wait where
did it go ah wait it wasn't green it was
just wait I think I have to stand up
here then it will come
right hey but I can't reach that what
what does this
do a it's like one of those
games oh motion controls yeah B
oh wait I can shoot all these
things oh fun I want to shoot
everything I can shoot all the pots
too it
t that's why these things were aligned
like this is like a shooting range
um what if do I get something if I shoot
literally
everything maybe a
bone or some
money oh no I didn't want to get that
yet wait wait wait wait
[Music]
wait I'm like switching between motion
controls and not motion control trols
because it's a little bit
[Music]
messy okay last one I
think
wait no wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
no wait turn around it dropped it anyway
just one of them didn't drop it okay
okay okay okay I'm so I'm so stressed
out I'm so stressed out oh okay you get
something I missed one of
the one of them okay these [\h__\h]
always stress me out so
much
[Music]
wait
nice yippe
[Music]
[Applause]
we have a restaurant
booking
y should be this
[Music]
one okay telling waya where to go at
what time
[Music]
wow
oh
Luigi Luigi
having fun being left alone okay is
there anything else I missed
here no maybe not oh wait this
money I knew it
Yoo making
bank okay just dinner or k no just
dinner let should go k one of those days
for
sure I'm excited for the
dinner
oh haven't have I seen waya I don't
think I've seen her in a
[Music]
while
out I sucked it
in golden bat out of nowhere
[Music]
ni hope you have a great time catching
up yes I think we
will that's the cute girl I was talking
about there it could have been anyone
because there's only cute girls
[Music]
okay that almost seems like a like boss
because he's playing that there but it
doesn't look like a boss so I guess it's
not a
boss
[Music]
suck okay oh ow oh oh baby it's double
yes that will bring bring big
money
yeah
nice okay I see you I see you
okay it's in there wait how do I
oh
hello give me my big ass
earring I want it
back you
can't can't wear it anyway can you give
me give me give me give me you don't
need this I need this
[Music]
yippe okay let's find secrets in this
room is there
[Music]
anything is there a jewel in this
room I can't tell maybe
[Music]
not random frog what what are you doing
in there
okay I don't think there's anything
else I'll go
unless what if I get rid of all of the
lights on the candles is that a
thing but they get turned back on
relatively fast no actually not ah
ah is that a
thing sometimes in other game that's a
thing my God I'm not talented enough for
that
though see they turn back on really fast
but that could be why it's you know a
[Music]
challenge no it's probably not it
right can I go behind I can
ah what there's no M you're still behind
what there has to be something
[Music]
behind
weird can I play it oh
[Music]
I don't know I don't think that does
anything I
guess
oh I don't know I don't think so I don't
think so let's give
up organists organizing the orle you'll
need that for later oh okay
[Music]
wow what is this
angle
hello he doesn't know I'm watching
him is he looking at himself in the
mirror and he's sad that he can't see
himself a
a he's like I used to have a
reflection I used to have a reflection
long time ago now I can't that's
actually so sad and
depressing poor
[Music]
ghost what the the vines
for
H that's why he's angry he's trying to
cope with the fact that he's dead we
can't be mad at these ghosts they have
to cope with that they have to live with
[Music]
that they they have to live with the
fact that they're dead
[Music]
making fun of
ghosts the irony you have to live with
the fact that you're dead No in fact you
don't have to live with that because
you're
dead Ain't It Funny do I get something
like a golden spider
eventually no
[Music]
okay uh do I have a
key for any of these
doors was there a key out there
[Music]
does it have something to do with this
angle just say that to
ollie I don't think she'll find that
particularly funny I don't want to make
her sad actually no she's she's not a
ghost she's a zombie that doesn't she's
alive she's actively
alive I think that was just to show of
the pretty oh okay could a key have been
in
here the room behind the giant mechanism
[Music]
what he's still there do you have the
key bro
[Music]
she's dead after she found out you on a
date with
her well she's welcome to
join just got to come to
[Music]
Japan help chat
what do I
do the room where I have to go all the
way back
[Music]
there no way oh yeah I guess there's
exclamation mark rooms
[Music]
um on
F1 yeah I don't know how to get there
I'll just keep on going down hopefully
I'll end up
there
why the game made me go this far and now
I'm missing a key from somewhere far
away usually the key that's necessary is
really close
to where you need it at least that's how
I felt like it was like that
[Music]
we go down from here yes oh there's
still a mouse going around
there everything's so empty
now I must have missed it but like why
is it a key that you use so far away
anyway
um which way wait that door is fake that
door is fake okay I here we
are
uh just checking just
checking oh there's a rope up
there okay Luigi go through there
again you should be able to avoid that
by now because you've witnessed that
before but okay
[Music]
that why is that still
shaking I'm done with the ghosts
here boo is that
you wait can I take them
no h I think this place is haunted H oh
hello
where you going no don't go
away
Mia there
backet what is this I can't
[Music]
tell a lawn mower is that how lawn
mowers looked in Medieval ages oh it
opened up a path to there
cool wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait what about the other
things
[Music]
this if there weren't lawnmowers in
medieval times then that's honestly
their fault that they didn't think
harder because judging by what I just
now saw now
I feel like they could have made
one that would have oh looked exactly
like
that honestly they missed
out wa I want to okay let's get him
let's get him let's get him in one
go oh don't don't okay feel like I was
about to step on the gloop and slip on
it
oh there's no one to disturb us now
let's do it oh one
go I need to I need to try out the
dodging I should try out the dodging be
you said
[Music]
be okay well he already died there
so oh I see you
[Music]
wait
hey I saw you hiding
[Music]
there I'll try again when I have like a
fight where I need to dodge I'll try
[Music]
again I need that for a mini boss oh
no oh no
if a if a mini boss really needs that to
be done if that's like its whole gimmick
then I don't know if I can really do
well with
it I don't trust myself with
that you know how I am
kfp okay he anything else
no wait there's a oh that's so cute
there's a b
plant he wouldn't be hiding in there
would
he oh I might not even have to look at
the other flowers if that one already
gives me that but the others we'll give
me other cool stuff I'll take
it
[Music]
yippe what will you donate to the Wawa
church thank you money money
money
yes okay um anything
else here to do oh can look over through
this window that looks like a that looks
like a
jibbly
fire to the W church thank you blessed
be you and your chicken
nness why would you look through there
why does what does that tell me that
there is fire
[Music]
just suck it suck
it damn it maybe if I would have sucked
it in there would have been a golden bat
right
after N I got the jewel I probably have
everything you can get in
here I probably do
go for here W it
donations Alig
thanks why is why in my time zone are
you here to stay no please say
no but no I'm I'm glad I can do a few
PST streams even though it's still kind
of weird what the
hell what the hell this room is spooky
oh another
one but then I think that might be the
last wheel where'd he go oh did he go
down a
level what's this bucket
[Music]
for
balloon for
[Music]
what there a hole in the ceiling
was there what what does that
mean what does any of this mean there's
a leaky ceiling yeah and for some reason
I can open that
[Music]
up I'm turning this wheel but St doing
anything getting some money
turning
this no this time
to oh wait this okay okay bucket on not
to water anything but to put on this and
does it do anything over
here
no or maybe we need double
weight
yes but what about the balloon oh it's
the balloon to go back up should I have
taken the balloon with me oh no there's
balloons here
too a double wait
n thank you for the Super
Chat yay I'm glad some of you guys can
see me when you normally have to even V
or watch me at Unholy
times I'm happy to provide you guys with
some PST
waha oh dear oh dear the plant oh dear
oh dear
hey where do you think you're
[Music]
going I'm getting used to catching
ghosts
[Music]
now I'm reading I'm actively reading
don't worry guys I'm taking it all in
why is this plant looking at
me okay we need one of those balls
[Music]
eh where are the
balls
stay I thought I had you
all ah okay I thought the plant was the
problem okay lights are back on
ah Church OFA contributions thank you
thank
[Music]
youell Oh
Come that was the last bin let's
go bin is what you call
that oh
yes yipp oh mission complete but I
didn't kill the plant H guess that's
fine oh and I also ah in this Mission I
was never meant to go up there and see I
didn't even find any more keys I was
just supposed to find all the pin wheel
thingies I was never supposed to proceed
up on that level where I went
[Music]
huh I just felt like that was a
natural succession of where I had to go
[Music]
progression I think egad is secretly a
chicken that's what's he he's hiding in
those shoes because look how thin those
legs are those are literally chicken
legs I think he's secretly a chicken
no human can have legs like that can
they those look like Twigs to
me compare those to Luigi's legs he's a
chicken he's a chicken wait that's
literally listen to that that sounds
like something he would say that
something it just sounds like something
some random
random phrase like cha cha he's a
chicken he's a
chicken he's a chicken he's a chicken
he's a chicken that sounds just like a
random phrase he would say that makes no
sense not a real
[Music]
word good job scaring those ghosts out
of their hiding spots young
fell
[Music]
yippe yeah not bad not
bad oh won't over heat us quickly let's
go
we are fedal as Birds bipeds oh do mean
birds though that'll be more
fun thank you
unknown
Yol D in for the super chats guys yeah
suddenly you guys are feeling like
throwing money at me maybe I should
claim to be at church more
often would' be in a real pickle if we
lost those pin wheel veins I'm sure have
something in my toolbox that can
be yep I tell you you really have a
knock for staring up trouble
youngster you haven't even reached a
hollow tree and the ghosts are already
giving you a hard
time but I already went to the top I
think that was already the top so feel
like I'm getting
there yeah what's next we put the vein
the veins back on
there just don't tell the tax people
maybe I should maybe they'll leave me
alone
then
whoa it look like one of those things
you use in the in the Japanese shrines
to pour water over your
hands but just normally it's made out of
wood
[Music]
okay just bring me there let's
go a book of WWA please make it I mean
you guys made several books before for
like birthday SL
aniversary uh
presents but it's more like art books
and thank you messages
books not Bible of
[Music]
Wawa
okay uh plant Chan is back and looking
as gorgeous as ever head was that
inevitable let me out let me out no
don't think that was
[Music]
inevitable uh
okay uh yeah
[Music]
water but also this is sounds why is
there a SPID we there now something
going to come out of there
no oh no no I hate myself
no death perception and also like
controls [\h__\h] me up
there come back
please come back what if I restart the
mission you know what I will do that
we're still in the beginning I will only
ever do that in the beginning if I
really feel salty about
[Music]
something
yeah we have only just begun and then I
won't get eaten by that stupid plant
either I know it's just for one Gold
Bar L chicken costume worn by during the
Minecraft stream
what that AI analysis is rarely this
wrong about what we're talking about I
feel like this is more than
usual wait what it went back up way
faster than last time but okay I got
involve I still panicked though
[Music]
this is me throwing water like holy
water it's my
subject don't they do that also in
churches the holy
water you shall be
cleansed from your a a I'm to wait
that's a bug is it not I'm on top of
it I don't think you normally is
supposed to be riding
it
not like I I'm too I don't understand
how you shoot this thing I'm sucking and
then I'm Letting Go but like cuz I can't
shoot while I don't understand I will
never understand this
it's all just a trial and
error are there any health benefits to
holy waha water no it's just a scam but
um don't tell don't tell the other
chickens
that it's all just a
scam
okay is that it
[Music]
maybe that's
it oh I didn't expect anything here
actually okay a golden ghost is in
there h
not supposed to tell a people a scam
that's a scam I was just telling one
person surely nobody nobody else
heard I was telling that to you in
private no don't take the last one
[Music]
stop he's
panicking oh he he abandoned his friend
oh one of them is no they're both
wearing plants as on their head
skute
[Music]
uh-oh both of them let's
go oh big money oh he's
back now you come back after the others
are gone and you have less chances of
winning here what's the
point
okay I don't know if I need to do that
but I'll do it
anyway
so can we
like like put them on there in a way
that they're not going to be stolen
anymore
cuz like what who what guarantees me
that they're not going to steal it again
they were literally just on
it how do I know they're not going to
steal it
again
did
[Music]
beautiful find the mysterious
Mage where is it oh floor four isn't
that where I got stuck last time also I
just
realized this shape it looks like a
ghost with this is the arms is that on
[Music]
purpose which way is the best way to go
there I don't know
I knew you were there I momentarily
forgot about it
but I reacted
fast what that was the challenge of the
room that it huh oh Treasure Chest wait
what I get another bone didn't I get a
bone from the same chest before nice
excellent excellent oh do I get money
again
too I
do feels like a little bit less than
before but
okay oh okay out of here I don't get
money
again oh fine fine then
[Music]
which way do I want to
go oh ah the garden nothing new here
right let's go let's
go I'm not
lost I'm really not
lost I know where to go but wait I could
isn't there a kind of an elevator in the
other room if I go the other way maybe
the other way would be better but wait
there's the stairs are
fixed that's when are the stairs fixed
or were these no these were not fixed
[Music]
before okay that one door is a fake
door spin the pin wheel
[Music]
but
the it says to go up up
[Music]
here
oops but it didn't say spin the wheel
but I guess I should what does that
do I I I mean sure like
H
[Music]
H they shouldn't let me go without
spinning the wheel I would have went all
the way up just now if it weren't for
you
guys I know this hour is rare waa hours
treasure it it's kind of spinning on its
own ah is there a shortcut to the ah
because the gate over opens up and then
I have a
shortcut cuz also now I'm on a higher
level like I'm standing on the same
level as
that so I can actually walk
through
ah but hey I wouldn't have gotten the
golden
ghost if I didn't go the other
way looks like a Zelda
[Music]
dungeon Pro tip all according to Kaku
guys is there a spider
here could it
be okay I need something to put the fire
on
nice oh it the blue flame just turned
into a red
flame interesting it's like herb turned
into me
am I
[Music]
herb
weird something will happen at the top
the spider will
appear is it going to be a spider or
oh
oh oh oh wait why is this so chill and
cute and nothing happens this is
anticlimactic
[Music]
okay that really hurt
me that pain went through the game into
my real body
I felt the door snapping on me I have
actual wounds from it
now they were 5050 because a ghost I I
what mm I always went the right way to
not cause a ghost
encounter without knowing it they would
have been ghost if I went the other way
each
time that's hilarious
[Music]
uh found something it's a special ke
that opens that door but it's hidden in
the CPS I hope you are not scared of
graveyards it's not like they're full of
vengeful Spirits or anything a key for
this
door I was going to say it's just a
wooden thing but it does have a
keyhole so Ghost Encounters can probably
still happen heyo
[Music]
oh yeah what are you
doing why are you doing
that oh here I
go wait were the stairs blocked up or I
didn't even look why do we have to do it
this
way that wasn't so bad that wasn't so
bad at all Luigi you made such a big
deal out of him you made me think that
something was going to attack me down
there or so oh
[Applause]
[Music]
[\h__\h]
can't so bad at this like shooting stuff
pick it
up oh my God
yeah will one of you
please come to
me should I just walk over there instead
of shooting
yes is that where the graveyard is
behind
[Music]
that why did the earth just shake
o or is that a shortcut to the top no
well I think this is probably where I
need to go
[Music]
right oh yeah probably
mhm oh
dear I am creating earthquakes
here another one maybe
wait there that's like a curtain over
there endless spider spawner this is
what I need to do
apparently it's a trick believe me what
trick
ready
[Music]
uhhuh so that was a fake pink to suck
and the real one is that the
trick wow
o nice slide idea nice slide
[Music]
design Bingo cing
catching jackpot baby welcome to the
graveyard gem well that's an easy one
[Music]
where are all the ones that I
missed hey don't go
away playing Gardener now no more
Plumbing I give up gardening is my new
best
friend Luigi being green and all I think
it fits
him and the thing the the vacuum on his
back looks like one of those yeah blowy
thingies literally like what all those
YouTube gardeners are
using he's already ready for his job
leaf blower yeah he already has the leaf
blower and he used the lawn mower before
in this game too I think he's he's in
for a job change
it's a very satisfying job Luigi trust
me
okay what is this
oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait no
wait feel like I I was about to let him
go
[Music]
nice so is that implying that the person
who is dead here that was their ghost
and obviously it's a a golden ghost so
rich person obviously because they they
lie in a special
grave unlike the
others died of ligma deepest Luigi lore
oh a
coffin a
cough a
coffin I I cough in the
coffin ha wait there a
button what
no maybe got to put a bucket there I
don't know but I don't see a bucket
I don't want to go up there yet I have a
feeling it's going to start something
that I don't want to
start wait what is this about I need to
know
it doesn't let me
go it won't let me
go this is for
later
okay if there's candle you must be able
to light them oh but probably not at the
moment I don't think I can light uh I
don't think I can use the fire
another C
oh that's also kind of weird like
getting hearts and life out of the
coffin it's like I'm stealing the
remaining life that whoever was laying
in their head going for
them oh oh oh oh oh oh
what I didn't know there were toads
stuck in this game too like in L's
Mansion 3 I didn't even know that was an
issue we were looking for toads all
[Music]
along I was about to say too I'm free
I'm
free wait Luigi what are you doing
[Music]
here it doesn't matter you're right here
hero says o to me
too come on are you going to fall wait
now with you you can stand on the coffin
maybe and we can do something with that
but anyway why did we find a toad here I
didn't know that was a freaking toad
here e did you
know C me that's one of my toone deists
CH oh how did he get trapped inside that
painting I sent him to look after the
place no wonder why it's such a mess we
better get him back to the bunker you
might know where the the key is when I
can't pixelate both of you okay lead him
to the gardener
lab
okay an old
Prototype all righty wait we can shoot
toad can't
we yeah go wa I need to collect the
money
Don't Panic so much
don't we have to work together now okay
oh don't oh no he's
crying can I shoot you anywhere in
here I don't understand this mechan
[Music]
mechanism I really don't understand it I
know like sometimes I get it to work
right so in Fury I know how it works but
like I know I need to blow but then
sometimes it just stops just I don't
[Music]
know oh know it's weird it's
weird oh is there something there there
[Music]
is dippy oh boo bua I used recovered and
blow but then I went on a diet
okay okay okay
boo
okay come
on where is
[Music]
he told let me teach you the ways of
ghost
hunting go away to I don't want to suck
you right now
[Music]
what what what
what ah wait I don't know what I'm doing
huh what what happened to
that wasn't that there a moment ago are
you in there mushy
mhi what your told
God damn it okay so
painful I'm going calm
down oh the ball has stopped bouncing it
has out bounced
itself
a could have done that in one goal
probably calm down to is he happy or
panicking I don't
know wait I think he's
happy I guess he's still happy that he's
out of the picture now which almost
sounds like I killed
him oh what he's there what do you
[Music]
mean
what hey
what come
squeaky
shoes squeaky
shoes can we shoot the boo
Plants anything up there
no
oh oh hello The Gardener
lady and another
one is that
resurrecting some weird memories in you
Toad were they were they doing some
weird stuff with you these
ladies while you were in the picture
poor
toad boss fight I suppose so wait boss
fight me boss I
guess they all got
mirrors how do we do this oh I don't
know if I need toad here really go away
go away let's
[Music]
go but after you received hold you would
think that
maybe
oh interesting you would maybe use
him how does this
work how does this work
[Music]
I wish I could turn this while I'm
charging it without doing claw
hands I already don't understand this
can toad hit the mirrors
no get here
to
to to oh my
God he's like stuck in there
[Music]
oh
Jee hold okay are you free
now to is he scared of the
ghosts okay I got him I got him I got
him I got
[Music]
him I'm really bad at shooting stuff
though
no no don't you're so annoying
already aim for the small one
first that's an easy thing to
[Music]
say what how did that not hit
them
T oh my God if this is how you're
supposed to do it then why does he just
always run away from
you you have to flash the one down first
[Music]
well that's e but that's
difficult cuz they run so I don't be
told huh wait what the [\h__\h] am I
supposed to do this is making me
[Music]
rage one is going to let their guard
down flash them
next huh they're not letting the guard
down can somebody get [\h__\h] rid of
toad
okay
wait I think yeah now I understand I got
one gu with using
to and I die throw me a bone please
[Music]
do a bit faster please thank
you
okay so I got to do the yellow one
again this is where dodging would be
good probably I pressed Beetle nothing
happened maybe I'm doing it wrong
still oh now it's
one
okay okay now they're kind of out of the
way ah but it resets that
huh it resets the
the suck
[Music]
meter I'm already kind of low on health
again wait okay okay okay okay okay
we're good we're good we're good I got
some
hearts Circle me [\h__\h]
[Music]
I reset the sakom but I'm still getting
to drain the health of it okay oh that
pretty good that's pretty
good oh they get faster too don't they
the less they
are damn it
wait
oopsie
sorry did it too
late okay
[Music]
okay no I'm PR be
nice
[Music]
nice nice nice dodging I got it
now yeah got the big one before I got
the the middle
one you still want to play that
game okay no problemo with me I'm still
down for it
now nobody can attack me while I'm doing
this so I don't have to
[Music]
dodge can't you at 1:00 a.m. let's go
let's
go let's have a sleepover huh how about
that I lost more Health with this than I
wanted
to oh
well once I really knew how to do it it
was all
right never mind
it's always you know the problem of not
knowing how to do
something and then you figure it out and
everything's fine everything's cool wait
I want to try the thing with the grave
over
there but I feel like you're just going
to run around aren't
you if you stand no stay what if we
stand there together hm
oh that's what wait is that what leads
to the place where I need to go
anyway I thought it was like just an
extra
secret we're invited to the next girl
talk oh yeah you are you're going to be
our plushies you're not going to be the
girls um you're just going to be the
plushies and we're going to hold you
while we do the girls talk how about
that just don't move and don't talk then
we we can fool them into thinking that
you guys are just plushies and then they
won't
mind
surely having you guys listen into all
the yappa yappa I
accept wait can I get oh
what what kind of bars are those what
kind of metal bars are those I hope no
prisons are made out of
these that would be
concerning does the other one also work
like that no oh it's just that one
interesting oh you can even suck it in
it's like a
curtain speaking of curtains
H
wa that might be a relatively smart way
to hide your money because who wants who
which normal person would like to open a
coffin like you would assume there's a
dead body in there I wouldn't want to
open that so put your valuables into it
no one's ever going to attempt opening
that right except Luigi hey yo
I think I did find something really
special oh no oh no no oh no no no no no
no no I how do you do it that
fast let's go what is
[Music]
this you underestimate how we some
people are I guess so I mean especially
if the cough is like in the middle of
your house okay that's kind of weird and
sus and not really where you would
normally put a coffin with a dad person
inside so maybe it would stand out
weirdly I've never found such a big
secret that transports you into a
different [\h__\h]
world
[Music]
what bananas
nice
come grave robbers are a whole issue
guess so is that really a
common problem what's there to Rob do
people put a lot of valuables inside of
graves wait where do I go do I go back
no through
[Music]
here in the old days they did yeah
nowadays not really right and also I
feel like they're more
safely
um put
together you can't so easily go into a
cemetery and dig up a whole grave and
then look inside like what the [\h__\h]
maybe they're wouldn't they even be
locked do they lock
coffins why are you staying there you
going to
actually stay
there do I need to carry
[Music]
you huh
okay he can't
swim he's afraid of
w
weirdo wait I have an idea I have an
idea
toad I I am know a place where I can
keep you
[Music]
safe did I glitch him
inside wait I don't it's weird like is
this open or not because it looks like
there's glass but he just walked through
it what I wanted to shoot him over
it oh wait is this the teleportation
thingy that we were looking
for he's
here he's right here what do you want
how do I call him to come
closer Mama
Mia let him
go let him
go what do you mean he's right there
what the
[\h__\h] here you
go oh my god get the [\h__\h] out of here
toad
get the [\h__\h] out of here I was so happy
to see you but oh my God that is
obnoxious huh I don't
[Music]
understand he actually mov into position
you kept moving him out of it no I
wasn't mhm I was just standing
there I'm so done with him good ridd it
wasn't that annoying and luig man free
he said H well
well don't even okay 30 minutes
well that's not too bad at this point
seems to be normal
[Music]
number
whatever whatever I don't care
Oh up below now below 30 wooo
but it's also a lot of time comes from
me trying to explore everything
thoroughly you
know that's that's what D tender would
[Music]
do there you
go was that the fourth level or still
only the third
one it's been three
hours I hope I'm finishing this Mansion
soon too bad we have to keep the free
sisters down in the vault but it's for
their own safety what what do you mean
too bad where else will you put
them what do you want to do with the
sisters I feel mad for that to fellow
being trapped inside that painting can't
have been fun he seems to have trouble
remembering what happened you know for
having such a big head he really doesn't
have much rattling around in
there for real I agree with that it do
seem like he was very
smart wasn't a complete waste of time
really he brought back a little snapshot
taken by my special tridimensional
security camera give me a couple of
minutes to unscramble the
[Music]
egg wait we missed a boo in the in this
level I don't care I don't actually
care and that was indeed only level
three oh my
God you know what this reminds me of
this image here of all of the ghosts
there that reminds me of Super Mario
Sunshine the level where the the ghost
the Boost can be turned into um
stairs and you kind of do it in this big
open room
and then you climb up
[Music]
Tipp Tipp Tipp
tippa
[Music]
uh so many DMS again there's like so
much going
on okay Tipp Tipp
[Music]
you could go back and beat Sunshine if
you ever want to
maybe maybe I do really like the game it
has a special place in my heart even if
I raged a lot at it
probably yeah maybe at some point 64 is
a different
story a that's a different one
oh that's the key that we need yeah
yeah wait there's a is that Mario that's
Mario's shoes Mario's feet why is Mario
stuck up there in the picture toen Mario
is there peach also stuck somewhere or
[Music]
Daisy what are those boo carrying
suspicious I already know
it seems to be a meeting point for the
boo
no are we looking for something
specific they're out of control the Boos
seem to be encouraging their bad
behavior they're bad influence for them
yeah never seen that kind of ghost
before
really wait are I looking for something
specific no
right the king the image it must be the
special keing we're looking for you know
the king that unlocks the door inside
the whole tree the ghost must be hiding
a key from
[Music]
us
indeed no match for the intellect of the
living my my intellect yeah I I I I I
would say it's at least more than of
those ghosts not very much more
but a little bit
[Applause]
more right
chat thank you so
kind uh-oh
uhoh n what's weird
now what it's the same as all
reach the rooftop pool okay can we take
the shortcut
again or is it even a shortcut it's not
really a shortcut is it over
there like
this can it serf as a
shortcut
actually
no no probably not we got to go back
there when there's um when we have the
keing wait where where where are balls
okay I got to go here I think the other
door is blocked
off
hello why are you looking at
me why is this flower looking oh what
oh I never saw that flower doing that
before even though we encountered it
[Music]
before spe
up how did that hit
me which door do we want to go through
there's so many
doors I don't remember all the paths and
all the rooms anymore
[Music]
Is that ah an important
one oh okay we want to get rid of this
there's a bucket right
there
[Music]
but what now ah
water ohuh oh okay I got
it oh my God I don't think this is good
we're leaking a lot of
water we're going to overflow everything
maybe we should turn it off
again n
no why would we do
that new room rampus room
[Applause]
what is it
[Music]
what oh it's watching me it's watching
me I stop watching me I got confused
[Music]
okay how did I do
that how did I do
that what what were you supposed to
do huh
ah it's a sound of a charging back I
thought I was sensing
something well there's definitely a
ghost here
[Music]
what I'm looking at
myself how does this work well that is
some magical crazy mystical [\h__\h] hey
you
n window
setion NY wait
what he went in there but I'm already in
there I maybe this hints to me where is
he where where he is cuz here it doesn't
Rumble but when I look for the
window Ah that's a cute little
riddle
[Music]
uh-oh ah I wish I could have gotten more
oh wait how many is there oh my
God is this like the ghost of many
children are
they did they all die in
here in their children's
room how much do you want to read into
Le just Manion ghosts like I wonder if
there's people who make like deep lore
videos about all the ghosts and make
like assumptions about how they died
where who were they and all that it's
pretty [\h__\h] dark like what I just
came up with was kind of
dark cuz this made me think that this
was
um this whole building was maybe what do
you call it again where the where um all
the kids go with no
parents uh an orphan I thought this was
an orphan
maybe that's why there's so many ghosts
in one children's room orphaned not
[Music]
orphan why do I come up with
these really depressing story
lines something's wrong with
me one thing I have learned thanks to
watching don't end's videos is that if
there's a room where there's curtains
that you can suck you want to suck all
of
them and then you'll be
rewarded this the first time I'm doing
that
though
scam
ah no wait that's not a window I thought
that would give me another window
[Music]
maybe I got to suck this
too ah maybe that was part of
that maybe if I didn't suck the windows
at that point when I pulled the towel it
wouldn't have given me
money I don't
know we will never know
maybe okay I think I'm done with this
room right
[Music]
would be funny though if I could add oh
God I
F if if if I could add the head back on
like this with this
thing weird can look at the
mirror
no okay I'm going
[Music]
family room another new room okay
thought I saw everything
[Music]
already there's like never ever anything
in the drawers it's kind of lame
[Music]
okay I don't see anything
here but here there's definitely
something special in this room where am
I anyway hello am I on the completely
wrong path by any
chance cuz I know I need to go to a
different floor I was just I was I was
trying to get
[Music]
there I'm so bad at this
no I'm good okay I'm going the right way
okay
yeah yeah yeah I was thinking I should
set it straight still okay boo be
trap booby trap wait booby trap was a
was a word that's not for actual boobies
right they that's not what they mean
with that
right
surprisingly I feel so bad I don't want
to hurt him
I love him too
much oh my God that must have
hurt but must have hurt all those
bounces wait what was what does booby
trap mean if not booby like falling into
the Trap of boobies or
sa what does that actually mean
[Music]
oh okay I was hoping that if I listen
long enough I get something I was hoping
for
that a disguise hole a switch hidden on
the floor
[Music]
oh okay so it's not it doesn't have
anything to do with
boobies why did they where did the booby
come from
I don't understand
[Music]
Solarium this I'm sure this used to be a
really pretty room with lots of light
before it all broke down like this what
you
want no poies
in ow ow ow
[Music]
ow a bone and what two things in one
treasure chest
is that
allowed literally a trap for a booby a
type of bird in this case ah I
[Music]
see I think I heard of that before and I
I just needed to explanation
again cute
what a mischievous
devious Little
Ghost having a sleepo what the [\h__\h]
that's a booby trap too is it
[Music]
not wait I want to go
back okay
[Music]
instead of girls talk ghost
talk oh what about this
[Music]
one oh wa what
what I'm supposed to do that am I
not
what I almost walked through this room
without doing that I swear he's just
watching
he's now you're pretending to be asleep
aw that's
[Music]
cute I have to wake them up
huh ah ah I suck the bed sheets away
from them
I swear to
[Music]
God cute wait this just confirms my
orphanage uh
Theory cuz that's just childish
[Music]
behavior so cute
surprised I don't get hurt in that
process you're going to switch him again
oh
probably okay one is definitely
here this is
fun is this room even optional because
it's like I feel like I could have just
walked through
it look look it's optional but it would
be so sad if you miss out on
this is it required oh okay I get the
key from it ah I wouldn't have been able
to go through the door
[Music]
uh-huh
uhhuh now now I don't feel so smart
anymore about finding that but I think
maybe you would have tried to open the
door and then realize oh I can't go
through so let me inspect this room even
more eventually you look at the
[Music]
ceiling I guess this is a hint if you
think about it you saw the ghosts in
there and you think like wait why are
they not here shouldn't they be here
[Music]
yeah I found it before the game like
forced me to look for
it wait a
second is the
carpet
suckable no that sounded like Tu
suckerberg sounded like how you guys
pronounce that name even though it's
actually very German name
[Music]
those endless speed us again but hey
look where we are
ah we're here
now but previously I came through this
store
remember I wonder if there's anything
new here now cuz obviously I was never
supposed to go that far
before here the money
does the ghost still do the same thing
in
here
yeah he's
[Music]
mad I'm going through I'm not killing
any more
spiders
what open the door
H I am I I I I I I need to go in there I
couldn't think of a good reason just now
but I have
to I need another key
now I'm backtracking again after all
maybe
[Music]
now maybe now there's something new
here this feels new I be
[Music]
so I was going to say a soft Landing
but and then for a moment I thought I
just glitched through the floor but no
no no no let me go here first there's a
golden
balloon
why is it an invincible balloon
or just spit out
moneyy wait but I just the balloon but I
ah okay wait what no no
[Music]
whatever I didn't need that money I
don't need that extra money it's just a
few coins it really wasn't that much
anyway I want to try
[Music]
something can I land on top of ah
no and then can I go through the I want
to go through
it oh maybe not maybe that's not
possible it was one coin each yeah not
too bad right unless if you collect all
of wait if you collect all of them maybe
you would have gotten something really
nice
[Music]
so D
it just going to walk around it
I feel like there would be a lot of
people who kind of mess up there and
accidentally suck in the balloon I
wasn't sure I thought maybe I would have
to suck it all
[Music]
in that's a
sus
one I thought maybe I have to suck it
all in because maybe if I suck the
golden balloon in
maybe I uh get extra
[Music]
gold that's what I was still thinking
is there something with this
candle whatever I have the key whatever
I'm
[Music]
happy yeah it's a bit too punishing
you kind of already have to know what's
going to
[Music]
happen but maybe I just maybe I'm just
bad at
this maybe I'm just bad at this maybe
I'm just bad at
games see I fought so you get a gem if
you get all the money is oh I wasn't
going to be mad about the money but damn
is this supposed to be a
riddle I already know he's
there ah
ah I could have done it in one
go if I did
not Dodge him
[Music]
okay I think there's a difference
between sucking him him in without
pressing
a um because then I don't think you get
the gold P so you always
what let me out let me out you always
got
to
unlimited the [\h__\h] was that Z
[Music]
ho what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] you can't do that you
scare the [\h__\h] out of
me oh no one I'm playing spooky
game what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
maybe she warned me via
DM no she didn't she didn't she didn't
[\h__\h] she didn't [\h__\h] warn me she
didn't even warn
me JMA just JMA just came out of
nowhere opening the door to my apartment
and I I heard like footsteps through my
headphones so I was like it what what's
happening and then I heard footsteps
coming closer to me and I well I don't
know anything about Jemma coming today
to give me something she already came
over yesterday to give me stuff why
would she come again I mean you had a
controller but I didn't think she would
give it to me today and then she's just
walking over and I'm I'm
scared scared me
[Music]
jenma scared
me wait how do I wait I don't need the
controllers the joyes need thing wow
finally though I get I get the I get to
play a little bit
more
better suddenly game play improves by
500%
imagine I have a controller now not just
joycons I mean it's the joycon
controller
but this
[Music]
is why were the glasses
floating this feels different now ah I
got used to the joycons a little bit too
much yeah well thank you JMA but should
have warned
me I really did not expect
that I'm so
[Music]
scary I'm so scary think
she oh
[Music]
girl this feels
weird feels weird
[Music]
now always suck on the toilet roll guys
always that's the last one I missed a
couple huh
does this count as a test of Courage she
definitely be testing
me keep that in mind
yeah yeah um open open up FBI is that a
bday I don't like B they're they're
weird who the [\h__\h] has this kind of like
vacation section in their [\h__\h]
bathrooms why what
is oh I can lie on it oh it's going to
it's going to turn into a
trapo where are we going roof T oh
that's it's a secret entrance of the
rooft okay now it makes sense but
through the
bathroom through the bathroom though
that's
weird did you not have a better spot I
guess because the rooft pool is built on
top of the bathroom
coincidentally but build it somewhere
else looks nice though nice rooftop
pool okay oh
[Music]
wait I don't think I'm necessarily be
playing better with this after all ol oh
what oh we're not going to get it that
easily unless we do a perfect Olympic
dive and we fail immediately thank you
ollie for the
raid ah Ollie you probably don't know
but I read out your message in the
beginning of my
[Music]
stream
ol
[Music]
OE we're about to start a fight it seems
oh my behind right behind you
Luigi literally what happened to me just
now with JMA walking into my apartment
because she has extra
keys
oopsie no no no I see I see you I'm not
I'm not scared by that at
all oh we're playing hide and seek huh
oh but I can see you in the
water I figured it all
out a that was F for on we got another
try
okay oh there's two uh-oh oh there's
fre
[Music]
wait go it's in the way the diving thing
is in the
way get get out of there get out of
there
hey hey no no no I I not [\h__\h] fair
not [\h__\h]
Fair no I was not surprised by
that they claim they assume my surprise
but I was not surprised in fact
[Music]
oh
yeah I like this fight though it's cute
nice
[Music]
gimmick can we do anything with the
frogs in
[Music]
here like shoot something into their
mouths is there anything to shoot
[Music]
oh can we do that on the other side
too get the key no not
[Music]
yet I need to see if I can find any more
secrets no
really maybe there's
nothing okay I'll get the key oh but
wait I can't go from here
[Music]
all right that's a really cool looking
key I mean the face is kind of dorky but
hey what are you doing you little [\h__\h]
you're a friend though
right is it does he meet the dog for the
first time in Luigi's Mansion 2 or did
he already meet it in lui's mansion
one yeah
oh so at this point he doesn't really
know yet for sure if he's a friend or a
foe but probably by the end of this
we'll be
[Music]
friends where did that ghostly dog come
from now it's finished
[Music]
completely let's bring you back
okay yeah no just let me go directly to
the tray you you
oh yeah
hold below 30 again what how did I keep
on getting like 29
minutes
oh why is it always so
[Music]
bad
man wouldn't call it a speed run oh yeah
I didn't get those coins and that would
have led to another
Jewel I did lose a decent amount of
Health
G damn
it I think it's mostly the health if I
didn't lose that much health then it
wouldn't be so bad I
think okay but now we have to hunt the
[\h__\h] dog cuz he has my
key ah
ah we supposed to replay
levels yeah I think so too but we're not
doing that it's fine I'm I'm not a huge
collector I don't feel like I need to
100% each
game we're fine we're fine don't tendo
will do that for
me but we got the bull I think no we
didn't oh yeah we did o o o do gone key
theone the theone key the gon
key
[Music]
the that supposed to be a pun Doon on
his own is not a word though is
it Courtyard dog is in
[Music]
Courtyard dog gone
key dogon
key dog dog gone
Keon Theon is an
expression old cowboy Oh it's actually
something people say what in what case
what uh situation when do they say
it where is Birds always
[Music]
red oh my God I flashed my light and had
activated the Thunder I swear I can
control Thunder
now damn Luigi she certainly fought so
just now I
[Music]
think this [\h__\h] tree triggers me
got to do it again got to do it
again I tried to recreate the
moment there we
go I knew the direction I knew
everything okay Doo huh where are we
going why did you there are you ghost
peeing
as long as you were
happy than
you
no how does that work doggle shouldn't I
be seeing it for your body
though God damn
it wait so
what I
thought I thought that Trace would
remain oh is is not showing
[Music]
me exclamation marks I actually have to
look for him but I feel like he would be
behind it's
covered
what would he be here then I thought he
went left
side oh but he would probably go into
the garden maybe again oh no bone this
time
no
bone grey are you V light oh okay let's
see oh my God the
spiders golden
[Music]
spider
no oh my God wait why does why does it
affect me when I'm
inside okay probably not
[Music]
here ah uhhuh now okay he is over there
but I cannot go that way cuz he can go
for walls so I'll go this
way makes sense
H
oh
hello don't act like this is your first
time Luigi you freaking
Pretender such an
actor we should give him an
Oscar we have to do something specific
when this
happens ah
[Music]
hey but I want to go into the Garden
or how do I get there again
[Music]
wait what it's so dark I didn't see the
door was I thought I had to go for the
fountain oopsie thank you taimo
[Music]
bye-bye okay do where are you probably
got to use the lawn mower
[Music]
again
okay suck good
it's it's not
working
[Music]
why why that's so
weird know
like right
[Music]
there I did this before that's how it
worked Maybe ah because they don't want
me to
maybe they just simply don't want me to
I'm on the wrong side of the
garden how do I get to the other
[Music]
side it just doesn't work because the
game is blocking me from doing it
intentionally is there a way to go there
for here no right I don't that
[Music]
was I'm I'm
I'm
ah do I have to go really far roundabout
way
I mean I saw where the tracks went what
do you mean focus on the tracks I went
into the garden he wasn't there because
he's kind of like over the over the
hedges now I don't know how else to get
there without mowing the
[Music]
lawn was there another path
okay what I guess he didn't go into the
garden he turned around
there but I didn't see any po prints in
the other room did I
[Music]
H I activated the Thunder again
wow
thanks well I'm pretty
[Music]
Lost first room which room is the first
room to you
Yeah Yeah well yeah I went
there I went to where he
went do I have to
[Music]
it's just the same Footprints as
before a he comes out I thought that
means he goes through the
[Music]
wall to ass
dog oh no oh no go uh-huh [\h__\h] lawn
mower curse
you that's why I'm a cat
person okay let's go follow
him let's go follow him he
went over there
a why
why a it's those ghost again
[Music]
ah okay wait I can see their Footsteps
in the
botles that's count that's
[Applause]
count still one left can't let my guard
down yet ah oh no a no no no not fair
not
fair
so oh the
flame turned blue too it used to always
be red over
there what what is this
[Music]
why is it so
spooky
what was he scared by The Disappearance
of the furniture the French Brut aren't
I beautiful
a yes you are how do we play this game
[Music]
again oh I found him
ah
you I should play this game without
catching
boo because I I don't want to hurt them
I don't want to support this kind of
behavior this is bull abuse AB
[Music]
abuse [\h__\h] I'm so bad at this I'm
aiming wait I forgot how to do this
while I'm doing it
wait I forgot how to
do wait
one no he took the door bring the door
[Music]
back
ow h
um
guys
[Music]
hello
I how much of OBS disconnected a little
bit how much of that did you not see cuz
I hope you didn't see much of it because
that was
embarrassing I I I didn't want to him I
wanted to give him more time to live
let's not talk about
it let's not talk about
it none of this really
happened wait
ah can't go there for here I forgot
[Music]
well at least I got the
boo hello dog we're going up now eh quit
playing games with me wait was there
always a bed
here can I get some health from the bed
that would be nice I don't know how the
hell I get down to
25 it's quite
embarrassing ah when he's gone it turns
back to Red it's like ghost action means
Flames become
blue but I would assume he he went up so
I just have to go
[Music]
up nice heart thank
you the bed seems new I thought so
too but then again never know oh what is
I he's I thought he was carrying
something new but that's just just like
the the shadow of the gem I suppose that
we got
before okay let's let's just
um move
on ah now you go there fine with me
that's where I came
[Music]
from can't get the spiders from here
oh he went he went up
[Music]
right that was so
Random I see the the steppies there but
I don't see where he actually poured it
through you think I have to play this
ball game with him
is he in one of these could that be or
did he just go
[Music]
up
no a [\h__\h]
spider well the bone might definitely
come in handy at this
right
okay what did we bring back in any case
he oh
[Music]
wa oh this is how you properly do it
okay I I would assume he's inside of
this so if I play it he will come
out cute he's so happy to have someone
to play with I guess the other ghosts
ignore him and don't play properly with
him oh that's why there's a path in the
back only for us to play around here
ah I can't jump over
that did he already
[Music]
leave bro
bro wao
[Music]
okay let's focus on the big one now what
are you eating Fri is that a whole
turkey or a chicken or
what
shees
ow she's eating real
food I don't know what the hell that was
guys I don't know I didn't need to get
hit that often that was not necessary
[Music]
did he go this
way oh actually Maybe
not maybe he went up and I got to go
with the
balloons does the game want me to go
with the balloons
[Music]
or are there steppies oh oh yeah
ah did he go for the window did he join
him in the
toilet wait the red guy is
gone guess he's done with his
business
finally took him a while is it still
occupied or may I enter
wait no I think he was done for a while
yeah right right right right right we
killed
[Music]
him is he in
there
no no I don't I don't I don't want that
again an accident
[Music]
what does this
mean I guess he went up right that would
be a logical
conclusion wait I
can't there's an invisible wall
oh okay I just have to check I don't
know
man I don't
know I'm a cat person I can't read the
dog's
mind it's not my
specialty it is
not the language I understand
[Music]
just looking for some things here but
okay go this
[Music]
way ah right there's no door here
whatever
was oh
dear no no me Al me
Al oh immediate
stons stons are you in here do oh yes
you are wait
uh they have funny
[Music]
voices let's focus on the dog now
please is the
she ew stop blinking my face I hate
it oh finally we get to hunt
[Music]
him let's
go
I
no we captured him I thought we would
play a while
longer oh no
yellow it's okay we we we capturing we
bring him to safety we we get him an
owner we get him
adopted this is just like you know any
other dog rescue mission out there in
the wild did we're capturing them but
then we're giving them a better
life 20
minutes but I don't even I don't know
like some missions are just longer than
others but oh my god really I get silver
on first try for once
really I thought I lost a lot of
health
NY must have been the controller we have
eight DMS again what the
[Applause]
[\h__\h] waya is worried like she's asking
me what I'm going to wear she wants to
match
with her limited casual wardrobe what am
I going to wear I don't know what I'm
going to wear
uh not sure yet um I'm still streaming
in
pajamas I
can tell you when I get
[Music]
dressed
okay oh my God so many
[Music]
DMS
uhhuh
[Music]
uh-huh okay
okay
[Music]
uh just a
what I
I have to write a message
[Music]
okay okay okay sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry
[Music]
sorry
uh
okay trying to the cold while one
l oh
drink hydrate guys
hydrate hydrate hydrate who's
Dr hyr how you doing hydrate or
dehydrate that's aggressive I like it my
butt hurts is
uncomfortable Maybe
maybe I don't know my pillows are too
big you know what would help surely is
[Music]
something little
snack
because I'm a bit
hungry need a chair upgrade
nah honestly this is so much more than I
I thought I would have to stream on like
a normal dining chair or even on the
floor but I have a gaming chair they
freaking provided me with a gaming chair
what more could I ask for
[Music]
nothing so I have a
comini sandwich I bought like
yesterday thinking that I might need it
it's quite a nice one it's the BLT one
actually fa tea sandwich
oh m m
nah not one of the whole life chairs no
no those are too expensive to give to
me actually I should probably write to
GMA too
[Music]
um CH my
oh
oh oh
[Music]
problem
solved problem s
[Music]
yeah that was your
problem let's check out The Ghost and
the dog will he have a comment about the
dog rank
[Music]
up
wait upgrade wonder if
I could you get all these upgrades
really early and be like really
overpowered early in the
game and on the other hand could you
like never get these upgrades and finish
the whole
[Music]
game like never collect the money or
so happy birthday
UMR
Canada Oh Canada
oh can't
escape I should have looked then I could
have stopped it for
sure what do you mean that can wait if
the dog can escape from it then all the
freaking ghosts that I caught so far
could
Escape so maybe that takes priority you
fixing the containment unit HH e get
what you think don't you think
so here you
[Music]
go wait one more thing sorry one more
thing one more check
[Music]
one more thing to
check huh
okay okay now I'm back back in the game
and I had half of the sandwich so
there's two slices two halves of the
sandwich I ate one half it was really
good yummy yummy yummy
I finished my analysis of the spectr
gentic parac composition what Luigi got
a headache from that me
too you think that's funny you think
that's funny huh torturing us with your
knowledge and your
intellect taka how do I put
this I basically as their Dark Moon
pieces where their friend is
hiding their friend is in the their
pieces wouldn't call it a friend but
okay wow so
go Tre that is the last one it had a had
a boss evil evil sign is that the boss
one the boss
level let's go finally finally finally
finally finally finally
finally the piece we're looking for is
located in the treehouse at the very top
of the big tree surprised would have
thought we were on the right track after
[Music]
all yes the
key here's the special key it wasn't
tough to fix no
gy okay let's go to The
Treehouse no I'm going to do another
match I'm at least going to started I
don't know if I can finish it but I
think I I think I could we just got to
be a little bit faster than this
one this one took me 4
hours yeah I'm going to try to be fast
with it I don't know if we can at least
get halfway through that would be
good the other one took you 4 hours to I
wish but this one is obviously like more
intricate already than the last one I've
been trying harder on i' I've been
tanging less so that tells you this
F this Mansion it was just like more
difficult and all and every Mansion is
probably going to get longer and more
difficult and more intricate the first
Mansion was a tutorial Mansion so the
only reason I took so long is because I
was tanging so much it could have been
much shorter and this is just like maybe
the normal time you need to finish a
mansion but in that case in that case I
think
um
wow in that case I think yeah we might
not be able to finish another Mansion
but we can attempt wow here staircase oh
is this going to is this a thing again
with the
possible appearances of the
[Music]
ghosts oh was that
right that means it's correct
huh oh my
God okay okay
well we got to remember it or does it
change each time I I I think yeah oh
it's already
set and it it doesn't go away anymore
okay okay okay well I don't mind getting
a few ghosts wait why would I go this
way or can I go that way
now cuz the other lights are off I don't
know maybe I
could but wait a second ah it gives me a
preval I was like why are the lights not
on
there I Nexus middle Dam
it but I didn't see past that it gives
you a preview if you fought a ghost I
guess good that got so frustrated
really but it's okay like it locks the
lights in and then you
know then you
know not too
bad got to pay attention though to the
preview although it's going to be so far
wait wait wait wait wait uh wait I can't
see it's so far it's so far it's so far
it's so
far I don't know middle uh [\h__\h] I can't
I was trying to see
okay good I didn't lock in what do you
mean she Oh you mean she didn't lock in
as an she didn't lock in like a gamer oh
wait I don't get a ghost this time
uhhuh wait I'm not looking ah ah it's
hard to look it's so
far middle and left I think and then
[Music]
it's hard to tell from here ah they
already turned back on
[\h__\h] okay oh
wait no I thought I I thought I saw
another hint
but I think maybe it's double
no maybe wear
glasses yeah the music got a bit faster
[Music]
wait oh God I can't see
it it's hard to tell while I'm walking
and um okay middle right middle middle
left
okay and then middle again maybe middle
middle oh see the lights got a little
bit smaller
there
oh
middle okay so here from here on out I
don't
know maybe right
no that's quite the progress
though but there's no way I can see so
well from below but maybe maybe the hand
stay up longer if you are going from
that far maybe they stay up
[Music]
longer can you just go up straight
without without like just ignoring the
lights at this
point no I'm not going to risk it no I
don't think
can uh
uhoh I can't look up I think it's
[Music]
middle middle
no can't
tell uh right left right left right uh
that's kind of all I
got ah
[Music]
okay and now I don't
know
left each fall is going to be longer and
longer and
longer oh and it those stairs that you
kind of turn over they stay like that
interesting what does that mean so can I
walk here no
okay ah the ones that didn't turn over
are they can't turn over because they
are they are like the real paths
okay not that that really helps me of
anything come on don't get stuck no
don't get stuck
I can't see it's too far I'm not going
to even look I'm not going to bother
looking until I'm further
[Music]
Above This is maybe a little bit
unnecessarily long honestly I like it
but it's too long okay
left
right when they turn back on it's also
kind of easy to see Left Right middle
okay when they turn back on it's pretty
easy to see but now we only had three
left so obviously it was easy to
tell they don't overlap so much
there yeah they could have like had
maybe less of this like maybe 70% only
of this less than it
30% I would have been fine in my opinion
[Music]
he does a little he does a little
triumphant little spin
cute yeah cool segment though I don't
have a problem with it I a
prob of the
[Music]
segment okay let's go let's go let's go
no time to
waste care about extra
stuff I don't know if there is anything
you could get
but
bedtime good night yeah EST is probably
pretty late now
huh we're on top of the
world I look in
there no well at 2: a.m. at 2 a.m. isn't
too bad for people who stay up late
kute how do we deal with
[Music]
you how do I deal with
you okay wait wait how do I deal with
you
oh oh okay long jump pull
oh
okay what are you you got
[Music]
horns
okay
nice and then we just dodge until it
happens again oh what the
hell oh that's a little bit different
[Music]
now oh
just do the big jump again
please big jump
please maybe now big jump big jump big
jump can I trigger it
somehow oh oh there it
is
uh what is that
floating ah it's like a timer I think
no what ah did I mess it up oh no I
still got a chance
okay it up
bastard okay let's go let's continue
this
Rodeo maybe last
round it's like eyebrows or something
when when does the big
job um they like kind of turn into some
kind of timer if you look at it that way
ow oh
dangerous okay ah thank you see up there
they're spining and then they start like
turning into something else and lighting
up and then probably going back to their
original rooll
[Music]
yippee is that it
cool see I did pretty well with this one
I did good with this one I immediately
understood this one it was more
intuitive oh we turned it into
stairs to get the corrupted
Crystal huh why did that thing just fall
down wow W I want to shoot it in the
[Music]
hole Dark Moon
acquired do I get to chill here or do
you teleport me
immediately luig are you okay who would
have thought another processor goost
guarding the dark moon pie not at all
planted there by me for my entertainment
no no he was one one tough costumer but
you really took care of business cha cha
nice work my boy I'm sure to from up
there is nice but let's go back
okay that should be at least
[Music]
silver that's the thing yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah I was wondering about
that oh it's one of those sticky
[Music]
things to
you
cute ooh 10 minutes she's serious about
it she's so serious
gold my
gold I did it KY will you stop making
fun of me now for sucking at this game
it's sucking is what you meant to do in
this game can't blame me for
sucking that's pretty good Redemption
Arc
[Music]
I got the gold thank you you're not even
bad you just Yapp a lot that's true that
adds a lot to the time but no I've been
I've been embarrassing myself of some
fights for
[Laughter]
sure
aha great thank you never doubt you
thank you tot will never forgive or
forget me neither [\h__\h] him he really was
kind of annoying in the way like he
would like stand one meter away from me
and that meant like he was too far what
do you mean then why doesn't he come
closer it smells like
popcorn see like he's I think that dude
he plants all these ghosts and then he
I'm his experiment and like he's doing
all of this just for his [\h__\h]
entertainment like why does he even have
popcorn to begin with huhuh
interesting ghost is the ghost of a goat
or
[Music]
what my brain's been percolating on the
subject of those processor Gods I don't
think it's a coincidence that both of
the processors we've seen had dark moon
piece is in them speaking of which let's
get our dark moon piece all cleaned up
shall we
T yipp oh my God look at that why I want
an
improvement there's no boo there yeah
you can't get a boo there right see this
is the new one Old Clockworks that looks
weird this Factory once produced the
world's finest clocks and time
measurement devices you watch probably
comes from here and you don't even know
it okay a timely entrance
okay let's go before I was first
abandoned this place once produced the
finest time pieces ever made but years
of neglect have turned it into a
favorite haunt for ghosts so it wasn't
surprising when the Periscope detected a
dark moon piece inside of the Old
Clockworks
Che after tuning the Periscope a little
more I was actually able to pinpoint its
precise location the top of the clock
tower surprise the top of course it's on
the top of the Clock
Tower always it's always in the hardest
to reach
spots let me try to eat my second part
of the sandwich so
let can make it through the next three
maybe 3
hours comfortably and not be cuz by then
when I meet with way then I should have
empty stomach again maybe
[Music]
by this Mansion you mean the upcoming
one
M well good night thanks for coming
[Music]
by oh there's some people who weren't
here when I first mentioned I'm meeting
way
okay yeah I'm meing way for dinner m
cuz she was like hey does anybody want
to go to dinner anybody anybody and I
was like me me
immediately I'll go with you anybody
else can join too I said anybody else
can join too but I have claimed the
Wayne don't want her to be
alone
uhoh m
that's that feels pretty original at
least it's a sand level
[Music]
huh strategy meeting
maybe I remember like from some other
event I think it was also the ID Club
maybe or something else but way
doesn't does not prepare much for these
kind of events like she doesn't train
much behind the
scenes so we'll see how it
goes what the [\h__\h]
oh there another one of those
gold m
[Music]
hello
mhm it is
um free3
no could could it be
um it
oh is that the actual time right now I'm
kind of is
yeah but I F my switch had a different
time okay
you know I find this already very
interesting because in terms of like
level
design I feel like when you think of a
sand level for luiges Mansion free
making it all like pyramid themed that's
that's kind of like an easy one to think
of kind of on the
nose but where do this go
oh yeah I see that ah what the hell ah
what the is explode okay oh my God
what but for this I think this is very
original like what is this
even it doesn't seem so obvious like oh
let's make a sand level oh okay but like
what exactly is it going to be um yeah
let's just make pyramids and
stuff it's just too how do I get
there maybe
later sand of f but like combined with
Clockworks that's kind of
cool I like that do I have to make it uh
a specific time but which one there's
several the one on
the on the top of the or it doesn't even
matter do I just turn it and see what
happens
no should I do 3:30 oh God oh God thank
God I know how to read the time for now
um okay wait
um now I know how to do this 3 years ago
I would like crumble under the pressure
right now I would [\h__\h]
cry what is this
not wait what the [\h__\h]
the time
just wasn't that kind of
it
230 but this is one two no
that's but it's like going not where I
wanted to
go can I go back oh yeah I can
here no that's why I was trying to
go
H
okay
yipp so me analyzing the time up there
was the right thing to
do look through what's going on here huh
spoiler me about the Next Room
no idea what's going
on anything
else oh another bomb wait can we use the
bomb
somehow yeah can you blow up this stuff
here so I can pass through
oh oh
nice big brain
okay what about these
turbines is there anything else besides
money coming out of
it maybe just
money really
oh Money
Tree tiny smaller smaller Money
Tree okay I'm going to go
in I
think so curious about that pop
but time will tell right time will tell
us what to do
I'm going to
intrude he's mad because I'm not taking
my shoes off but I took my hat off for a
moment at least
hey we saw Luigi's beautiful
hair
what what
[Music]
what I pushed it but I feel like it was
also moving on its
own oh maybe not maybe it was
[Music]
it's not working is it
too
little look down look down
[Music]
put it
down yeah I hear something too sounds
like it's coming from up there
[Music]
actually okay maybe that was never
necessary
[Music]
can I go through oh
yeah
uh I guess a bomb would be nice here
will I ever get bombs
[Music]
yeah there's a
boot
[Music]
somewhere let's go down
again it's is it was it
[Music]
usually uh something that I could like
move oh
uh maybe he wasn't there on the left
side
[Music]
ah where is he
huh what does what does all of this
[Music]
mean
ah no I was just moving because I was
blowing on
it I
[Music]
I thought I was on the right track well
let me just open this for now
money oh golden oh or a yellow one I
don't know this one's
special
why it's heavy isn't
it not sure what for oh where is
the ah let's you unravel them oh I see
yeah the ghost was trying to do
that ah so maybe he's in one of these
but this one should have
gold did that
no oh he has a
key hey hey golden key it's still gold
made out of
gold let's unravel them all unravel the
mystery okay that was just
money I don't think this is the believer
it's
probably the green one over there
oh isn't that the one that was uh
standing there on the
boxes oh hello
be
[Music]
nice oh oh
okay is that the one that was standing
on there maybe maybe it's the other
[Music]
one come on ban show yourself I know you
like to play with me
maybe the boo was not in any of these is
there one
left this
one maybe just another spider
[Music]
though a
finally oh computer says yeah was that
mean eh computer nerds tell
me
okay oh
baby oh don't be scared I will end your
misery
ow
ho that sure look
painful got him stuck in the right place
hey give me that money hey hey hey hey
hey hey hey come down here don't
disappear get down get
down get down I can't go up there yet
will it
disappear please please come over here
oh wait if I get you to if I get you
to get under there yeah yeah yeah come
down come
down please please on it won't come
down wait I think it's gone no it's
still there it won't come
down
no [\h__\h]
it okay I got the boo and I got a key
was the key for this
door dam
It Whatever at least I got the boo
maybe it won't disappear oh you're
making bombs a big
one um
[Music]
hello death perception or I just
can't oh oh dear oh
dear oh okay
[Music]
that's why you don't try to Bonk a bomb
oh
yeah
mindlessly
not
very
save
oh no no no no no no no no no
no I hate ghosts
[Music]
all my homies hate
ghosts I do I do what if I pull this
one
oh is that going to be an exit
[Music]
eventually
one oh money
[Music]
and here's some money
too and there's some people I'm I'm just
opening the path for the
[Music]
venting uh
imposters basically asking
them to kill me but
okay I could go for here
nice we are in the room they're asking
us to be
in lots of
bombs more
bombs some
rat what's going on in here is that a
rat
world oh it's a rat's Spinning
Wheel but the
the spider is using it that's
beak what what did you learn from that I
didn't learn anything from that
[Music]
Luigi it
oh ah ah I suck him up after I activate
them I think but what do I even want to
blow up I'm not
sure I'm not so sure
oh godam
it
okay the door no I could try
that H we missed the first
[Music]
one okay um
what a cat pick him
up then what are they for what is the
point I tried
[Music]
closed okay hey what they don't follow
me and I can't pick them
up ah I think maybe I can pick him up
with X
no clear all the
sand um it doesn't go away though not
really
well let's look at this maybe I have to
just look at
it thank you oh yeah we just need to
observe it to have this dude call
us M clock hands are missing those
ghosts arew a club a bunch you see the
clock hands operate the clock tower gate
the ghosts figured that out and hid them
from us incredible thanks for the
membership it's actually pretty terrible
it would take a strong surpr of those
ghost hand M scan the area for any
powerful
okay okay oh wait that was the whole
first mission no there's
more ah this is what the bombs are
for I already activated a couple of them
wait no the bombs are gone oh no they're
not but like
wait going to come here come here I'm in
in
wait maybe we can do it without the
bumps I think we
can
[Music]
right oh ah ah ah ah
wait I think ghost combat I'm bad at now
with the controller
generally still not the best but I think
you can tell a
[Music]
difference gu X near the wall my sense
is tingling tingle are you tingle tingle
Tingle are you
tingle Carle
room cargo
vom oh
yellow I have 5 DMS again there is just
so much going
[Music]
on
mhm
okay MH
[Music]
um
wow okay uh what
[Music]
blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah mhm the drafting office but by my
wasn't it funny what I just said though
the cargo
room if only there was a car in the
cargo
room huh
W is that water or sand looks like
both that was a riddle
apparently not a very difficult
one but I want credit
anyway anything else here
[Music]
do you get something for cleaning up the
the webs still maybe
not thank
you thank
you not again falling down the stairs I
have PTSD from
that so uh
uh um how do they help
me I was I'm trying to utilize them you
know but I don't really see a
[Music]
point these are just normal ghats I
don't need bombs to help
me unless what the
hell what the hell
stairs are so
scary I often think about when I walk
downstairs I often think about like
accidentally
stepping on my own foot and then falling
down and
dying it is quite a real fear that I
have
[Music]
yeah say
oh wait wait I was trying to get to the
box I know that there's a hole
there not going to happen the first
time
F okay I get rewarded
yipp I was turning around I don't know
why he has to turn around in a big
circle
movement
braah is this a fake door
no real it's
real
Ohi okay but
uh seems like a dead
end is that my gold over there or is
that just a random
one this room
maybe I just fall down here oh I
can't
a watching you life once wait what if I
what what if I what if I use the dark
the dark
light can I get the path back yes I can
oh my God I almost gave up on
it
ah
y does that work for all of these
[Music]
paths go down explore okay does it work
here yeah
ah
sorry this is going on for too long
okay
wo let's turn this big ass Clockwork
it's barely
turning is it doing
anything does it need me to do
that a it's turning on its
[Music]
own now I can turn it backwards again
you know
no thought that's what was going to
happen thanks for the MIP
Rea you recovered the boo gold was that
the boo gold you sure
[Music]
are you
sure
[Music]
yeah what is his
room
[Music]
office oh oh oh no oh there's a weird
pink ghost again
[Music]
wrong room what oh wait yeah this no
what do you mean wrong room this is the
room I have to go go to
actually
okay why why are they gatekeeping
me wait let me open this first check no
okay wait wait wait if I do it
closer to
there a there's so
many yeah
Yahoo I don't want to lose the
[Music]
money getting two always feels good free
would be even better
man okay now we can try that whole thing
again this time no one will gatekeep
me what's that a compass
[Music]
for
what just looks fancy I gu hello
hello must special Compass I'll bring
you back so I can take a gander hey I
want to finish looking at this room wait
wait wait I want to suck off the paper
of the walls oh yes bro he's always
like Cliff hanging
me well yeah I took my time okay okay
okay shut up I didn't lose that much
health is that what bronze should be
silver at least I got the boot
too hey boo I have another pun name for
you next time you need a pun name
instead of boy toy you can be my boot
toy they won't use that because it's a
game for children
[Laughter]
but children won't get it they won't
understand it you can put the jokes like
that any anywhere children won't get it
and if they get it then they already
knew
so I really thought getting the dark
moon piece would be a Bree really really
did you think so really you are even
naive or you're just messing with me
think you're messing with me you know by
now how this works this is the second
game in
this
series uh yeah look at the
compus looking up how to become a Bo
don't die don't
die looks
cool why don't we use compasses anymore
huh they look so nice like real
compasses and and and Sun
clocks Sun dials is that what they call
that
actually wait is a sun clock a sun
[Music]
dial kids these days
man perhaps you'd like to visit the
vault in the meantime
no no I would like not to do that I
would like to move on in the story thank
you the special Compass reveal an
alternate entrance to the
underground how did the compass do that
I thought it just chose
directions I've M it for you whip out
the Dual scream and take a look
M how you can't read the ancient Sun
runes wow such an uneducated little [\h__\h]
brat takik doesn't know how to read hero
damn did she even go to
school huh okay can't even predict the
freaking future by looking at the
stars ridiculous
pathetic looking for the clock hands
okay Professor L games I don't know I
never play them
hi
hogp can't even speak Latin I did learn
it for a while short while very short
while the Clockworks Court find your way
on the ground
okay let's speedrun this
guys but I still you know there's so
much that you have to like look for you
don't want to miss out on anything it's
hard to speed run this
this ominous music yo feel like I'm in a
spaceship I need way under theground
they
say could I be needing to go this
way no
maybe inside is fine and this this time
we go
left what what is
demotic demoic
what uh straight I mean
actually ah
n the fun thing about public sundal is
that some old ones can still be used by
everyone even a giant molive can be
sundal yeah yeah yeah no I know um I
remember my hometown has a uh a public
sun
dial I remember that one although I
never tried to read it didn't I don't
think I expected myself to be able to
read a Sund dial when I wasn't even able
to read a real clock maybe now I could
give it a
try but yeah speaking of my hometown did
you see Lily
Pichu
and uh her brother went to
Austria and went to my hometown I was
like what the [\h__\h] why why that's so
random that feels so Random out of all
the places oh it's a boyfriend I don't
know out of all the places she could go
to I feel uh so surprised and and
flattered that they would go to freaking
sbook what the hell why I wonder where
else they went H but it seems like they
were enjoying
themselves
[Music]
H gets quite yeah we do get a lot of
Tourism and and zbur also gets a lot of
Tourism yeah but I was still surprised
like mhm it still feels so Random like
why not go to I don't know like the more
obvious choices in Europe like Paris
London and Rome and you know it just
feels so random but I I appreciate that
it really
cultured maybe they already went to all
those places and couldn't think of much
more I think maybe Sound of Music was a
part of it but they seem relatively
young are are like I know that in
America like everybody knows sound of
music but I feel like it's more of like
an adult thing I feel like people in
their 20s maybe have lower chances of
having seen it but maybe I'm wrong maybe
everybody gets to see it in America even
young people whoa that's so funny
because I told you before guys that in
Austria
normally
normally people haven't seen it unless
they're like 50 or 40
maybe but anybody below that normally
doesn't really find any reason or
motivation to watch it I only saw it
because they made us watch it in hotel
School h h
what she's ver plus she looks like much
younger sound music still has a major
following yippee tourism go spend your
money in my country come on
guys
well it's it's a fun cute movie I still
like it very much I'm glad that I was
forced to watch
it sometimes I wonder about you so what
what what do you want what what's your
problem
when to all that trouble finding the
special Compass just ignore your
map did he
just what do you mean ignore my
[Music]
map he called me
out what he called me out I don't see
like the usual exclamation mark though
is that X for me like to go to I thought
that was something
else I noticed it but I I I I was
looking for exclamation marks if
anything
bro exclamation marks is how you usually
go about it don't
you wait is it wait wait wait
damn you really called me
out okay okay okay
bro he knows he knows that I need to
speedrun this so he's trying to help
me
[Music]
yeah
storm someone's stuck in in there and
once to get out I have to save
[Music]
them I'll help you ah you didn't need
help did
[Music]
you okay o this is like a bunker huh
maybe survival
[Music]
bunker ooh the jam is there I think
yay
[Applause]
Boni okay okay I only missed the first
one so far that's pretty
good ah I thought I could suck it up and
then throw it somewhere what the hell
why no more bumps it's a one time
[Music]
thing okay um
okay does it stay like that though
[Music]
no
stone
[Music]
hey no don't f
do I have to go around to place it
[Music]
properly he just he won't shoot it up
there guess it's too heavy to be
shot a very uncooperative pebble
[Music]
I don't think it wanted to be shot I
tried uh dead L probably probably too
heavy what the hell
I I can't see it's too
dark what is that oh money money
machine in the
bunker are those stones
don't think there's a point in doing
this it's too
dark wait is this is the bomb was I
supposed to lead it here to this Stone
can I get another
one
no oh no
[Music]
[Laughter]
I think I was supposed to lead it there
I'm so sad would that have brought me
another
Jewel thank you for
watching see you again wait look at
that follow me no oh no it's for here
[Music]
only what is
that ooh
Canyon
nrows America is so
beautiful welcome to the Grand Canyon
I've never been here before one day I
want to
go I want to
go oo another h
USA
[Music]
hello oh it's a
mirror oh what a smartly place miror I
no many no matter how many times I
shot at
that I did not realize I mean I was
getting suspicious of it
oh it's hiding ah it's hiding in that
one I have
it where' it Go ah no it trapped me oh
oh let's go let's go let's go let's go
it's my
chance I got it I got it okay ah finally
it's bright in here relatively bright
can't fool me
[Music]
again I don't know why I chose that path
first can I go the for the other door
too or is that one
[Music]
locked ah e
wait where are we before we get called
out again is there an exclamation mark
no this might have a bomb again let's
look first if we can find oh no this has
a
bomb but I can't lead it anywhere
anyway I don't know where I would
want a
bomb I guess they're just to bamboozle
me
used to have a Grand Canyon nightmare
when where i' visit with family would
camp out and in the morning they left
without me I went to the other side so
you tried to jump it end of nightmare oh
God midf fall mid
[Music]
jump
uhhuh careful who knows what is this
supposed to be a riddle it's pretty easy
to tell what you're
saying ch I like how he never really has
much to say feels like we're
like oh this is interesting it's
watching me but it also with that gem on
its head reminds me somehow of be
boo it's a secret level like that other
one oh
not let me out
[Music]
wait what what did he just hide there
I'm not sure what it was he's hiding
there and the
[Music]
boot he went
down so do I want to go for what they
hid oh it's a
bomb okay then I'm going for the go wait
H but what were we looking at
at I'm not sure what we were looking
at that's
weird I he invisible the other
barrels ah
[Music]
ah I thought we were looking here but it
was
weird
[Music]
now oh yeah
okay so the thing I placed was the bomb
though right because that that was the
left
barrel and then here's where the
boo put nothing I
guess originally there was also a bomb
in
there okay but we didn't get the pool
yet not yet
[Music]
M hit slide oh that looks like
fun
uh uh really we're not going to be
sliding down of course we
oh wait do I get the money oh yeah I get
the
money cute little segment
okay
yippee a little bit delayed yippe
[Music]
I hope this is the way they want me to
go because the other
door where I went through first I
abandoned that
[Music]
one boss incoming the Quarry isn't that
like a horror game or
show
[Music]
door let's disturb the spider sh we
uh-oh that's what I get for disturbing
the
spider can I go over here
no game first time viewer really hello
yellow
Yello
welcome you are welcome to watch me be
miserable at this
game but I'm still having fun that's all
that matter
[Music]
no I got
one I got
one
oopsie
oh what's so funny to you thanks for the
membership gift
maybe they're laughing with me and not
at me
huh I remember hearing that a lot in my
childhood oh we're not laughing at you
we're laughing with you really really
really
[Music]
though
[\h__\h] okay they're all in one
cluster ah how do I still mess up
[Music]
huh wait did I not purpose properly kill
that
one no that's a different
one at least I can dodge now she says
while totally dodging
I hate
[Music]
myself what how's there
four okay now there's only
two he was
saying f you I'm almost dying I'm almost
[Music]
dead that's probably only going to be a
bronze
[Music]
again what the [\h__\h] what what more ghost
oh but I get
Triple is there a fourth
[Music]
one ah
a I thought he killed me I thought he
killed me in that moment when there was
a heart right next to me
[Music]
man that
was very very close
y
oh is that just telling me to go there
or are we creating
[Music]
something
a what
B I kind of um forgot about you
already are you still there no where are
you
uh-oh oh
[Music]
bounce bounce bounce bounce bounce
bounce
boun I feels like we're playing that
game um
pinball pinball with
boo they should make a little game out
of
that oh wait you're still around oh I
forgot about you I forgot you was I
thought we were done
[Music]
where'd he go up there is he
up no no B please you can't you
can't oh what the hell
no oh please
[Music]
M
no no the whole mission the whole
mission the whole mission
I no but I don't have to get the gems
again that I got so far right uh that I
got I don't know did I get a single
one
[\h__\h] no no no
that resent me so hard but bro I
was I was actually I think my I wasn't
oh I wasn't doing that badly was
I I was trying but they just threw so
many enemies at
me
bro
BR I was trying no no there is so much
oh God what did we do here um Stone
[Music]
a any gems no I think gems I have to get
again don't
[Music]
I do you guys
know I'm pretty
devastated holy
[\h__\h] oh I don't know I don't want to
like double check everything again I
don't remember where I got gems was
there any in here I feel like there
might
be is this just a bomb yeah no no no no
no no no no no
no don't
remember ah ah yes Gem Gem Gem Gem Gem
Gem
[Music]
really devastated at that I hope I I'm I
hope I'm not forgetting anything else
here that was just a bomb
[Music]
but I wonder about this Stone wait maybe
we
can come here no it just it won't
even go over there so maybe that's for
another
time
okay blow it
up I got to play that whole like hiding
game over there
too m
yeah I think Luigi was thinking the
exact same
thing
[Music]
m is it scary or more goofy it's
definitely more goofy I did have a few
shook moments but it's not an actual
scary
game that's just me
oh wait how do I not
get I know that's you're thereare I know
that's you're
thereare ah there we
[Music]
go St relatively fast
I'm trying to be as fast as I can I
looked into that door but then I decided
to go back so let's just go straight
now this was yeah the little riddle
there's just bombs in there for now
[Music]
so can do this already and then I look
at
the the weird be boo corpse
yellow
M
out it's scary to people that get
excited by the minions ride at
[Music]
Universal you think that's funny
huh we'll see if that's still fun when I
put you in the usual
room can I drink
[Music]
[Applause]
water
[Music]
okay actually I Saw the Wheel up there
is there nothing you can do with the
wheel no
um
a I feel like he resets his position
when I turn on the light so
often and I don't know if that's really
what's happening it's
[Music]
annoying we're not done yet Luigi
although this one H didn't this one just
have the another bomp in
it it's okay we're going to revive it
anyway oh no nothing at all
okay how long is my sentence Oh I wasn't
actually going to throw you in but uh if
you're asking like that
perhaps I should send
you to it
do you
want how
[Music]
about I don't know one
month okay let's
ride the highway to money oh okay maybe
bouncing is good bouncing off the walls
I think I got the maximum amount of
money this time
woohoo no Hearts this time man
[Music]
the bone wait did I get this last
time probably not because then I I might
have survived there I might have
[Music]
survived now this time I don't really
need it
though okay we're back isn't this where
I died
oh yeah oh
yeah oopsie I thought I could cancel
this cut
scene
okay
morning can I go inside here
no a couple of wild theats just try up
at my workplace dang are those pretty
are you is that a joke or did they
really maybe try singing to
[Music]
them no I should have known that this
time I was kind of just remembering it
as I was doing it chica no no I was I
was I
was distracted by my sh
um okay this is where I died right
because it was just so much
after after one
another okay already got rid of two of
them the ones without the
[Music]
shovel come on now come on come on come
on
[Music]
wait this is filling up with sand for
how long I'm not going to die in here
right with the sand that's not going to
be the reason of my
death oh another one came
out D dodging guys I'm
[Music]
dodging another one how many are there
do it do it do it oh suddenly the sand
decides this is enough this is where
we'll
[Music]
stop do it what is this weird Showdown
okay and next is the pink
[Music]
ones wrong
direction oh let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go let's go
[Music]
no no no no no
no would you look at
that and a
boo wait did
[Music]
I why not
boo oh wait no so boo boo will still
show up if I do this right yeah
thought I did something wrong I thought
I forgot a step before coming
[Music]
here
no I hate collecting these
[Music]
sometimes okay boltin with extra
gravy I didn't see the gravy before
[Music]
wa leave me
alone not sure what that does like when
you're in the middle of the boo
[Music]
fight
oh does it spawn him there maybe
[Music]
poor po suck him in suck him in wait in
that moment are you supposed to flash
him normally
or do I have to get him again
anyway ow I'm already down to 40 HP even
though I'm doing so
[Music]
well
damn this is really a challenge yo
don't worry we wouldn't have another
reset
I I
Liv yo but you got to admit that's a
lot even now when I knew about
everything coming and was way more like
prepared for it it was
still a lot without the bone might get
dangerous but yeah anyway is there
something up
here
h y the reward for making the bridge cuz
I guess without Boo the bridg isn't
there or
what
okay I don't know maybe maybe it would
be
there or you could always summon boo
anyway what is that why is it so dark
Mark that looks
weird excuse me what oh God what's
happening wait I need a ball there's
fire I don't see a
ball is that a ball oh yeah ah I have
it become my torch and my
protector my
tool my
everything burn him with
fire this how the nerys felt at the end
of Game of Thrones H
powerful what it felt
powerful we are in the Tomb we're going
to be raining some tombs let's
go am
I the bad
one if I'm raiding tombs actually in the
previous World Mansion or was it this
Mansion no no the previous Mansion we
were also opening
coffins I feel like that's not something
you would do if you a good person
oh
wow can I has no no why
not I would like to poke and open your
head like a pimple with that H clock
hand looks like that would be of fun it
does remind me of mega mind yeah
hey
you do I suck off the toilet paper well
it's not sucking so
far that obviously doesn't work does
it oh he fell
down I have to lead him against the wall
huh
you that's like you guys in the trench
coat reminds me of you
[Music]
guys oh there's
more wait if I light them is that when
they run oh yeah
how wonderful I figured it
out
[Music]
ow
okay see I'm getting better I'm figuring
out things
faster I'm not such a lost cause after
all maybe hey where'd you go what the
[\h__\h] ah he moved way fast I Lally have
my flashlight on him
cheater
cheater yippy I did it is that
all you follow the big one
now oh no oh he's calling me oh
hello you right did you see that
bigheaded ghost he ran off with the
clock
hands oh you're going to pixelate me
okay that's an end of a
mission oh
yes oh
[Music]
yeah knows s oh 15 minutes yeah but
because I'm obviously faster now because
I did it kind of before
yeah yeah otherwise if I did a first
try it probably wouldn't have been
silver
okay oh well saw you made the stream of
DS yeah I did but yeah people pointed it
out that month was indeed like I know it
was a really good uh one of those Ms was
really good because had like Al reveal
and Minecraft Arc and uh football Arc uh
and all that stuff
so yeah no surprise
actually actually in hindsight that was
probably one of my best mths in a long
time in a year or two
years yeah thanks for the
membership had a good strength there
yeah Good Very good for my
channel Been a Good
Year yeah I've been I mean I knew that
it was going to be like not forever but
I'm still trying to kind of continue the
momentum at least in in a smaller SC
Escape scope scape SC scale
scale h
on the bright side that very power will
allow me to track him down while I scan
the can you go to the VA no I don't want
to go to the Vault let me go to the next
mission I don't want to go to the Vault
I'm going to check out the Vault when I
play Fallout
BR C2 okay we're already at C3 that's
not bad that's not bad in 1 and 1 half
hours it's been 1 and 1 half hours
roughly since we finished the
other Moon Mansion right
so bad I
mean considering how I like died at
pretty much the end of that mission I
had to redo the whole
thing has a lot of time on
his get
it h maybe I'll try the whole man I have
to look up how long it takes me to get
to the run Deo
point and I went to shower before I
go and dry my
hair let me see how long it
takes be too bad
okay okay okay
okay I think if I stop playing in one
and a half flers would be good enough
time for me to prepare and get to the
rondevo
point
[Music]
spicy thank you huh
what yeah I
snows I snow I have snowz
in I did indeed
[Music]
snows is that
uh what do you prefer me gaming or me
reading super
chats what do you
prefer yell
gaming super chats up to
me gaming gaming gaming gaming gaming
tonight tonight we game both one are my
other streams this week I forgot
uh Minecraft Minecraft and and uh
Olympics or which spring
[Music]
huh okay okay Luigi okay really I think
any normal human could walk over there
but
okay I won't judge
[Music]
you wait I mean I I can't get over there
right no right I I have to go
around pretty
sure how would the Olympic stream work
return on our TVs or an online
stream and we watch Olympics at the same
time I turn on my Japanese
TV yeah I hope you all have a way of
watching the Olympics
somehow it should be one way or another
it's the [\h__\h] Olympics
[Music]
there's always a way ah this is what
that door is for wait is there a way up
from
what which way do I
go oh now this is blocked off
[Music]
now what this is still watching me why
are you still watching
me maybe there's money inside now
[Music]
no
nothing yeah so far I've also only been
watching
Clips I'm a Olympic clip
Watcher Olympic clip
Watcher that's actually
funny you could call someone that who
just literally watches Olympics all the
uh Clips I mean all the time oh you you
get a [\h__\h] medal in watching Clips eh
with how many Clips you watch instead of
streams Eh this is almost like you're an
Olympic clip Watcher
ha funny a
it maybe you should watch a stream every
once in a
[Music]
while nah it's okay I don't I don't have
a problem with people who watch um Clips
but I mean if it's really only Clips you
don't have to watch full streams but it
would
[Music]
be nice if you checked out a stream here
dare a little bit like I don't know you
really only watching
Clips are you
really like do you really know who I
am do you really
[Music]
know I'm
sure people who watch Clips every once
in a while for sure they uh check out
the stream sometimes right some some
streams sometimes I think I was on the
wrong path so I'm going to go
[Music]
back attention span yeah yeah I get that
like honestly I don't think I would be
able to watch
like a six 7 8 n hour stream in one go
unless it's really
a m
a game and streamer that I'm really
interested
[Music]
in yeah in one go live probably not like
I I would watch vods more often I think
like I never minded watching P streams
as
vs for p though like when I was in my
biggest noragi
phase I definitely watched like
everything I I don't think I skipped any
anything really what the [\h__\h] guys I
don't understand what am I supposed to
do I there's no other thing to explore
wait ah wait wait wa wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait
[Music]
wait Pi is so py mouthed
I can't even like so
what what so what making money
again
Yoo wooo
[Music]
yippe
bro which huge ass spider nested in
here that's terrifying
and how do I get rid of this there's a
bomb
here this one I can actually move we
blow up
the this bird
nest well shoot
it don't follow me don't follow me don't
follow me don't follow me don't follow
me
don't okay it worked
stay there no follow
stay oh oh my god let's
go
wow in this
economy that's pretty
big I swear to
God hey the sand is gone wasn't this all
the full of
sand I can do that again maybe no no no
more sand somebody cleaned up all the
sand I wonder who was it
[Music]
EAD
I
okay ah this room
any new surprises perhaps
oh but I found this one
before maybe I get nothing
[Music]
now
yeah do I get extra points for doing
that again maybe maybe maybe maybe my
score will be higher
[Music]
we just go here oh
yeah
yell look young fell I know you're
scared but don't pretend like you
forgot I'm being called out what do you
mean what do you
mean try to lift near a man
[Music]
bro I'm I'm I'm I'm really
trying I know
I I was trying to find a way around it
because I obviously couldn't go over
that bridge you can call that a
bridge I mean this thing here how the
[\h__\h] am I supposed to know
oh now maybe we can blow it up I don't
know if that thing from
[Music]
afar that wasn't there before was
it
y hey stop
stop stop stop stop stop stop stop
stop st you sh
well we'll see who laughs last you
little
[\h__\h] is that so funny do
youuh that was pretty funny I
appreciated
[Music]
that kind a good
laugh it had no intention of stopping
ever
[Music]
okay yeah that was kind of right there
in front of my face
ouch you have a gem there you're
sleeping with it is that like cozy
really maybe maybe you give to me
instead we need to probably wake him
up maybe I can shoot something at the
alarm
[Music]
clock oh dog phone that should be
useful yeah I know the thing there Su
but I was going to explore a little bit
more before I do that oh it's SPS the
time
until wakey wakey what time are we
waking up Mr
ghost
hello haven't
we
[Music]
already maybe
backwards I do I have to stop at the
right time is there a time that gives it
away there's some clocks there but
[Music]
how do I
know check the alarm clock oh okay makes
sense
um 9 No 9
9:00 ah perfect okay it has to stop
there I thought just I thought that
would be fine either
way if we just come
on Zoom through it that was not the way
to
go
interesting looks like a pretty
comfortable bed and we missed
one but we I'm getting better at
this I would
[Music]
say definitely getting better at
it okay
had reading clocks to
yeah no I always knew how to do
[Music]
that what is he
[Applause]
doing is he pretending that to be a
magic wand
[Music]
yellow yeah I've done this before e
dead coincidentally I've done this in
the first
[Music]
world and how do I jump to the other
side did he tell me
that wait
[Music]
what right stick
hey shut up over
there if only it was cats
meow close enough
[Music]
what is
that that's a that's just a a painted
picture of an
outside something on a on like a curtain
or
[Music]
something okay please open
is that a key Oh I thought it would be a
person again
huh
funny
bye-bye what is the catch
[Music]
here oh how fun but then it's all I'm
never making progress though
I guess I can't go that
[Music]
way too much spooky shit's going on
here yeah oh no the bomb I activated the
bomb too ah ah ah
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah that is mean to place the bomb
there yeah check where I am you can
never be sure I'm green like you you
have to need you need a clear
view do not mistake one of your ghost
Brothers for me
and this is so fake how do I can I get
rid of
[Music]
that money
what oh it burnt me some money it
smelted me some fresh
money fresh money is
[Music]
best ah
can I smelt the helmets
or what is this Arrow trying to tell
me ah wait if I turn the ER around will
the will the path outside go the other
way is that even a thing that can be
done kill
room is that a real
[Music]
word what's what going on I don't even
see the ghosts anymore I just see see
the
[Music]
action oh there's an arrow that looks
upside I don't know if there's anything
I'm missing here but I'm going
to oh oh not what's really outside is it
not even outside actually is it all a
facade wait it's hard to can I get
it suck it in there we go have to think
like the opposite way oh is that a
secret like the game door like like oh
it must be it must
be let's go let's go to a different
world I now one of these okay oh got to
go right wait I don't know I don't know
I don't know I don't know right or left
right or left right left I
[Music]
think oh red red I think and then it
goes around to the left side anyway oh
it's hard to see it
uhoh I can't fail this I can't fail
this
okay it got so dark I was scared guys
scared for my
life
nice I got the full
[Music]
amount I was about to leave this room
but that curtain was so obviously like
something about it just was
[Music]
wrong ominous music
hello hello again scary cuz we're
outside
huh this feels like uh it sounds like
the soundtrack soundtrack so to say from
Ulus like the same kind of music can be
heard in amus
I
think it's moving
again guys it's moving
again um what does this
mean
bro wow such a jump scare game so
[Music]
terrifying need mental support for to
play this
game
wow I pulled out everything that I could
out of that
one
oh oh even more money W we're making
bank today wait am I supposed to add
even more bombs
no maybe not but am I supposed to let
them go
off oh no oh no oh no I should have done
that from the other side ah okay it's
okay it's okay
because I can just do that
again fill up with more bombs at least
they gave me a second
try shy boy thank you is that enough
[Music]
yippee I have to go for this
door
wa ah I can't no I can't go forever
[Music]
a sorry it's okay
easy worth it for the money
[Music]
okay don't get too greedy don't get too
greedy
no is this a
sauna steam sauna
y it's getting
worse am I going to die in
here I can't change this
one what did he
mean how do I get him out
maybe I turn it
back but how do I open
that I don't understand
chat
help
uh I can't
see I'm going to die
ah it doesn't have a v that's why it
doesn't
turn wow smart
people this is how it feels to be
smart
Okay is he going to die
now does all of that air go in there
instead the hot
air instead of going out here
what
now
[Music]
huh no the steam is still there
though can I suck the steam up a I did
suck it up the remaining steam maybe now
the light will work the
flashlight maybe that yeah I was
confused by The Flash uh the the
steam
ah
[Music]
ow that makes so much sense now that
I've done
it I understand everything a bll who are
you B Ulus is in the building a my name
makes no sense that's badonkulous
wow wa I forgot how to do it I forgot
how to do it I forgot how to do it I
forgot how to do it I I I don't I don't
work well under
pressure oh there you are oh thank God
oh thank
God a a this a Tor
jump camera camera
camera what the [\h__\h] was
that
no
[Music]
no bonus has been
captured and brought to
safety my private Boo
collection is the only place where you
will ever be safe
TR what is
this oh a golden bomb um do I really
want
[Music]
to activate
this please be money please explode in
money um still do damage
it still do do some
[Music]
damage I thought I could trust
it there's definitely a whole lot more
to suck in in Lu's Mansion
free isn't
there okay
[Music]
um oh I just walked back
okayy I got the key and now we walk back
something's going to happen something's
going to
happen nothing's going to happen
nothing's going to charge at meit what
what's in this room ah why is this one
green over there
still I went through
it oh wait wrong wrong wrong why is it
green is there a reason is that doesn't
mean I didn't find a a thing
[Music]
there hey yeah I'm in Japan right now so
my stream times are different
welcome oh because it's
outdoor not hold oh I need the heart I
need the
heart I need more Hearts
please
[Music]
no
oh did I miss another one I miss another
one whatever I don't care don't
care I don't care at all it is uh 5:00
p.m.
[Music]
now tomorrow I have dance
lesson going to learn two dances
[Music]
um what sorry my
brain at least I have a bone oh my God
what is this I press the
[Music]
button wait how do we ah ah okay just
normal
okay I thought there was something more
special tiny one they're annoying
oh nice
heart ah no
no what
the what the hell can I stop
that is it is it a matter of
[Music]
time
Y is it over no no
stop no no I have him I have him bro bro
bro bro bro bro
bro oo I got the boss before I got the
minion
yay
Yahoo
oh worth coming back for a moment
n a jewel
[Music]
no okay let's go no me me me me
me and I press this button it's not a
button or
[Music]
ah wait that one clock hand is that our
first one do we have more I think one
more we have wait wait wait we got all
of them then there's only two in a clock
or threee if they had seconds but this
one didn't have seconds I did it oh
maybe it
did oh yes oh it's been 6 hours
wow yeah I think I said uh how
[Music]
I think I'll probably play uh like 40
minutes or so another 40 minutes 45 40
minutes roughly bronze for real I got so
much money and stuff huh I didn't do
that badly I'm not saying gold but like
give me Silver
bro wouldn't call that fair but okay
this whole game is rigged
anyway no no no no no no nothing's
gyy I have calculated my
time let me check one thing I got more
DMs
[Music]
ah okay okay what's going on today man
so many
DMS and
[Music]
tags there too much to read tldr maybe
later
H upgrade
reached the cooling component in the
dark light device has reached its
maximum efficiency those ghosts can't
hide from you but it's still going to
blow up if I use it too long
right yes CL
yipp these are totally not stolen from
crony not at all these are my own they
belong to me
that's only the minute hand where's the
hour
hand do I have it I don't
know one hand is better than no hands I
suppose where could that other hand be
okay we don't have it but I'm assuming
there is no second
hand maybe we can buy the the our hand
second
hand
[Music]
but all right I'm mean
Next Level being the fourth one and I
feel like we could finish it we got
pretty far then
almost almost full Mansion
finito I do actually have a soundboard
with this Yamaha mixer and a few things
are already programmed in
here wait you don't you don't hear that
huh ah is it um ah
oops it no no oops no what I do stop
[Music]
stop no
stop damn it I don't know what I just
did oh no oh no what turn it off it's
like recording something s how do I stop
it from
recording I don't know
[Music]
it's
blinking it's
blinking whatever maybe we go away if I
ignore
it it
[Music]
so got to turn the wind stronger had it
pretty low for the night the rain but
the temperature should be actually so
low
[Music]
it's still like doing
something I don't know I'll leave it
like
this it's going to record me on my voice
for this whole stream I don't
know I'm overriding something but had
some sound on there I just don't know
why uh it wasn't playing it on your side
but I can potentially put my own sounds
in there and then make it work so I
actually did
say um to that ghost
girl who's who did I tell you she
offered me one of hers she has two of
these for some
reason I'm buying it off of her for half
the price
[Music]
wow what a deal I I do like
it I do like it I
think like it's not like the others are
[Music]
unusable but I don't know I feel like I
want to use it maybe
maybe okay don't go chase once again
there's more of
them there's more of those dogs
they went inside headphones are these
headphones are kind of
[Music]
painful starting to Hur it I think this
is one of the longest streams I'm doing
since I'm
here now I'm noticing the
flaws wait could I have potentially
gotten all of those ghosts not just one
I let them
[Music]
go
H what exactly is that
creating first time I did that I also
wasn't sure what I just cre
[Music]
it oh wait I thought it was stopping
there
[Music]
but it didn't okay oh wait ah wait I was
wondering
maybe was there something in here again
usually second time no but yeah okay
[Music]
oh what about the money here is back
again just I think maybe a little bit
[Music]
less thank you for the membership
welcome
[Music]
I guess he went
out the dog or did
he he always resets his [\h__\h]
[Music]
aim there he is found him ah oh a wait
my map was too big I didn't really see
what you guys did up there did you did
you go somewhere together is he your
owner am I disturbing the peace of a dog
and his
[Music]
owner and where should I
go they went up
let go the other way you became a member
and now you're gifting memberships what
the hell thank
[Music]
you there's
a which way is the best way up is was
was there a good way
[Music]
here Maybe not maybe it's kind of more
intuitive to go the other way anyway but
oh
Alo the elevator should I take that
one okay wa I kind of ended up in a
weird place
I'll I'll go
[Music]
back no I'm not tired no not really I
mean honestly I could sleep forever and
always I I'm a big sleeper love
sleep I'm somehow always tired but I'm
[Music]
fine
what but my brain is
certainly kind of malfunctioning already
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah I wonder if the spider knows what
it's
doing huh crafting office
how do I get out of here
again from this side is it even
possible
huh why did I go with the elevator
[Music]
um oh that's what that is for to get
through the other side
[Music]
die ah wait if I go from here then I
don't have
[Music]
to run run run
run
okay so is the dog here oh yeah
I liked it better when the dog was on
his own to be
[Music]
honest feel like you this bad
influence of that guy with him
huh I see you oh you want to fight you
want to fight me now eh why why are you
invincible oh there's like a barrier
that I have to break first oh that's
new new
Challenger
[Music]
appeared so did I just kill his owner
and suck him in
Forever oops how unfortunate now now
the dog has no owner anymore too bad
maybe I should become its owner
oh actually kind of
evil again asking myself the
question are we the evil ones are we the
baddies I'm getting better at this dog
search
one can't tell me that ain't
true am I the B oh you want to play here
you're not going to Bonk me off of there
are
you you wouldn't do that to me right cuz
you you do like me I know you like
me no the dude is still
there what the hell
[Music]
what a goose chase is this still the
same oh
no ah wait no wait maybe maybe they did
went there no they
[Music]
didn't no please let me take shortcut
no oh oh oh oh they're in here I thought
they would go straight to the the
[Music]
front ow
why is Jad so angry
[Music]
again
God is there one that looks like the
green one
too feel like only the red one really
has a a twin in
[Music]
chat oh yeah I I thought so okay but if
the barrier is red it really means I
need to go all the way up to red right
and I I thought I had it but I I was a
little bit too
[Music]
early that one actually yeah when he
laughs that could be
him maybe they were inspired
by what you just Mansion open up without
hitting me oh
[Music]
thank
you maybe the YouTube emojis are all
inspired by just mansion and we didn't
know this until
now well that's easy for you isn't it
that's funny to
[Music]
you got to do this whole thing again
oh uh what
now am I supposed to run towards him
oh
[Music]
see I wasn't
sure
huh trying to
sneak is he there again
maybe he is
okay sneak sneak sneak sneaky sneaky
sneaky sneaky
sneaky and now grab his tail
what was I supposed
to suck him in right away or or Flash
him in that
moment flashing him from afar didn't
work so I didn't want to risk
it I can't read this go dog's freaking
mind
Untitled ghost
talking oh
[Music]
wait one more uncore one more is he
there please be there
I don't think he's there
[Music]
bro do I have to do the whole thing
again oh
[Music]
no are we doing that
again without
the what okay I can just H him in here
okay I was like you're just going to
chill there now he really wants to be
captured by
[Music]
me are we down now don't
go I get the clock
[Music]
hands
the oh
Hallelujah is that mission complete Oh I
thought it would be
[Music]
longer
nice H 1 minutes
[Music]
only
okay is the next one the boss
I could potentially do
it oh it's a long
one okay then maybe better
not how
long the last mission before the
boss you say the wrong
[Music]
one it's another to I don't have the
neres for that I think even if it were
short I don't think I have the nerves
for another toad
escort diey he escaped again I thought
this time he would stay inside at
least bro you lost him again are you
[\h__\h] stupid that means in the next
Mansion we have to play cats with the
stupid dog again this is why told him
priority would be to fix the leaks in
the containment
thingy like he didn't do it right away
but he could have done it within the
time that I was gone now for example he
had so much time to fix
[Music]
it hey I didn't get the boo there was a
boo there was a boo
I was so focused on the
dog
bro
okay H if that's a to Mission nah
nah no thank
you you didn't want to back seat and
point it out you could have I I wouldn't
mind if it's for a boot
[Music]
next time next
time why is it still so
hard is wrong what's at this [\h__\h]
[Music]
air I'm going to turn on the like in
inside cleaning function maybe that will
help I don't really think it it will
help significantly
[Music]
but I see
please I think yeah it just hasn't had a
proper cleaning for a long time
probably oh no I never had such a
problem before with a air conditioner
[Music]
how hot is it
outside it's
cloudy even though it's cloudy it's 3
free
de
[Music]
C I'm
sweaty humidity in Japan is never
manageable in the summer never
have to look at it while you're at
dinner no probably is couldn't be
handled so spontaneously
but
[Music]
okay
okay I do humidifier I don't feel like
hum is an issue inside it's only a
problem
[Music]
outside
mostly I don't mind it inside it doesn't
feel like I'm outside it doesn't feel
the same
way still significantly different from
outside no
worries
so yeah that was 6 and 1 half hours of
Lu's mansion definitely made more
progress than last time so I'm I'm at
least relieved with that we almost did
two Mansions so that's not
bad that's really not
bad I'm still waiting for the like
Olympics good to
go but we have like 2 Days in between
now with no
Stream So is free streams a possibility
probably not if there's five Mansions
you guys said there's five Mansions but
this one would be the third one yeah
no if there's two more after
this although I almost did two
[Music]
today and honestly with this kind of
game there's no real like
story that would be like or content
that's like so um y oh no we can't miss
it maybe tomorrow the day after tomorrow
on one of my days off I'll just finish
this Mansion
honestly yeah so that I only have to do
two in the next stream and then we can
finish honestly with this game I don't
think it
really matters
[Music]
much
yeah this man doesn't even have a proper
boss fight what
really
really oh cuz I think I'll have some
time where I'll want to wind down anyway
after my dance lessons and all that it's
not much it's just one more uh Mission
the stupid toad Mission you guys don't
want to see me rage at that again do
you and the boss
of this yeah
Mansion see
[Music]
no I mean I would hope that this time it
won't be so painful because I already
know better how to handle the stupid
toad oh maybe it won't be as
[Music]
bad let's see how much time do I have
reservations okay I think I can read a
little bit of super chatos I'm just
going to for Simplicity sake I'm going
to read them from this
[Music]
stream eh what what
don't complain why would you
[Music]
complain
um where is
[Music]
it schol school school school school
school okay here we
are maybe we should write it down
[Music]
wow beautiful
amazing okay take 47 d zly d Jimmy
Russell D Ro TOA
D thanks for the red chat so happy to
see you alive are you still here or is
it too late by
now so is Big Cat he wanted to be held
and now he's licking my face which isn't
as fun as you'd think sand paper foolish
wait does he like lick your
nose I've had that experience maybe like
once or twice with not with my own cats
like me sometimes they like lick me kind
of
accidentally when I'm like petting them
while they're cleaning
themselves but sometime long time ago I
think I've been licked by a cat before
in my face
too it's
cute but I guess yours does it longer
and more
intensely I
wish I wonder why why how do I get my
cats to do that
more maybe maybe your
face is a little bit I don't know sweaty
or maybe the beard is it licking around
the beard then the cat is trying to
groom your beard probably like cats like
beards I should grow a beard that's the
trick all all right I'm going to grow a
beard I'm going to do my best can you
guys send me like your advice and tricks
um about growing beards on Twitter like
anything that could help me grow a beard
I would appreciate your input on
[Music]
it I just can't I can't I tried and I
can't I didn't annihilate my hair on my
face
CU there wasn't
[Music]
any put the razor away no I'm not
shaving my facial hair there is no
facial hair I have nose hair though but
it's too hidden for a cat to find it and
groom it I
guess maybe I'll put on a fake
beard they don't care about my other
like they don't care about my normal
hair for example they don't want to
groom my normal hair but I think they
specifically like fa uh like beard hair
cuz it's like shorter and like looks
more like fur than longer hair you know
what I mean maybe that's what it is well
thank you spankenheimer to grow a
beard is the I don't know if that's how
I pronounce it but thank you D Ro to
Jackson f thanks for the
pinky I already kind of discussed the
Super Chat so I think I'll leave it at
da but thank you
[Music]
than
P there was a sudden shift in yen
exchange rain does it have to do with
this like stock market thing that I
read what is the Yen more expensive no
suddenly
is the Yen more
expensive how much
more
he is that is it
[Music]
big it's going
up a little okay not not crazy
significantly
[Music]
oh I don't understand like how these
things happen and why but
n well well who knows how long it's
staying like
that I just got my salary like 6 days
ago couldn't have couldn't have been 6
days
ago man man it's probably not going to
stay like that for that long honestly
[Music]
people were borrowing yen to buy us
stock W and now suddenly suddenly how do
you okay I'm not going to ask too many
questions uh Ty D py Dan oh
um no no
[Music]
no I mean I'm not so confident in that
right
[Music]
now oh oh it was correct actually nor
you
huh uh come for the Super Chat it's a
red
one let me translate
this I found yesterday with an unknown
algorith you found my stream yesterday
with an unknown algorithm let's go let's
[Music]
go are you still here maybe not but
thank you so much for the support come
[Music]
welcome if you're new here jaob 47
D Jim Tracy D the steel D Alexa D
Moonlight dun Duma
dun uh Alexa dun water watermelon waiter
Dan The Gamer cre dun Cruz Dan G thanks
for the red super chat
I also love getting to see my beautiful
boss when I normally miss her stream due
to being at work at the other
job what the job which went well today
by the way oh okay good job
literally congratulations and I'm happy
that you can watch me relatively
normally on a human
time good time sorry I cannot normally
provide that to you guys but you're used
to it aren't you used to it I'm sure you
guys are used to
it now you appreciate those times even
more when I can stream at a PST prime
time let's
go thank you
[Music]
g no
no
h unknown than for the
pinky must for F all Mortal possessions
to the Church of Wawa hash W hash Kil
forever indeed today I don't know where
where where all these like church
donations came from but I appreciate it
thank you so
[Music]
much thank you J SP thanks for the pinky
for the na friendly kiaba stream and the
new vocabulary words great myth speaker
ofen thank you thank you I'll I'll try
my best to
continue getting a better even though
I'm already excelling at English
language I am the best of all English
speakers there's no need for me to
improve but you know I want to stay
humble so I will continue doing my
best with Abominations and stuff yeah
yeah yeah yeah thank you Nathan cotton
thanks for the py that's got J for the
irel wa jump scare legit that was not
okay but she
[Music]
apologized
bro
bro that really scared the [\h__\h] out of
me I thought I accidentally like left
the door lock open and somebody was
coming in because maybe I overheard
knocking and they were coming in because
I'm too loud or
so and like oh like about to
complain and coming all the way over
here and be like hey [\h__\h] you didn't
react to our KN so we came in on our
own what the [\h__\h] so
[Music]
scary omr dun again happy birthday the
gamer CR d py
d from
Pinky the Stream do remind me of the
early days really was I streaming during
like these hours like 11:00 a.m. for me
J have fun with rainy later since you'll
need a retro game for the Bingo how
about Zelda Link to the Past especially
with the new game next month good luck
with work this week um no I I'm not
going to start another Zelda game before
that there's another retro game thing on
there what about um there's this
new uh uh new Nintendo game it's kind of
purple and there's a lot of mini games
and it looks retro is that not is that
not
retro ah I researched in research for a
clip I watched that jet like the game
about bies that you mentioned I didn't
believe your reaction but now I totally
get it thank you but did you never see
bies before that
either yeah Nintendo World Championships
what that that be
retro I know NE and retro don't go hand
in hand but isn't that
retro doesn't
count
eh
no I think about what to
[Music]
do is Lu's Mansion to
Retro it was on the fre yes is that
Retro by now
I know it's crazy to think of that being
retro
but after so many years it might might
as well just be retro
already
no a Fallout it's Fallout
retro Fallout the New
[Music]
Vegas that might be
retro not yet I say so what if I say so
[Music]
God damn
it 20 years old being retro okay but is
there an
official
[Music]
count that decides it
eh with those Graphics I'd say yes yeah
that's what I was thinking
bro I could play Sims 1
again Sims 1 is
retro yo Sims 1 let's go
but
uh I think I wouldn't
really but I'm still I think when this
whole thing ends I'm still in Japan no
um yeah I am low key gy
gy but I would just go home and play
Sims 1 at home cuz I have it at
[Music]
home I don't want to start a whole Zelda
game now but I'm starting one next I
can't start another
series one off game maybe what about
Nintendo 64 Super Mario for one
[Music]
stream I can play that on the switch cuz
I have it on the
switch that works or anything from the
uh that like Nintendo simulator that's
like on in the online
membership Mar is retro bro really it
has better graphics than Fallout New
Vegas in my opinion at
least yeah anything from Nintendo switch
online from like the 64 or
so which Super chats are you reading the
ones from
today okay okay okay I found a few
options
then Bru Le thank you we worry about you
sometimes I want you to be well thank
you I I'm I'm trying to take care of
myself don't worry I'm I'm trying to
always um find a good
balance you
know I I'm very aware of
like like uh a lot of the stress around
me and there's there's a lot of things
going on and stressful and and
pressuring and all
that um I'm more aware of it that I than
I tell you because I can't tell you all
the things that are going on I can't
tell you all the details and
so what but what I can't do is um try
to kind of counter that and balance it
on my own
[Music]
with you know taking time for myself as
much as I can and in those in
between
times
yeah between TW streams and all
that I'm always trying to balance things
for
myself
yeah but thank you Gary azra Dan Elie La
Dan and roic stun wait so what you
didn't know bies before Elsie Lain
oh good morning from Austria you're from
Austria thank you
roric thank you can you greet my cats
for me please can you go and check up on
them it's not in my
state but you could have like visited
one of those States
before I would
think but they're usually
like on in the middle of some big field
on the highway I
assume 12-hour drive so what like how
old are you then maybe there once was a
time where you traveled to such a state
for the sake of a convention or a family
member what do I know what do I know
could there could be an opportunity so
far in your
life
n you went to the parking lot of a bies
before how was it was it were you
traumatized was it too much for you to
take in it would be too much for me see
you've been to Texas before you little
[\h__\h] you're using that as an excuse so
like like oh never such a long of course
you've been there before so there's a
chance you know you
know that's what I'm
saying why are we fighting why are we
fighting huh I don't even know
yeah how dare you not know the entirety
of Texas just by going there
once okay I finished reading the super
chats from today that's something that's
something I did something against the
backlog a little bit hey
amazing and we're almost at 7 hours
yippee I'm going to go take a shower now
get rid of the stank and make myself a
little bit pretty going to put on some
MC
[Music]
maybe why haven't you memorized all 47
prefectures of buies you mean you mean
Bucky stores
locations that could be a America
equivalent huh oh wait it world to me
[Music]
again ah
waya is taking this whole cloes thing
way too
[Music]
seriously don't know
why okay I shall
vanish
oh oh wait before I vanish do you want
to see another preview of
[Music]
merchandise well I guess you probably
want to see that happy
[Music]
next I as I said I got it yesterday I
got the sample yesterday I don't get to
keep it um but I looked at it I
perceived
it it looks really cool I'm so glad cuz
like I really when I had to choose all
the design elements I I was really
hoping that I'm making the right choices
because some things are really different
from each other and I I really hoped
that
the CH choices I've been making were
like the best ones
possibly and it came together really
nicely it looks good uh IRL
too
so let me show you this is the folded
item oh wait ah It spoilers the other
thing well you already see the duck look
I'm pointing at the duck no okay then I
don't show you that one because it shows
the other thing that it's not too
special it's just the card holder thingy
but you didn't see it yet
so okay uh frontal
view it's just like
these and it says and in that is really
nicely um
embroidered really thickly embroidered
[Music]
yeah and then the back side of course is
the most exciting
thing
wow
cool
yeah yeah I like the vibrant colors I
think it's more vibrant IRL I don't know
this looks kind of less vibrant on my
screen right now I'm not sure how it
looks for you guys the Flames are cool
the Taki Ki is quite nicely visible easy
to
distinguish and then when your wing
flaps are up this is what it would look
like flap flap flap those wings flap
them to
Freedom yeah
nice almost covers your hand
ankles so that it's not too
scandalous yeah that small hat smuggled
itself in there
yeah with this if you wear this at
conventions in the future wherever I
appear or I don't appear doesn't matter
conventions or concerts then you can you
can represent it should you know arrive
in time for the next uh Hall of Fest of
course not implying that it happens but
so far so far it happened every year so
I'm not supposed to like imply anything
happening but logically
thinking uh it would probably happen
again
so um yeah you can wear this it's the
official waa happy I know there's other
ones fan-made ones that look really nice
too so that was really a big big
conundrum for me but if you like you can
get this one link is in the description
and of course including the squeaky duck
that I showed yes
today cute little
boy or
girl keep on saying duck but it's a
chicken it's a freaking
chicken watching the concert live that's
fine you mean on stream that's fine
that's fine of course maybe you can wear
to a convention someday though can we
hear the squeak again yes I thought you
would never
ask wow it smells
[Music]
when I squeeze
it some interesting plastic smell I
don't know it's
interesting but I like it it's really
smooth it's soft it's it looks so
chewy it's literally a dog toy yeah God
so you probably should buy one extra in
case you have a
dog no I didn't bathe with yet I have to
give these back so I probably should not
bathe with it
I have to give them back I don't get to
keep
[Music]
them so for polter Pub no don't give it
to him he'll never give it back to me
never give it
back pter pup going to buy one for
himself so yeah I'll upload this on
Twitter probably tomorrow uh or if I
still remember tonight maybe maybe maybe
I will maybe I won't we'll see
yeah sales are ending
soon uh I think what was it 13th or
so I don't remember right now but soon
so uh if you haven't bought it yet you
know what to do and enj we s v z thank
you for watching see you see you for H
either Olympics or witch spring
[Music]
thank you for
watching
[Music]
[Applause]
bye-bye I'm going to choke toad to death
now let's go
[Music]