[Music]
whoa that was perfectly timed actually
hello everyone
[Music]
everyone here to witness the battle yeah
it will be
an epic mythical showdown
yes something like that maybe i think i
think it'll be
a little anticlimactic though because
i'm not feeling so great
ah you're deaf i should be scared of you
you you
you own me right i mean
in reality yes but not in video games
necessary oh you own me in reality i
like being owned by you no
no no we're not saying oh no it's not
what you think it is
okay all right guys
is the audio fine like do you hear uh
btm from the game and do you hear callie
and on the other side i guess do you
hear me
oh yeah good point hey kiara do we need
to censor the match id
no because it's already filled up oh i
see it can only be two people
yeah okay okay yay then i guess we're
fine
nice okay wait wait wait i need to
adjust you a tiny bit
okay do what you gotta do there we go
okay
uh first of all we obviously uh
i mean it's written here but it says
this stream is sponsored by
shadowverse again thank you
freaking
[Music]
thank you so much what an honor it is me
it's a big honor thank you so much
wonderful game
really really wonderful game i love it
it's lots of fun i'm quite hooked
myself and actually i even got my
roommate hooked as well
my roommate started playing shadowverse
um she
of course used the download url in my
description
so guys if you didn't download yours
[Music]
be as smart as my roommate and download
the game from the url if you're going to
download an adult
yeah you can you can use either one
either one i'm just happy anyone can
play this game it's
it's fun it's a good time despite being
not very good at it i genuinely enjoy it
and uh with that that is actually a good
way to
uh lead into some talking points because
this game is
free to play not only on pc since we're
both playing it on pc but you can also
play it of course on your phone free to
play
[Music]
that's right the big ups to you guys hey
shadowverse official thank you for
tuning in
yeah i appreciate you letting us play
the game kelly
you you want to say the next point oh
yeah
yeah i just wanted to give give a shout
out to shadowverse what'd it do um
let's see also uh i just mentioned this
actually i freaking love the artwork
there's uh super dope amazing anime
style artwork and fully voiced in
english and japanese
the voices are are you playing uh did
you turn the voices to japanese or
english
japanese oh me too me too but i heard uh
i heard the english voices too
in on in a youtube video and they really
uh sound really well as well like well
done as well like they fit the
characters in english as well
good so whatever floats your boat i
guess um
yeah exactly whichever whichever one
which would
yeah that's right then sorry i was no
problem
the other thing is which i mean we
talked about this before if you have
seen the other shadowverse streams that
we did but
uh well this game it's a card game
obviously and it's very strategic like
you have like eight different crafts
that you can choose from like eight
different
leaders uh like for example i play with
havencraft
which is like very it focuses on healing
me back up and all that and doing
countdowns and [\h__\h]
and callie has which one shadowcraft
oh what what does this do
shadowcraft is it's all about that
necromancy man and you use really like
like dark characters but then also in
the in the game play you can summon lots
of
love never mind i'm not going to tell
you my strategies
when you said necromancy i thought you
meant uh
neck romancy what
i misheard you sorry my english skills
it's okay no no worries chiari
you're all good i'm just a romantic type
of person you know
yeah i guess so i can see that so yeah
what i wanted to say with that yeah it's
a very strategic game
with all kinds of classes that you can
choose from whichever you like the most
whichever fits you
your personality and i think we both
chose
uh personalities that suit each other
quite well
yeah i can see you being heavencraft i
don't know why i thought you'd choose
dragoncraft but i think having crafts
it's pretty i like pretty things yeah
yeah that definitely fits you i would
say and i like being on the safe side
you know
being able to heal myself up a lot makes
me or like
feel reassured and safe oh
yes yeah so
next up let's see i wanted to remind you
guys about the
the dope event that's going on for three
more days
until may 2nd it might actually be for
depending on where you live in the world
but until
may 2nd they're still doing the
kaguyasama love is war
tie-in event you got the characters from
kaguyasama lova's war question mark
they appear in shadow verse for a
limited time
and you can purchase them from the
in-game shop yeah and you get a special
daily log in bonus
as well so make sure that you log in get
your daily bonus play games and
receive an exclusive emblem sleeves and
more i i know that this sounds like very
like like i'm like i'm giving you away
like a prize or something like that or
like
get fifty percent off now click
subscribe etc
by my merch check out the i'm actually
not excited
i'm not excited yeah there's lots of
free stuff yeah
not only the kaguya um
stuff campaign that's going on but also
you get a card pack tickets
between march 3 13th
uh until i'm not sure when
on it but uh yeah there's a official
release of the 21st card set and tickets
will be available to all players who
have cleared the tutorial and played
shadowverse
during the above window 30
40 of march 2
to 1. so until the 2nd of may i think
yeah there's free stuff
there's all the free stuff many cards
pack tickets you get like
card packs for free lots of them lots of
them really epic once you get super epic
cards like me if you're lucky and gotcha
nice nice or maybe you just have mama
luck but you still have a fun time like
your boy
so so do it for free
all you have to do is the tutorial is so
yeah yeah and then there's uh the three
temporary decks
as well you can get a whole deck uh i
think was for
like what one month or like how long can
you use that especially
i actually am using one for today's
match
oh a temporary deck i did all the gacha
so i could probably
build it by myself uh but
i i you know to save some time i chose
one of the temporary decks uh for today
okay you made a deck
well on your own uh yeah so
kind of technical not technically i
know a quote unquote tournament winning
deck but
me and the deadbeats had to really
search for all the required cards so
it was a long it was a long battle of
liquefying the cards that we didn't need
and um and sacrificing some of our souls
but we barely squeaked it out at the end
and we got we got the quote unquote
tournament winning deck we'll see what
happens by the way my deck
is named staying forever with kelly
oh there's a reason
there's a reason okay matches are never
gonna end because you keep healing
yourself
yeah that is kind of like the the the
thing about
the deck that i chose is sanctuary haven
craft
and like it it's based on like dragging
out the game a lot
but it might not really be dragged out
that much i might just
kill you before the 10th round so
okay generally that's like the
the what it is famous for i guess that
people told me that that's what it's
famous for it drags out
match a lot oh god no
i really don't like healing like bosses
who heal a lot
it's like stay down get down just die
but that's like kind of
you know like how when you in in games
you heal yourself a lot but when the
boss heals themselves you you get mad
but
well we are doing the same thing so
all right all right all right are we
ready for the first match i think we
said everything important
i guess so yeah well i guess we'll just
see what happens
i really don't know what's gonna happen
well chad we will um not be looking at
you guys anymore during the match but
you guys should still
hype it up and be active in the chat we
might watch the archive and if you guys
were too quiet i'm gonna kick your butt
yeah yeah yeah by the way both kiara and
i are streaming this
so if you want to see the inner workings
for both of us
you can go look at kia's stream and my
stream in two different tabs
yes exactly my
link for cali is in my description and
then the other way around my link for my
stream is in her description
yeah so check it out and uh cheer for us
and um as yeah we can't read the chat
because otherwise that we could
someone might say just one thing that
alerts us to what the other is going to
do
yeah so for that we won't look but yeah
you're right kiara i want to go watch
the archive afterward and see what you
guys were saying
um while we were fighting so keep being
hype about it
in the chat do it anyway i'm ready to go
all right oh yeah
yeah let's do it the battle of the gods
let's start yeah something like that
no more npc fights finally battling
against you
i know right oh man the skeletons really
suit you
i know they're like my dead beats i kind
of thought you were either gonna choose
like shadowcraft or bloodcraft but yeah
you went with shadowcraft
but i'm not quite the vampire type so
hmm
ah yeah black crab looks like vampires
huh
let's see where i switched i switched
something out
i'm not gonna switch mine i'm happy with
what i have
good luck ally thanks good luck to you
my dude
i have i hope for you we'll see what
happens
i need to do some reading again okay
because i forget everything that i read
about
instantly i practiced a lot too and read
my cards a lot but still i've i need to
recheck
because there's just so much text every
now and then oh yeah i feel ya
here let me just move myself a little
bit let me scoot a little bit to the
side for my dead beats
so you guys can see kind of all the
cards i have in my hand there you go
okay let's see what can i do do you see
what i'm doing with the ground noise
only on my side
i think it's only on your side okay
brown
i was i was playing around if you tap on
the ground it goes like boom boom boom
oh the grass is pretty cool
okay
yeah yeah watch both streams deadbeats
and captain please
yes watch them both
okay for ultimate insight
is this just won't happen i don't know
if you've noticed but i'm not using the
the basic havencraft leader i actually
purchased on my gotcha stream i
purchased a different leader
and switched them out so that's one
thing you can do there's like
uh eight like eight basic leaders but
you can switch them out with others
mine is by the way from grandpa fantasy
my leader
you see oh yes
very cute i just like my skeletons too
much so i really want to change my
leader but very adorable
i i noticed that that was a grand blue
fantasy you see it in the style yeah
i know this character yeah she's also
from granville fantasy
wow so cute yeah
[Music]
okay that doesn't hurt me
at all
all right i believe you
[Music]
did you choose like cute girls deck no
actually no
no i made i have this pre-built bat deck
and i just uh learned to play with it it
does have a few cute girls in it
but also some really powerful
guys okay cool nice
i'm
okay um
all right
let's see let's see i like you
i like this this little rest a bone
fanatic
oh i don't know what does this what is
this last words necromancer someone's
skeleton okay
[Music]
uh hold on hold on uh let's see
oh that could be helpful um
i really ought to just go ahead and use
[Music]
something
my skeletons
you done and then i'm just go ahead and
i'm gonna do something else
okay take your time kelly
she reminds me of thor senpai i was
gonna say that too
same oh yes oh lucky okay okay okay
bad poker face poker face
which one do i choose oh
[Music]
okay now that my holy sanctuary is out i
just want to let you know that that is
the card that pretty much like
shapes my deck and it will never leave
my side ever that's my
amulet and i
gotta figure out how to get rid of it
okay next next turn i'll play that
so
[Music]
oh wait i still have oh
okay all good oh good oh oh wait i have
one more
huh
okay
easy easy easy
fun fun fun fun
i like the pgm here too it's so epic
fighting for our yes indeed i actually
want to move you real quick hold on
i need you to be in the top right corner
because there's text i want to show
people about my cards
and uh you're in the way kusa
i'm kidding it's not your fault it's not
your fault
yes touch me move me whatever you
wherever you want me to be i'll be there
oh my god all right i'm not move the
chat real quick
and by the way guys we'll play um as
many matches as possible
in two hours so who knows how many it'll
be
because if you were gonna drag out these
matches i don't know man i don't know it
doesn't have to be dragged out it won't
depends on you as well
[Music]
ooh she's hot whoa no right beautiful
reminds me of ollie
do you want to damage your random enemy
follower
[Music]
early but um
go with that
wow
[Music]
oh no you haven't seen um ah uh some new
card i see i see
okay this is the homie right here i
freaking love this homie anyway
oh that dude my character is just the
best
listen
you got a lot of kitty cats i feel like
she has
cat ears the garage dollar this dude
doesn't he have cat ears too
use this yet maybe
skeletons and kitty cats that's your
dick
yeah that's right oh he opened his eyes
he opened his
eyes yeah what sorry i love when the
closed eye characters open their eyes oh
my god okay i was like what is going on
i just love when they do that
[Music]
no i'm actually
wait no wait that's not no no that's not
what i want to do
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is it what is that tyler
you revive the card
and you're one of them i thought it was
gonna re-like re-revive my dude like
kill him and then bring him back at full
health but that's not what it did so
oh well i learned i learned a lesson
that's a unicorn yeah my unicorn
altar it counts down that's one of the
things that my deck does it comes down
and then gives me something like
a special um okay
if i do that then
[Music]
skull fish more scary skeletons
hey that's right
okay it's time to heat myself back up
another necromancer he doesn't really
look like a necromancer okay
the gold mine necromancer
neck wrote
wow okay you got no more wolf points
left and i got
free hmm maybe i should start using my
little fonts
yeah all right all right all right
you oh yeah yeah oreo
it looks like a [\h__\h] red wine and
shadow verse in the evening
yes yes yes okay
there we go
[Music]
more unicorns wow you got a lot of
wishes my dog i got only ambulance on
the field now
cannot attack you but but but
wait for it am i really so
dang out of cards okay
whatever um i don't want to use hang on
a second
unicorn army
i wish i knew how to draw some cards
well you draw one per
turn unless you have some card that
makes you draw cards
oh yeah i see that makes sense i don't
want to use this just yet so i'm going
to not use it
can i use you my dog because you're
already on your turn all right well
oh whale all right okay
[Music]
and a lot of cards
yeah i've noticed that when i was
practicing with this deck i've i've
have like i have like a it looks
a luxury with my cards and i always have
like too many good cards on my hands
i actually like sometimes like don't
even know
uh what to do with them anyway i'm
healing myself back i've seen how it was
at 9 hp a moment ago and now i'm back at
16.
i better use this one
i really don't need to evolve to be
honest probably some people in the chat
are probably roasting me by now for
doing mistakes but whatever whatever i'm
not even looking yet
all that matters is they were having fun
man yes i feel like i'm doing
fine probably still
some things to improve but yeah
no what have i done um i'm not sure what
you have done made a huge mistake
but you did do six damage to me and that
is something
it was a really really big mistake i
made a huge mistake
i didn't know it was gonna do that you
piece of [\h__\h] you dumb freaking
graveyard eyeball
i might i might as well reap oh that is
perfect that is perfect banish that
bastard
you don't like him i got rid of him
[Laughter]
all that matters is you have fun callie
thanks shadow first i did
i did look a minute to see your message
all right well i am having a good time i
will say
i could have evolved them then they
probably might
even be dead by now
[Music]
okay yeah yep okay oh there we go there
we go
wow that one's really cool that card if
i don't play it by the 10th turn it gets
automatic
automatically played at the 10th turn
just by being in my deck i don't even
need it in my hand
yeah wow anyway let's
end it there i go there we go
lasting forever with kelly i didn't even
need to dub out a doll
yeah i guess not huh nice first match
well played clap clap clap but watch
i shall adjust the score me too
let's see
thanks guys okay let me take a tiny look
at the chat hello hello hello hello
hello
hello clap clap thank you thank you
guys got a lot of good cards they say
yeah
i do i mean i could i could tell that
much immediately but you
you you got a good deck as well no you
got it from like some
like a a co a deck like a deck coat and
then you
like re build that one
yeah i feel pretty confident about this
nest this next match because i made
about
two huge mistakes like game alteringly
bad mistakes
but i learned my lesson yeah you started
it
yeah sometimes it got me pretty low i
was sweating a little bit when you got
me down to nine or eight hp so
it's not impossible if you play your
cards well i'm sure you have a chance as
well
should we get into the next match
yeah let's do it let's go i'm ready
oh who is she whoa
okay we're in the forest
oh i'm in a castle oh oh you see a
different screen interesting
that's why you saw the grass
indeed okay i think i like all these but
oh no no
i like all these no
[Music]
oh okay you really want to be with me
huh some card that i switched out
i got the same card again nice
okay
it's card gathering time did i
actually not evolve a single card
last match i really didn't
uh well yeah um
[Music]
very classy ghosts his voice sounded
funny he sounds like really
really excited yeah like you put some
kind of like interesting audio effect
like
boom yeah
[Music]
the effects on your card when you evolve
him it's pretty nice
um yeah it says he got a lot of stuff
going on
yep indeed okay cool i like this
[Music]
sexy [\h__\h] again yeah it's ollie
except for a different lemon i like how
she
like spawns with like a rose
i love roses
um
[Music]
i need my amulets better get them next
turn
well with this one i could get it
[Music]
oh no though i see
your cards look very scary i know
they're perfect for me
[Music]
okay that's just a scratch
yeah definitely
where is there we go no that's also not
it okay
[Music]
oh
okay okay i feel safe again
you get me worried when you when you get
all those hp
from me and but but no problem no no
need to worry i'm i'm fine i'll be fine
i'm a phoenix i will rise worse
yeah that confuses me too because
because the shield
is red but red is always attacked me
you know ah was that what you meant why
you confused it
yeah same thing
oh she's she's so cute i know right i
love the little horn so i can't kill his
head
red hairs
[Music]
kelly would you describe your own eyes
as pink or red
um oh that's a good question red oh
okay because we had that discussion when
i was like creating you in sims 4 in my
stream
and i would have said it's like a dark
duck pink but others said it's red and
i'm like okay well if you say red then i
guess it is red officially
yeah maybe i mean i feel like they're
red personally i feel like they match my
my pendant and my pendant is red
ouch thank you skullfish
it's a homie right there
okay chill cali chill
ghost rider what to do
another spellfish yup i like the skull
fish ah
can i do i have something to banish
no not right now
wait wait i don't i don't blend yeah i
don't i do i do
[Music]
the speed jam gives me such like middle
i guess you're hearing a different one
right now because you're on a different
map but
the music generally gives me like
middle-aged medieval vibes
and i love it because it reminds me of
the times when i went to
medieval festivals with my mom and my
brother
and my sister we used to go to a lot of
them
oh that actually sounds like a really
fun time like a really fun family event
where the [\h__\h] is my sanctuary what the
[\h__\h]
you still have so much i'll give you
some
i'll give you some hp back i'll give
that to you there you go
oh in change i banished your dude the
difference between banishing and killing
your dudes normally
is that when i banish them they cannot
affect their uh
let their um like last wish
uh come to effect well i can't speak
english oh
i see i see it's so exciting
so anyway i'm gonna play that
and
please give me what i am looking for
oh my gosh what the [\h__\h] okay okay okay
sure whatever i love it
actually this this match is a little bit
yeah because i'm i'm
for once not getting the car that i'm
looking for
and you are uh
we're doing quite well okay okay
okay okay i'm getting a bit stressed out
there's no reason there's no reason to
be
ah okay okay and i need to use my both
points what the [\h__\h]
i don't need to what the hell okay okay
okay well
um okay no
no don't worry kelly don't worry
wow
so what do i have
[Music]
we only have two of them
ah there we go okay there we go
[Laughter]
no more worries now let's see
i was waiting for that by the way dear
chad i'm not looking at you but i just
want you to know i was
waiting for that
i really can't do anything huh
oh what was that again
anyway finally my sanctuary is here
and bye
uh this i'm i heal you with that card
but you were already at
maximum hp so i don't care
okay four points left we can play
[Music]
can't play him so i would say play you
and restore free hp for me kill someone
from your side because whenever i heal
myself my holy sanctuary does something
special
and i get no i guess we can do that one
too
okay i'll cook and there we go i hear
myself again so my holy sanctuary
summons the tiger
nice thing oh it's dope and tired yeah
let's see cute tiger oh [\h__\h] i can't
just
why am i not evolving again what the
[\h__\h] so stupid
oh damn it i probably could have done
something wow whatever it doesn't matter
i have no cards dude well in the end
kelly we're both still beginners so we
both make
lots of mistakes it's it's okay but i'm
like
yeah i don't know how to get more cards
i wish i had more cards
i have no cards
maybe it's because i keep playing all of
them i probably should try and play less
cards
it no i don't think so whatever you can
play and what is smart to play
yeah but i have like none
amulets now
[Music]
okay yeah i also i have like
lots of amulets on my field so it's like
i can't i barely can play like actual
like
cards that make damage but that's okay
i'll see you know we need a switcharoo
no i'm a almost max hp and urine
oh those stupid ghosts i uh when i was
when i was practicing against an npc i
had uh
them like like summon all those ghosts
as well i was like what
how do you do that
did you just call your deadbeats and
they came
yeah that's usually how it goes noise
let's get rid of the unicorn oh well
[Music]
no yeah because i can't attack you with
him yet
not until the next turn so
what could we do why do i have something
[Music]
a little bit but the deck really is just
way too strong my deck is like insane
yeah it is quite good maybe i'll try
playing with a different one
i don't know you have one ready right
now
yeah i have another one i mean i have
your i have yours as well
your temporary deck but i don't want to
use that same one
as you um this one's not very different
but i'll
still try it anyway okay i'll stay with
the same one because that's the only one
i really have
okay next match let's go thanks guys
thanks in the chat thank you thank you
thank you thank you
here we go oh bats hmm
so oh you're still on shadowcraft but
you changed your deck
i really want to try to make it work if
i can
guess i just gotta think real hard hello
hello i don't need this one yet
let me draw this okay that's fine
you know what i'm gonna run with what i
get i'm gonna roll with it
let's see what happens
[Music]
pretty pretty unicorns
is the deck you're using now or
temporary one
uh no it's only a little bit different
than the other one oh okay i think i
used
i need a debt code to get it oh
i actually don't know what fanfare is so
i'm looking it up right now
if i understand correctly it is
uh it triggers something in the
in the in whatever you know what i'm not
gonna i'm not even i'm not gonna say it
from the hand okay i see what was it
if you just play the car like by playing
the card
okay okay that's what i thought
something like that
that i have right now it's like it
didn't happen so i'm like i'm wondering
maybe if
i messed up somehow maybe i have to wait
several turns i know
now let's see well for now um i love
the the bone fanatic's voice
he has a cute voice yeah it's cute
um let's see
and i'll hold on to these for now
you know uh the other day when we played
um
uh the clubhouse games you won a lot
so yeah i'm glad i'm finally winning
something too
yeah i'm gonna bring out my specs with
you though i do enjoy them
do i wanna play huh i guess yeah because
no
i don't have any of those
so we're doing
nah we can we can play our finger in our
fingers
oh i literally hurt
everyone on the field just now even
myself
wow but that's okay
okay bye bye john it was nice seeing you
um she didn't she have last words
was that only on the role
oh it's still my turn i see i wish i
would have
i wish i would have felt this confident
in school
during math tests yeah
i don't know that numbers aren't my
strong suit either
yeah okay we didn't even have
to didn't even have to think about that
move
the ambulance really never go away huh
what doesn't go away i'm gonna see
um my my unicorn amulet is a countdown
amoled it goes away after four
turns and then activates itself
and my holy sanctuary doesn't go away uh
at
all yeah okay
see you really do get me quite low on hp
every now and then but then i hear
myself like absolutely
really strong yeah you kind of you kind
of need to
like prepare something like think think
i guess a few turns
in the future and then maybe you could
get me down maybe i don't know what your
deck has
yeah that's that's the thing we have
some secret weapon
i don't know
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] i wanted to evolve that's why i
clicked the wrong
damn it and that was a mistake
i know i can't attack but i want it to
evolve anyway
oh hi ghosts
[Music]
okay okay
you're making me sweat again
bye bye ghosts bye bye bye bye bye
that's unfortunate i guess i didn't have
a enough room for my bike
okay so um
horsey go hoisting now we got one more
left so i guess we do that
oh now we're about the same hp oh it's
getting close here
close battle um
again the bike guy you have a lot of
those
yep of course oh what is that car that
looks so pretty what the [\h__\h]
yeah i really like this one oh
he got like someone with an apple
who is he he's cute
[Music]
oh that sucks oh
i don't know why i couldn't evolve but
okay
oh yeah yes
it's
[Music]
do you feel better with that deck than
the previous one
um i think it's exactly the same
[Music]
well let's see i guess i'll just go back
to my tournament winning deck
okay sounds good to me unstable is mine
i mean
yeah i'll probably just like keep trying
until i at least get one win out of it
because
i'm sure you can do it you can do it
believe in yourself
take take as much time as you need to
read the cards i know it's super
confusing
okay yeah i feel like a lot of times i
just don't understand what they do
yeah um
like very similar cards and a lot of
like dupes as well
so maybe that's a bit easier um
[Music]
i'll go with that no changes
this is the fourth match let's go
[Music]
and pray to it
respect
[Music]
i probably should actually wait to use
that
[Music]
too early i think let's go with that
what were his last words again ah some
in a skeleton okay
yes i'm in a deadbeat hey dad beats
lurking now
dead beats looking now oh wait i'm
still my turn i yeah
ouch
[Applause]
[Music]
no don't leave me you always die so
early damn it
i mean health is pretty low i mean the
defense is pretty low
[Music]
yup
okay i'm feeling healthier now
[Music]
there we go
help you feel feel
[Music]
oh is that did it get oh yeah that's
right thank you about it
i did i'm sorry my brain just doesn't
have a lot of room for anything else so
yeah thank you for a lot of valuations
oh yeah and did you did you hear suicide
senpai trying to learn the song
yeah yeah i heard it was great really
maybe i should try yeah if you'd like
there's a lot of fast rap but
if you'd like to give it a thumb
[Music]
learning was already
so difficult
yes a tough one
[Music]
try a different approach here
it's a wolf time
oh you got that you're your favorite boy
again
i know this is definitely my favorite he
looks like
so sweet so nice his smile is so kind
that's a good dude but it could also be
like a kind of expression that's like
i'm
i'm gonna i look nice but i'm gonna kill
you
yeah that's how i mean that's typically
how it goes with with closed eye boys
why i like them so much
[Music]
okay i would say we need another one of
those
and then give me my
freaking sanctuary please
dude
oh
there's a party on your side a ghost
party
[Music]
[Applause]
i'll get more
wow wow we're evolving that cart looks
dope
got it okay i got what i wanted nice
that's good
can you calm down my ghost dude i was
just reading about you
[Music]
that's cool turn six
there we go something like that
[Music]
oh wait maybe i should have oops
no problem no need to worry
don't really be happy
i've had that song today in my ear the
whole day
oh yeah
[Music]
yeah i know it's like my deadbeats what
[\h__\h] my dad needs
he dreams about a better future
yeah a better life something
yeah but now he's got to go
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] i'm down to 10. what did you do
kelly
i was just at 20 hp
[Music]
let me drink some hydration time
yeah you too why oh hawaii
nice
oh it's still my turn yeah it is oh
i'm drinking some kind of disgusting
low-key disgusting
uh i see that is also somewhat good
yeah there we go okay you
you really have to punch me one more
time before ending that turn huh
yeah i mean it wasn't me it was my
followers that wanted to do it so
playing flames okay
that's a really powerful one yeah it
does free damage to all
enemy followers and restores freedom
defense to myself and makes me draw a
card
that is really really powerful yeah i
i like i like healing myself up i like
to keep that card for whenever you have
too much on the field
[Music]
yep okay
so now the field is clean again swoop
swoop sweet sweet
i'm you i'm your maid kelly i'll i'll
clean up all those skeletons
in your closet oh
okay if that's what you want to do
[Music]
where is where is my freaking
it's just not coming but okay okay
[Music]
um
ah finky time thinking time
eight points eight points
i don't know
but all the way six
five okay yeah yeah yeah yeah
now we want either you it's really
powerful
yeah it uh um for stories as much hp
as the card that i banish
has a defense so your card has six
defense so it
restored six uh hp for me
wow you see haven't craft really
annoying
[Music]
okay okay chill the game was already
like stressing me out to end my turn
[Music]
again i like seeing her on the field
a little bit of an eye candy
but i really like your leader luna is so
cute she's also already
eye candy yeah it's true
we've had a little um nui guru me
plushie yeah
is that a mouse or a bunny i think it's
a mouse
not sure though
darkest desire what's your darkest
desire kelly
reaping some souls
[Music]
well
the unicorn wish came true let's see
that is very painful but i feel like
like doing it anyway there we go
oh wow yeah that was painful for me too
but whatever okay
i i i wanted to play it a bit risky
[Music]
another beautiful she actually looks
actually she looks a bit like you
yeah hang on one second
shut them up i'll wait forever
uh
[Music]
the next next turn is tenth turn
or ninth turn
[Music]
i see i see
what does that do select two shutter
craft levels in your hand keep the first
follow up
way too fast it goes away so fast
oh my god that's way too much text
that's way too much no wonder
no wonder there's like some confusion
ah my brain is on fire right now
yeah come on
there we go you took some time there you
[\h__\h] sanctuary why why did you take
so much time
dear lord it was kind of tough without
you
okay okay well
uh i'll wait oh yeah
[Music]
oh now you give me another one of those
huh too late
no i never should have evolved anything
god
ah i should have saved the whole thing
time yeah that's why i keep on saving it
but i save it for too long i still have
free evil points
oh my gosh uh hold on a second i'm not
sure what's the right thing to do
keep them for special characters or use
them early
i don't know i'm just going to use it
[Music]
wow oh yeah he evolves himself doesn't
he yeah
oh damn it if that [\h__\h] thing wasn't
uh
that word was enough god damn it
yes sorry i had a lord oh you were so
close oh wait could have that could that
have killed me if i didn't have a water
at the end of return destroy six other
running photos and if the enemy leader
has 70 friends or more
do you oh my god oh my god oh my god
until then
i don't know it's not a lot of text
[Laughter]
uh okay
oh
[Music]
oh um
oh wow oh wow
okay first of all healing myself back up
and
finally getting that defense going and
still four
i'll get you out there and then
thank you okay we can evo uh
heal a bit more and just
for fun involving you
into a pretty flame tiger
okay i can't attack you though yeah when
you evolve you can attack in the first
turn but
only other enemy followers as far as i
understand it not the
[Music]
did my homework
yeah i tried i can go
i've been really visit toodle because
i'm moving on the weekend
oh that's right yeah and i didn't i
didn't even really start packing but i
painted
like my walls in my new apartment
oh that's cool yeah maybe you can
one day visit me one day sure if you
will
[Music]
always
it's me so sam you
[Music]
it was it was pretty good kelly you were
at that you were you had this one point
where you were
really about to kill me
close huh pretty close maybe maybe next
one
you gotta use the same one yeah
i wanna try then we go on to the
fifth match yeah
thank you thank you yeah it was close
at one point we were both like at six hp
that was really really
scary oh thank you what a great starting
hand
okay
now this looks good
[Music]
actually one reason i think why it was
so close
last time is because i didn't get my
freaking holy sanctuary
until the end of the game oh yeah yeah
cause the holy sexually
heals me it's all over yeah it heals me
a lot
so you were able to get me down a lot um
you're playing this yeah playing the
same day you're playing the same deck
okay okay but i know my deck very well
so
yeah this is funny
oh you've been you've been telling me
quite a bit about the deck so i'm
curious
oh okay maybe i shouldn't have told you
so much
oh you you're oh oh how the
how the turntables doesn't it
maybe i should play your deck no
you would die yeah i like my deck i'll
keep it
i know what i'm doing yeah
but this is getting interesting
sanctuary haven against sanctuary heaven
[Music]
those unicorns are freaking powerful i
tell you what
um jelly you know what because we're
both playing sanctuary haven now
this might be um like you remember our
super long
uno match yeah that dragged
itself out for 40 minutes
we might be dragging this mess out for
40 minutes
because we're both playing
[Applause]
well now finally the title of my deck
comes
to truth because it says staying with
kelly forever
so yeah
but i still feel like i might end up
playing it a bit different than you
um well you definitely would need uh
some kind of warm-up with the deck to
understand the cards
yeah it's true they also have lots of
texts
they all do
[Music]
you play the [\h__\h] card
okay depending on what you have on your
hand you can literally just
copy every movement yeah
huh you're done
and let's see oh yeah i guess so
okay i'm really curious about this fight
wow that's cool okay
that's an easy one to do
oh cool i don't really need to do that
but okay
[Music]
unicorns
let's see what else can i do i don't
need to be
so healthy right now i don't
yeah sometimes sometimes um
even when you're full hp you might still
want to use the card because it has some
other side effect that you want to use
yeah i guess that's true but i'd rather
kind of hold on
[Music]
it's a freaking party what a unicorn is
that
[Music]
i like four unicorns i don't know why
i'm evolving now but yeah that was kind
of late
should have done it at the beginning
whatever
i need to love more
at least it stays alive maybe maybe
or it keeps me a lot longer
[Music]
or whatever you wear
oh cool
i'm gonna hold on to that
i kind of want that though
i don't want to use this one yet so ah
well you know
oh hi i set yeah i like that one
okay what am i gonna do with that again
i forget
oh my short-term memory i tell you what
same um i know i did something else but
i kind of forgot
okay let me heal myself back up
attack you a little bit um
and i guess play that whatever
more unicorns unicorns
[Music]
okay let's see
this might actually be a good time to
use this
[Music]
i'm still standing my tiger is still
staggered good job holy flame tiger good
job
stay strong tiger
[Music]
okay turn six
yeah you can't evolve right from the
beginning uh i think after the four
full fifty turn it lets you start
evolving
okay
this really looks like it's going to
take a long long long time
oh you got your sanctuary
oh man
[Music]
angel or archangel i think it's i think
it's angel
oh i'm pretty sure i'm not certain
well i can do it okay well
[Music]
okay so what do we do what do we do i
say we banish him
wow that is really op a lot of health
though that's nice
yeah you're welcome
yeah zero class so let's do it
and four points left
give it that one or we got another one
of those
or actually you know hey i have that one
too oh
but i'm gonna go with that one do at
least
a little bit of damage get the tiger
eat steam eye of the tiger
what's this
[Music]
oh kelly by the way yeah are you
planning on repairing my stairs in
minecraft
oh yeah you got you betcha you better
i'll do that
will do yet maybe if you have some
if you ever have some leads you know
because uh some of my llamas
uh pockets were unleashed as well for
some reason oh
i haven't i have no idea they were just
like that listen
they were unleashed but it's the good
thing is that alpacas usually stay
together
um even if they're unleashed
yeah oh well yeah there's a there's a
kind of a safety hazard at kfb right now
yeah i can tell my people can't go to
work because they all fall into the hole
because chickens are not very smart
so they go up the stairs and then they
just drop into the hole
uh that's really unfortunate i'm quite
sorry to hear that
[Music]
are you able to retrieve the chickens
from the hole
no they'll die
that's unfortunate yeah
i'm quite sorry
okay well i can't attack you
right now unfortunately i'll keep the
last of wolf
uh okay wow wow what is this fight
yeah yeah i'm starting to kind of feel
that too oh wow
battling each and all of the same deck
is
just like triggering
it's something all right
when i chose this deck on my stream
everyone was like oh my god
cancer cancer oh really why
yeah because it triggers so hard that it
drags out the game but having two
of the same deck and against each other
is even more
cancer yeah it's pretty
it's pretty intense
but i should have maybe um prepared one
more
dick i thought i thought one was enough
and one more deck would have been fun i
guess to
play around a bit more
maybe if there's next time or for the
tournament who knows maybe i'll get
another deck or
i wonder if you're only allowed to use
one deck in a tournament
but yeah i think that's a good question
i'm not sure
also i wonder who our opponents will be
just random people
oh yeah i wonder too oh i mean i doubt
they'll be random people i bet that
they'll be people who are very
experienced at the game
probably need to have a long talk with
the coach beforehand
i really actually learned the deck
before i get in there
get rid of them at least and then
okay i got nine nine points nine points
we play another one
this is so much a holy sanctuary
so much to read whoa yeah
get me that holy water thanks lorena
thank you
okay now now i can finally do some
damage to you
i don't know should i really end the
turn okay okay okay
[Music]
that's the one i told you about that you
don't even need any points for
to play yeah pretty strong
that's right
can i play there be two that's so that's
so weird to me
yeah but the thing is it's not stackable
oh then what the [\h__\h] it's like annoying
it's just like sitting there oh wait i
think it's not stackable so i don't
really
maybe it is i don't maybe it is you know
what maybe it is i don't know
[Music]
i guess it is stackable maybe ah i
always wondered why
why i would play like two holy
sanctuaries but i've seen other people
do it
we had to destroy each other no
oh well there's no more salvation on the
field at all that's sad
[Music]
okay okay
wow that was pretty crazy
well you damaged yourself too yep
so all right what do we do
i don't know should i play one of those
as well
ah so much choice
i i clicked
now there we go okay a little bit of a
heel
and there we go tiger
[Music]
i don't want to keep that card but
we can do that one
[Music]
oh yeah let's play this turn oh ah
eight more points left i guess we'll
play you
and yeah that that's that's it
that's it
there we go now i have two whites
can you get through that wall cali
um
one second i need to read something take
your time
oh wait actually oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
oh oh oh oh oh
okay hi guys i guess yeah that's
that's what happens when you have two
sanctuaries
i guess so
[Music]
um i guess that's all i can do
this game can be played by two people
i can see that
it's not over it is not over
ah play it smart keanu
i don't know all those choices seemed
really good
god damn it
oh you're down to one what happened well
i have no clue
[Music]
you got six points back again
things are getting really intense
[Laughter]
okay
well not much i can do now okay
okay well at least i'm back to full
health and i got two tigers
okay
that was my sanctuary i think okay okay
okay wow wow
wow that was difficult dang
it was like fighting myself
wow do you want to play that again with
the same deck
sure okay
okay that might be the last one how long
did this one take felt like
half an hour but i think it was maybe a
bit less
well then it's definitely longer than
the first
war yeah all right century
haven versus sanctuary haven guys
yup this this this might be the the last
one maybe
yeah so who's there i mean now that
kelly
understands the deck quite a bit more
i mean a little bit what what do you
think will happen for the last one guys
um clap crop thanks guys good game well
played
and good job oh oh thank you
thank that holy sanctuary card seems
nutty i don't know what that means but
it is
is very strong oh they mean they mean
that it seems ridiculously powerful
um yeah it's what the whole deck is
built around
since then since i mean the name the
name is sanctuary haven
and the card is called haven't sanctuary
wait was that it
oh am i mixing things up
yeah ra is also super strong and
salvador dal
there's a lot of super strong cards in
this deck
and i guess this will be maybe the last
one let's go kelly
yeah let's go go go go go go
show them
haven craft versus havencraft second
match
i go second you go fast
[Music]
maybe one
okay i like something different okay
chad bye bye again bye bye
see you in a little bit
i'm mowing your
la
lawn long
okay you're starting out with cutie pie
eel
yeah very cute she's so cute i love a
twin tin twin tails are so cute i want
twin tails too
ah hi you bye oh hi
[Music]
oh wow we have the same one yeah
are you really surprised
it kind of started out like this in the
in in the other match too both of us
were like oh yeah
eo unicorn
repeat the history repeats
[Music]
and itself um
let me think i don't want to use this
one
i think i might use this one
[Music]
three points um so much choice
ah yes we can
ah there we go
like that yeah yeah yeah i'm looking for
something
uh-huh okay i forgot to attack what the
[\h__\h]
oh no
okay okay she got the sanctuary out
oh wow you're still alive what the hell
[Music]
okay sounds good to me
i got a word huh
[Music]
oh i feel so sorry for her she's
enjoying being on here and i keep on
like destroying her so early yeah we had
about three of
three of her
[Music]
okay well then
it's your turn my lady okay
[Music]
how are you already putting the second
one out
you really want to win this one huh i
mean
i would like to um
i would i want you to win one as well
but i'm not gonna
kill them because i won't like it if you
throw them back
please don't uh yeah you won't throw the
match
it's fine
cat hair in my nose
i don't think i got him last time i
actually barely have experience with
him because i got him so rarely
but okay i think i know what i'm doing
[Music]
okay
um oh yeah he's the one that gives you
five maximum defense extra and restores
them
what a good guy
yeah okay let's see um
maybe i want
[Music]
yeah we'll try and work on this
all right
where is my freaking haven
sanctuary where is it
that's what i like to see
[Music]
one second please no problem i'm just
surviving to the music
[Music]
i want to learn how to do like like one
of those medieval
dances that you see in medieval movies
and game game of
uh chairs
[Music]
but i can't even dance the waltz can you
dance the waltz
kelly can i dance a wall
yeah i mean yeah
i guess i mean am i
a very long time ago if we ever have a
3d
like a collaboration in in 3d bodies
let's let's dance together it doesn't
have to be the world
but i really want to dance it's very
simple
one two three one two three yeah but my
brain can't i can't wrap my brain around
i just can't
yeah i mean i mean i guess it's hard for
for some
people like like it's hard for me to
wrap my head around card games
everyone's got what they're good at
i've been having this issue of get
not getting my my sanctuary so you might
win this round
oh i see yeah
[Music]
um let's see
i should have used that damn it oh
oh well
don't worry this deck is very [\h__\h] oh
i just freaking realized
uh okay hold on a second hold on
[Music]
let's just get this one out there
want a second
[Music]
a half waited for you
long enough there we go
this unicorn goes away soon i want more
room
does it does it do what i think it does
yes it does yeah yeah yeah i fully
understand my deck no
i'm happy okay
that was the last effect right
okay i'm happy
i'm happy
i know you killed him so fast kelly
he deserved a better life than that yeah
my fluffy companion
[Music]
doesn't matter
okay um
[Music]
oh
oh wait do i want that one maybe instead
yes yes yes
uh-huh
[Music]
and then try that
okay now we got some tigers going
and now we want that
yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay okay okay now i have a word too
now yeah
wait i can't attack right okay let's go
let's go kelly um let's see
um to get that stupid unicorn down
i should probably wait on this wait no
[Music]
all right i'm gonna do it
i already did it okay
already attacked okay
[Music]
see
uh oh yeah i guess you can't i can't
evolve that one whoopsie doodle
uh you're wrecking your brain over there
hold on hold on um
i'm just gonna no i don't want another
one unicorns are good
don't underestimate their palace yeah i
know
oh wow
[Music]
[\h__\h] finally what's about time
okay
and one more let's get myself back up to
25 hp
yeah that's what i like to see hey
double double ward yep okay okay i can't
i can't
i can turn this around
[Music]
lots of brain trying to
get get the last pieces of my brain
puzzled together i don't even know what
i'm saying
okay um concentration
uh let's see
nine
[Music]
all right here we go mm-hmm what you
gonna do what you gonna do when kiara
comes for you
now let's see i can do that next later
[Music]
oh i guess i can't go up to 25. that's
very silly oh well it doesn't matter
oh well i got some tigers i guess
oh fancy seeing you here
who can who can play the most
ah
[Music]
now the thing that i don't understand is
if i do this
does this does this disappear see i
cannot look at the chat so i will never
know the answer
ah i'll just
[Music]
what do i really want no
but i mean that doesn't yeah
i want to win this
[Music]
i just hope i'll just help
and now i'm definitely
that's okay because
[Music]
[Applause]
looking into a freaking mirror
oh what else can i do and i only got a
[\h__\h] card left
okay
yo thank you funny kelly
no i don't um
i will destroy you anyway i will destroy
you the power of unicorns
yeah yep um
let's see
now i'm done okay oh my [\h__\h] god
there's three sanctuaries
it's a lot of sanctuary yeah
uh
i mean sure okay give me that kind
oh but this one doesn't
okay oh my oh my god um yum
well not much i can do
even though i got some points left but
but i'll i'll let
destiny play this one out
may the one with the most rng
loch quinn yeah rng's
that'll be fine
um
this looks so ridiculous yeah it does
look pretty crazy
you have a lot of sanctuaries you do
oh my god
[Music]
do i want that or that i can only play
oh it's just not
in the end it doesn't matter i think
i'll go with him
oh my god oh my god
whoa a lot of automatic things happen
i don't even know what's happening right
now to be honest i have literally no
clue what's going on
[Music]
yummy
um
ah let's end this game
no i want to feel
[Music]
me
oh god wait who's gonna win this
i have no idea
[Music]
okay oh my god what's what's
ah ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay okay i feel a bit more protected
but okay
um yep yeah bye now now this
really it's just like like
if oh god i think yeah
i might die because of wrath
oh [\h__\h] yeah
because next turn when you end your turn
ross i think going to kill me
whoa really yeah this is like
with the automatic damage now wherever
that happens yeah
okay i want a game
i was i won a game
yeah wow
i won one game congratulations
yay i got a game
one game yeah that's all i needed
just one i'm glad you got one
wow yay celebratory drink
i hope that was not too painful for the
audience i hope you guys had fun
watching that
wow i learned a lot i feel like i
actually learned a lot more about your
deck than
than about the deck that i chucked
yeah yeah well
yeah maybe you can
like make an even better shadowcraft
deck
for next time and then yeah
maybe better for next time yeah if you
practice with it and understand your own
deck maybe you'll be fine
[Music]
i think so i just need to learn how to
do it more but i feel like that play
style is a little more
like suited to me i don't know maybe
i'll try some of the other crafts
the one that you had the whole thing
yeah you should try other crafts not not
only like go for a shadow craft because
it has skeletons and stuff maybe others
have like better effects and play styles
for you yeah
yeah not only the visuals yeah
well um so everyone that has
been our little showdown and the
showdown champion
[Music]
i won five and you won one and uh
we will both participate i think both
uh in a tournament sometime soon we will
both get actual
coaches for that until now we just
learned it on our own but next time we
will have
like experienced coaches who teach us
how to do things
so that you guys don't have to face palm
that the whole stream anymore
i kind of like making them face palm
though it's kind of fun
yeah not gonna lie yeah there's some
there's something fun about it everyone
who thinks they can do it better
download the game from our description
you better download it and prove us the
obvious truth
yeah also it's it's free so as we said
it's free so please
play it on your own it's a lot of fun
and lots of free stuff you can get
and maybe if you're lucky you can play
against us someday i don't know how the
tournament really works maybe that's
already decided to participate
i don't know it can't be someday i mean
i'm going to be practicing against
randos
just to prepare for the tournament
because i won't lose this time
i will lose i'm going to study my cards
well and i'm going to need to play
against some random other players
we won't battle against each other
unless we
both get to the very last fight i wonder
yes i guess we i guess we better get to
the very last fight yeah
well any anything you got to say
[Music]
nope i had a great time though that was
fun i was i was super focused but that's
just how i get when i play games like
this
i actually really was having a great
time oh yeah yeah you were very focused
yeah but that's what happens to me when
i do like anything that
is like i guess this kind of game i
suppose i feel like i'm obligated to
focus because if i don't then it'll just
be it'll be a nightmare
if i don't really try you guys know my
attention span is is that of a goldfish
um i had a good time
i'm glad me too i'm really really hooked
on the game i'm gonna play more i'm
looking forward to the tournament
and i hope all of you enjoyed today's
stream thank you shadow verse for
sponsoring it
thank you thank you thank you that was a
great time
also a personal advertisement please
watch
heart challenger and my most recent uh
song cover
bokudo which reached 100k
today so if you didn't see it yeah if
you didn't watch it yet
it's an acoustic cover please check it
out thank you
and that's it for today for me i'll see
you guys tomorrow
yeah that's it for me too i have a
members only stream tomorrow so for
those of you that are tier three see you
there and um
we're going to be doing tabletop rpg
stuff so look forward to that
um yeah with that being said i guess i'm
pretty much done
um what am i gonna read i think i'm
gonna read super chats from this
stream at the end of my asmr drawing
stream because you guys seem to like the
asmr
super chats so i will read them at that
time
so look forward to it yeah softly spoken
super chat
writing indeed yeah it do kind of sound
like that
so look forward to
[Music]
that verse bye bye everyone see you next
time
[Music]
so
you