[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music
]
[Music]
yes I love you together with review I
love you I love you
[Music]
full introduction of each we can Start
with Srikandi srikan
nih okay
[Music]
okay
that's familia family yes
Hello  everybody loves you
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] [
Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music
] [
Music] [
Music]
nice nice nice
already
using  yourself
[Applause]
[Music]
Pertiwi
okay
[Music]
that's it, how come he can
see that's the picture of five, it's
possible no no download points deh
understance
thank you
yey
[Music]
everyone my name is defeated  the blacksmi
from follow ID genre Hurray ID sanq Seno
kajia Kaira deh si risk ini mah
yes
[Music]
spicy
enter the
best version
[Music]
now
please 6
[
Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
[  Music]
hi
[Music]
My name
is today
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] it's
time for us to have a shouting match
because there is Pertiwi on stage
Pertiwi first No,
zombies
[  Music]
[Applause]
okay okay
start okay
[Music]
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
okay okay let's go let's go Srikandi le
Let's go Let's go Let's go
[Music]
hahaha
okay okay
[Music]
okay okay okay
[Music  ]
two one
in the afternoon
[Music]
[Applause]
Noisy aura
Oh my God,
it looks like it's ready to fight, yes, every team on this team's
spirit is above the sky, ready to
fight. In my opinion, yes, that's really
Wow, Pertiwi fish
[Music  ]
now that's right after this Munasin Pay
will tell you the list of these little games
guys
event in the killne eventory school
ayomi Mas regarding
[Music]
[Applause]
from chapter the fourths with Colin
fort and up to date remove To The
Potter the secrets  and up to date
without shop for and then after that we
have badminton from the eye site and
badminton from beside and also of today
soccer
and that's
or and day
[Music]
[Music] are
we going back to respectivisi
or not?  each team, okay, okay, okay
[Music
] [Music]
[Music]
[Applause]
games
[Music]
Next we have to move to the word
fortification. Let's
interview,
move
on. Yes, we've told them to move.
I already said that I wanted to interview according to the
rondon, but
suddenly I pulled
out, so stay for now, okay? But it's okay, okay,
if that's the case, we'll just move,
OK, let's just move, okay,
let's go
[Music]
Come on, guys, what's the fillet? That's the fabric
[  Music]
guys
[Music]
Thank you Thank you Thank you animation
[Music] [
Applause]
okay
[Music]
What are you most a Friday of the years
team not
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
[Music] Are
you afraid that we have tactics?
Really there are tactics? No, I don't think so, I don't think
we have to believe that
we only exist, but if
I were them, I wouldn't have any, I'd
say yes, you know
[Laughs]
for the Srikandi team, the leader
seems to have forgotten to click, yes, the
initial stage, No, he hasn't
chosen a team yet
[Music]
He was
told to just type it in, please don't forget to
choose a team, yes, red Heroine yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes oh thank you Thank
you Thank you
[  Laugh]
I want to fly, please How do I do it
here, just be creative, near here, here, everywhere
[Music]
click Wow, then when does this start,
okay, okay
[Applause]
[Music] [
Music] [
Music]
each one and then this is it.
White, who's Pertiwi? Pertiwi is just
walking straight away wow
in
Pertiwi, there's no one
looking after them at all
[Music]
but it seems like Pertiwi has
started wow
ver please comment squishy really fast for
a moment Winner please coming
we need an explanation of what this is
[Music]
right?  who
[Applause]
yes I know
n
[Music]
draw to go to and me backhand and
basically
wow
[Music
] [Music
] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
Pertiwi impress
coding
[Laughs]
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
hmm
already play the fort only just for
like one time playing so we move to the
Nur game okay okay
keep going
[Music]
we can't be that fast Wow that's okay
kiyoso is that the name  The Japanese Yes, I
prefer potato Kyosuke because of the potato
that who from
Pertiwi will race from Pertiwi
is jeng jeng jeng jeng Who
is the
fauna risk and Sora sempak
from Srikandi there is
also a Marine
representative from in
GP yes guys so look at this they have to
play 3 times  You have to do three laps,
not just once, so I think this is
a bit longer than the other one,
it has to be longer because it's longer.
That's true, yes, the Alien team that
wins from the capture will win 40
points, right?
Winning Story Oh, this time 30 this time  30
points, so this is the game, no, no
relay, no relay, so it's
straight away,
whoever comes in first, right?
[Music]
start, Brother. Yes, they're
really excited, yeah
[Laughs]
I think Yes, that's it. It's all ready
[Music]
red-red.
H here's the starting point
[Applause]
[Music]
squishy is
quite advanced, that's senpai's voice. It's already at the
front along with the fauna Eh,
I think apples are stupid
[Music]
here's the fish still attached to
spider-man Oh my gosh ora  Oh my God,
it seems like they've been practicing a lot,
right? And they don't
know
where they are, guys.
[Music] there are
only two left, so the
server
has disappeared. Oh, if that's the case, I can enter
the server first, I can just enter the server first,
this will be given to me  Do you know what's on
Raise, it seems like I'm giving it, so I've done this,
don't ask, please. Try Oh, look at
the trend. Try, there's one of the highlights,
tell us to recard, okay?
Sorry Guys, my squishy is that so nothing
not
[Music]
Dead and
God, okay, okay  Guys, no, it's okay,
but now you can enter the
mainhop,
thank you,
thank you, okay
[Music]
if that's the case,
but if that's the case, it's better for us like this,
for the DC one, maybe it's
okay, we'll repeat it, but for the next one, I think
according to  I'm not being fair to
people who have done this, can't
say it anymore, it's okay, let
's try again, okay? Let's try again, OK? Here I will check again
[Music]
Maybe I said it first to the
teams, both of them
just told them to have a sack race  instead it ended up in the
kidnapper's sack,
who's it's kind of
at the edge of a cliff, sorry
[Music]
here's the score, it's not a score like 1 2
3, but the score is based on points,
so if for example you
see if you guys and the explanation
and I for  ready for it on the Twitter
and no so talking about it on
[Music]
where talking a Where pointing about the
Coins on every game
yeah
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music
]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music] [
Music]
[Music]
hmm everybody that's the best but
in sack racing you have to do
all three  who finished first Oh I
thought there was only one person who
had to be all three,
this is really crazy, it
turns out, yeah
[Laughs]
[Music] I
already won, which was really cool,
now they win, they will also be
able to make a comeback. No,
I don't think so.  selected can still comeback
wow wow
[Laughs]
[Music]
thank you
guys thank you guys gold everything in the
back Already won twice you want
twice you think you can with the next
one yeah yeah yeah  yes yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
Wow, that's
really high, you
can still give because we've only
just given two, really
[Music]
I really want to believe in Mother Earth, I
really want to trust like that
[Music]
[Laughs]
okayokayokay
so everything is ready hmm I think
Let's ask these guys to choose Indo okay
[Music]
who do we have to ask
there are three Bocil this death there is a frog
there is a Gura there is a fire kurase Empire
but this is funny you know this is really  Isn't it true that blue
versus pink is
cool
[Music]
Wow, is
n't it true that if Pertiwi wins, for
example, if you win,
for example, if you win,
you have to go after the softcase
[Music]
hang on, the team
one of his friends is
still under
[Music]
guys
[Music]  ]
this stitch is really cool
[Music]
actually cool,
different from Srikandi friends by
being chased but not Pertiwi still
[Music]
This is already 100 points, the difference is
180 rings, 180 points,
not yet
chased. It was 3 but it could be really far
this is really far,
it's already 50 Diamonds Yes, there's no
difference Heeh 100 only one left wow
[Music]
I like it
wow wow I know the finger finally
their first
Wow indeed the finger Queen is on the edge
Queen
queentem really Queen really wow
[Music]
thank you  you
alright yeah guys
Pertiwi with the first when What yes What yes is
this if they wih this can catch up
loh this is this now
[Music]
eee the badminton
Please just like one thing
if one team wins the badminton just that
one adds 20 right to
me because no  watching them practice
badminton, you know, badminton is difficult,
in my opinion, the most difficult of all, let's
see what badminton is like,
so badminton is divided into two.
Next match
[Music]
we'll be there for a moment hehehe
Pertiwi has Kayla Kiara Ilfi and afternoon
[  Music]
cool for Pertiwi there are Kayla and Tiara
so they will fight yes against a
and b against B
versus
ready okay
[Music]
lots of practice so it looks like they can
carry if they can just hit once.
From one save so
what are the badminton rules like?
for the first save it has to be
diagonal after that it can be any way
if it reaches that means ee
e the other team can be like if we hit
or pants then the other team gets points
but if we hit it then it turns out that we
touch it in our place meaning the
other team still gets points like that
Wow  but I've practiced, I'm sure I
can do it hmm
Come on, let's fall, we're ready, the gang has
started, I don't know, okay,
now it's
versus Kayla Kiara, eya
[Music]
with Pertiwi with Kayla Tiara and
Srikan with Toraja,
then that's it, the ball is on the team, it's on
here
[Music]
this is Pertiwi
oh oh oh oh oh
oh
[Music]
we look at it too far up,
so the technique is we have to go
straight
[Music]
[Laughs]
[Music] it's
really hard, she looks like yes, it's
really hard, this is hard  really no,
no lie
[Music]
[Applause]
too excited maybe
[Music]
earlier
Oh no no that's not in that's
why Oh it's not in. Oh
yes because you have to diagonal it
Oh yes for yes this will be
up to what the score will be?  up to 10, that's right
[Music]
just keep catching up, this is cool,
maybe the film came out
but it turned out to be TV
[Music]
Wow, this is a relay, this is cool,
they are here
[Music]
who took one more point from
Srikandi but there are still 3 more or not,
still  Oh no two more
[Music]
game finished 3-10
310 a
So now Pertiwi's points are
60 Wow, this really can be caught up
Let's see b what happens
then we go straight to b no
really
continue to the same grave  Bey and also let's
go to their respective positions
[Music]
dozo in the position
okay
[Music]
will win again Oh my God
sip sip sip sip
OK
Heroine starting from Heroine this time
from Bay directly welcome straight
in come on
I can't  this game is over, is it
trillintar
one by one one by one, cool, cool,
come on, okay, so it's a fierce battle,
coffee and Iyo, flora, friends, yes
[Laughs]
[Music]
So the secret is that if you can't
lay it out, how come it's hard to paint
because later  I have that, so it's
really easy for the opponent,
right, so as long as the first service
can be relayed, they can speak, but
if not, that's okay, hmm,
unfortunately, it's auto, but it's still on,
but the sound,
but if it's from American pop, it's
hard, isn't it, really hard to see?
like this
[Laughs]
[Music]
hitting a stray at the same time is
indeed more difficult than it
seems, I've seen it too, this is
how we play it,
how else is the
direction too high so
our short fall is affected if for example we are
too above him So  short Oh yes
because he is too high
[Music]
[Laughs]
29 only one point left for Pertiwi
[Music]
to win
so we are 40
so 70 80 can now be replaced 70
Pertiwi 80
wins narrowly so that Srikandi
can win
[Music]
Oh  my God,
where is
[Music]
everyone has practiced as much as possible
and
that Let's see the results of
their practice hmm I'm just here watching
football
of the Galaxy
[  Music]
is starting to come in oh no one's buying it
right he's ready too they're okay
[Music]
but I'm the one who's close
on the way team
oh hang on a minute
[Music]
senpai Heaven click Draw
they're
[Music]
just
giving it away  this morning before
it started, I wanted to practice
badminton
[Music] I
really wanted everyone to practice for
this, Holoid Cup this time
everyone practical event super last
minutes like you hours one our for this
that I want to be practical
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
from everybody
okay okay
[Music]
crazy
I keep going from who
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [
Laughing] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
he saved me  keep vowing to hold
on
[Music]
cool too
[Music] it's
a shame
[Music]
yes that's right
[Music] it was
taken again
less enthusiastic that the kick was
emotional
then
straight away
[Music]
started to be taken but I don't know
anymore the team is holding it now
from Pertiwi but was kicked again by a
gokick from
[Music] I
was really excited friends
[Music]
still no
one has entered,
goalkeeper
[Music]
OK, we have entered the 5th minute
and with a score of 10 for the Srikandi team, OK?
friends, he's right, he's 10 10 minutes. Then
rafting for another 10 minutes.
Oh I see,
that was the ball, it was like going around and around
[Music]
ouch.
Let's look at this. Yovi, this time, he'll
make a splash. If they make the
wrong move, they might score a goal. The problem is this.
The ball is really close, we'll see what it will
do
[Laughs]
oh,
how about this, how about this, will
there be a breakthrough
[Music]
there needs to be a very aggressive skull, yes,
as a goal scorer from the first one,
but he's still aggressive,
okay?
[Music]
oh,
there's another score  the goal was just discussed, it
turns out you're really good at
kicking. Wow, aggressive guys,
now I'm
[Music]
OK, I got kicked and it's starting to get close to the
goal, but
yeah, it's okay, I'll start again,
kicked by Emil, who was
taken by Ouch,
if I look at the distribution, what's going on?
Yes, the Srikandi Team actually has
someone guarding each area,
that's very good. Yes, for example, if
there's a ball here,
whose job is to take it? Yes, what's more,
Emmy looks at that senpai, sometimes he
seems to come forward too, you know?  if
they advance, everyone advances, so everyone,
no one can enter
the area, they are crazy hmm
[Music]
Let's see Mother Earth
[Music] it
's almost 9 minutes and 5 seconds until we
enter and in 1 minute we will
end the first hall
[  Music]
maybe because it seems like it's going to be a while now
[Laughs]
[Music] be
careful
where he's going to kick three
more [Music] to get in.
Just a few more seconds before we
rest for a while
Yes
[Music]
456789 10 minutes
[Music  ] it
would be interesting if we called
one of the Srikandi teams, okay, yes,
we will kidnap one iron and then kidnap
one by three, do you want to be curious or not, the
strategy is
first, then stand up,
if that means the most,
then who is our opponent, the one
from Pertiwi who has to  We
invite you
from Pertiwi. Who can win?
Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe,
maybe, okay, okay, maybe
[Music]
hi,
Lionel Messi's mother
[Music]
[Laughs]
Astagfirullah
OK,
first of all, guys, Sushi Master will give it
to China, come on, one one
[Music]
OK,
we  send
[Music]
even though I only practiced once
the ball was high, I didn't reach
it, so
the wall was the height of you, the short one
[Laughs]
oh my defense, yes, this defense, that
one is above all  How come the ball
doesn't reach it? Oh, that's
all. I think if the moon
was lower, I'd definitely get hit.
How do you feel? You're
guarding the goal, it seems like it's
really tight. Yes, the ball is being held a little bit.
Yes, that's fine. That's a good
ball, isn't it?  It's there to hold and
to be held a little, that's how
I work to touch
the ball, isn't it?
Bold handler or not,
but if the handle smells like that, actually
Pertiwi has a strategy
to use our feelings.
How do you feel when you've been in this,
right, because Srikandi has already
stolen gold?  First of all, is there a strategy
so that we can make a comeback, maybe Pertiwi,
we really believe in being able to do Epic
Comics, because earlier, we can
now also be like that. Oh,
there is a Miracle Shot, so you
have to be careful,
Srikandi is crazy when we look at the
defense from above.  they are
really strong, so you have to step up too,
okay, the
two MPVs from each team are
really cool, eh, let's ask
if
this all looks like it's really vengeful, right?
Eee these two
[Laughs]
I'll give you this so that your team wins,
like that, for example in  the original game
has been given this red card but we
can't give you my record,
are both teams ready
like they are, yes, both of them are
fierce, you know,
and thank you, thank you, the Pertiwi team
believes in Lady Luck, I
wonder how they can make a comeback?  Yes, in the end,
friends, there is still pain.
Let's continue, it seems like everything
is
brutal [Music]
fortunately he was immediately held by the
winner, he won straight into the middle.
But unfortunately there was Srikandi.
How about
it, he went straight into the
middle of whoever it was and that's
ironing.  who
else, apparently a little more friends
[Music]
where do you think it will be,
oh
Pertiwi Pertiwi How do you have to try
hard so they can make a comeback,
because three of them are already here, okay, three of
them are really hard, fortunately, it's hot
for irvice senpai, if not  that could
happen 4 0 that's it hah Abu rises
Yovie Come on, come on, come on, who is he,
I'm calm again, you're not water, that's
really scary, I think,
oh,
this is a bit worrying because he
said earlier that he really believes
in Lady Luck, but the glass is dregs
[Music]
but  It's really cool, I saw the Srikandi, it's
like every time they fit it, it's just
right, it's so accurate, so it's like it's
right and it's like I already know
each other's house
[Music]
tomatoes wow, it's
very, very blue-blue, it's a bit
scary, it's really scary,
fiber Yes, maybe  Is
this like revenge or not
because of the tug of war if that's possible?
Anyway, we have to uh flatten them. They're
already starting to approach and ah,
through the Sun, it's a shame, it's just not
enthusiastic enough, if you can get in,
football is full of passion,
yes, it's a shame. Said
who would have thought?  -I thought
the direction was towards the water hole, there
was waiting, but suddenly the
counter, but finally it was caught, okay,
okay, okay, okay
[Music]
wow,
come on, come on,
take
it, it's been 3 minutes and it's been 40 How come
I'm new, I just said it's done, I can't feel it  It's
been more than 3 minutes, I know,
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
If I'm the
white team,
but if you look at it,
Srikan's position is really good,
yes, it's really good, you know
[Music]
but if you say it like this, it means that
Pertiwi also seems like they're really
trying, yes, offense there, how many
times did they attack
[Music]
[  Music]
why did I jump from the oath chair
[Music]
but like this,
but I was kicked again by Zaskia,
I was being chased by Kayla and
Mori,
bye bye bye, come on, come on, come on, do we still
have 5 minutes? Is
this a comeback or not?  no, they
can't, they've found it, it seems like that's the
right strategy. OK, that's gold.
[Music]
the ball is
free-free-free to take it, okay, but
often if you want to push again, what
will happen is they'll
go straight, guys.
[Music]
starts  again the kick from science via
send to the center was taken by the government
[Music]
that time, right, watch the back, yeah, then
there's Luna. Then the ovens are
Koyori and Kiara, actually it's
not bad, it's just like Come on, stay again
so you can draw if you draw, what
happens BTW  Oh, if a drama happens,
then there will be a penalty, there will
still be a analyzer
if the penalty is a draw too
[Music]
time is running out, friends.
Is the Miracle cake that we are hoping for
going to happen? Let's watch the boholder
finally get held by YouTube
[Music]
[Music  ]
finally it's horrifying
Wow, this is what it looks like, oh, it
looks like Srikan has won, this is
really good. I don't know how it's
like eh
[Music]
so even though it's the same as this, it's also
in the position of being divided, but it
seems like Srikan is always like
always there to receive passes like that,
really, sometimes on Pertiwi
they pass like that but there's really no one
there.
[Music]
seems to be spread everywhere so there's always
someone who can pick it up
Oh it's started it's started but it
seems like it was taken by Srikandi  passed
again into the middle, finally it was taken by
[Music]
maybe what Pertiwi lacked was a
lack of defense, yes.
In my opinion, it's not a lack of defense,
more like if he passes,
it's rare for someone to take it straight away
[Music]
so it's over-over.  it's better,
that's why he's good,
come
on, let's do it. Can't do it?
[Music]
sometimes it's too late, right?
thirty seconds later, not yet, but I
want to receive this receipt. His defense is very
sharp, friends, it's true, it's true, he's
always the one  take
[Music]
Oh my God
it's like I'm ready to catch
[Music]
again
five four three
[Music]
[Applause]
wait for
us who are sweating yeah I think I
really understand
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
crazy
World
[Music]
golgi
Yes guys
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause]
[Music]
come on, let me start this  selling meatballs
before the competition starts but before
I can't, I can't even go up on meatballs
[Laughs]
[Music]
lings
Your Heart
peop you
[Music]
[Laughs] [Music
] [
Laughs] [
Music]
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [
Music]
[Music]
Pertiwi
sport Pertiwi [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [
Laughter]
[Music  ]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] [
Applause] [
Music] [
Laughter] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Applause] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
thank you
[Music] [Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you thank you
say Our last cave is a
fotbar or not yeah
let's go let's go
nded On The Spot okay
y
[Music]
with you ready
okay
three  two one
[Applause
] [Music] Piece OK thank you [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Laughs]  OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it 3 2 1
[Music]
but are you paying attention to
these viewers? Unifornia is all
wearing jerseys and has numbers.  -the number
if you're paying attention. Oh
yes, how come
I have long hair so I can't
see it, but let's look at the
others.
I wanted to see which one, which one,
yes, because the committee has all long hair.
If you look at
yourself, you know the number. Oh yes.  there are some,
there are some,
but it's not very clear,
that's the truth, but yes, that's the
skin. For this time, a
special skin for the Solo ID card 2023 has been prepared
and everyone uses a jersey
with a number on the back to
add to the spirit of the hollow ID card. No, the
trailer continues to run out, that's it.  everyone
got a skin and then this until it was made
like so that the game could be played
smoothly, like before badminton,
suddenly there was a racket like that, right, the place for
meatballs and soto gave the guys a
way first Oh yes, this is eee This is a new
Hello ID card, yes, while there are
so many of us  Oh, the series of Gelora
holo.id events that haven't finished yet, that's right,
there's still a continuation of the event on
the 15th and 17th, what do you think,
basically, just have a look at the
Halo ID Cup event this time, this one,
isn't it all? This one is up to the
point.  closing Yes, that's right, what's the
impression and message of everything?
Wow, who did it start with, ah,
what a long time ago.
I'm actually asking the viewers, but
if you want to answer, you can also
watch YouTube, it's
really exciting. Oh, the most difficult thing
is that it seems like everything is difficult, actually, I
hope you all enjoy it too  Yes,
with the Halo ID Cup this year and hopefully
next year it will be a Step Up again.
Next year, do we have to think again about
how to make the game even cooler
so that it is more popular than this?
Yes, what does that mean, if we imagine,
what do we remember about the Hola ID card that was
last year?  the print is also just like
this one, it's much neater, right? Yes, that's
right, but I'm very happy. Next year,
next year, what's more, it's
crazy, the pressure is already high,
yes, it's still another year, yes.
Yes, I've handed it over to oli or MC
MU or MC  again or maybe Muna
wants this, there's something else, so far, that's
all, so we can close this event
because we are at the
end of the event, so
for the teams who might still
want to play this, um,
that's the world.  there will be. So if the
teams want to play again. That's just until
what date,
20 20.
Yes, if you want to play, hurry up, that's right, that's
right, August 21, the world
will be there until August 21, so
maybe there's something that's just a fad ah  I
want to play this or or maybe there are
other members who apparently
don't do this, don't come here,
then I want to try it, you can, you can,
yes, fans can play or not, wow,
you
can look carefully at the description,
maybe you can
[Laughs]
That's it.
Yes, then let's close the event.
Thank you, Eee, Oli and Rainy, they have been
really helpful because
actually using it doesn't really mean that much.
See you again in Halo ID Cup 2018
[Music] [
Music]