[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
thanks
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
huh
keeping that button activate
at all times again
[Music]
there you go
I used to always do that and then it
stopped and now it's happening again I I
deactivated it now it shouldn't happen
next time
[Music]
I'm crying
brings back good memories yeah
I guess so
terrible traumatizing memories
wait wait a second
okay okay
do I sound any different
from now on to compared to a second ago
to me
no oh that's so interesting I wonder
what the difference is
um
because
you know
I've been using some
go XLR settings profile since forever
since the beginning that Abby sent me
and
and I change like it no matter how many
times I save over it it always goes back
to what it was and changes back every
time when I reopen it even though I stay
safe over profile and doesn't do it but
anyway so with the mic setup it gives
you the choice between a dynamic
condenser and 3.5 millimeter and it
always defaults back to condenser and I
always change back to Dynamic
but it doesn't
apparently it makes no difference in
sound
you would think that would be important
because microphone can be dynamic or
condenser or apparently the 3.5 I don't
even know what that is
I don't know it's okay sometimes I
forget selling it back but you know
I'm a bit low I mean I can make myself
louder to see if that's what you want
and then I also turned down the high
frequencies
every time
every time I turn them down
but not that like that makes a
difference anyway we Jam a little loud
okay
hi how about now
turn it down a little bit
well I'm not the only one who's not able
to tell a difference let's suppose
begin to quiet are you for real
ah one thing
I already wrote this when I put up my
schedule
um yesterday did you see my schedule
here it is
we're now on Tuesday but
um
I already said that you know long
streams
are tiring or tired me out last week
um but you know I kind of said I want to
finish my trade Prime and I want to
finish fighting blue
um but I might change Friday turns out
while I was sleeping
some
girls decided to set the date and time
of a collab on Friday
um
so which I'm happy about too because we
were waiting for that
but it was literally a couple hours
after I put out the schedule
those Rascals yeah I already pulled out
the schedule well now fact is
Friday is probably not no night I mean
pretty much 99
no no no it's not not Ian girls
but uh
fine blem will be changed to a collabo
not on my channel not Wilbur no no no no
no as as if do you honestly think that
while I'm sleeping
anything is going to be decided while
I'm sleeping
when when I'm the one who's pushing it
do it
think about it
for a second
yes now you understand
[Laughter]
progress while I'm sleeping
no no no no no no
oh yeah I mean I would appreciate you
know
somebody taking the the wheel
food arranges a date using a keyboard on
accident
nah
I mean I could see a future where she
can do that but
that's not now yet
no no it's not about the time it's about
the you know who's who's
who's
you know in charge
even unofficially in charge
for who's typical to do such things and
who's untypical to do such things
uh today I ate
my beloved
chocolate pancake breakfast again but I
didn't use strawberries
I didn't use a banana
you know what looked good
this time in the supermarket
because I gave up on strawberries right
now
one of strawberry season is upcoming in
Austria though
never know
blueberries
look no raspberries are like even
Advanced baby season raspberries are so
difficult raspberries are like always
moldy unlike at least after one day
they're moldy but blueberries are
actually surprisingly
sturdy
yeah
and they were good
pancakes
they were good yum yum yum
yeah Frozen too
I had like I I warmed up frozen
strawberries a while ago but those
tasted disgusting and then I warmed up
frozen blueberries and raspberries
and they turned out pretty good what is
it with strawberries eh I just want some
strawberries
yes frozen strawberry why why do why do
frozen blueberries and raspberries work
well but frozen strawberries don't work
at all
in terms of taste
frozen blueberries tastes like ice cream
fiber structure Oh serious replies
Frozen gray is what
two hours
yeah I mean I saw it yesterday oh should
we do a watch along
in two hours there's a 10 minute thingy
we can take it like as a break
a 10 minute
um
uh tears of the Kingdom
is that what it's called
can I get it right
oh I got it right because I just read it
uh two seconds ago
uh I was watching a little bit
um's birthday she was learning a
choreography at the spot that's cool
um
I saw a cliff you called my name with
pop no papa go yay I wasn't going to
school well now my prop only problem is
I can sleep at least over 1am because I
have to study and homework ah
yeah that's gonna be a problem you have
to watch my archived
vods okay
buds watch go home
before sleep open kiwamo Channel and
then watch most recent Chihuahua video
I did go to the post office yesterday
and I was genuinely concerned
because so there was a leather they
needed me to pick up personally with a
thanks to the memberships with a uh uh I
needed a pass passport or whatever to
proof I am myself so normally you know
that gets you a little bit worried oh
what is it
but I already already saw that it's from
this marvelous beautiful
ass company called GIS in Austria
I hate it I hate it I hate it I hate it
[\h__\h] them
um
my whole life my whole life everybody
hates kiss
uh
I already saw that and I thought but I I
do I mean I I remember you know paying
um a large Bill to them because I I
forgot to pay it for a while or I just
evaded paying for a while
um but then eventually I paid it and
it was a little bit more than it should
be because of that but I I wasn't pretty
sure yeah I paid it why are they sending
me a letter to pick up are they trying
to sue me because I forgot paying
something that I didn't know about but I
feel I felt got paid it but I got really
confused and I started doubting myself
no no no so GIS in Austria is
um yeah it's like uh
[\h__\h] them I don't even know what that is
yeah TV text
like if if you have a TV at home even if
you only use it with like one of those
sticks to watch Netflix Etc
um and you don't even have
it connected to watch normal TV
and you're not subscribed to anything
like that no no no even then yeah or
radio then
um if you have something that is in
theory able to receive something like
that even if you're not receiving it
then you have to pay uh that every month
to them and if you just move somewhere
they will find out and they will come to
your place
and it will come to your place and
they're like no no and then when you
open the door you're like [\h__\h] and
they're like so so miss kiwawa you
registered to the gis hmm
may I come into your home and check what
what receiving products you have they
ask they don't have a right to come in
but they ask and you know in the past I
was like always very intimidated by them
yeah
and then one time I think I I was
actually brave enough to say no and
close the door on them and they said
they'll come back with a permit to to
get into my place to check if I have a
TV for real
my mom advised me to always say no to
them and say [\h__\h] them well yeah are
they
their books do they fake they are
so
they're the IRS loves TVs
yeah and I think they never came back
after that but I was always like nervous
when somebody rang my doorbell I was
like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I was looking through the
little peephole and and uh
yeah when there was someone there that I
didn't know who that was sometimes I
would be way too scared to open up even
if it was just you know somebody asking
for donations or whatever you know
yeah blue so that was in the past and
now I I moved like from Japan to Austria
all right so I had to
pay that again in Japan thankfully I
didn't have to pay it [\h__\h] them but
oh I wondered they have something
similar in in
Japan called NHK
um
but turns out so I never I was I've been
paying
them just because it's too annoying I've
been paying them even though I don't
have like I have a TV but I'm I'm not
using what they would need you to pay
for you know I'm just using Netflix and
stuff like that but in theory my TV I
guess could if I attached it to that
little box in the wall
I don't even have a cable for that
though but in theory I guess it could
receive TV stuff so because of that you
have to pay
a whopping
here it comes
54 Euro or so minimum
minimum uh per
month that's like 50 bucks
even if you don't use right it's so
ridiculous and I've been paying that
monthly and it's just been pissing me
off so much that's why sometimes I don't
I just wait I just ignore the letters
ignore them until they start adding
extra money onto it I know I know it
makes no sense because in the end I'm
paying it I should just pay it when it
first comes in but yeah per month that's
crazy right right right right right
right right
yeah so anyway I get this letter that I
have to pick up and I'm like oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] am I getting sued for not paying it
[\h__\h] dumb and then I go there and it's
like a blue leather blue Leathers are
very scary in Austria
so I don't know sometimes most of the
time I suppose it's like something
really important
hmm
it's so so expensive and then I'm
if I didn't have this blessed job then
holy [\h__\h] I would I would throw this TV
out of my apartment just so that I don't
have to pay that because 50 bucks for
someone who works a normal more normal
job is [\h__\h]
government communication mostly the part
of the taxes in the L yeah I think it's
something like that most of the time I
don't know they felt they were super
important so they sent me a blue letter
and I picked it up and then and then
I get really nervous when opening it up
but turns out they're just in Atlanta
they're just asking me Miss kiwawa uh
what products do you have
do you have a radio yes or no do you
have a TV yes or no
so funny if you think about it they
don't no they just assumed I had [\h__\h]
have been charging me for it I have been
paying for it because it's annoying
but they they just assumed it
and then State a certain amount of money
that I have to pay even though they
don't even know how many and which
products I do have
for real but turns out that these 50
bucks my brother told me those that's
like the minimum
that should have listened to your mom no
but I never let anyone in I never did
I just assumed
it's so stupid and so my brother tells
me oh you should just ignore that letter
because they're gonna get rid of GIS
soon don't you know and I'm like
honey
and he tells me
and I'm like oh
finally Justice he tells me that uh
apparently it's getting like for if your
kiss has been around for centuries but
apparently they are being canceled and
now the only thing you have to pay is
like 15 euro per month anybody so this
any literally anybody even if you live
in a tent with no radio and no TV
exaggerately on 10th okay where you
obviously can't receive it but even then
if you registered somewhere with an
address
you will have to pay 15 bucks
15 not 50. so the guess is gone but this
goes to the country the 15 bucks they go
to the country
but at least it doesn't go up to the
minimum of 50.
it's it's better it's better but this
way no one is getting
around
not doing it
it's it's better for me because I
I guess I prefer
just yeah yeah I prefer it this way yeah
but this one it goes apparently if you
have a normal job it will be just taken
off of your salary
uh you know many things that just
normally if you have a normal job they
just they just take it off of your
salary like insurance
Etc
but I I have a not so normal job so I
wonder how I will pay that I don't know
but
um so that's the future
and I just I think
I'm just so happy that the guests will
be gone because they are the biggest
[\h__\h] in
Austria
[Laughter]
I'm just so shameful
German word
[\h__\h] them finally they're gone all these
years when they have been bullying
people into paying their [\h__\h] even
though you don't use it oh my God that's
incredible that was finally over this
torture
is basically the same okabe
you can pretty much just yeah
oh just a soft
I didn't know that man
I didn't know about that happening at
all
can't believe it
yeah but
it's the same meaning but Sean Paul is
like saying it's an adjective I would
say I guess is that the right word
shot in Florida is the
the big word and Chad and follow is like
saying I am shadowful but uh you could
say I feel shot before that but you can
say I am shampoo you can't say I am Sean
Porter
yeah objective versus nounia
you may have heard of the noun but I
don't think you have heard of the
adjective possibly
hmm
no I don't even use cable
yeah right like legit it's not just me
but I think so many people have just
completely stopped watching normal TV
and just use those streaming services
which you don't have to have a TV for
you can just use your PC monitor for it
in theory
choose your PC for it so there's like no
need
um
I watch YouTubers instead of TV times
have changed
anyway that was the letter that I picked
up on the last day of the what was it a
month of a deadline or so but most of
that time I was in Japan you know so I
couldn't have picked it up thankfully I
don't know if I'm gonna reply to that
letter because they're already charging
me the minimum and I don't think it
would be any more than that and [\h__\h]
so
so I
I just
I have this problem where I ignore all
my problems
but they would be smaller problems if I
wouldn't ignore them
uh ironically
ironically
today
[Laughter]
foreign
your problems no that would just make
huge huge huge huge problems
problems
unbearably yo no that's not good
you can ignore your problems first maybe
but you can't ignore the problem of
ignoring your problem
ah
um
Hernandez
being asked to believe paying the
minimum is a good thing
[Music]
um
you can't ignore it because at some
point they're gonna sue you
um
anyway so okay in two one and a half
hours
we're gonna watch the Nintendo thing and
I wanted to start a little bit earlier
today but I moved it for an Energy's
birthday stream just because I don't
want to overlap with her
um
but my brother said he'll be back around
like 5 PM
and then we have to fix those [\h__\h] ah
the disaster of the furniture that we
have tried building up if you saw it on
Twitter yesterday I posted the picture
and then
I'm saying I have to say the replies
um
annoyed me a little bit
huh
um
so many people were just like oh just
flip it or so but like what what you
guys don't even understand you guys the
only one
if that was the a solution that would
make sense we would have tried it but
the planks are the same size and the top
one is supposed to be at the top the one
that is up there is supposed to be up
there because there there's like two
little you know it's it's be like that
but I think I know what the problem is
but I don't know how it happened
I don't know we'll try again because I
have a second one that I have to build
um
it's not from Ikea
what
[Laughter]
yeah I think the sliders are installed
too high because just looking at it
there's like the space that is missing
at the bottom because there is space
missing at the bottom
uh is too much at the top
plus well there's like a margin in the
middle
as well
um
but the thing is like we just installed
the sliders where the holes were already
pre-made
so that's weird
that that happened anyway
uh
we don't have to start over from scratch
I think but we have to take apart some
things yeah my brother was absolutely
losing it yesterday in the beginning he
was like oh yeah
just uh need one hour probably for one
of them
guide also said one hour
okay please you can backside backseat me
on games but backseating me on this
furniture piece where you don't know the
facts will obviously not go anywhere I
just feel like you guys are
underestimate or or overestimating my
stupidity okay we are not that stupid
okay give us some credit but anyway we
were three hours at it but my brother
was like oh we just need one hour and
then the second one will be faster
because then we already know how to
build it
so we'll try that again later he'll come
back he said around 5pm
and then I will we will attempt it again
though I helped more than I usually do
also my brother is a
uh
a job interview is having going well he
has yet to get a big okay but he says
some companies said they will reply to
him on Wednesday and you know generally
like everything has been going pretty
well for him very sad he said so let's
go
um I said to my brother that even even
if the holes were already there
I think we should just brute force it
and assume that maybe maybe the holes
were in the wrong place I can't really
imagine that happening but apparently
sometimes it happens right
in production so I I say yeah just let's
just make our own holes because it looks
like it must work if we just
scooch everything lower
make our own holes we can we can
um
yeah we just make our own holes scooch
it down
and then it should work
but we'll build the second one first
today
from zero
and see if we missed something but we
really looked at everything so closely
we paid a lot of attention to it
why not
those machines make no mistake that's
what I kind of thought
no nothing is Switched no nothing is
Switched
because
nothing is Switched period
yeah I just make my own holes
I am pretty confident yeah I am
okay I'm gonna lose it reading these
comments
thanks for trying to help but we are not
we're gonna find a common ground because
you are not able to see it in person are
you guys
and I with my brother have seen it in
person for hours
I am the one who came up with the genius
solution of fixing my table when about
10 people were not able to figure it out
okay so ah if anything I I am the genius
I may not use my hands often to do this
kind of hand work
but I was the one who came up with the
solution for my table which was wobbly
forever
trust in my brains right now
I just told you this because I was
trying to tell you when my brother is
coming back and why I will have to end
the stream at that point because I have
to finish this furniture thing
um
what the [\h__\h] what what ads why ads go
away ads
no super Jazz no no I will read the
super jumps now where where
it's probably the new hair super chats
right
or is it the
no I think I read the part two out of
400.
right
the new hair ones right yeah
because then I was like it does That's
So Many and I was like nope nope nope
nope I'm gonna run away from my problems
again
[Music]
look at it look at it thank you Al
oh no oh no
this is a beautiful beautiful thumbnail
Theo's mail
big brain excuse me I actually
I actually made my head smaller
I went around the outline of my head
and then I even made it a bit smaller
because I thought this looks insanely
huge anime heads are huge this is the a
little bit smaller version yeah yeah I
did
oh
yeah
I know it's it's incredible it's
unbelievable
let's go to the hair no I I took that
into consideration that hair will take
up like you know a little bit
but
um
oh this is almost almost wait here let's
let's see
but I think I took
I think I I definitely didn't take this
hairstyle as reference
uh apply
which one's gonna be
this one
okay you see this
so how big uh
we just have to get my eyes to align
wait my chin okay
all right I can't talk oh my God wait
it's already pretty much aligning
wait maybe like around here
oh God that's quite a bit right
so big hand I know
I know I know
but all hair no look you see my hairline
here because it's
think okay if we think it's into a
ponytail on the side so actually yeah I
may have a fluffy braid on there but the
hairline behind that that is like pretty
tight this will not take up for
enlistically speaking it will not take
up like five centimeters no
it would maybe at the most the hair
would maybe at the most take up one
centimeter
in reality
no not even I don't know unless you have
like but look at my hair
it's not the type of hair that takes up
like so much space
no no no no no no no no
oh
that was such a good episode
anyway okay okay enough
banter between us kfp enough of that
can I drink my tea out of the Nana tea
cup I'm celebrating another two's
birthday
yes I'm gonna use whole lighter why is
there something I shouldn't see
GD
or is there something that's missing
the number column what do you mean ah
you wanna see him
foreign
[Music]
the innovator
okay you want to tell me
questions
ah yeah uh check out 47 out thank you
thank you
who likes the question meme so I've been
like joking around with him too
I think so he says
simply thank you for the rest of the
chat and I've been trying out the Kiwa
blanket for a few weeks I have to say
it's the best thing which I've ever got
y'all
what a review
what a nice review it's a beauty to
behold and it keeps me warm in the cold
North my naps have never been better
thanks tencho my God what
a shiny sparkly reveal
it's it's a really good blanket
yeah I think I saw something like that
or general you didn't say which blanket
you just said eight blankets that was
the blanket
did you check uh like did you contact
them for like lost and found
maybe if it's hard for you to contact
them maybe a Japanese person can help
you
tried everything
oh
my God
oh you bought another man
you gotta be careful
I know you're really sad and upset about
it but you gotta be careful
what's up
only once
in a lifetime
big kids that was already expensive as
it is
nah
guys let this be a lesson to all of you
if you take
kiwawa's precious merch outside
somewhere
you better be really really really
careful
with it don't lose it
new one won't leave the room yeah it
shouldn't
I into slippers not fitting
and I saw by the way today in my for you
wait is it for you which which one is
the one that is like uh
messenger yeah my four you
by far you call them on Twitter
showed me today that
um
some people have been trying to contact
a whole Live email about merchandise
shipping being weird and them thinking
it's uh like what there must be
something wrong with it because it makes
no sense when it's more expensive and
more and cheaper for others Etc makes no
sense and apparently they have been
answered and been told oh this is normal
but then other people say that at least
with geek check I know I know I know we
all have like our experiences with geek
Jack but list of kick Jack uh the
shipping prices are not this insane
because they don't get decided right
away when you buy the item no it gets
updated later right
I haven't used big check before so I
don't know but apparently that's how it
works so you end up going away with less
shipping costs with geek check
[Music]
um
I'm Ian kitchen is my only option anyway
yeah I don't
I understand guys
I don't understand why it must be this
expensive it makes no sense why does it
cost so much
it makes no sense
um
per a proxy
what what's the you mean
shipping it to someone in Japan and they
ship it to you
I've heard of such services
um
yeah but I can imagine that like just
more casual fans will not like bother to
take the time to look into something
like that which I totally understand
like it shouldn't it shouldn't be
necessary
forwarding service yeah
it shouldn't be necessary but for
everyone who's listening now if you are
if you don't want to pay this much
shipping which is 100 understandable
then maybe consider looking into that
because that seems to be
um the best yeah tensor um
yeah yeah geek Jack has had history with
having kfp lose their merchandise I
heard of I know of that too so I know I
don't really want to encourage that
either it's difficult try try a proxy if
you want to get kiwawa merch
use tens of a comicat stuff oh yeah yeah
so you can even for other stuff yeah
that's nice
if you ever find something you want that
only ships to Japan
oh
well this is something where I really
recommend the community exchanging
information with one another
yeah
yeah yeah please do and
get smarter through that
save money for that
okay
thank you anyway uh simply for that
beautiful beautiful review I'm very
happy you like it so much thank you soon
foreign
[Music]
for your pretty showcase I'm so proud of
you it was an amazing showcase I cried
the whole time seeing the chickens and
pretty was so cool you always do your
best and it shows my beloved ocean you
always inspire me you'll do great in
four Fest I wish I could draw more often
but life happened and I had an art block
for a sad and sad for a while
I'm feeling better and ready to draw
many while I wasn't Simpkins again sadly
time zones are a pain but I always try
to catch up I'll always support you
thank
you thank you thank you yeah you've been
trying more chickens recently I always
love seeing them you're so cute we need
more more more more Champions and so
happy now we can talk about the fact
that uh
chicken has been officially what do you
say licensed we have to write and we
turned it into into 3D chicken we
already contacted dacoma about that like
over a year ago I think because over a
year ago we already implant all of that
um
do we still call it Takoma chickens when
it's official or when you if you wanna
be very like exact about it sure
yeah
I'm so so happy with my timkins I think
document drawing all those symptoms
um in the beginning especially made me
really love
this like mascot made me made it easier
for me to find an interest and and love
Mama God so thank you
I see chickens they're different lights
than I did uh before Holo
that's for sure
and you're part of the reason dakama
thank you
[Music]
same same
yeah
stop using money for yourself
[Music]
yeah they're so cute they're so fluffy
cute chicken
need more chicken more and more more
mama
even his food they're so cute huh
okay
don't say that though they're not
supposed to be food they're supposed to
be fluffy little hug pillows hmm
good verb
Good Burger
tender no no
it's a word to describe food no
no
love chicken I like chicken
I love live chicken
my birthday was the third but the Japan
schedule has made catching a stream live
of super jets enable difficult sorry
glad you're having fun but I can't wait
for a return to your normal schedule
here's another year uh of fun here at
Cafe are you here because this
is this I mean although today we started
a little bit earlier than usual are you
here
um where are you where are you Pony
collection
phony I saw him earlier oh really
okay I am happy to announce I am back to
the usual times
yay
sorry for the wait and oh my God it was
your birthday let's go birthday happy
birthday to you happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear Pony Claudia and
happy birthday to you
congratulations
[Music]
sorry I'm a bit late but thank you for
waiting for me and for the big support
that's a double red thank you oh my god
thank you soon
[Music]
did you get yourself something nice
maybe a croissant
turning ancient at 31
31 one well at least you're past the
30 you know the 30 must have been hard
right
for anyone it's like yep
I assume oh it's happening oh well oh
wow wow
I I imagine 48 30 and 40. 40 and 40 are
tough ones and at 50 you probably are
like just like whatever
[Laughter]
at 50 you reached acceptance
well like after maybe after 45
unless unless I mean unless you fall
into a midlife crisis when does that
happen at 40
age is just a number don't think about
it too much
yeah I mean if you can think like that
all power to you that's great
yeah
40s between 30 and 40. oh man
have you seen my hairline somewhere oh
no
don't worry look at this
I lost my hairline too and I still am
absolutely I was rocking it look how
beautiful I looked with bald head
so do not
give up do not fret
you can look like this
wouldn't you want to look like this
it grew back in like a week
maybe it's always maybe underneath I'm
always this otherwise
had hair length huh
every day how else could I change my
hair length
back and forth
United
I am bald and I'm proud
ah
so convenient it really is
okay where was I oh yeah thank you Pony
I hope you'll stay for a long time thank
you so much for the support glad you're
also here today let's have a a fun day
yeah go go go celebrate yourself some
more let's say your birthday is today as
Nana Chi's birthday stream title said
every day is someone's birthday
and I feel like every day can be your
birthday because every day there's a day
after you were birthed
so
yeah it's just you're you're a 31 plus
so and so now
it's also a birthday
celebrate the fact that you're still
alive let's go
wise words
oh don't credit them to me those those
credits go to ninity
14.
so where are you now Al huh because I'm
like at what 20 20 or 19. chapter 19 20.
better catch up Al
so
hurry hurry
[Music]
thanks for the pinky though
sanguini foreign
but after 3D showcasing
yo it was nice everyone together this
time
getting an equal amount of
uh Spotlight that was nice
um
thank you I hope you enjoyed the studio
Rob I hope it was worth it for you
hope you had a good time watching Yoki
Wawa
I did my best
to ride my best
thank you
[Music]
also foreign
thank you
thank you be faction anyway I'm glad you
are one of the cuaso supporters as it
should be
thank you sir
this is the fifth time I see this one
you must have asked that several times
right so I won't answer it now but thank
you Jeff stop or the pinkies
[Music]
no
processor
how do I say this
she Aaron Kieran thank you the IRL name
is also Kiara um beautiful name Kimmy pH
thank you soon
thank you for the there it is thank you
for the rest of the chat I've been
listening to your ghost recover with my
own repeat
I love it so much excited for when my
album copy arrives we have that one
apparently arrived really fast
also really Keen to see the new
hairstyle and I can't wait for this
weekend uh to see you perform on stage
as the wonderful Idol Kiara thank you
did it arrive
I think it arrived at everybody who
ordered it probably
thank you for ordering it I didn't even
like really
um advertise it that much and yet you
guys are getting it thank you I
appreciate it thank you soon
finally that I guess that's the first
first time my singing is on the physical
copy
on the physical CD
so
I guess that's special
um
I got my oven mitt yesterday oh finally
it's not that long yet
[Music]
you got my singing on cassette
Castro has the most lessons on Spotify
out of the covers you mean
really
what
in the album
in the cover hour
thank you
wow burps strong
damn thanks guys well I didn't expect
that I don't use Spotify so I don't keep
up with that stuff
hmm
Spotify
[Music]
wow
well I mean you know women's thing is so
beautiful she did such a great job
I feel like she's carrying it but I did
my best too
and I put a lot of emotion into it as
well
thank you thank you it's beautiful
supporting us
Ricky no nothing so the pinky I'm happy
with the new bold style to represent the
game of Ian
[Music]
oh that was not my new hairstyle it was
just the preview of something beautiful
I hope you like the real new hairstyle
too but bold is nice too
bald is so versatile
baldness is so versatile
your part was amazing thank you
you both did so great thank you
when will holbroads finally become an
official unit hmm
I don't know but I always push for it
hopefully at some point they will
recognize
how genius it is
because I feel like I've said I said
this again and again but I think uh
Whole30 has like a perfect balance for
this kind of stuff because I think all
of us are great singers like for real
there's like really good singers
everybody can sing decently but there's
some like even exceptional singers
in my opinion
um
for me the best ones are mermaid
but everybody sings really well in
horotoni and then the other thing is
that everybody's like except mummy but
let's just let's just say everybody is
uh you know very very good with
languages we all speak many languages
and we can communicate with each other
even though it's a unit consisting of
all branches
um
and everybody you know has like fun
personality everybody's very
communicative and and um yeah many many
energetic personalities
many interesting personalities
um
it's funny that like
two two of the very very very few
Japanese members who can speak decent
English are in horotori
that's
that's quite the coincidence
hmm
do no branchini
uh yeah so I will continue supporting
who would you guys say is the creator of
horotori
if you were asked who is the creator of
photo toy what would you say
this is me right
yeah
I don't wanna
I don't I was the first real burp anyway
wasn't I that's actually surprising why
was I the first one they already had so
many generations in whole life Japan
before me how come I asked the first
part because after
yeah it was made before Dana debuted but
like I
when when I I remember that when I
collab with Subaru senpai
I was like thinking of uh collab names
right and there were so many good ones
and then I settled with horotori
that was
that was the thing
that got it rolling
yeah but okay but if we do real talk I
was the first bird
but of course for promotional reasons
is also a bird
yes
and the first real bird which really now
thinking of it surprises me
because like now it feels like every
generation has a bird
almost every generation has a bird
it seems like
or something with a bird on their head
or with something that seems like a bird
now they can't stop spamming birds at me
um
new burp coming soon I hope not I don't
want another bird because I like The
Fountains of five five is such a good
number I want to stay at five
but like I feel bad like if there was a
new bird I
you know if I weren't to include them
it would be kind of like what the [\h__\h]
what what why not but five is so well
balanced if we keep on adding and we'll
be 10 eventually and then and then it
will be even more difficult to use them
as a unit because you don't you have to
use them all
um
birds of a feather flock together
it could burp
you must accept all the birds maybe we
can have a subunit then the upcoming
birds can have their own burp units they
can use one of those other like genius
names we came up with
um
and they can be Holo verbs I don't know
foreign
yeah but this I feel like we're complete
now it's so well balanced it's two en
members one ID and two Japan members I
it's it's so well balanced I don't think
it can like I feel like you know there's
such a thing as just uh as
first of all quality over quantity and
also just you know
the sometimes
less is more
right
hmm
yeah yeah yeah
but I will be in a as apparently as the
Creator that I am
I feel like I would be in a difficult
situation if they add another bird
I told
told jenma not like she's in charge but
I said please do not add any more birds
just because out of like organizational
issues
ah but then after that one you could
probably add LaPlace too
soil groups just call them sort of verbs
that's kind of a cool name
soil boobs
excuse me I asked for no more birds
no dinosaur does not [\h__\h] count
no no five is better than six no
there's a reason why most uh Generations
in whole life come as five
even though I often wish they were four
because most party games and so on you
can play with four people
there's a reason why they do five and
not six all the time it's just such a
balanced number
it's a good compact amount of people
it's not too much it's not too little
hmm
yes
accept it it's a fact
but I wish I wish I wish they were four
it makes it really difficult like uh in
the beginning when it was only myth when
I wanted to play like Mario Party or so
I was like well I can't
I can't because I invite four people and
then people are gonna be like why why
you don't invite the fifth one well
of
okay the game is for four and there's so
many games that work like that
so I I try to avoid those kind of games
most of the time
until there were more than five just so
that there wouldn't be like a oh why did
you not invite this person this person
and I mean I would personally also feel
kind of
if the other four would do a collab with
just without me
everybody but me I would feel like kind
of sad too
yeah we were limited definitely
to a certain pool of games
yeah Uno as well
smash as well
also for people pretty sure
yeah that's why garlic phone is good
yeah yeah anyway I think
uh
General Brown thanks for the red super
chat
didn't you hear red Super Chat are 99
off today
thanks for sparing me to go to Japan
it's been a blast so far going to energy
on Monday with lots of people oh
seen so much so far love your boss
you're the best gonna cheer my fro to
death this weekend watching you
yay that's so sweet I'm really surprised
so many of you guys went to Japan
even without a ticket
um
I hope you guys made good memories
yeah
it was so much fun
ah I can imagine that's really nice
happy for you guys
to be so close and make friends I want
kfp to make many friends and
I wanted to go for Kirby Cafe anyway
I was like uh you know when I I uh on
like one of the last days I was trying
to go to Kirby Cafe
but then I saw that oh my God it's so
difficult to get into Kirby Cafe what
the [\h__\h]
so I just looked up a other normal more
normal cafes and I found one that's
really really fancy and didn't need
reservations at least
no no no it's not about lines Kirby's
Cafe is like you have to
there is a certain time and day
per month or so where they update their
website and you can then make
reservations for the upcoming
month or two but once they open that
because everybody knows about the time
it is gone within like five minutes
ah it's per month you reserve for the
next month yeah but it's like gone
moving within the first couple of
minutes
so you should you should try to if you
ever tried it I've read that you should
try to go for like purposefully go for
an unpopular kind of day so weekday
and then an unpopular kind of time
whatever that is
um
yeah
demand way too high
yeah how the [\h__\h] did you go twice
motion
how the [\h__\h] how did you even know
um
maybe next time I try to get in
oh you tagged along with someone else
who was also smart enough to reserve huh
[\h__\h]
I feel senile
because he lost track of the topics oh
no oh no maybe just today you're a
little bit you know out of focus it's
okay it's okay you're not senile
Final Fantasy Cafe was amazing and
sometimes when I walked through
akihabala station
there's like this one path where you go
not really underground but you go
through a tunnel that has like really
small cafes in there and there was a
like a
small Final Fantasy Cafe that was so
empty
oh I think I think that was Final
Fantasy or no maybe not Final Fantasy
but like
uh octopus traveler or something like
that
yeah okay maybe maybe it was it was a
Rose Cafe
some Square Enix stuff and I was
surprised to always see it empty every
time I passed by
oh
maybe it was octopath whatever yeah
it was so empty it looks so nice though
like the the food
um
[Music]
the one by the station is octopath okay
then that's what I meant maybe if it was
Final Fantasy it would have been Fuller
um
surprised because I thought that would
do really well
did you ever go to the Tails of coffee
no
what
did I completely forget about that why
did you guys not remind me what
when was that
because you only remembered now
that was important
probably
um
what no I have to look it up tales of
Cafe Tokyo
oh
potatoes
coffee
20th 25th anniversary Cafe
hey this is August what
which what I can't
find this
level 2023
yeah what are you talking are you guys
gaslighting me that never happened
there's nothing recent I think
there is a tales of
Festival again
in June
yeah June
June
pretty early in June though I don't know
if I'll be in Japan already by that time
ah don't
call Festival Festival
[Music]
is it which menu I think previously it
was always Yokohama
Arena again damn
Arena
000.
miss it
uh yeah this one doesn't give a clear
information
has way
way
yeah
seventeen thousand can uh
please in Yokohama Arena please
yeah
I wonder if I can travel gold set now
I'll try
um
I'll try I don't know if they started
selling their Pro did they start selling
tickets yet
um
I don't know
but if I missed it I'm gonna try to get
it through my contacts
have to use them somehow sometimes huh
how many superstars did I read
are you waiting for yours to be red huh
[Music]
I'm doing this for you
of my day that it deserves you know
um
so I can watch on intercourse rapid this
time
I love you
one two three four five six questions
[Music]
thank you I love that so much
pinky very excited for your duet I
bought the digital version uh for holo
27 original cover thank you very much so
does that mean you're the one you're the
one who's listening on Spotify is it you
are you the one
who's helping it reach number one damn
thank you
thank you thank you soon for listening a
lot to it it's a really good version I
agree
it goes through
let's go
okay
good luck to you and everyone else at
the best this weekend kick ass out there
okay
mom man it's already like what has it
been
one and a half weeks or so already
or two
how long I don't know but damn
it's been a while
already ah and now we gotta wait so long
until the next thing
oh actually well actually
surely
en concert
[Music]
this time yeah we have something
that keeps us going
in between
yay
thank you sea bass for the big support
thank you soon and we have strategy also
little pinky totally love my sweet
summons thank you yes hello Tony lots
and lots of love for horotoli
Ryan Minecraft
candy yummy smile
hmm
my 1220 love
see you know what don't be sauce
oh
no no no no why sad why
so sad are you sad because ever since
ever since I finished Tales of arise and
I didn't get all the owls that why
you're still so sad
don't be so sad at least
damn
it's really that because of that no
on YouTube don't don't look at me like
that that face that said I'll face
[Music]
that it made me sad too
please be happy hoodle
happy
[Music]
and then at least collect mermaid
I feel like I already collected her
I put her into holotori after all
I want to see this frown turned upside
down soon please
sanctions
why not
foreign
[Music]
I guess gotta do both shaving and saving
yeah no I have to I have to walk walks
wax her yeah
thank you thank
you thank you Lord there's no message
here so can't say much but thank you for
the big support
[Music]
thank you for the uh Pink super sticker
well
it's a a gaming
what's that animal Gaming Animal
from
the wild
uniting with its chair and turning into
a big Mecca
got tie a hippo yeah
gaming
make a hippo
you couldn't it's right there
here
wow yeah that's what's happening
[Music]
soon for the pinky oh this is where it
shows up oh look at them going crazy
I mean especially these two
it's just a down bed
look at them
look at those chickens
[Applause]
thank you short cute short cute cute
cute
thank you I'm for sure when I'm
embarrassed
why you shall be proud
thank you making me sigh he
soon for the sweet words guys I am
watching
thank you soon counting chickens
thank you for the pinky
um
and bread that's all I'll say to that
thank you for the pinky
and bread and bread some bread I'm a
bread wee-wee bucket
Jacob 47 out thank you soon
[Music]
waffle
really come really
no what the hell
that's not the case at all I don't
dislike them at all
it's just my priorities will always be
to like collab within my company
but don't worry this week we already
have been out of company collab coming
up Friday
um
you might see it on their schedules
you can't expose me for anything I'm not
sure
what yeah that's what I meant for the
one on Friday
um five engage is canceled
it includes problems
and then I have another
fun collab coming up maybe already next
week
foreign
[Music]
for the pinky
oh no I'm in love I really love this
hairstyle thank you I wanted something
shorter but not too short a little bit
in between and girly and cute I'm glad
you like it thank you
Vietnam
cute new hairstyle and that's what the
cat ears and die right
is so perfect that the cat ears work or
dad oh my God
so many things work a bit
so glad they made that work
only though a little bit unreasonable
difficult things don't work but that's
okay
I can't hear sun hat yeah
yeah I wish they could just like add it
on every
uh
uh outfit or like more than just one
hmm
because why not
but I wonder I wonder how much I don't I
don't know how to do live 2D stuff so I
wonder if it's really that difficult
oh well oh well thank you ever
I've been using that hairstyle a lot
recently so I hope you are enjoying it
thank you soon for the support yay
for the pinkies oh now I can't scroll
down anymore so you might lose track
again
thank you thank you soon I think now you
get a kiss you know what I'll give you a
kiss because you said two pinkies you
get one come here I'll come here
um
I'll I'll eat you
wait
what the [\h__\h] why did I get
what did I get changed when I went undo
oh well ah
uh
[Music]
they spit you out
go back there go back into chat
hey
so big
here we go here we go
let her eat
is that we were on food yeah that's why
I spit you out
not you but uh
that's why
um
kind of like seeing the messages in
homelizer you want to read with me you
mean the whole messages too
oh
okay
I don't I can't promise I'll always stay
in the ones that are visible
oh
I can't scroll down anymore that's the
problem
um
that I read this one before that she
wait which one comes first
no the little one actually
something
you
all over that's
so bad
please touch High touch
for the pinky cute cute no you
no you don't know you
you're pretty cute too right Ghana thank
you soon for the pink Super Chat thanks
for the support
thank you soon
[Music]
for the pinky ponytail Bros we might
lost today but we still got killed as
hella yeah no
you want to see if the cotodies fall off
for science
that's not what you really want to see
huh they don't move
what was I saying oh yeah sorry no point
although this is kind of a ponytail
sideways kind not really though
um
eventually
I will eventually
eventually get you guys a ponytail don't
worry
a name for the other Kotori
um
did we I don't think I ever came up with
a name
one is maybe Kotori
and one is kotora Maybe
well I think that's the name of a
character of an anime I watched before
there was some anime
yeah you guys know it too
not Cortana because Richmond was [\h__\h]
he's the girl with the short
orange yellow haired hair
that was a also weird anime I think
mind reading the perfect friend ah
an old one
did I say hair hair and me colored hair
is
what about you
[Music]
hey
yeah thank you
Jones also sent a pinky thank you I
don't know what kfb did in the past life
to always be winning like this thank you
but you are definitely the cutest in the
world
no I can't be the cutest
I already know like off the top of my
head people that or or cats that are
cuter than me
specifically cats
so
I think you're exaggerating quite a bit
but thank you anyway
my cats are already killed there
people know
cassia people know
I guess it's a personal choice thank you
though that's sweet that I am in your
personal view the cutest that makes me
happy thank you thank you
[Music]
you're extremely cute way too cute it
should be illegal to be this cute I
don't think anyone can even come close
to the level of cuteness you're the
absolute cutest ever I'm dead
I think that was the cuteness overload
but since you have arrived hopefully
safely with your Phoenix
feather the one that I gave you
everyone's so damn bad yeah
take a shot every time a Super Chat
mentions cute
no I don't want you guys to turn into
alcoholics please no
thank you unknown 17 questions
[Music]
these are finished
next is
the
fourth okay these are quite a bit four
fast super chats
Hoy hoy
yeah
and these are very many
oh my God but in 15 minutes the thing
starts okay so uh in 15 minutes we'll do
it watch along and then we'll go back to
reading these
thank you for the rainbow
blue the Super Chat contains incoherent
screaming of an excited alpaca cheering
for it or she please ignore it for the
sake of your throat in future Super Chat
reading stream
okay I'm too late now thank you
yeah
that's so sweet
[Music]
and Martin eight thank you for the pinky
had to leave before the hairstyle was
revealed just wanted to say it looks
amazing by the way since you've
mentioned Magic the Gathering before did
you know they're actually making a
little ring set
no
looking forward to the perform to your
performance what
I didn't know that they're making it
it's not there yet they're making it
ooh
a set of cards comes right into moms oh
oh God that's cool
I don't know I don't I don't like
actively follow that stuff no
um
[Music]
oh yeah yeah I did hear about the movies
they're making a lot of drinks Diablo
game too excuse me what
what the [\h__\h]
suppose are out there are at least two
Sam Cuts yeah
yay
[Music]
Sam
oise County
thanks for the information damn that's
cool gotta get back into magic then W
thanks for the Super Chat thank you
Jacob 47 out action for the pinky
you the game of Korean thank you soon
thank you for the rest of the chat holy
that surely means Molly
Kiana I think I'm in love
wait we're too high that's blue
you did amazing you had an entire room
of over 60 people and that watch along
the job the one in Japan
was that so many people
you guys got about 16 people for an
offline watchable
or you mean in combination
of like
the ones you guys were
a Discord calling with
because it didn't look like 60 people
oh yeah
we're in combination right
even then that's Manny thank you the one
at azak Star was like 16. I hate chicken
is worth 10 people
East USA at 10. thank you guys I saw a
little video of you guys cheering thank
you very cute
I want so sweet
my cute chickens
I was very happy to see that makes it
more real and I know like most people
and that's just this is totally fine but
most people just watch this kind of
thing at home quietly
um but you guys go out of your way maybe
because you want me to see it
to like you know make little grips and
cheer with pen lights and all that and
record it so thank you for that
hey you're amazing you're an entrance
the whole audience I said to you also I
saw the wave oh yeah
I never got to do the wave again
Chihuahua hitting again with the wave
I can't believe
oops I need it again
I did the way
I'm
yeah maybe maybe I am
Not Innocent
tradition with quinoa yeah it's pretty
much a tradition I explained it to I
asked like before and can I do the wave
please because I always do that please
hope I can continue doing it
oh
did they did oh
I think they did a wave on day two too
right day two two
I think I saw them doing a wave on the
second day as well
um
but
but I think my wave was better
my way was better
no okay maybe it wasn't because it was
really funny yeah that code on it they
like waved they followed Corona said by
the horse
when she was Galloping all over the
stage
and that was pretty funny but at least
that was the wave opener
started away from event yeah
haha
nice thank you
[Music]
then Serbian popping up is this like
already oh it's already happening at
this point it's already happening
this is not waiting room or I mean it
was a waiting room but it's like already
like here it starts
typing thanks for the rights of attack
the kind of open room I was watching
from was dark so the people couldn't see
me cry
Charlie belong on them you truly belong
on the stage in a week full of
highlights going around Japan seeing you
put on so such an amazing performance is
the highest of fights Heist now until
the next toy
[Music]
Japan group in the karaoke room
python
okay good place to watch thank you
don't cry my sweet sweet chicken pie
they complimented you guys on your
cheering
thank you
I feel like it would have been crazy if
I sang something like black work shooter
you know there's so many things you
would want to sing in this kind of
situations make the most out of it but I
thought you know I I should I should say
my original song
but imagine if I would have done
BlackRock shooter I think that would
have been crazy emotional it's just you
know certain songs they hit you
differently
yeah
oh yeah yeah yeah you probably would
have made even me cry while singing
no no maybe not because I focus but
it's always the next year
but then again I would probably wanna
um
I would probably want to promote my
original song
a new one by that time hopefully
official cover
[Music]
I don't know if I'll ever do one
I think the live version was just fine
but
hoping it goes well with the live band
oh yeah okay well next time I'll
consider that because I this is the
second year in a row right didn't they
use a live band last year too
in that case
I will consider it and not choose the
one I want to perform the most but the
one that would fit the most
if they use the live band again
unless they can like promise me to or
like give me a preview of how how they
will arrange it that would be
ideal
I was told that wasn't possible but I
mean they have to rehearse somewhere
right
somewhere somehow at some point they
have to rehearse
how they're gonna perform all these
songs
so
I
what they do they could record it
I mean obviously this time it wasn't
recorded but next time they should just
record it they should have them recorded
hmm
but yeah they did like what 92 songs
like I understand you can't just like
make adjustments for everything
um
they must have like practiced really
hard and they did well with like
everything in general it's just my I'm a
personal like I have different
expectations but my God I wonder how
long my Pro uh Pro practice and how how
they come up with those arrangements do
they just like listen to the song and
then they start like jamming to it
or or I wonder how it works
um
it's just just Jam however they think is
suitable or
um
it's interesting
it's far beyond my understanding same
8-bit drama cell yeah like him
but then you have to you can't just like
individually be jamming out you have to
make it so that it fits with the other
people who are
instrumenting
93 songs holy [\h__\h] they had to learn all
of those they had to listen many times
to those songs to get like to know them
by heart when the drops happen stuff
like that damn so big respect
like really I don't want to
I don't wanna
like blame them it's just like oh
they're really good it's just like lack
of communication I guess
um
so I didn't know like how it would
actually sound
and okay
wait
um
now until the next time
for the pinky
you were amazing you were absolutely
glowing on stage loved every second
might have teared up once or twice I
wish I could have been cheering in
person but I get more chances later you
worked so hard and I can't help support
my Aussie
I appreciate it thank you Sharon I'm
glad you could enjoy it so much and be
proud of your own scene thank you for
supporting me
all the time oh thank you no thank you
no thank you
no thank you no thank you
thank you thank you soon
please continue supporting Wawa
be very happy
thank you
and marching eight thanks for the pinky
great job thank you lots of Horror Story
today with you and Louis and then you
next episode at the end connect finally
reveal to be what everyone expected and
since it's not a lottery maybe I can
actually get a ticket since I can't seem
to win those ah very unlucky with
lotteries huh
well
in this case you have to be really fast
or like maybe not fast but just like
hope that
this one's also kind of a luck thing
it's from experience from what I hear is
that you know those servers are just
like crashing
um
just be be ready in any case be ready
maybe have
two PCS or so
I wish you all lots of luck guys
I feel like you know from
experience with like doing for example
garlic phone or Mario Kart where you
have to put a code in
um because just because
of how Japanese people normally don't
type in alphabet
um from what I've seen it's like they
are very unlikely to get into these
things when they have to type it out and
they're against like kaigai nikkis
so I feel like
when it's like a something like that
like an English website with stuff that
you have to type in I don't know how it
works but I feel like they have even
less chances
you know what I mean
to if it's like time based to catch up
yeah
because they in the garden phone and so
on
I always see my Japanese Bros were
struggling
to get in because they're always too
slow and the en Bros always made it in
fast super fast
yeah entering games
um
that's how I feel with Japan stuff 100
yeah yeah the other way around you guys
also face challenges so hmm
hmm for it so because of that I feel
like Lottery would be more fair or it
just is more fair
because so many things can go wrong if
it's by time
okay let's ah
um
let's watch the Nintendo thing it's live
on their Channel if you guys are
watching the board then I don't know
maybe skip the 15 minutes
um
link
tears of Kingdom I'm not gonna mirror
anything because I can't
um There's the link I only see when I
Google it on YouTube
and all I see is
what a bit other videos
I can't find yeah I can't find any of
them I see the one on Nintendo Germany I
think
oh no no no wait are they just not live
I
think what is this ah
drop it oh
uh uh wait uh is it just a trap like a
box
Nintendo uh America or so I don't know
Nintendo of America
you don't see it I think I no I don't
see it
there it is where is it
okay I see it I oh it's it's just a
video not a live stream okay do you want
to watch it together
here's the link
I'll pin it
okay okay okay okay okay
well if it's not a streamed and I feel
like both watches can
line up with us too
let me just write something down
[\h__\h] is this
it's old
quickly
watching along the
uh Zelda video thing
I guess
do do
what are these fonts
ah
oh that one looks nice
oh my God my screen everything's blood
okay perfect
hi and music could stop food
all right are you guys ready
[Music]
on your mark ready on go okay on go
okay
ready
Set Go
click
hello
hi
[Music]
complete the honey
no delay
oh a little bit not like I really care I
don't care
what
he's gonna play the game
horse
I gotta watch this later in HD
but it's just an automatic
let me switch it now
hmm
my sofa just looks like breath of the
Wild
oh
um
fly
mm-hmm how convenient
oh
everyone
it's like that game that I played
oh
[Music]
yeah it's representer
game
clothes
oh dragon
hmm
all the sounds are so nice
and like the foot sounds and the I don't
know jumping sounds pick up sounds
I like this one it looks funny
cute
zonai
oh what's that a temple
looks like a temple up on the right
oi go there
but
what
so much smaller though
swinging it like a cotton ball
oon
hmm
what okay
uh can you fuse anything
why would
yeah that makes more sense
but wasn't that already freezing arrows
wasn't that already a thing and
previously
but you had to get actually like ice
arrows or so
um
skill issue
I will need a lot of those eyeballs
aha
my God I will be farming those
yeah like a missile
what
eh
oh
[Music]
I mean
the water looks nice the reflections
laughs
Ultra hand
oh
I see the slime in the gooey
or you can place it how you want
one's turning into Minecraft you could
make like huge structures if you wanted
to if you're bored as [\h__\h]
I'll come back we're like watching the
video right now I'll be back soon
it's a Beyblade oh no it's a ventilator
man
but there's batteries on it
I load back up when you turn it off
[Music]
he's making a speed boat
oh
I'll be a genius and I'll turn it the
wrong way but okay
[Music]
I can't believe it
will this disappear when you go too far
or when you like reload your game
Ah that's how those are made
all of them are self-made
it's a crafting game now
what
hmm
or ah
no way
[Music]
oh
hmm
[Music]
that is broken
okay wait did it also make its own
don't Smack me don't Smack me it's like
a flag
what
can I make a la chancla
rip
quickly
ah there we go
that's a that's quicker
that River looks pretty
not so deep
I feel like that would have hurt him
hmm
thanks for showing us some gameplay
oh
yeah that's really cool
that's really cool
oh
what oh
cool
that switch
oh
[Music]
I love the golden White
oof
but I will never buy any of these new
Switch designs when I already have a
switch
but it's an OLED
I don't have an OLED
well did it say pre-order
for that stuff
[Music]
I have an old one and then all that yeah
yeah and all that maybe
that stuff looked good
I wonder if I can get one or do they
sell out really quickly how does it work
I never tried
oh
a little Twilight Princess
ah
they do but they restock blood pretty
good
um
but again I
feel like it's a waste to buy a second
one I'm always like this like yeah I
wait so long until things are completely
worn out or useless
uh
which is I think how it should be we
live in a society that has become so
wasteful and you know
fast fashion
Etc is insane
so you know I really shouldn't uh to be
honest because it's not like the OLED
will help me because I always play for
my PC screen
yeah
am I doing it maybe the controller
though I mean
the control or maybe
I mean I already have a pro control I
have a I have two
controllers but
Maybe
social critic
off collab bragging rights oh no I don't
care about that either
[Music]
but for the game
I mean I guess it's like cool additions
but I care less about that I want to
know about the story I think that is
understandable
I mean they added like such
um
crafty functions
I feel like
it will be fun
but I don't know
we'll see
um
I wonder if it's just beat Ganon again
ah I doubt it
I don't think so
I will fill all those diffusing and
gluing so much I'm actually gonna hype
now I wonder though if it's like always
necessary and if you will ever be like
frustrated about it
if it ever becomes an issue if they
force you to always do stuff with that
or if you could just completely ignore
that factor and play it like breath of
the wild just without that function
completely
for the people who just don't wanna like
blah experiment with all of that
um
and it just makes everything easier
and if you don't want it then it just
stays the way it was
I mean some some things like the the
making the boat and making like a car
and whatever I think it's really cool
but some of the weapon combinations
are stupid in my opinion like the the
overall things I think are awesome
combining those things makes sense to me
more or less yeah they do but like the
the the the like sticks with us or the
stone with a sword well no the stone of
a stick it's like when you get really
really desperate and you have no nothing
else okay
I guess but it's like I don't know those
those seem a little bit ridiculous to me
but I like the combinations for arrows
like the ice one makes sense I don't
know what the
um the one with the Croc Leaf would make
don't make fun of stone age people
[Music]
and like even in that size it makes no
sense
don't look be too heavy for stick
maybe late game they'll be worthless
yeah I wonder early game helpful and you
might want to play around a lot with
that because you don't find good weapons
Maybe
how good are they gonna be for real
though hmm
yeah the attaching tool is kind of weird
but it's kind of a dorky thing to add in
my opinion
so I'm kind of like half off some of the
crafting I think is cool
like the boat Etc
but then also like overwhelming because
then I wonder oh if I if I spend 20 more
minutes on Crafting something
Maybe
I have to spend 20 more minutes on
Crafting something and you know
you know how I am with crafting mode oh
this is still like an acceptable amount
of crafting
hmm
yeah and then you leave it behind but
you know I wonder if it's like really
necessary
must be hard to think of new gimmicks
what
the mix and I don't think like yeah
I don't think it was like
unless well the fact is that they kept
the graphics and everything the same
right so if they're not gonna improve
the graphics which they were totally
fine of course but if they're gonna make
a second part of the game and not
improve the graphics or anything like
that then okay where else can we improve
and then I guess it went to that
they had to add something new
[Music]
yeah they did make it the major Point
hmm I'll see how I like it in action
when I actually use it
ah
oh weapon weapons breaking up the one
yeah they broke pretty quickly right
like at least the weaker weapons I don't
know I don't remember
this way you can quickly come up with
new weapons
okay I think I'll quickly go to the idol
meeting and then I'll be back and
re-read some Super Chat speed reading
BRB
foreign
[Music]
okay okay it's half past four
I think
I'll tell my brother to tell me when
he's on his way back so that I know
maybe we can do longer
smack me Evan
um
okay hi
and I want to eat a bowling Stone
I'm genius I have balisto
this is what cookery sounds like
exactly like me what
bamboozle wasn't Kotori
um
[Music]
mm-hmm
thanks for membership
and Joanna Jones in my head for some
reason
[Music]
why
is one of my recommendations after that
video
a Tetris 99.
42nd Maximus Cup gameplay trailer video
but there's Fire Emblem Ali are on the
thumbnail
does Tetris have a fire emblem
collaboration
hmm
oh
so basically
huh yummy
it's just like a skin just pictures in
the background and the tetris block so
I'm
the weapon style so
um fighting style of Fire Emblem
but it's really not that much special to
it
and I guess you get Fire Emblem music in
the background
[Laughter]
okay okay okay
back to
Super Chat people people where was I'm
where was I
where did I stop
um remember do you remember
which one why did I stop
that
you'll meet
Martin
okay thank you
beautiful Gore forget oh
Martin Martin this one
yeah okay okay thank you check his
monkey thank you for two Pinky pinkies I
was saving up for a joke super chat but
your performance is broke me like a twig
I felt so proud to have you as my number
one orange when he really
because of it
I was so proud to have you as my number
one or she watching your singing and
dancing on stage solo with your gen
mates and with your senpas you were
dazzling up there and when you did the
little solo dance section during the
holy and collapse song it really made me
think yes she's truly the dancer of
Halloween she's our Idol our Oshi
takanasikiana thank you for all the work
you put in Kiara
thank you thank you sir that's so sweet
and I'm liking a joke is that a dad joke
could you consider that a dad joke how
do you know if something is a dad joke
dazzling has been underused as a
compliment remembering that for later oh
copying
when it makes you go face palm yeah
that's I don't like can't really go by
that because many dad jokes the way you
guys say it's a dad joke I I do not face
palm
I laugh but I guess
I think this is not a dad joke this is
too good to be a dad joke
did anyone face palm hearing that from
Jacob's monkey
does that make me a dad
oh because I'm enjoying them yeah but I
mean
I mean
it went over my head what but at least
you didn't face palm no no no it was
okay not for this one all right this is
a certified normal joke
thank you for all the sweet words
Jacob's monkey yum
and
I'll continue doing my best with dancing
and all that
I don't think I I can be the dancer of
Ian anymore but I am a dancer and that's
okay
[Music]
um
thank you very much for supporting me
and believing in me
[Music]
oh
no thank you guys no but for real she's
she's better it's really so I know you
guys want a competition another
competitional comparison
dance off but that would just be
embarrassing for me
I cannot keep up with her I think
judging by what I saw
too old
I'm too old
um
oh well biggest monkey
nah
it's okay though I so I would like to
you know I told her hope we can dance
together someday something some that
song that is dance heavy I hope we can
like perform something together one day
hmm
as
[Music]
so proud of utensil really happy that I
can call you my horsey and you were
singing together with your senpais you
rock the stage today same way as you did
last year and that wink at the end of do
you totally killed me wow my OC wow is
the best oh well actually
well actually thank you first of all
actually you know
I wanted to wink a lot because do you is
so Kpop heavy and I don't know if you
guys ever noticed you might only notice
if you watch a lot of Kpop music videos
or performance videos but they do be
winking a lot they love winking they
wink like in so much like every time
when they do a live performance
like let's say it's a six Mambo group or
so
um every time somebody is like on close
up because they always know which camera
is on them they always know but when
they see their camera on them and they
have like a part where they sing
they like it feels like they implement
a wink into every single line that they
think
they're so wink addicted
they are winking so much
yeah
they're flexing their winking skills
they I must say I feel like they're kind
of overusing it but it is cute when they
wink
it's cute but it's just too much when
everybody tries to do it in every
close-up and then you have them
constantly winking and you wonder do
they have something in their eye
problems
hmm
too much winking but you know because I
kind of felt like you know this is kind
of like how your Expressions should be
for Kpop style it's not like I can
really have that many expressions like
my face is kind of stiff and 3D
um but I I said I want to wink
at many many times because of that
that's the lore behind it
yeah
not as much as they did but
quite a lot
um
I wish I could you know one more thing
that K-pop does is like they do so many
hair flips
so so many hair flips
Swiss swoosh with their with their hands
or just by flipping their head but a lot
of the time they like go with their hand
through their hair and just like you
know make it flow back and I wish I
could do that I wish I wish I could make
my hair and 3D move that much it has
some Physics but not that many also
because my hair is on the shorter side
compared to other members
so it doesn't like moves that much
yeah new jeans they literally
implemented it into the choreography
hahaha
the attention
I wish I wish I wish stuff like that
would work but it doesn't but I feel
like if they were if there was more
physics to like realistic physics to her
hair of course it would look weird
because
that doesn't really suit an anime model
like that I suppose
in terms of Aesthetics
but
but that way everything could look even
more
like Dynamic you know
imagine Anya with real hair physics my
God I'm not like my God her hair is so
big and so it looks very fluffy but also
very Tangled
[Laughter]
I think like with Anya you know because
she has a very
um what's the word
the very
[Music]
special what's the word
special art style like her eyes
especially I I was wondering is that
really gonna translate well to
pretty isn't that gonna look kind of a
distinct yeah I just think that's what I
was looking for I was thinking that
might look kind of
uncanny
but
I didn't feel that at all when she was
moving and reading it
I actually thought it was really cute
hmm
[Music]
her eyes didn't feel weird to me in 3d
nothing of about her felt weird to me
already
uh surprise to me
um
looks even more huggable and pretty
looks great and pretty yeah she's cute
and and I like that she chose uh pants
the ID I idle costumes are really cute
um and I like the pants version
I like the pegs version and all three of
them the Japanese one the ID and the en
one but I really like the pants on Anya
because she's so small and and the pants
make her look a little bit tomboyish and
sporty and it's really cute
changes a lot depending on the image
color added to it um
I don't know it's just generally they
chose very pastel base colors for the
costume
so they all except for like Elena
because she has like a darker blue
most of them look just very pastely to
Me overall
pastel is very strong in their outfits
it's very refreshing
yeah oh if you want to get nihongo Jose
by Osaka people say my doll as a
greeting Mido middle and say okini as a
thank you
if you didn't already try
and and another example instead of
saying for example
something something
or
yaranai just replace the knives with hen
and then you get very very osakaishaish
because for example is not doing it but
hen instead of Nai is the the Osaka band
version of it so for example
this store is not open today
[Music]
teaching language
you will sound very like natural
what stream Super Test are we reading oh
oh I didn't put up the thumbnail oopsie
uh we are reading ah the um after talk
of day one
let me put the thumbnail up now sorry
I'll put it here
you know that you're welcome
oh okay where was I
think uh here uh thank you RS
a cafe onions
we love you I love you we love you I
don't have words again you left me
speechless we are so proud to be careful
so proud to have you as our Aussie I
know Vala is so cute and your
performance was [\h__\h] amazing
I wish
I could just perform my whole concert
there
if only
well generally write this down thank you
you're welcome
[Music]
you own the stage thank you thank you
thank you
thank you bro bro
you want it alone or did you watch it in
the group
um since you were in Germany right so
maybe you could you were only watching
it alone but still I'm sure in your
heart you cheered for me just as loud
thank you so much
for the support I appreciate it very
much
you guys leave me speechless too
I watch it with my sister thank you wow
I am
[Music]
for the recipe chat you're amazing it's
not the first time of your 3D
performance but still left me speechless
and teary-eyed with your singing and
dancing I'll be re-watching the Vlog for
your performance repeatedly
well it's only up for a mom oh ah
reminder to myself to remind Le Idol
that I performed one of her old songs
I should
ah
should I
how many can you guys tell me how much
time is left
does someone know for real
more exact
I don't want to be like annoying you
know
no how much time for the VOD
of the concert
21 days
that's still plenty isn't it
still a lot
yeah I should I should remind her like
one week before
Maybe
can you guys remind me to remind her
yeah I feel like it's too pushy if I
remind her now like hey there's only
only 21 days left to watch it
that feels too pushy
thank you thank you
well thank you very much CD you also
still have plenty of time to re-watch it
endlessly and they even extended it a
little bit so
yeah enjoy it while you can and then
hopefully eventually we get Bluer but at
least this time I feel like you have a
Pinot sorry uh the quality was really
suffering from the fire and all the
graphics you know but this time I I
don't think it was the case was it it
didn't bother me at least it wasn't too
noticeable for me
quality looks better to me the bit braid
actually overall throughout the whole
concert I don't think I noticed any
bitrate issues
um
[Music]
a little like this one only at the very
beginning dance move oh
this
is what did they fix the photo mistake
already
because yeah on day one they they
uploaded photos from from day one
and they were missing only my photo
I'm not mad with all
but they were missing only my photos
they sent me though like a whole
folder of professional photos
it was uploaded but not embedded oh
oh they fixed it the next day that day
because I told them thanks to you guys
telling me
hmm
sounds good Air Salt mate are you
allowed to share yeah I am I was
thinking maybe I'd upload them as
Members Only
all of them
and then let's see which one is now on
the website uh Polo Fest
what store how do I
um live
what's it how do I
do I get there uh
bright Parade day one
website
where did I send it to my manager
I sent it here
I yeah
here I'll send you guys a link to
oh now I can get rid of the other one
so where's my photo
which was mine
mine don't go
[Music]
um
what is it this one
oh
oh mine's really far can't see me well
but all the graphics in the background
look cool
and mine style I mean depends I guess on
what kind of screen you're looking at it
but I am wait I lost track where was I
ah second bro
second from the left if you have like a
bigger screen I guess I'm next to the
Louisville one
Roblox
on the right side next to me I'm the one
two three four five six seven eight
picture
eight yeah with orange light sticks but
I'm not the only one with orange like
this
one of them
can't right click save it unfortunately
so I can't show it right now
a picture for ants yeah
I didn't see a bit on the screen you
know
problem we wouldn't have that if we used
my idea of making me much much much much
much much much much much bigger on the
middle screen
then we wouldn't have this issue of
trying to see where I am in the preview
either
we would see it so clearly
I still agree with the idea even if it
was a joke thank you I mean
I mean think like
some aspects of it is a fun idea maybe
for like a one-time gimmick right
it could be fun it could be interesting
maybe not for every concert but it's
it's I think it is
um a strong point that we have that we
can make use of that others can't
hmm
anyway
thank you
for the pinky
my eyes in my tent so I'm so proud of
you you're the best fantastic
performances today forgive my
encouraging and casting and the pile of
super chats will throw at you while you
were trying still trying to catch up
you're dancing there and do you and the
group song was killer so much legs and
hips you are right it looks so much more
interesting in the eye of it right with
that lovely skirt that dance solo too oh
my God and the wink I'm gonna need that
Revival early I love you thank you
I know like I'm so good the dancing
looks so good with the
matching outfits like especially because
um in a group now that where we can all
be matching it looked kind of weird with
in the decor stage with mume and me next
to each other and she has this big
outfit and I which is fantasy themes and
mine is like this really short skirt
skimpy
fast food outfit
well that's weird now we can have
matching outfits yeah
hey
it will be skimpy it will be kind of
skimpy
be real
um
and they flow so nicely so I'm happy I
will use it at many many occasions if I
can
um
I like it very much thank you Navidad
you seem like you're just overflowing
with love for me these days these days
am I right or am I right
hey
thank you Mundo thank you
you are absolutely amazing your choice
was great for Ian and do you was so
perfect it was so much fun to watch with
other KFC oh yeah yeah what part of the
group we all shared loudly in the
morning for you oh yeah early morning
how early was it for you guys I didn't
think of that did you guys do a
sleepover and then wake up together
is that how you did it
5 a.m or did you guys stay up
did you guys sleep or stay up
oh my God
you slept okay so who
who had to wake up the others was there
somebody who just wouldn't get up was
like this is a no five more minutes
I need to know the off collab lure from
my chickens
I woke up I woke up
we're also hyped
did nobody have issues for waking up
oh Taco spice left through day two what
well that's not a chicken the hype woke
you up
six to seven A.M
we got some coffee right after nice nice
also I saw a message from my brother by
the way he is really
um either starting to go on his way at 5
PM or arriving at 5 PM so let's try and
hurry a little bit oh my God
where was I did I read this all you've
accomplished so much and I'm happy to
call in my own C thank you so much moon
dog
it's so so salty to watch you guys being
titty it makes me really happy thank you
thank you soon and I'm glad you like
sukijan you know I think uh man most
people didn't know the song but it's
such a hype hype pie pipe song for
concerts
um
so thank you for appreciating it
um super stick Mario donation for the
pinky I'm so proud of you Kiana you
killed it out there on stage doing was
amazing you're dancing and singing are
always stopped here I also really
enjoyed the Ian performance as well I'm
looking forward to seeing you in Mumbai
on stage tomorrow I love you thank you I
love you too wow thank you for
supporting me throughout that weekend
thank you
I hope you cook
many many many
screenshots for personal enjoyment
thank you thank you soon I don't know
what to say anymore because this is the
point where I get like
just thank you thank you guys because
you all got you guys also say the same
things
you say the same things to me so I can
only say the same things back
but thank you so much
[Music]
soon
thank you guys
it's a loop of Love yeah
I'm so happy for you first was what made
me realize that you mayoshi oh really it
took you that long
and this time definitely did not
disappoint either thank you for being so
amazing
[Music]
Queen
actually moving around in 3D made you
realize
I mean
that's understandable but so
thank you doll now you can never go back
I will forever be yours
Ultimo MK to offering for the rest of
the chat I still can't process properly
process just how amazing your
performance was you've proven yourself
again as a dancer of Polo Ian the stage
is truly where you shine the brightness
and I'm so happy that you get got so
many opportunities to show off your
talents yeah this time I'm really glad
to yeah both in the big big group songs
and a smaller group song and in the solo
so it's really really really
nice
of her life to give everybody all the
members a chance to do a solo song
I wonder if I hope not but I wonder if
one day they will
um not be able to do that
if we get more and more and more people
I hope not yeah
yeah you've seen like not everybody got
to doing them scene but I think they
definitely try to get as many en and ID
members as possible to give them the
chance
there was definitely
lots of overseas members doing MCS this
time
that's very nice I think we deserve it
for not having that opportunity until
now so I'm very very grateful that we
got to do that
everyone admit for an emcee
I don't think I'm still an emcee
okay am I
completely forgetting it but I was only
ah ah yeah yeah okay
um
did Ina do one
yeah maybe didn't
write
what she did with your feet
did I do one
I'm not the only one who didn't remember
right away
dip
huh
[Laughter]
[Music]
I don't remember that one at all
what I forgot that one the one with I
mean only I remember now
the inner one
I don't remember at all
I'm very confused now did I do one
was I even there
was I at four Fest
who am I am I a part of myth
what what is my name
Salah Gutenberg
anyway thank you so much
[Music]
yeah then I can't be here now okay okay
sorry why did I think I was Kiara what
the hell miss this
instructions
thank you so much and don't worry it's
okay hope you enjoyed dokumi very much
[Music]
um
I'll cut you for a rainbow thank you
thank you thank you no words though
wordless super trip well
with Chad
[Music]
you know Anka
I have to think of Paul Anka the um
Gilmore Girls they named their dog Paul
Anka
thank you for your big support it's a
beautiful rainbow thank you soon so many
colors wow
the foreign
[Music]
my tears too many I can't see no
wipe your eyes you have to see you have
to look
it's precious you spend so much money on
it
you have to watch oh
ah beautiful rainbow and the chickens
get more and more and more and more
they're so cute it's a chicken pyramid
or chicken stairs I guess
chicken slide
against building a slide for me and I
slide down
nice
rotary status
hopefully he takes his time
take your goddamn time he's asking me
how is it
what
don't don't come yet I need to make
progress
Kevin oh he's already there
person
please
that give me 15 minutes
you really are at your brightest when
you're on stage a true Idol your
performance really got the blood pumping
the dance moves were amazing also that
wink at the end should have been illegal
my heart almost stopped
sorry oh my God you should be used to it
maybe I should wink more in my streams
ahead
to get you guys used to Market wings
okay no
[Music]
he's not cold freezing it's pretty warm
again
it's not freezing temperatures don't
worry
simply thank you so much feel free to
send me your hospital bill in case your
heart stops Again by my own actions
thank you
fantastic performances
I'm in two separate days you ride the
stage with Doyle and it was a blast to
see you and Ian on the stage together
Sing Sing see you
see you in your element at full power
was amazing so practical in my office
but now that you say it you really want
to make me wanna look back on the
on the
performance I want to watch that again
it was so cute
thank you so much Jim Tracy thank you I
am proud to have you as my Champion
um
however I should say it function for the
rest of the chat sending my annual Super
Chat thanks for the amazing performance
you were the most stylish and radiant on
the stage oh come on what
I'm still lurking after these last two
years and I'll keep looking forward to
what you have coming next signing up
from the kfp East Coast you're a lurker
but you went to the KFC East Coast
Meetup
I thought all the locals are like also
holding back for from stuff like that
nice glad you made it go there
[Music]
public lurk
never underestimate looking power
and they're class less lurking please
more gherkings less lurking more cooking
cucumbers
no no I don't I wouldn't say they're
anti-social but I just thought that you
just don't end up having the I don't
know
cold outside no way
really
enter the building
they sent me freezing emoji
yeah he said it's really really cold
again
sure that was worse
should be hardened against this kind of
stuff
let him in no
no
thank you favorite
you're always welcome to uh look less
yes yes
and thank you for letting me know of
your existence once again it's nice to
hear because some people they just
disappear without saying anything but
now I know you're still here thank you
very much
day one thanks for the pinky
thank you so much oh my brother's
stressing me out I should just turn off
my phone
it was showing us the great performance
in the fourth first day one I was able
to feel more moved and thrilled than
last year I cheered from afar same last
as last year but I really put my heart
into it I really love you and thank you
my best
oh I hope you get a chance
maybe at some point to watch a concert
in real life that would be nice in
person not through streaming services I
wish you all the best and good luck for
that because all you need is luck all
you need is luck
that's how that song goes right
it doesn't flow so well something must
be wrong
thank you
guys stop
he'll be fine come on just seven more
minutes
for the red and the pinky
they wanted to come that was great do
you rock Edition was a lot of fun when
the guitar and drums kicked in
oh yeah it really felt like a rock
version and you turn and the link at the
end was high-stoppingly cute thank you
your new casual hair looks amazing too
the glasses and pins are great
accessories they're so cute I would have
sent this earlier but I had to leave
halfway through your one hour long
tangent reveal stream
oh yeah
dude I'm not gonna reveal it in the
beginning but I also didn't reveal it
after an hour did I
so much
so much for the support and the sweet
words glad you like the new hairstyle
too thank you
[Music]
oh guys you're so dramatic
you know how to build suspense yes
I know I know
your performance is awesome like the
last group song after it's finished you
spin your arm and then point to the
front really cute and stunning you wrap
the stage on bamboo for your whole 27
show why in German it's even much horror
ah yeah yeah right right
so what's this meme where you say things
like this um
in in English you say uh
what was it
break a leg Yeah but in German we say
and I think that's beautiful
because we make you break basically your
whole body instead of just
like
but this is meme worm uh I think some in
videos they will say but enchantment or
some other language we say
but it then means something completely
different and they're just like
um making some [\h__\h] up
that really doesn't mean
anything close to what they said before
that's the funny part about it but I
think it's funny how in German
we don't wish you to only break your leg
we wish you to break your neck as well
which you might as well die
um
so aggressive man I guess German is an
aggressive language after all
I guess I'll die
so intense yeah I may try to get LA
tickets even the flight price is kind of
insane
see make sure to check
um I don't know which website you guys
look at but
um
make sure guys to check
several sites maybe you'll find cheaper
flights you know
and I think like this time even if you
book a flight to
L.A and then end up not getting a ticket
though
there's something else fun apparently on
that weekend going on that you can go to
instead
and then have a fun dance party I'm sure
there will be plenty of hollow Ian fans
in La who would be open for a watch
party
I'm sure there is plenty
that can't get into the concert Holden
all right
um
I'll fight to my life for like 40
dollars damn lucky 30. wow
uh okay I'll read one more Islamic
fellow
thank you for the rest of the chat your
incredible reckon it's danger do you I
love your performance and then the MC
bits officially yeah they were getting
crowded wave
wow wave the Wawa wave
we should write that together
finishing it with yet another great
performance with Anna Ina mummy
[Music]
happy with our unit these are all girls
that I love so so much
as I said before that I would have liked
to see different combinations too but I
really love our combination as well
made me really happy to see us paired up
so I could I could just forget about the
other pairings that I would have liked
to see because this one is also
marvelous
um
[Music]
for the big super chat okay
um
we will stop here
spicy chicken butt
there's a little bit more
and it only gets redder and Pinker it
feels like
I have read like half though because the
scroll bar
scroll bar yeah and look look yeah yeah
yeah yeah this thing it was like half of
that
so not much progress uh yeah I'll go
make some furniture now
um yeah
yeah a little bit of progress
and these are all big super chats so
I have to read many many
yeah we'll do our best now to assemble
some furniture and then tomorrow I will
play
Metroid Prime so I'll see you guys there
all right
good night everybody or good day and in
German we say
no
bye bye I'm gonna rescue my brother now
that drama queen
[Music]
thank you