[Music]
okay
one of my japanese friends is like oh
yeah haha in japanese we say o pekipe
and then later she was like nah i was
just [\h__\h] with you no one says that
anymore
so i guess i guess i got tricked never
heard that before
yeah yeah yeah i wouldn't be surprised
if a lot of other people haven't heard
of that before
hi guys are you purposefully still on
the loading screen no
yes well yeah i wasn't but now now we're
not now we're good to go
now we're ready to park now
hi oh hey i think
i think one layer in obs is uh
behind me oh no oh no you've gotten
you're rending yourself oh man it's
transparent and see-through
yes it sure is here let me change the
bounds of space and time
there we go hold on yo so many cups
all for me one two three four
five and tiny ass macarons those are
tiny
they're pretty small they're definitely
on the small side
yeah but definitely very tasty who's so
cute
yeah how is it what a cozy room oh my
god pretty cozy i would say
how's the uh how's the volume everyone
is that all right
[Music]
a bit loud volume
half of my possible uh
uh kano
what is the can't speak english it's
gonna be problematic today
that's okay no worries i mean doesn't
it's not something that your character
has
in common i mean i wouldn't say that i
mean i completely understand what you
say all the time but
thank you but uh maybe i don't know it
will become a fun character thing as
well
yeah i was gonna say potentially my half
of my potential yeah yeah no my
character does have a little bit
like she is trilingual but
it does have a little bit of a
communication
problem i mean i'm not not not trialing
multilingual is the skill uh the merit i
gave her yeah yeah
yes i think ina also gave herself that
one
still i'm still quiet it looked like i
was peeking a bit but if you guys say so
i'll
up the volume a bit hello hello check
one zoo hey hey
how's this let me know guys and we can
go ahead and get started
i could do howdy home ee already in
character i see you'd be correct
let's see better better now this is good
you're gonna you're gonna start learning
uh kiara that it's you're gonna
come to a point where you're like um
what is in character and what is not in
character you shall see
and speaking of which how about we go
ahead and show i'm gonna go ahead and
show
your character sheet to everyone that's
very large okay
all right i i added uh one
flaw and one merit since last time
you guys saw this sheet i added uh
curiosity with two floor points
therefore i added loaded for bear with
two floor points
nice nice nice wait wait no wait i have
to i haven't already oopsie oh my god
oh oopsies [\h__\h] oh everyone's already
had that one
oh i guess so gosh i didn't know what
i'm just gonna add and another one
married instead of that sure go ahead we
got some time yeah
do you have to do something do you have
to do some explaining or something
sure i mean i can basically explain how
it's going to work to everyone
so basically um for this stream
we're just going to be introducing
kiara's character tiara into the world
of darkness and basically it's like a
prologue a little prologue story for her
um and we will be kind of
role playing it out and learning how to
roll dice
and going through all of that i wouldn't
i wouldn't say painstakingly slowly but
we are going to try and learn from
experience you guys
um i got one i got one all right what's
the merit
direction sense i'm gonna quickly
edit that and then i'll send you the
updated version
alrighty sounds good and i just have
that for my reference
do you just have all of the
merits and [\h__\h] in your brain all the
time now i pretty much have to look them
up in the side but um
i also kind of it would be great if if
you guys
learned the merits as well and i will
also learn all of your individual merits
so
it saves us some with time we will all
know our own merits by heart
yes and uh little known fact you can
earn
experience in this game experience
points exp
okay we'll go over that at the end um
once you have played through the
tutorial
another thing to note um is that um
guys uh i'm not a huge stickler for the
rules
um but basically
essentially i may change some things
from the traditional world of darkness
so that things are a little easier to
understand
um especially for like the combat system
um i don't do anything too
in depth and integrated i like for it to
be a basic combat system with
a lot of role play um so yeah i think
uh the golden rule here is that there
are no rules
um but there there kind of are there's
enough there are enough rules to keep
the game
within a certain bound but not enough to
detract from the fun
um or make things so painstakingly
detailed that they stop being fun
that that's when it's the worst is when
is when we're like wait how does
this combat thing work and the gm is
trying to explain the very
i guess in-depth way that the the combat
system is and everyone's just like ah
what so um yeah we don't want that
so um if if i do something that's a
little different from the traditional
world of darkness sense please
understand
um that that's just how we're gonna roll
and i will explain
i will explain how uh it's how it's
going to be changed etc
um yeah i also saw kiara shrunk for a
second she's fine now though
okay as long as you're okay now my dude
that was me i sent you the update yes
thank you very much i will be using this
for my reference
awesome um now before we get started
i do think it's best to learn by
experience but i do want to kind of talk
a little bit about rolling
um so due to various uh circumstances
beyond our control for now all of the
tutorials will be rolled by
your boy um but i will teach you the
commands so that you know them
um and in the future everyone will have
access to being able to do this
but for now i need chiara to be my math
wizard
can you do that for me sorry guys
can be my math wizard excellent crazy
i'm gonna be
oh i'm all kinds of winters kelly
fantastic fantastic yeah
all right well so one one two three four
five
at least i know how to count to five
it's okay if you have to use your
fingers i have to use my fingers too
bye i i have the calculator open
excellent excellent now let's
try and and just do your first roll okay
so in this game a role you're going to
be doing very often
is a perception check okay okay okay so
like looking around
exactly when i say uh roll a perception
check
um or you're like what's in my
surroundings i can say well role
perception
and your perception is going to be your
wits plus
your composure okay
which is one composure is two so i roll
three dices
exactly and this is going to be
understanding maximum big brain
galaxy brain okay huge brain so you'll
type
dash why is it caps roll
it's slash roll and you said three
oh yeah three d10 it means that you're
going to be rolling
three d10 dice okay okay so here we go
three d10
i've rolled the dice and what i'll do is
click on this little drop down and here
are the
dice that you roll wow
[Music]
yeah the 25 isn't exactly important
right now
the dicer was important yeah that's
pretty good um that's two successes
however it depends on the difficulty of
the task
so let me explain something um that's
going to be kind of central to how i'm
running this game
essentially when i played this game
difficulty was not a thing
um eight nine and ten were successes and
that's all that there was to it
um however the more research that i did
the more that i realized hey
some people set difficulty for things so
for example kiara
give me an example of a really easy task
that anyone can do
walking up the stair walking up the
stairs
all right that should be decently easy
but some people will probably have
trouble with it
um maybe all right so okay so let's go
ahead and say
now i can do another one okay uh
picking up a stone picking up a stone
all right
sounds good um i think that should be
fairly doable
so we'll go ahead and set the difficulty
at four
okay oh pretty low because it's a pretty
simple task to do
now to pick up that stone kiara i'm
going to have you roll
your strength and athletics
okay string free athletics
two so five five dices please five okay
let's do a roll five
d10 and here's what we got
now the result is oh no you got a one
but you also got a ten because you got
because you got a 10 that's actually a
re-roll and also
we set the difficulty at four correct
yeah so four is a success okay
wait do all of the dices each guys have
to be a success
yeah so all of you just need in order to
succeed
you just need one success just only one
success
in order to moderately succeed like you
can kind of do it it's not perfect but
you at least kind of did it all right
and then we're going to read
so i can reroll okay exactly so here we
go but you only got it two
so in total you got two successes
and one one failure this one right here
now
some gm some gm would say that this one
cancels out one of your successes but i
don't i don't do it that way
especially not in the beginning um the
only time that you will fail is when you
get no successes
and it will be um a pretty significant
failure if you get no successes and a
one
but because you succeeded in the first
place with getting a four and a ten
um i'm going to go ahead and say that
you got two successes which is you
decently succeeded at it good job
yay now let's say i picked up the stone
and now i'm going to throw it at you
kelly
no bit higher difficulty because i suck
at throwing
yeah and i'm also real quick i'm good at
throwing
well your boys real quick so good luck
hey what
no no no no no way of i i throw games
and i suck at games
i don't think you're that bad at games
cuz sorry i think you're pretty good
thank you
yeah yeah whatever yeah no no no problem
got your bag
anyway think of a really difficult task
history
on a difficult task that's difficult for
most people to do
really difficult yeah
[Music]
um
uh think about okay how about the it's
uh think about a back flip
all right i was about so i was about to
roast you a little bit there but you're
fine your finals
no no no roasting no roasting the
phoenix it won't
get anywhere with that i'm constantly
get some chicken
um all right so let's say difficulty is
going to be
let's go ahead and make that nine okay
difficulty is nine so let's go ahead and
roll your strength
plus athletics we're going to have it be
strength in athletics you've got to be
dead again is five five nice okey dokey
so we're gonna do a roll
5d 10 and let's see what we get
[Music]
um so we got eight two five one six but
because the difficulty is nine
um unfortunately no successes you try
and do the backflip you bonk your head
you didn't break your head or you didn't
break your back but you did
bonk your head on the ground and you're
gonna take two bashing damage
um we'll go up we'll go over how damage
works a little bit later once it becomes
relevant but yeah you're going to get
hurt because of that
right man ouch i expected that
that was the outcome i expected yes
all right so now we basically know how
the roles are going to work essentially
you've got kind of an idea
yeah that yeah let's see what is the
i think we're going to go ahead and get
started then if you're all ready to go
i guess so so now i am
tiara you see what you want
okay i'm nervous about role-playing oh
my god it's gonna be a bit embarrassing
in the first session i think i'll do my
best
that's okay you'll be fine i'm gonna be
doing it too i may get
a little in character as well um
a little update uh because my members
saw me drawing
my character it's like i i couldn't
finish it for today but it will be i'll
finish it sometime soon when i got time
but yeah my members already have a rough
image of what tiara
looks like and i'll show it to you guys
whenever it's finished yoroshiku
excellent
sounds good all right now let's see
go ahead and um set the stage in just a
moment
but first
[Music]
um let's see well first
um i'd like to kind of set the scene by
um
i guess introducing overall the the big
setting of the story
so basically uh our story begins in a
coastal city
called mythton f10
mistan that's right how very original
original name i like it yeah
so here's the special thing about miftin
um
nothing essentially
essentially uh mithtin is known for
nothing but its abundance of corn
and absolutely nothing else why did you
choose to come to this failing tourist
trap of a place
because you are clean clearly must be
something like that
okay are you asking yeah okay i i have
come to this place
because um i want to find more birds
yes essentially that that is correct for
tiara
there's only one other thing that could
have piqued your boundless curiosity
and uh the only reason that you could
have been drawn to this lackluster town
a specific
besides corn besides corn a specific
breed of
owl tends to nest here
indeed i know that though a rare find
indeed it is one you've set your sights
on
for a while so continuing your ever
perilous journey across an unknown land
you've settled here at least for a
little while a dusty old tattered
apartment will have to do as you've
burned through the last bit of money
you've saved
and you've been out of a job for quite a
while now but
at least your birds have been well and
the town has been quiet and peaceful
so what more could you ask for nothing
this is wonderful
yeah exactly so before we go ahead and
dive right into the
the scenery of the story how about you
go ahead and
give us a little idea of a day in the
life of
our protagonist tiara
a day in the life all right sure
from the moment you wake up in the
morning
okay well so i i wake up
quite early in the morning because some
foods are
active in the morning um
so i uh after uh eating a little bit of
bread because i can't um afford much
more than bread
i uh i make myself
out into the woods and go for some burp
watching allah
[Music]
oh yeah by the way of course i'm
accompanied by
my little owl which i brought with me
from my homeland sana
and while we're watching some verbs i'm
also looking
for some foof who pretty much eats
anything
um especially mice um so i try to find
some mice but
who can probably do it better than i can
do so
i leave it to uh
yeah so after the book watching that
what we're gonna be doing for some
some hours i i go back into the city
and i um i try to
learn more about the city because i've
just arrived i try to
uh find some new restaurants and stores
and maybe some new accessories for
my my my
home and my clothes and fi trying to
find some weapons because
apparently i left my weapons at home
so yeah i'm still still on the search
for some weapons but also maybe
perhaps maybe for a small side job and
to afford those weapons out of cause
life is tough out here
uh yeah and uh
oh dear um so yeah that's and then it's
probably evening time
and then i'll go i'll go back home after
that stroll in the city
and i i just hang out with my ow
[Music]
uh
and i write in a diary because i
apparently keep dying
diaries i don't um yeah
great sounds good
oh yeah and then i i try to make some
dinner which is usually
just um a bone and super
bean soup cheap as hell but it will do
it's it's all i need i'm not very picky
about food i'll eat anything
and uh yeah and then i
i go back to sleep that's a basic basic
basic day maybe but
uh i'm waiting for some adventures as
soon as i get my guns out i'll be out
there getting my boobs
yes indeed interestingly enough uh the
main reason that you weren't able to
bring your firearms along with you is
because you had a hard time
getting them through customs and
immigration
oh that is true yes yes that's what was
where we travel some yeah i don't
know yes um however um
who knows anything could happen in the
future so you know keep on keeping on
we'll see what happens
um but yes essentially tiara
you've been a little uh bimbo for a
while as in like no money
no money sadly um japanese japanese
bimbo yeah yeah japanese beanboozled
yes that's what that's that was the bean
bow that i meant listen
that was
yes exactly correct correct you would be
correct
so you have been living off of um off of
bread
and uh some cheap soup and living in um
a decently
old and tattered apartment kind of on
the uh the outskirts of town
which is actually pretty good because
since the apartment is so
old it's also um infested with
mice which is perfect dinner for my owl
that's right that's right that is the
one nice thing
very lucky you got pretty lucky that's
exactly the reason why i chose this
apartment it was all planned out
from the beginning all part of your plan
do you uh
do you have any other birds with you
aside from uhu
if i'm allowed sure that's fine ah
there there is uh there's a crow
that followed me started following me in
the city i had some crows
uh back in my hometown as well but i
left that one
those there because of and i felt that
it might be safer for them there
uh but i uh recently i don't know maybe
burbs just like
me but a crow has found a liking in me
recently and sometimes accompanies me
and chills and hangs out with woohoo
okay wonderful sounds good yeah they let
also they let you
take birds in through customs and
immigration but no guns
so that's kind of an interesting thing i
suppose but
you know you really like those birds and
maybe they felt kind of bad taking those
birds away so
at least it's only possible it's just
quite quite a hassle of documentation
and vaccination and stuff you have to
get your bird vaccinated and checked out
in order to bring it over yeah but i i i
do what i have to do for my favorite
verb
yes exactly that's what makes all of it
worth it
yup and so all of you are here in this
brand new place
in this brand new country that you've
never been to before though you've been
living
you've been living here for several
weeks now i would say
at the time of our story several weeks
you've been here
so let's go ahead and start off by
throwing you straight into the story
and i'll have you make your first
perception check
tiara okay okay
yes i understand uh oh wait do i grow
what was it wits and
wits and composure
uh that's free dices please all right
here we go i'll switch to something a
little more calming
all right here we are and um for
perception checks i would say all
difficulty is going to be six
oh wow so you got that was an incredible
success
that was a significant wow okay okay
nice
as expected yes very very good okay
three successes nice all right
so i'll go ahead and set the scene for
you in this case
okay i'm looking um you've come you've
come to your favorite park
uh this one is decidedly your favorite
uh you've been to several parks around
this city but this one there's just
something special about it there's
something
delicious smelling on the air not not
really like a delicious food but just a
freshness that you can't even describe
um and so many birds many of them are
birds that you've seen before um but
occasionally you see one that
that you've never seen and you take a
quick picture of it but they all seem to
gravitate towards you in some kind of
way it's almost like they can tell
that you're one of the good humans yes
yes
they love miata yes indeed
so the birds are chirping as per the
usual on this lovely day
your favorite wait i can i can hear
sound
oh nice you're
that's right yes exactly now everyone
can hear the birds
[Music]
and the trees are just full of them
today especially because it's a nice
sunny day
and um the grass is swaying ever so
lightly
and uh the flowers that bloom in summer
have just begun to poke out
just a little bit ever so slightly um
and it's not quite that time of year
where where bugs are getting
too um too feisty around these parts so
it's
basically a perfect day and you hear
some children laughing off in the
distance
all kind of playing together by the edge
of the forest um
and you're sitting on your favorite park
bench and uh just admiring the birds
above you what do you choose to do from
here
i choose to take a little bit of
bread out of my pocket and feed it to
the birds
i'll try to get them to come over sure
so to do that i'm gonna have you roll
um an animal can roll so to do that
um i'm gonna go ahead and have you add
up your wits
and your animal ken and let me know what
that is
[Music]
ah that is five dices please anna right
and do you have a specialty in birds
i do i have verb communication all right
so i'll go ahead and make that uh six
dice
okay oh yes and the difficulty for this
will be six
so let's go roll a six d10
and let's see what we got here one two
three successes
all right that's very good so uh you've
done this quite a few times before tiara
this is nothing new to you
so you kind of spread out the
breadcrumbs on the ground
and gently wait for them to come to you
um
you don't do anything any two sudden
movements or anything shocking that
would scare them away because you
typically know how to interact with
birds
and um just like clockwork every single
time they
they come just bobbing up to you um
eating the crumbs and then even after
that sticking around you
um surfing happily
just like that just like that
business you've got about 10 of them
surrounding you right now
oh damn i'm the bird lady
in fact one of them one of them is
sitting on my lap
yes probably at this point yeah with
that kind of success i would say so
in fact
yes definitely you can tell that uh your
friend
your owl is um is a little on the
jealous side
kind of uh turning their head back and
forth
in a curious motion tilting gotta tilt
that head
oh come on you know you're my number one
ana
you know it i would never replace you
who hears this and just turns their head
away like
[Music]
oh you're freaking cinnamon
[Laughter]
and by now actually about five birds um
are kind of sitting up on your lap
yeah in fact um they seem to be
interested in
something that you are wearing as a
matter of fact
oh and um you glance down to
kind of remember um
you actually are wearing a pendant
around your neck
it's a necklace a necklace you received
a long time ago from someone you can't
quite remember
the pendant is in the shape of a phoenix
okay yeah and birds left
i look at my pendant verbs looking at my
pendant i open up the pendant perhaps
um actually it's um it's not like a
locket or anything
it's just okay yeah it's just a gold a
gold
uh pendant in the shape of a phoenix and
it glimmers in the sunlight
wow sparkly so sparkly that the the
crows around me when i want to steal it
they do kind of want to take it from you
i will not let them i will protect it's
an
important pendant all right sounds good
sounds good um the birds are kind of
approaching and getting closer trying to
get a closer look at it
you can rock you can roll to tell them
to go away if you would like or to stop
bothering you about your pendant
well i have verb communication so i tell
them
no take no take tiara sparkly finger no
no
all right let's see what you get then
difficulty
six okay we've got 666 uh the number of
the beast
saint numbers all right but you still
managed to do it um they understand
yeah they kind of tilt their heads
curiously and um eventually just kind of
hop away from the pendant and kind of
focus back on eating the breadcrumbs
very very good very good so good and at
this time
um go ahead and make another perception
check roll for me
okay uh that was a wits
and composure
width and composition free dices all
right here you go difficulty six
oh wow that's another very high success
um so at this point um
you do notice something kind of odd um
well first of all you notice a friendly
old couple is sitting on a bench across
from you
um and seem to be looking at you with
kind of a sweet look in their eyes
because they've seen you come to this
park before you feel like you've seen
them as well and they seem like a
friendly old couple
hello hello there young one
enjoying a day with the birds yeah they
are being a bit
uh a bit too greedy today but i i tell
them what
where their place is at anna
[Music]
the old couple chuckles ah yes the birds
around here are usually a little feisty
but that's because we feed them too much
yeah they looked very fat indeed adam
the old couple chuckles and at this
point you also realize that um the
children that were playing by the edge
of the forest
uh have disappeared
yeah they're gone um
yeah but i mean you know the kids around
these parts like to
and they have to go back home to their
mommies
yeah of course perhaps that's what
happened um
and you also noticed something else um a
tall
figure in the distance um has been
looking at you for a while very far away
though
well that's that's kind of creepy yeah
i asked i asked the the the couple if
they
know that dude in the distance
um um let's see to ask something
specific like that you have a bit of um
you have a bit of a hard time with um
the country's language correct
well i'm multilingual but but
just just not let's speak the language
because it's not perfect
let's see uh because it's a fairly
simple thing that you're asking for
like hey do you know that person over
there um i won't have you roll for it
we'll just have it be an automatic
action but
that will be something in the future
that may come up keep that okay
if you're asking for very specific
things i'll have you roll um
now the old couple kind of glances
behind
uh their shoulders and they don't seem
to think anything very suspicious of the
person behind them and
just kind of shrug it off and say oh
they're all there are folks from all
around
that come here like you for example um
sometimes you don't see the same person
twice we certainly haven't
seen any strange character like that
before
[Music]
oh i don't quite trust them
the old couple does look a little
worried but uh
[Music]
but by the time that um that you've said
anything
the figure has actually noticed that the
three of you were looking their way
and has since begun walking away
oh okay well that's uh that's
that's probably for the better i guess i
hope i don't meet that person
anymore although hmm yes possibly
potentially
could be could be just you know any
other passerby but
you know shady folks you take note of
them sometimes
recently i've heard i've heard about
some incidents in the city so
gotta be careful out there that's right
especially in this city the city of
mythton crime has actually been on the
rise recently you've seen in the news
yes indeed so you gotta be a little
careful you can never be
too careful in this kind of situation
can i can i make ooh follow
dude sure if you'd like to uh go ahead
and
do the same role to communicate to your
bird
that's what you would like to do i think
that was six
six sizes all right here we go and um
let's go ahead and make the difficulty
of this one seven i would say because
who is going on a tracking mission which
can be a bit difficult
and you need to give some specific
instructions yes yes
all right so we've got one two three
four
four successes that is a very
exceptional success
yes all right so what do you say
to uh
[Music]
you have to be careful but follow that
dude a little bit and see where he's
going maybe if he enters a restaurant or
something
let me know where it is later all right
um ooh kind of does the the typical head
jerk that you're used to and then flies
off immediately
um because who pretty much knows exactly
what what you want them to do
take care adam all right off they go
um now it's starting to get a little bit
later um the sun is beginning to
set just a bit on the horizon what do
you choose to do
[Music]
i choose to
wait here for ooh to come back because
otherwise uh maybe
has trouble finding me i don't okay okay
sounds good so you wait
and wait and now it has become very late
at night
oh no no who didn't come back
um just as you're beginning to believe
that your owl
has gotten lost uh you hear a familiar
flutter of wings
approaching you and it appears that ooh
has returned
i hug i hug kind of jerks their head
around
who loves me i know
so what do you say to uh mm-hmm
[Music]
well i mean hmm good question
would you like to inquire about
something specific
[Music]
did the do you know where he
went to did you see where he went
we'll go ahead and do the same roll and
we'll make it a 7 for difficulty again
oh wow okay okay well you got two
successes
um oh man i said you won
i won't i won't cancel it i won't cancel
it but um it probably won't be an
amazing success
in this sense um but you do get some
information
essentially from from ooh who's kind of
a telegraphed jerks of the head and
whatnot
um you can tell that um ooh is telling
you that that figure basically just
went to their house um some old
tattered place but who also tells you
that um
that they've remembered the location
just in case
good job oh i gave her a little bit of a
snack
as a thank you who is overjoyed and
ruffles their feathers
and gladly takes the snack from you and
eats it with me
a cute good good cookie all right
now that it's about um probably
rather late in the evening i would say
what do you choose to do
we go back home and eat our bean soup
adam
all right sounds good we're gonna go
ahead and uh go home then
here we go let's see now
home for you um is
well like i mentioned before a rather
tattered apartment um
pretty old and dusty but you've done a
decent job cleaning the place up
you know it is what it is it's home it's
just enough for you at least
so you go ahead and do it at night yeah
so you enter your home and
and begin the usual nightly ritual of
preparing soup
uh for you and your birds um and the
birds are of course as excited as ever
to get a tasty meal made by tiara
herself
high quality five star hotel
meal yes of course of course
and you guys all enjoy a nice meal
together
yum yum yum yum oh i hear i hear a
mouse uh crawling under uh under my
ceiling
so who is uh very
very excited to get that message yes
absolutely get him
go get him i say go get him who flies
off
flies off to presumably go eat the mouse
another casper did
oh gosh not casper
[Music]
and just like that uh ooh disappears
under the ceiling yeah under the ceiling
definitely still in your house right
the birds surround you as you're
enjoying your soup
and they chirp in a way that you are
familiar with um
kind of nudging at your phone because um
as per the usual some of the birds are
curious about the pictures that you got
today
yeah i took some pictures so i'm editing
them to to upload them online
yes of course yeah
so um you take out you take out your
phone and you begin
uh scrolling through your photos as you
usually do
showing off the birds that you have
found today sending them off to be
edited on your computer presumably
but but in one of the pictures
of a bird in the background i see that
dude again
yes
yes in fact wow very perceptive of you
you didn't even have to rule is that
what you were going to do
uh no not quite but um well you'll see
basically there is a blurry image you do
notice that in one of your photos
it's a little weird it's a little creepy
but
you know apparently they went off and it
seems like it was
it was no harm no foul nothing really
wrote my picture though he wrote on the
picture
sure he did maybe you can edit him out
who knows
i'm not good with technical stuff i can
only only take photos just not do much
more
that's right that's right tiara is not
exactly the technical type huh yes that
is
true well that's all right
i mean the the photos themselves are
pretty good as a matter of fact
maybe some of your powder work
i know what the chocolate side of a
barbie's is
is that how you say it in english the
chocolate side
yeah wait do you not think well there we
go i'm stroke playing here this is
totally wrong
even the birds are like what is the
chocolate side of me
that is the language of somewhere
somewhere else in
somewhere else the end correct exactly
that's where that's where tiara is from
as you're scrolling through your photos
actually um
tiara you kind of um you get to the last
photo
and then on your phone if you scroll
through all the photos you tend to kind
of go to the very first
photo once again in your phone um and by
accident you kind of scroll
and return to the very first photo
in your phone which is a picture of you
with someone whose face
you can't quite discern it's blurry for
some reason that person's face
oh oh i tried to zoom in but i can't
really
see much yeah you zoom in and you start
to realize it's
it's not so much the phone itself but
rather your own foggy memory that isn't
allowing you to understand the face of
the person in the photo
how about you go ahead and roll a memory
check for me
that's going to be intelligence and wits
four dices please four all right we'll
go ahead and roll a four
d10 and the difficulty for this one is
going to be seven
so here we go oh dear
oh no oh man i don't know who the hell
that
is adam you have no idea you've got no
clue
um but don't remember there is one clue
there is one clue in the photo that is
just very obvious
i'll give you the obvious one and it's
that um
in the photo that person is giving you a
pendant
[Music]
the gold pen that around your neck
that's why i got the pendant from aria
tell
yeah you're not really sure and the sad
part is
you could swear that you remembered at
some point but
the more you try to remember it's almost
like the more you
keep forgetting why have i forgotten
but but kelly apparently i do keep a
diary
you do keep a diary so would you like to
go take a look at it
oh yeah if you let me out i'll go take a
look then
sure you go to your diary kind of brush
it off and open it
i need to update it before i go to sleep
too i need to write in about that dude
as well
true true exactly so you go ahead and
you um
open up your diary um and in order to
do some research to try and figure out
who the blurry figure
in your phone is you'll need to go ahead
and do
let's see let me see what kind of role
i'm going to have you do
um in order to research who
that person is um i'll have you go ahead
and roll
intelligence and let's see
we'll go ahead and make it an academics
and intelligence role because you're
doing some research
for four dices okay
for the 10. and i'm glad you didn't say
investigation because that's also a
thing and i have no points in there
it's okay it is the tutorial after all
so
so things might be a bit on the easier
side for this go around
um the difficulty for this role i'm
going to go ahead and make a 7d10 again
so here we go
oh gosh oh goodness
oh man i wonder if the luck is starting
to run out
no no hints no hints about the dude in
my diary huh
would you like to try again because if
you try again
you can try to do it again but it will
take more time so it might get to be
decently late at night maybe like 2 a.m
3 a.m
i will try again because that got me
quite curious
all right apparently a flaw but in this
case it could be a merit
true true true all right now we're going
to go ahead and roll 40
difficulty is still seven i won't up it
this time so here we go
okay you've got one success
one success here so you kind of scroll
back to your diary
um and to be honest a lot of the the
mentions of
people in your life and would not um
seem to be
fairly distant like friends for example
um but you do stumble upon
um a page from decently long ago
um i'd say about
maybe two or three years ago
not so long ago right not too long ago
but you do
you do read an entry that mentions
um someone going away
for a long time and interestingly enough
the name of the person
has been completely blurred out
[Music]
did i spill water over it or what yeah
it's like
it's kind of worn away over time almost
as like as if someone has taken an
eraser and tried to erase it out very
frantically
that's what kind of catches your eye in
the first place but just because the
name
[Music]
not sure of the speculation but just
because the name is erased
um doesn't mean that uh your
investigative abilities have lost sight
of the fact that someone is mentioned in
the entry
someone specific particularly your
brother
[Music]
oh oh yeah i have a brother oh yeah yeah
yeah he taught me how to use guns
yup that's actually what the entry is
kind of about
um you are reminiscing about your
brother
teaching you how to use guns um
a long time ago actually you you really
learned how to use them
since a younger age because your brother
had some kind of business that he was
doing
and never really told you a lot about
a little bit um mysterious brother
indeed but about two or three years ago
um he left to go on a journey somewhere
far away and
and the way that he worded it made you a
bit nervous
um because it sounded almost as though
he was
in a bit of trouble but he was trying to
assure you
you remember that things were going to
be fine didn't tell you where he went
or anything like that just kind of gone
yeah he just left me and that was that
was uh
sad for me and maybe partially the
reason why i wanted to go out
uh finally as well on my own mm-hmm
wow what a fine memory that you have
just procured in this moment
and though you're unsure exactly if the
person in the photo
is your brother you get the sense that
it is certainly a possibility
yeah maybe maybe that was him on that
but maybe he looked at me from the
distance and also wasn't sure like
if if i am who i am because he can't
believe i'm here or
who knows who knows maybe i'll find him
again maybe
maybe now that we know where his house
is tomorrow
we can go and say hello hmm
indeed if that's what you'd like to do
tomorrow is a new day after all
sounds a bit dangerous though um and i
don't like to trust people that much
maybe i'll just go to the park again
tomorrow and then see if he comes again
rather than going straight to his house
yeah i think i'll do that
and now i'll sleep good night
[Music]
good night your birds kind of swarm
around you and give you their good night
greeting
before kind of slowly slowly but surely
um falling asleep with you in the same
room presumably
cute they are protecting me exactly you
do feel
fairly protected and secure thanks to
all of your birds around you
good bib now
the next morning comes and
see but for now for now you are dreaming
you're dreaming and let's see
next song
[Music]
all right you awake in the morning to
something fairly unpleasant
tiara oh no this is what you hear
yo wake up
i'm a rank i'm a wake up who is this
someone is knocking
firmly on your door and is very upset
i look for the keyhole the keyhole not
the keyhole that did that that one hole
oh the the the the glass one
even i'm forgetting the peephole baby he
pulls her a little it's something like
that
something like that you look through
that little glass
thing that's in the door you you look
through it and you see
um a fairly
a fairly short and um
agitated looking woman with
black hair kind of pulled back into a
ball and she seems very angry
um oh [\h__\h] is she asking for a friend
is that my plan
you do recognize her as the person who
who gave you
the key to this place
[Music]
i i keep the the lock
the the chain lock on the door but open
up the door so only like
a little bit all right sounds good you
open it up a little bit and she
immediately begins going off on you
saying things like
you know rent was due about two weeks
ago and i've been very very
patient with you giving you this place
letting you stay here for so long you
and your birds
who keep me up all night with their
endless squawking
and you think it's okay to not pay your
rent do you have anything to say
i sorry i i i am
new here i don't
speak your language another foreigner
[Music]
i i have i have money at all
uh will will bring uh money
soon how soon give me an estimate i need
numbers madame please tell me ah i did
not
practice numbers yet
i would love to let you stay here out of
the kindness of my old heart
however however i also have bills to pay
[Music]
ah
uh sorry do not understand dada no no
i closed the door
you can't run away from me i own this
building
she seems very persistent
okay i think i think she uh
um believed that i indeed was this bad
with the language
uh i think she believes me
she knocks again
listen do you have a job
ah i
open the door again and say job
i look look for job
you have job do you want
a job yes please job give me
aga i work hard
the landlord sighs and she kind of rubs
her eyebrows
and seems very distraught but says i do
know some people
oh you know people i do
[Music]
look you can have your choice of a job i
know about
three different people who are looking
for someone who can do
menial tasks just use a word that you
don't know
what's task
easy tasks easy tasks for people like
easy you see okay okay
[Music]
um unfortunately that's not going to cut
it for some of these jobs
hate to tell you
yeah i um you can get your ass i can
learn new thing
so be it and with that
the landlord whips out a notepad pulls
out her
flip phone and start and start scrolling
through her con
her uh contacts that's the word
contacts and begins to write some
numbers down shoves the paper through
the mail slot and says
get some money fast you have two weeks
okay
thank you very much
[Music]
all right close the door and take the
paper
okay now go ahead and roll a perception
check for me
wits and
[Music]
intelligence uh what's in components
uh three dices yes all right here we go
oh what was that what was it the
difficulty six
okay you got one success uh the
landlord's
handwriting is pretty bad like really
not very good
the last do you think i can read that
unfortunately
out of the three jobs that are listed on
the paper the last one's
number is very smudged out um but you've
got
three different jobs that look like they
are available to you
with phone numbers the first one appears
to be some kind of cafe job
um it just it just says cafe
and then number under it the second one
appears to be some kind of bird shop
[Music]
with a number under it and the last one
looks to be
some kind of old theater but the contact
number is completely smudged out
i'm going for the bridge sounds perfect
for me
great would you like to call the number
yes i call number
people people people people people
the phone rings a couple of times and
a couple times more and a couple times
more
the line seems to be a little busy but
then eventually
you do get an answer oh
hello hello
hello my name is
hello hello can you say that a bit
louder my dear
hello my name is hello
yeah can you say that a bit louder my
dear
hello you're breaking up my dear i'm
sorry can you
just can you just come to the shop i
can't hear you for the life of me
okay i i come to shop do you have
address
address do i have
what can you one more time you're going
to have to roll
you're going to have to roll your
expression
and presence
[Music]
three expressions hot [\h__\h] okay
three dices please all right however
because you don't have a
you don't have a point an expression
it's going to be a minus one for being
unskilled so it's two dice
all right so roll two d10 difficulty is
six
see what you got all right one success
one success all right so you can barely
you can you can i mean you can hear her
fine she's the one that can't hear you
but she says the the oh the ad
the address um let's see who can i even
remember
i forget everything these days one
moment um
let's see take your time
oh oh wha what was that can you say that
one more time
oh okay let's see do
do you know where the forest is
the for the forest with with the park
next to it the the forest
yes yes yes yes yes if if you don't
enter the forest it's it's very
dangerous if
if you go to that park and and you
head east it will be the first shop that
you see
on on a very busy street can you do that
[Music]
i think i can yes no problem
oh all right i'll uh i will i will be
waiting i will
quiet silence you hear some you hear
some squawks
you hear some squawks over the phone
some angry chirps
[Music]
can you say that one more time and then
the phone hangs up
[Music]
the phone all right all right
all right well since it's so early uh in
the morning i first
eat some bread for breakfast and then i
think i'll get going
all right sounds good um now you kind of
remember the directions that
uh that the woman on the phone gave to
you it was it was kind of hard to
understand but
you can remember so in order to navigate
your way to the shop
i'm going to have you go ahead and roll
let's see
what shall i have you roll um
let's just do a memory check
intelligence and wits
right excellent
all right and the um difficulty is gonna
be seven because it was really kind of
hard to hear exactly what she said
you know she said forest she could have
said florist who knows
so here we go all right let's see
six six five one uh
dang it but
but but she said park and then and then
forest and east and she said dangerous
the florist is not gonna be dangerous so
yeah i mean
right but but tiara remembers going to
the forest and then that's about
it so you kind of wander around that
area
you can roll again if you'd like to try
and remember again but it is about
early afternoon at this point if you
want to do another roll
i'll roll again all right roll four d10
difficulty is still seven
all right you got two successes
excellent
all right so with your two successes you
remember ah
that's right east east from the park by
the forest okay okay
so you kind of figured it out um
all right so you you believe you've
arrived when you see a kind of
busy street um quite hustling and
bustling
um we'll go ahead and go to the shop and
you can tell that it's a bird shop
because immediately you can see out
front um there are some cages with
little birds
who look like they're enjoying some time
in the sunlight kind of
chirping merrily i know cute
i never saw that bird before i wonder
what that one is
now i guess i try into the shop and find
the lady all right so before you do that
i'll have you roll another perception
check
oh three does this yes
oh for perception
[Music]
that's the memory check oh sorry ah go
go go
okay free dices okey dokey and
difficulty is six here we go
[Music]
all right and that's another roll whoa
okay even though that was already an
except a success
yeah can i see the first one didn't oh
no it's okay
so basically because you got a 10 and an
eight yeah
and the six yeah so it's an added
success pretty much
so you have one two three you have three
successes
now okay that's an exceptional success
so pretty pretty good i will give you a
nice detailed description of the area so
when you
approach the front of the shop um you
can see that
there are of course many cages with
birds chirping merrily
they seem to be enjoying the day you can
see that they're well fed and well taken
care of this seems like an area where
the birds are decently happy thankfully
um you get just kind of a good aura from
from this particular shop um an aura
that you can kind of
trust though the shop itself is rather
worn down and um
it looks like it's seen quite a few
years and and the windows are rather
dusty and you get the feeling that it
doesn't quite have the level of
of upkeep that is usually necessary
required for
for this kind of uh for this kind of
place unfortunately while it feels
as though the owner is friendly loves
the birds and maybe takes good care of
them
uh the shop itself is pretty dirty um
even once you enter the front door
you can tell that um it's not very clean
and
you get the sense that only one person
is running this shop
all right and uh after that i would say
as soon as you enter the shop
you see there is an old woman kind of
perched behind
a cash register and she is on the phone
once again kind of yelling
uh pretty much the same situation as
when you called her on the
can you say that again my dear
i couldn't quite oh i'm sorry excuse me
i have to go i'll call you right back
and she hangs up the phone and
looks at you and the first thing that
she looks at when she notices you is of
course
your owl yeah
nice to meet you uh i was the one on the
phone
tiara hello oh
hello there a bit a bit late but
thank you for coming nonetheless i
appreciate it
i was a bit difficult to hear you on the
phone
so i was a bit lost me but but i
speak loud and clear i was having
trouble hearing you
[Music]
also i'm sorry i was speaking well
no matter no matter i must say you seem
rather friendly and i'm most intrigued
by the bird that you have with you right
there on your shoulder
i brought it from somewhere else in have
you heard of that place before
somewhere elsian ah let me see
well that's difficult you see i really
haven't traveled out of this town
basically ever so it's quite far away
it's over the seas
i see she seems to be
kind of off in another world now at this
point oh
she's got that kind of that uh that
thousand mile stare
i i clap into my hand
oh you have to excuse me sometimes i
space out a little bit
and then as soon as she says that
several of the birds start making quite
a racket inside of their cages
fidgeting around oh
oh you you're smoking
i need a little bit of help with those
burps i i would love to get a job at
your place
uh she at first doesn't quite hear what
you say because she's kind of gone into
a bit of a frenzy trying to quiet down
the birds she's not
physically harmful to them but she
screams quite a bit at the birds
kind of sounds like a bird with my
animal ken
and the burp communication i'll calm
them down i'll try to calm them down and
then she'll be
super impressed and be like ah hi are
you all right
sounds good so what do you say tiara and
what do you say and do to calm down the
birds i'll do the roll
after you kind of play it out i say
be calm everyone i'm trying to have a
conversation here
and i'll i want i want to get a job here
so
if you behave i'll give you lots of lots
of bread pieces
all right gotcha
so because it's already rather loud
there's a ruckus going on and the owner
of the shop has kind of
found herself in a frenzy um it's going
to be um
a little more difficult so i'll go ahead
and put it at um
let's see a seven difficulty ought to do
the trick
let's see but i got six dices yeah no
problem
all right woohoo wow
okay uh you got three successes
so that's pretty good actually that's a
very good success
um so as soon as you begin speaking
while the birds squawk for a little
while
all of them kind of do that you know
that bird head turn at the same time
look straight at you and you um you tell
them about the breadcrumbs and they're
most interested in the breadcrumbs
actually they seem to um
immediately focus their attention on you
and um they haven't completely quieted
down but now it's like uh
just little mumbles of bird chattering
and whatnot um
and the owner who is initially in a
frenzy and still kind of calming down
like why you little oh
rat rascals wow you've done
quite a good job yes yes i am
i i know a lot of burps out there i'm
very good with them
it almost feels like they can understand
me
well clearly they never listened to me
but
i've been looking for someone who is
good with birds
shall we say to look after to look after
the little ones
and the big ones yeah
you notice around you there are birds of
varying size and varying variety there
are some birds
bigger than any birds you've ever seen
before and they're causing quite they
were causing quite a ruckus but
thankfully you were able to kind of calm
them down
oh i'm quite interested in your verbs i
would love to
take care of them and and study them and
maybe uh help you out in the shop with
some things
if you would accept my help
well sure that that sounds fine my dear
but you see i have a very specific
job in mind she says she kind of makes
her way back behind the cash register
oh what is that well you see i can
really take care of the birds just fine
during the daytime
i don't think so but never mind excuse
me
so i what i didn't i didn't hear you can
you please
sorry sorry keep keep keep on going
well all right then she says that she
kind of squints back through her little
spectacles
um and and pulls out what looks to be
something like a job ad
um she says i posted this around the
town but no one would really take the
job because of the um
the working hours they're rather late i
need someone to take care of the night
shift here
oh okay why
i can there's a night shift i have a
night shift in a burp shop
we are open almost 24 hours because
anytime is a good time to buy a bird
oh i see okay ah um
i mean my hour's a night out um i can i
can
adjust uh quite well so that i think
i've been
uh forced to adjust to my owl's sleeping
habits every now and then
excellent well then i guess you'll fit
the job quite perfectly
yes your shift would begin sorry
the what the salary ada
oh you want money
yeah yes really
yes i need it for my rent please that
would be wonderful lonna
oh dear my landlord recommended you know
when i asked for
a job and so i you're a landlord oh
edith okay okay i think i know
i i see edith is quite the penny pincher
all right fine let's see
how about this if you do a successful
job here for the next
two days i will go ahead and settle your
debt with your landlord and after that
we'll go ahead and do um how about this
um hmm let me think what is fair
well back in my day i believe
the minimum wage was two dollars an hour
how does that
sound
[Music]
i get is that is that normal in this
country well my first job was about
it was about two two dollars well i
think maybe the times have changed all
right three dollars an
hour i say uh uh eight hours
a dollar eight hours a dollar wait
okay sounds fantastic so that means one
dollar per day
all right you're hired sounds good you
begin immediately
language problem let's say sorry sorry
eight
dollars an hour please add half um
you drive a hard bargain little missy
all right i think you will see it it
will be worth it because
did you see how well i can communicate
with the burbs it's gonna be all fun you
can leave it all to me and you don't
have to worry and you can sleep sound
and safe
all right well i'll go ahead and put my
trust in you
little lady for the time being okay
thank you so much anna i was about to
get kicked out of my apartment here
you're saving my life again
yes no no problem i'm i'm very sorry
about them
about edith in any case if things don't
really work out
you're certainly welcome to come here
and sleep in one of the bird cages
well i guess if you got a big one i
guess okay
they're very cozy come to them yes
sometimes i like to go sleep in them
i prefer my apartment but yeah let's
let's see how it goes
oh suit yourself then all right
well then you start tonight at 10 pm
okay i guess i should take a nap until
then
all right i'll see you then i'll give
you the keys and then i'll be on my way
after that so don't be a minute late
is there uh anything like specific do
you have a plan
of of of of tasks that i have to fulfill
in the night
so that i know what i need to do i'll
leave a little list of things for you to
do but thankfully there is a janitor so
you'll mostly be manning the cashier uh
tending to the animals and and that kind
of thing okay sounds good anna thank you
very much
of course no problem now get out
okay okay thank you bye bye bye
bye okay bye bye now she says that she
kind of
opens up like a magazine
and off you go you're out of the shop so
what do you choose to do until it's time
for your job
i think i i guess i am gonna go back and
and take a nap
how what time is it right now uh right
now
it's about 4pm
[Music]
i think i'll go to uh uh
like two hours at the park and then take
a nap at home
all right sounds good so you head on
over to the park and um
today it seems as though there's
actually no one there
oh i was wondering if the uh that dude
from yesterday was gonna be there at all
well not from what you've seen but so
far um go ahead and do a perception
check for me
with composure yes that's three three
difficulty six here we go
all right that's two successes and a
re-roll
all right so you've got two successes so
basically
today is um it's not exactly a sunny day
it's like one of those bright but cloudy
days outside
um the birds are a little active but not
quite as much as you'd like
not much like yesterday unfortunately
um however
the most striking thing is that no one
is really around
at this point um but
that could be a good thing no real
nuisances to worry about and that
strange
guy from the other day is also not
looming in the distance so that's nice
okay well what do you think i take a
little bit of a little bit of time with
the birds until
uh those two hours are over
and yeah i just take some photos snip
snap snap
okay while you're taking those photos um
let's see i'm going to go ahead and have
you do another perception check as um
you're taking these photos and then you
realize that you feel something strange
on your foot
so let's go ahead and roll a perception
which is 3d 10 for use
and uh difficulty is six what's that
strange thing on your foot
wow that's uh three successes see you
immediately look down and notice that
there's a big old snake that just
slithered across your foot
ooh who likes snakes okay google attacks
the snake i think
do you order who to attack the snake or
do you just kind of yeah
all right sounds good i think ooh does
it out of instinct and out of protecting
me
he definitely seems interested in the
snake who definitely wants to go ahead
and grab the snake but it's kind of
awaiting your orders so would you like
to uh
oh yeah i'll tell i'll tell you what for
my six dice is what to do
all right sounds good difficulty for
this will be seven
one all right one success so you tell um
you tell uh to go ahead and attack
and um attack at your orders who tries
to grab the snake
and um ends up kind of dragging the
snake away from you and into the grass
that's about the best um ooh who can do
without getting bitten by this
big old snake because it is a big snake
you've never seen a snake this big
yeah but i wonder what kind of snake it
is if it's poisonous
better not better not get i mean don't
try to eat it or anything
at your order who goes ahead and throws
the snake into the tall grass and you
hear a kind of
slithering noise as it uh it goes away
and leaves you alone
yeah that's the sound that it makes and
leaves scary
yeah forest is full those or even the
park can be full of snakes you guys got
to be careful
never saw one here before all right that
was a bit of a scary so i think i think
i had enough of that i'll go
back home perhaps all right sounds good
so you go ahead and go and take a nap
all right you are nice and well
rested for your shift in fact because
you used your time that way so
that will be helpful if you weren't well
rested you might take a penalty so
that's a good call
all right
[Music]
and now it's time to go to your brand
new job
so you head on over to the um
to the store you remember how to get
there this time or do you
go ahead and roll with an intelligence
to remember
four dices all right and since it's your
second time we'll go ahead and make the
difficulty five which is really isn't
that bad
all right so one two all right so you
got two successes to basically remember
um so you pretty much arrive only one
minute past the required time which
isn't that bad at least not to you
[Music]
one minute one minute late um but as
soon as that one minute is
up um you see the familiar um
watch on waiting at the door and she's
kind of
got like he's given you the stink eye my
dude
i i i arrive never late
i arrive perfectly on time when i want
to arrive
she kind of glares at you and says
well at least you managed to arrive just
don't make a habit out of it
yes it was just
yeah i i i had to mentally prepare
i brought some brought some snacks for
the birds
really as soon as you say that uh
she kind of perks up a little bit of
that and sees that you've gone the extra
mile
um to take care of the birds so she
seems happy about that and says all
right
well i've left you a list of things to
do it's it's on the counter so just make
sure that you uh
you take a look at it and um and just
do what i've written there i'm going to
go catch my
sitcom i'll see you tomorrow
okay make sure that you lock up at about
2 a.m
okay who i am oh that's quite early okay
no problem
all right it's just a four-hour shift
for this first time
oh i'm looking forward to it thank you
very much for giving me this
this this chance yep
and she just walks away
[Music]
so what do you choose to do tiara
i look at the list what i have to do all
right
i'll go ahead and roll a perception
check which is going to be
3d 10. okay
all right let's see what you got
[Music]
okay so it looks like um two successes
because difficulty for perception checks
is six right now
so with two successes um you're able to
basically read the old lady's
handwriting but you know it's kind of
bad
um however you are able to read what is
written there
um there are only three things
actually oh um
the first one just says feed them okay
the second thing says petum easy
the last thing says someone wants a bird
take their money
give them a bird
that sounds very manageable
yeah you get the feeling that she was
she was
kind of trying to um to make it as
clear as possible but you know old old
old ladies you know it's all right it's
natural that kind of things
things slip away over time and you can't
explain things perfect but
thankfully it got transmitted so it's no
problem
all right then i'll start doing my job
like start feeding and petting them
[Music]
sounds good so in order to do let oohoo
sit down
at the counter oh cute that's so
adorable
all right so you go ahead and let uh sit
at the counter
um now go ahead
and let's see in order to do your job
effectively at the shop
uh we're gonna have you roll an animal
can uh roll again
the one that we usually have been doing
the 6d10
however since these are birds that you
don't really know very well we're gonna
make the difficulty seven
all right here we go wow
okay and that's another one
okay so you've got one two three four
successes
that is an exceptional success they love
me
the birds do actually tend to take a
very keen liking to you even the bigger
more british ones that seem like they
might be a little tsundere you know like
cinderella birds and [\h__\h]
yeah they like you too you're kind of
surprised it's kind of
thinking about even buying one yeah well
they seem to like you very much there's
there's a very big uh black raven
um that seems to take a liking to you
and then um
there are also some little blue birds in
a cage uh that trip very excitedly
as you feed them they seem to like you
are an eagle do we have an eagle
would you like to roll perception to
find an eagle i will find an eagle and a
chicken please all right
gotcha we'll do two rules all right
first we'll roll to find eagle
well that's not dash roll three d10
first the eagle and difficulty is six
here we go
you look around for an eagle and oh
okay so that's two successes all right
two successes um and i'm not gonna let
the ones cancel out anything of course
naturally
so you look around and um it takes you a
little bit because you know
the eagle is probably kind of rare um
but you do
actually find in the way back of the
shop
there is a small eagle a baby
yeah baby eagle oh cute
oh i don't know what it's doing all
there in the back seems
a little bit sad definitely a bit lonely
is what you can discern that's the
feeling that you get kind of wanting to
make friends but
you get the feeling that it might be in
the back for a specific reason and
if you recall bird law because you
probably know a little bit about bird
law
totally you get the feeling that there's
a chance
that this particular eagle isn't really
allowed in
allowed to be kept at a pet store in
this country
it seems a little suspicious so
[Music]
i i'm going to
buy it with my first salary once that
comes in
and set it free i have decided tiana has
decided
upon that it's it's a promise i i would
also love to just set it free and then
say like oops and hope the the lady
doesn't notice but
i don't want to get in trouble on my
first day at work
right totally understandable do you
interact with this bird at all
i wonder i will tell it i will tell the
bird that i will set it free
as soon as i get my first salary six
six dices please okay
[Music]
the difficulty for this is going to be
well let's just make it six
one two three okay so the bird
was looking rather downcast and sad and
lonely lifts up its little head
looks at you squints its eyes seems to
fully comprehend what you're saying
pulls back its head and screams
screams it's like a good scream it's
like a happiness scream but
the screech is enough to kind of all the
birds look
and if it wasn't a success they might
kind of freak out but they
they're like what
[Music]
this is a loud one you realize
being set free yeah be like a bird
scream
that kind of thing that's gonna be good
it's all gonna be okay
yeah you can't believe such a big sound
comes out of such a little eagle but
there you go it's a promise you get the
feeling that this eagle has screamed at
you
uh to forge a promise that cannot be
broken
i scream back
[Music]
all right sounds good now would you like
to do anything else
i'm just going to take care of the tasks
sounds good did you want to look for a
chicken i guess so we can check but uh
probably
not going to be chicken here huh all
right well let's find out
curiosity yeah that is quite curious
[Music]
all right let's see two okay uh there
are no chickens here
oh yeah interesting yeah maybe she
should get one
i know right especially if you have an
illegal eagle
yeah and no chickens she should have all
kinds of birds here
all right so you kind of do your tasks
right
um now go ahead and roll perception
because it gets to be about midnight
and um you hear an odd noise
oh growing perception wits
and composure all right free it's just a
noise so we're gonna make the difficulty
seven
all right so you get one success um you
hear something that sounds like a door
opening
the back door and then kind of a
crashing sound
and then you hear someone go well oops
this is that this is a drunkard i'll go
check i go
check all right you go towards the
source of the sound
i'm gonna roll another perception check
for you
and um and it's going to be
difficulty six all right so one success
um there seems to be a lad
um a bit of a striking lad um who has
kind of
tripped over the mop bucket in the back
um seems to be what people might
consider a stereotypically handsome dude
but weirdly enough dressed in like a
janitor outfit
[Music]
whoa sorry about that i made quite a
mess here
hello nice nice to meet you i'm tiara
i'm the new
new new girl in the shop whoa
your name is tiara isn't that like isn't
that like a
oh hold on i got it it's on the tip of
my tongue um a word for like a crown or
something are you a princess
ah well i come from a different country
and my family was
a bit a bit more on the wealthy side but
i
i'm not a princess no no hara oh
i was thinking you're a princess because
it's a common name
[Music]
um so what are you doing here he raises
his eyebrows and is like
oh i was just i was gonna i was gonna
say that like you you look like a
princess because you're real
cute i'm just gonna sorry excuse me hold
on i've lost my manners
i've lost my manners you see i actually
used to be a prince
believe it or not uh-huh okay
do you believe i used to be a prince
come on look at melana
no i just wanted to introduce i wanted
to introduce myself
sorry um
i'm the janitor here my name is victor
most people call me vic
um i work the night shift doing like
janitor stuff and i like to clean a lot
as you can see
he kind of spreads out his arms and you
can look around
and see he's gesturing to the whole shop
but the shop is dirty as [\h__\h] so i mean
clearly he's not doing his job yeah
you're not really doing your job are you
vic also weren't you late
what were you doing it's uh two hours
past midnight
i mean what are you doing listen
princess got duties man i tell you what
there's all kinds of duty to be on time
huh maybe i should tell
our uh our the person who
gives us this job listen listen there's
only
please believe me there's only so much
that i can do in a certain
period of time it's hard to explain my
situation just
look listen it's kind of hot in here
he starts like fanning himself and he's
like can we turn down the lights a
little bit
just like a little i'm not this is me
trying to hit on you this isn't me
trying to hit on you i'm just
listen no it's just it's really hot and
you can see he's visibly like kind of
sweating a little bit
oh maybe you should go
back doing your job otherwise i'm gonna
tell the boss no please don't tell the
boss leader i really need this job man
all right look
i'm just gonna go mop the floor you can
keep doing your thing
have a nice day the shop better be
squeaky clean
at after hour shifts you you got it
yeah sure thing okay there seems to be
it seems like his focus has kind of
shifted on to something else entirely
um but you can't quite tell what it is
would you like to
try and perceive
i guess so because he keeps looking over
your shoulder
it's like my shoulder yeah
all right all right let's do the check i
don't
i want to know what the hell his problem
is why is he not focusing on this jump
when i'm doing it
all right also um you can roll a
perception check anytime that you want
so basically when you want to do
something like a perception just say i
want to roll a perception check
all right okay here we go difficult six
all right with your one success you can
tell that he's looking at your owl
mm-hmm you got a problem with my owlara
huh oh no no no your your owl is very
beautiful
but damn uh i just wanted to say that's
a very
very lovely owl and you're very lucky to
have such a beautiful owl
just letting you know that owls are much
smarter than humans adam if you're
doing some suspicious stuff there then
my owl will be the first one to find out
anna
i'm not suspicious you're suspicious the
way that you
the way that you say ara is real
suspicious
well excuse me as because i'm from
another country what's your problem huh
you have a problem with
no i wasn't trying to no listen uh okay
i'm gonna mob the floor
i'm gonna mop the floor i'm gonna go do
it now
do it all right sorry
[Music]
i'm sorry
he takes the mop and starts mopping the
floor
but there's no water in the bucket so
you're just kind of
throwing the mop around are you kidding
me i'm not here to
to supervise your job this is ridiculous
okay i am uh taking
because i am good at taking pictures i'm
taking a picture of him doing his job
really bad
all right sounds good you take a picture
of him doing his job really badly
he starts playing air guitar on the mop
and like puts in his headphones and
starts rocking out
oh my god yeah that i'm just just gonna
take the picture and
start ignoring him and then i i know
what i'll do once the lady is back the
boss
all right you take a picture of him um
and once you take a picture when you
look at the picture there's like
something weird about him
[Music]
okay okay there we go there we go
roll three d10 to perceive the picture
difficulty sticks all right with two
successes
you notice that in the picture
like for whatever reason um
he seems to be like extremely
like almost you want to stay sickly
looking but just like
kind of kind of pale and weird looking
hmm okay just like just very strange
just not like a person should look but
it's not something that really bothers
you too much
but only in the picture i go i i chat i
look up from my phone and i look at him
and i compare those two things to
picture and him
yeah do i do a check for that the
perception check
sure
all right let's see what you got
[Music]
difficulty six so one success um there's
only a minor difference
you think that it could just be the
shitty lighting of the shop after all
ah i started getting i started getting
suspicious because he wanted also to
have me turn down the lights and his
sweating
[Music]
yeah i
i asked my owl because owls are smarter
than us
if ao chan notices
anything weird about him if if
if if she knows if he knows something
all right so we'll go ahead and roll 60
10 okay
difficulty seven
let's see that's one success
all right so with only one success ooh
hoo just kind of tilts their head
and like lets out just a tiny little
chirp noise and uh
from what you can discern um there's
really nothing that who can tell
personally
[Music]
just seems like a stupid guy
okay uh well um
i do have my trust issues so for the
rest of my shift i try to just
not talk to him and stay away from him
as much as possible
gotcha from what ooh is telling you
i think that all that who can perceive
is like
oh this dude is a northerner for
whatever reason
yeah they really like the cold up there
you know uh-huh
so like i don't know they're used to
they're used to like
some cold [\h__\h] and this place is pretty
hot to be honest and like
the lights don't make it any better you
know it's bright
bright and sweaty even though it's late
at night okay
okay i guess i don't think that much of
it but
it still says i'll be careful
sounds good so the rest of the night
goes pretty normally
i mean the dude doesn't bother you or
anything but it's just doing all kinds
of stupid [\h__\h]
like tries talking to the birds and
starting conversations with them but is
not
doing it right all right i think i'm
gonna go get him fired then
all right sounds good
okay now um your shift is over
it's about 2 am and it's time to close
up shop and not a single customer has
come in
but first shift completed success
all right nice job
very good does the boss come to to pick
up on my shift or there's there's just
no one coming
um so it would appear that you're
supposed to lock up
and then the next day you will surely
meet the uh
the owner again kind of thing okay
walking up
saying goodbye to the burbs all right
sounds good and with that um you kind of
just head home after that
and uh i mean you gotta walk home so
it's like uh
kind of um it's really late might be a
little dangerous
but you go ahead and make your way to
the alleyway
okay well sun is sun is coming up slowly
slowly yeah oh it's 2 am
at 8 00 20 did i say 4 am i feel like it
was 4am
i think you're heading home at about 2 2
30 a.m
oh okay all right now
as you head home however um it seems
just kind of like um
i don't know it's a it's a bit of a late
spooky night
doesn't really feel very safe
no problem i do have by the way i do
have a dangerous sense
and direction sense oh okay cool sounds
good so you'll be able to kind of pick
up when there's
something dangerous going on um
all right so you go ahead and
and take the route home uh that you've
kind of
figured out for yourself but um you know
nothing else
on all right sounds good
because it's dark difficulty is seven
oh wow 3 8. very nice very nice
all right so you kind of make your way
um through the alleyway
and um you don't necessarily
notice anything too strange
at least not at first
walking through the alleyway it's very
clear that this is rather late at night
and no one's around
so naturally um there's a bit of an
eerie feeling in the air
a bit of tension that's always how it
feels at this time of night but um
occasionally you'll hear like a a
wrestling noise
from your right your left
probably just a mouse right something
yeah yeah yeah certainly it's it's fine
surely well
i got i got i got uhu with me so i'll be
fine
right you'll be protected i confidently
walk continue walking
all right sounds good out of the corner
of your eye you feel like you
you spot a strange shape
a figure perhaps but when you turn your
head it's gone
[Music]
um okay
suddenly you feel as though
you might not be the only one here
anymore
i uh i ask
you around to say hello hello anyone
here
no response
um i uh i
i ask who can sense
something
difficulty seven
all right that's one two three successes
um so uh turns their head
in a direction that you hadn't
anticipated um and screeches
as though they've found something but
when you look in that direction
there's no there's nothing immediately
in front of you
[Music]
i say
i i i run away i run i'll start running
towards my
apartment all right you begin running
and uh to run i need you to roll an
athletics and dexterity check
uh next 32 of
let's do four dices four and it's rather
dark
so we're gonna have that be seven
difficulty seven
all right so you've got two successes
all right okay
so you run and run and run and it almost
seems as though the alleyway is
never ending um along the way you step
on some trash
um and then
you realize that um once you've come to
kind of a dead end and you're supposed
to turn
you've stepped on something something
strange something
something squishy frog
yeah all right seven is the difficulty
all right that's pretty good two
successes and then
three successes you look down and
just in time as soon as you've stepped
on it you realize
that you've stepped on a snake again
again
that is now hissing and slithering away
again yeah enough of a snake
uh i continue running i guess
all right you continue running home and
eventually you do make it home
just in time for it to be about let's
say
2 45 or so and it appears that your
neighborhood is
fine nothing suspicious about it but um
that lurking presence
it still feels like it's around you
somehow it's hard to describe
okay i uh i make sure to uh lock
the door and everything properly
and i try to um calm down
all right sounds good
do you go to sleep after this or what do
you choose to do once you've entered
your home
i'm i'm still quite awake so i s
i write in my diary all right
you write about the events of the day
also about the sus things that just
happened outside
good to keep a record and with that
um it's gotten to be about
3 a.m and um for whatever reason even
though
you're safe in your home and whatnot
you've locked all the doors
you can't help but feel like
you're in some kind of danger well i
don't have a dangerous sense yeah
but it's hard to tell really what you
should do about it you just don't
feel well well well i didn't eat dinner
yet so i'm gonna
start cooking some bean soup all right
sounds good
even as you continue
even as you continue your cooking um
your birds seem a little tense more
tense than usual at least
no one's making any kind of excited
noise no one is rushing over to get
dinner
everyone's a little on edge right now
i ask what's wrong maybe my
my animal can all right
difficulty seven
two successes um basically the vibe that
you're getting from your birds is that
they
are kind of maybe reflecting your
emotions or
they could be sensing the same danger
that you are it's kind of hard to tell
which to be honest
um but they also aren't used to you
coming
home this late at night so
could just be something different for
them yeah
i guess so um well
i eat my bean soup all right sounds good
your birds do not actually join you for
the meal unfortunately
they all just kind of seem on edge
ah well i'll stay on
alert as well all right no problem
sounds good it gets to be about
5 a.m or so and it seems like the light
is beginning to kind of
come through the window the light of day
after your first day at the job you're
so
exhausted you kind of
feel like maybe the danger has left you
perhaps okay it's hard to tell for sure
it could just be the sleepiness setting
in but
at this point you're going to need to
make a roll if you want to stay awake
i am going to go to sleep
but i think uh it still wants to stay
awake
all right mama because who is still a
bit worried about mama
okay so you go ahead and you tell you
tell your owl to kind of
stay on the alert for you
okay and you drift off
into a very nice and relaxing sleep
or absolutely deserve because
yeah the exhaustion has kind of made it
so that you
it made it much easier for you to go to
sleep
you close your eyes and you
begin to kind of dream
oh
and cream in your dream
would you like to rule perception
yes because you are in a dream after all
which is technically a whole new scene
difficulty is
eight because this is a dream
one
okay so in the dream
you are about let's say
perhaps 15 years old oh
yeah yes 15 years old and it's a
it's an old old memory
it's almost as though the memory itself
has been
clouded in some kind of sepia tone
filtered in gold from times where
times where things were much simpler
perhaps
simpler times being a child
being young still learning so many
things and
and you recall that um at least at this
time this must be some kind of memory
from what you can tell um because the
memory is still a little foggy and the
dream is still a bit foggy you can't
tell
exact people within your dream um
but you realize that you're holding
some kind of gun maybe like a small one
not like a really intense big gun but
something that you might have been
training with
and at the same time in the other hand
you're holding your golden pendant
and at the same time in that hand
someone is giving you the pendant
is it you really you realize that it's
that memory
from the photo and while you can't
determine an exact
face you hear a voice a voice that says
to you
tiara this is very important this
pendant is very special
and you may not know why for a very long
time
but it's important that you always hold
on to it
and never let anyone take it away from
you not even your owl understand
okay okay i understand
good because someday you'll realize why
it's so important
i promise and at that time i'll join you
again
okay keep it safe anna
[Music]
good well don't worry
i'll still be around for a long time i'm
not going anywhere
trust me oh and someday i'll teach you
how to use it
okay dependent okay
[Music]
but you must hold on to it i'll hold on
not gonna give it to anyone nada
and as soon as you say that the dream
begins to kind of break up a little bit
it begins to kind of almost fall apart
in some kind of strange way oh
almost as though the pieces are
beginning to crack
pieces
it is a very happy dream but
unfortunately all dreams have to end
and as the pieces begin to fall away
uh you hear something that sounds um
akin to some kind of screaming noise
from one of your birds
i wake up immediately and do a
perception check all right
you wake up and do a perception check
because you just woke up
you do have a danger sense and it is
going off right now
100. um because you just woke up
difficulty is going to be seven
all right so you got two successes all
right with these two successes
uh you wake up and realize that your
birds are in a
big frenzy uh they're screeching and
running into each other um almost as
though there's been some kind of scuffle
but when you get to the door it doesn't
seem like it's been broken into or
anything like that
okay it all appears to be fine for the
most part
except i look oh except
there is something missing you're a bird
oh okay my bro your bird ooh
is gone no no that's impossible no
and not only your bird your pendant is
also missing
no what the [\h__\h] you can't do that to me
i can't
no no no no no no no no no no
no no you were having such a restful
sleep
you stayed up so very late you had such
an amazing sleep
you slept right through whatever may
have happened
i panic you panic
um let's just say that you panic real
hardcore and it's bad
um you feel all of your limbs get very
hot
and there are prickles in your hands as
though there's something that you want
to do but you can't
and you realize at this moment you have
no idea where either of those things
could be
at all
well there's still some other birds in
my apartment right mm-hmm
well i will ask them if they if they saw
where uber went or who took them
what what all right sounds good
roll 60 10 difficulty is seven
all right let's see one success
two success oh you're right two
successes three successes okay
so with three successes your birds um
you can't get exact wording out of them
of course but
um it seems to indicate that they are as
shocked as you are
uh they didn't really see a person
all that you know is that um there was
no breaking and entering
here in fact all of the windows are
closed as well
it's almost as though your owl and your
pendant just completely vanished
thin air what
okay uh
but um your birds actually kind of seem
as though they want to uh
look as well okay i sent them looking
all right you open the window and your
birds fly out
birds scatter and go to every corner of
the city
to look for your owl and for my opinion
and for your pendant well the panda is
sparkly and
and uh gold i guess so they're probably
gonna
they should find it they should find it
yes most definitely you tell you tell
them i i also uh ran
outside to try to find uhu and i i
[Music]
all right you yell and scream to try and
find your owl
um but all that you get is your your
landlord comes out and yells at you
hey keep it down
it's 3 p.m i'm trying to sleep i leave
the apartment and run around in the
in the city all right to search for your
owl it's going to be
a wits and investigation check
one dice oh but it's unskilled so
it's going to be um this is a really
important role if you don't get a
success on this
uh then it's almost it's it's a really
bad it's a bad thing you will fail
um and it will be good if you get a one
you're in big trouble
so we can go ahead and chance it but
come on come on all right and the
difficulty for this one
is going to be um let's see you know the
city
decently well and you have some
direction sense let's just go ahead and
make it a six
difficulty six oh no
oh you find nothing you're rigged rigged
game
games you scour the whole city
and even your birds seem to be having a
difficult time but you can find
you can find nothing unfortunately and
it doesn't seem like any of the locals
have seen your bird either they just
seem confused
it's almost as though ooh has vanished
without a trace
no i i rented a burp shop
all right you run to the bird shop and
by the time that your investigation is
done it's about
uh 10 p.m or so when your shift usually
begins
oh well then that's good and then go
there
you can't forget the you can't forget
the part-time job man we gotta pay edith
so you arrive at the shop um
and you're kind of you you know in a
frenzy and whatnot
looking for your owl and the the old
lady kind of appears at front of the
shop and says oh
good you're on time here are the keys
have a good shift
wait wait wait i tell her to wait um
i asked her about the janitor's history
how long he's been here and
and and if she's seen him recently
and what she knows about him oh what was
his
rick dick i can't remember
that's that's the one yes um
that's very mysterious actually only
hired about
two days ago perhaps um does a fantastic
job cleaning i will say it does not
i mean i have i show her the photos
first of all first things first
oh and she looks at the photos oh is he
is he playing the mop like it's an air
guitar
yeah where he was definitely not
cleaning the shop and also he was uh
trying to flirt with me anna and he was
also insulting me because i'm foreign
me of me and my youth i mean well not
that last part
the last part is very bad and i will be
having a chat with him but but for now
just try to play nice while i try and
think of how to deal with it he came
late to his shift i
just want wanna let you know he's also
not here now is he
oh i suppose not i guess i'll have to
give him a call
anyway i'm late for my soap opera so i'm
going to go ahead and give you the keys
and i'll figure out a way to deal with
this okay
now have a good shift okay bye
bye all right uh i
uh well i guess my bird is also not at
the bird shop huh
um so are you talking about uh
yeah unfortunately ooh is not in the
shop and it appears that the other birds
have no idea what's going on so they
can't really help you out unfortunately
but um
do you proceed along with work
no no no i can't
i i ask i ask the the eagle who found
the liking in me
if he can help me out i'll i'll set him
free
for this once uh all right
and i tell him it's about my brother
who's about my uh i need his help
well please all right sounds good we'll
go ahead and do an animal can check
and difficulty is going to be seven
all right you only got one success here
but um
it's enough to kind of almost convince
the eagle
the eagle kind of screams at you a
little bit kind of in protest like
really do i have to help i mean it's
cool i'll be set free and whatever but
like
it's kind of a pain in the ass kind of
thing plus eagle doesn't completely
trust you yet even though you guys have
a deal
so no he doesn't go
well do you let the eagle out of the
cage
um yeah
but i put a little tag on his footsie
all right sounds good you put a little
tag on the foot of the little eagle
um and the eagle hops out of the cage
and kind of just kind of does that
little bird hop you know
on top of the cash register tilts their
head at you
squawks a little bit
doesn't really do anything i asked him
again to do the thing
all right we can do another roll cause
it's gonna need a little convincing
and it might take a bit of time
all right seven difficulty
all right you've got three oh [\h__\h] four
four dice uh four successes
excellent okay let's go all right so
you managed to instruct the eagle who's
finally listening to you you've managed
to get it through to the eagle this is
something important
you really need to go find your owl
however
after this um the eagle kind of uh
begins to take flight and uh speed
through the door
but at this exact time at this moment
it's about
11 pm the eagle immediately crashes into
someone walking through the back door
[\h__\h] jan days oh wow oh man that's a
that's a that's a really strong bird
i say
have you seen my alloy knight
[Music]
adaf the the janitor the janitor kind of
like
it is like very very disgruntled at this
point in time and actually isn't really
fully wearing the janitor outfit
looks like he just got up out of bed
like literally two seconds ago to put on
the outfit
looks very disgruntled he's like huh
wait what
an owl what what do you mean i i don't
oh you mean the one from yesterday
acting a little bit suspicious
mm-hmm yeah my beard from yesterday that
you kept on looking at the whole time
is for some reason gone
oh gee i wouldn't know anything about a
very pretty bird
wow what a shame now
i do a perception check actually
what's gonna happen here is uh it's
gonna be a contested role
so basically basically he's going to
roll to lie to you
and you're going to roll to perceive his
lie oh
okay so what i need you to roll
is i need you to roll um let's see
let's do let's do intelligence at this
point intelligence
and subterfuge what
so is that uh i got one okay three dices
all right that's three um what's the
intelligence oh but your
subterfuge is zero dots so that's gonna
be minus one unskilled so that's two
dice
okay all right now this guy is pretty
easy to see through so i'm gonna go
ahead and make
the difficulty b6 now first this is
ciara's role
okay all right you got one success
now this is victor's role
does he get the same dices uh no he's
got a different character sheet
oh and let's see for him difficulty is
probably gonna be
[Music]
seven
looks good to me
so at this point um while victor is
trying to lie to you
completely you're asking these questions
about about who
and what not um and maybe even find a
feather on his shirt
well interestingly enough it doesn't
seem as though
he is the one that took your l but he
definitely knows something because as
he's trying to explain himself
he gives you this long-winded
explanation i just thought your bird was
was real beautiful and
listen it's it's got nothing to do with
me it's just you know
there are some people that he realizes
that he's kind of
people what people
go i mean listen he says go
that's you go he says god
i mean i just think there are some
people who would really want that but i
didn't touch the bird
well i i i didn't i didn't touch the
bird i didn't
do anything i just watched as things
happen listen i i just watch i don't
really do
i'm really good at watching things kind
of like an owl hahaha
it's a skill that i kind of share with
the owls is that i watch things when
they happen
sometimes i can't help myself when i
just kind of
watch apparently the owl that owl is
kind of special
i don't know i
interrupt him push him against the wall
and then really close get really close
with my face and i'm like
you tell me what the hell you did to my
bird no i don't
or are you gonna get in suit into a lot
of trouble
dude why do you say ara all the time
it's freaking me out man
tell me why the [\h__\h] my birthday
okay okay listen listen listen listen
listen listen listen
i'm listening i've been listening the
whole time and you know the only things
you say is [\h__\h] talking
um okay fine fine
i'll tell you what i know i'll tell you
what i know yeah tell me right now
so the bird's been captured okay
i watched it happen with my own eyes all
right look
i was walking home i was walking home
after the shift just like you and
i followed you i thought that once you
yeah but it was it's just because i got
the feeling something something was
weird okay listen
i can tell when things are going weird
i'm not weird you're the weird one
you're the one that says otta at the end
of all of your sentences
you're the one who's sweating while
you're looking at me it's only because
the lights are really bright right now
okay listen what's your problem with the
lights huh
tell me about that no they're just hot
man
all right so proceed where's uh where's
my bird
there's a house it's an abandoned house
it's not just your bird though
there are a lot of owls the dumbass who
is looking for your bird
can't tell between owls so they took a
bunch of owls
there are a whole lot of them over there
i really hope you know what your bird
looks like because you're gonna have a
tough time
finding that owl and you are going to
bring me there
right now huh wait me
yeah you you i'm gonna follow you who
are you gonna go in that house they
ain't my friends
you are you saw it and you didn't stop
it while my bird was being captured
it is somewhat of your fault as well
so let's go it wasn't supposed to happen
like this
uh i'm just a bystander i promise i'm
just doing janitor stuff trying to make
just trying to make a living man you're
trying to make
[Music]
you're gonna go with me now uh i take
his hand
he's his wrist a girl touching my hand
he's wrong a girl touching my wrist
wow i i grab it really tightly
so that it hurts oh great the more it
hurts the better it is
i slap his face wow thank you
i'm i'm taking
the key from the shop and i slice
s slice his
cheek he said you shut the [\h__\h] up now
and bring me till my bird stop
stop being so such a [\h__\h] idiot
you can't really tell if like the
slicing his cheek really made him upset
or not he is a little shocked
he's like right away ma'am you got it
you got it my damn all right i'll lead
you there
all right finally
all right so you are led to an
old house
now let's go ahead and roll a perception
check for this brand new area
okay tree
yes and it's dark so it'll be seven
difficulty
oh [\h__\h] it's really [\h__\h] dark you can
tell the house is old
i let him do the perception check you
tell him to do a perception check
i tell him to do a perception check out
he says only he slapped me again
[Music]
i punch him on my fist instead
all right to punch him with your fist go
ahead and and roll your strength plus
brawl uh strength
three bro no so two dices all right it's
gonna be two dice here we go
all right difficulty uh difficulty is
gonna be six
uh you kind you you punch him a little
bit he's like ow
question mark yeah do a [\h__\h]
presentation check now
you brought us into this [\h__\h] now you do
you check around
oh fine i'll do the [\h__\h] he says i'll
do the freaking perception check
whatever the [\h__\h] that is all right now
for some reason difficulty for him is
only gonna be six
interesting says all right with two
successes
i don't know it's an old ass house looks
like it isn't being lived in except
they're like two lights on right now
wait no three three [\h__\h] lights it
looks like it's candlelight though
probably not like electric that place
definitely doesn't have water or a
luxury system in there
looks like it's someone's hideout it's
definitely someone's hideout
and you know the person that lives in
there don't you lara no i don't know
i don't associate them but we're we're
kind of the same in a way
it's hard to explain
uh i just i know i'm from business that
i do like i said i'm like a prince and
whatever you don't freaking believe
me
princess have to know a lot of [\h__\h] um
i'll
i'll uh stay about 20 meters away from
the house and you go knock on the door
please and say
you want my bird okay fine
all right oh do i have to
you have to i'm waiting as a prince
you have to monitor don't you once you
say that he kind of perks up a little
bit and it's like well yeah i mean
i i i do want to listen i want to help
you it's just i
i don't want to be the one to do it i'm
just supposed to lay the breadcrumbs for
you man
you know
that has been stolen from me because of
you okay fine listen
uh what you gonna do for me
i push him i push him to walk towards
the door
all right to push him to walk towards
the door use your strength and athletics
uh two and five five dices
all right and difficulty is gonna be
seven all right that's a pretty good
success
wow all right that's a really good
um so he doesn't even really contest to
you to be honest because
you push with great force and he seems
to kind of be like all right fine
whatever fine i'll go to the door
and he goes to the door looks back at
you
looks at the door looks back at you
looks at the door
looks back at you where are you right
now
i'm 20 meters away from the house all
right
he rings the bell shoves his hands into
his pockets looks back and forth oh man
right it's fine uh-huh
no sound at all
on this night
barely even so much as a creaking noise
from the old floorboards as
victor kind of shifts his weight from
foot to foot waiting for something to
happen
and then suddenly before your eyes all
of the lights in the house go out
almost as if the flame has been snuffed
in one fell swoop all the way
disappear i
yell trying to look for him
you you get a reaction all right you
yell for your bird
um do you want to use your bird
communication i will definitely
all right who will recognize my voice
all right and difficulty is gonna be
eight because because
if your bird is in that house it's gonna
be hard for your bird to hear you
here we go one success
with one success however you hear
nothing unfortunately
but you've made quite a loud ruckus
and vic turns back and kind of says be
quiet
you can't just you can't just do
something like that man
you're gonna get us both killed i'm
longer until
i tell him to uh to
try to open the door maybe it's open
anyway
he very slowly reaches for the door
handle
looks back at you and says what are you
gonna do
for me
[Music]
what do you want i don't oh
um dan let's see
how about how about
um oh [\h__\h] i really think about that um
let's see i'll cover for you when you uh
don't come to your shifts
tomorrow oh yeah you are going to get me
fired
yeah can you maybe not do that well
yeah if you managed to get us into the
house and get me my bird yes
all right gotcha
all right i'll i'll go in then i'll go
in
okay here i go here i go i'm going i'm
going in
he turns the knob very slowly
the door creaks open he looks inside
and from what you can see at least from
where you're standing
it's complete darkness
he kind of turns back to look at you and
says
i don't know it seems like there's
nothing in here really and as soon as he
says that
he screams as his body vanishes from the
front porch
the door slams shut and victor is no
longer in your sights
[Music]
i i go to the door
i guess all right you go to the front
door
and before that we're going to take a
five minute break so i can go wash my
hands
okay all right from here on out we've
got about
let's see maybe 30 to 45 minutes left of
session you guys
um so we will we will head towards the
final
chapter of this mystery once we return
okay all right everyone take a little
break
i'm gonna go wash my hands okay oh i i
will stay all right i'm gonna go i'm
gonna
i'm just gonna no not me not you i'm
just gonna i want to descend into
darkness hold on a minute
i wanted i wanted to send stand what
what will happen
next
[Music]
this is scary yeah darkness
what can i do i don't even have weapons
yet oh
yeah okay still have to
come up with something i don't know i
don't know
who could say who could say oh why am i
woo
i'm going to the scene
i'm going to be muted but feel free to
if you want to say anything if you don't
if you want to take a break that's fine
here i go goodbye guys help me
help me me what do i do
we go in there am i going to die i can't
die this is the side of the story i
can't die
let me check the book let me see what's
going to happen
i want my birthday
oh my god my my cat is doing like a
like a roll on the floor like a stretchy
roll
she's like please pat me
pet me i don't know yeah
yeah hi baby hi jonkers
hi baby guys by the way i
i now have free monitors i have uh
i set up my my monitor arm for my
wacom my new wacom tablet and i now for
for the time being because my table is
not as big as i wish it would be
i have it like in portrait uh from it
it's really tall and i got the comments
on there
yeah it was quite a pain in the ass to
set up that
um arm for the tablet for the monitor
it shouldn't have been such a pain
opinion yes where if you said it was
easy
the the the men the men many of the
the thingy also looked super easy it
really wasn't that difficult
but for me any tasks like this are a
pain in the acid seems
uh but it's functioning and i also drew
some stuff on there today
and very was very productive before
the stream mm-hmm i did
two two important tasks that i have been
meaning to do for a while
yeah also i wonder what to eat
afterwards did you guys see him on
twitter in my my curry that i made
yesterday it was way too spicy
i can't eat it like spicy kind of hot
because i said it was too hot to eat
hello jungkook stop
scratching my chair no no no
yeah but now i still have so much left
over i made like more than i
needed on purpose so that i could eat it
for a few days but like
yeah did you hear that
um someone wrote to me on twitter that
is does someone know how to fix this
like afterwards after i already cooked
it
like someone wrote if i put in like
lemon or or
or something like that in it does that
really work
can it will it be less spicy add yogurt
well i already put in
um something called cream fresh while i
was cooking like i put in
the curry paste then i put coconut milk
and then i put cream fresh fresh
which is something my my mom always adds
so that actually already helped but
at pineapples afterwards but like
afterwards hi baby what is it
um add more
okay maybe i'll add another cup of creme
fraiche tomorrow i don't have anything
here now
meow oh hello kelly
i have i have a scent
[Music]
can you eat spicy food i would love to
give you some of my curry because i
made too much curry it's too spicy i
can't eat it oh sure
any day of the week my cat has been very
very
uh attention uh uh uh
grabby oh oh i see i see meow
indeed yes she she climbed up my chest
looking for pets yes once pens
cute you know who also wants pets to
owlette you took away from me kevin
i didn't take hey i didn't take away
that listen that's not how this works
what's your decision to take away my
album let me get it back
hmm but but tiara it was your decision
to stay up late and then
fall asleep
okay don't blame me now
it probably actually really wasn't your
fault or anything like that
but um whoever was doing this was
definitely being kind of crafty and was
definitely waiting for you to sleep at
some point was it was it a vampire
i don't know you still have to find out
that's where we get to the second
part of this grand adventuring game
things are about to heat up
as you head over to the front porch
yeah of this old house and do you
attempt to enter the home
[Music]
yeah all right
i do all right
let's see let's go ahead and
set the tone let's see
we'll go ahead and put you in the uh in
the house
here we are oh [\h__\h] go ahead and roll
perception in this brand new area
yes perception check please all right
it's gonna be a
rule
and since it's rather dark difficulty is
seven
all right so you've got one success here
so this place
well it's old you can tell that um
it hasn't been properly lived in for a
long long time
and it almost seems as though at least
when you
enter no one's there
for whatever reason you just get the
feeling that
is anyone really there are you sure that
victor isn't just playing some kind of
prank on you
um i called for
a call for victory for uhu
all right you call out to them
victor victor you pastor
where are as soon as you
begin calling out um you hear a ruckus
begin
a ruckus of footsteps and yelling
i who is that
is it her is she finally here
we've been waiting for so long my
footsteps steps back i take a few steps
back
towards the door just for security so i
can escape
immediately and i wait there
all right so as you kind of
move back you notice that there's a
strange
rustling noise off in a room to your
right do another perception check
reception check
let's see difficulty is going to be
seven all right one success
with your one success
you hear that the rustling in particular
sounds like cages
clashing together
cages yes cages okay
so i go over to that room because that
must be bird cages
all right as you enter the room with the
cages
um you realize that just as you entered
that room
the people inside the house
have entered the main hall that's right
in front of the door
they don't see you yet you've entered
you've entered the other room correct
with the cages they haven't seen you
they haven't caught are there birds in
the cages
do you do another perception check yeah
there you go all right
difficulty seven oh no
oh you can't tell in the darkness
definitely some kind of creature inside
the cages but you can't see
you're a little too focused on what's
going on in the other room but you see
that there are
four people and they're all carrying
guns
and they look real scary
they haven't noticed you yet but the
tallest
one goes and locks the door
i sneak up try to sneak up
onto one to
perhaps maybe unarm one of them that is
the closest
to me all right
all right okay this is this is this
seems like the the one chance for me to
get a gun so
oh man all right are you going to try
and do it in a
in a sneaky way that um won't alert them
or are you cool with them being alerted
to your presence i'm going to sneak
up in a sneaky way and then well once
i'm close enough
but i definitely will alert them but
that's okay because then i got the gun
hopefully
all right okay sounds good
uh let's see let's go ahead and do
a dexterity plus stealth check
you just want that that is one dice
all right and what difficulty is gonna
be
seven oh yeah it seems about right all
right
here we go
oh wow that is one success i was i was
gonna ask
is this possible to end in a bad ending
the tutorial
i could imagine if your character gets
killed it might be kind of ya bye
no bye well i i succeeded
all right you take uh the closest one to
you
um you see out of the four figures one
is very tall one is very short
and then there's a very well-built um
there's a very well-built one who's got
like a
well they're all wearing hoods it's
really hard to tell they've
they're all wearing tattered hoods but
the one that's very well built has some
strong shoulders
um and has a gun that's that's facing
you
uh out of the back pocket uh and that's
the gun that you
aim for it looks like a pretty cheap
little pistol
but you managed to grab it and uh
you take hold of it and
you can tell that you you haven't quite
alerted them
actually but they definitely feel that
there's something weird going on they're
looking back and forth
and one of them you see one of them is
also
very well built and on the other side
with incredibly
wild and crazy hair that looks like it's
been hair sprayed to [\h__\h] death
um says
[Music]
did you see where the prince went
and the other one of the other one of
the other uh
minions one of the smaller ones the
shirt one says no no no no it's it's
fine it's fine i got him
we got him tied up in the back room
should be okay we will be we'll be ready
to strike when it's time
okay i i because she's definitely here
i can smell her um
i make my way to the back room
all right you're gonna have to roll
stealth again
i don't really have stealth
well let's go ahead and try anyway baby
all right difficulty is going to be
seven again
here we go come on baby
as you make your way back the floor
creaks
ever so slightly
and all four of the figures immediately
turn your way
and look directly at you no no no no
wait no
wait there she is
no no no no wait i take you're looking
rather fine tonight my dear
says the well-built one with the crazy
hair as she approaches you
ever so slowly i use my i use my clothes
or something like that and and pull pull
i'll pull up my gun just
just so that i i'm ready to shoot
whenever whenever okay
you pull out your gun that's fine and
they all immediately pull their guns out
on you there's three guns on you
wow and everyone stops moving i i asked
them
who are you laura
[Music]
all of them kind of look at each other
as though someone's waiting for someone
else to speak
and the well-built woman says well why
don't you speak up i don't know tell her
what we do
the kind of well-built guy that you can
now see has a beard and a mustache
shrugs and says i don't know i didn't
really i don't really prepare a speech
or anything
what are we supposed to tell her
and then the one of the one of the
shorter ones with with the gun says this
is getting boring we should just shoot
her and kill her
[Music]
and then one of the other ones one of
the other minions who's a slightly
taller woman
says wouldn't that be pointless though
she looks rather delicious
and plus maybe she can help us with the
owl you have something very very
important madame well no
probably you have it because you stole
it from me where's my bird
hmm we didn't steal anything yes
you did victor told me oh yeah
oh you mean the dumb ex-prince yeah what
did you do with him
no he doesn't know [\h__\h] he's like tied
up in the bag forget him forget him
we're just gonna ship him back to his
family he'll be in big trouble for
trying to help out
one of you okay listen you're gonna give
me back my burp
i have a [\h__\h] ton of gun skills or
what's up doing strikes loaded for bear
human prey
iron stamina quick draw danish sense
uh you just start listing your merits
yeah
you want to find you you may be more
people than me
but i'm way more skilled than you and i
believe in that i got trained by my
brother
the one and only oh yes we know who your
brother is
your brother is also very important to
all of this they say slowly approaching
you
owl of tea yes very important and as
they say this you're kind of slowly
being backed back into the room full of
cages
and it gets even darker some of the
cages kind of
go in front of you as as you guys kind
of back up into the room
and now there are some bird cages in
between you and
these
you predators we're going to craft a new
world order can you believe it
because our god is sure to rise again
very soon
the time is almost near
god you're talking about but i want you
to give me my birth back
well you need my bird for anyway i don't
oh jeez is the bird the only thing you
want
really yes
and and some more birds perhaps
you can give me all of them all of the
birds you have here what do you need for
them
would you like to do a perception shack
or do you want to depend on some
sentence
do you perhaps have my pendant
is that what you asked them about yeah i
forgot about the pendant stories
i asked them also you don't you have my
pendant as well
as soon as you mention the pendant um
the two leaders kind of
gasp the very well-built
ones they gasp and say do you know where
the pendant is
can you lead us to it because if you can
we'll let your bird go free they're
asking
me uh well it was stolen from me
from you guys if we had the pendant we
wouldn't be having this conversation you
see
huh well my bird and my pendant
were stolen at the same time while i was
sleeping
so i think it has something to do with
one another
you hear at this moment what sounds to
be a shotgun
that's cocking in some kind of way and
you hear a loud
gruff voice coming from the well-built
one that says look we don't have time
for this
listen are you gonna give us that
pendant or what your owl can lead us to
it
so which one is it which owl is it
[Music]
oh you're gonna give me back my elmo all
right all right
well um i think to myself
i am not gonna give them my [\h__\h]
pendant
so you're gonna you're gonna lie
uh no no not necessarily
wait do do i see my my owl now because
it's very dark you're going to need to
roll some kind of check here now it's up
to you depending on how you want to deal
with the situation
you're pretty much being backed into a
corner by these four strangers and hoods
uh they all have guns and they seem like
they are very capable of hurting you
they're talking about weird cold [\h__\h] um
just kind of setting the scene now as
for your owl
we can roll another perception check
here as you are kind of backing up and
you can do at least
one more in this turn before you hit a
wall
i will i just do a perception check all
right yeah
all right and difficulty here is going
to be
seven in the darkness wait what that
what was that a one d
i [\h__\h] up hold on sorry 3d10 that's it
all right
here we go all right you got one success
uh from what you can tell is that in
this room
they're all owls
[Music]
it seems as though all of them have been
captured for some purpose or another
they all seem to look a bit similar to
ooh
if but who is from different place
special owl right exactly
shouldn't i be able to recognize my owl
right but there are many owls in here so
what you'll need to do
is perhaps uh i don't know
[Music]
i am going to uh
say i'm going i'm going to
um mix away that who knows
in twin sentence hopefully without
i mean it's going to be like not a
natural sounding sentence
but will recognize the word okay
um well i i i
could perhaps help you i could also
no to help you i don't i don't know
oh okay i see i see so you're trying to
kind of get your owl's attention
at this point yeah yeah and also just uh
um
um and trying to get some more time
time all right buy some time gotcha okay
so in this case um let's see if you're
trying to buy
time that might be one rule um
a different rule in this case but it's
clever that you're trying to mix in a
word there that your owl knows
so let's see i'll give this to you you
can go ahead and roll
um to buy time i'll let you
i'll let you use your presents
for the um for the initial kind of
trying to buy time
okay express yourself right and then
also animal can at the same time
all right that is eight
dices all right sounds good
go with that however it's going to be
exceedingly difficult
i would say let's go with seven just
because it's the tutorial we'll go with
seven
easy easy eight dices see what we got
here one
two three four five so that's a big
success
all right so you managed to buy yourself
quite a bit of time as it seems as
though
your pursuers have kind of stopped
moving
um because they're noticing that the
owls are are kind of
rustling a bit in their cages beginning
to sway
back and forth and and you can feel as
though
ooh is trying to reach out to you in the
midst of all of these cages
there can only be one a cage off to your
right
okay i know another i shoot at the lock
of the cage with my oh you're gonna
shoot
all right here we go now with your gun
in order to do that you're going to need
to
roll your firearms and let's see
so let's go ahead and do firearms and
strength
five plus three eight all right
it doesn't get anything from my marriage
um let's see that's a lot of merits that
sound like they could do something
let's see i'll go and look at them um i
think maybe
maybe oh it was quick draw i mean with
quickdraw
it basically means you won't have to
like take a turn to do it you just have
your gun
you need to take a turn oh yeah okay so
we'll just go ahead and do this roll
as hd10 and since you're shooting at a
lock
um specifically that's decently far away
from you i am going to make the
difficulty eight
okay here we go
[Music]
all right there's two successes with two
successes
you managed to shoot the lock
and set my outfit yes
your friend uh uh comes barreling out of
the cage
immediately to your side and rests upon
your shoulder
nice yes
so what do those people have to say
well uh let's see how the music has
gotta change
dangerous music
one moment we're just gonna go with this
one for now
oh you banking music yes it's me it's me
all right so as your as your feathered
friend comes barreling out of the cage
um the aggressors kind of seem a bit
shocked
and are saying what did you do that for
hey wait a minute and you hear all of
their guns
[\h__\h] into place and they're they sound
like they're ready for a battle
but there are many cages between you
guys since you did buy yourself some
time
so you have your owl by your side and
four aggressors that are kind of
standing in between the scattered cages
within the room
um and they all seem like they're ready
to punch your lights out
at this point in time i i send
who to the back room to free victory
because he seems to be on my side after
all
oh okay cool sounds good all right
six misses yes all right
all right here we go 6 d10 and
difficulty seven
last period all right
i've got a okay so with those three dice
um you send uhu off to go free victor
and um who seems to immediately get the
picture and flies off and now it's just
you with these four strangers who have
increasingly begun
shouting and um talking their rifles but
you hear that there's something
something kind of feral going on and um
in the midst of the commotion um
one of the um the particularly tall one
um begins kind of like
a jerking in a way that you've never
seen before at least not
for a human being um seems to be kind of
losing control in a sense
um keeps repeating things like i'm so
hungry though
do we have do we have to shoot her it'll
spoil her please
we should we should just give in we
should just give in to our senses
come on i know the rest of you want to
it's been so long after
all i while we're talking i'm trying
while they're distracted by their own
hunger i make my way slowly
back like stepping one step at a time
backwards
all right sounds good you can tell that
they're kind of getting a bit
disoriented but they're definitely hot
on your tail and trying to find their
way to you
so at this point do you have a direction
where you want to head or do you
want to look around or what do you want
to do in this moment because in the next
turn they're probably going to begin
shooting at you
oh well then i'm gonna uh
quickly shoot at one or two
more cages to open them up and let's
make them scatter and
and and you know make this whole thing
into a chaotic situation
oh okay gotcha that sounds like a good
plan um let's see so for your gun
that's going to be eight yes yeah yeah
all right and usually the gun would do
some kind of damage because you're not
rolling to inflict any damage
um we're just gonna go ahead and um
we're just gonna go ahead
and not add a damage modifier just gonna
roll and difficulty is going to be
um eight here we go
all right that's one with one success
you managed to break open
one cage that's about the point and then
while that uh the owl is getting out of
the cage and maybe like flying in front
of their faces
okay okay
you try to run out of the house yeah i
mean i'm trying to escape yeah
all right sounds good
[Music]
all right we're gonna play this for your
escape
all right
okay now the cause of distraction
however
i'm going to have to need you to make
another role in this sense because
you're doing something very calculated
because the birds
they won't just listen to you if you
just shoot the cage open they'll
probably try and flee and not try to
cause much of a commotion
so in this sense you're going to need to
instruct the birds
okay instructing all right try to
try to try to
oh yeah tell them to do [\h__\h] you got it
you yell do [\h__\h] to the birds um and
this is gonna be difficult he ate
because you don't know the birds
all right so that's one success um and
you managed to cause a bit of a
distraction
um with the one bird that you set free
um the cages begin to rustle a bit um
moving back and forth causing a bit of a
commotion um
and about two of the members are kind of
thrown off and actually fall to the
ground
in time for you to kind of escape
however there are still two that are
going to be hot on your tail
so as you manage to try and make an
escape
there are still going to be two
following you and you make your way out
to the main hall
um to realize that victor has also been
freed
um and ooh is joining you at this same
time
and you all meet in the main hall and um
and now it's the two of you and these
two aggressors pointing guns at you
one of them is uh in a state of frenzy
at this exact moment
and you are facing each other now
at this moment in time nope
victor is dang useless at this moment
but he's there with you i guess
all right i'll use him as a human shield
human shield
gotcha all right so
now we're going to do
something called rolling initiative this
is when a battle begins
all right so for this battle
uh let's go to your sheet now rolling
initiative is going to become very
central to uh this game
so go ahead and check your initiative
mod what does that say
initiative where is initiative it's
under flaws and then you go a little
further down and it says initiative mod
all right yours is four all right so
let's roll for you first
in order to roll your initiative it
works slightly different than a normal
roll
so you'll do roll one d10
plus where's my plus sign
um it's something i also never know
where it is god where is the freaking
plus
oh my gosh do i really have to go into
the internet and search plus symbols put
me
next to the l if it's a japanese
keyboard next to the l
yeah it it is but it's like it's not
it's it's only giving me a call
it's fine a copy paste baby all right
one d 10 plus you could put in japanese
type
in pura that's also a good idea
here we go all right here's your
initiative mod your initiative mode is
12.
now for these other characters i will
roll for victor
whose initiative mod is six i'll do a
roll
one d10 plus six
victor is also 12.
now we're going to go ahead and put
mysterious character number one's
initiative mod
mystery character one is roll is going
to row one
d ten plus
seven
[Music]
seven only got an eight nine nine
nine all right and mystery character
number two
rules a one d ten a plus
seven again and this one got 15.
all right so i'm going to go ahead and
look at these character sheets so this
is the turn order okay i'm gonna go
ahead and type it actually
um into the chat box so the turn order
is going to be first
mystery character two
and then after that tiara
yeah he's part of the battle
yeah and then mystery character one
can uhu do something too um let's see
i wouldn't count ooh as a character in
this battle but you can certainly
instruct your owl to do something in
your turn
you can give him an instruction it'll be
like a shared turn thing okay
okay so the first thing that mystery
character two does
um is pull out what looks to be a
revolver and says you shouldn't come
here little lady
you really shouldn't have come here we
didn't need your help we were going to
find it without you
but you really shouldn't have come here
and with that is going to take a shot at
you
now let me see what i had for this
character
this character has a club actually
a revolver and a club but chooses not to
use the revolver at this point in time
probably thinking that they can just
bash you up
so okay taking the club swirls around
the club
in his hands can you try to dodge um
what you can do
is tell me what your defense is in this
moment
defense uh defense you mean my
health for i know i want one oh [\h__\h] one
okay
your defense is one um so in this moment
um and you usually can roll to dodge um
but we're going to go over that at a
different time um
yeah so let's see for your defense it's
one
all right this is gonna be a 5d10
but minus your defense so it's a 4d 10.
oh and difficulties rolling for the
damage
yeah so this is this is to roll to hit
you
if the roll succeeds they will do the
damage
okay with the weapon all right so here
we go
difficulty difficulty is always going to
be six
[Music]
[Applause]
all right so they barely managed to do
some damage to you
um because there's only one success i'm
gonna go ahead and just like home rule
this usually it would do two bashing
damage but i'm only gonna have it do one
bashing damage to you
now on your sheet do you see where it
says health yeah i got a lot of that one
two three four
five six seven eight so on the square
there's some squares underneath the
health bar yes
oh yeah in one of those boxes go ahead
and put
one slash which means you have one point
of bashing damage
oh okay
one okay all right
sounds good now it's your turn what do
you choose to do
i shoot at the same guy alright sounds
good
with this gun uh let's see this gun that
you have stolen
from this one character does two lethal
damage
um so let's see for your gun roll
see what you got for guns
that's going to be a strength plus
firearms which is
five six seven gunslinger specialty
eight
dice and you draw on the same turn
so we're going to go ahead and roll a
dice
can i can i perform a short burst
a short burst it says at one dot can
perform short
for for gunslinger short bursts with
revolvers at three dots can make a
medium burst with
robots but doesn't gain an attack bonus
and five dots blah blah how many do i
have gunslinger
four uh okay so i don't know
i don't know whatever a medium burst is
what is that even
uh but you don't you don't have a
revolver though it's a pistol
oh there's a difference okay
i don't know much about guns yeah it's
okay
it's okay you can still do a pretty good
attack with this it's got to lethal
damage
okay all right so here we go and
difficulty six
okay one two three successes so i would
definitely say that you do the two
lethal damage to
this uh who did you aim at by the way
that's what i should have asked you who
did you aim
the first food that hit me all right
that's mystery character number two
uh you aim and you shoot um however
however even though you feel like you
should have done some damage
this character shakes it off like it's
no problem oh
[\h__\h] yeah
how do i know well i try to escape i
guess from now on
yeah you you can re you realize at this
point that these beings are not exactly
human they are halloween does victor
have anything to say in this situation
yeah victor sure does have something to
say does he say maybe thank you and uh
you know uh
see i have to be honest you should get
out of here
victor rolls to run away nice that's
what victor has to say to you
oh wow victor you asked he says bye
anyway i run with them i hope
all right that can be your next turn
okay all right next up mystery character
one still has to yes right mystery
character one is going to actually
jump at you [\h__\h] [\h__\h] oh
wait no let me see lift
could you have stayed but
oh you can try you can try um mystery
character one is going to jump at you
because
this mystery character seems to be in a
bit of a frenzy and is very very very
hungry
this character is going to roll to jump
at you now you may contest this
uh i will contest it all right so we're
now going to rule a battle
role right now to contest each other so
you're going to need to roll let's see
how about strength in this case
strength and athletics what's your
strength in athletics role
uh three and uh five five dices
five okay
oh let's see and for difficulty we're
just gonna set it at six for this
just for for simplicity's sake all right
at six eight and six that's two
successes now
okay this character is going to roll to
jump at you and they've got 60 10 and it
will be six difficulty for them as well
oh no
oh gosh okay with that one success it's
just enough
to throw you to the ground
fiera uh you are on the ground and it
would appear that this
snarling beast of what once seemed to be
human is now on top of you
and you can see something strange tiara
something that you didn't notice before
when the hood was still on
because now the hood is off tiara
and in front of you you can see a crazed
snarling something
with fangs and skin
so pale you can't even believe this
being is alive but their eyes have
turned completely black
there is nothing human about this being
on top of you
and they want to bite you
can i just shoot at him in the moment
sure okay but first
but first it's now for it's now time for
mystery character number two to make a
move
okay seeing you on the ground
well then that that dude on top of me is
my meat shield now isn't he
oh technically technically
i'm going to go ahead and say that
mystery character is going to
roll to get closer to you at this point
okay let's see they want to kind of
sprint
so we're going to do an athletics and
dexterity check here
maybe let's see for this character
defend difficulty six
all right oh no
all right with one two three successes
mystery character number two is now in
your face
fiara and almost seems as though
they will be able to help their friend
if you don't act quickly
i will try to push him away and run away
all right
sounds good to roll to push to to run
away
we're gonna have another contest to help
me out with uh
distracting them as well please sure
would you like to
would you like to make your move to be
convincing to help you yes it must only
be one at a time well then
then i will instead just try to push and
run
all right gotcha in order to do that
you'll need to use your strength and
athletics free and flat class
all right sounds good you're gonna roll
five
d10 and the difficulty is
six oh wow that's very good wow that is
very good
i think i managed to to to escape
i think you did um but i am going to
have them roll one more time and they
might say
we'll have to do five d10 give them a
little penalty
difficulty stick out here [\h__\h]
all right so with three success so that
means let's see
well they did get three successes and
you got four successes so
you will be able to you will manage to
kind of push and shove
you push and shove the frenzied creature
from off top of you
and they roll to the ground and begin to
snarl
even louder and begin speaking some kind
of language you've never heard before
but just hearing it in your ears
terrifies
something feral something you've never
heard before and your instincts are
screaming at you that you need to get
out of this house
right now right all right well did they
already do the turn basically
they take all of them after me so it's
my turn again
let's see your move was to push
um and you got them off of you
yep victor's gone and so now this
frenzied creature is going to try
one more attack on you
all right let's see
i do actually have me miss miss
come on let's see miss
focus was victor though
uh they're probably going to um let's
see wielding their claws
they're fangs sorry excuse me fangs
wielding their fangs
they lunge at you again
now if you manage to escape from this if
you manage to contest this role
you might be home free okay you can feel
it
at your fingertips this might be your
chance to get out of here i think all
right
now your strength rule your strength and
athletics again
oh five please adam all right
here you go come on difficulty six
alright alright you got three successes
and now they will roll to lunge at you
three i think it's four let's see one
two three four successes correct yo
oh wow they kind of sucked all right
they only got two successes so here's
how the scene plays out
the creature before you who is
definitely no longer anything even close
to human
lunges at you again and you manage to
dodge them just in time
by moving swiftly to the right and as
they lunge at you
they kind of continue running and manage
to bonk themselves into the wall
which begins to kind of snap them out of
their frenzy a bit they shake their head
and try to like pull themselves together
but
very clearly have kind of taken the
focus off of you for this one moment in
time
as you've managed to dodge out of the
way
and now mystery character number two
is going to actually pull out the pistol
and aim at you and fire
boy am i not escaping already um you
just dodged out of the way
but in your next turn you might be able
to run
because you are next so this character
pulls out
their pistol aims directly at you and
says oh well guns are the most effective
way to kill a human
plus i'm not really hungry so we might
as well just end this right here
have you out of our way for good and
they roll
your defense is one but defense does not
apply wait
depends will apply because they got
close to you so just kidding
it will be 5 d10 and
difficulty is 6.
oh geez so they shoot you directly in
your arm and you're going
to take two lethal damage that's okay
that's okay
so on your sheet where you have the
health boxes
yeah do two x's uh
on the on the health dots or on the on
the thing is below the things below
to keep track of how much health you
have two x's okay
all right you have two lethal damage and
it hurts like a mother f word
and you wanna scream out in pain but the
adrenaline the adrenaline is keeping you
from feeling it too much
okay now i'll try to run again
all right so your turn is to try and
escape in order to escape i'll need you
to roll
i'll need you to roll dexterity and
athletics oh
six uh two athletics okay four dices
four dice all right row four d10
and because you have set up a clear path
of getting away
i'll go ahead and make the difficulty
only six
okay here we go
and with two dice uh that should be
enough for you to
uh manage to escape
because thankfully the one good thing
that victor did manage to do after
escaping
was was break through the front door
that was the one thing that he did right
leave the front door wide open for you
useless guy really but you
you run and you run and you run and run
for the hills tiara
owl follows me right of course of course
your trusty owl is always with you
okay and you run and run and run into
the forest as a matter of fact because
the forest is what stands between you
and civilization at this point
through the woods you go into the
darkness
and though your danger sense is still
going on because clearly there are still
things in this forest
after you in some way or another even
though your danger sense is still going
off
the only thing that your mind can think
right now is to get away
to get away from that house that's the
only thing that matters right now
you look i run i run i run
roll again to keep running this time
you'll need to roll your stamina
and athletics uh
[Music]
okay five all right
and let's see make the difficulty seven
because it's dark and it's been a long
freaking night
oh no you trip
oh [\h__\h] you trip and fall and you hurt
yourself
for one bashing damage okay
put one slash into the box
done thankfully your trusty owl is
waiting for you
and even though you can hear footsteps
off in the distance
you still feel like you might be able to
escape
[Music]
i keep on running all right you'll roll
another
stamina check
difficulty seven
right okay that's better
okay with two successes right three
oh three sorry i can't count no problem
one two
three oh four successes one two three
four successes
oh all right let's see
wait it's seven just kidding sorry it's
three it's been a long morning baby
yeah yeah i believe you it's been it's
been quite the morning but
with three successes you managed to keep
running until you feel like your legs
are going to fall off and eventually
eventually the footsteps that were
behind you do
very slowly slowly but surely
begin to disappear into the jungle
and suddenly rather ever so
slowly more so than suddenly you begin
to feel
your sense of danger is slowly beginning
to wither away at this point oh
and you no longer feel like there is an
immediate threat
oh thank god kelly that was scary
but you made but you made it out you
made it to the other side tiara but i
lost my pendant
but i got my owl it would see what time
is it by the way can i do a perception
time check
sure all right by the time that you're
able to kind of pull yourself together
and do a perception check you've made it
outside of the forest
and you roll perception now you're still
a bit a bit in a frenzy so difficulty is
going to be seven
[Music]
you still can't perceive very much
unfortunately only that you're in an
alleyway you're in you know that you're
in an alleyway and oofu is with you and
at that point
to you that's all that really matters
right now
okay just both of you
alone in that alleyway and perches on
your shoulder
and seems to kind of tilt their head at
you and um
[Music]
and seems to be wanting to tell you
something
okay what is it uh-huh
would you like to roll to perceive what
who is trying to tell you i will
i will what up uh
all right this is gonna be sixth
difficulty because ooh is really trying
to communicate something to you
okay all right so with one success
with one success um tells you to wait
there
who jumps off of your shoulder leaps
into the air and then
flies off into the darkness leaving you
alone in the alleyway
with nothing but your thoughts and the
quiet around
scary i try i i wait under
under the lit up area there
under a lamp that one lamp
you wait beneath the one beneath the one
lamp that is shining in this dark
alleyway where nothing appears to be
moving
until you hear a noise
footsteps are approaching oh no
i better be [\h__\h] victor heavy
footsteps
i however do a prescription check there
you go
now that you've kind of had a minute to
gather your clarity we'll make the
difficulty
six all right with one success
you can discern that the footsteps are
not footsteps that you have ever heard
before
it's victor is a monster
if you squint in the darkness you can
see that there is a figure approaching
you but it's not victor
it's that dude from the pike
would you like to roll another
perception check i win
all right
it'll still be six difficulty
with two successes
[Music]
the figure slowly begins to approach you
and you realize
although there is some similarity with
the being that you saw in the park
this isn't the same person at all in
fact this person is
a woman a rather strong looking woman
with a trench coat she has
long brown hair in a ponytail and is
wearing shades
oh she slowly approaches you
[Music]
and gets within about i would say a
decent
bit of space between you and just stops
walking stares directly at you
takes the cigarette from her mouth
stomps it on the ground and says let's
say chad
you look like you've uh seen some [\h__\h]
huh
i i don't trust a person so
i don't answer
hey i'm talking to you
[Music]
you're having some communication
problems i see um yeah you guys are
having a tough time communicating
who you who who am i
um yeah
not really important more importantly i
have a question for you
you saw something didn't you
maybe i did otta saw something strange
right
something that you've never seen before
yeah
none of you are concerned at all well i
think it's very much my concern you see
i'm interested in people like you
how so because i know what you've been
through
simple as that really okay
not just you either know what your
brother's been through as well
my brother you know my brother huh sure
do
everyone knows your brother at least
everyone in this community
where is my brother somewhere far away
by now
probably hiding
could even be in egypt i suppose egypt
okay wow that's where he said he was
going but hey
that was something about two years ago
oh or acquaintances you could say
i mean i suppose you make plenty of
those in this kind of business
you know this kind of business
what is this kind of business arnold
business of knowing you could say
others don't do you know who those
people people things where that
tried to attack me at all
very perceptive of you you could tell
that they weren't people
right something a little strange about
them
they they were like
like monsters precisely
interestingly enough those so-called
monsters
they're a little more common than you'd
think hell you couldn't even really tell
could you
your little janitor friend
i mean he was kind of sure but the world
is full of sus
people correct but we don't really bat
an eye because they seem
human enough yeah you're suspicious too
though i am
maybe a little bit but i think you'll
probably grow a little suspicious with
time as well now that you know uh
things others don't i suppose
okay so what do you know about those
things that attacked me um i know that
they're definitely not done looking for
you
and they definitely know where you live
what do you think i should do adam
well i wouldn't come out of the darkness
just present myself like this if i
didn't want to help you
i will admit i've been watching you for
a while i mean they have too it's just
you know i kind of uh
i've been waiting for a bit longer i
suppose and
i need to take action huh where are you
with the parkour on
the other day
she kind of smiles and says it wasn't
necessarily me but i suppose you could
say
it was an extension of me snake
snake what's snake
no it was a
ah there was a snake
you have to tell me more how many snakes
did you see
meant two snakes in the past two days
so that's how they were tracking you
oops i'm kind of trying to
attack me i guess or i'm
not sure how much a snake can do but
i really should have approached you
earlier sucks you had to find out this
way but uh yeah they wanted what you had
but your owl was really smart i tell you
what
hiding that pendant very smart indeed
i wonder if that's where who went to get
my pendant
i think i know where your owl is but
you're going to need to kind of uh
trust me on this one now i was told to
wait here i'm going to wait for my own
okay suit yourself fine with me
but here's something for you you don't
have to do anything with it
but if you are a little worried about
where things are going to go from here
just go to this address i can't promise
you anything
but i can promise you a possibility
a chance for something different
after all of this a chance to stay safe
and um she hands you a business card
oh it looks like uh i look at the card
yeah sure let's go ahead and roll a
perception check
can i read can you read let's find out
maybe you can difficulty six
all right with two successes very nice
with two successes
there's no name of a person per se but
it looks as though it's a business card
that leads to a bar
that you've never heard of before
when you look up she's gone
just like vanished into the wind
i put the card into my pocket
and continued to wait for while being
very
confused and thinking about the things
that jay chat said
sounds good sounds good all right and
when your bird does return to you ooh
comes back and of course as expected
drops into your hands the phoenix
pendant
thank you i give a whole little little
bread snack that i had in my pocket
ooh who nuzzles you and then eats the
bread snack
and looking at the pendant now it's
almost as though there's this increased
sense of you need to keep that thing
close to you
what kind of hidden secrets it has you
still don't know
but someone wants it and you don't know
why
oh i put it this time not around my neck
because it's too obvious i put it
put it in my bra oh
i sounds good
safe place all right wow
standing in the middle of the alleyway
what do you choose to do
i will go home let's sleep um yep
your house yeah
yeah yeah no ah wait no
ah do i call it a boy i mean it's up to
you man you can go to your house but
you know it's up to you
[Music]
or should i even go to the hospital
is there a hospital i am hurt
wait what time is can i check again the
time let's see it's about 4 a.m
oh and my shift is over yeah that sure
is
the place did i no you sure didn't i'll
i'll go to the boob shop and lock it up
all right you go to the bird shop to
lock it up
roll perception
oh my god wait what the [\h__\h] are you
good
hello kitty wow
we got about five minutes left a session
here ladies and gentlemen
okay okay it's yeah the day-day-day-date
they
um made a a table fall
down oh no babies
no whole table gosh
it's okay okay yeah i have i think i
hope
so i go to the to the shop please
okay we're gonna roll perception it's
starting to get a little bit lighter so
i'll make it six
uh difficulty six
with one success um it's enough for you
to tell actually that the door to the
bird shop is actually open
and when you look inside it looks as
though
all the birds are gone
i guess that's that was my job uh it's
over
over um i i go like welp
uh close close uh i lock everything
and i go home all right
here you lock up for the night maybe
maybe the birds got set free who could
say maybe it's
a happy ending oh gosh and then you go
back to your house
yeah yeah i'll go to my apartment
all right you go to your apartment and
you enter your home
can i can can i save before
can you save uh there are no save points
sadly
it's up to you my dog
and then the cliffhanger and the music
ending music starts in the credits roll
right i mean technically
technically you are correct because once
you make it to the bar
in the light up sign you open up the
door
and you enter that is that where we'll
all meet in the bar
that would be cool see you next time
everyone
so that's the end okay what would have
happened if i would have gone home
well uh i guess you'll have to find out
next time
if you want to go home wait until i make
my way to the bar
well not not necessarily anything can
happen in these games
anything can happen
thank god i went to the bar yeah i mean
perhaps
you know yeah it was pretty dramatic you
might have sustained even more
injuries maybe ended up showing up to
the bar with uh
like five lethal damage or something
like that or you didn't you don't have
to go there at all
but um it's up to you really yeah how
does
like does this just heal automatically
or
how does it yeah it'll take time so
different amounts of damage takes a
certain amount of time to heal
bashing damage for example is the
easiest heel usually within a day or so
lethal is going to take longer maybe a
couple days but we'll get more into
those details a bit later
okay wow wow i didn't think that
you will i thought this was going to be
a happy tutorial session
oh my gosh didn't think you would get
right into business i was scared well
you got you gotta you gotta enter the
world of darkness by um
seeing something kind of spooky after
all didn't even have any weapons but
that was smart smart of me for
to to try to get one from that was a
pretty sick move that you did i will say
that was kind of awesome without dad
i would probably be dead by now yeah you
found it you found a good way to solve
it i will say
i got pretty lucky with your dice most
of the time
very interesting very interesting
session very funny i
also like how you um really made
like all kinds of things matter like my
brother
and then i mean i didn't didn't i didn't
think of the pendant but you did and
you gave it an important role it seems
as well as my boob
yeah i think so i have to say
applause of course for preparing this no
problem i was i was really trying to
work on the plot line and whatnot and
there's still there's still more to come
the story doesn't end there so you'll
hopefully uh it's like one of those um
like cliffhangers at the end
what is the importance of the pendant
where did tiara's brother go
find out sometime in a future episode of
and how is all this connected if it is
connected to the other keys
exactly because who knows what kind of
stories will become interwoven with each
other
yeah oh interesting
yeah welcome to the world of darkness
tiara i hope you enjoy your stay
i don't think so all righty painful and
scary
right well that was something very good
i hope you enjoyed your time it was
certainly fun for me and i i planned
quite a bit so
i'm glad that um that some things uh
most things went pretty good i mean
there were also several
uh different branching paths that i set
up as well
for example like let's see i have what
are the backgrounds do i have there's
like a theater
there's like a cafe you could have gone
through
i would have went to the cafe yeah
exactly they probably would have taken
some different branching paths
so there were there were different
options kind of set up but um but
overall you took the bird shop kind of
thought you might take the bird shop
but it ended up being fun so heck yeah
all right oh that was very fun it must
be very late for you super sorry that it
ran kind of late but
i got really into it no problem
this kind of stuff takes time that's
okay who's the next one by the way
the next is going to be ina i believe
next week yup yup you'll be all
right is going to dive head first into
the world of darkness i wonder what kind
of uh
being what kind of being you
will run into very excited to find out
i am already scared for her
uh yeah it'll be interesting maybe to
say the least
terrifying to say the worst but that's
how it goes in the world of darkness and
um
things are bound to become even more
dark so
please stay tuned to see what happens
next you guys i hope you guys had fun
and um yeah uh just just so that my
view is no tomorrow um
i'm gonna put this a reservation up asap
tomorrow is japanese only stream but you
guys are welcome to watch anyway
and also collab with tamaki and
yamatamaki on
tamaki's son's channel after the
japanese only collab well that will also
be japanese but
i would love to have you guys there
anyway so um just check out
twitter and and the notifications and
everything
all right all right sounds good can't
wait to check it out
thank you thank you kelly for doing this
thank you no problem thank you for being
an awesome player that was very fun
i could tell you had some experience
with role-playing stuff because you kind
of knew what you wanted to do
and you knew what tiara would want to do
and that was kind of dope so
yeah i would still need to get a bit
more into character because i wanted her
to be a bit more
quiet but yeah at the same time
well the not trusting people thing and
all that
has to be a bit more implemented i think
but yeah okay
yeah after a couple after a couple
sessions i'm sure that you'll settle
right into the character and
and i'll also get my uh my storytelling
skills all unrusted and
it'll be fun i'm very excited
thank you being said i guess
yeah you're welcome see you guys soon
i'm going to be collabing with amelia
shortly so
okay guys and in german we stay
avid zane that's right
for watching everyone bye-bye
peace
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
you