[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
hello
[Music]
Baby Bop
I wanted to be outside I noticed I don't
have any anything beachy summery you
know
and I was really in the beachy summary
mood the the closest I can get is this
background but
um
same either
I want some beach or pool background
that would be cool
wink wonk wink wunk wink
Eden is busy making something else for
me right now though
wink long
look at my eyes wink Wong
no beaches no [\h__\h]
got something in my eye
[Laughter]
ah
no beaches
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
I have that in my mind every time
every time
no [\h__\h] meme
[Music]
alien looking person
where is that person from anyway
no [\h__\h] Know Your Meme
Megamind oh
no beat no beaches
he doesn't say it though right
why how wait I genuinely want to know
how did this become
let me read
or Jack the [\h__\h] off
no [\h__\h] refers to a series of memes
based on an image of a character
Megamind
[Music]
originally use the value capture in
December 2021 the image was captioned no
[\h__\h]
and achieved virality online first as a
reaction
with the advertisements I'm getting
it's freaking me out
[Music]
there was like some cats movie
uh uh screenshot on the advertisement
and and it's like if cat girls existed
and something about
cat girls and Cat boys nickel life what
the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] uh
what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] too much what the [\h__\h] on
this website let me get out of here
what the
wow
[Music]
yes
also I could have chosen any color but I
chose blue today
light blue
what do you think
you like it looks good doesn't it
[Music]
I mean it kind of also gives me pajama
Vibes but
I mean not so inaccurate I am in my p no
actually no
pajama what I'm wearing
send
opening Coca-Cola bottles
[Music]
foreign
new jeans
[Music]
I like the Pepsi one more
you watched you watched the I have Pepsi
song
new jeans Coca-Cola
I mean okay as a song as a song yeah
it's a song I would say okay I've I've
song was better
but
well
as a group I prefer new jeans
da da
who says
[Music]
more and more I'm getting like addicted
to new jeans and I actually last night
dreamed of them
like I remember I was at uh I think
don't call me Dusseldorf
and
uh seems like new jeans was like a guest
there
and I was like walking on the street uh
it's like evening after convention where
you know everybody's like eating food
everywhere and I was just like leaving
the convention and on my way to my hotel
apparently and I see some like outside
like you know some restaurants have some
sitting outside uh quite common here so
I saw like a group of people sitting
there and I look over and I see
uh looking at me and she's so cute and
I'm like uh
is new jeans sitting over there having
dinner outside and I go a few more steps
and I see Danielle
and I'm like oh my God the whole group
is there holy [\h__\h] oh wow and I'm like
yeah bye what do I do I don't wanna I
don't wanna disturb them so I just
walked by I didn't say anything
so you you many now okay
yeah
I want this to be real
if only
while I will be the Sixth Man for future
I don't have the Aesthetics that they do
you know they have a specific kind of
aesthetic going on I mean maybe one
could force it by dying their hair dark
um
no but I do think like they have this
whole like super cool historical
no I don't I don't need that I don't
need to be I don't need to be part of
the group they're perfect the way they
are
um
would be cool though if uh one day I
could meet them but it's never gonna
happen never gonna happen never gonna
happen
they're so cute though my God
and I was watching some fan cam not fan
cam actually no a close-up of
um uh I mean I I've watched like all of
them every once in a while mostly I
watch uh like Danielle hidden and honey
uh
yeah close-ups and when you see it's
like a close-up throughout their song
performances of the official camera they
released like for Kpop you know okay let
me explain for Kpop for everybody who
doesn't know Kpop so well like when they
perform on TV you know they they perform
a lot on different music stations when
they release a new song and then
um you know they release on YouTube they
release like the the main performance
but then they some of them also release
other Cuts other like angles like
specific angles for the whole video for
example they will do like a stable One
camera only thing where you can see them
dancing or there's like a specific a
special whatever version or and the
close-ups the close-up version
where they focused on one member only
and they follow them
uh for the whole dance wherever they
move and yeah it's a close-up and and
you can see their face the whole time
and oh my God I mean these girls are so
young right they're like around 15 or
whatever 15 16. I think the youngest
when they debuted was 14.
so they're around that age now and I was
like damn
their skin is so pretty like first of
all their skin is so pretty because
they're still so young
like I see nothing resembling of a
Shiva uh
uh
fold in their skin I forgot the word
yeah but then also should yeah wrinkle
shouldn't they also be in the age of
acne but look no they love acne
because those cameras are so high
quality
so high resolution like 4K I feel like I
would see like even if they have good
makeup on and all that
you know
uh a delighting of course the lightning
is like super super optimized on those
K-pop stages
but still yeah Korea is the like the
country of skincare and I'm guessing
that like you know when you're in an
idol group like that they will like
make sure that your skin is well but if
you can't help it then you can't help it
because no matter how much care you take
of your skin if you have acne
like hormonal or whatever then
[Music]
oh thank you come on then doesn't
necessarily mean that skin care will
always like keep your skin clean
[Music]
so I don't know they must like you know
you can't plastic surgery acne away
not everything is plastic surgery guys
I mean sure you know okay Pop there's
lots of plastic surgery going on but
still like when we're talking about
acting right now
they have really good skin
it's crazy it's crazy
I don't understand how they can have
such good skin I'm really jealous
because they're so young they're like in
the age of getting like a lot of acne
um and then and then what I wanted to
say is like they're also like obviously
super busy because they're like booming
they they debuted what last year and
they're like one the most successful
girl group besides I don't know twice
who's like who who've been around for 10
years they're like really really really
really uh successful right now getting
so many brand deals releasing so many
songs doing so many performances thanks
for the memberships so obviously
that and then they're still going to
school too I would assume so imagine how
stressed out they must be and that
should yeah lack of sleep too like doko
I don't see it in their faces how can
you
how are they
like like from what I know from like
K-pop girl group uh schedules
[Music]
but that if they're looking so good on
stage
they all look so healthy right now new
jeans then makes me hopeful that they're
being treated really well by their
company that they take good care of them
because they're also still like growing
they're 14 15 16 yo
yo
they have to take good care of them
they're still growing so they gotta make
sure that they eat properly you know
that they get enough sleep
yeah they have to they have to they have
to take care of them they're babies
they're natural babies
it just came out of somebody's womb
like yesterday
yeah
[Music]
um
yes okay K-pop be like no that's more
like J-pop straight out of the womb onto
the stage that's more like Shape Up
K-pop isn't uh
for K-pop it starts a bit later
ALS are like oh straight from womb to
stage
um
also because generally like training
time
is like less most of the time
in Japan so instead of training for five
million years they go straight under the
stage after training Maybe
zero to five four zero to four years
maybe but then there's like Kpop
trainees who've been doing it for
I don't know
five six years
more maybe
oh my God I'm already like tangenting so
much I haven't even turned on my PG I
didn't even get to turn on my bgm yet
can you believe it
I brought something tropical to make
everything look a little bit more
tropical here
um
I mean I could probably put something
together that's like kind of static
but moving backgrounds are nice aren't
they
um
I mean
Coca-Cola making me burp please no I'm a
lady
what was I gonna look up oh yeah
I was checked sozani no Saito they
always have like new backgrounds for
thumbnails and stuff and they're all
free to use they're so good
they really make like the best
backgrounds
good stuff
let's say summer themed
[Music]
um
whoa oh they even have a background
themed after like sports event now cute
they have like mountains they have
forests they have grasslands they have
Halloween they have the Frog background
that I used before they have the jazz
bar
they have a rainy background they have a
rainbow okay and here we have the beach
um
oh they're they're so cute
pink Peach no
oh my God Maldives Beach
where'd that go
look
let me let me down
wow
nice nice but it's not moving
just overall like I don't know I have so
many things on my screen
um
about how about
[Music]
let's make everything look nicer
graphic design is my passion
uh-huh
wow wow
[Music]
I feel like I'm making a puzzle
do you like the BTM I just picked it out
before the Stream
that's right
and that would be nice if you guys were
blue instead of green
I'm being a perfectionist right now uh
uh here let me try to make you guys blue
um
[Music]
uh
wait oh what's uh
here
[Music]
um
like a nice
nice blue it'll be the seaweed and
[Music]
that's that's uh
yeah
remember wait which one is members is
sponsor color supposed to be members oh
yeah that's why y'all are green probably
we'll have a darker blue for the members
see what is gray I'm actually not a big
fan of seaweed like if it's like a
little bit sprinkled over like
a dish you know then like they do a lot
in Japanese food and I don't mind
um but
hey
but like for onigiris
if I'm very honest I
if if I actually like for example I I
was given an onigiri to eat as a snack
it wasn't my choice I didn't buy it
um
but because of that you know I kind of I
kind of had to either there was nothing
else to eat
um
and I I yeah because it's kind of like
wrapped around
I took kind of took it off because it's
relatively easy to take it off and just
eat the rice bowl
but I want to become a person who likes
it
I want to
oh
[Music]
yum yum
this is fine
I didn't change much I think I think I
just changed the color
I'm gonna try this
oh sugoi
let's insert the CSS and see how it
changes
say goodbye to the seaweed
write something oh did I break it
oh
oh I kind of oh I kind of broke it
um
wait
ah wait I broke it
[\h__\h]
um
why break things that work but I don't
know why this is broken
this happened before and I really have
no explanation what about now
okay this works
ah much nicer you're blue now
that fits
there's some there's some lighter blue
ones and some darker blue ones
wow
[Music]
foreign
well I am drinking Coca-Cola right now
if you guys want to be my table here
super chat table
or do I need a proper table
there's no no really uh
a no table that really screams vacation
what kind of table says vacation to you
or Beach
because there's nothing really
bamboo
wait
um
uh
white plastic
that's so lame
[Music]
um
table
Beach
team
oh
wow sugoi
not really useful for me but very soon
oh
um
yeah I don't really know how to use this
oh
okay I should I should why am I stalling
wooden table and there is some wooden
table here but it doesn't really test
like speak to me as
vacation table
well a beach table Beach
[Music]
yeah it's fine
it's fine the way it is right
um
too bad I can't have attachments right
now I would put some sunscreen blobs on
my face
I did go to swimming again today I did
go swimming again
this time I counted
my labs
although it's not really an impressive
number yet
and the labs aren't very long either
but I it was like okay not lab like
lengths one pool length
uh but it's pretty short the length is
pretty short of this pool
um yeah one length Okay let's let's not
say Loops because that will make the
number smaller
18.
hey I don't know how many meters
should I count that too next time
25 I want to lose 25 no probably less
than two I don't know
25 meters
I don't know it doesn't feel like 25
meters
it depends it depends sometimes
bigger pool sometimes smaller pool
how many bananas all that I'll bring
some bananas next time
I'll see how long it is
I'm doing my best okay for me it's it's
a good amount because I'm always like
I'm not playing
um
I'm trying to go on at my own pace
a good pace for me
and then I got ice cream again I've been
eating lots of ice cream and going lots
of swimming so I would say
my summer is going very summery so far
um
I know
ice cream is
um
[Music]
over 50 meter pools
15 minutes I've swam in 50 meter pools
but I feel like I swim worse and
it stresses me out because they're so
long
nothing to hold in uh hold on to in
between I like to swim less then hold on
and wait a moment and then swim again
hold on wait a moment swim again Etc
yeah I think the 50 meter pulls they
have a psychological effect on me and of
course also physical
I've noticed it's like too much
and and and also those are like insanely
deep too like they're really deep really
long pools
they scare me
they overwhelm me
um
no there's floating separators too but
even then I don't know it's kind of
scary because also everybody else around
me is just swimming normally
but I'm dying
so I prefer to go to smaller pools where
I can swim smaller loops
and then takes take some small breaks in
between
because like I I I run out of breath and
my arms become noodly
no
within the 50 meters
Sammy tonight
I'm going to swim in Japan ah Yes
actually I was actually thinking oh yeah
I've been going swimming so much these
days but I guess I'm taking a break from
swimming doing my Japan trip but no I I
booked hmm
um
you know one of those days is a bit of a
special day for me
um well and I didn't want to be alone on
that day so I asked Kelly to be with me
and she coincidentally had the whole day
more or less off
so we're gonna have a spa day again
where we can swim too
um
I will swim swim
yeah thank God
thank God
yeah another nice takamuri spa day
yeah
she's always in for a spa day
yeah we'll be good
morning Kelly is always up response yeah
good to have someone like that
unfortunately she lives in a different
country but whenever I am in that
country it's good to have her
hmm
oh but last time when we went I think
she didn't go into the pool
she
oh yeah she
she only
went into the whirlpool with me I think
um
I don't know why
and I don't wait
did she even have a swimsuit with her
because yeah no she didn't
I think she didn't because she's in the
whirlpool also she was just sitting um
like with her legs in the water next to
me
jacuzzi whatever yeah hot tub
um
and then when I was swimming in the
actual pool she was also not she wasn't
fully clothed but duh I think on that
day that's we had several spa days until
now on this day
I think she even forgot or [\h__\h]
purposefully didn't bring it because she
wasn't sure if we were gonna swim let me
tell her let me remind her
this time bring swimsuits
we go and swim
Burpee burp
foreign
wait I have to answer something
wait
okay okay
ah
um I'm just planning some things
don't count me don't tell me Kelly's not
sleeping yet uh
I don't know
she might be
um
no no I don't I don't think Cali is
necessarily still up
that
the back and forth oh that wasn't even
back and forth yeah but the other thing
I was written I was writing to someone
else
um
she's streaming for four hours so she
ought to be
well she see her sleeping or she's awake
doesn't matter
she's uh she's an adult she must make
her own decisions
hmm
and on the other hand
on the other hand somebody like jenma
I keep on telling to sleep
and yet she refuses to
because too much work
um
Ma
[Music]
um
you're managing my own manager for real
for real
Gemma needs an assistant I mean
I think you know it's a whole team of
people so they help each other I think I
was ideally
say my right thing to me
[Laughter]
gossip
what time is it oh my God in Japan it's
like what two
three a.m or so
yeah
almost 3 A.M why is it so hot in my room
[\h__\h]
oh well I mean who am I to speak I
normally am a wink at 3am but but but
at least I also get a lot of sleep
yeah
I do get a lot of sleep
China is awake all the time
did you change I didn't change anything
it's just this room this room gets
really hot
and I don't know no
stuffy stuffy
whoa the burpees
okay superchato timer guys
[Music]
foreign
after I read one more message where I
got pinged
ah okay yeah
Jenna pings me some reminders you know
when I said yesterday I think I'm I got
pretty much all my deadlines done
except one thing that I still have to
re-record and I did that after the
stream yesterday
it turns out no
I still have
like one more deadline but shouldn't be
it's not too much work
it's not a lot of work
it's just another little voice recording
you're done with your deadlines
it turns out
um you know what you know what's best
son
don't you think
now you're gonna be like but you're my
son all right that would be actually
really cute if you say that
[Applause]
[Music]
well
well well well well
something like that
now I'm the Sun
your son
you are my father
yeah
yay
this works nicely
I am your son
you like this color on me I think it
works really well right now with the
blue background
um I don't think the yellow works all
the time it depends on what background
you know matching
[Music]
oh pudding you're still alive ah
hello
it's the Sun
praise the praise the Sun
ah okay I will sit like a relatively
normal person image
half Goblin
okay so here we go we continue with
Munda Gallery just again okay
yeah thanks for always being the bright
Phoenix oh
I am especially bright today now
you're always so sweet to us as well as
having some I mean so many amazing
talents you're a great inspiration to me
and many other kfp thank you for being
the best Aussie
and do my best I try to be a good Aussie
to everybody
why should I installed for because it
would have been an hour [\h__\h] one
[Music]
anyway yeah thank you so much fun down
I saw you in the in the video uh from
wiki wiki
I watched the the Yago video or like I
skipped a little bit through it watched
some parts more than others
but I still remember you Moon duck so I
recognized you hey
um it's okay man I think it's very
understandable to have shaky hands in a
situation like that but you know what I
was thinking when I was watching that
um
because like well damn like he had a
lion
of
tens and tens and maybe like a hundred
of people
um waiting to get a picture and maybe a
signature with him right it looked like
a huge line judging by the video
uh yeah I was surprised that he was
giving everybody
an audience the time of his day
I was really surprised because like it's
not like he has to and it's not like
he's an idol and it's not like he has to
keep up a certain
you know like
how to say you know he's not he's not a
talent or anything
you know he doesn't have to do this
to
you know
do fan service or to improve his
popularity or whatever he doesn't need
that but still he did that so big
respect for that but at the same time
if I
judge that correctly by seeing what I
saw and I only saw like a video
um
like he would take a picture and he
would sign something and that's it
there's no chit chat in between so that
reminded me of yeah okay he's not an
idol
because if I if I want
there in that situation oh sorry I
switched because of reasons it was
accident
if I was there
I would like you know I would talk to
everybody like at least a couple words
and be like oh my God thank you so much
for coming and smile and ah you know
so while he was doing like total Idol
things
I still I still can see like oh
yeah he's our boss not not the idol
I need to give him meet and greet advice
nah just kidding but I'm really really
like surprised he did that so this is
amazing yeah yeah
San Diego
although it's on more than Yago I think
understands a good amount of English
I think
doesn't yango also study English
actively more or less
I think it's on some English is better
but still I think yako speaks like or
understands okay English
I think
but yeah it looked like everybody was
well behaved yeah
yeah yeah
I'm just I'm just like shocked
seeing how popular Yago is
and how many people just like wow
try
to get an audience with him
at the same time made me realize how
popular her whole life itself is
like seeing it in situations like that
and in reality is just once again
something that makes you realize bam
the scale
um
yeah
I I hope he wasn't too exhausted after
all of that though because like I know
how meet and greets how exhausting they
can get
like I've done like two hour meet and
greets where I talk and chit chat a lot
with
um you guys
two hours or long I mean dokomi for
example I figured it was longer and
without a break
um
how how long
how long was it because like if he
didn't really talk with the people then
I guess it was faster
you didn't talk much but he took photos
and all that and wrote signatures and
all that right so he must have
been a little bit exhausted
two hours Jacob was there for 30.
other people say he was there longer
after the pictures it was 30 minutes oh
after the big photo session
eh you're telling me he did that line of
like a over 100 people
at least it looked like that in half an
hour
is that is that possible
after the line oh why are you cutting
all those important parts I want to know
the whole amount of time that he spent
there
if anybody knows
two hours damn
Peak efficiency
well Japanese businessman knows how to
be peakly efficient American
is
nanka
foreign
I wonder how you felt
if he felt like oh yes this is so nice
maybe I should be a YouTuber maybe maybe
instead of being behind the scenes maybe
I want to be in front of the scenes now
because this actually feels so good
he looked like he was loving it really
I wonder if that gave him like a little
bit of a taste
or a desire for more
I mean
I feel like in Japan when he shows up
somewhere
it's a bit more like tame like the
people freak out yeah but there's not so
much like tattoo touching Direction I
think
foreign
I think he was like extra nice to you
guys because it was overseas and he was
like adjusting to the open welcoming
free Vibe of America
that you guys also gave to him
you were extra nice to him too nice to
dance to me huh
foreign
took a photo with him and stuff
one on one
oh
okay you guys who did that
were you nervous yes or no
were you [\h__\h] your pants yes or no
no that's in law okay
no you were very happy I snuck no not
really
no
you guys want
not nervous about meaning Yago
even I was nervous when I first met Yago
you little shits
[Laughter]
yeah I can't use my boss but you guys
idolize him somehow though then you
should also be nervous
funny
um
we pay him technically why would we be
nervous
well I mean
what the [\h__\h] okay whatever
[Laughter]
huh
you would be nervous around me thank you
but you guys keep on saying you would be
nervous for meet and greet with me
so you guys are not nervous about Yago
but you guys are nervous about meet and
greet with me
[Music]
[Laughter]
hmm
okay okay
I understand I understand
my face hurts
oh
stop
okay shut up I need to read super chats
Mundo thank you holy
holy [\h__\h]
one two wait wow 15.
Mamma Mia is that two Reds and one pinky
no wait
one two three four five one red one two
three four five one red one two a two
red three Reds
eh yeah
uh
oh my God
I'm sure you already know what will
happen next that is correct is this that
is
is that time where was I uh to bring out
a new set of orange carpet now we're in
this time I kept it very short it got
longer
it surely wasn't this long last time I
can't believe it's already been first
birthday okay and my God the time goes
so fast speaking of third we also soon
to have Third Year Anniversary soon and
then follow up by three year membership
Marcus wow membership I can't read
anymore what the [\h__\h] is wrong with me
but I understand
it was really nice to see so many
wonderful artworks and great video
message to tencho it really shows that
you built a pretty damn good Community
around you I want to say I'm quite
impressed to see such a supportive
community that look out yes you you you
you impressed I'm impressed man
you guys who show supportive so sweet
I'm looking forward to tosumachi and
event you have prepared for first
birthday stream which was like almost
nothing but thank you also wonder what
kind of cake are you going to bake this
time a [\h__\h] cake it was real [\h__\h] I I
want to eat better cake
I'm sure you have heard many many times
but always thank you for wonderful
stream and being who you are you have
been always caring being sweet to
everyone and always consider it to other
people I'm glad you're I'm glad I'm
proud to have you as well
to have you as my fan you know
like ah
I know not everybody can be like really
like super super super
like open and crazy about their support
you know in person
um and that's fine but like Jindal
you're so over the top
and I feel like you make up for like the
cave
um but let's say there's a room of
of uh one person per fandom but you
don't only make up one person you make
up for five people you know what I mean
you're worth five kfp
at least
so like you're strong you have a strong
presence and with the strong presence
that gives kfp a strong presence too
yeah so I'm I'm happy to have you
I don't know it's General even here
right now hearing my high praises
doesn't seem to be here I think
ah there you are
uh wait yeah and for the middle very
much I hope I can get them did you
I think you did didn't you well so
there's another thing I should congrat
you about then other than birthday
congrats on First and concert in L.A
would you know where do you normally
live I see you everywhere
I mean give me just the country or the
continent doesn't matter but I I I I see
we're everywhere it's confusing me L.A
whoa
sick wow what a place to live
wow well then that was actually really
convenient for you huh
that was super convenient for you
the first time as a whole group yeah
we got our own thing you know it may
have not been like super huge in terms
of like venue and all that but you know
we have to take some steps first and and
this is like the the first step and it's
really cool that we got our own thing
another one I would see the day where
there will be free whole concert in
overseas but glad that I was lucky
enough to be in the venues to see live
oh yeah
um
I'm happy for you don't speak for
everyone but I say it was quite
successful first and for your concert
I'm hoping to see more in the future as
always whenever the goal might be don't
give up remember they are always care if
we next to you to give you the support
that you need I hope you enjoy the rest
of the day and everything goes well
thank you
[Music]
foreign
ly I'm learning uh past tense in Korean
soil
uh
what soil
um
yeah
is it too difficult
it's okay last time when when she when
my teacher first taught me it was
a bit overwhelming but
um today we repeated uh a lot of it and
continued and I think it's it's okay
um
do you know shorter version of
come some uh
[Music]
or
comms.com
I don't know what you mean
um
Korean browser let's go
[Music]
random fact did you guys know
I learned this today did you guys know
Korea
introduced the five day work and school
week
in 2004
until then
it was six days
that is that's pretty recent
what the [\h__\h]
and Japan is all right also five now I
think I don't know when they changed it
but
and here we are pushing for four right
in Europe we are pushing for four days
right now
hmm
yeah that's so that's so short
uh so recent I mean 2004 that's so
recent
well we are yeah I mean at least in
Austria I keep on hearing it
sometimes I see articles where it's like
uh
uh politicians one two
want to uh do for a week work week a
four day work week
um
or something like that
I've seen them
[Music]
yeah but I don't know if that means that
you will work longer days I wouldn't
really want to work more than eight
hours per day if I was in a normal job
um eight hours always felt enough for me
uh
I don't know I think five days generally
is fine
maybe maybe what would be nice instead
of that is more vacation days although
we already have lots of occasions I
talked about it with my Korean teacher
who told me you know like she lived in
America and she said when she came from
Korea to America she was surprised by
the amount of vacation days because uh I
think she said it was two weeks that she
got in America two two weeks of vacation
days
and and then in Korea it was like barely
anything maybe like
maximum one week per year
um Japan is like around the same to
and then she came to Europe and she was
shocked because you get even more
vacation days in Europe than you do in
America
[Laughter]
so now she says she doesn't want to live
in Korea anymore
she's lived in a lot of places and she
knows a lot of languages
and I think she's a great example to
tell the world
how great Europe is
yeah we have we have good labor laws and
stuff yeah
and
[Music]
Americans though
I know
vacation
is
[Music]
I have 20 locations for my job but
that's really really good here
yeah yeah
not even the days off the benefits are
what really gets me yeah yeah good
benefits
[Music]
like I don't know maybe
I don't know I don't know what like what
but yeah Healthcare I don't know uh
I don't know what you get it's so normal
for me
Healthcare and and uh
wait there was another thing I had in my
mind
ah yeah if you get pregnant
I think afterwards you get a lot of time
off maybe more more than other places
Maybe
maybe and
I've been calling sick for work and you
always get some money
always get some money apparently that's
no not normal everywhere I am shook head
what do you mean you can't just
carelessly call in for work sick for
work what do you mean I don't understand
I mean yeah you have to go to a doctor
here but it's easy to cook to convince a
doctor that you can't go to work
it's very easy you just say I got a
headache and then they'll arrive write
you uh an okay
yeah paid sick days endless endless paid
sick days
you know what I've seen a lot of my
colleagues do in the past I didn't have
to do it because I was working part-time
anyway so I had plenty of days off so I
saw my colleagues doing like their they
had a vacation upcoming
and but they would take like two sick
days before because they're just like
they're like whatever I don't care
anymore I want to I want my vacation to
start early
um
yeah and and coincidentally a lot of
sick days were always on Fridays or oh
whenever whenever they had days off like
in the week
wherever it was on the weekend or uh
during the week
days would always like kind of happen
the day before or the day after
their weekends
hmm
give themselves along a weekend hmm
it's a coincidence right
oh yeah and uh one of my friends
um she's currently on vacation
officially from her work
she got vacation days but she's sick
right now
so you know what happens then
she gets a sick note from her doctor
and those vacation days she gets back
because those are now sick days
and she can use the vacation days
another time or get them paid out
smart
I don't even think I even thought of
doing that before when I got sick during
a vacation
um
yeah good stuff
sacrification classification double
vacation oh she's a genius double
vacation
apparently you guys know how I was like
considering doing a hair removal off
collab
thank you
Dana just told me that somebody else who
asked about wanting to do that in the
studio was turned down
uh apparently the reason is kind of like
what if there's residue because
everybody uses the studio or something
like that because it's kind of I guess
dirty but no
no
it's not bad during what
ah I mean if you wax you know with the
sheets it just stays on the sheet
and I don't know I mean yeah with an
epilator that like pulls it out if you
if you just do it over over a table then
it will just stay on the table
[Laughter]
don't do it we can't I don't want to do
it in the studio because I can't do it
in the hotel I want a proper setup you
know
but I gave them several ideas of what we
could do
I'm having Wayne and mermaid shoes right
now
yeah I mean we'll clean up whatever mess
we made I think it's really funny reason
it's not funny
oh man
[Music]
how much you don't like
I don't know yet what it's gonna be
it's gonna be fun nevertheless still
could sell the residue no why
oh I guess that was something I talked
about on my member stream okay
change music because it's too repetitive
ah thank you
thank you my God
I went on a lot of tangents so let me go
back to
topic not low thank you
and happy birthday boss the concert was
amazing thank you not Lou
you know what I always wanted to ask you
I don't know if you're here right now
maybe can I ask you a question
if you're not Lou then what are you
what can I do what can I uh call you
if you're not Luke
hmm
but I don't think you are here right now
I don't see you in the chat
anything but Luke ah
muzukashi difficult
[Music]
no no anyway thank you for the rest
now next time when if you watch this
archive feel free to give me an answer
sometime soon
thank you thank you soon for the
surprise
bread dog I don't like that it doesn't
roll off the tongue
[Music]
I'll be at work when this
goes live
uh sorry but still happy birthday you
deserve all the love you're getting
today I hope you have an amazing day
thank you for inspiring me to become a
better person of myself a better version
of myself please accept this gift with
the blood of our enemies oh yes
beautiful red colored blood I love it
thank you
so
which enemies did you take down can I
get a list of names I need to take them
off
of my list
all of them all of them
wow
good work
thank you so much for the support
please continue supporting the wow
thank you for the rest of the chat
happy birthday thank you love you my
Aussie really I'm your Aussie thank you
if I'm your student you are my chicken
then kitchen for the love and support
thank you
sadly I will be vlogging today but I
want to wish you a very happy birthday
regardless it is still kind of crazy to
me that this is already the third
birthday of my beloved tension where the
heck did the time going on
anyway happy birthday attention thank
you
yeah it's uh
crazy how how fast time goes by Indie
down
yeah
especially this month because of like so
many trips
no wait
when did I leave Japan I don't know why
I wasn't
when did I go to Japan
last time was it the end of June
yeah but I'm spending July
traveling a lot so
that makes time pass by so fast
week by week I'm somewhere else
um
it's crazy
I hope we can take it a little bit more
slow and easy in August
so yeah
thank you though
um
[Music]
yeah chicken nugget thank you for all
the pinky happy birthday Kiana recently
your memorable performances in connect
the world and your important role in
whole summer
ah important important was I important
I mean I guess we're being chosen in the
MB and all that I think we were all
important all of all of the ones
who were there but
um
yeah I'm one of the whole life English
girlyos
really cool I was so so so so so so
happy and honored to be chosen I've said
this before but I I really really mean
it
for the cemented how proud I am of you
you made this year be amazing and I'm
already hyped for your album and for
your birthday live when they come yay
thank you thank you thank you
really excited ah I mean this will still
be a long time to go
album first So currently I am only a
hype for the album
this is so far away the 3D birthday that
I I don't feel any hype towards it only
um disappointment but yeah egg
yeah we'll make it hype
yeah yeah yeah fighter
thank you for your sweet words yay Jeff
star thank you for the pinky happy
birthday thank you thank you shut up
Windows did you hear that
question happy birthday to you Tom
medium so loud it was one's attention
oh
subscribe
[Music]
foreign
let's get this forever
come on foreign
[Music]
foreign
I appreciate that
no don't transition age before any of
that
now you have to learn German just
kidding read red bear translation looks
very accurate
yeah it looks accurate I am prob
foreign
you just want to be
you just want to be difficult
yeah let's chat you can scroll up and
then you can scroll back down
basically he said he made Austrian
kaiserschmann the Austrian dessert and I
said I've never made it myself it's kind
of difficult and you gotta use your
mommy's or your grandma's recipe
because that will make it extra good
don't just take a recipe from the
internet you have to use Family Recipe
those are the best
and and I've been hoping to randomly
receive kaisersman by summoning it
so I've had like applesauce in my fridge
for eternity
because that's kind of what you eat with
the kaisersman
yeah I've been manifesting it
but so far no kaisersman yeah Loki
hoping that Mama told you will make for
me
but she's far away
um
yeah because there's no other way I'll
be eating that applesauce
it's not applesauce by the way wherever
it's Apple
moose because this is The Alchemist
episode
Apple moose
because in German it's also not
applesauce it's Apple moose
shouldn't it be apple Mouse
mashed apples yeah something like that
it's not just sauce
you know it's like I think it has the
consistency of like baby foods that's
like with apples
um
m-u-s
I put m-u-s
I think it's just mus
C
Les
nah
Nah by composing Club is
purified apples
Apple puree
anyway
chat
come on Happy Birthday I've been feeling
a bond with you recently um
just like you I'll soon be going home
after an extended time in Japan oh
I remember how tough it was for you I'll
be watching your streams as always to
stay positive thanks for always being
here for us where are you are you here
in the chat
talk to me about it
I want to know more
how was your trip because you say you've
been feeling a connection
but I hope you had a good time in Japan
for me it was you know
kind of rough in the first half year
and not here I guess maybe you're still
in Japan so you're still living by
Japanese time zone
oh well maybe you see the Vlog if you do
then maybe tell me sometime
I would be curious I want to hear if it
went well
but I wish you all the best and big otsu
on that Japan stay I hope you learned
some Japanese I hope you made some nice
experiences
and maybe some friends maybe maybe maybe
um
thanks for the support and continue
watching
[Applause]
actually yeah recently
I think I didn't see Titi that often is
it just me
but suddenly a triple Tai Chi
I think I've been seeing a little bit
less of Tai Chi
Tai Chi are you okay
[Music]
are you busy or did you lose interest in
me hopefully you're just busy
you won't answer me anyway because I
have super chats off and you never type
in chat
our only means of communicating are
turned off right now
man
feels bad man
Batman
[Music]
don't forget about me typing okay thank
you for saying hi again and wish me
happy birthday
hope you've been doing well
tattoo we miss you okay happy we miss
you
[Music]
yeah thank you could send the free
members to pass but
Tai Chi is
a big big Chad
I feel like he does not allow himself to
have any other communication with me
except for
except for super chance
yeah there's no other way
um
he maybe feels like he has to
um thank me for the entertainment
which I appreciate hmm
hope I'll see you again taiji
[\h__\h]
right Ghana wait did I give that
Checkers I think I did but here's one
more
thank you
oh
member Yoko song
thanks for the rainbow wow
happy birthday attention and also
congrats for the concert you were
amazing I can't wait to see you perform
during the whole summer with Paula Tony
love you thank you
can't wait either
exciting
I hope this will be an era the start of
an era
of more and more holiday activities
hmm
I hope they you know it it is supported
by the official side now
so I hope they will do stuff with us
like with umizi
um
yeah we'll do our best
support us
as a group so that there will be more
and more of us
and please wait a little longer
to see some holidays
I'm excited let's go regano thank you
I think
I'll be organizing uh another big Horror
Story collab before the
concert
sometime in early or August Maybe
I think
yeah I'll try to get something going
play some game
too right yeah I mean I I think for us
again I'll just like throw it in the
group and be like hey hey hey reminder
should we maybe do a collab and then
I'll leave the planning to someone else
because usually you know like in usakan
senpai
are very like active and outspoken
and they like to
plan things too
so it doesn't have to be me
thankfully
we have right the new one two switches
out
the group one
hmm
yeah but
don't you have to be in the same room
for that one still though
yeah today she was surprised to see you
eat with a chopstick
wait did she say that to me in person
because that sounds kind of familiar
somebody said that to me
hmm
[Music]
I actually
we were eating
oh yeah non-japanese people can use it
yeah yeah I mean it's pretty common
overseas yeah
you said it during the Elena Club oh
yeah yeah there was this location where
we were eating
I think where wait wait
oh I remember we were eating Bento
during the official program that I was
part of
he probably is thinking of the time we
went with Shabu
yeah because I don't think I ate with
putang Senpai any other time
yeah I guess yeah I was using Chopsticks
there
um
in some Japanese restaurants they don't
really even
have anything but Chopsticks I mean if
you ask they might
bring you something from the kitchen
that's normally not used
um
eating salad with chopsticks honestly
honestly it's pretty pretty you seem
pretty useful I must say
hmm
sometimes I have a I have a harder time
eating certain foods with normal cutlery
then with chopsticks
they're pretty useful with certain foods
guys
um
[Music]
yeah no no spaghetti pasta still
uh I would not use chopsticks if it's
like spaghetti
I always use Fork and Spoon
but if it's like penne like shorter
noodles
then I don't mind eating with chopsticks
but in
I I I've been to like pasta restaurants
in Japan and they don't make you eat
with chopsticks don't worry they usually
bring you normal Cutlery
um
Ramen is not pasta no
I mean I see why you would want to put
it in the same category but no
this sounds funny but I think what you
mean also is like basically
uh you will maybe stir the Miso soup for
example a little bit with chopsticks
before you drink it and then you drink
out of the bowl
and then you pick the little tofu pieces
and all that out of the soup with the
Chopsticks and eat it
foreign
as well as Ramen but I I
always use a combination of spoon and
chopsticks for ramen
eating a lot of [\h__\h] hell okay let's
get out of this
hell of a topic because it's leading to
Cursed
cursed abdominations
of tangents let me turn on the lights
look
wow I'm so far away
um
Abomination I guess
[Laughter]
[Applause]
no I'm not drinking the corner with a
straw
but I will eat a fruit candy now because
I think the Coca-Cola is not good for my
throat
okay
oh
[Music]
thank you wow
no I don't want to read the master
because then you don't have proof that I
read them so I'm reading them now
um
[Music]
oh yeah that was sad
my row is never never at fault
sometimes it's a little bit
um
weird
feels like closure episodes yeah
[Music]
um
I don't remember poodles
[Music]
foreign
yeah hopefully
hopefully this is beautiful woman on my
screen
[Music]
thank you thank God
thank you soon wow season two over
let's go
[Music]
sorry these days I just yawned so much
that was the stretch yeah
I can't finish my yawns [\h__\h]
eh
what do you mean moon dog why do you
need to write some wrongs
okay it's just y'all
no I never watched The Witcher
maybe I will sometime
you got the info wrong I
I oh my God
every time I'm updating you guys but I I
watched a little bit more about Mrs
May's one yes I found another one or two
Grandma girls actors again
crazy [\h__\h]
hmm
this time it was Kirk
Kirk from gamble girls found him in
marvelous Mrs maisel which is actually
so much fun because he's so funny in
Gilmore Girls
yeah he was still funny and marvelous
Mrs maisel but just got a pretty small
row a short one for one episode
and that episode was so weird like
like generally marvelous Mrs maisel is
telling a story
in a I guess linear way
and then this one episode suddenly
was doing like a mix of
uh you know showing you the future
from like 10 years later
or five here yeah showing in the future
from five years later and then ten years
later and then going back to five years
and then going back to the actual
current time and then going back to the
10 years one again and then going to the
current time and then five he's gonna
end so on
they kept on like switching for this
just just one episode kind of like
the future was throwing back
you know that they were like doing
like a roast
to one of the characters like a big
roast shell it was a big dinner show
where they celebrated the success of one
of the characters and in order to show
how she got so successful
they're throwing back to five years ago
but this whole thing is like 10 years
later of the actual timeline
and so on so it's like whoa why suddenly
it was well done but it just felt like a
like a final episode or or like um
I don't know
the end of an era but it wasn't really
because like I checked the episodes and
they're still like three four episodes
left so I really wonder why they did
that so suddenly in the middle of the
season that's just what's confusing me
because the episode afterwards is
completely back to normal again to the
usual no they did not reuse old scenes
it's all new
no and they've never done this before in
in how many seasons five seasons
it's kind of the first time where they
did that
I'm so confused hmm
mysterious but it was interesting
definitely to see the the future already
it's like
giving you
a teaser of how this season might end
and apparently I think it's last season
I think they announced that there will
be no more
so I'm sad anyway
thank you.com
we will look but Brave Bird thank you
Sharon oh just like me that's like just
me
thank you for the pinky thank you I wish
you the best birthday possible I want to
thank you for all the work you put
yourself through
uh couldn't have found a better boss to
work in two for long thank you I love
you too
question shall we try to deep fry cake
for the cake free menu seems like our Mo
what's ammo
monthly
[Music]
um
modus operandi what the [\h__\h] is that why
do you all know it
why do you all know
the meaning of this word
never heard it before
what the [\h__\h]
meh
we don't use that in German
is how we do things
[Music]
[Laughter]
no
no that's disgusting
nah
nah please no
no need for that hmm
no no what you can deprive is
Apple
apples and bananas all those fruits I
think you can fry it on its own
but don't fry
the creamy whipped creamy cake please
ew
disgusting
if
if you chat disgusts me
ew
I don't want to look at you guys anymore
ew anyway thank you so much
cute little bird
you do look so proud in that picture I'm
proud of you too
[Music]
cornless
happy birthday
thank you thank you for being there
ready for celebrating with me and
celebrating me thank you
hope to see you again
thank you
oh deep fried ice cream I tried that
before
that was pretty good
um
I'm already looking at you again I'm
already looking
see what
that's different
I don't know
I can't resist you yeah you guys are so
sexy
I can't resist you
I've got the hearts for you
that was those juicy fries
[Music]
that fluffy butt
hmm
shake it shake it [\h__\h] just shake it
shake it shake it like a Polaroid
picture
I told you to shake it
shake that butt for me
I want to see it jiggle
wonderful
um
satisfying
[Laughter]
wow
yes you please me
[Music]
now into the fryer with you hoppity hop
Hoppity Boppity
you are now
my dinner
Bobby
and where was I oh yeah
you guys can't see it
[Music]
more Australian money
happy birthday again thank you it's been
a delight watching your videos over
these years for the longest time I was a
lurker and I sadly appreciated you
because I've always been a shy girl but
this year I came out of my shell and
announced myself as a proud coffee
should have done it earlier
hmm
thank you where's the other one here
all right
see it okay it's the best decision I
ever made I've been able to meet so many
friends because of Tanto you've created
a wonderful Community when you have days
where you feel down on yourself please
remember how much of a positive impact
you have on QP
costume I'm so happy
happy that you actually wear those here
also won
I was free
you labeled it too but it was free
hmm
cutting yourself
short or whatever how you saying
no that's not the right word I think
was that it selling that's it selling
yourself short but yeah thank you so
much I'm glad to have you around I'm
glad that you decided that now is the
time for you to shine as the chicken
that you are
to come out of the chicken closet
finally admit to yourself
that you are kfp
you're now you were before and you were
forever being and hopefully this will be
an inspiration to other lurkers
to also come out of the chicken closet
coming out of the coop
I'd clock with it yeah
beautiful
um yeah I hope it's been fun for you and
kfp and I hope that you will continue
supporting me for a long time thank you
gospel my cute ticking
thank you for the big support
wow what
thank you
soon thank you for picking and happy
birthday
wow a certified Chef yo this this Super
Chat
is so
so feminine there's so many emojis
and the number one bus in give me wow
remember we love you and are proud of
you hope you have a wonderful birthday
I'm sure you're going to make amazingly
delicious cake no
I appreciate that but let's be honest
I'm not gonna I'm not gonna [\h__\h] you
guys
it was very mid
um
but that was just my first one I'll be
I'll be making more in the future and I
will
improve myself yeah
hopefully
yeah or I'll just stay with normal food
thank you though thank you for believing
in me thank you
[Music]
continue to believe in me don't don't
don't forget about me
foreign
if I don't like coconut I'm gonna not
gonna go out of my way to make a coconut
tart what the [\h__\h]
is
um
[Music]
thank you
questions
no I don't like coconut
Studio round face
you're the heart and soul of myth you
take my sad song and make it better oh
I'm dying thank you for everything Joel
yeah
it's it's quite special too
we called something like that thank you
wow
I I I I
I'm honored thank you
for you sweet words
means a lot to me thank you Studio Rob
yeah
happy birthday thank you I'm excited for
another wow I filled year ahead yes me
too
I want many many more years as many as
possible please
I hope we can go on for a long time
but I need you guys to Stay With Me
okay
need you guys to Stay With Me
I'll be here for you you'll be here for
me okay
good
thank you hey
stay
Thank you Logan I hope you will stay
around as well I'll see you hopefully
again attendance check one year later
okay or in between as well though thank
you
question
we had fun dancing
[Music]
um
thank you for the pinky happy birthday
gravy show
I saw
find
it's kind of funny when we talk about
gravy or when I use Gravy to make jokes
because
gravy
such an American thing
or a North American thing
you guys love gravy so much and yeah
it's fine
but
it's not so important here in Austria
so it's just funny to me I just I just
thought
you guys can relate to it
yeah
I like I mean I don't taste like gravy
but
I feel like what wait well don't you
guys like you know in in North America
don't you guys have it for like
all kinds of foods I feel like you guys
kind of overuse gravy
um yeah
don't you even have it at KFC wait a KFC
what do you eat the gravy with
wow wow
just another kfp and nabita maybe you
two are in sync
your two comments are like next to each
other for me and you've rubbed almost
the same thing and it comes out as
almost the same length you guys just
have to decide whether or not you write
potatoes with OE or or just oh
then you would be perfectly in sync
you can dip Chicken in it
mashed potatoes and chicken but mostly
mashed potatoes
I now give
ah [\h__\h]
are you guys sick of the bgm yet
sometimes when I focus on it I I get
sick of it
no
good
okay
I'll leave it alone longer
um
anyway thank you
you know what
I'll give gravy another chance I should
eat gravy again somewhere somehow if
it's available somewhere somehow
thank you
thank you coffee Gremlin Nathan cotton
thanks for the pinky when cover says no
more fruity Bob's fine I'll bake my own
cake
yeah
life's not [\h__\h] Fair
it's not [\h__\h] Fair
I wish I'd get another chance at the
let the body got jumped
but it's okay uh I feel like sometimes
well it looks pretty decent it makes me
wonder the other times where it's not
decent are they using my old model like
I'm confused like in the um you know
kanado made the video uh
the little video where I was standing in
front of the crowd
in America
uh during the doing the cheering
yeah there it looks like I have some
decent cake
and then also the video he made the
teaser video
for the summer theme song
I know I feel like I look like I got
good cake there too
but that was also a good angle
but not only there
I don't know I feel like trying to
infiltrate and delete the old model yeah
I actually wrote to management the other
day I'm like
it's confusing me too at this point like
sometimes I'm not sure that they use the
old or the new model so let's just make
very sure as incidents still be
happening as we've seen with MMD of my
old model being uploaded or used for
something just making extra sure can you
guys just like completely delete it from
the like database that we use
so that it doesn't get used anymore
or just make double sure
I I don't always want to like add
recordings and all that
you know we we always like do a model
check we check if everything's okay
and I always look at my butt first
things first I always turn around and I
look at my butt and everybody else
around me looks at me as if I'm some
weirdo as if as if I'm some like
like butt obsessed
like horny horny erotic chicken
but that's not the thing I'm checking it
because it happens too often that my old
model is being used and then I look at
it really closely but then everybody
looks at me so weirdly that I feel like
I can't look at my butt too close
um
so I don't know it's it's hard to tell
sometimes from like my point of view
yeah I hope it doesn't happen anymore
old butt bye bye I don't want to see you
again
I like to sound this is the wrong booty
um
I wonder if this is my new butt
probably 90 of the people there never
know what I'm talking about
what does she mean you butt is she going
on about again oh there's gaijins
my kindness
foreign
it's important to me it's important to
kfp should be important to everybody
it's an international matter
okay of importance
of
um
but is a matter of utmost importance
worldwide internationally
even the U.N talks about it daily
grave matter what do you mean a gravy
matter
but most importantly
you amuse me
continuing
game is real thank you
under that TV ah we on it oh
wow wait it's the first time I
understand like you know this part
wow
is under
hmm
wow
foreign
[Music]
I don't know
foreign
[Music]
no I wasn't showing him out I was
actually like
I said that even just by this I kind of
get the feeling that their English must
be good
even though it's not using like
difficult words or whatever but the fact
that they're using verb day
and wow wow like that I don't know it
just gives me this feeling that their
English is actually decent
I know you know
it feels like they know what they're
doing and not just copy pasting off of a
translator
let's go it is
[Music]
[Applause]
happy birthday
here's to another great year for kfb
your performance at connect the world
was divine
exquisite
stream Sparks your energy in one form
personality continues to be an
inspiration as well keep up the great
work thank you
I like how people still use that I
should make another one something like
that
um oh
once I have my motion capture suit
um
I think the possibilities are endless
aren't they
yeah
[Music]
no it won't even be sweaty because it's
your spell core straps
straps
yum
endless potential
yeah
Freddy
I mean people already asked for or like
put it out there as an idea before when
I just had home for a day normal home
Freddy I don't know I like the charm of
the Simplicity of mzu the way it is
right now
make one
no I don't always want it to be 3D you
know I think I should say the latest uh
it's been over here what the [\h__\h]
what do you want
maybe I'll make one today
what do we want
what's an animal like a rape
Raptor
there's no way that Raptors actually
sound like my love
Raptor sound
I think I can risk
for [\h__\h] Raptor sounds to have the
sound on here but
Velociraptor sound
well how do you even know what they
sounded like
it's from a million years ago
ah
that's an advertisement
and we don't
we don't know Jurassic Park doesn't know
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
huh
that's not what I sound like
I hate you
ah what the [\h__\h]
you want to apologize huh
wait what
I'm totally I don't really look angry do
I I look kind of more like well my angry
face is free is weird right now
more like disappointed I'm not
disappointed don't I look disappointed
well I am disappointed right now
well did my angry face and Freddy change
whoa
well the eye shape changes so much it's
crazy
hey I like this one
anyway that looks really weird
if you did a bear or maybe a seal
hold bear
what does a bear sound like
the one that we want Pilar bear black
bear brown bear
whatever
Grizzly Bear Grizzly Bear
that sounds like a saw going through a
chunk of wood
foreign
that sounds
terrifying
that sounds like a cat
trying to throw up a furball
[Music]
but that was really extreme sounds like
this
hmm
[Music]
oh my God
no I don't really like to make these
sounds
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
ing
spots
[Applause]
it's so good with subtitles
I think
the [\h__\h]
um
[Music]
oh
cute
[Music]
[Laughter]
there's just being cute closing its eyes
like hmm
and then it goes like
leg
[Laughter]
oh my God
let's blink
s
that's um
not ideal to impersonate
hmm
I think about it I'll think about it
more
energy
[Laughter]
[Music]
let
that
how is that
how is that that how is that how how how
man
how how
why why is it so bad at being a seal
um
try harder
and what was I
did I read this
yeah I think I did
why did I go on the tangent
why did I
why did I go on attention
I don't understand what's wrong with me
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you for the support I don't know
why I changed topics so
so drastically but thank you for
listening always to my stupid words
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
actually I want to read this I want to
try reading this yeah
[Music]
foreign
I mean I probably heard it before
is it from pomonida
apogo what form is Pogo
[Music]
I never heard Pogo before
oh that's watching well then I know I
know I know watching I know the word for
it but I didn't know this form Pogo
[Music]
yeah
but what form is that
[Music]
uh
watching oh
um
[Music]
foreign
take care of Health
take care of your body
only
ah mom buddy
quantity take care Oh Long going oh
[Music]
nice
uh
[Music]
foreign
next I mean you have so much time to
think about what to do next year
um I think you should just wear kiwawa
cosplay again because you look so cute
as me I want to see more of you as me
and
maybe maybe take some
like professional looking photos with
cosplay photographer so wear me at a uh
cosplay event in Japan
only if you want though like no pressure
I'm just giving you ideas you know you
don't have to
you know maybe you prefer to just wear
me
in in your own privacy private time
yeah and maybe I don't know maybe bake a
cake with my face on it porch red cake
yes where my skin
hmm
but anyway you also can do just the same
thing and I would be happy too
yeah as long as you're still around I'm
happy thank you
I also love you in connect the world
watching your life was amazing thank you
thank you wow
damn wait
you guys
make sure to you know watch it at least
one more time before you before the
archive runs out but if John just did a
watch along right
like yesterday
I was surprised
hmm
that's so sweet did you guys watch with
her
yeah she said she left Sparks
she probably said about every song
but thank you later
he called me koawa oh that makes me
happy
it's hard to get Japanese people to also
call me that but I'm happy when they do
when they understand that that's my
nickname
gets it
she was singing along sweet cute I
should take each of the karaoke again
because my songs I checked last time I
was in karaoke I I couldn't like sing it
because you know I didn't want it to be
too obvious you know
to leak outside or so but I saw I saw a
lot of my songs around there there's so
many so many whole life songs on
Japanese karaoke machines now
it's really cool
yeah
mixed with all the other songs of the
world
anyway Thank You Phantom Kudos I'm happy
you were watching it thank you for the
support hopefully we can do it again
right it would be nice
oh my God there's so many bees
breathtaking Blossom and now Bulldogs
barely have blossoming bouquet of
bright-eyed brilliant bubbly and bold
benevolence oh sheesh basically
bargaining for a blast of a b-day bye
bye love you
why what what compelled you to
use be so many
[Music]
did you watch the Bee Movie before
writing this to me or while writing this
to me
or did you just start out with Bazinga
and then birthday blessings and then you
were feeling like a b flow
[Music]
[Laughter]
and you're like maybe I should keep this
going
so many bees by accident maybe I should
make it on purpose
thank you though I say all of this
applies to me 100
um
Betty Betty
thank you for
baby birds
please
be kfb
whatever
[Music]
they made a buzz of their Super Chat yep
MK
Ang oh
second one there we go the final puzzle
piece
the second one is for present while who
is working very hard every day to
provide us with the best experience we
could ever ask for right now she is
baking a cake and being very cute while
doing so wait isn't she actually reading
super chats now Chip Kim brain horde oh
it's it's a
trading with Wawa
sure dingers Schrodinger
wait see Schrodinger is a good example
of how to pronounce uh because there's
an uh in Schrodinger as well how do you
guys say it do you say it correctly hmm
you got his own Wawa I also got his own
cat yeah
he's got all the things he needs
[Music]
how do Americans and others
sorry I always I always were
um
I always say Americans but it's not like
only Americans watch me
how do English-speaking people say
Schrodinger
you should say Schrodinger's cat
[Music]
foreign
yeah
ah
my underarm hurts from swimming she's oh
[\h__\h] oh wow when I in that position I
really notice it
um I swam a lot
Schrodinger it's not destroying her
though it's flirting um
I am feeling it a little bit well not
like a burn but more like weak
butter
today
[Music]
ah
hey oh no
so young
[Music]
um
yeah swimming
[Music]
motion more most most
Motel Mateo
[Music]
yeah
um fighting and I say I can't swim well
um
foreign
but here I used my past tense in the
first sentence the thing I just learned
Soo Young
and
[Music]
when I say I say I swim Young
and past tense is
and
[Music]
always polite for him
both are polite for him
it comes from
Hada Hada the verb to do something and
so young is swim
or
is imperative I think that's what it's
called
past tense
[Music]
different form of the past tense
yeah I know I know I know what's up
hey
so young
[Music]
Young on
ES
swimming is really lots of fun
[Music]
I want to do Korean study stream so I
can repeat all of my
um
Korean yeah great exercise
in Japanese is undo and then Korean is
undong and then today we learned some
words about family and again
in family in Japanese is kazuku and in
Korean is kajok
it's so funny there's so many similar
words and the whole time I have to hold
myself back from saying ah
it's like in Japanese
um
so many similarities but you know what
pissed me off today
like okay
also has uh like two counting systems
but they only really use one for
everything
you know have you heard hifumi before
that's the their other accounting system
but they don't really use it you don't
have to learn it you can just go by with
each Nissan scene Etc
but Korean so first of all they have two
counting systems
[Music]
foreign and they have the Ile Samsung oh
and depending on what you're counting
you use something else
but then the thing that I've been told
today
she told me how to count age
uh
and and and and
it was it was using the the I think the
Le sums are all system
right no wait maybe it was Hannah does
it
the thing is
normally
shut up normally it's like
uh numbers
after 10
you know 20 30 40
Etc is just like easy
you know the number
then you need like free and then you add
10 and that's 30.
but
foreign
uh
it was it only for age I'm not sure
because I just learned about it today no
I think it's not only for age just like
we've found out those sad numbers
uh
after 10 every 10th 20 30 40 50 60 70 80
90 until 100
is like completely different there's no
system
it's completely different everything
sounds completely different there's
there's just like it's a completely new
word
[Music]
and uh
let me let me tell you
is it here
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
uh
ah no
Aya here
okay
10 is your so it goes hanado said
I hope y'all
in the other system it's early samsa or
York ship
and then in the other system it's from
ship like if you want to say 20 it's
Egypt because e is two and ship is ten
if you want to say 30 it's uh
it's just a Sam ship and then Starship
or ship yorkship Joseph pirate ship
cruise ship until 100 which is pick
[Music]
um
okay then
Korean counting system
second their second counting system
10 is your
20 is
sumul
30 is certain
40 is mahoon
50 is swim
60s yes soon
is
yodun
90 is ahun
[Music]
like
it makes no sense
there is no like repetition
there is no
nothing that I don't know
it's easy for a foreigner to hatch onto
you know
yeah there's no pattern
I learned that today and my teacher was
like until next time you learned all of
this okay and this and there's also
other things besides this
like all the family name member names
like
[Music]
um
uh
hello
the grand Papa I don't know
and
oh and then you know in Korean
uh sister and brother older sister older
brother
from the point of view of a girl is
different than from the point of view of
a boy
for me it's uh
oppa and
only
but from the point of view if I was a
boy
I would say to my older brother
uh something I forgot I think was Hume
or something like that
and then for the older sister I think
they say uh
but younger siblings are the same
hmm
for some reason I thought
that also that guys also say opened only
hmm foreign
no no that's just like whatever you want
to call your mom's like Mom and Mother
and Mommy that kind of difference
um
yeah you guys call Korean Bros maybe
call me Kiana Kiana
or whatever the younger one was
um
there's so many
she also wants me to learn all the
uncles and and aunts which are also all
different depending from which family
side they come and whatever and if
they're the oldest uh uncle or the
youngest uncle but then for aunts they
don't make that differentiation
apparently maybe because women are like
whatever
but there's like separate words for
uncles wherever they're the oldest uncle
or the middle or the or the youngest
uncle
um
but and also oh there's also a word for
I mean okay that's I think maybe normal
but there's a word for
uh the the wife that's married to the
uncle
whatever yeah yeah what if there's only
one Uncle then that's just that one
uncle
but if you have more than one then and
they're they're not just uncles they're
you call them directly
by that specific knit word yeah ah
that will be fun to learn
very fun
on on Jimmy
it's
not fun
[Music]
I don't think I'll really ever use it
though cause like
I don't
no I don't have Korean uncles or aunts
so well I don't think Elsa I never would
talk about my uncles and aunts to
anybody
uh in Korean I think so I don't think
I'll ever need the words in Korean
I don't want to use it to show off
wait I don't even know in Japanese Where
do I
the word for uncle and Aunt wait wait do
I do I know
oh
yeah
I guess I know that
aunt
yeah
that's that's
um hmm
it's very similar to ubasan there's a
difference between obasan and obasan
now yeah I've heard those words before
no
oh no
[Music]
what about cousin what's cousin in
Japanese
foreign
[Music]
for everybody
I don't think they have a million
different words
hmm
yeah the thing is though that in in
Japanese like if you talk to uh like an
older older older older lady
you and you don't know her name it
doesn't happen that you want to maybe
call her
foreign
to old old lady
uh
yeah so I guess for your stuff like that
I would probably in Korean also want to
use that
um
okay okay I give up
I need to learn this but not like all
the different like oldest cousin and all
that I just I just need uncle
and I need I need auntie and I need
older brother older sister and all those
yeah yeah yeah but I don't need the
specifications I think
okay back on topic
[Music]
see I already started reading super
chats my gym Kim brain hordes too
um
thank you Ultima
thank you so much
for the sweet sweet Super Chat
Schrodinger's Wawa thanks you very much
wow thank you soon Domino
thank you
the red super chat happy birthday to the
radiant sun
again I am the Sun
your son
of KFC it's hard to believe how much
happiness you've given us over these
years your performance at the concert
showed how much of an Entertainer you
are and you just keep stunning us every
day
whoa I'm stun locking you
thank you Empress long may you reign
thank you I hope so I hope you guys will
be
my chimpkins for a long time I will
continue to stun lock you and and and
spawn Camp you
hmm
beautiful I love how we communicate
[Music]
thank you
wow
so sweet you know how to be Charming
calling me the sun and the empress damn
thank you
foreign
thank you for the pinky happy birthday
thank you thank you very sweet of you
very kind I'm present thank you
thank you
Alita that's kind of nostalgic I haven't
seen your name in a while I think
and you are you here now
are you still actively watching or and
just not sending ah you are just not
sending super chats as often anymore
which is totally fine or I was gonna ask
are you just not watching me as often
anymore
but you're here
thank you Alita what's up are you doing
well are you Genki
it's nice to see you thank you had a big
move recently but I'm back oh well that
sounds like almost like a like country
over another country kind of move
I hope it all went well
oh there's a cat entering my room and
guess who it is
free
two
what
it's movie poofy
YouTube she was like lying on the table
and on all the like printed out
Korean documents the whole time today
while we were doing the lesson
um
so cute
and she's very annoying yeah she woke me
like recently in a couple of few days
recently she's been waking me up at like
eight
for uh breakfast which was fine but
suddenly today she woke me up before 6am
and I'm like what the [\h__\h] girl
I thought we were getting better at this
uh
um
I I tested out not giving her food
anymore at night two two to three days
ago and it didn't result in immediately
at least not in her waking me up earlier
again
she she still like woke me woke me up
for breakfast at the same time but today
she woke me up much earlier than usual
what the [\h__\h]
um
don't know what her issue is I didn't
set up the robot yet whatever it doesn't
matter now because you know I'll be in
Japan but and my brother doesn't get
really annoyed or bothered by the cats
in any way because he wakes up early
um so for now it doesn't matter
when I'm back from all my trips and I
got some more time
then I'll set it up yeah
[Music]
rotori is an early bird
yeah yeah he is
but yeah for work anyway Alita thank you
did I miss any more comments from you
like answers to what I was asking
scrolling up Scrolls girls
girls
oh that's it I can't scroll any higher
oh well don't think so ah you got
distracted by my cat or by your own cats
oh she's just chilling on the floor now
she's staying in the room that's kind of
rare
she didn't even properly look at me I
just saw her ears move at my
foreign
[Music]
I love them
and I got immediately distracted by my
own cat yeah
uh my cat no country move just half a
way across my current country right to
my hometown oh
Hometown huh that's nice I wonder what
made you decide to move back to your
hometown
like sometimes I I in the past I thought
about one day
maybe moving back to my hometown would
be nice
and
yeah I don't think it's a bad idea but I
don't know we'll see how life goes
um
[Music]
instant of exploring the country decided
to return tomorrow that's nice I don't
like that
no after seeing other places you also
appreciate your usual your old home more
your old scenery and everything
the the fact that you know it so well
makes them more comfortable
um
there's it's just different
[Music]
I wish you all the best
yeah
yeah yeah yeah so I hope I'll see more
of you now
yeah I better be seeing more of you
this is this is not really Japanese so
let me transplant it because
it is a donation in something else so I
think
I'm gonna translate this
um
or Japanese
maybe I don't know but thank you for the
Super Chat
and pets
um
[Music]
too low
what's that on your picture
there's a lot going on your picture Skye
Duncan Jesse Lockhart thank you for the
pinky
Happy Spirit Journey formation
anniversary what
Kiana in congrats on the wonderful what
the wonderful concert so cool to see you
the fact leading the way and standing
out on stage Prince alone coming thank
you
yeah I I feel like they wouldn't repeat
that ever again
because that would like feel weird to
have me always be in that spot so yeah I
cherish these moments very much
BM appreciate it very much to be given
some time to shine
although honestly I I don't think it
even matters that much in the end
whether or not you stand in the middle
because I I
it's kind of important to me like when
it happens I'm like really really
it's special to me but when I think of
myself looking at like four fests Etc uh
when only like Japanese members are on
stage I
I don't like I look everywhere I don't
only where I look where my Oshi or my
favorite member is
anyway so it doesn't really matter
but uh
[Music]
still nice
um
yeah the i in the end will go to
wherever you want to look at
either way I'm looking at Vala thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you guys
thank you
[Music]
I remember actually
when I used to be an idol fan going to
idle concerts a lot uh like people would
exchange tickets or well over Celtics
and so on
um but yeah they would like often for
example
um
like it depends uh but for example when
they're like promoting a new song and
it's like a promotional event where they
they especially perform the new song
also some other songs but especially
your new song or or or it's like a tour
where they already they already know the
set list because on every in every city
they kind of perform the same songs
uh so like buying experience the fans
know
where their OC is on like which side
their Oshi is the most during this tour
setlist you know so they will go out of
the way to get a ticket on like a
certain area you know sit
I am
[Music]
and then there's you know really popular
members who always end up in the middle
and then the
members who like get less lines and all
that they tend to be more on the side
yeah
so depending on who your ocean is
so I've seen people trying to get a
ticket on that specific site so that
there or she sees them
more and that they also see their OC
more
both ways they want to be seen and they
want to see better
you think that's hardcore
I think I think in the eyes of an idol
fan in Japan that's
not that hardcore no
it's just strategy tactics
but you need to already kind of know
what's going on
and you know ah this is kind of like an
otage move I guess but and I think maybe
I mentioned it before but there's
something called ulti jump which has
been banned a lot in venues and concerts
but I think some sometimes they still do
it especially in more underground venues
um so when you or she sings a solo line
uh
you as the fan
during the whole duration of the line
will jump
like as high as you possibly can and
bounce bounce bounce
with ideally one hand lifted uh with the
pen lights up to the sky
and you go like bounce bounce bounce
bounce
bounce bounce
bounce like that
until Yoshi's done singing it gets bad
sometimes because yeah it's
Troublesome annoying and yeah in the way
and could Bonk the people next to you
because I tried it too I've done it too
I've done it too a couple times to get
the attention hoping to get the
attention
to make her look at me to stand out a
bit more
um
I've done it a few times
and you feel like kind of like you know
when you when you bounce it's hard to
stay really in one exact spot you you
you you go a little bit like you land
differently and bounce bounce bounce
bounce like that
hmm
do you feel about the entire stream
it's not a monster but you're not
bouncing against the other fans you're
trying you're trying your best just like
staying in your own little
Square
um
you don't Mosh Pit no no no no
but it's funny because like when you
look at it from like a distance or maybe
from a recorded video
uh you'll see like in the sea of fans
like
singled out fans that go like
really passionately hmm
you did that for the holy and concert
did you know it did you do it knowingly
yeah
like did you know it was an Oshi Jam
yeah random heads popping up over the
crowd yeah yeah
it's cute
pogo stick
I'm really passionate about it hey jump
so high
it's like they they did jumping
um competitions
as a teenager in high school
must have some experience with it
I'm not telling you guys to do that
though
yo I mean you can't but if you do that
at a concert like this one in La where
nobody has an idea what you're doing
yeah they'll probably just think you're
really excited
for your honesty
oh it would stand out certainly a lot
and eventually maybe someday it will get
banned too in America
[Music]
where was I oh yeah Jesse Lockhart thank
you
thank you
and smiling
Wicked tones thank you for the pinky
just so you know you're the first one I
had issues getting limited merch crashed
three times at pay but I think I got it
so happy birthday you beautiful bird
boss your hard work and success is
always well deserved I look forward to
the merch
I got it I hope it didn't fail but yeah
it's always a little bit of a struggle I
hear
sorry about that
[Music]
um
you still not sure if you really did it
I had to edit my car at the last second
to get it I've at least
um
heard that one way you could help
yourself is by like getting
like your payment settings and
everything readied up in your account or
so beforehand I don't know how it really
works I never I never bought something
from the official store I think
yeah
I think I
think I did never
maybe yeah
if anything maybe I didn't want
to buy a pickled a shirt maybe when I
was in Japan
I'm not sure anymore
I don't really know how it works
foreign
[Music]
oh man I'm so sorry it's such a mess
sometimes
ah
oh well anyway but thank you for trying
and thank you for supporting my my me
and my merchandise thank you I
appreciate it I hope it will arrive
safely especially the chicken the
chicken fussy
mmm
by the way like jenma asked me what do
you want to name your birthday
merchandise this time because look it's
always like we decide unless you don't
want to decide and you leave it to the
people but I literally I typed out
wait actually let me check was it really
wait
I need to count
we need to count count
did I really
mmm
[Music]
I want to find
ah it's difficult to find
here probably here
okay let me count the exclamation mark
if they properly took it online
uh
one two three four five six seven eight
one two three
[Music]
last one
for free
it might be seven it might be seven and
then on here one two three four five
or there's more wait wait wait wait wait
uh
one two three four five six seven seven
one two three four five six seven eight
nine
oh but in Japanese I actually wrote more
than seven maybe they just took the
amount from there let me see
one two three four five six seven eight
nine yeah they might have taken the
Japanese amount of exclamation marks
no you didn't get robbed if anything
they added more what a bad translation
what do you mean because of the
exclamation marks
no they were even more excited than me
maybe no well I just wanted to make sure
I didn't I didn't use less
just wanted to make sure they didn't
lose useless
then I gave them
[Music]
I don't want to get scammed
yeah the other one is beating with lava
very big towel but I lied to you guys
it's not very big I'm so sad
it's not so big
[Music]
huh
small towel
smaller than the average towel but still
use a ball
in many ways
um
[Music]
also chunky wonky has been sleeping on
my Rizal towel
enjoying those flies
um
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
happy birthday Dental ever since you
first hooked me by streaming Atelier
you also got to try it earlier
that's two at least two you've provided
nothing but entertainment and joy I know
you might not need my services too often
as a bartender yeah but I will still
always be proud to be careful thank you
yeah I don't go to bars often and
whenever I do I just drink mocktails
but I think it's very important for a
bar to have good a good mocktail
selection hmm
um but you know what it makes me quite
happy when I go to a bar and and they
don't really have like a big selection
they're still always so nice and
accommodate me and they're like do you
want me to make something like whip
something up for you what do you like
and I say oh yeah you can look so maybe
something with berries and stuff
something berryish and then they bring
back something really nice and yummy and
tasty it's really nice
thank you bartenders of the world for
for for making me nice mocktails
yeah I've never had bad experiences but
I haven't been to many bars so
um
yeah bartender is nice yeah
Fancy Fancy Fancy mocktails cute
mocktails
pineapple mocktail is nice to pineapple
[Music]
you got a free soda all night as a
designated driver wait you really
investment
yeah anyway thank you thank you I'm sure
it was you every time I went to a bar
I'm sure it was you soapy right you're
just like an international worldwide
traveling bartender just making sure
that while always gets her mocktails
thank you
thank you they taste wonderful
[Music]
oh you still got it nice
Mr Halland that question for the pinky
boss I lost the gotcha awards for full
merch but I'm getting the towels so cool
yeah thank you I hope you'll enjoy the
towel whenever it arrives in a million
years
please wait until then patiently
extra life thank you thank you
thank you
thank you for watching this event
in the Bank of you boohoo 723 Honolulu
[Music]
but wait your name Ashley is not
Honolulu
one
don't
queue oh
foreign
romanized version now I know what it
actually says
thank you for the rest of the chat happy
birthday Kiana I hope you celebrate your
birthday next year and the year after
that and other kfps I have a question I
haven't received last year's birthday
goods yet is there anyone like me
oh
did you order on geek Jack
or on the official shop
last year that's pretty bad
they come very late but can you check
the like can you contact the shop is
there any like update and like shipping
where it is or if it's been shipped out
you should maybe check
[Music]
and if if you've checked
like I've heard of cases where with geek
Jack like they just lose it and they
give up on it they don't give you a new
one they just cancel your order
so that's that I hope that didn't happen
to your birthday merchandise
[Music]
I mean I do think they send you back the
money but it's still like annoying to
wait for months and months and months
and then they tell you sorry we we have
to cancel it
well I hope you will find out where it
is
and safely receive it but surely in any
case this year's birthday it can't
happen twice in a row so this one will
arrive sooner I promise you I will I
will make it happen
um
I will wheel it into existence
I will summon faster
producing and shipping
I will manifest it yeah thank you
Honolulu
Evans
hello there
mate
um
hello
I I act like this but it's at least I
see like you keep on coming back to say
like hi every once in a while you're not
completely gone like certain other
people so
that is very very much appreciated
Australian chicken
yeah nice actually kind of nostalgic
every time I see your name I feel so
nostalgic
happy birthday kimama cheers to another
wonderful kfb year and I'll be looking
at picking up some of the beautiful
merch really
thank you
I didn't mean Albedo albino we have keep
on seeing him gifting memberships
thank you show up some more bullya
um
show your face somewhere I miss it
I would Invader thanks for the pinky too
boss foreign
[Music]
okay
again
um yeah that that film was had episode
of two showers
[Music]
um
yo yo
actually I've been thinking this like
brings me to that topic
uh
um
[Music]
question
wait did Cali
[Music]
let me check something
no never mind dad
oh no yeah yeah she did she announced
them
she announced it 24 hour stream right
um
[Music]
on the 24th of the 25th
yeah
[Music]
and that made me
um
think of some things
ah
because that's the day where I want to
do something too
and now I don't know what at what time
um
like I was
[Laughter]
um but
[Music]
um like first I was like
uh no no I can't postpone it it has to
be on this day
because the day after I I I go to
UK
um
and then I'm gone again and I I'm I
already I'm already delaying it you know
so and you know so
I I was like
um first I was like okay do I do it at
my 3 P.M time slot which would be good
for
uh
like sea viewers in Japan Japanese
viewers and so on
or do I do it at like the the typical in
a time slot because it's short anyway
and that would be decent for Nan for
Europe alone
or should I dare to for once do it in N
A I've never done this but for one
student in n a prime time
somewhere in the middle of the night for
me or the very very very very very crazy
early morning
now
now that's what I was already thinking
and then afterwards I saw oh Callie is
doing
24 hour stream starting at 6 00 a.m my
time taking up the whole day so I'm like
oh
hmm I don't really want
to like overlap such an important stream
for me with that
I I want it to be given the attention
it deserves
so now with that even more I'm thinking
okay
then let's do it before her stream
starts
in the middle of the night
then it's [\h__\h] for Europe for once
and I'm sorry about that but I think
I've been catering to Europe for a long
time anyway
I'm sorry Holcomb but that way
that way I wouldn't uh over overlap with
Cali's thing
um
and then
and then I can I can maybe if I once you
know stream at any Prime Time and see
how that goes
um
nah I can't do it the day before
foreign
[Music]
that's my problem
only on this day
yeah so sometimes between
like two to five a.m maybe if it's like
two three am or so I can stay awake
if it's like 5 A.M
then I can wake up for it
um
yeah
EST and PSD Bros will be very happy yeah
maybe some some whole life
en members will actually
be there at the reveal then and write
something in chat
yeah what do you when you think about
that guys are you guys gonna be there if
I do an EST POC primetime
what times are you talking the free to 5
a.m that's kiwawa time c-e-s-d
foreign
[Music]
wonderful
no okay
okay
[Music]
then I might actually want to do it
earlier rather than later
at like 2 A.M
2 A.M is uh let me see here
[Music]
2 am
is 8 P.M EST
ew 5 p.m PT
and I think like some Europeans are
still awake at that time
and it's 9 00 am JSU
maybe two two A.M
[Music]
that's um depends on where you are zebra
Monday or uh or Sunday
foreign
[Music]
it's difficult to choose a time for
something like this it's so difficult
and why I can't wait I don't want I
don't want
I don't want delayed
already delayed it
and then even if I delay it honestly
then then I have the like question
of
okay when do I do it then if I if I
don't have something that's like pushing
me away from my usual time slots
then the choice is even harder for me
so you know so somehow I appreciate Cali
doing that stream on that day
because it gives me a limited choice of
options
I appreciate that it pushes me to try
and I practice
um
[Music]
I could cut the one even earlier than
that I've
think it doesn't have to be 2 am
I think
I could probably do it like at the inner
time slot
on the Sunday
I'll still think about it
I can't decide
[Music]
um laughs
prime time would be better I do kind of
want to see what happens if
I try and a prime time
because I'm I never stream at any prime
time
I'm kind of curious
how many VOD viewers will show up
um
I'll think about a little bit more maybe
I'll do a poll
maybe I'll do a poll
and
Europeans will
fight for their life
not now I mean on YouTube Community
border so
[Music]
they will fight for their life to make
it the inner time slot
[Music]
you always watch your classes at 4A and
they'll show up
which one you mean the en concert
don't use all the cans
okay back back to this uh thing I just I
don't know I wanted to hear you guys
opinion good to know that you guys are
mostly in for anything anyway thank you
I just it's really hard to hit the
choice
I can't
and science if you guys have to help me
I'll make a poll okay
because I don't know what to do
I don't know
[Music]
thank you
thank you soon
happy birthday Kiana I have the super as
a token of my appreciation and love you
had some really cool ideas for your
birthday and I'm really vibing with the
big caking
how could I it's written right there
cake baking
I don't think you guys would have even
noticed if I would have just continued
to talk
I think you guys would have just
autocorrected in your brain
now you wouldn't have noticed if I would
just continue talking you just know this
because I stopped talking and I was like
[Music]
you would be like did I hear something
wrong ah well um it should be fun
whatever
yeah well what was that oh probably all
fine
bake caking
absolutely love the merch set Sally GJ
was sold out on the Leo but I will try
to pick it up very funny yeah I've heard
the Ellie GJ why are we speaking in
these code languages GJ was
this yeah did not have much
limited edition available
um
I was apparently gone
faster than
the speed of light
[Laughter]
weird yeah
sorry
now you know guys now you know next time
better to use the official store and
just go with tensile
or something like that
thank you though thank you Unity Chad
yeah I hope you'll get your hands on it
if you really want it I hope you will
get it I wish you luck take a look at
the school dance
foreign
happy birthday and thank you for helping
me get through a very difficult year I
look forward to all the amazing things
you will be doing and how so many others
will get to see how amazing My OC is all
the best for the coming year thank you
oh
hmm
why did you have difficulty yeah you
deserve good easy year
[Music]
I hope the coming year will be better
for you
but I hope I can continue making
those heavy not so nice days better for
you
no
well that's [\h__\h] sad
um
was she old
was she did she die of like that
relatively natural causes
[Music]
movie was delivered in there
oh man
I'm sad sorry for that loss of Kato
I hope Kato is happy and Cat Heaven
eating many snorkel and fish
and chinkin
and getting many many
memory pets thinking back on the times
Kato spent with Yokai record
no
no maybe you can get another cat someday
[Music]
to get more fluffy love
what for now
for now
next year will be better
it can only get better at this point
right
always look on the brown side of life oh
you haven't
as sweet
so you still have Kato
not all alone very good
nice
sweet
I'm happy
human needs cattle chicken also needs
cattle
be fast and thank you for the recipe no
alarms
[Music]
more and more I'm getting I'm turning
into bucket arms okay
with all the swimming I've been doing
yeah
and uh the lifting although I haven't
been lifting much but I feel like as
long as I'm swimming
on the days I don't swim I should maybe
be lifting
well I've been giving my arms a good
workout these days oh
and once I have my baguette arms I will
punch all of you who have been calling
me new alarms
I've been keeping a list secretly
I'll smack each and every single one of
you
in your face
and I think you may say buckets crack
easily but I think chicken necks crack
easier
especially if I leave the baguette out
to dry
in the air for
hours maybe a whole day then it's Stone
hard
smack you
and there goes the chicken neck
[Laughter]
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I take it
back I take it back I couldn't do that
I couldn't
I wouldn't be able to do that
um
because I love you too much
you sexy chicken
I never called you noodle arms not
mockingly eh not mockingly but what but
seriously it was
hopefully not at all that's what you
mean right
you love brutal chill
you want to pack up the baguette arms
go away my back arms what's gonna be
left if you Peck away my bucket arms no
no bucket cramps for you
no
I'm working hard on those bucket arms
[Music]
while so arm is too soft I had a
croissant today though that's why it's
croissant chats
had a quattle it was very fresh and
fluffy
waffle
mmm kind of still warm even
good quaffle
of course filling with nougata
chocolate cream waffle
[Music]
topped top topped with some nuts
quaffle
but only slightly
[Music]
good question
or chocolate I think is
good whenever they don't have a cornful
[Music]
it's like a
low-tier Castle
[Music]
is
I don't have the problems I don't know
so many spots for emotes
[Music]
all right
for wake up
[Music]
Maybe
you don't nothing
[Music]
oh you guys really don't like it but
it's not like we use croissant that
often either
I would replace it with something else
probably
something more useful
is kind of like seasonal thing
it comes in waves and then it disappears
for a while
a one guy demote oh
or a simple F letter for all the times I
press F or all the times I die f is
versatile f is really versatile
[Music]
and one guy how do you make a one guy in
the mode maybe a silhouette of one guy
hmm
I don't think we can really like person
purse personalize that one into kfp
[Music]
it's fake yeah but you know like when
you use it in that context it makes
sense
[Music]
um
yeah I don't know that's also the more I
think about it is difficult
to turn into an emote
if there's something
like
realize oh I really need this
then
we can do it
um
but that will probably also just be the
letters though
wow
what was I ah thank you be faction don't
call me that no more I'm about get times
now
I'll cause that is in for the pinky
happy birthday induction
so much
for the support
illegal to do
okay
critical hit marker that says one guy oh
whoa
I am good night
you look cool
is real so going no oh but this was uh
yeah this was when I was showing off my
arms
uh one day I'll show you my bucket arms
and y'all will apologize
down on your knees
pink bacon Max was the first time
question and endless things on the rest
of the chat even if the turret doesn't
meet your expectations I love the stream
I do some baking myself sometimes and it
was fun watching your attempt something
new
hey why didn't you scream louder some
advice at me
while I was doing it although I think it
was already too late at the time where I
made up the concept of one I want to
make
in my head it was so much better
than it came out in reality
ah yeah I wish I wish I wish I could um
but honestly people keep on saying
baking is just about following the
recipe and I guess that's true
should be true
because my thing the thing that I made
there was no recipe for it I kind of
just like
just put bits and pieces of other
recipes together in the hopes that what
I have the vision in my head
like to for it to become to come true
and yeah I hot winged it yeah
with advice from my mom though on how to
make all those like separate things like
how to make the jelly and all how to
make the the actual dough and all that
but the whole thing like I was looking
up recipes for what I wanted to make but
I didn't find something that was really
the thing
even though I thought there should be
um
weird I found similar things but not the
thing so I was like okay I'll just I'll
it shouldn't be too difficult
I'll just throw it together somehow
yeah oh well oh yeah speaking of fruits
though I checked my my balcony tomatoes
and more and more are turning red now
um
I kind of wanna compare
balcony cherry tomato
to the cherry tomatoes from the
supermarket that I have in the fridge I
actually wanted to do that today
there were like two smaller ones that
maybe were in the sun already too long
because they're like like wrinkly
but now there's like two fresh ones
there's a really small one and a bigger
one
and before they also wrinkled I feel
like I should eat them
should I get myself the the red the the
Wawa tomato I want to get it
we should taste test it because I've
never had uh my own balcony tomato
before
um
okay
I'll mute I'll be right back
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I have failed and instead I got a cat
smoothie poofy was just looking
so cute but I'm gonna let her down and
I'm gonna get dude
did you hear her purse
do you hear
um
like I was I was walking uh to the to
the balcony door and she was like
sleeping there and she sees me and she's
like meow and she turns and all out and
goes like and I'm like oh my gosh she's
so soft so okay I got I got a little bit
I got a little bit um yeah yeah it's a
tangent in actions
I'm I will try again I did get the
Tomato from the fridge though now I got
the real tomato that we need
I am
Peppa
oh sure
okay
[Music]
on
the right side of the Ring we have a
beautiful very very plump and red and
relatively big sized cherry tomato from
the supermarket while on the left side
we have the Challenger the new
Challenger that has yet to gain any
experience in winning matches but it's
looking pretty good rather than being
very very saturated red it's more of an
orange also it is much smaller in size
than the big Supermarket tomato so
people are questioning whether or not
this is a fair match or not as well as
the texture of the skin feels a little
bit rougher than the big cherry tomato
from the supermarket even though they
have both been washed prior to the this
match to make sure that this is going
down fair and square well well well did
this tomato actually have enough time on
the balcony or not we will see how it
tastes
maybe it will be even juicier than the
big one and defy all the laws of science
because it is so small well well we
start with the supermarket Contender
yeah we already know this Familiar Taste
it is it is Flawless it is perfect there
is nothing to complain about here goes
the explosion of taste and love and
passion in your mouth
um
[Music]
yep
after all there was no disappointment to
be had because we know we can rely on
this Supermarket tomato whenever we need
it but but but don't give up people
because you cannot forget about growing
those balcony Tomatoes here we go let's
see if we have succeeded this year
because last year this tomato died
before it was born and now we see it for
real
if there is a future for takanasi kiwawa
with her balcony tomato team whether or
not they will have a chance in the
upcoming World Championships of tomato
nests here we go
and free a two a one
[Music]
wow
it tasted very earthy not like soil but
however very natural and earthy less
sweet than the big Supermarket tomato so
if that's what you're looking for then
definitely you should place your bets on
the supermarket tomato but you are of
course very proud of the self-grown
balcony tomato aren't you yes so are we
and the audience very much because it is
definitely edible
and therefore even though it has lost
its match against the experienced plump
and big and colorful juicy Supermarket
tomato uh it may have lost but it still
has chances for the future definitely
there is hope and we're looking forward
to the growth uh of what what this what
is tomato may be able to accomplish in
the far farthest in the future but it
will definitely need a lot more training
from the manager that is called takanasi
Kiara that is apparently taking care of
the tomatoes way more carefully this
year than in other years probably
preparing for a very very big season
trying to get those medals finally in
yeah because also these Tomatoes aren't
getting any younger these days yeah
that's what it is yeah so unfortunately
only the wind does not go to the
newcomer but
I think the Tomato can go out of the
butt with its head held up high
eventually after it's being uh yeah
digested in the digestion system
as they usually do uh as that's that's
just how it normally goes as we all now
yeah so thank you everybody for coming
to the match of the tomatoes today it
was quite something
exciting to see that has never been done
before something so new so fresh
straight from the balcony straight
picked from the green plant yeah yeah
yeah it is fascinating it is inspiring
and we hope to see you all in the future
for the next match whenever we see some
more like developments and uh progress
um maybe maybe she will step up her game
takanashikara in the future with her
Endeavors of tomato growing hopefully we
can see some improvement and maybe she
will have to kick out some contenders
and switch them out for new ones she
will surely learn maybe she will need
some uh new um
the stuff you put in there for the
growth to be improved maybe she will
also have to completely switch out the
base you know the soil it also plays a
big big role I think fertilizer yes
fertilizer nutrients
yes yes yes but that all depends on
Coach Wawa
um I think I see I see good good
tomatoes in the future yeah
yeah this was a announcer uh uh
tedro uh had a nice night today very
exciting I'm gonna go home to my wife
and my kids after this and enjoy some
tomato salad thanks guys and goodbye and
in German we say
nothing because we're not ending the
Stream
[Music]
[Laughter]
hmm
yeah okay
[Music]
thank you endless
lemon thank you for is that a rainbow
I think I see a rainbow thank you
wow
yum yum
happy birthday Kiana thank you for
always giving us the best I genuinely
Adore You music and streams if I had to
choose my favorite my brain might start
smoking
you got my hopes up for a moment there
guy I would have been curious to hear
what your favorite was I'm happy to be a
fan and part of the lovely kfp Community
I love you all
I baked myself with spices into a
birthday roast chicken from the first
birthday has been lying on the table
waiting for you to join me until last
year you cooked me into a chicken soup
Frozen in the refrigerator this birthday
you will take me out to eat I use the
cafe secret recipe to keep me fresh and
delicious wink
mmm
[Music]
only if you promise
after being eaten by me
to reincarnate as a chicken once again
okay
can you promise me that
cause I you know I'm very hesitant about
eating you guys you know from what I
told you about phoenixes you know not
even we
revive properly after being eaten so for
chickens it's uh
chances are much lower even
um
[Music]
I you I don't see you here right now but
I'll take it as a yes
yeah okay I'll eat you tonight
I'll sprinkle some lemon over you too
because that sounds kind of good chicken
lemon mmm chicken lemon pasta I'll make
chicken lemon pasta I love you lemon
chicken pasta chicken lemon pasta pasta
chicken lemon
lemon chicken
lemon butter
[Music]
sounds good yeah although I would prefer
probably something like
lemon
asparagus pasta or something like that
I've had I've had that before I think
um
lemon cream I just generally lemon cream
pasta is so freaking good
[Music]
um
sounds buzzing
yeah it do be bossing
no thank you this is
more than cases later him then it will
be Nom Nom Noms
Patsy Duncan Grumble dog Danke Schoen
orange Apple cynical thank you for the
pinky happy birthday Daniel I wish you
all the best and hope to see more funny
streams in the future Long Live give me
I hope so too I hope I can be funny
I don't want to be done funny
as an Entertainer I can never be Danny
with the funny
[Music]
it scares me
doing pretty good announcers enter
really
I put a lot of effort into that
[Music]
it was very important the Tomato match
was very important
for me
hmm
yeah I always have problems with this
kind of stuff because
um my English brain
cannot so quickly come up with cool
words
I can without thinking about what I want
to translate I just like
speak English
fluently naturally but uh when it comes
to like really difficult words
and funny things and and witty things I
I'm bad with that generally yeah
yeah I I definitely am better at that in
German sometimes I I feel regretful
about that because I wonder if I would
be more entertaining to people
if only English was my first language
but maybe maybe the things that I lack
because of that maybe I can make up with
it
uh elsewhere with because of my lack of
English skills because I I say funny
things because I say things wrong like
abdomination
and ties
stuff like that hopefully that makes up
for it
yeah my weakness
as a strength instead
um yeah
[Music]
me
last time I was with Kyla I sat by Omi a
bit more confidently did you notice
at least once
you did
but I said it very quickly and and
hoping hoping she wouldn't like question
it
[Music]
ah the population possible boy let's go
you heard the waiver in my voice
there may have been some waiver yet
is still talking in one more than one
language which is at least twice as many
as me so speak how you like thank you
well well
if you're a homie you say biomi
[Music]
anyway thank you for the support yay
thank you
I wonder what this part means I couldn't
figure out this part but not the other
one
and David Askew too thank you for the
rest of the chat oh Canadian chicken a
very happy birthday to you Kiara I am
happy to celebrate and have a birthday
with you on kfb the hello Ian concert
has been the highlight of my year really
[Music]
I wish I could have been there in person
you weren't even there in person and it
was still the highlight of your year
thank you for being the best all she
have a wonderful day oh
wow I'm happy that it's like
such a big thing to you wow
oh wow
maybe we can top it
um
maybe we can still top it
foreign
[Music]
there you are
you are I see you thank you for being
here love you I love you tickets you
little shits I love you
[Music]
I almost wrote another I love you kfb
tweet last night but I stopped myself
[Music]
can't tell you too often
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah I don't know it's embarrassing
a little bit embarrassing
thank you David
thank you for supporting me and loving
me I love you too even though you didn't
say you love me I still love you foreign
[Music]
thank you
yeah yes that's what you meant really or
um
you're saying yes dot dot dot this kind
of sucks it's like you're hiding
something
that you also don't really know what you
were trying to say or it was a typo
ah okay
okay it was really that way
oh because you sent one on the content
okay
I wasn't sure if that's how you meant
but I had a feeling okay
oh why are you doubting so much senior
scares me
[Music]
it's like when people like write to you
like chat with you and then don't add
emojis they're always serious that those
kind of people who never add emojis it's
like so scary
um
you like the dot okay if that's just the
way you like to write then it's okay
I thought I thought maybe
you're disappointed in me
or sad or something like that
I mean I've I've had that too before
like
but it was actually I think honestly
on point like I would like be maybe kind
of mad or annoyed or whatever and then
reply
without emojis
[Music]
um
and then
I mean I don't I don't remember any
specific case but I remember it happened
before and then they would be like Kiana
what's up
why you mad
I'm not mad
there's nothing wrong just because I
didn't use emojis I just I just didn't
feel like it but that doesn't mean
anything
but then there's also the other way
around
where
like I just had this recently I was like
pretty angry at something
but I
I didn't know how to reply to it
I I did want to kind of show my anger
but at the same time also not really
[Music]
so I used some emoji
what did I actually
[Music]
thank you
what did I use
ah was that even it
[Music]
what I like to use when I'm angry
or like disappointed or so
but still don't really
and I want to show it too much but I
think it still kind of makes a point
is um the the emoji with the the head
turned around yeah yeah
that one
the smile but the head has turned around
it's like it's like it feels so ironic
like
it's like when I write thank you and
that you know what I mean you know I'm
saying thank you ironically
does anybody use it like
out like without trying to convey this
kind of feeling
that's how I see it yeah
or I mean it doesn't necessarily mean
that I'm half angry at someone it could
be
that I'm like angry at myself because I
messed up something or that I'm
just yeah usually though I'm mad at
something or disappointed at something
yeah
passive aggressive
not math I'm not mad I'm just
disappointed
hmm
I like that one
I lost my wallet today yeah I like that
like that
oh great
I love the year jail DHL yeah yeah
DHL
thanks
I love you no
no
had a great day today
ah it's so good it's so good like I
don't know what about it
does that creates that effect but it's
so good
laughs
love you Kiana yeah that that conflicts
me
[Music]
yeah that's very conflicting
this was a nice dream hey
it was
okay shut up guys you make me very
conflicted
thank you senior membership
okay
he who eats faces danger and I'll see
okay thank you for the words of the chat
wow
thank you for your attention
[Music]
feeling dead
haven't heard that in a while
[Music]
that song is right down too oh
I guess so yeah
a kiss for you
why is this on
toilet paper things for the pinky a lot
of supers are broken scent of pink and I
said I paid it said I paid but didn't
show up happy birthday oh
go it was trying to
help you with your life decisions but
you turned it away
and double down on it I say good job
thank you toilet paper Diamond
chat oh oh no you already went to sleep
oh man
oh man you did right you said you would
so you should be gone now
are you properly tucked into bed now
you got a refund good I mean I assume so
I just assume so
[Music]
okay
Yoko seems gone
no okay
good
I want you to get proper sleep
once again happy birthday Mama you're
the brightest star that has ever
appeared in my life oh
and you continue to bring happiness with
your ever shining eyes beautiful smile
on cloned heart which all successful I
love you usually
you're so sweet if you were here I will
devour you
good that you're not here really good
for you
to follow you right here at the spot
because that was so sweet
if you say such
sweet words surely you should be sweet
on the inside right
um
thank you that's so sweet thank you for
your kind words and for supporting me
like forever I feel like you've been
around forever so thank you
I hope you will stay
longer and longer
pink bacon dancing
space waterfall
thank you
I managed to buy a limited merch too
which is also my first ever yeah I still
can't believe I made it in time after my
blonde of putting the wrong order in the
basket we well did you do it on geek
Jack or that's so shaky but my heart is
very happy wow is the best I'm so glad
you got it
good for you and happy my first ever
limited version you got it nice
good job good for you not to not give up
nice nice
and then we have tsukinokage
and can you believe it that's it
I mean I could have done it faster
surely I could have done it faster but I
chose not to
[Music]
let's go
four hours for that really wow really
[Music]
but okay I think I read something
like for example I think I read one
or both of the Zelda streams
which one
that one of them right
was it the finale one because that one
had less super chats maybe I read those
let me let me see if I can recognize
them
no
[Music]
no not the finale one
may have been
yeah may have been the side stuff and
Lionel and gliocunting one
oh yeah yeah
I recognize this green welder rainbow
I remember okay good good for me did I
read the
oh it's barely any oh wait we should I
probably
oh I should just quickly go over
the anarchive broadcast rebroadcast
karaoke super chats
um
[Music]
what was the thumbnail this one
is
[Music]
foreign
mm-hmm
[Music]
there it is
just a quick One Direction for the pinky
thank you there's so much to be proud of
lately your Stella concert performance
fabulous
birthday streams and huge collabs like
hulasama I spent Anime Expo with lots of
kfb and they were the best to share in
the joy of being your fan thank you
[Music]
ah I wish I would have been among you
guys that sounds like fun
but I'm glad you're getting along well
with kfp
in these
special
events nice good for you
easy to recognize him
Ohio
thank you
you love my leave me alone thank you
leave me alone
[Music]
oh that's right
so tomato
[Music]
wait was it this let me
is it this
uh
I can't hear it
ah
laughs
so this part here uh
what
you can run but you can't hide
that part is purposefully like so
emotionless because
um they gave me a
um a reference
but then at the end they want this like
crazy laugh right
they cut it quite a bit I laughed so
much when I had to record I got you now
former CEO die
oh School
[Laughter]
that was just one of them I recorded a
couple of them
but I I
had some crazy ones that I had to like
delete because I just ended up laughing
about myself you know when you're like
just laughing about myself you know
did I have any others
I feel like I had more where did they go
they also usually they give like a kind
of a guide but it's kind of like a
vocaloid guide so it reads everything it
reads a script off
uh kind of like in a very monotone voice
which also makes it kind of funny so
sometimes I'm not sure maybe maybe it
should be read in a monotone way because
that actually is what makes it funny
often
okay
ah
I have one more
I think
when does it start
Ed
the role of the CEO is mine
oh
I was trying to time it I got you now
former CEO day wow
here it comes
[Laughter]
on level one I think
that was that was me laughing during the
recording
but holding back
I think one more
oh psycho
uh
[Laughter]
oh
so that's four different ones
I don't know what that was I was like it
was going crazy because I think that's
what they wanted for me just like a
psycho
like that
[Laughter]
um
I think that's the one that used I don't
think so I don't know they they
definitely use the short one or just cut
it
yeah
anyway
whoa
there you go sorry sorry that was loud
wow
laughs
yeah it's not tickling love because
um I I I don't know judging by the face
oh and I think it was also written in a
script kind of like
an insane laughter is what they need or
want
um
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
my cut off body
next one will be the last one and I'll
have to go fast through it because I
have to make dinner
I'll just read the finale of the Zelda
one
yeah I'm buried in the sand somebody
buried me
[Music]
uh picture
oh my God I'm so [\h__\h] depressed in
this picture damn
[Music]
doesn't it hurt you guys to see me like
that
[Music]
yeah
down
[Music]
okay it doesn't it's not called the
smiles of the Kingdom yeah
[Music]
um
oh
Nene diesel thanks for the recipe
testing chat and then be fun to cute wow
wow by the way today I finally make time
to watch Lord of the Rings one in cinema
oh did they like re-rebroadcasted
like an unarchived
karaoke
and I love it and we'll watch all of
them and you'll watch along later oh
nice
I am a little bit
upside down emoji about you watching it
so late
what took you so long
but better later than ever
hmm
thank you or maybe we should make an
upside down emoji Wawa for remote slot
nah
I don't know
I don't know if it will come across
well yeah thank you
for the update and uh oh yeah for the
support for the MV and all that
I'm glad you liked Lord of the Rings one
I want to hear how you like the other
ones too
stop
rice
and missed my monthly paycheck oh no
problem let me preemptively congratulate
you on completing teotic
I didn't catch all the streams as I
found out the more fun to play than to
watch understandable
I do have a look forward to ff16 streams
next yay let's go
[Music]
um well actually next is GTA
but then yeah because GTA won't take so
much time anyway apparently first I was
thinking of running it side by side
but turns out GTA is pretty short
so I might just wait until I'm done with
GTA and then we do fs16 or something
like that yeah
[Music]
yeah it's surprisingly short uh yeah
um
yeah I'm glad you guys are enjoying my
videos but I hope you also look forward
to the ff16 streams please uh be there
thank you rise of free
oh yeah the deal since I do have access
to the DLCs I think because I bought
this like complete edition thing um
thank you
[Music]
no no it will arrive
in Japan in Yen I think they probably
just pay it all out in the end
um
first and then
you know do their thing and then send it
to me
and then it gets converted again so it
gets converted twice kind of
[Music]
oh my God that's terrible
foreign
oh my God
don't even think about it
[Music]
uh you only experience of the pinky
I may not be awake when you finish the
game but I really had so much fun
playing totk along with you you made the
experience more enjoyable and catching
up to you got to got me to actually
finish the game too oh
thank you wow and good luck with the
finale I'm actually surprised you didn't
finish it yet because I feel like
like streamers and and YouTubers who
make video series obviously they need
more time to finish games
because there's like time in between
they do other things too
and and they split it you know
um
[Music]
what was it what was it that made you
wait so long
[Music]
but I hope you had fun with it because I
had a lot of fun with it and thank you
for for watching me play it even though
you're also playing it because I feel
like in some cases maybe it can make you
lose the interest too
because you're like oh I already saw
this as I already saw that and I don't
wanna
I don't care this is boring because I
know what happens you know
actually it surprises me people prefer
to watch streams of games they already
know
because you already know everything
there's no surprise element
hmm
um
you want to see uh my reaction our
reactions
yeah
I guess I'll make sense yeah
let's go
[Music]
thank you
this has been my absolute favorite
playthrough of yours
really
hey it's also kind of you know been one
of my favorite ones because I just had
such a pleasure such a blast playing for
it was so chill and uh for me it was
probably more entertaining partially
than for you guys but you know
different I think for this game uh
playing versus watching it I think it's
quite different
[Music]
yeah partially
this was so much fun to play at the same
time it's sad to see it end but I'm so
glad you are able to experience this
game can't wait for the next hour yeah
well we will definitely play another
Zelda game eventually in the future
don't worry
they are definitely
one of my favorite things to stream and
to play
so there will be more thank you for
being there for out a very long series
Once Again
[Music]
and simply also thanks for the pinky
congrats on beating the game and thank
you for thank you taking us to the trip
review no thank you
it's rare to find a game you enjoy this
much I really love to see you have so
much fun yeah I do want to say though
it doesn't mean that I'm not like really
really enjoying the games
just because I'm not playing them off
screen
um I feel like you know one of the big
reasons for me playing it so much in
totk's case is there was so much that I
felt like it it wouldn't be a loss to
not stream it it would actually only
help the playthrough if I were to not
stream it and like a lot of side stuff
that takes a lot of time at the same
time it's not like it's boring stuff
it's still very entertaining for me
um
yeah
it's like I think uh we only benefited
from me doing the side stuff mostly off
screen because as much as we all love
this game
[Music]
um I know that when seriouses go on for
too long then they overstay their
welcome as well and then it's less fun
for you guys as well
so I think it made the series a lot more
compact
and I had some fun time off screen too
um
and it's not like we were losing any
like super important content
uh like main story
um
so only benefiting from it yeah
yeah yeah so yeah well but that doesn't
mean that for other games I I that I
don't like them maybe it's just I don't
have time or it's on a platform that I
can't really play off stream like if
it's on Steam yeah I could use my steam
deck nowadays for a long time I didn't
have it though and I don't know steam
deck is kind of heavy and I keep on
forgetting that I own it
um and yeah I don't know PlayStation
games for those there's no way for me to
play it like elsewhere uh unless I move
my whole PlayStation and that's bad
although for the switch for the switch
for playing tltk most of the time I
wanted to play it on the big screen
because the tiny screen it's difficult
to play tltk on handheld in my opinion
like the controls uh if if you're used
to playing it on the Pro Controller it's
difficult to switch back and forth to
the handheld mode and also everything
gets so tiny I want to see the big
picture so I did bring over my switch
set up to my bedroom TV many times
and then brought it back to my office
and then back to my bedroom and I'm back
to my office and bed in my bedroom back
and forth and then into an airplane and
this and that
um
hmm
yeah but really it depends on the game
and on the circumstance doesn't mean I
don't love it so much you know
but totk was a special case
for sure
in many ways
production Alex is
[Music]
induction and Fred Panda Kitchen
hi
okay
and
whoa
did you guys hear that lag
I just deleted the whoa
[Laughter]
I just deleted the thumbnail and my
whole PC went like what
what's going on
I just did nothing
and all of that after upgrading my PC
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
I'm not still Robo while why am I
okay guys I actually have absolutely no
time to be
spending so much time here right now
so I gotta go
but we think I think I I I caught up
pretty well in Super Chat so yeah
and had fun to chatting with you guys
tangenting installing as much as
possible
yeah thank you everybody
I appreciate you being here once again
and next stream
coming soon please wait on the info
thank you James Jackson thank you thank
you X okay thank you thank you muscle
bug thank you sorry thank you
space wonderful thank you ghostly thank
you thank you
thank you oh no I don't have time for
this
you have a lovely day or else
gosh I look so
not angry did this change
[Music]
out
foreign
[Music]
yeah yeah
foreign
[Music]
thank you