do
hello
[Music]
is
welcome to hololive ends
third collaboration
okay originally we were going to play a
game called uh human fall flat
but we decided maybe gang beast was
a better game to play today so that one
of us
can go home with the golden yago
yes yes yes again for a third time
i'm not that great at games like these
so you never know
you never know everyone has a fair
chance
okay um so do you want to take
a little bit of time to introduce
yourself to everyone in chat
starting from gura
how are you you look delicious
[Music]
i will always laugh at that i love it
iconic yeah yeah
okay i am
wow today i am
not unfortunately not next to cali
i was separated because i i was scolded
for touching her boobies
whoa that never happened
but i had to i was a witness i had to
separate them otherwise
yeah it's good to have someone flat in
between us
oh
[Laughter]
it's okay as girl said i'm hydrodynamic
science science wins today
saves the day okay um
i am you know i am
human not taco human
really are you sure
yes okay nice try though you put in a
good effort
nice we'll see we'll see okay
cali oh yes okay
hello everyone hi i'm your mori i hope
you'll remember wait no hold on a second
though
we're not ending gosh i don't have an
actual opening greeting
hello and then i cough a lot um anyway
hello
i'm kaleidovi and i'm death let's play
the game i'm really excited to
get in there and show you the business
can we introduce our characters maybe
oh yes i'm very yes excited about my
character
um we have our names above our
characters uh do you want to start off
maury i mean cali kind of covered on my
screen but
you're kind of covered up by my hands
but do your thing no it's
all right
[Music]
yes you'll be able to see my character
in his full splendor very soon so
because there was no um reaper or
shinigami costume in the game i decided
instead of making
a character that looks like myself i
would make an original character which
is what i prefer to do anyway
so my character's name is burgerboss and
he is the mafia boss of all burgers
um i chose this because i like the fact
that you can put a achievement
on your head in this game uh don't mess
with him um
i don't know he'll be he'll be slimming
in the deep soon
i want to make something clear my
costume
is not a chicken i have wings on my back
which means i'm a phoenix okay oh thank
you
um i have been stupid no no no what did
i hear gooda
what did i hear what do you mean no you
heard nothing
okay i heard the majestic sound of a
phoenix thank you
of course of course of course
and uh i'm not a firefighter but for
some reason it says i'm a firefighter so
apparently i'm a firefighter now
i'm definitely a detective this is my
disguise
that's right i'm a doctor detective a
lawyer firefighter
yeah you put out yours flames which is
very
flexible just like how your arm you know
usually
yeah how your arm just breaks on stream
we love that
very flexible
it's okay i'll take it if you don't want
it
are you a shark girl or ah i
uh thank you for asking i am a uh shark
the stories wrecks
they didn't have a shark so it's a
dinosaur with a cape
turning like the shark pakistan was
wrecked
before sharks evolved when they were
walking on land yeah this is before they
they went into the water deep
and maybe i'm traveling i don't know
that's great yes yes
for sure and uh me i'm just uh
there wasn't a taco costume so
i guess i barely had a chance to look
through all the costumes uh decided on
this one
yeah i have worked hard with those 3d
glasses i must kind of looks like
tentacles
i guess yeah you could you could spit it
that way
second nucleus okay is there a reason
for
the mustard i just must fish um i'm uh
in disguise yes you know just like just
like that
i see you like i can't like
don't worry
okay okay well we had a warm-up round
earlier so
is everyone ready to get started yes
we'll be in the wrong coach
put me in i need a trackpad
it's okay you still have a fairy tale
not an excuse
master killer here we're going we're
gonna go in in three
two one oh wait there's a countdown
[Music]
for here golden yellow yes whoever has
the most wins at the end of the stream
will get a golden yago and do your best
still don't have one when ina is the
only one who has one right
i have two i have two only one one i
want it for my new
place i want one too
wait how come it's finding other oh oh
yeah yeah it just says that
uh-huh yoga will be mine
[Music]
yeah i don't know about that one we'll
see here we go oh
oh why am i blue
oh wait this is
[Music]
oh man oh no let go of me sir i don't
know who you are
[Music]
why does that happen my apologies i
should have double checked
escape escape
uh
i think i'm back yeah
i mean they were beating me
okay old dad that may not be swinging
you've got a burger on your head that's
kind of threatening
maybe he was hungry i don't know okay
okay
everyone back everyone back yes
okay we're starting now this is a custom
game okay
here
i don't want to meet those strangers
they're scary i want to say
uh you know that is saying there's no
background music
oh um maybe it's not loud enough
okay while she's wearing
[Music]
watson you're asking for it
okay we're good we're good
yeah what you gonna do huh
[Laughter]
oh yeah you can get totally bonked by
the sign coming at you yeah
i completely forgot
oh okay don't fall in the uh don't fall
in the hole what do you mean
okay
let me give you a headphone jack
all right it's not chicken turtles
running away
[Music]
if i'm going down you're going down with
me
[Music]
i will never let go
wake me up
my what's going hot happening
i don't know why i was even running i
always wanted to die together with you
and go to heaven with you
oh
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
ah this is good this is fine i like it
amelia
why is
[Music]
oh
come on come on let's go
no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no
no no how did you get out
you did
i'll go around
[Music]
oh
able to have enough power okay okay i'll
grab it no no no no no no
no no no no no
she's so powerful it must be all the
[Laughter]
not me not me okay
maybe you guys should go back to
fighting each other for a chance against
y'all let's go have fun
let's go have fun let's make some
chicken nuggets yeah
all the nuggies come on
come on okay
okay i'll keep dragging your punch
[Music]
knock her out again
uh
[Music]
yes i avenged you
what you still have a long battle
well i must say bullying is not good
together as long as possible
oh
over here you can get a really nice view
of the ocean
right i like the ocean but i also like
when you want to go back in it
yeah come on come
on
[Laughter]
right
while we kill each other you gotta be
part of it
but your headphones are strong
how do you head butt
talk about it
girl
[Laughter]
[Applause]
my great granddaddy gave me that
no not the joke the cape the cave
jar is escaping
good job
all right we're gonna have to do this
the hard way no
i hate to say it but i think my money's
on the chicken this round oh
i don't know it's really good until the
end which is very
in character yes
[Music]
my money's on watson go go go
pay for that class you're gonna pay
[Music]
oh
in school i learned this in school when
everyone was throwing balls at me you
just gotta run away
and then you'll be the last standing on
the field that will be all bullying you
at the end but
but you stay until
[Laughter]
how did i win i was drowning you're
struggling
wow is it finally time for my golden
wait we still have time left in the
collab
okay but you have you have three okay
you won the first
round okay okay okay oh oh no probably
in the end if we only can do one more
match i think we should count the stars
because like if it
matches one by one then it's just a draw
again
okay okay okay so far you have three
[Laughter]
is the best way to stay alive
all right noted now that i know oh
where'd you go gotta
tell her oh did someone disconnect
[Music]
she pulled me what i did in the first
collab come on
tell me dude okay okay
okay let's figure it out we'll figure it
out don't worry yeah
one second we'll be off the screen you
guys can still
keep fighting
i've got to assert my dominance my
burger
[Music]
do we have to settle something here here
guys everyone's gone now everyone's gone
watson just
lays down and takes it i'm i'm
i'm um there's some oh my gosh
that punch you like wound that up
don't worry guys i'm fine i think we're
all gone now i'm really crawling around
with the plug
can you move over now to the left
yes i'll tell you when to stop
oh hold on i'll stop messing with you
keep going
keep going keep going i mean f-word
kiara disappeared again
no i don't know it kicked me out
[Music]
can i get my hat i just want my hat
can i wear waffles my my hat burger
can you pick up the burger
i wonder fell off i tried to save you i
tried to say
okay i opened the gate but then you just
like slipped off i didn't try to kill
you it just happened
i see i see
is there a way that i can just like lay
down and like die
if you just uh if you just stop moving
it will do it automatically
for real stay automatically go to night
i should be back yeah yeah uh can you
shrink yourself a little
yeah perfect more yeah
charlie can you punch out this gate sure
one second hold on
i love how we're all just sleeping
together ah we
always wanted to do a sleepover with
everyone
yeah punch that geek maybe
for my sins we have a pajama party
together
can i sleep next to cali um depends on
what you guys do
i might have to intervene again
[Laughter]
why am i gone again we don't need to
count that we don't need to count that
oh yeah why am i oh no
why does i wonder why kiara keeps
disappearing
it's very strange she keeps going away
i'll make myself bigger
[Music]
ah wait no don't do that
let me see those arm pits yes excuse me
one second
hello
let's see now i wonder can you uh
headbutt the pole
okay but the guardrail that's not about
wait i was just testing what you say
you can head back
nice and silly
you want to go oh can you charge it wait
all right
okay
i'm ready to fight now i'm ready i gave
up on
being very good
i just i'll just fight
you tossed me into the pit of death
actually is what you do
[Music]
i don't know you're jumping in there by
yourself
a stereo spine
[Music]
wait for a moment for just a second
sorry we're just figuring something out
we'll be right back one second
[Music]
ah we're back hello
hello cara's having a
bit of technical difficulties it's okay
she's just kind of throwing it over 30
seconds it's going to be yeah
sometimes
you're going to sacrifice yourself
no
[Music]
[Laughter]
i got this
you can do a uh headbutt only
wait wait i don't know how to do a
headbutt you know
what's the headbutt oh we're moving
all right hey everyone
a yellow a bunch a bunch
a
goodbye friend i'm just going to find
out it's okay you're phoenix you can
come back alive right
oh your half flew off
i'm just gonna oh how do i head
butt
oh
how do i head but i can't figure it out
oh yeah
it's okay she does that sometimes it's
fine yeah it's totally her uh
frozen daring i'm staring into all of
your souls
yeah just don't worry about it what do
you see in mine
i see apex predator oh thank you cool
okay i wanted to do a cool trick right
off of one truck
where are we going
how are you gonna duck the sign coming
up oh um wait i got i got this
you guys died first i tried to jump
finally but didn't work
how did you know how are you able to
walk again i forgot
[Music]
where your choices matter hold on
kelly come to sleep this way this way
this way oh you saw
my foot huh yeah
i got you i don't think
oh
[Laughter]
what
oh no it's not the snap again
all
[Music]
wait come on
wait um there's a good chance she has a
hole she has a hole in the building
360.
like my sick moves
got three points now and me too oh
they're tied
oh wait it wasn't yeah oh it's a new one
[Music]
can i go down this way oh i will do that
for you girl
girl
[Laughter]
curiosity killed the shark satisfaction
did not bring it back i would just one
block fall down
why would just one wait there's a
chicken hiding here i can smell her
i can smell her no no no i can
smell her
oh goodbye chicken
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
i'm just taking a nap ugh
oh no no i
hope i can make it up
absolutely iconic
well played west and well played
and we're back don't run away
go run away kiara do
oh
[Music]
i got you i got your eye i got your eye
oh no am i stuck no i'm alive i'm alive
let's go get we can't have the chicken
he's going after kiara trying to grab
her trying to knock her out trying to
push her off what do you call these
things the
window washer boxes stop talking
stepping into them over here oh good
just playing into the
long game
[Laughter]
[Music]
why was the bridge gone on in a screen
models look different on mine by the way
very strange
oh yeah i don't know i don't know why
okay
anyway i started
ah
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's the gloves isn't it
[Music]
i don't need your elite tactics
oh
give me the burger get his fat head
knocked me out
let me go
[Laughter]
[Applause]
die here and then jumps out of the ring
and dies now
let's find out somebody had a first step
yeah there's like nowhere specifically
to fall off you like you really have to
push people out yeah
this will be a draw i think
[Music]
in her deathbed coming
no i'll join you in death
[Music]
oh no okay i need some help
my soul
[Music]
i only know how to raise my hands
dodging all your moves
[Laughter]
wait she's just she's just posing let's
get her
i know i'm gonna wait i'm just waiting
let's get it
get it
mustache off your face
get her out of here and get her out of
here
get her out of here well yeah
i'll knock her out with my big shirt for
you
oh no i grabbed the wrong thing
no i'm here i just chose not to respond
to you
go
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh god all right so let's get it
something's got to get here
something's got to get here it's okay
all right i don't know who to root for
oh
no get the water
okay i'll grab watson and jump off it's
the only way
it's the only way
[Music]
all right i'll sacrifice myself
[Laughter]
okay next one is our last round last
round
all right one yes that's the train the
best map
decides okay don't get disconnected
from the top
everyone's just making their way
safe players safe players
all right let's go let's go wait no
is
oh
wait why didn't i win yet oh there you
go
absolutely classic inna gets another
golden juggle
no i don't have enough stars uh no yes
she didn't win win okay
one more one more to break the tie
yeah we got to break that tie okay i'm
in an
elevator with death all right watson you
and me
oh wait wait we're gonna die wait why
are we wait why are you guys going up no
we were gonna die
wait how did he go up how do we go no
uh i think something's wrong with you
guys track i don't think he can go up
oh
[Music]
is
if we jump off on this side we can join
them jump together
okay fine oh we made it
wait where are they oh wow
everyone died
wait if i win this i get i get a golden
yellow oh yes when i'm the tide for
you and i are tied for first place now
it's the magic it's a magic that i'm
destined to have
what's happening
do you guys see the weird bodies come on
watson give up the ghost
button get out of here
it's michael let's go
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
well it was beautiful a well-fought
match i think kiara should get a goalie
i go too because she wrote
she won the first round yeah i won this
round okay
[Music]
so we shall now
we shall not commence the golden yago
the award ceremony ceremony
[Music]
winner of the first round chiara
my strategy with just running away was
very um
good yes
okay it'll work in the second round
it's okay strategies change
and the second golden jago goes to
our number one detective
[Music]
oh yes a memorable moment very powerful
okay okay oh
wonderful you strong girl
okay it's good so that
is the end of our third collaboration
together
it's a full group very clear
very chaotic pure chaos
chaotic thank you everyone for coming
again today
it was a lot of fun hope you enjoyed it
yay
that was super fun actually yeah i'm
very impressed by how fun that was
okay um before we end does anyone have
any announcements they want to make
what meet for
yes yes golden one has something else
i haven't i have an announcement i'll be
streaming
in four hours and my announcement is
i'll be making
an announcement
[Music]
announcement assumption oh but also
in the stream for hours i might if i get
it to work
finally use my long-awaited
microphone and then we will all get
crispy chicken
can yeah imagine i might have a
completely different voice after that
looking forward to it that's it
okay anyone else anyone else
so i i will be posting
uh actually it's really just kind of
business as usual for me i think
just a regular schedule i think yeah you
guys go ahead
okay i have a schedule that i'll be
posting later tonight uh
or tomorrow morning i don't know
i am also working on schedule this week
i know superman
okay
okay schedule okay
well that is it for today uh thanks
again
for everyone for coming to watch our
third collaboration
uh we will be having another one next
week correct
yes
so we will announce it when that is all
decided upon um yeah that's it for today
thanks for coming to watch everyone say
bye bye
bye see you around catch you up on the
flip side
oh
[Music]
you