so think I think
[Music]
I
see
[Music]
me
know
[Music]
you
[Applause]
[Music]
obession I don't if I was made if I
could
[Music]
call me I you don't even know what to do
this your me around
[Music]
[Applause]
see sh
me you me see what I want I need do you
you
[Music]
K KY key
I say while looking into chunker's
eyes K KY
key she's gonna go isn't she
oh
oh yeah I didn't forget to kiky hello
hello she's not leaving yet she's still
purring oh oh there she go wait can you
like go while not walking over my mixer
but you can say hi hi say
[Music]
hi okay you can go now bye-bye my mental
support my
beloved
Kitt how am I I'm stressed
um because yeah I don't know yesterday
was my day off but I like I was so
busy I did a lot of work and
socializing um yeah I worked till 4 a.m.
bro bro I wanted to sleep
earlier yeah and then today also I've
been like working on
stuff so
I am
stressed
so maybe I'll take tomorrow off because
actually tomorrow I also have some work
to do uh that I would be doing before
the stream but maybe I'll take the day
off after
all I feel so hot right now I was like
feeling chill and then it cozied up with
a sweater and now I feel too
hot even I already took off the sweater
of course I took it
off but yeah did you see my video on
Twitter oh the
SK did you see
it sure
[Laughter]
did I just wanted to put something on
Twitter because I I I was recording
something and I was like oh I look so
cute I look so cute I
must you know do something to uh
immortalize this cuteness if you know
what I
mean I did look cute
right the wink always kills me it was a
pretty smug and nice wink I
think paddles need to go for this every
day yeah like imagine like you guys are
making a fuss when I meme once
but imagine how you know the Pebbles are
used to this you guys need to toughen up
you know I need to I need to get with
the the Zoomers I need
to understand them so I'm studying them
I'm studying their every
move yes yes yes yes well well today is
Holo cure day Holo cure came out with a
another
update uh I played a little bit off
screen um so that I could gather a
little bit of money but I heard there
are new ways of making money as well so
we might as well try those
too I already got spoilered a little bit
here and
there but it looks to be a fun
update haha
[Music]
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah change window
size
to yeah we're so bad go H cure oh that
size is not good
[Music]
I don't understand why does it never
really
fit ah whatever is this okay you guys
are going to be like there's a bar on
the left side look my lineup I was they
have a new starting screen it looks so
nice when you have like so many
characters but have you noticed I
noticed something when I was like just
staring at the screen for a
while the
graduated members are sparkling every
once in a while if you pay
attention I I was like looking at it for
a while to figure out if it's really
just them but yeah it's really just
them mhm look at the Sparkles they're
only on them see no
two wow I notice things that other
people don't
no is this why why why
why how about how about how about now
okay I think I got it why are you
sparkling what I'm not
sparkling no no no no that's that's
magro Senai above me who's
sparkling
no so we're going to play this today I'm
so
excited and then in two hours or less
than 2 hours now uh we'll figure out
what the next V collaboration item will
be yesterday I didn't stream so we
didn't check it out together but I hope
you guys all checked out what it is got
your email checked it out it's a k
ceramic keramic
ceramic keramic ceramic keramic
ceramic ceramic ceramic ceramic
ceramic a bowl in the shape of a kfp
bucket yeah oopsie
[Music]
yeah yeah and I was thinking you can put
so many things in you can use it as a
popcorn bucket or you can you know put
some soup in or some fried chicken
or um I don't know
but first and foremost perhaps Ramen
Ramen
ceramic ceramin s Ramen Bowl
ooh water for dog
no don't use it as a dog's water
bowl I'm going to
cry bro
oh man St around water for cats no not
for the cats either
no no use it for
yourself so now we have um a pin and uh
an apron and a bowl and we that's three
things out of nine so we're still
getting a couple more look forward to it
soorry I'm just yapping yapping before I
even start because I feel like I'm going
to forget about it out
otherwise
sure I don't want to forget about it
okay
so let's see I
tried I tried I tried to GA a little bit
of money at least because I was at at
like 500 coins this is probably not much
but I
tried I I didn't have that much time I
have work to do man and this is um like
one and a half hours or so of
grinding with Iris in
uh in in the endless
mode which brought me to learn some new
collaborations by the way I I I I I took
a list because I wanted to learn new
collaborations and there's some cool
interesting new
ones I don't I don't know if it's the
ball might not be new but I don't like
the ball that you have to
continuously hit because I started
focusing too much on trying to run run
after the
ball H try using GRE I didn't find a GRE
St but yeah I definitely uh used the
Super Chat the time things yeah yeah
ball is old right yeah okay so where is
this
casino this is in the Hol
house I haven't been here in such a long
time hello how does this
work where's the
casino do I have to unlock it somehow
down left oh
okay I got
some I got a error
message era in uh Kai k kou are you
listening let me read my error message
out to you says error in action number
one of alarm event for alarm zero for
object object hola house manager DS map
dscore mapcore findor value argument one
invalid reference to DS map yeah yeah
got it you got it requested 71 Max is 90
uh #
# and then gml scriptor load play
at gml object
gml
objector o OBG j obj uncore plant
manager uncore create uncore 0 line
58 and then almost done you got it gml
uncore object uncore obj uncore Hol
house manager uncore alarm uncore zero
line 14
okay my PL start right is that what
that's
saying here I I'll copy paste it and
I'll send you
the I'll send I'll send you the um error
message per Twitter DM there you
[Laughter]
go okay uh should I click abort or
clear oh I pressed abort maybe that
wasn't the best choice
[Laughter]
wait what I already got a reply that's
quick customer support it's already
fixed making a new opdate
now what okay it's not fixed for
me I'm a bug tester
y okay h house how did I make this
happen how do I not make this happen
again I guess I just I just shouldn't
enter the house okay bottom
left uh ah down
here oh there's a dead
bunny oh oh North Hollow House South
teas Forge West usas
Casino East cute girl ahead cute girl
ahead I must go there
first who is cute girl is
itago here
I heard
about I never played Jump King before oh
that is that how the controls in that
game work holy
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh God I I never played this before
how do
I what I cannot change my direction
anymore once I'm jumping [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
wait I'm lost
[Laughter]
forever Bounce from right side ah okay
okay oh thank you can I not do it
otherwise nah nah this ain't for
me
nah ah this ain't for
ah ah
ah I'm
leaving
no how do I get
out how do you get
out save and
quit I'm also
exhausted
um maybe with a controller or
so anyway is this the casino place
here oh there's another path here but
that's that's they're still building
something there I
guess
[Music]
oh it's so shiny
bra hello Mama but did you lose all your
money
talk welcome to casino pickle this is
the perfect stop to take a rest from
your adventures and just enjoy some fun
games fun end games pickles we offer a
variety of mini games here just for you
to win first you'll want some USA casino
chips pickle what's our main currency
here you already have 100 starting chips
but if you need more you can buy up to
1,000 chips from me to get even more
you'll have to win at any uh of our
casino
[Music]
games with enough tips you can exchange
them for a bunch of different prices Pi
But be sure to take a look look at our
prices to see if there's anything you'd
like pickle I hope you enjoy your stay
here
pickle
prices oh I can buy with Holo coins too
what the
heck those prices though that's like a
100 million or or 10
million legendary secret artifact
discovered by the only only one exists
in all the world increases attack by 2%
in the main game definitely not no no
scam very much a
scam H GAA lost all her Holo chips and
went home crying oh
no oh this is expensive
too uh are these things more like for
the hola house area huh I can't I want a
[Music]
cat the monkey the [\h__\h]
monkey don't let this pet monkey
distract you from the fact
that worker breaks purchase rights for
workers to have breaks workers will
spend stamina
2%
[Music]
what ooh creat Sakura petal effects on
moving the okay cute cute cute kind of
interesting
[Music]
so I can with the chips I can later
exchange them to holoc coins they have
Blackjack I love Blackjack so okay they
have black jack what
else they put my favorite things into
this casino
huh only the things that I can play is
this all black no wait this is something
else and this is just
slots feel like slots are going to be a
real
scam h
lower or higher or lower uh that sounds
like something I heard of
before uh cost
10 all right let's let's give it a trial
though I think I'm more of a black Ty
kind of person do you think this is
worth
it uh okay okay wait that could be good
but how the [\h__\h] am I wait ah it doesn't
have to the ones in the middle it can
also be diagonally or the top ones Etc
okay
okay oh no
way
[Music]
[Applause]
nah ah dang it that's what bibo
says oh I got
something wait I started out with 100
coins right so I I made a little bit of
a
win
oh
[\h__\h] ah [\h__\h] no so close the nin the nin
were so close but the nines aren't very
worth
much I'm going to be losing all my money
on this is it better to
kick
oh wait does kick move it like by by one
spot or so
oh I was saying nining it's a carrot
should I
spam hit the machine for a chance to get
some some of the bonus pool chips if
failed some chips will be lost forever
oh no okay that's not what I thought it
would do I thought maybe it will like
from the last one it will move it by one
or so that would be
nice last try last try then I'll go to
blackjack no way no oh
[Applause]
away okay let me
out I didn't I didn't make too much
loss not too much not too
bad how's my child
doing oh what what we can play junk and
pawn she has 940
coins I can gamble against them I can
play against
some paper I win how much do I
get scissor
[Music]
[\h__\h] scissor yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
three out of five okay I'm I'm
winning okay chill
chill die I win I
win I got 157 coins from
winning it does everybody play
Duncan oh no she doesn't want to talk to
me how about you guys wa what's up okay
okay whoa way is kind of
Rich h no I just took the back that she
stole from my purse when I was
sleeping don't misunderstand oh no wait
I I I understand I understand t t t t t
t t t
t
wi t t wait does she always do fist what
was her first
move was it try paper a
wait a minute what the heck is going on
I'm
scared
[\h__\h] there's some kind of weird
connection between me and
her back to
fisting B get out of here she took 96
coins from me can we do it again right
away oh okay give me my money
bag what
yes yes yes how is this coded like how
do they think are some more smart than
the
others I
wonder oh
[\h__\h] T
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah yeah oh I I understand how the
computer is thinking
coins I started to
understand how much money oh she's like
so
broke she's so broke I can't take much
from
[Music]
her ah ah peace peace
yeah yeah I sense a pattern there I
understand I can read computer's
Minds PE
PE okay you get that one but no
more oh
[\h__\h] no stop
no
I I let her oh how about mik mikai
surely has money a good amount
okay Kobo lost all her USA chips and ran
home
cry yeah ran home run home to
Daddy [\h__\h] bad
start f are you good are you okay she's
crying too everybody's running home
crying this is this casino just makes
everybody miserable
no no I've learned how they work but now
they know how I
work okay okay we can still we can still
do something about this she just did
scissors I'll go again yes yes
yes [\h__\h]
no
434 chips are you kidding me m but
what the what do I have left do I have
something
left okay it's time to play
Blackjack uh hopefully this isn't a
scam um how does this work again uh we
should probably start with something low
currently it's minimum bet 10 okay let's
do
20 how does this work again um what what
can I not wait
what
oh oh great I got it she's beautiful
she's the
queen uh I shall not go over 21 right
okay okay nice keep
that
16 uh hitting is adding another card
this okay nice keep
H and then I stand I can bribe no
stand there you go I win again black Che
is where I believe in where I will get
rich okay let's
[Music]
do uh maybe
80 14 20 well I'll Stand of course I'll
Stand
and you lost ah this is easy
money yeah the card art is so cute is it
only aan and NOA or maybe is there a a
Yago card or so I
wonder
um what 12 uh I'll hit wow Black Jack
baby keep
bet yo King oh there we go yes he is the
king wait this a reference to you are
[Music]
King ah [\h__\h] that's that's bad 16 is bad
I kind of want to hit
again but this could go really badly
well if I lose once do I lose all my
payout to complete 168
[Music]
should I bribe hit or stand you still
lose what
why no you only lose the bed ah okay
I'll
hit what did you say about hit or stand
I still lose no you have no idea what
you're talking about baby I am takanashi
Blackjack yes
understand one more time done Yago was
watching over me and gave me luck got
keep my
bet they got 10 I got 13
HIT
stand H easy easy easy easy you got
yourself into a little
kff your chances of winning in this game
are higher than an IR Casino oh no hey I
got the king I am
King hit [\h__\h] first time first time okay
one time it had to happen that's
fine here we go again I wonder how much
money I need to unlock all the
characters like what am I aiming
for play Win
yippee check it out 1 million no
no no way okay but then we try out a
character we play for a while we G we
gain some more
money I spent 400,000 to get them all to
20 okay no I mean I mean just to unlock
them I just but okay
50k yeah that sounds doable reasonable P
coin doesn't I know but you can surely
exchange them for normal coins
right wait I can't
cou what are you
doing
no oh
[Music]
no I
ah push
push oh we both kept that 17
okay one the
prices okay all right oh he's at 20 [\h__\h]
that's hard to
beat yeah
[Music]
I'll just I'll just probably take the
hit or should I now in this case I feel
like I should just hit
it cuz yeah there's no reason to
stand oh same outcome in this case same
outcome unless I would have gotten the
lower number of course but
[Music]
one more
time so low what's with these low
numbers hit one more one more time hit
me baby one more time okay now I'll
Stand
y one more one more one more one more
one more 1 15 hit
[\h__\h] I'm still on a pretty good winning
streak
though and yes uh somebody asked before
I saw if I finished Arcane yeah I
finished the first three episodes are
there are there new ones already out I
thought it was
Saturday the new
episodes Get Wrecked
tomorrow
wo let's go
I oh W beautiful I'll have something I'm
I'm quitting I'll have something to
watch tomorrow so wait you let me look
at your prices again go
chips huh you really can't exchange
them who such a
um what should I
get I mean
wait what can I afford oh nothing wait I
can't afford
anything all right
goodbye I'm going to I'm going to go do
something
else safe for
cat yeah if I buy a pet it would be the
cat what's wrong with you are you
okay can't talk to the
bunny hello oh cute oh my God it's a
baby
wood cutting level mining level craft
commission cell
Talk welcome this is Kia fors right now
I'm helping taking care of the for here
while my big sister is out doing her
homework you can craft tools and other
items here that might help you in your
adventurers to do that you need to go
gather materials first if you go further
down you'll find a bunch of trees and
rocks you can hit for resources this is
Minecraft GA a whole bunch and bring
them to me and I craft whatever you want
I can even make you better tools to help
you gather stronger materials tools have
different stats un let see Power is how
strong you hit things strikes is how
many times you can swing your tool and
the resource until you get tired The
Gather stat will increase the amount of
resources you gather and precision is um
how easy it is to hit the correct area
when Gathering yeah by the way we also
offer commissions too if you bring the
required materials and give it to me to
craft the I will give you lots of money
as a reward but you don't get the item
because it is ours I hope my sister
won't get mad if we pay too much no go
get me some materials
H oh
god oh [\h__\h] I need to go I need to be in
the red
right oh
God sh I'm dumb but I get a plank
oh this one's
slower good good good wonderful very
good I got sticks five
[Music]
sticks
woo home run baby all
close
[\h__\h] I get
some lead lead I still don't know really
iron give me some iron give me some of
the
good
ah
iron one
iron wow this is just Minecraft now down
here what there's a
pebble wait I'm not for mining sorry I'm
just a pebble
o okay I'll leave you alone
then PEB pe's also totally in Minecraft
yeah yeah I've seen
them
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] oh it's gotten so dark
now ooh Why is this red stripe so
small oh should I be hitting the same
free actually you failed to
GA
NY was that in or out
tool coish
amazing okay at least I had one hit
there so wait what what do I do with
these things
craft ah better material better resource
Gathering
tools but
then okay then I gather more and
then wait are these for the main game
or I just sell the materials that I
gather do you guys just sell
them you just you sell
them you get coins for those yeah oh
mhm ah for this okay if I have the these
materials I get the coins but these
items they don't go to
me
mhm well I I want to
[Music]
try so close to getting that stone
properly wait let me see if we should
aim for
something um we got the five sticks for
the plate armor let's get more
stones and more sticks also
[Music]
nice five sticks that's pretty good and
it's already daytime again the cycle is
pretty
[Music]
short at this rate it will be 2025 in no
time
woohoo so if you consistently hit the
red bar do you get more resources out of
the
session I would hope so cuz now I did it
again okay 5 five yippee let's try this
one
again ah yes
[\h__\h] at least I got
two thanks for the r than oo not bad not
bad hiis it's Iris you playing Minecraft
huh having a good time playing Minecraft
I saw by the way I saw fauna um playing
Minecraft um she started at midnight my
time and she started an hour earlier so
I wanted to join her too
bad I know a couple girls
joined yeah if I would have started then
I don't know I probably would
have stayed up way too late ah
[\h__\h] although I really want to help I
did offer her hey I I I I I I would love
to help
you if you still need help a while
ago ah ah can't I
suck
oh it's it's pretty good when it's on
the side there somehow I did better now
is that mikoi behind the
tree mikoi
Tamp ah
[\h__\h] she always needs
help get get get some
help oh good
one she took a yeah right she took a lot
of money from me is that what she's like
hiding behind the tree she's she's
trying to like sneak up on me and get
some more
oops oo okay let's let's do the plate
armor at 650 that's pretty good oh I
have to Bunk
it hit the critical spot to polish and
increase the quality of the item how do
I know it's a critical what how do I
know is it
secret that seemed pretty
good and I now I'm not supposed to
but yellow is
close red is closest
aha oh green is f oh [\h__\h] oh
[Music]
no oh well that's fine plus 6 Plus
357 yay let's
[Music]
go now I need more stones
again but that's a pretty decent money
source
and the stones are relatively easy to
get not bad check
craft
[Music]
ah oh I don't have the level for the
other ones yet it
seems last tab
uh
block the
prisms ooh o wow wow wow
[Music]
wow what are those
materials these are simple but these I
guess the materials I can gather will
later on be upgraded or
so yeah these ones are in the main game
I realized
[Music]
that but I mean those are just a little
bit
small uh upgrades to
have so do you guys remember I have
something to tell you I I have a riddle
for you are there any people who work at
um phone providers perhaps isps or
something like that people who know
their way around phones in
particular riddle me this
kfp I've I've talked a little bit about
this before but there's been
some
updates remember when I talked about
[Music]
my
phone not having a connection like I
can't call or receive
calls in my home but when I go outside
the moment I go outside it works so
there's some kind of like reception
problem this
it but it it worked oh nice it worked
the day
before and so suddenly from one day to
another it stopped working okay and
outside it works inside it doesn't
inside of other buildings it works just
just here yeah but like I didn't change
anything nothing changed around me or I
didn't change anything with the phone so
really you wonder
why there was no no it's not Wi-Fi
calling it's normal normal signal
calling
whatever um wait should I make
can I I need more
Stones well you guys say it's my house
but like why did it work the day before
and suddenly from one day to another
even though it worked fine for months it
suddenly it stops working it's not like
my walls got even
thicker so anyway that's this this has
been going on for like at this point
what 2 months or so
pretty long in any
case and when it happened I called my
phone provider and I asked them about it
and they couldn't give me a solution and
couldn't even give me a reason or
anything like
that
um but yeah I talked to them like two or
three
times and time has passed since and yeah
and um nothing changed they did send me
because they wanted me to try it out
they were like oh yeah we'll send you a
a new SIM card please try with the new
SIM
card ooh la l no
Mythril oh
god
oh
no yeah but I I thought like why would
that help because
when I go outside it works so it's not a
sim card problem it's just a here
problem a location problem but they
think I'm [\h__\h] stupid again just when
I had just like when I had uh internet
problems and the problem went way way
way way way deeper than what they
suggested but okay they have to go
through their stupid whatever list of
solutions even if they're very
ridiculous
let's make the stone
axe but that's for trees should I make
the pickaxe first I don't have enough
for that and let me I want to I want to
save up and get more
Stones no even even when I stand right
at the window it doesn't uh work but I
swear when I step outside and stand on
the outside of the window like literally
next to it then it
works it's like that
exact which is a bit ridiculous
honestly uh turn on 5 I've tried all
kinds of things including that 5G was
always turned off anyway but I tried
also with
5G
nice see signal
jammer I I really don't know but so here
comes the update because on this this
part of the story you guys already knew
if you heard it before but I did tell
this before
um so even though I knew that the SIM
card wouldn't be the
issue I you know had some time so I I
tried it out I put in the new SIM card
into my phone and it didn't work of
course it didn't change anything but my
friends came over and um you know just
for fun they tried my SIM card Eva one
the old and the new one in their
phone and when the SIM card was in their
phone they were able to make
calls also they have a different phone
provider and generally with their phone
provider they were also able to call in
my home inside of it so anyway my SIM
card Works in their phone but but that's
the that's the thing like when when they
put my SIM card into their phone they're
using my
provider
so what I figured after all that is it's
my phone
but but then but then how is that
logical because it's still my phone with
my SIM card works when I'm
outside if it's my phone then why does
it only not work when I'm
inside H but my SIM card on their phone
works inside but my SIM card on my phone
doesn't work but my phone outside with
my SIM card works you understand that's
so weird
that's so weird so now I'm wondering do
I have to buy a new phone or yeah
something with the antenna is that
something that is worth like sending
into the factory or so to fix it or
should I just buy a new
phone I have a Samsung S2 Samsung Ultra
s22 which okay it's not that old so I
was going to use it for a while
longer but now the thing is I still have
my old phone to use for some things
um so uh I put my SIM card into my old
phone and my old phone is now my calling
phone for the meantime because it works
on my old phone my new phone now I just
use for like Wi-Fi and pictures and
whatever I guess so now I'm using two
phones actively again but should I get a
new phone or or or is that fixable the
antenna thing does anybody
know is it even worth cuz like sometimes
certain things they're not worth fixing
cuz it will be so expensive that you can
just buy a new phone
already get a new one new
phone get new
phone well yeah I'm now a couple of
versions behind already with my Samsung
s22 could get a new
phone I wasn't planning on doing that so
early though did you drop your phone no
not really no it has a case too
protection
case as an IT Tech let me just say that
it's rough to diagnose issues in houses
there's so much that interferes however
note that even things like Cloud
movement or Cars Moving can mess uh with
sell signal bounced ANS are also
different okay but like I mean I've
tested this for two months now and it's
always been the
[Music]
same it really seems like
a issue with the phone now which is
weird here though what but why does it
work outside what's why why how how if
it's the antenna then why does it work
outside I
guess I guess it could make
sense you like this topic good try
factory set I don't want to because
don't I lose all my data and I have to
like save it first but that's so
annoying I don't want to do that
yeah the signal is perfectly fine
outside don't Factory res said
okay do you use SD card uh do I uh I'm
not
sure no I don't think I do I don't think
I have this SD
card no signal in my office I need to
turn on and off airplane mode to fix it
I've tried that too though ever since OS
upgrade maybe there's a chance that it
started after an upgrade the OS upgrade
for me to update for me too maybe I
don't remember so well
anymore
but
H outside there are less things blocking
a signal mhm did you buy the phone from
another country
no should o there should be a plastic
spot on the frame of the phone which is
where the antenna gets its strength from
make sure I Tred without the case and
with the
case if it's being covered it makes no
difference buy an indoor cell phone
signal
H the phone antenna is not that strong
but poor design that will be
[Music]
yeah yeah a booster I know what you
mean okay ask if your IP provides sell
signal booster for you I'll I'll discuss
that yeah I'll see I mean I know there's
like those for internet Wi-Fi signal
boosters I never thought
about uh signal boosters
for the telephone
[Music]
interesting okay should I craft can I
craft the other one yet I I want to no I
want to look at this one ah so close
five more Stones I I think I want the
pickaxe you know why am I even why am I
even here I need to play the normal game
there we
go I should be playing the normal game
why is it so distracting
here let me
out let me out of
here
please so I have the new pickaxe
now what where's the
difference it's still very difficult
he knew what he was doing he knew that
we just couldn't stop doing other things
now maybe he wants to move on and make
Holo cure into something else that's why
he keeps on distracting us with other
games so he wants to turn Holo cure into
like Minecraft or
so
[Music]
don't
don't don't do it
I mean these are fun don't get me wrong
these activities are fun
too I'm just
joking pretty good for
yapping not going to lie I really have
to focus to hit the the red
areas oh
well it's a nice break from the normal
gameplay that's
true
but oh nice I didn't even play yet so
why are we taking a break before I even
played H that's the
question okay I will I will I will I
will do it I'll play the
game I'm leaving
goodbye I'll see what the gacha uh uh
can offer to me and then we'll try out a
character I have 15,000 what it barely
became more I guess I didn't yeah the
casino didn't give me any more money
so all right how much is it again
to uh try once it doesn't say a
price 15 g p okay 1,000 no
that's pretty good I'll try it with ha
life fantasy third
generation oh
uhuh oh I've been spoiled I saw that um
waa has new outfit so I guess uh all of
myth maybe has new
[Music]
outfit let me
see wait which one's new for her I'm not
sure but I think my dle is new yeah wait
no it's not is it secret why can I not
see it
here everyone has new
outfits is this a d no that's not a dle
is this a dle it's hard to see when it's
uh
monochrome but yeah I think this is the
dendle cuz it has the birds the birds
are so hug they make me like double the
size
is cute and so for C it's the rapper
outfit I guess this one right and
then also it's like casual outfits but
but for me they
chose e wa what how many new outfits are
there that one's new for sure
right all of these new except for this
one okay the Sleepy one
sleep this one so
cute okay I don't know one
[Music]
each all
right got distracted again let's let's
give it a
try
de
taada first try pick up pickle pickle
pickle well that was easy
I mean we had to get someone right you
can't fail and just get a non character
right yipp cute cute
cute no dupes no dupes no dupes baby
easy mar mar
mar okay we got a dup that's
fine you want dupes for stats no but
first of all I want all characters there
we go we got the whole
J oh my God is this a p stream what what
I thought I was listening to a takasi
Stream
force
force wait since when was the fourth
generation officially spelled like that
I didn't know in English
I didn't
realize I didn't
realize hold a
for I mean I understand the pun it's
actually pretty
cool that makes
them like it gives me the same Vibe as
like
justice nobody calls him that but
yeah I know gen free is fantasy I've
always known that that was way more more
apparent to me than this I don't think
I've ever seen this written out before
in
English
yeah whole life fantasy I hear but this
I don't
hear okay let's
go oh let me check let me check
something
[Music]
okay here we
go cute cute cute she's so
cute I wonder how she will
fight K let's
go I C them again oo
no dupes please give me a new
one ah what what's with the dupes
now
uh good morning
[\h__\h] good morning good morning
[\h__\h] let's
go I again oh wow my canot will be
really strong and I should play with
her I've never tried doing an impression
of her what the
heck I have only three more PS come on
come
on give me
TOA
no come on channel
[Music]
it now I got like all of the top ones
like triple I think one last one come on
please give me give me new one n
[Music]
n
BR that's it with my money that's all I
got okay but the the
dupes uh they just like make them a
little bit stronger automatically right
I don't have to do anything
mhm okay look it's so full I'm only
missing these
two okay then let's play the game a
little bit um now rank threee rank
threee rank four should we start with
vat Senai cuz she's rank four
baby she has a harp sonaki harp pluck
the harp to create sounds around cell a
harp a all right cuz she does have a
harp that sense it's so cute though so
sophisticated fires multiple beams in
all directions to deal rapid damage
watch my beam okay okay cool that's her
ulti that sounds like a good
ulti um let's try stage should I ah
should I do
endless what should I do stage mode
angry o Mama noises
stage okay yeah there's a new stage
right this
one or is it wait no this one this one's
new sorry uh Fantasy
Island 150 okay but it's not like more
difficult than the others uh like the
hard stages right but there's a hard
version of it okay recommended upgrades
5 five all right I do have that well
then here we go let's go are we on the
be
oh
what's you
song but what's this song again I know
it I
W that was a wrecking ball
Cannonball ah the fantasies a okay okay
cute barely nothing wrong
I need to learn how to do her voice I
literally don't
know did
wrong
translation I would translate it
as what it's not V's fault or
so oh oh never mind it's kyy that's what
it's translating never mind okay KY
D it then it makes
sense all nearby Targets receive a
debuff where they take damage equal to
85% of any healing received by that
Target increases haste by 5%
M okay I mean let's let's
go so many
bunnies I'm already in pain you
bit
uh we shall try also
to use uh new uh
collaborations um feel free to help me
get in the
die all heing is a% character level okay
let's go I need that oh wa disco disco
party party
uhoh I do not like these cannonballs
holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
I wanted to go
[Music]
down
it okay for now let's go upgrade the
main
weapons what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] I'm
stuck I got stuck on the tree I swear
I'm not that bad
actually uh yeah I I I I uh learned when
I played offc screen I learned one um
sausage upgrade sausage with what was it
something electric I did sausage with
something some it became something
electric this a tough stage okay thank
you thank you for saying
that yeah the lightning sausage a yeah I
yeah yeah yeah that was pretty
cool now I want to try something I
haven't done before of course
ideally um see there's the sausage I'm
sure there's another upgrade with the
sausage and this one damage plus 15 I'm
going to go for this um what's what's
another new collaboration I uh like
result for the sausage that we could do
boys love book okay okay then I'll be
looking out for the bo
Lau
ah wouldn't it be cool if uh if V if you
as V take Uber sheep you get like an
extra
buff click the right arrow here to see
the combos oh the the right
arrow what
here I'm scared to click it cuz it feels
like I'm going to be selecting it to
choose oh this oh it's a cheat sheet was
that always there oh it shows me what I
have what I could
make wait where where is the boys love
with
sausage wait never mind I'm blind I'm
I'm stupid this and this no but still
where is boy love of sausage does it not
show it because I don't know it
[Music]
oh okay anyway Let's
uh work on my main skills
though oh God now this stage is really a
little bit difficult
already but I got a gun ble I have to
gun
ble H my
uh wait we said we said boys love this
is I'm going to
roll ah okay better um I'll take the
Vite
fever sure wait so every time I see the
disco ball appear I'm being healed or
what was it I already
forgot should read it
again yeah okay said
sausage let's improve my
sausage I was playing pretty well as
Iris in Endless mode off
[Music]
screen but I
didn't I didn't play that map I didn't
play this map H limiter might be helpful
to have honestly
but I'll I'll incre I I'll I'll make my
own
choices don't worry I'll try to make my
own choices today but I do I do kind of
want a limit
her that is also my own choice
but I wasn't sure if I should get it
right now Super Time ah I'll get it
because I'm still working on getting
more
money I appreciate more
for by the way yeah let's try this wooo
wow that is
insane
wow maybe not the best timing to use it
but I had it ready for a while and I
forgot about
[Music]
it h a sticker
wait I I'll get there
[Music]
eventually let
there those palm trees can somebody get
rid of those palm trees
please okay sticker stick
no I was right
there wait wait wait oh with this have a
nice day 75% of any healing is shared to
all nearby Targets he
any heal amount is stored on targets and
if the total heal amount is greater than
their current HP the target is
saved what I'm healing the
enemies Sav yeah safe truly means
killed any heal amount is stored on
targets the total heal amount is greater
than their yeah so whatever I guess it's
just going to be good right hopefully
healing them
now but killing
them who W wait let me get out of
there y y y y y y I'm so yeah
B There we go all my problems are solved
question Mark and that barely killed
that army of
people damn it I thought that would do
more oh shackles that's is that new I
don't know I think it's new reduce
effects plac reduce the negative effects
of any items placed on the player by 33%
cool don't have anything like that yet
Mouse aim yeah what I didn't aim what
wait
what huh
oh what there's an
aim I thought because it goes kind of in
the circle the those beams are like
twirling around me I thought it just
hits
everybody with those
Twirls oh wait a second I need to read
that again is that in Synergy whatever
that said that was in Synergy with the
with the healing thing wasn't it uh
let's do
[Music]
this the Pirates are
here
mean the cannon balls are back to high
ah what what the [\h__\h] is that what's
happening
um all NE targets receive a debuff where
they take damage equal to 95% of any
healing received by the Target okay I
there's some Synergy going on there my
brain is not locked in enough to
understand cuz I'm locked into the game
and not into this text I'm dead
uhoh what did you just say all these
doubs doing black trick as
well you doubted me but look at me
survive
um I need my I need my ulti please
oh my ul and I need to do it correctly I
I
oh okay uh how does this work I don't
where's my ah there we go there we go
there we go there we go I understand I
saw it I saw it Oh but this is rough
this is
rough good kiding thank you I am trying
my best it's pretty rough oh Big Bird
Big Bird is here a small Big Bird oh
look at all that oh oh that destroyed a
lot that one ulti
[Music]
suddenly yeah yeah there's the there's
the haste boost going from uh fast to
slow
is not so
[Music]
nice I always my problem is always that
I lose track like when it gets too busy
I don't see my cursor anymore I don't
know where I'm uh where I'm aiming
towards
and then I try to reset it cuz sometimes
it just uh seems like it needs to be
recalibrated turn down the opacity
uh-huh
okay the opacity of what
[Music]
attack capacity turn it down my own
attacks I i' I'd rather uh
just
somehow make the cursor more visible by
making a glow or something I don't
know I don't know if that really helps
to be honest that doesn't help me at all
or like make the enemies uh little bit
more monochrome or
something oh hey look at that uh where's
where's it where's it where okay am I a
am I did I aim I don't know I I couldn't
see
it oh
God holy [\h__\h] ah so stressful so
stressful so I'm so slow I'm so slow
what the [\h__\h] why was I so
slow I mean that was slower than usual
did they slow me down or
something that
hurt slow area enemy debuff what the
[\h__\h] is it this blue
circle I did see some weird circles I
wasn't sure what that was the fandy
buffer
bro I'll never make it but that sucker
but uh with that kind of debuff you
really need to play a character or or
use items that make you
fast blue slows green heals the enemy
Red does something that I can't read
right
now green red is damaged de oh wow it
all sucks okay
it just all sucks y y get out of what
the
[\h__\h] help food food
food going to try to upgrade my ah har
harp earlier this
time oh my God
should I still do Super Chat U yes oh
there's a sticker all Abby I won't reach
it for a
while and I need the radius again I
really need the
radius
[Music]
a cans are un fixed SAS if you don't
move in front of in front they don't
shoot oh what like around the the the
beach area or so like where the sand
[Music]
is did I do it right did I do it
right no
I I saw my cursor so I was just
like it aimed down what I thought it was
aiming where the cursor
is
but turn the opacity back up you turned
off cursor
aim oh oh I was off what the
[\h__\h] I didn't turn it off it it was just
because I restarted the
game it turned itself
off there we go got a sticker weapon
hits have a 10% chance to St enemies
temporarily also have 20% chance to
destroy enemy projectiles okay whatever
whatever I don't have a single sticker
yet so anything is good
except the one that makes things
colorful I don't care for that
[Music]
one yeah I guess we'll get this item it
just makes sense with what the Miss
sire a sheep needs to eat and a sheep ah
the [\h__\h] needs to deliver
items AKA
Burgers so honestly this didn't help me
at all so I'm going to bring it back up
then maybe I will be able to see my
ulti if we're lucky I'll be able to see
my Alti yeah okay now I don't see I
don't really understand but I see the
pink uh thing again
yeah okay yeah I I understand oh nice we
got the rainbow exp that picks up
everything
[Music]
yippee okay I'd like a second weapon
now
TB let me get out of here let me get out
of here let me get out of
feel so fast but now I feel so
slow oh god oh y y y y give me money yo
not so far y yo give me
money whatever yo I don't care do what
you got to do if you want to bully me
that's
fine still no no real weapon so I'll
suffer a little bit
longer I suppose oh my
God I got stuck by the
tree I got stuck by the
tree I know I can roll but I don't want
to waste it too
much all right let's try someone else
because we want to try many different
ones let's try p s she has a rocket
launcher which fires a rocket missile in
in the front
mhm oh her her ulti is like a slot
machine Casino
Casino deal 1,000% damage to all
Targets if a jackpot is rolled all
Targets are instantly defeated and
turned into hoc
coins oh my God that sounds amazing if
you're lucky you might be able to make a
lot of money
she's made for grinding money I wonder
how high the chances
are ah shall I try again the Fantasy
Island I feel like I'm just never going
to make it
but got to try she's great for money
okay
okay it rolls on its own right I don't
have to like press something to oh my
God why why is she doing this to her own
fans
okay yes okay
okay uhoh I thought I could make
it getting [\h__\h] isied by cannonballs
oh cute what is that her thing lucky
bunny all weapon and skills have a 5%
chance to gain 10 size gain stacks of
luck that is equal to half of current
crit maximum 30 luck increases the
success chance of all skills and drop
rates
oh but wait he's 15 I need to get this
one I want to get this one and anyway at
some point but this one has 15%
size I got to get
it I got to get it oh God take we need
to find burgar we need to find burgar to
heal it's
urgent
uh-oh okay good good uh stuck stuck
stuck ah what the [\h__\h] is
is I don't see him
[Music]
sometimes my my boys laa book that M
Senai entrusted onto me I wasted it I
wasted
it
okay time to lock in
Gambler every 15 seconds roll a slot
what if successful scatter holoc coins
oh when picking up H coins heal one HP
and gain a stacking buff that increases
attack by 2% and crit by 1% sick
whatever you say
um I I will get the main weapon don't
worry but this sounds fun so
I'm
what how
fun pyro maniac when deing a Target
there's a 5% chance it will trigger an
explosion that deals one50 holy [\h__\h]
well let's get the rocket launcher okay
chill chill chill chill chill we'll get
all these things
anyway gotcha gotcha SL machine
woohoo
okay um let's take the pyromaniac
we want
explosions
[Music]
explosion there's the there is the boys
love
book get this one's not buffed but
whatever I feel so slow I want to speed
Bob SL
wohoo oh my God no no no no no no no no
no
no I hate this this such a stressful
map you do a good pickle person I
know yeah
I know I'm good I I it [\h__\h]
tr oh oh all right I was expecting uh
the B uh beam but yeah
okay we are playing a different
character now
[Music]
ID custom forco is good oh
really uh sure maybe if we find it again
but by the
way it has a collab but I I've done this
before right that's why it's on the list
I wonder if it has other ones and I
don't know yet but we're going to aim
for the boys love with what was it
the sausage
right spicy that makes so much sense
boys love of
[Music]
sausage M okay
um oh I kind of want to take the ninja
headband I want to be faster speed
bunny oh yeah oh yeah there's so much
money on the ground all the
time I like
[Music]
it my I mean I can level this one up
more I don't know I don't take
it
o o
have you guys also been playing a lot
since the update it came out
today some girls were playing it
yesterday because we got a little bit
early
access but I had my day off and I really
needed it because I had so much work to
do so yeah yeah yeah just one run so far
oh holding back huh I played a ton did a
few runs before the
stream oh a bit before bed
unfortunately I'm at work so I
can't it's my first look
heyo want get a good look will
you Feast Your Eyes Upon My Godlike gam
play
ha come on give me seven s lucky salmon
no wait if I don't get the same thing at
all like now it still got rid of the
enemies but not all or
what greet them yeah yeah I'm I'm on my
way I'm on my
way it just deals damage okay oh
[Music]
man um
that's better that's good
choices
um he want being increases
attack have to level up my
weapon my rocket
launcher okay the Pirates are here now
things will get increasingly more
stressful oh my God there's so much
money no no no no no oh I'm alive I feel
like I didn't even take
damage
sick explosion
explosion uh what was this again attacks
have 3% chance to hit holoc coins out of
Target per head chance and amount is
increased for okay we're fine
yay oh there's a box I'm coming I'm
coming I'll try
oh no I can't reach
it ah biger right I'm on my way I I'll
make a big big circle I'll lead him over
here while picking up the coins and oh
okay we got attacks have 30% chance of
slow targets by oh yes I like
slowing and Tra
M M M I love you thank you very much
thank you
tasar H miasma is one I didn't have
before okay so I guess we're leveling uh
miasma
now and this was increase the chance of
critical hits caused by this Weapon by
10%
sure
[Music]
okay this is going okay
okay miasma is there another one that I
don't know yet that you can do with
miasma that I haven't done before do you
guys know I've already done these
two there's still only one
more ah the Ian yeah I was trying to get
that one going offc screen but I always
died before I could get it okay then I'm
looking for Ian curse and sausage and
everything else will be
denied but this run seems to be more
about money now than winning the game
itself which takes a little bit of
pressure off of me okay they're doing
the thing with the circle now but the
green circle is barely visible on the
ground
but I saw it I see it I see it oh my god
get away from
me
sausage oh I got it I got I got one I
got one I think it's pretty much killed
everything I
guess
lucky KCK
imagine P
singing Because she likes she likes
money right in this game at
least
stop ah aners what's up what's up
no need for AI song covers I am your P
to cover all your dream
songs
I no I hate
this going to
fing this than
reduce time between attacks by
[Music]
15 I'm stressed out I'm stressed
out
out yeah
uh almost for years thank you so much
going to die going to die going to die
no no no not in the slow Circle stay
away from the slow Circle stay away from
the slow Circle slow Circle uhhuh a slow
Circle I'm going to stay so far but my
sausage doesn't reach that
far ah leave me
alone come on please I need one I need I
need
one k
oh
God
uh sure ah Double
H Triple no okay
fine I cleared the whole area and
immediately they're already stacking up
[Applause]
again ah I hate this I hate this I hate
this I hate this I hate this
help help where's my
mouse please I want to see the
collaborations oh uh
upgrade um what's the CL they're all not
really close but all
right I got stck
six minutes is the Fest you've made it
yet thank you so
positive positive thank
you okay okay okay
okay as long as those Circle [\h__\h]
stay away from
me um I had this in my off screen run
this is so amazing actually should I get
it being able to use the Anvil
feather
okay you just you really like the
feather maybe because of
[Music]
me but yeah it's good I know I'm pretty
good you know my
feathers they're just
op we all know it the phoenix feather
although that looks honestly just like a
normal chicken
feather but it pretends to be Phoenix
Feather
[Music]
um
H oh wait does say chicken's feather
ridiculous I don't have chicken feathers
I only have Phoenix
feathers wait I I don't think everything
died they're lying to me
oh nice nice look at that cash cutting
cing e money good
money good
money it was Nota was it
um imagine imagine more more slot
machine
activation RIS
let me
it
no
no it's okay I have a feather I have a
feather no it's not okay it's not okay
it's not
not okay not okay I take another chicken
better thank
you
ah let me get down again thank you thank
you thank you pass passing through oh my
God what I can't I can't do that I I'm
too stupid for
that I
[Applause]
5% chance to cause explosion that hits
near by targets for 30% of the weapon's
damage
[Music]
um no I think I'll just strengthen
something
maybe switch
increase I'll Str him
oh God I need I need healing I need
healing I need healing I need healing I
need Yum Yum
Yum attacks have 20% chance to reduce
attack and death of targets by
20% flower um
[Music]
I
think
May we'll just strengthen what I already
have oh my God I am in the territory
again uh my special is ready that's good
news
please please please
please I'm in the midst of getting
isekai what by The Cannonball or by
something else and then the Cannonball
hits me afterwards or what
uh
okay holy [\h__\h] whatever Even If I Lose
I'm making so much bank here I think we
don't
mind wait so I used one revive my thing
is on level two so I only have one it
doesn't like go back up again does it I
only have one revive left now but I
could get another
[Music]
one please
why did I run
in I'm winning either way I'm
winning a y a
y but our cool down on MAR special is
very very fast so should be good in
general oh what the [\h__\h] is that the HH
is that a
boss 10 minutes we're at the
10 okay okay okay okay okay okay let me
before I die let me just get all all
these things all these nice
things oh you have a Godzilla
beam no no no no
uh Let's do let's
do should I should I get nor
FEA or should we work on this my my
attacks well let's work on my
attacks please come on come on don't
fail me now
Yoo big big big big big
big get out of there
okay okay okay this is so
intense is this also does it end at 20
minutes or is this longer for some
reason what about your main weapon I
don't know it doesn't come up wait my
main weapon is awakened is it
not level seven is that
awaken 20 minutes okay and then the boss
yeah
okay what we're halfway through that's
already pretty
good in a money focused
run okay I see then it's fine
um okay where am I right now
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay okay
okay sorry
sorry I want I want to I still have one
more revive though um I I I have one
more revive but I think taking another
one thank
[Music]
you stuck D very much stuck
D oh my God help please die please die
please why are you I no no no
no please no no
y
minutes need cab a St yeah
yeah yeah I know I know the cannon has
like a region and I know I'm like
constantly running around it but it was
difficult with the boss
okay also I know there's a box there uh
hard to reach right
now so close so close so close so close
so close so
close I'm locked in I'm locked in I'm
locking in I'm locking in I'm locking in
I'm locking in I'm locking in I'm
locking in oh no no no no no please okay
now I'm locking
in stop stuck
stuck why is the Box in such a difficult
position
ah get out of get oh my
a no no no
no what did I fail in the slots
69,000
monies that
was that was so
rough that's a good amount of money
though that's rough um time for some
gotta for stress relief
we're only missing two
characters here we go should be enough
Luna is tough she just did not want to
die but yeah my my collabs if if I had
at least one collab ready I was close
though there we
go you killed me and now you show up in
the gcha I see how it is that's how it
works another C
zai
and a
no shows herself once
again and okay maybe we'll play Coco
Senai
[Music]
next there we go
finally
um so
[Music]
this we got the
characters then I'll play orange power
sen by she has a dragon Katana that
Lashes in the front and oh she
transforms in into the dragon and she
has a Kik me no way Koko transforms into
her true Dragon form for 8 seconds in
this form cooko is invulnerable and
briefs fire to deal damage wow 8
seconds wow that's pretty long
okay now I don't really care much about
the money so it's all about
Survival how can I tell um besides
noticing like is is there a visual
cue of where the Cannonball start I I I
saw that one just now obviously but I
don't know if there's a visual like on
the map like
a the ship uhuh
is it
[Music]
there
great okay might switch it out
later ah I ran into that and immediately
got a lot of damage
oopsie
oopsy oh
stuck what
sorry I I I I it was already pretty low
because of the greed sticker
greed brings you only bad things guys
don't be
greedy don't be
greedy okay I'm not going to go lower
than that
ideally but eventually when things get
stressful you just sometimes you can't
help it oh stop stop Stu Stu Stu
this can I slice the trees
please I still haven't seen those
collabs that I wanted to
see Yum
Yum
Yum uh yeah great
[Music]
start two two shitty short
runs might want to seen them the easy
level no I feel like a loser if I if I
don't play on the new map I feel like
I'm weak ass
[\h__\h] I I feel like I'm already like a
weak ass [\h__\h] but that will just make
me a weaker Asser
[Music]
bitcher each new map is harder than the
oh God okay really
uh um all right if a target takes damage
with the first 5 seconds after spawning
they take a
1.10% damage uh increase all asak
weapons have a CH 20% chance to life
steal 5% HP asako items negative effects
are
negated oh I might need
to go for all the
asako related collabs in this run if I
survive that is which is so for example
this one sausage with that one at least
on stream I haven't shown it
yet
okay I I I I'll take it for now but then
I I don't know no no worries I'll
continue working on the
katana no no I'm so slow I can't get out
of here no
why why why why why do I suck so hard
suddenly upgrade
speed uh upgrades like that
are you mean the the general stats like
that goes on all characters I should
upgrade it more ideally that would be
great of
course ah what it's already 9:00 p.m. oh
my God oh my God oh okay when I die
again we'll take a look at it you can
already send me a screenshot if you
want on Twitter if you've seen it but
besides that don't look at it
yet Dragon of whole life defeating
targets may drop random objects walking
to objects will automatically pick them
up and Coco throws the objects to deal
200 or 300% what skill damage when near
Target holy [\h__\h] the special attack
action can execute other attacks when
the special goge why does she sound so
powerful 50% and 70% dealing one uh
times thir strength
SK C is broken she is just because she
is this just all sounds so powerful
I might not live for does she have
really low HP or
something is it just me I I
Su okay I I'll try again I bicycle oh
it's Yak some style items that the
random items that they're dropping that
I used I see now oh [\h__\h]
bicycle oh that brings me back that
makes me feel like I'm playing Yakuza
now first Minecraft and all that [\h__\h]
the casino also makes me feel like I'm
playing
Yakuza okay then toate everybody I know
you want to see the gameplay but uh
we'll get back right to it but for one
momento we are going to look at the the
Vite update because I have a current
like sponsorship collaboration thing
going on with
v so I'm download Twitter video
let me go get the video I'll show it on
[Music]
screen uh two minutes ago this
one My Game just crashed and I was about
to finish new stage
no oh man did it give you an error
message it seems like there might be
since the update there might be some
some rough spots that need to be fixed
there
soon okay I'll I'll put up the video uh
it might be loud in the first moment Tom
hold your ears I'm In Too Deep yeah that
seemed like it was loud for a
moment
okay was
it was
[Laughter]
it monitor only there we go okay we'll
watch the video and then we'll look at
what the revealed item is here we go I
lose my
way what did you say I lose my way are
they in my way oh no no way no way ain't
got a choice don't look
away he's running he's running
away where do you want to go I don't
know breakr listen up cuz here some
advice can tell by now temperature is
crazy off that wall and that [\h__\h] scare
me well go ahead and do it what you
waiting for going to break in the
door I am turning back let's
go day left I know what to do with this
mess going round and round well life is
the only way you make of it don't know
what to do just
take that's me Raj and Sparks I think
chance commit to B
play Hello convinc myself I'm doing all
right but you know n i w pretend the lie
that I tell myself so I'll survive who
who are you talking to flames burn me up
down into my core and every part of my
being doubts the past and the present
and my dreams I just hear your voice I
can't be sure
why I hear your voice it down to just
what I want to he's going insane that's
the light it will lead me
back back I'm ready to admit it was all
me who destroyed everything I
am you
wish keep Lally the whole script is just
my lyrics now so I demand some extra
extra
monies because I basically okay money
money basically wrote your whole script
in this
episode royalties go go go I'll sa if I
can so seems like he is escaping
successfully he stole the
files he almost got caught but only
almost man kfp you have one job
protecting our
files and our company
Secrets who had one
job okay oh I
see it's the
Chopsticks it's the
Chopsticks
perfect with the in combination with the
bowl
amazing Chopsticks and there's can you
there will be better pictures of course
later on but there's little cies on top
of the Chopsticks
yeah yeah I don't think this picture is
doing it justice at all it it will look
nicer when you see it for real for real
yeah yeah yeah yeah I won't read the
whole thing this time um I think this so
long I don't want to I don't want people
to run away too much uh in the middle of
the stream but yeah K Chopsticks
Chopsticks featuring a silicone CI CI
mascot on the top yes cute don't break
it manufacturer reports concerning
Rhythm patterns emerging in injection
modes quality control expresses
increased the stress over over
Chopsticks tendency to align themselves
at a precise 45 degree angle optimal for
visibility from stage huh product team
demanded a carrying case come with these
Chopsticks side you never know when you
might need uh emergency USS what there's
a case coming with it really just a
small one I suppose like a not not not
too fancy but like something something
it comes with notable observations
accounting notes concerning increase in
idle merchandise purchases among testing
staff H marketing advised that super
chats can't be expensed and the
coincidental link between the red collar
of the super chats and some of the kfp
brand colors is not an
excuse I can't write it off
off uh well I'm not the one sending it
so whatever you guys can't write off
your super chats is what that's saying
Chopsticks demonstrate unusual light
reflecting properties when exposed to
stage lighting oh oh oh you're saying
they're like light
sticks imagine people as a joke kfp go
to concert kfp bring Chopstick don't
wave around light stick kfp wave around
Chopstick no no you can do it for one
one second but then bring out your real
light sticks okay team members report
intrusive thoughts about what
gay why are you gay management
struggling to correct excessive hip
movement during standard serving
procedures when Chopsticks
are oh these are so well written they're
so funny okay if you guys want to read
the rest open up your emails if you
registered uh previously then you should
be able to read the full thing in your
email okay
and if you if you're not registered um
I'm retweeting the video right now on my
Twitter and if you go uh and look at
that as a reply there is a link um to
vit ramen.com SL kfp where you can watch
all the previous videos and you can also
sign up for the uh like newsletter
because we still have a couple of items
to go to be to be revealed and you can
vote for which one will be revealed next
[Music]
check the shop you're missing a core
mechanic that's new to this
patch uh okay
later uh yeah so very hype we're getting
we're getting there that was the fifth
or was it the
fourth I think it's is it the fifth item
revealed yeah it might go into your spam
or something so check it out and then uh
yeah make sure that it doesn't go into
spam again all right four oh wow then we
still have five oh my God so many things
to
reveal
um can
I I I I want to like buy more
speed
uh
uh stats okay I still do have put
potential in my speed but I have no
money what
18,000
18,000 so
much AR
Marine yeah that's oh there's still so
many undiscovered
collaps what and super spam collabs H
but I had jingus is that one uh I did
that rarely is that when you combine two
collabs or is it just one collab with
one awakened
item it's been a while since I've done
that I never really get
there collap with item ah I see I
see under
ability um what
what what are you trying to show
me red
bottle unlocks the support items
allowing the use of support abilities
choosen before a stage okay it's pretty
cheap will that help us enough
already well
I don't think I ever cleared stage 4
either are you guys sure it's easier
then we might want to try that
one
it yeah I never tried it I never
finished it I tried it like one or two
times and I never finished it I never
got anywhere it I don't think I even
what what did I do I did no I never
finished the boss did
I did I finish the stage
is there something that says I did or
you just remember
it oh I did huh no
what oh otherwise I wouldn't have stage
five
really damn it okay now I got to get
through
this uh what's a good one protect from
Project projectile attacks for 30
seconds but wait is this item something
I can use only one time in the whole 20
minutes instantly heals 33% of Max
HP oh oh
okay that's
nice dashes forward in moving Direction
and gains invincibility for one
second
um 10 second that's pretty good that's
good if I'm need to like quickly get out
of a tricky
situation just a Dodge
yeah cast a net in front pulling targets
together and collect all ah
okay
uh I guess we could try to dodge on what
but on what key does it
go aha
Ctrl that's a pretty big distance
[Music]
covered how early will I die this time
so far with Coco we really haven't gone
anywhere so
far not past 3 minutes or so even
yeah yeah yeah leave me alone oh God ah
y it's already off to a bad start I need
to get the sticker but I also need to
run out of the bomb but I don't want to
run into the Cannonball right now cuz
the ship is right
[Music]
there yeah it's so over it's so over
already I could have dashed I forgot
about the
dash but
for a moment I'm going to step away from
this
situation get some
distance cool down yeah oh two of them
are
here two
stickers wow we're faster and our attack
the attack is faster and our attack is
biger
MHM Rand but
okay W I need that food actually but I'm
too
far ah no no no no no no no no no no no
no
no I'm so close to the food oh well oh
my my special my special is
[Music]
ready ah
[\h__\h] that was good
timing uh wait I know we wanted to see
Ian Cur that's
the I don't know I want to get the Coco
things but we could also get another
thing with the anur the what was it more
Katana okay for
now okay
there's so much exp
there uh already
awakened but I want the limiter I'll
take the limiter sorry
oh there's another
sticker myth logo sticker
yeah now we can
awaken all right that's pretty early for
me 2 minutes in and I have my Katana
awaken
yeah this is a sunburnt uh
uh um oh my God I'm
dying looked so orange to me a t t no
Sagi okay we surely want PLU type
as uh decrease damage of the main weapon
by 20% but increase damage nah I will
strengthen something in that
case I'd rather do
that then lose so much oh my God ah
yes thank you I really needed
that
um uh a little bit hard to figure out
where and how I'm aiming but
okay oh
it's going better at least are you proud
kfp are you proud I want to make you
proud remember you have a dash it's hard
to push honestly C I kind of want to put
it somewhere
else yeah
[Music]
yippe um
increase speed increase attack size pick
up
range
roll there we
go uhuh energy drink increase it no [\h__\h]
get rid of that N I don't want to I want
to waste I want to waste to drop it I
don't want to lose 20% HP I need that
it's worth can I still drop it after I
accept it and try it out for a
while you need the
speed
no well 40% speed is pretty
fast okay don't feel that much faster to
be honest okay
oh my God please just [\h__\h] off oh this
one's also some uh bird
tan they can all T oh wait or is it my
attack I dropped it
what
subconsciously I I did not want to have
it I
suppose there's a bicycle and there's
the the the the pile the orange triangle
Illuminati cone cone cone
[Laughter]
cone are you kidding me are you kidding
me [\h__\h] do d
nice um become upset are you [\h__\h] why
am I getting all these useless stamps
right
now I'll actually sell this one cuz I'm
not sure if I want to keep the uh the
beig so I'll sell
it no point in upgrading it if I'm going
to exchange it is my opinion you might
not
agree want the B yeah yeah yeah oh wait
I'm ready I'm so
ready burn burn this island must
burn okay we're we're rolling now we're
rolling I get another limiter
but should I yeah
might not Max it out but a little bit
more oh I can back oh [\h__\h] I can
backwards Dash that's good to
[Music]
know uh help I'm
dying
okay good good good situation is back in
control
[Music]
we want to have a collab before 10
minutes but we're already 5 minutes in
and I don't have what am I combining it
with uh anything really anything that
works
but uh a
toilet I don't remember using toilets in
Yakuza games to uh spam enemies
with skiy toilet fan
beam mhm
ah I I I I I got to get this one because
I I don't I won't have the yeah the 5%
loss oh it's a reference to to something
she did okay okay the toilet RTA I
thought it was you know cuz the bicycle
and the Clone was
hands off my box my Amazon
Birches
no no it's kind of when you're that big
it's kind of hard to come back to being
small you know what I mean and the
debuff made me slow huh
[\h__\h]
um one thing I want to do
is change the where is this this one
to
maybe can I not use that
button oh I can't use any of the mouse
buttons damn it I was going to put it on
one of
the wait is space being used yeah
a
maybe what's easy for me to
push maybe
see can't promise but this will go well
still I suck so
there always the Hol house food
Puffs
[Music]
a wait I I don't think I have ever made
use of them so I don't really know how
achievable that
is will I get it later or uh should yeah
I'll probably get it later
hopefully
ah probably would have been fine but
still and defeating turs let's do this
one oh oh oh now the the objects that
they drop because they glow the same way
that like the other things glow
like uh the anvils and stuff makes me
think something special is
there I mean it's still
special there's a new shop upgrade like
eliminate or reall called hold where you
can pin an option to pick next oh
cool yeah that sounds good
[Music]
I I really wanted the
con I wanted it a little bit too
much ah should I get the speed
up oh wait my special is also ready
um should I get the speed on
no don't spawn in the red circle of
[Music]
Doom makes me want to play yakaza
yeah I had a moment to think about
pressing Dash on
[Music]
time 2 minutes
in can we redeem ourselves can we redeem
myself
not die before the first boss at
[Music]
least you can special early
now oh oh that ah but that wasn't Bo for
cuz I was so close to a real special ah
but yeah those are the 5050 % and 75%
once H
H in this case I should have just
waited at least I'm not running into the
cannon balls constantly right
now okay let's try this oh machine gun
[\h__\h]
yeah oh that felt
good uh are we doing sausage
with something with or with the with the
with the tail with the
uh should I take it
no yeah okay I'll work a bit
moreo we're in Cannonball territory
that's not good I I'm
chill chill give
it I'm sorry I'm so
hopeless I'm sorry I need to stay out of
the Cannonball
territory I thought I could make it it's
when you try to cross the street when
the lights are red and you think you're
going to make it but then you get easy
kite but it's okay when you're a phoenix
but cple zire is not a phoenix so I need
to be more
careful leave me
[Music]
alone when you try your best but you
don't
[Music]
succeed when you try your best but you
skip
[Music]
it when you get what you want but not
the r you
need you don't like my song what why
you guys are so
picky okay good stop good stop good go
good good
we're too old for this me
[Music]
too ah guys did you watch yesterday I
uploaded the cheering guide video for
Mirage which I mean you already saw if
you watched the stream but cow carage
made it into a clip thank you so much I
I asked if if please make a the video
into a watchable
repeatable clip so that my kfps can
become Masters At The Art of Mirage
cheering
chanting I hope it's a good reference I
think this will be very
helpful right and maybe
I don't know I mean I know I I know I
know I know but I don't
know um it's best to just be
ready just be
ready where's my
Mouse oh B get out of
there Mirage life will be dope yeah
imagine everybody screaming me me me me
me me you me me me me me me did I miss
twice because
yeah yeah I did yeah I
did I'd be so excited but I know that
like it's hard to get everybody
to do it to even like know about
it if it's like mixed uh fandoms like
not just
kfp I'm sure you know I I I can't I'm
not
expecting everybody
to to get into the
fun but it would be cool would be cool
[Music]
but I hope you guys don't get too
intimidated um should I get the this
one hope you guys don't get too
intimidated when you're like the only
one doing it and the people around you
are not doing it feel confident keep on
doing
it believe in
yourself yeah it's Prett very
simple thank you believe in the me who
believes in you and then I hope you
believe in also the me that believes in
you oh God I got
stuck I might die oh hey there's
food that didn't heal so
much I'm going to die goodbye goodbye
good night good night
[Music]
[\h__\h] I mean I do want the fan
beam eventually
but maybe there's a higher chance of me
surviving if I get one more four now
ninja increase
speed yeah okay
Happ I missed the
[Music]
thing okay let me just get the [\h__\h]
food
here
[Music]
okay yeah I really need need a second
weapon though so I'm going to go for the
saet again even though I don't like it
that much cuz it's I like things that
you know go further into the
distance oh okay we have received a
defense item against our wh but it's a
good one it's good I like
it not
bad the way my heart stops when I get
stuck on something
it's not
healthy by the way for next week when
I'm going on my little Spa
trip I booked some more appointments I'm
so excited I have a massage every day so
much that the the lady on the phone was
concerned she was like yeah maybe after
free massages like one per day three
days in the road maybe if you really
want one on the fourth day as well you
should probably go for a more smooth
soft one I'm like okay I guess but she
doesn't know she doesn't know I am a
massage like
Pro in a way that I I can get massages
every day my body just like after
getting the massage usually immediately
forgets that it has just received the
massage
I'm an addict yeah I just I just don't
sometimes I do get sore muscles from a
really in insanely uh hurtful massage
but yeah as long as I don't let them try
to murder
me then I'm usually
okay okay Dragon is almost ready Let's
Wait for the true Dragon form once again
again and B them all dra
haris the nerys is here to kill you oh
wait this is not the nerys close
enough not into the Cannonball territory
we don't want to go there we don't want
to oh look look what is
here I'm going to upgrade the
[Music]
sausage I think I like this more than
the office at least the office map cuz W
the office is was that a hard
map I think the office was the the first
hard map or it was it I might be
wrong but I struggle so much with the
office cuz I get
stuck all the
time I oh that [\h__\h] that
[\h__\h] that mother but I can dash
out of your I can dash out of your
shitty zone now go [\h__\h]
yourself yeah that's that's really what
I need to dash
for help there there's so many
enemies
help but I'm surviving somehow
I need something that's more distant to
be honest maybe I even get the the
glasses
yeah I might get the
glasses help me GA more things in the
end oh my God the hamsters are armed now
those are noid those hamsters
right woo
oh down down down down down down down
down no no no no no no no
no holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] holy
[\h__\h] please please please what is
this projectile up stamp is it
purposefully looking like a
DOA
emote useless for
Coco okay this this is useless for
go
okay bro don't get me don't get me in
trouble oh look at all the bicycles the
bicycles say
uh campaign I want to buy a
bicycle one of my friends has a really
cool bicycle that you can fold I really
am tempted to buy one
too I was trying to dodge out of it but
my Dodge wasn't ready I hate my life I
hate my life I hate my life you know
know what I want to see some collabs so
I'm just going to go on a different map
now I
think or we go get a
buff uh wait do I have to go in with the
character that I'm planning on
playing or does it not
matter yeah I might go for an easier
map just
to you know actually see something from
the game
again you think I need more gold I guess
I do need more gold we should play P
more then cuz she she was fun and she's
still
new wait so what is this about
food how I don't even know how that
works like any of that this is for
fishing right M how do I make
food I don't really I really don't like
like gardening whatever harvesting
simulators as mini games in games so I
really don't want to be bothering with
this to be
honest I really don't want to do
this do I have any seeds to plant no
can I what can I cook do I have enough
things to cook
something
temp okay we increase attack by 30% for
the whole fight or but what if I die
after 2 minutes I'll be so
sad for the fire okay but then I just it
will be so sad if I die right away for
five Maps oh really
all right five oh my god do I have to
like um select it also like e now or is
it just automatically happening for the
next
five okay so it's working now it's in
effect
now you before you start a map oh during
St oh okay oh wait is it is it separ
separate from the support item like the
dash that we used or is it
additional wait that's the
same how's this work again oh
God
what what's the middle what's the
circle yeah I said the same thing but
okay so it's separate I can have two
things cool uh space okay
Come On Come Back to Me fishy come come
back to
me I hate
fishing hi M
Senpai can you teach me fishing you as a
pirate surely have more experience with
this than me right being on this see all
the time you don't have much choice
of foods right that was good that was
good lobster baby
wao Lobster is just a bigger shrimp oh
my God [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] yeah I don't deserve anything she's
a cosplayer
though I I no she's she's more than just
no for sure she she's been on a big boat
before I know I know I know she does say
that like
yeah but has she evolved in her lore
though
clownish has she evolved yet
like maybe maybe nowadays she's
[Music]
pirating it's all just fantasy see what
what what are you telling me pick what
without Senai is not a real bunny ah
what the [\h__\h] that was so fast and so
many she got a [\h__\h] eel are you going
to give that to me
or tuna
do not disturb the tuna hi guys by the
way um is this like the people that I
hired long time
ago the the
people that will now show up for this
was this like something where you guys
signed up for it long time ago I wonder
if that was how it
worked uh would they maybe cuz that's a
long time ago will you guys be able to
still sign up or like maybe the list
will be cleared once and
then did they update it are there more
people in there
now
cool what free no I'm not going to use
my money for that but you guys do I need
to do how do I how do I deal with you
guys you're all exhausted and you want
food okay if I feed you a tuna is that
going to make you happy again you want
so many though
[Music]
you want potatoes you're lucky I have
some
Tomatoes here I'm doing I'm doing the
thing I'm being a tental I'm feeding my
fish uh my my chickens with
fish I'm hand feeding you
guys I'm such a great
Tel now that I think about
it I'm
honored that we are being represented in
the Holo house area with all these
chickens here because this means that
other people have kfp chickens in their
Hol Holo cure streams too right what an
honor
je or is it their owns is it always
chickens
oh it's
okay I forgot about that so yeah
anything can run around
here all right then yeah probably I'm
the only one who's using
chickens hey they left me some stuff
here oh the
eel the eel was a
steel wait yeah
uh collect types how many do you
3,69 what wa they're going so fast too
oh yeah cuz now I fed them they're so
motivated look at them
go look at them
go if my subscriber count would go like
that
[Music]
nowadays amazing oh my God collect so
much money let's wait until it's 4,000
let me tell you something really
exciting that maybe only German like
people who live in German C German
speaking countries will
understand um you guys know Pringles
right I think Pringles are like
worldwide um
so there's there's these
[Music]
chips I need to tell you about this so
my favorite kind of chips I showed you
these before are these pom be they're
kind of fluffy bears I like them the
most in just normal um in just really
basic uh uh salt flavor these are the
original yeah I like them they're really
fluffy
um and then there's Pringles right who
come in these
tubes now there's I think it's I thought
it was an official poman and Pringles
collab but it just looks like it I think
they just absolutely copied the design
of the Pringles
tube uh cuz I legitimately thought it
was a collab but they have this now they
are less fluffy they're like more
compressed B
and they're like shaped like the
Pringles like with a slight curve and
they lie in there on top of each other
in this 100% copied Pringles tube tennis
ball tube yeah they're called klies for
krisly Bears but I bought it because
this is new and I was like Shook at I
was so shook at I was like what the hell
is this
real legally
distinct I surprised this that this is
legal is it though is
it but I tried
it I have it right next to me actually
it's really good it's like it's like the
pom band it tastes like the pom band but
it's a bit more
like how to say it's like when you take
one of these plastic bags that you put
your luggage in your your clothes and
then you vacuum it the the air out and
it gets compressed compressed they're
more
compressed yeah so the texture is a
little bit
different a little bit
more M I still crunchy they're both
crunchy but this is different I wonder
if you guys could find it overseas I I
think probably not even the original is
hard to find but overseas but is it so
good it's so yummy I want more pom be I
love them
but people who uh live in German
speaking countries where you at are you
in the chat are there any go look for
these I think they're pretty rare cuz I
haven't seen them in every shop I go
into either just saw them in one one
place go try to find him what you waffle
the man is already
exhausted why what do you want to
eat you're the Clown no you're the tuna
guy okay I think I still have a few
Tunas you're lucky but the clown fish
guy man clown fish are hard to come
by but okay we have in the UK too oh
really UK is pal Bears
awesome sasuga dope blit super based
UK okay let's plant some things because
we needed to feed eat the
[Music]
chickens I was really hoping off screen
to make a x potato collab with forgot
what it was I think the the CEO tiers or
or something else I really wanted
to but I died I kept on dying maybe we
can try it now
uh the bomb no I don't think I was
trying to make it with the bumb yeah the
song the song potato and song that's the
one I wanted to
make wait where did my stuff go did I
not buy it wait Did I buy the seeds or
did I buy
ingredients I bought
seeds I need soil
bruh why does the soil
disappear oh my God it's taking all my
[Music]
money I hate this I hate this process oh
my God it's so
tiresome hi s
by nice concert
s already announcing her next
concert very much a
Senai can
reach all the
heights that she
[Music]
wants was so surreal seeing so many
people yeah sa super Arena and now buan
oh my
God but I think sa super Arena has the
the bigger capacity but Budokan is just
like a special place that Japanese
artists always aspire to go
to
so
yeah yeah there's actually like so many
solo
concerts like announced
and like yeah some happened some are
coming these past months the coming
months there's so
many they're like really getting busy
planning so many yeah Fuki zai is uh
coming up and yeah we just had swi zai
yesterday
mhm yeah minin has a tway solo
live there's so many going on
it's like the the life Department really
wants to do more Ira lives
huh yeah Expo coming soon very soon Hol
Fest coming very
soon very exciting time to be a fan a
Holo fan in Japan when you can go to all
these
concerts all right let's play Picola
again and then let's let's choose
[Music]
H I don't
know
um yeah yeah actually let me do endless
because that sounds good to me
but should we just do the
planes but hard
[Music]
okay and then we're going to eat the
Tula wait that
music it's the endless at truck the not
not endless ad truck the ad truck
more speed would probably do good as
well
uh-huh wait do I still have to dash I do
right okay okay cool cool
cool but at least now I have a distanced
attack
again I think I prefer that
generally guess we're upgrading the main
weapon
[Music]
see already looking better than on the
island we're gambling
again this is a money run I just want
lots of money
please to get get more cool
things we got the Kotaku computer
yippee slow the
enemies what what are those Box is doing
there oh wait what is that what is that
those Stars I saw them
uh off screen I wasn't sure what I was
collecting
there for my special oh does it like
charge my special a little bit
more has that been around before is that
or is that a new addition because to me
it
looks like something I've never seen
[Music]
before since last update oh
really um this one has a
buff so I kind of want to take
[Music]
it what do you think I am trying to stay
on a distance also want a limit her
too be
sausage
chicken where are you running to are you
Escaping The
Factory are you trying to escape Your
Destiny come on
what am I going to do without
you how am I going to make the customers
happy we want to make the customers
happy we need to feed
everybody it's your destiny it's your
duty should I get the
glasses maybe not it's more
about Mommy
oh good
okay yeah I mean at least we might get
more collaborations
[Music]
going I don't know I'm just randomly
picking whatever belongs to peka for now
no particular
priority
oh Amazon has
delivered Amazon has been delivering a
lot of things for me
[Music]
too maybe I'll
speed oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my God do
something you know for my bathtub I had
a like a little table which is really
nice to have cuz I I'm not a big bath
person but with the table I I put my
iPad there and then I watch something
and it at least forces me or like pushes
me to stay in the back upb a little bit
longer than I would feel like
without but it's made out of wood and I
noticed after I came back from my trip I
don't know it probably already started
molding before but yeah some parts of
the wood look kind of
moldy um I guess probably because I'm
not going to like Point any fingers this
could have been me this could have been
my um friends or mother who took care of
my cats but uh when showering in the
bathtub the tray was probably kept on
there on the bathtub while showering and
so a lot of shower water was probably
falling onto the
tray and so it was
probably unnecessarily wet a lot of the
time
yeah and then I noticed that some
sections of it became moldy and just
doesn't look nice anymore and then I
don't think you can fix that like you
can remove mold from from other surfaces
like tiles or
so but not from wood as far as I
know the tray shouldn't be able to get
moly in the first but it but it is wood
so it makes sense like I don't know how
you
[Music]
would yeah it's okay I bought a new one
but this time it was hard to find one
that's not made out of the wood I just
wanted something that's safe so I got
one out of
uh I I don't think it's actually glass
but it looks like glass but I think it's
probably plastic but it's like
transparent and it has golden handles on
the
side it looks kind of fancy and pretty
it looks more luxurious than the wooden
one oh my
God bro
so
yeah I bought that too so that my
visitors who shall soon
hello look at my big
schlong sorry
but I just noticed
[Laughter]
now I I didn't realize until now how big
it was
look at
that oh my
God anyway I wanted to make things more
more nice for my guest so um upgrading
everything I also bought golden Cutlery
it looks so fancy look so
pretty
uh now my uh cooking
Adventures oh baby oh not a triple a
super study oh [\h__\h] does that go on top
of the ones I already
[Music]
have yes it does but it goes back to
level
one H that kind of sucks cuz I had on
level two of three I
think oh one is Max oh okay
cool whatever then it's fine
I can't seem to focus at all what do we
want to make
anyway uh with the sausage I was going
to I I made this one
before boys love okay let's look for
boys love or just something that I'm
already working on
okay woohoo
maybe we should prepare another
one or I should drop some food n
actually I want something else for my
defense I don't really want the Uber
sheep food music for potato yeah okay
okay true but why is the potato so rare
is it just me or does it actually have
like more Rarity in this like
shop doesn't seem to show up as
much it's just luck
man oopsie that was by
accident also I want to play some flat
character and use the cutting board
because it's more effective on flat
characters I don't know if PE Senai
counts as one she does have a little bit
going
on I wouldn't I wouldn't I mean I
wouldn't quite stay you L though I don't
works on her do you have know she would
count oh for
real uh are we using the end curse for
something for now no
right okay well damage output and
everything pretty decent so far we have
have a maximum
sausage just need the right
collaboration item you check on
cie Callie what because
well don't don't
worry don't worry guys
there's something strange going
on CI no Call's not goofing around CI is
in real
trouble but I hope nobody's really like
like for real for real concerned if
you're for real for real concerned then
chill
H what did she put up some weird
thumbnail I didn't see
[Music]
it she has a weird stream oh is it
happening right
now uh is this is the stream happening
right
now m
I
see no we're not collabing with fanbeam
I want to collab it with something else
but I guess we're not finding
it bro what's this Phoenix SN looks like
a phoenix collector stamp if a Target is
defeated
within uh 2 seconds after being hit by
this weapon they have a 1% chance to
drop ah that in ah yeah color wise that
makes sense to drop a stamp but may drop
a mushroom
instead
oh I I I don't know about that I don't
like
[Music]
mushrooms seems like the game doesn't
like mushrooms
either should I should I prepare a thir
collaboration with the bounce ball with
the Lammy water or so
here the reballs okay wait the tears the
tears was I going to do something with
the tears no but I
could my my my
my mommy save
us as long as you're here with me you're
safe right I don't even like the bounce
ball collab
M I'll roll one more
time huh huh what the [\h__\h] that's like
the same lineup that I just
had the
limiter limiter is
good
nice ah there it is right right oh
sausage with Bo oh sausage
fest we're
[Music]
coming it's going to
happen I feel it I'm becoming
stronger just don't die waa just don't
die
have you tried not
dying okay we're almost maxing it
already 7 Minutes in so a Boss shows up
at 10 probably again
right what boss have I seen it before a
they're closing in
[Music]
no why did I go up here I want to go
down
[Music]
again I'm so
sorry but we made
money wait do I uh when I press
retry the food does it take the second
out of the five
I should have gotten one more like
defense
item it should
okay is there a counter that I can see
[Music]
wow
explosion I kind of want to go for the
same things
again but now my my sausage won't be as
big how
[Music]
disappointing my my deck will be trimmed
sorry for saying that that's a kfp meme
in case you're not uh here very often
please
understand it's a kfp meme to say trim
your
dick I'll take one for dire times and
dire situations
I can't think of deck without thinking
of trimming exactly
[Music]
perfect me neither
though and every card game that I play
now I think of deck trimming but I mean
every card game need needs deck trimming
anyway it's pretty important
usually it's a core
mechanic okay the dash is really good
cuz you can just you you get in ability
for one second so you also can just zoom
through
uh the enemies if you like want to go
back up quickly question should I take a
roll or just get the bunny I'll just
take the bunny
okay my rocket launcher has awakened
let's
go cooking an Ian
curse uh
yeah would be cool to
have I think is that the one that I
wanted to do but I haven't gotten
uh completed
yet we want sausage and boys love and
Ian curse
and MMA I
guess or something else
whatever a
triple okay change of plans we're doing
whatever works with
the fan beam stick whatever that was
yeah fan beam and we got Uber sheep
[Music]
okay I'll gladly take it
the dragon okay Dragon
de oh right I have my
ulti I should have had more enemies on
the screen cuz it only kills what it
sees right
yeah stuck
[Music]
T what that is are they going to
war oh c they they left something on the
floor they forgot something but I'll
take it fin
finders finder
Fe finder's
luck find your keep find those keepers
oh oh my God
[Music]
chill fre my sausage is getting bigger
in different way never mind that's the
that only makes my main weapon bigger so
sad so
sad I had sausages before the stream by
the way Vice vered
white sausage the one we like to eat
with with sweet
mustard big recommend my mom is also
addicted to
it she ate so many when she was uh here
to visit
speaking of food yesterday I ate a tuna
pizza but it had white sauce I don't
know what it was but white sauce instead
of tomato sauce I think that's the first
time I had a a pizza that was not
classic tomato
sauce except for like dessert
pizza it was pretty good
[Music]
ever had one with barbecue ah I mean
yeah but I think it was combined with
tomato
sauce love barbecue
pizza but yeah yesterday I said that I
socialized and did a lot of
work because ah please let me no please
leave me alone going to [\h__\h]
die yeah I don't know I I currently have
H fresh on Paw so I don't have that much
food oh
God and I was cooking the past days but
my cooking motivation is
K so I was like well on my day off how
about I go meet up with my friends who I
haven't seen in a long time and we have
some pizza that's what we did yesterday
[Music]
yeah I know and the funny thing is um my
friends they also uh found out about
this hiy koni quiz and they all took the
quiz and out of my friends I am by
far by far the highest score some of my
friends have like 22 or something or 30
or
so and and one of my friends was like oh
I bet I bet she aka me has um the
highest score Among
Us and yeah she was right she knows
me but I thought my um friends in
general were pretty antisocial or not
antisocial but like um actually not not
antisocial at all that's not what I want
to say wrong word but just like like to
stay inside home bodies
um I thought they were but I guess I was
wrong cold s if the player does not get
attacked by the Target for 4 seconds the
target may become Frozen and take 50%
cold I don't know if I want
that I think I'll strengthen
this maybe I don't like any of these
stickers that
much but it will do but yeah uh what was
I saying
uh yeah we all did the
test I show them my results cuz I
already had it from before my score is
76 have you guys done
the test what's your score
I am weirdly proud of my high
score oh oh oh you guys are all like at
least over 50 most of you
guys not bad nothing to be ashamed of if
anything just like me you should be a
little bit proud of
it I can't reach the Box
I'll take a
revive now we have two
revives I know that's pretty suicidal of
me right now but I'll I'll I'll I'll
dash out of it
they're gatekeeping my Amazon
boxes okay okay okay okay okay okay
maybe we're fine
y oh look at that
how did I not level up from that the EXP
bar went
like but there we
go the fan beam wait a second wait why
do I have ASA Coco when the [\h__\h] did I
just accidentally choose asak coko at
this very
moment or was
that what or what am I doing what am I
planning I got it from the Amazon box
oh right I don't remember choosing
[Music]
it okay but it's about time that we get
a collab
[Music]
you know how people sometimes
say that you
should take your take a moment to like
call your mom or your grandparents or so
or your dad and tell them how much you
love them and
everything cuz you don't say it too
often and I think you know that
sentiment is is nice
and correct but nobody says says that
about your
friends is it not necessary do people
already always say that maybe they do
but I took the opportunity yesterday to
oh my God I'm going to
die what's going
on oh okay I took the opportunity
yesterday to tell my friends like I I I
made this whole speech I was like you
know recent things in my life made
me think even more that I'm so happy to
have you guys because you you love me
unconditionally and you
guys are great friends that I've had for
a long
[Music]
time wait but I should not have taken
the membership cuz that's making me lose
coins isn't it it's making me those
coins
no two coins per second or something
like that what was
that m m time to die now I'll keep going
but
I I'll just have to collect more more
coins I already have 6,000 in this
run
whatever are we ready for collab yet yes
we are ah ah [\h__\h] that'll be hard to
reach wait let me o let me pick up the
sticker maybe uh or maybe
not okay okay okay okay yes finally
[Music]
finally need shackles does it help
membership yes you get less
coins yeah it'll be fine we won't go
down to zero right
what's it going to be what
oh that's unexpected but nice yeah
sausage the the the the game the sausage
game continuously spinning sausage spins
faster than spins faster As you move and
plus 15 size
yo oh oh yeah that's a long that's a
long oh
wow look at it
[Laughter]
[Music]
nice
nice it's
beans I forgot about my
ulti I could enhance my legendary
sausage but no let's work on
this uh am I
combining can you can you combine the
ASA C plug uh with the fan
beam I don't think that's what I was
planning but you
can okay we might have
to what the [\h__\h] what
a is that you a oh it's 10 minutes and
yeah yeah okay yeah I get it it I get it
that's what's
happening how you going to how you going
to dodge my long
huh you can't that's
[Music]
right
Yoo I'm sorry I'm going to stop I'm
going to stop saying it now stop saying
it woo that was fast woohoo
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
wait this is great we should use that
why why am I running around it I don't
know I was scared I was too
scared it's like I don't want it it's
like I don't want to have
it there you go oh triple again oh my
God I'm so lucky in this run
Oo we get idle
song Idol song X potato or what was
it is that possible
yippee we're definitely oh wait see
we're at 7,6 I was at 6,000 7,000 I was
at six six six
six I was at 6,000 before so we're going
up we're not losing money so far y
be all right here we go second collab is
looking good dragon fire yeah wait I
think that's new for me yeah I don't
think I ever had that oh
[\h__\h] there is a lot going on now
wait there's something down there I I
didn't
realize ah
sticker nice this is a good run we can
make a lot of money here if only I
didn't take the [\h__\h] Super Chat
thing M Staker
yeah now need gorilla paw
there's barely any enemies on screen but
I'm going
to yay play Slots play
Slots addiction is
real H so uh what do I want to be
looking for if we want to do something
with Idol song is there anything new
that I or anything not even new I
probably also haven't done all the
collabs before as well
glow sticks I I think I already combined
those before is there nothing else
potato yeah but potato never shows up
for me but
yeah the ax one I think I've done
before shut up
LPN I want to look for the
potato wish me
luck in the meantime if I don't find it
I'll just I don't know I'll get some
defense
items look how look how it
[Applause]
goes it's
crazy do you guys also swing it around
like that sometimes this is like she
only questions
[Laughter]
again I'm sure
sorry I'm sorry I don't know what's
wrong with me today what a triple again
get away from
me why do I keep on axe okay I guess
that was a combination too right then
I'll combine those I I can't keep on
waiting for the freaking potato the
potato comes to me when it wants to when
it's potato time then we know that it's
potato time speaking of potato
time did you guys see the clip that K
Caren
made uh with Corona and me I actually
kind of requested
that but then after I requested it I
already F like wait is it maybe it's
going to kind of be like weird um
but I I had to laugh again when I saw it
for the clip again I just feel so
evil I just feel so
evil the Panic between you and cor was
so funny yeah I I I don't want to
completely blame the sink chronization
the English uh one because I
think it's also
100% no okay 80% on me oh my God what
what
what for not being immersed enough oh
wait I still have revives why am I
panicking so hard I have free R
still I hate this where the [\h__\h] am I
supposed to go tell
me but the the fact that I'm not immerse
enough is also I think because I just
didn't play for such a long time time
it's literally been like what a year or
something I'm not following the story
that well
anymore you
know so I feel bad
I I don't want to like
disrespect the game and I I don't want
to seem like too
emotionalist but I kind of thought it it
would be kind of ironic to put me in
that situation and that kind of
comparison where I'm
the the evil one because I have to think
back to that one time long time ago
where I was like in that
comparison um where they used a clip of
me talking about the cancer um patient
Super
Chat and I was the good one in that clip
and now look look how far I've sunken
how far I've fallen after four years of
streaming I have become one of the evil
ones seemingly but no I'm I'm
still good old Tak I have feelings okay
I'm still a pretty empathetic uh
empathetic person I would say
I don't want to I'm not sure if I want
to upgrade this I'll just leave it at
[Music]
that I have two two collabs man what am
I going to do next have I decided oh
yeah the axe the axe wait no no no I'm
going to do the axe we're going to have
free collaps this is my best run in my
whole life
maybe this might just be my best run CH
said that it's
I for one enjoy T's chaotic
nature try to get Gorilla PA does it
does it like fix my problem there's GRE
stamp
now I guess I'll switch it with the size
then I think that's already enough to
fix our coin problem coin loss problem
seems I have a hole in my pocket
but I'll just like pick up enough coins
to um flood
it
and wait I'm looking for nothing right
now man uh what do I do what do I do
what I I I rarely like have such a great
setup where should I be going with
this R
roll
okay increase damage of weapon by 15%
and crit damage by
5% I think I'll
exchange with the marking
[Music]
St Markus op yeah it did it did Mark my
I it did Mark the
boss previously
to no okay then F I'll I'll strengthen
instead oh my God we're almost getting a
bird
collab look at my Dodge
game take me down to the Ball
Game oh wait I have something to say uh
some people might already know I didn't
know that she already announced it kind
of on her side so I was still keeping it
a secret but seems like she talked about
it so I'm going to talk about it too
next week's special
collaboration is
finally with
go from is
Idol it's been a long time
coming uh I've been busy I've been
traveling yeah but it's finally going to
happen next week in
3D um I do want to open my own
[Music]
po I'm just I'm I'm going say [\h__\h]
it uh uh cuz yeah she used to stream on
Twitch but now she streams on Africa TV
because they've been the yeah they can't
stream on Twitch anymore because region
lock uh wait what why is this
it and I don't even know how to watch
streams on Africa
TV and yeah hopefully I'll be able to
get you guys a YouTube PV should be okay
should
work we're going to be
streaming together in
fre we have free [\h__\h] collaps now can
you believe it I'm going to get the Anan
CR now maybe
I'm going to try not to die
now I'm spinning many things
yep that's new rock
sure um I'll take
it uh but I already have like upgraded
things so
well I I don't know maybe the
knockback
okay come on do something do something
do something do something
ah okay okay A little bit of panic even
though I'm supposedly really strong now
I'm still
panicking there's a lot of
enemies what do we want to combine that
with um miasma right if we find
it or is there one that I don't know yet
gorilla pal is what oh [\h__\h] I I wasn't
really paying attention to looking for
gorilla paw sorry I know you keep on
saying gorilla paw and I I just I don't
even I don't
listen oh my God [\h__\h]
off
oh save me
I'm
scared spider cooking goost of Ian yeah
uh that yeah yeah that's the m i
mean why girl is pi better with C I
don't know I think they're trying to
negate my Super Chat uh debuff that I
have
maybe getting hella intense
yeah help a for super collab oh with the
Ian
curse oh no for super club with one of
these things that I already have oh okay
sorry I'll be on the
lookout I'll try my best to pay
attention oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God
I want to
die I hope that cleared a lot but I no
they don't stop coming saplings
oo uh I'll take spider
cooking was it a jackpot I can't really
pay attention to what I'm getting
honestly I don't really notice
never I never
do oh
Anvil I I I'm longing for the day that I
will be able to touch you what the
heck there's a long snake with sana's
hair and
many running loaves of
bread am I
hallucinating it must be
hallucinating I feel like it's a little
bit laggy
hell love
friend oh my God I want
to I was so close to getting
the at least it oh another one at least
it wasn't the golden one that I'm
missing out on a g
attack so now a golden anval will appear
or what or it will take a
while so [\h__\h] if I die now I don't
want to die this is like such a great
set
up oh doesn't have to a level three
okay
no now a jack buug jackpot jackpot would
have been
nice oh I killed her
yeah level for there we go now please
spawn somewhere where I can reach you
I I'm I'm I I am I have free anvils
to okay I still have two revives though
so uh this is a normal one um let's do
the spider
cooking
M no no I'll come back I was I was like
right next to it are you kidding me
memberships aren't Max yeah that's kind
of on purpose I I don't know I'm scared
of but I guess I
could that's the pillow
okay where's where's uh where's my arrow
where's my where I feel so
heavy yeah what what what just happened
what finish
oh oh the purple one is up there okay I
can reach it I feel like I left
everybody
behind noise oh there it is there it
is oh this and this dragon fire and
gorilla's
paw I don't think I've ever seen that
before oh let's go Holy Fire spits
Flames which contain the strength of 50
kg all attack damage is also multiplied
1.3 times and we got damage plus 15 and
science plus 15 let's
go I hope I stay alive forever
now can't be too difficult right oh oh
God oh God what what what what what what
what what what what what do you expect
me to do what the [\h__\h] is wrong with you
what what's happening is this like some
weird Rush right before 20
minutes understandable have a nice day
oh where are the enemies it's just like
big red circles and
[\h__\h]
um spider
cing so is there anything else that I
didn't pick up yet I think the field is
clear now
hello I don't know if I've ever seen you
before nice to what no no no not
not no no no no no no no no I can't do
to I can't do to I can't do to I can't
do to no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no I need to kill her
need to kill her otherwise it's so over
for
me no I'm so dumb I'm so [\h__\h] dumb
I'm so [\h__\h]
dumb
aim oops
please die please die please die please
please please die please die please die
[Music]
die I can't I can't Dodge I can't
Dodge I did it I did it I got an
achievement yeah I know it's easier to
dodge for the W but I wanted to stay
close to the damage
wa
W Hallelujah I don't think I've ever
gotten this
far cuz I got the achievement so
obviously yes I've never gotten this far
before
[Music]
wow nothing even gets close to me
now oh
yeah yeah I mean threee crazy collabs
and the super collab and we got more
coming where's the where's the Anvil or
is there can I not get
anymore where is the
Anvil yeah this is endless I guess maybe
I shouldn't have done endless because
now I'm not going to get an achievement
for clearing the stage
[Music]
um I
did an oh there it
is no I didn't now I did
is this is this allow is this legal to
be so overpowered I
mean maybe in Endless it's okay ELD
horor something I've also never done
before summons unknown Horrors May life
steal up to 5% from targets defeated in
warpool yeah
oh is the spawn just really little or or
is this like a nice break cuz I don't
see many enemies why am I just killing
them way too
early where is everybody I can't it
doesn't even make sense to use my slot
machine CU there's no
enemies what if I just stand I guess at
this point it should work
right is this going to work maybe not
it's not
working it wasn't working how
disappointing
um so I can't make any more collapse
right you you still can't make collapse
out of Defense items can
you okay but can I make another Super
collab oh only one super
[Music]
collab
okay then
yeah yeah I think I'll take the
socket I mean we can choose one more
attack item that we can level up to
seven if I want
to can't be anything
get sucked into the black
Whirlwind the black
hole of the Ian curses
oh now they're sending some more
different kind of mobs out again welcome
welcome welcome you are here to
die Isn't it nice what an outlook on
life to
[Music]
have where's my mouse I can't see my
mouse oh well
here
there what the
[\h__\h] that
hurts okay this this is dangerous oh
wait why don't use I forgot about my
ulti no it
failed but the enemies at this point
they're so big in
scale that like you can't even get that
many on the screen if you're running
away from
them unfortun
very very D
us I think I'm going to die soon even
though I'm so
powerful
membership uh no suck
[Music]
it I think I'm just going to sell it
oh my God try it out take membership
okay next time I'll take membership
then leave me alone guys
help
help endless mode is just depressing
because
it only Ends by you
dying then you'll feel like a
failure it's not not a good way to end
it it's not
satisfying
yeah nice clear
got to clean up a little bit every once
in a
while that's endless mode for
you I'll take it I'll take
it you shouldn't use Rock heart St
because you can't stand still and you
basically only using two STS really
really but
it was a nice
joke maybe it's time to
use uh to get
another maybe the bomb I think I'll take
the
bomb it's a nice joke I want to keep my
rock hard them it's it belongs together
with my
sausage they've gotten used to each
other now I can't take it away now it'll
be very disappointed
I don't know if my sausage will work
properly anymore if I take it
away it'll have some ah arrows
ah it won't swing
anymore okay
um well why not why not ah okay true I
do move all the time okay okay okay
okay my my sausage can take
it
ah gain 280 hoorns
concealable
280 I
mean two
[Music]
a good angle good angle good angle we
like to see it
yeah oh
no come on do it do it do it yeah I
risked it by standing close to everybody
trying to Center myself with some
enemies got a good view over
them yeah yeah yeahoo
[Music]
I'm not liking this this is quite the
spam is there another boss com
eventually or we're at 30 minutes
almost it's
crazy okay I'm stuck I'm
stuck I saw the end of my life in front
of
me my whole
life as a
slideshow I saw it all my
memories of whole
[Music]
alive and my previous fenus
lives all because of one [\h__\h]
fence Dodge is really good even if I
don't really need to dodge it gives me
one second of invincibility I love it I
love it I love it I love
it oh my God pleas oh no it's it's it's
a Spam again they're spamming again I
don't think I have a revive left or do I
oh my God got y so yby so
wait wait the revive was are cleared
every well now I certainly don't have a
revive
left oh it's not ending
ah it's not ending it's not ending
than it's okay wa it's it's endless it's
not so wait actually wasn't the thing
with endless that it does end at 30
minutes at least for achievement or
so come on Tak you can do it I believe
in
you to
[Music]
victory to Victory
I'd like this to end
now this is very over stimulating
I want it to end on a high note
[Music]
ideally that's my fault I shouldn't have
gone up I wanted to do a
curve and go back
up it's my
[Music]
fault I should have continued going down
I don't think I'll ever be this op
[Music]
again 29 minutes and 1
seconds I could have gone to 30 for my
probably the first time in my
life the performance of my sausage was
outstanding Record
Times spinning for winning spinning the
winner to win it's
like it was like a
dream how has it already been 4 hours I
feel like I've only been playing for 2
hours New Stage unlocked oh well that's
at least something stage two
hard
uh I'm not going to play it but let me
see which one is this oh oh evening H
office well at least I unlocked
something
yeah I think we're going to play again
cuz there's new characters that I
haven't tried out yet we're going to
play again another time I have to get up
a little bit early tomorrow for a tech
test with
gusu u I'm going to try out their
software cuz like for the collaboration
the special collab that we're doing um
I'm going to use their
software I need to figure it out
yeah
yeah yeah go a collab I need to like
urgently brush up my Korean skills ah
I'm going to open dualingo before I go
to sleep for the first time in the
million years that's why I said a while
ago like oh man I need to I need to
brush up my Korean in a little bit again
bring back those memories of the few
words that I know passion
[Music]
Korean uh dingo gorilla nah dingo
gorilla isn't possible we have to ask
like what was it five days in advance or
[Music]
so
unfortunately but yeah the collab is
next week on
Wednesday
um Korean prime time so like same same
time zone as Japan so it's going to be
like a pretty bad time for us I guess
um yeah but you guys can watch the
archive if you want I'm sure I can do my
own POV so there should be an
archive I don't mind waking up for it
early a really on a Wednesday thank
you sasuga kfp so early afternoon you
yeah I don't know something
around uh I think yeah noon 12 noon or
so I think it's
8 8 7 or 8 p.m. Korean Standard
time I'm nervous I'm so nervous like
Go's fan base you know they've always
been pretty nice seemingly like when we
had some more communication going on
they were always like reporting
everything I said about go to
go and then they reacted together uh
they're really nice yeah but I I don't
really understand Korean well anymore I
forgot everything I
knew and oh
yeah I'm nervous it's been such a long
time since we first interacted
especially because uh the VBA awards are
about to happen again right and the
whole reason me and goo started
interacting in the first place was the
vtu awards last year I guess
so it's pretty much a year since we
started
interacting great timing huh we can
celebrate our
anniversary go k anniversary a year in
the making yeah this collab will be a
year in the making how did it take so
long I don't know I'm sorry
um we've come full circle yeah speaking
of guys I think the nominations are
still open you can still nominate me for
whatever you want Google ret Awards go
to their website and if you feel like it
you could you could nominate me if you
want
to
yeah please check on Dad I'm scared
let's
see let's see let me
check oh
um h
[Music]
H oh what does that
say okay okay I didn't know it had such
a voice this weird cat
oh she's advertising the
plushy
genius I see what this is Cali it's a
marketing
plot ah it's like taking up for 40% of
the
screen oh yeah you guys get yourself a
weird cat plusy but don't put it next to
froggy waa first of all I'm scared of
them trying to kill each other but at
the same time there's chances that they
will you know put their powers in their
little brains together and their will
for chaos and
murder uh so they either kill each other
or together they will kill everybody so
don't put them
together this is terrifying shut up this
I don't want to hear that that's going
to give me nightmares I already have
many problems with nightmares
although my last stream last night was
actually good for once I'm going to mute
it now because I I have enough
nightmares as it
is I have a feeling that stream will go
on for a while that c
stream if you want
nightmares go for
it I muted the demon yeah you can do
that who would have known you can mute a
demon demon the demons in your
head yeah I'm going to go eat something
now I'm going to not read super chats
today I need to go grab some
food um and sleep try to sleep early cuz
yesterday and the day before I slept so
late but I need to sleep a little bit
more early so that I can be ready for
the tech test with goose go I hope
that's okay for you guys yeah I had fun
I I want to play again next week I don't
know if I have time if I can squeeze it
in otherwise next next week
mhm then we'll play with all the other
cute girls that I have gathered in the
gacha and maybe offc screen I'll play
some
more gather some more money although now
we have a good amount at
[Music]
least but can never have enough right I
always need more
[Music]
money sub it in for inscription
it no I think so tomorrow maybe I don't
know I'll see uh how I feel
tomorrow I was kind of stressed out
today and yesterday was like dragging my
mood down to be
honest uh we'll
see bring your steam deck to the spa my
steam deck is so
thick it's so big and thick i' rather
bring my switch honestly
[Music]
I spent 1.5 million since yesterday whoa
on
what
[Music]
she I already checked your stream like
literally two minutes ago and I played
the audio on my stream you just arrived
here huh wait the cat is gone where did
it go where did it go it's
gone no it's there
what a relief is it a relief that we see
it
now or is it more
concerning is it a sign is it going to
climb up what is that Tokyo
Tower is it giving us a
hint guys be careful oh the stream was
buffer ah
she's not a good streamer is is is a
good jump scare going to come I'm scared
no it's red now it's red it's
red no jum SC
what I can't cycle the the break the
cycle break the cycle how do I break the
cycle somebody cut Call's internet
cable or does she mean a bicycle
I don't have a bicycle does Cy have a
bicycle do we need to break the
bicycle oh the text is gone maybe the
cycle has been
broken although I have a feeling it
won't be broken for a while why don't
you answer
me she pinned the
comment maybe because it's kind of hard
to read
okay I I I uh will leave you uh with
this whatever that is if you
want um
yeah good luck Chad in German we say
alen mm you want to be raided should I
carry you there is that really
responsible for me to drop my kids off
my
chickens at the weird cat's place
doesn't seem very
responsible you can't really defend
yourself so
well I submitted your nomination bus
thank you that's very nice of you
appreciate it let's see if we'll make
it when do they announce it though I
don't even know
[Music]
thank you for
watching okay
a stream Mirage bye-bye
[Music]
oh I might have the next
Mirage uh dance shorts by
tomorrow just
need confirmation
[Music]