[Music]
hey
bye
[Music]
foreign
get down again
ohio
ah i literally just woke up
hello everyone i did not show for sleep
i woke up for
10 minutes before the stream but some
things
didn't work right away ohio
[Music]
today we are going on a vacation
we have recently played
[Music]
super mario 64 which was fun
for the first stream but everything that
came after the first stream
was horrible and painful
totemo
so we move on to a game that i have
way better memories with
way better i played i never um
finished this game and i never like
played it like completely
but i remember playing it every now and
then
a little bit probably i
i just uh used my brother's
saving uh data
ah others music
[Music]
yeah probably just always use my
brother's saving data and then play it a
little bit
uh but it's so nostalgic to me i love it
ah let's go
go go go go go go
oh my god i missed
i missed 0 for 40k last night
because i went to sleep all right so
here's for the two for the two thank you
mwah let's go have a vacation
did you guys go on vacation this year
it's kind of hard to go i know but
i actually went to vacations anyway
look at that oh so thanks for the red
super chat
welcome to the tropical paradise of isle
delfino
we're so pleased to welcome you to our
beautiful home is the audio too quiet
come enjoy a natural wonderland to which
we've added the world's finest resort
facilities
a spectacular amusement park and
succulent
[Music]
someone suspicious
volume up italian okie dokie oh just
went up by itself
[Music]
i love this music i want to go to hawaii
sunshine
everyone press a press a
press a press a mario sucks
very much indeed hey
[Music]
[Applause]
that's all the options you give me wait
that's all the options to give me
[Music]
yes i gave up on 64. yes never going
back again
oh what's wrong with mario he had like
hearts in his eyes he was
ready to make some loving
what happened here
don't touch that stuff oh no
did that sound like peace
here comes the guy with the brush
peak voice acting i am most concerned
with the well-being of the princess in
this dreadful heat
master mario if you would cross over to
that show the makeup is melting
[Applause]
mario be careful i have a bad feeling
about this
no problem
[Music]
remember psk use it to show me some of
those famous jumps
oh i'm good with something leave it to
me
wow okay okay now we're not really
supposed to go in there but am i
supposed to do it just to show uh what
happened yeah okay here we go
[Applause]
beautiful colors what do you want me to
do oh
hello my new friend my best friend
[Music]
power up complete thank you for
purchasing this item from gad
science incorporated was expensive to
register customer information
scanning and classifying subjects
here's my face look at my face i am
flood
a flash liquidizer dowsing device i hope
to be of assistance
checking me out man
[Music]
proceeding with user instruction
use the button
and one of those people who always has
to look at their controller
to check out where it's at r r and c l
and
ellis
so what do i do with that press the x
button to
switch to the hover nozzle uh-huh you
can okay
actually there okay just have to check
where accident
is empty no water can be sprayed
[Music]
okay
i kind of want to hear it again but i'll
uh i feel sorry for you guys so i will
not hear it again
okay what was that ah okay the normal
one
no problem
[Music]
can i only um
control the pump by moving my whole body
right
there's like no separate uh control
thing thank you for the rest of
fantastic
thank you oh i'll reach all of them
later
how do i yeah i can't aim right ah r r
[Music]
mario okay
wait am i in front of the water tank
thingy
yep okay i don't need to see that
thank you
i told you guys i'm gonna buy this uh
uh-huh i told you guys i'm not gonna
have any problems with this game because
it's
easier than 64. and now should emma
supposed to do that
it's gonna be a fun fight my friends
very much fun
i'm looking forward oh no how do you
keep spreading it
[Music]
maybe
oh someone's stuck in there let's help
them
[Music]
oh you're bouncing you're bouncing
hey hang on it's you this whole message
no
no no no no no that's an imposter
it's not me believe me i did nothing
wrong
okay give me a break i still need to get
used to the controls okay but we'll
we'll get there we'll get there okay
there we go
just fight
i got water
wake up it's morning time
hydration check my friends
[Music]
you need to drink about one liter per
day or maybe two liters
i don't know i definitely don't
[Music]
we're gonna save the island nice work
oh thank you quite an unusual device is
it some sort of
pump yes lord glad to meet you
i don't remember what the name was in
the german version because i used to
play the german version
oh [\h__\h] oh that was the police no why he
only did
ah because of his chat
is there anyone in the chat who didn't
play the game as you are no doubt aware
someone has been senselessly defacing
fair isle deltino
using some paint substance actually no i
think the german version is also
english voices but only german second
way of life
how can one not be aware of what it is
so many people
though it is daytime what our poor
residents tremble beneath the veil of
god
has arisen because all of our guardians
the shines damn
have vanished from their gathering spot
at the shine gate
damn it's quite obvious
this horrible graffiti is to blame
behold this sketch of the perpetrator
witness descriptions
i just literally just came to can you
maybe start thinking logically i just
came to the island didn't you see the
goddamn plane
if you would use your goddamn brains for
one second
i hereby order the defendant
is completely free of his vile magic
objective
to leave court adjourned
wait today did i accept my plea no
doesn't look like like it this appears
to be quite a predicament
mario data analysis [\h__\h] italia is
[\h__\h] inhabitants are indeed troubled
by poverty just came to this island boy
how was i supposed to do all this damage
mario you witnessed this object idiot
airstrip
correct it is a shine sprite
shine sprites are the source of power on
isle delfino
together in great numbers at the shine
gate but the gravity
incident has polluted the island and
most of the shine sprites have fled
there is no longer any power to support
the peaceful lifestyle of the islanders
it is most pitiable bird swears
beautiful
way to ensure the return of the shine
sprites
is to keep the island from becoming any
dirtier why you not join the l-14
club i don't
remember being invited
tomorrow we must do our best to resolve
this situation
no thank you go straight you can't miss
the mess now
your first job is to get rid of all that
ugliness
and remember we'll be watching you pal
we'll know
[Music]
my favorite city in the world
what was it called something delfino
plaza delfino or wait is the whole city
called plaza delfino
try bouncing off two walls in the corner
to complete a triangle shape jump where
do you want me to do that
sure i can do that i can do that totally
no problem i can do that i'm a pro
jumper
i'm a pro jumper but why do you want me
to do that
oh mario yo i just knew you would be
oh [\h__\h] what that looks like
damn someone's having stomach issues
here
what's up sorry didn't we this is hardly
my idea of a relaxing vacation
i want to go home right now
ah should i talk to you too you seem
very excited
well i pleased to see you safe i must
tell you
we were walking around town earlier and
it seems the area near the shingen is
still quite bright
perhaps you should check it out
should i maybe clean this up why are you
not acknowledging this mess
i'm gonna help those
clean yourself man don't go take a
shower or something
unbelievable
[Music]
another one of these boys
ah i haven't finished cleaning him when
he wasn't finished
this team's gone oh thank you for
another red super chat
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
okay no problem i'm aiming i'm aiming
drink it
drink it i said drink it
now's the time
nice do i get another shine surprise
[Music]
no no no no no no no no
it's an imposter oh yeah we gotta oh
we're gonna run after him now
oh mario i'm coming
princess peach wait i can't spread right
there was no sprinting option
oh wait i think i remember
oh no problem i remember chasing him
for the whole city like for like 5
million loops
wait that was it oh no here we go i
guess yeah
that's what i remember wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait i'm not hitting him oh wait am i
not supposed to hit him out
okay
[Music]
where did he go i don't see him
in the plaza where is the plaza what
exactly is the plaza
is that here
hello
[Music]
he's heading for the square where's the
square
[Music]
see i can do this can you do this i
doubt it oh there he is
i'm just supposed to like get him like
that oh no
oh you want to show me something okay
okay i wasn't supposed to catch you okay
that's lame you escape into the graffiti
mario try spraying it with water no
problem
and here we go our first world whoa
let's get in there
it's not really my first time but i
never completed it and it's been years
so um it still feels uh a bit closely
bianca hills oh i know what we're doing
i know what we're doing
oh he bent it he totally did i saw it
emergency meeting oh the music
not really huh well he he ran so fast
though
this is so much easier than 64 though
like for real
controls are so forgiving too
see like in mario 64 i would have never
made that jump
or this one okay but this one yeah
[Music]
hello stupid children
look where you're walking i'm i'm older
than you okay
so you gotta you gotta respect me
respect your elderly
little brat
[Music]
bug
no
wait for the right moment okay too early
professional i would say wait wait i
want to get up there wait wait wait
[Music]
okay
so these are like red coins my friends
watch oh blue coins okay
blue coins watch and learn
[Laughter]
[Music]
bottom right huh you can see i'm already
playing this much better than mario 64.
anyway we gotta go there
so are you guys gonna miss the mario 64
gameplay
i'm not gonna miss it i'm definitely not
gonna miss it my friend
please never again it was only hurtful
for me
it hurt my heart my brain my everything
yes you're gonna miss it but maybe
maybe if i'm like super skilled thanks
for playing oh the trees are coming back
maybe if i'm super skilled after playing
this game
maybe we can come back to 64 one day
i'm not completely saying that i'm ever
ever ever gonna play it ever again
mario is gonna get cocky if his family
isn't threatened
do i even have to clean this much i
probably just have to clean my own path
[Music]
probably right
myself
he's aiming for me
you will regret it i
will
[Music]
don't disturb me right now i'm busy wait
for it
actually
i always uh try to aim to the ground
even though i want to aim up i don't
know my control sticks just
kind of wants to go up down
we did it friends we did it
and here come the stairs right that was
right
okay the bridge i guess mine
[Music]
nice the path is clear
victory
that's the first sunshine in here oh
my father have to go to the top already
we already got two two two two
amazing my favorite name i think it's
also my favorite mario game
yes yes just like how my favorite zelda
game is wind waker
vote for gamecube games what happens
[Music]
here
i love all the fruits in this game okay
what's up pete
mario welcome back
we're so glad you're safe mario this
vacation has just been a whirlwind of
bizarre events huh
and now the boats to the hotel isn't
even running
oh [\h__\h] wait the hotel oh i remember the
hotel
you better not go there it's it's better
here right now
do we just go into the same world i
guess yeah let's go into the same room
[Music]
bianco hills down with pt piranha oh he
had a name
i'm so glad that this uh
super mario 3d pack whatever
got released uh
right around our debut time
because i only have a switch right now
with me
i used to have a gamecube but probably
as [\h__\h] again probably doesn't even
exist anymore
yeah and capturing uh those old
uh consoles is probably also a pain in
the ass
so i'm really glad oh it's all dirty
again
stupid baby aren't you right wearing
diapers
up here
ah
you have a baby i have so many babies
though and they don't they don't poop on
maybe it's me to change this one
okay ah no problem see this is so easy
like getting on that rope though
i i didn't even really aim for it but
like this is like how easy
super mario sunshine is
hello you want to explain that what oh i
mean you guys you guys are my baby
am i doing a good job i'm doing pretty
good huh
yeah well now i'm running on the border
no do i have to go down again
wait i have to go all the way down again
okay and then all the way up again
i can swim faster
very much enjoying this who knows maybe
one day this will be painful too
i mean it wouldn't be fun if it wasn't
painful
at all
this is so forgiving
oh yeah by the way if you guys haven't
seen it
you guys haven't seen it
uh i am planning
or like not planning i'm doing an
unplanned stream
hey
i'm doing an unplanned stream today
later today uh
at 10 pm japanese standard time
um i'm gonna play this game called molly
online
[Music]
uh which is a online training
not not virtual actually like there's
there's a real friend game
and you uh ah
do it i'm gonna play an online training
because
currently this game molly online has
like collaboration
with um
and they have like tekora and money
merchandise
did you see that guys
[Music]
no problem no problem okay here we have
to go
okay that's okay one one fail
is acceptable
i i'm not gonna try to get like all of
them
all of the merchandise but i at least
want to get
one of these questions
hello what's wrong with you by the way
oh we're already
[Music]
continue
i never imagined myself being someone's
mother
oh it's on top but we're gonna fall down
right
hello hello i came from you
should i change your diapers
[Applause]
my controller be viving
i'm an engineer cutscene
oh very heavy baby very happy baby you
gotta lose some weight
do some workout do you even lift room
[Music]
where do i get my why do i get water by
the way when i need
[Music]
to get water during the fight right
okay let's ignore those for a while are
you not gonna
do i have to do that when he oh god the
water came out of himself
i guess stop it
stop it oh that also gave me did that
give me what i wanted
i'm just cleaning up after him this is
not good
[Music]
and he has swallowed
yeah you tell me that now you tell me
that now
okay thank you for telling me that
afterwards um very helpful
that was really like
[Music]
wait i'm almost dead how do i get my
life back how do i get my life back
up the point the coins the coins the
coins
okay no problem we got this i figured
out everything i have
completed my investigation i'm ready to
ground pound ahmed
and here we will see how important it is
to
use quantitation marks
if i'm not going to grant ame i'm ready
to ground pound
i'm telling that
[Music]
open your mouth open your mouth
no don't look over there
[Music]
there's so much going on there's so much
going on
[Music]
where could you please puke out another
plant please
[Music]
i don't need water but okay
i don't want to die right now i need to
show my skills
[Music]
but he's not he's not doing it if was
that it
is there a maximum you're gonna do oh my
god what's happening
what's happening he's going crazy
lord save me
i'll go all in doesn't matter if i die
wait no no no no
[Music]
i'm ready
i'm bad at this game i take it back i'm
bad at this game
[Music]
wait wait wait
stop [\h__\h]
[Music]
i don't mind wherever
just keep on opening your mouth forgot
to please
we almost filled them up
[Music]
right
survival mode learned it from your mom
you know how to do it oh yeah
[Music]
she cannot die for some reason
almost
[Applause]
[Music]
okay we got it i think one more time one
more time
oh so i could use some new water too
[Music]
oh that's not why did i do that
it's pretty clean here now
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
over there okay
[Music]
i jumped on it
wait i can't focus on the baby right now
it's too dirty here
ah i need some kfc cleaning personally
where is my cleaning
[Music]
okay okay one more one more one more one
more
open your mouth open your goddamn mouth
it's feeding time
i don't have milk but i got some water
for you
i drank all the milk already it's very
delicious cali's milk
open your mouth
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
hmm
foreign
no problem we'll just do it all over
again
it wasn't uh that hearts to get up there
no
[Music]
we were so close though
we're so close
it was like definitely only one of those
uh
ground pounds left pretty sure about
that
and i was like so close to filling the
baby up too
like the valley was already like so
close to maximum
i need to be a bit more but why did why
did it not
produce any of the slant babies anymore
if i had those i could have filled up my
my 18s
[Music]
why
god damn goddammit sending me mixed
messages there
use the water
goddammit
we'll do it this time we have learned
from our mistakes i mean i have learned
some
mistakes you guys did nothing wrong of
course
very close okay here we go we're already
at the top
okay
it's kind of slow okay i'm back you
stupid
baby i'm back
bite me again
[Music]
yes you're fat is that the second time
you've realized
okay i'm gonna do it much better this
time i have to
from my learn
[Music]
okay why do you want to spit it out
first huh huh
huh here wait wait
ah i was in the right direction
[Music]
hey but this one was like got out there
like instantly
instantly i didn't even have to wait
like
the moment he puked it out it came out
there
[Music]
produced itself i didn't even have to
until it explodes
[Music]
but okay we gotta do what we gotta do
the game is telling me to do this
nintendo
everybody wear like more
[Music]
careful with this kind of thing
maybe maybe
[Music]
at least i stopped him from puking
number one
you and me mario and the baby
[Music]
ah
what
the map
ah come on baby
come on look at me look at me spit at me
no but it wasn't enough it was enough it
was enough
yes
one more come on this round is going
much better
this round is going much better
[Music]
now i finally understand where the
ground pound is but it's basically what
i imagined
yes that's the last one i think
[Music]
[Applause]
whoops
[Music]
wait
first try totally first try
but not i think it was pretty good i did
pretty well i would say
right now what do you mean
[Music]
here
thank you for coming does that mean the
collab is over
wait i keep on doing that but i don't
want to run over there ah can i make it
can i make it do i even know where it is
i got it i got it wait do i have to do
that with this one too
no problem no problem no problem no
problem i'm coming
[Music]
nice speed i am speed
okay what do we do next we go in the
same world again it doesn't it doesn't
seem like i have any other
worlds available anyway so let's go
neck crack bianco hills the hillside
cave secret
secret what was that again
ah i remember
that kid but i don't remember what was
inside
no problem we'll just let it surprise us
can i ever make this jump well at least
doesn't fall in
not bad
press r free to aim better hold our two
what is r3 oh
[Music]
you're welcome
you guys probably told me that a million
times by now thank you for the super
chat i have finally noticed
[Music]
i think
don't need this [\h__\h]
[Music]
and this boy on the left side wants to
kill me please no
i'm telling you what you're seeing here
is professional gameplay of super mario
sunshine
i can't i was actually really surprised
ouch
what is that i'm really surprised that
so many of you haven't played the game
yet
[Music]
you just asked me to hurl you didn't you
no no no no
no no oh
okay
i didn't really ask you but thank you
do i want to stay up here is there
anything
up here that i want to do do i have to
be up here to
over there probably not how do we
get there i remember it being a bit of a
pain in the ass to get to that cave
[Music]
a guy came out all covered in goop and
ran on the the bridge
i wondered something bad was after him
how disturbing
indeed disturbing indeed
suspicious i would say let's
try to i'm probably gonna not make it
make the jump but let's try
yeah oh i made it
okay
jumping from one platform to the other
like this is
not my strong suit but
okay now this kind of scares me how do
i i jump over right while i'm on the
on the rope i can do
oh he held on to it nice one mario
who saw that coming
[Music]
some water while we're at it
more time mario i'm still
not mad at you we're still having a
healthy
uh relationship so it's all good mario
don't be scared of me
i'm not gonna kill your family yet just
yet
excuse me mario
you've made that jump before why don't
you make it this time
got anything to say actually we can just
go from that side i guess
okay let's just go that way don't know
if it will make it easier
[Music]
oh close almost fell off there
water looks nice come on mario
come on come on control yourself okay
welcome to the membership
i forgot about that thank you
[Music]
nice job that's right i should use that
okay that's actually safer
oh yeah it actually gives me stable
landings huh
okay we can do this
[Music]
but this one can i even make that one
for me now i have to do like a side jump
or something right or
back jump
[Music]
so good it's so good it's so good it's
so good
welcome to the membership thank you
damn he's doing some really uh dangerous
jumps there
oh okay wait for it
now's the time mario mario
mario no mario mario
[Music]
okay
how do i do this one
[Music]
this is what i wanted to see and hear oh
yes
[Music]
be
we will have no aggression whatsoever
just happiness just good vibes
we're having a good time we're just
having a good time and i know i have to
jump on those nails
oh grandpa oh my god
oh all you give me for that is a coin
i'll take it
[Music]
okay forget that forget that name
mario
[Music]
no problem thank god we start in here
again
and not outside okay this was just a
warm-up
[Music]
we will not fail anymore
how many more times can i try until i'm
gameover
[Music]
no wait zero
okay concentration
real just concentrate it's not that high
it's the first one anyway so it can't
even be that bad
i've done this many times like
millions of years ago probably don't
quite remember
over there maybe take this one
oh [\h__\h] that was a bad one maybe i don't
know where to go
here
yes yes yes yes yes i'm here
i'm almost there okay now don't [\h__\h] it
up kiara
maybe we should change the perspective
for this one
i get those coins do i need them
for what
i just want me to fall down
or am i getting anything else besides
the coins if i get two of them maybe i
get a lie
i don't see it where is it
yeah so easy to reach thank you very
much thank you
i kind of need it now i have a feeling i
will not survive this
oh wait i don't even have my pumps
i haven't really practiced my jumping
much
is this a normal jump probably this is a
normal jumper i have confidence
okay have confidence
what do i stop in the middle or do i
keep on jumping
oh there's a train
[Music]
jump
don't fall asleep mario open your eyes
it's all
very important right now to not die
oh
[Music]
i'm so scared i'm so scared kawaii
uh
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
hmm
i just wanted that one um
[Music]
i kind of had it coming i kind of felt
it i knew it would come
[Music]
will we do it this time
yes we will confidence confidence we
just need some confidence
oh this time we made it right onto the
rope
we are getting better my friends this
dude is dirty again what happened
i need to get used to using that
perspective
[Music]
while getting into the cave should be
easy now
right piece of cake as many kids
as mug guy yeah
at least this game is forgiving with
these kind of jumps
realize i would have fallen down already
10 million times
okay okay
[Music]
yes english vocabulary top-notch today
no no no wait what why
why mario why didn't we go down here
for what reason what is what is so
special here
is there anything to see um i don't see
anything
always blame it on mario not on myself
always blame it on mario
sorry guys uh i i know it's a bit
frustrating to watch me play
wow this
this is kiara i'm a pro and platformers
it's my specialty it's the fun part okay
thank god
i can show you more of this failing
misery
this is what i'm good at
oh it worked actually i didn't even have
to do a big jump okay so
here how about you do it like you did
last time
just like that exactly
and now we're in again my friends we're
in again
[Music]
he stole my pump no
no no no
no problem all good professionals
thanks for the super chats by the way
mario is a whole giant
i agree
[Music]
how do people just get on these nails so
easily [\h__\h] those nails
sorry
this one is easy okay we're already here
again hello welcome back
that job was not necessary mario you
could have done a normal jump
why did you try to give me a heart
attack
[Music]
we wait until we get to the other side
okay
[Music]
here we go
see that was first track not bad not bad
not bad not bad not bad not bad
getting getting much better and working
better than when i played super mario 64
right i would say i would say it's going
much better
my neck crack disabled my
my my game capture cause i touched
wait uh could you come back please
could you come back
[Music]
the game is still on though the game is
still on it's just uh
it's just the game captured
why are you being a little [\h__\h] now huh
come on yep
yep yep
however now we need to get it to work
on the stream again
please please don't crash my stream laps
i have a deja vu with this
there we go she is sleepy boy
welcome back i have fixed my technical
difficulties there's no need to worry at
all
good
pete morning do you say have i been
doing a good job
mario welcome back
we're so glad you saved mario this
location's just been a whirlwind oh no
are you a robot by any chance peach have
i been deceived by you all these years
are you a robot keeps on repeating what
they say
[Music]
yep
i don't know where i'm going just
looking for something interesting i
think there
i think there was something interesting
down here
it was useful for something yeah i'm
venting right now
[Music]
maybe it's just a way to get to places
i will kill you in front of the whoa the
rest of the crew
[Music]
just like in among us
if you if you don't like the fact that
you know
then i bend it
[Music]
to have me shoot some fruit into her
basket
that was a another small cycle
i guess i guess i have to
keep on going into that one world until
it
activates the other world right okay
here practice
[Music]
wasn't there a sunshine spread for
getting hundred points
i think that's probably what the vents
are
useful for you'll miss one new world
did i the other world is open
head to the harbor wait ah
this one nice oh is that
is that the one uh where you can
we serve another one
i mean it makes it a bit easier i guess
nice already killed it
eliminated oh maybe not if you press r
i thought it was eliminated already
you shall not pass
new world activated i think
hey here's the new world
make it shine oh yeah that is the
surfing world
[Music]
is that the attention is that inna is it
time for inna
[Music]
we're gonna cut off or rip out her
tentacles wow that's
i'm sorry enough but i just gotta do
[Music]
that hurts it
i always thought it was kind of
aggressive how he defends the enemy
like a baby round pounding the baby and
then ripping out the tentacles
of a big inner tongue
from a different dimension don't worry
about it
i like that oops i dropped myself
press b for what
didn't i just press y to flip the gate
down i went hanging press key okay
why would you change life
i know where to go basically mario mario
mario needs a groundhog
flip for this sketch okay i don't want
to go
the sign is telling me to ah go there
[Music]
no yeah this is what's so fun about this
map
maybe maybe we don't have to go
[Music]
because i know it's up there
is that the only way to get there
anyone knows
[Music]
that's kind of difficult
which way do we go
[Music]
oh
oh i can't get
[Applause]
[Music]
maybe i don't need to go to the top
maybe here it's gonna happen
hey who told me i can get over there can
i really
i'm
[Music]
come on come on come on come on come on
come on no hey you're lying to me
[Music]
are you sure have you played the game
do that jump up here up up
[Music]
you have
but how did the game intended
sorry guys please don't be frustrated
with me yet i'm getting there i'm
getting there
sorry guys i'll hurry up
i'm running out of water okay so what
[Music]
now
these climbing things are a bit
frustrating though
as i remember
oh
[Music]
this is confusing
oh
[Music]
that's my big bro over there see him
he's been practicing
throwing people oh no i'm not gonna talk
to him then he's got ways to go but
practice my birthday
okay
okay here we go oh my does he have to
actually
maybe we have to get him to me
tells me to go there
and i should refill yeah but then i will
be
starting from the beginning again i
don't want to do that
water on the wheel
yeah i would never bother that
oh it's sinking again yeah what do i do
what do i do
water left oh it goes even higher oh
nice one hey was that only
worth a blue coin no
it's five five
[Applause]
all over again
[Music]
will we make it but is there water up
there
how did i do that jump holy [\h__\h] we made
it
[Music]
oh
or the ancient ones this is not inna ina
is human
she says
disturbing and painful
i don't really want to do this
[Music]
hello
what are you doing
keep on pulling with me
[Music]
[Applause]
huh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
no
getting a bit more
[Music]
why am i getting braces
oh
[Music]
baby
no chance against me
right here
[Music]
oh there we go
[Applause]
oh
first time
[Music]
japan bruce let me summon you
be watching people quiet in the chat
they probably feel like
there's so many english comments they
can't comment
in japanese
[Music]
think is one of my favorite levels
but it's a hard one i think ah they have
like different speed writers
[Music]
no okay you just wanna yeah
let me choose where i feel
the most connection
[Music]
there's a fruit fly right in front of my
microphone
i think this guy baby
[Music]
yeah you die right away just if you bonk
against something oh this is gonna be
hard
i might struggle with this one then
but if there's no fly it doesn't go
easily
[Music]
oh
you want to go for a ride uh guess what
[Music]
back
again
here we go again i'm gonna take this one
[Laughter]
you're the
[Music]
this is fun though
[Applause]
[Music]
mario party
[Applause]
all right but i have to do it in
like time right
[Music]
okay
one failure is not gonna get me down
oh
with me
[Music]
is
stay inside
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
yay
[Music]
and papa is scared because i did so well
what that sound
are we doing another race right away
[Applause]
great job australian why am i australian
oh yeah because i'm upside down uh-huh
funny
[Music]
what's going on now okay no more no more
racing
dad well let me go back home
oh [\h__\h] not the flex
not the flag me
me
[Music]
game is too loud oh i tried ah
i tried to turn my own volume up but i
uh i guess it was the game volume
is it fine now
[Music]
what is the mission anyway did anyone
read the mission what am i supposed to
do
wow thank you
uh what
sound is good
[Music]
what something about the cage in the
middle
ah i see it i see it i see it
okay let's follow the arrows
wait what can i hang on to that
can i hang on to that please oh i can
make such a big jump okay okay
i understand i understand come back to
me come back to me
[Music]
nice oh
whole dancing with mario
hey i did not expect to go here
[Music]
okay okay okay next go
get on the bridge and do not get
electrocuted by the
speed
i don't even know how to speak english
anymore i cannot find the words
can someone send me a dictionary
ah this is
thank you mario for like actually like
aiming for the poll
so oh [\h__\h] i have to
turn down the game volume more okay wait
wait wait wait wait wait
[Music]
already hey
volume what's up okay
middle ground how about now
never know what's the right volume some
people say ah
make it more quiet and then they say
make it louder
turn it up
[Music]
i was already falling down but she made
it good job mario where did we go now
here we go in that boat oh no there's
another one of these thingies
[Music]
yes ah are we getting a new pump
no it's not not right now
hello
okay this way i suppose
where's the cage again
over there ah
i'm coming for you my little sunshine
i miss summer already it's been getting
really cold i hear in some
places it's already snowing and i'll
actually hit him
like can i eliminate him like this
i'm gonna fall down definitely why am i
choosing this path
how do i how do i not fall back how do i
not fall down oh my god
just go straight guys she's going
straight
hello why do i have to go up i have to
go up how do i go up
up with that thing oh god it keeps on
going
grab onto it mario no i don't know
i probably have to hover again
[Music]
anyway i was saying i miss summer oh my
god i have to change to the
oh to the hover thing
sorry one more time please come back to
me
this is actually the right way to do it
yeah it should be right
we'll go over here because the arrows
are telling me to
go there am i going the right way
no no no no no no okay let's just go
get back on there why i want to turn
around like
okay
i like the sounds of the climbing
when he hits those how do you even call
that
how do you call that what he's climbing
on what is he climbing on
running out of water soon too yeah the
soundtrack is amazing i love the
soundtrack
fence page mesh
oh man all of those roots
wow you guys know so many words
concentration half is narrow but you can
do it
confidence
is there any way to oh no the only way
to get back up there is to do that fancy
side jump
there's no way i can do that there's no
way
that i can do that is there any weight
the wall jump there's no way that i can
do it
there's no way absolutely no way
it takes me
why do you guys think i can do this you
know how bad i am with gems
[Music]
um
let your dreams be dreams inspiring
[Music]
no this is what i hate about this level
this is it this is exactly it
[Music]
[Applause]
is
wait
oh come on come on you're always so
forgiving and now you're not
i'm learning yeah
okay there we go there we go there we go
change
maybe go to the other side that would be
helpful
oh
okay the other side why not wasn't
necessary but sure i'll take it i'll
take it
okay come on waiting for the next one
okay okay where am i where am i now
here
okay at least the mobs are gone oh that
one came back i guess
[Music]
we're back again thank you for the
membership
thank you very much you can do it never
give up
okay i'm never gonna
give you up
no right no no no no no no no no
wow wow wow wow i made it over here
okay so now what happened last time how
could you [\h__\h] this up
welcome to the membership
[Music]
oh
the right bouncy thing i guess bouncing
yeah there's no arrows right there
okay
wrong pump holy [\h__\h] almost died
i mean not gonna die because there's
water down there but still
no no no not the wind no no no no no not
so unnecessary so unnecessary
no
[Music]
go down one level
dress jump
panic a pure panic oh my god
i'm so hungry by the way i didn't eat
breakfast yet i just woke up and went
straight into streaming
but i do have food next to me i have a
banana
and some kind of bread
what's up
[Music]
hey
wait i should reload water
[Music]
i can do it
come on mario you and me
don't you want to impress me
mario we need to learn how to impress
girls
show me your platforming skills
what pyramid 2 electric bungle what is
that
is that a game
frustrated phoenix noises i'm not sad
i'm but no i'm not frustrated no no no
no no no no this game is much easier
than super mario 6
but for real like it feels much easier
oh god oh god
yes oh
losing my sanity i'm fine
this is fine
this is fun
this is fun love this
i'm enjoying it
[Music]
okay next come on
next pose waiting for you looking like a
candy
candy corn though can you bar something
like that
something halloween
am i even do you even have enough water
for me
candy cane is that a candy cream is that
what i'm thinking of
oh by the way at the end of the stream
please remind me because i always forget
to show you the another piece of the
of the puzzle remind me please by saying
the magic words
and here we are again
[Music]
okay we can do it friends we can do it
i'm getting better i'm getting much
better right okay
[Music]
is there any other way to fix this ship
can i bug myself into the cage maybe
i can't do wall jumps
i mean this one is special you can still
does it have a different
distance between
[Music]
mario mario mario get up there mario
come on no no joking around here
no no where do i go
no okay stupid [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
sorry
i'm happy
thank you for joining the membership
top say so i don't know
i'm getting really good at these parts
oh
i think uh somewhere over there right
before the trampoline there was
something to reload
oh yeah there's no other way to leave
all the products
oh don't run so fast mario
oh no
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
hmm
too much speed kiara too much speed
gotta go slow oh wait i don't have to go
just smile keep on smiling keep on
smiling
where's my taxi where's my backseat
don't have time man
i gotta run to the convenience store and
charge my gacha points for the
stream tonight
focus get out focus what happens focus
[Music]
in about nine hours i'm doing another
stream guys
that was not on my schedule just to
remind you again i'm doing a stream
where i spend all my money to get
pickled merchandise
yep this is how things are supposed to
be
after a while i'm also just a sim just
like you
yep online training will be the end of
me
however actually i gotta check my bank
account and see if
anything is in there
because it's uh the prettiest prettiest
very us pretty after
one of us one of us yeah one of you okay
focus
for real it's focus time shoot your
timer
one by one thanks for joining the
membership
can't even
is there no shortcut
like i really don't see any shortcut
besides that one
in the water but that's
no no no no no no
i will now proceed to shut
the f up
[Music]
is
you almost killed me
excuse me
[Music]
oh
is that a secret shortcut to where i
want to go probably not right
[Music]
let's go back
what am i trying to do no i can't do it
down there
it's too stupid
that screamed just now it kind of hurt
my throat
i feel like i kind of broke a vocal cord
or something
like
okay hydration time hydrating time
[Music]
let's go friends i
i don't know why why i just can't
get over there i don't know
why don't know what is my problem
it has to work now come on
a few failures are funny but too many
failures
are just ridiculous and frustrating even
for the viewers
so kiara get your [\h__\h] together
you can do it i believe in you
you are a phoenix you're not a chicken
who ever said you're chicken oh but not
again not again not again not again no
problem this is uh
not too much of a setback because i can
just get up there
over there no problem not
not a big setback not a big setback
without a potato
what are these things anyway put those
things in the water what are they useful
okay okay
have confidence okay you guys keep on
telling me to have confidence you guys
are so positive today
i mean you're always nice to me but
telling me to have confidence
wow okay
okay i'm the best phoenix in the world
but i'm also the only one
[Music]
you've done this like a million times
now
[Music]
yep wait for the next taxi taxi
oh yes i believe
i believe in the future of mario's
family
unless he wants to make me any more
angry than now then there might be no
future for his family
so mario you might want to consider that
you do want to make a family with peach
right
um the chances of that are
quite low now but
do your best i guess
no oh my god oh my god please no
keep on moving straight forward
come on mario okay we got there
oh my
[Music]
do you guys have any um tips for what's
going to come now again
any advice by any chat
perhaps
don't fall wow
that seems familiar to me i feel like
you told amelia the same thing before
thank you never thought of that you guys
are very uh original
when it comes to advice let's see
it's just some jumps yeah it's not that
hard
it's not that hard okay quiet time
that marima's
i'm gonna be quiet
i'm gonna stay quiet
[Music]
no you [\h__\h] win i'm not ready
no no no i don't want to see you
leave me the [\h__\h] alone leave me the
[\h__\h] alone you stupid little piece of
he keeps on [\h__\h] me
[Music]
yes
ah
[Music]
oh my god holy macaroni we
did it we did it
what ah tell me about a new portal
you okay
do we want to continue of course we want
to continue i guess i guess
we got more cleaning up to do
but probably this might be the last one
this might be the last one for today
clean this [\h__\h] up who made this mess
uh not this
oh there's a toad in there no save the
gold
save the gold save the door save the
doors
this hole get out of there
it's dangerous no you're gonna get all
dirty again okay let's not
focus on him right now probably should
focus on the left
[Music]
oh
so done
come out of there what are you doing get
out of there
let me fight you
oh there's some news going on down there
according to what according to new
information
the lighthouse on the eastern coast has
disappeared yeah i'm trying to fix it
but not getting out of there
oh there it goes
[Music]
why do i always think i did it
what am i doing
we fail yeah i should probably refill
thanks chad
okay i'm back sorry for the wait my
friend
hope you didn't miss me
i see you i feel you think i didn't see
you
totally saw you there
come on get out of there how much water
do you possibly need
thank you
[Music]
am i doing a good job friends
i think i'm doing quite well
after that shitty parkour stop it
yay
who says no who says no
look i rebuilt the lighthouse
okay buddy welcome
thanks mario are you welcome okay we're
doing one level in the lighthouse and
maybe that's the last thing we're doing
today
come on
oh goddammit come on there we go
wait not this one wait i forgot what is
this one i oh no i know i know i know i
know i know
gelato beach june blood sand castle
secret
i know the world but i'm not sure what
the level is
oh yeah hell yeah what is the mission
ah okay we gotta spray water on those
but what happens after that
oh not in that way secret level what do
you mean
what is secret about this
oh wow
okay um what am i supposed to do
[Music]
mommy oh yeah
spray the blood in the middle oh boy
thank you that was fun
leave me alone no
oh
my
what the hell is that is there any moms
here right now
with myself
i have to do it myself
yep
okay oh another one
[Music]
okay oh and another one what the hell
what is this
a lot and
[Music]
could use some mod in my chat okay
okay guess i don't have nuts
okay i still don't quite understand
what's i need to do
hey but what happened when i did that in
the middle
try all the plans come on leave me alone
i'm busy
[Music]
oh it's one of those levels again is it
one of those
that's what you mean with secret level
okay
that's a good that stop it hello stop it
stop it stop bullying me stop pulling me
oh my god
for real
no okay thank you next doll
have to open them all up again
oh thank you totally enjoying this thank
you
leave it
leave me alone
okay that one didn't that one didn't uh
raise me up into here
oh there we go actually there's four but
i only have to ask today
see
[Music]
[Applause]
okay we made it we made it
yay
[Music]
okay sand falling down beautiful
no problem i can do it time is
not my enemy at all time is not my enemy
the only enemy is
everything else
yep no problem no problem no problem no
problem no power no problem this is fine
this is fine no problem no problem
[Music]
this is how it starts panic rta yeah
feels like it
come on mario come on mario come on
mario
okay first stage clear
is there space between those oh [\h__\h] how
do i do those jumps
please tell me i can only do it like
with normal jumps
please tell me i can do normal jumps
jump jump no you can't hold on to those
no yes okay okay
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] where's the spread
something shiny up there okay how do how
do i get there
yes okay
try to reach that that middle ground
first
oh
yeah show us your platforming skills
sure
let me show you
okay okay let's just let's just go let's
just go
let's just go let's just whoa nice jump
party off
okay okay we covered they recover
nice okay
um wait how
does where is it
up there okay well
some pro gems are necessary mario but i
think we can do it
that's what i mean yeah mario yeah
now get up there come on
you thought this would be painful but
actually yeah
actually the panic mode got me through
there quite quickly quite fast
you just gotta be like full panic mode
and then
the panic will lead you will guide you
[Laughter]
though
[Music]
okay my friends i think
maybe we'll end it here what do you
think we can do super chat reading and
then
i'll stream again in at the evening of
japanese time 10 pm
let me show you the candy though
um
[Music]
what do you say to me
trick or treat that's right that's right
which one do we show you
let me show you this one
hi let me hide the screen
there you go
[Music]
screenshot it
trick-or-treat halloween is so soon i'm
playing my first ever horror game
tomorrow by the way my first ever
i am not looking forward to it
did you get the candy are you done
awesome thank you everyone who watched
my stream today if you would like to
leave now you're welcome to leave if you
would like to stay you're welcome to say
i'm doing super chat reading and
uh yeah thanks for watching today it was
a fun start into a new
new game uh we had some painful moments
but
not as painful as super mario 64 i would
say
i think i can do this one easier the
the controls um definitely
improved and the camera improved it
wasn't so bad that one level with the
climbing
made me lose my [\h__\h] mind but besides
that it was all good
yeah pain is needed to feel happy after
it yeah
and that last level with the sand wow i
thought i would fail there miserably
again but i didn't
yeah he did marry his family reunite or
what did it say i don't know
um for now yes for now they're safe
but eventually he should be careful he
should be careful
to not get too cocky with me because
i'm a phoenix my papa told me i'm not
allowed to transform
but sometimes you just gotta listen to
your heart and to yourself and not to
your papa
i could burn your whole family okay
so
[Music]
i will show you this one during the
if you want i can leave this one on the
screen
for everyone who comes in later and
still didn't get it
okay mario i know you want to sleep
wait i did save red after that right i
don't have to save anymore
i can just okay should be fine
also
nice
okay super chat we
ended last time by reading all the super
judge
i'm always caught up
as expected from kiara
oh and we need some pgm
okay let me scroll a little bit and let
me pop out the chat
thanks for joining the membership
oh wait you don't hear it yet or do you
you're done right okay
there you go
there we go by the way
you might have seen that i have been
recruiting
fan art for uh well
me in sexy uh
swimsuit attire yep
on twitter just use the hashtag to send
it in and the ones that i really really
liked
i will use for the thumbnail of this
whole series so
we might need a lot of those artworks
because um the series is gonna go on for
a while
yeah fan art creators i'm looking for
you
guys
[Music]
to get
and the current one is drawn by yuna
link is in the description
already so we are reading but uh
maybe i should drink some more water
please actually i've been noticing
a lack of fan art recently anyway
so it's a good a good opportunity to
motivate you guys for doing some more
get me some loots no there's nothing
lewd about
swimsuits there's nothing rude about
that
swimsuits are not loot it depends on how
you draw them and how
what pose you would put me in
no no no no clipping out of context no
no
no no
are you guys ready for some for some
super chat reading
yummy
please get those duncashers going okay
no sleeping
[Music]
keep naming bottom left moments so avido
keeps responding
[Music]
we'll ignore this super chat no i will
not
i won't be able to make the stream
because of white but even so i think
it's awesome that you're mixing up your
stream times
to help people in other time zones yeah
rip stream what
what we're back
he disappeared for a second youtube what
are you doing
vegan review eleven thank you shannon
because 311 thank you shane i said a
very long time ago that your dedication
to your fans and being as inclusive as
possible is one of the best
things about you even now you're still
proving that to be true
thank you
thank you thank you very much
sanji sean danke and general piccolin
from the halls of peach's castle to the
dunes of shifting sand
gear heads to the tropics this will be a
sunshine filled holiday we'll never
forget kfp let's hit the beach for the
kfb
cake
i hope not i personally enjoy a cup of
sand with a side of fresh salt water
eew washes right down my throat
perfectly and tastes amazing said no one
ever
yeah that's right thank you
but next is thank you and thank you i
won't be able to watch again but we'll
be listening while at work thank you
brighten our day with your sunshine
skills ha
[Music]
yeah i hope i brighten it up a little
bit
go get intentional thank you thank you
sangri teresco
jacqueline duncan general piccolin
harold mcfadden
gustavo romero
but here's a little donation to ukraine
game stream later thank you
hope you'll get all the pico de cushions
i'll catch the vods
after work and will witness ukraine
gaming skills thank you so much thank
you
thank you thank you for the super chat
congratulations on 400k attention thank
you
400k actually i feel like maybe
i'm almost like celebrating every
milestone too much
because uh i don't know i'm
i'm just genuinely happy about reaching
those milestones but then again
the other girls are barely
celebrating them so i feel like maybe
i'm celebrating too much
i don't know
is it okay to celebrate
i like a girl who likes to come up with
excuses to party
yay more body party buddy
okay i'll continue partying i'm a party
bird
tiny bird body boob pancaking
so happy to find her finally hatch oh
congratulations on hatching
and look forward to growing into a
healthy bucket of friends fried chicken
with you thank you
i'm looking forward to that too one day
i will eat you
check it monkey donkey [\h__\h] with the
word super chat thank you
congrats in front of the cake thank you
it's been an absolute joy to watch you
grow from a fledging idol to the
confident phoenix where today
i thought you were gonna say something
like a fledgling idol to
an impure swearing
chicken something like that just as the
sun provides warmth to
the world your vibrant personality has
provided happiness to all here's to your
future and continued success
you are so goddamn sweet
thank you for your kind words and your
generosity
thank you for your support thank you
thank you
67 thank you for the huge huge huge
super chat i don't know if you're still
here but
thank you so much i really really really
really appreciate it
thank you for always supporting me
hmm still there no i left a while ago i
see you though i see you
when are you hatching anyway are you a
late hatcher
i've seen you chisos de gondra duncan
employees thanks for streaming your
wonderful thank you too thank you for
watching
thank you
banjo kazooie thank you thank you
for the red super chat finally able to
say converts on the 400k
every stream has been so much fun to
watch and your collabs are always the
highlight of my week
it's always so great to see the
positivity that you bring to everyone in
their own way can't wait for what's in
store
thank you thank you
thank you so so so much
friend side quest
lincoln
[Music]
sunshine
oh i was supposed to go to japan and
korea this year but you know yeah
and congrats and for the k also sunshine
is my favorite me too
my favorite too but yeah next year i
guess
no no no no a fan of okay senpai
super chatted not okay
spector from baron dankeshen
kfb passed out midstream last night so i
missed the 400k but congratulations
thank you
they love 67 dankeshen
yeah you know did kind of nerf me a
little bit
in that art my
chest is a bit bigger than in that
thumbnail indeed thank you for noticing
don't know if yuna is watching but
yeah my chest is supposed to be a big
bit bigger i didn't want to say it i
didn't want to
i didn't want to say anything
are you nice watching
it's okay it's totally totally fine but
for next time
please more boop more boop on both sides
her dad is watching oh
hello i'm just trying to uh
have it be as accurate as possible you
know because
yeah let's not talk about my boobs
anymore
this is probably going to be very
awkward between those two
if they're watching it together uh-huh
awkward awkward
very awkward
it's just uh yep yep trying to stay
accurate
with the kids thank you and grandson for
the cake yeah you deserve it and so much
more always a blast watching and your
energy and good vibes are contagious
keep rocking on
thank you so much for the red super chat
thank you i'm dying oh god yoona is your
papa killing you
[Laughter]
or it must be me because i'm just so
sexy
i'm killing you with my sexiness i'm
sorry
i cannot stop it
i just can't stop it
we're laughing okay that's good that's
good
patrick billy
channel jojo thank
little sister who messed with her big
brother saves why must it remind me of
this
horror chicken why hey i don't think i
really messed with it
i didn't really ever get far
i mean there's not much you can mess
with you either complete a level
or you don't so i didn't really mess up
anything but yeah
on the 400k i've got a lot of fun
memories playing this game me too
i promise i'm not a zoomer yeah i
believe you
so i hope you have a great time as well
take the super chat so you can have your
own island vacation one day
oh island vacation that would be amazing
thank you thank you for the red super
chat thank you
dear australian mate
i visited australia in this uh
in this stream as well by going uh
doing a 180.
[Music]
this best language is german so i'm
trying to uh
integrate it a little bit in my stream
anyway swelling glasses thank you
jackets
steven booyah duncan engineer gaming
duncan
danny scope
are you planning to learn any other
languages out of hobby
i did want to but
yeah i i like the motivation and the
time
so i don't think it's gonna happen
anymore unfortunately
i did want to learn italian and spanish
oh my god i'm just getting so hungry can
i eat something
do i want to eat bread or a banana
okina danish donuts
gonna eat some bread i'm so hungry
didn't eat anything yet
[Music]
hmm
wow
[Music]
hmm
it's like a twisted twisted a
long donut with um
sugar it's kind of sugar sugar coated
danish danish danish
[Music]
ah
sorry i was so hungry i was so hungry
[Music]
ah
hmm
[Music]
yummy
okay that's good enough right now tory
is according
okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
celebration super superchats are going
no no no no no i'm not wasting your
money on that it's my own money it's my
own money
however when when the superjet
cash comes in oh what am i gonna do with
that i
probably need to buy new shoes because
my shoes are like falling apart
and maybe some clothes for winter
because i feel like i don't have so many
clothes for winter and it's getting cold
then i need to buy like um material
to sound proof a little bit in my house
what else
like things that i really really need
things that i really really need
is spend my money on all the same thing
you want
sorry i didn't read the rest didn't get
it
number seven to go please buy more
snacks
oh yes i'm like yesterday i i
ate so much after snacks you know where
do you remember when i told you i
i went shopping and then i came back
with
70 dollars worth of german chocolate
snacks
17. seven zero seven zero nana saying
no don't
i was going to eat it like slowly
now i like german chocolate it's it's of
course it's imported so it's a bit more
expensive
than other chocolate but it's the best
chocolate i bought so much
so yeah new shoe font thank you
but also my my brother's birthday is
coming
closer so
soon i will order a switch for him
because he said he doesn't he doesn't
want the ps5 he wants to switch
so i guess he's getting a switch i'm
gonna buy it for him
and maybe i'll buy a ps5 for myself
it's coming out in november right are
there any good games
like from the beginning that i would
want to play that i i
me that i would want to play
because i didn't really hear about
anything that looks interesting to me
demon souls
demons souls
what remake what do you mean what is
that game let me see
demons souls
that doesn't look like something i would
want to play
yeah you know i like
like bright and colorful games
and people told me to wait anyway to buy
the ps5 when it gets like updated or
something
ring fit adventure oh yeah
ratchet and clank is that a game that's
coming out of the ps5
wretch that sounds like another one like
this banjo and kazooie games
better than clunk ps4 oh that's cute
what is that like a adventure game
what is that uh genre
it's a platformer oh dear lord
hey i want more jrpgs
why are there not more jrpgs
also remember we have to get permission
for every game and
for the bigger games it often takes a
long time until we get permission
persona 5 oh we can never play persona 5
on stream but i might play it
privately octopus i can play it on
switch
you guys are telling me about games that
are not on playstation 5.
you're just telling me random games now
breath of the wild yeah i'm gonna maybe
start that at some point
why am i holding the switch controller
again just want to touch it when it's
right next to me
anyway anyway anyway random game
recommendations is not really what i
asked for but thank you
thank you for random game
recommendations that i've heard already
a million times
buck snacks is that for ps5
buck snacks yes five
i saw that one i saw um
a trailer of that one wow
yep that is a ps5 level
right there ps5 quality content
damn yeah probably have to wait some
time until
anything of interest is released on ps5
but people
yeah people tell me anyway to wait
yeah yeah
people tell me anyway it's not like uh
you should wait because it's like it
gets improved at some point
um tails have arrived yeah but that is
but most likely
also getting released on switch and pc
so there's no
need for me to get a ps5 although
i am waiting and waiting and waiting for
tales of arise
oh my god please finally release tales
of verizon give me a release date
there's still no release date right
there's still
oh wait i think there wasn't even a
rough date
yeah sad
of course tails is my favorite game
series my favorite
i played almost all of them let's
continue
mark shinji thank you arctic fox nan
kashan
[Music]
wow hurricane hit last night and we have
no electricity
using my phone to watch damn yesterday
there was someone
in a blizzard who was watching me in his
car
because you couldn't go anywhere damn
what did
why is are you guys okay
please be safe why is everyone
like in some disaster
situation holy [\h__\h]
please be
i sent you a few tweets about an easy to
use and an inexpensive device called
retro ting that converts console video
to hdmi
makes streaming retro easy oh thank you
interesting but at the moment
i only have a switch with me anyway but
it will be interesting in the future you
might want to remind me about that in
the future
shadowfox thank you and patrick
chandangashin
duncan's chat also be careful to not get
banned apparently someone got
or two people got like banned because
they spammed
the dankeshun too much so maybe you
should mix it with um
with some text or whatever
do you love 67 dan kashan cow tv freedom
every day impaired daniel duke thank you
evans
[Music]
it's my birthday today oh happy birthday
my name is my friend is helping me send
ah
send the super chat your perseverance
first how did i say that persev
is that how you say it perseverance
probably not
inspired me at a very dark time in my
life and moved me to pursue a dream i
gave up on
and number two your stream are the
highlight of my everyday
i can send the super chat because your
streams and tweets make me work hard
next year i hope to give you an aka spa
thank you i love you wish me luck
good luck and happy birthday that's so
sweet
perseverance perseverance
thank you happy birthday
and thank you for your support but don't
feel like it's necessary to send me a
rad super chat please
please please any support will do
any support just subscribing to my
channel is a huge support for me
thank you and happy birthday i hope you
have a nice day eat some cake
exploding gamer thank you shin
uh oh i don't know any dutch words no
zero dankeshen dr dan kashin aero jam
ravio dankeshon do you love 67
five tango shin ah it's easy to get
lives by collecting 100
coins rather than trying to get the
mushrooms hundred coins
ah
[Music]
okay
oh you bought house of caesarea nice
tales of brazilia is so
good so damn good everyone go get it
if it's still on sale go buy it it's so
[\h__\h] good
nobody
it's still on sale oh my god go get it
it was so expensive when i bought it
would you try monster hunter oh i could
give it a try eventually
fairy tales game oh
probably tales of celia one and two
they're both so different from each
other because especially in terms of
celia too the whole system is different
and the whole
atmosphere is different but that's what
i like about that
but tears of cilia one is just genuinely
so beautiful
and there's the story aha oh maggie lou
ah maggie lou
yeah those two are my favorites i think
but i i like
a lot of them all of them i started out
with tales of
symphonia um this period was also great
yeah
grace's grace's was also amazing true
true true it's hysteria
hysteria um if i ever get the mission
system might be one we might want to
play
because um i've i don't know why
but sisteria is
the only tears off game that i started
but never finished
and i got quite far actually
but then i guess i got busy with other
things or while i was playing
tens of sisteria it's weird
but still i have to play it it's
beautiful and one of the most
more recent tales of games and i want to
play
all of the more recent ones because
they're just so beautiful
syster is the worst one what
i asked you about that the other day you
hated so much on symphonia too
you guys are all like oh sinfonia 2 is
the worst one
i generally like all of them so
tempest tempest i never played isn't
that the one for the ds
i need to get a ds to play some
also test of hearts i think tess of
hearts is also one i didn't play
but i did play tales of the world
radiant mythology which is on the
playstation portable
super nostalgic
oh it's a 3ds okay
i need to get a 3ds huh
radiant it was really cool it was really
good actually
um uh
i think i played it yeah i think i did
welcome to the membership wow i like
that there's somebody tells our fans in
the chat
there's a skin nice yeah i was
thinking of getting a vita to play hard
tails of hearts art
i was thinking of getting myself a
playstation vita
only for that purpose
but first i wanna i wanna get uh
permission
so i can play it with you guys
i have a feeling it will never happen
though
have you played nero tomorrow yes i
tried before and i never got past the
tutorial bus
the last boss in the tutorial
um
[Music]
yup anyway dapper tree dankeshin
mtk kundan kashin
oh thank you for catching my stream
tonight thank you
delta thank you judas thank you alberto
jfp jfp huh
janitor danke navy boy five four nine
nine thank
here's to my favorite whole life girl
love watching you play sunshine thank
you
thank you murph er elahh
jalapeno thank you
director
i have to work now so i can't watch you
streaming but i want to tell you that
you're my favorite youtuber
thank you oh my god thank you so much
thank you
bloody tama gaming thank you mark sheen
i was wrong about coin and livestream oh
if you keep giving fruit to the basket
people in the plaza they'll give you
laughs after they give you a blue coin
oh
okay thank you for making call williams
thank you
this is ten dollars this ten dollars is
for the among us
ian and japan collab stream from last
sunday saturday great job providing
translations oh thank you
pretty sus you didn't protect cali from
getting bumped up in the first
eh i didn't even like realize any of
that
i was like i was busy with first of all
people complaining about my audio being
only on one ear and me
thinking about how i could fix it and
being like oh go like
hoping that it's not too bad
and then translating and then figuring
out the game and
figuring out the controls i was so busy
with everything
i had no idea what was going on
but now that i'm more used to among us
we should do it again
whole life ian and japan fifth
generation we should do it again
we should do it maybe maybe in november
we can all
come together again to play it another
time
because we have that logo too that among
us logo that was
uh made for only us nine
it can only be as nine again because
it's uh the number nine that replaces
the g
hmm
[Music]
still is there still japanese viewers
out there gotta call them out here
[Music]
foreign
too focused on this beautiful face to
write comments huh
[Music]
you are seriously a treasure and
watching you has been nothing but
glorious experience i wish you nothing
but success
is
stream is amazing thank you
[Music]
never seems to disappoint my ears i
didn't see what happened but i can feel
the pain in my soul
let me change my sitting position
come back
there's this complicated trick that most
birds can't do most
speed runners fail sometimes and i will
share this advice if you don't fall
oh shut up
thank you galaxia
take an idle phone call idle meeting
no no we're almost done
[Music]
refreshing
let's see what else we got
oh
in
ah your greeting was getting censored in
the manga chat because when you leave
out a and and if you leave out a
k kick it
key the first four letters become a bad
word
which well what is that
i had never heard of that
is that even english
yeah i'm not gonna say it but is that
even english
oh yeah never heard of that
[Music]
and my greeting wow they're like
even calculating like taking out some
letters interesting
deal of 67 thank you
not sure how to feel about my adoptive
mom asking for swimsuit out but i'm not
against it
thanks again for making me smile and
love almost every day thank you
sean r dankeshen sebas 1509 duncashin's
movie thank you soon
general scraggy duncan as you played
thank you
i was not able to watch the entire
stream but i really love that you're
expressive and you're not afraid to show
frustration and
thanks for being real stay true to
yourself
i cannot hide it i cannot hide it
[Music]
foreign
actually for the pillows i want to get
the the
pickled pillow first but i also want to
get the marine pedo pillow
i hope i can get at least two things i
did charge um i have i should have i
think like about eight thousand points
which is like eight thousand yen
has
[Music]
i'm not gonna get spend more than that
because i would have to run to the
convenience store midstream
and charge more
most people get a question about around
5000 yen okay
i wonder how big it is i want it
so bad
all righty let's continue immortal in
flames thank you
danke and steve jayden i'll be the
please buy more snacks wow is that a red
super chat to buy more snacks thank you
mwah thank you
i can buy a lot of snacks with that damn
dustin dan kashan kiana the stream was
hilarious whole life gives me motivation
to learn some japanese so i can
hopefully someday understand what the
other japan members are saying
have you any tips to start with to start
oh oh i have no idea because the way i
learned japanese is so difficult from
like how you would normally
um learn it
but the most important thing is
communication use the language
every day i told you guys before just
gotta use the language every day talk to
yourself
talk to a friend whatever just use it
every day
okay maybe end thank you
thank you for the red super chat mwah
thank you thank you thank you i hope you
have a nice and lovely day as well
thank you thank you for your support
general scraggy thank you
and thiago ttm thank you equivalent
exchange thank you
for thanking
looking forward to ring for the
adventure there might
be a ring fit adventure stream soon i
already talked to
a certain senpai that i will be
collabing with
next week already talked to her
and said
as i asked her what she thinks about
doing
rinford adventure together and she was
like oh
kitsuke she was like ah
oh no that's a exhausting one
[Music]
i think we're gonna do it
yeah we're gonna both be really horrible
and gonna die during the stream might
not be a very long stream
to try our best to keep it up for one
hour
we have permission for that so that's
coming soon
after fire
jrpg series no i do not know it
mak shinji dankeshen
thank you thank you thank you thank you
i'll be the lancashien and mark cindy
duncan
also oh last refreshing
okay last refresh
stop reading no more no
need spamming the the super jets
thank you so much
i wanna take a nap
foreign
ah thank you for watching today i hope
you enjoyed the stream
i'll see you in how many hours six
seven eight eight hours
donating to nab funds my naps cost
nothing but thank you thank you
oh i'm so tired actually i'm uh the day
before yesterday
i was able to sleep before midnight i
was very proud of that but
of course next night again i messed it
up i
didn't sleep before three o'clock i
think
i was at least awake until three am
yeah so i slept like seven hours and
that's
that's not enough for me that's not
enough i need to sleep at least at least
eight hours and then even then i'm
probably still gonna take a nap if i
don't have anything to do
i just love sleeping so much team
fortress 2
um no i
i don't think so it's not really my type
of
game i think
well i can't stop yawning i'm coming up
[Music]
tomorrow
okay
well then thank you
nice blankets true my blankets are a bit
too cold i have two i'm sleeping with
two blankets and still
still cold i should turn on my air
conditioning
plug skill i just want to make the
artists aware oh yeah
please
everyone uh in german in german we say
[Music]
see you in eight hours i'll go charge my
my crane game account and i'll go check
out if
if my maybe possibly the first
first salary has blessed my
my bank account so i can spend even more
on gacha just kidding
and i'll take a nap enough i'll finish
in
[Music]
see you later
see you 10 pm japanese standard time
which is in eight hours from now bye-bye
[Music]
is
so
[Music]
oh
i love you bye bye