[Music]
The Most Wonderful Time of the Year snow
is falling lights are shimmering Santa's
finally been taken care of and I've
taken his place
oh wait if I'm Santa and today is
December 25th
oh no oh no no no no oh shitaki I was
supposed to deliver presents to the fans
can you help me I was supposed to get a
present for the fans isn't that Santa's
job don't mention that name around me
who right do you know what the fans want
for Christmas I'm all out of ideas a
weapon do you think that's a good idea
oh what about a letter we can put all of
our feelings into it our feel
our feel I sure have a lot of those here
I'll start
I hope you have a Merry Christmas
[Music]
the thing that would be more meaningful
if everyone signs it hey Mommy can you
make sure everyone signs us before it's
delivered oh sure thanks mummy
I gotta go figure out presents for
everyone else in the world I guess
virus
oh silly Iris now I can do whatever I
want to this letter maybe some berry
juice some pretty art
oh hi Callie yo mommy what you got there
oh
oh it's a letter yeah who's it for
actually Iris gave it to me because
she's gonna know she's gotta get a gift
for the fans now we're writing them a
letter but now everyone needs to sign it
so everyone asks me if I can make sure
everyone signs in and now you're here so
if I don't use that and make sure it
gets to the next person make sure you
put your feelings into it okay okay bye
what ah that girl uh okay so I just have
to sign this letter Callie oh is that
the person for the fans yeah wait how
did you know about this I made sure they
went on iris's Nice List well maybe some
of them deserve to be on the naughty
list but I favorite I've been merciful
this year really feeling the Christmas
spirit ha Kiara it looks like Iris
decided on a letter something about
getting everyone to put their feelings
into it feelings let me see
what was it red that's not blood is it
berry juice or maybe mulled wine hmm how
about we turn it into a cute little
Christmas hen looks like you have it all
under control thanks tenshaw make sure
everyone else bye wait wait I didn't say
oh what's up
man I'm just a girl I wanted to see
could you do me a favor
that depends what do you need can you
get the rest of the girls to sign this
it's a letter for the fans oh for
Christmas yeah a gift from all of us to
them a letter huh did you ever think
about no no no no no no no don't make
more work for yourself I need you to be
free for Christmas so we can spend some
time together yeah but what if we just
don't forget about our plans make sure
everyone signs it I'll see you soon
adding a little something special
wouldn't hurt anybody just just a little
bonus present from Watson Industries are
we causing Mischief oh hi fauna uh uh no
no I was just something about adding an
extra something special from Watson
Industries no wait how do you I was
listening the whole time oh in that case
wanna help me hmm
as long as no one's around oh hey guys
I gotta go take care of take care of me
fauna oh
where'd Ami go she
um hey crony what do you think about gag
gifts
like no like
prank presents oh
no I want to do something like that if
I'm giving a gift it has to be perfect
all right of course uh me too I wouldn't
even think of playing a prank on our
precious fans wait a gift for the fans
yeah do you want to help we could use
the signature of someone perfect like
you sure and collect everyone else's
signatures too for me will you thanks
grony wait what
Kudos
hey it's Christmas stuff it suck can I
get a break just for today you started
it and I'm finishing it hey will you
sign this well you want my signature for
gonna sell it on eBay didn't realize you
were hurting for cash crony I changed my
mind I don't need your signature at all
what was it for wouldn't you like to
know
come on
it's a gift for the fans a letter from
all of us oh can I sign it here but now
that you have it you have to make sure
everyone else signs it too okay
all right who can I pawn this off too
[Music]
good take this wow you know what to do
with this right
great thanks Inna see ya Merry Christmas
[Music]
oh what's that
you want me to sign this and give it to
the fans
got it
so this is for you huh
let's see what it says
to the fans of hola en
we hope you're having a merry Christmas
and happy holiday
thank you for always supporting us in
everything we do
because of you we're able to chase our
dreams and keep reaching for the Stars
behind every performance every stream
and every song you are there cheering us
on
we couldn't do it without you
from the bottom of our hearts thank you
for supporting hola en
Merry Christmas
[Music]