[Music]
w
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
w
[Music]
he
come on
[Music]
hey
he e
[Music]
[Applause]
w
[Music]
he he
[Applause]
[Music]
w
he
[Music]
come on
he
[Music]
K
KY oh
okay what video was it it was actually
one that I think I saw before years ago
oops
sorry um it's definitely fake but it's
still scary just some video
of like a guy a crosseyed guy following
a girl and she goes into this person's
room uh home to hide and the dude's
already filming it though the moment
that she like knocks on the door and is
like hey this weirdo is following me can
you can you let me in I'm so scared he's
already recording but then ah the crossy
guys it's really creepy and I got jump
scared at the
[Music]
end why you watching it was randomly on
my Doug Hood it was randomly on my on my
Twitter feed Doug Hood you crazy lad did
you guys see yesterday on my Twitter
honestly people who don't have Twitter I
don't know how like you keep up with
what I do or maybe you don't
but I was so you should have not like
had me see this outside of a stream my
reaction was too
good I was so like holy no way and then
he was so
cute he's so
sweet Hank from Breaking
Bad no way
perfect timing yo also if only Hank knew
that he's kind of my favorite like I
said this before recently in the collab
when girls were like who's your favorite
I'm like H it's a tough question but
maybe
hang I don't want you to have to plan
any
reactions oh thank you so much that was
so
cool I was screaming yeah Jesse too like
Hank Jesse and Saul
which I think is probably a popular
choice now that I'm watching Better Call
Saul Saul really like grows on me
too because he's more than just a funny
guy now you feel for him you want to
like you want him to do
well start already yeah I'm like uh
episode five or six or something going
through it slowly because
um I have haven't had much time to
properly
watch Jimmy
[Music]
McGill if you got a cameo from Walter
what would you do he seems like uh Brian
seems like the guy who might be doing
cameos who knows maybe it's already
lined
[Laughter]
up have you seen El cam no not yet I
maybe one day in the future oh there's a
hair in my drink now it's
[Music]
gone oh no camera from bur no worries no
worries the Hank one was already
amazing
uh like that alone n you don't need to
send any
more that one made me plenty
happy so cool cool I got the hster also
did you guys see I was funny I was
apparently so funny that I started a
trend among ID
members wait I can't find it anymore
it's not in
my it's not in my
replies no never mind it might
be here there
let me show
you okay
so comedian I'm so proud of my joke I
have to show
you okay here there you
go joke. jpeg
I saw this I saw this
tweet
uh here I saw this tweet first this
person writes how did y'all get into
whole life and it immediately came to me
the reply immediately came to me but I
checked the replies to see if any other
member already perhaps wrote something
like that uh because it seemed so
obvious to me but no other member wrote
anything yet like that so I was like
okay I'll be the first awesome so I
write I
[Laughter]
audition funny mind you everybody else
was answering as a fan how they got into
her life for which member but I said
I and I feel like the joke is perfect
here but I continued it a bit cuz they
asked did you ever get end so I said I'm
not sure let me
check but that kind of
uh uh what's the word it it kind of
doesn't make sense cuz I'm already
admitting that I got into whole life by
say but by answering the question with I
auditioned sounds like I already got in
why am I unsure about it later oh well
still
funny and then I saw just now that eie
uh let me show you it all lines up
perfectly more jokes.
jpeg the ID Girls jumped on the joke
train here first
eoi then Raina I guess and then MAA and
then
o stealing my joke just kidding I'm I'm
trending I'm such a trans that's how
good my joke was that's how good my joke
was and it seems to maybe it's like like
only ID girls are reacting so maybe this
is a joke that isn't funny to like
native English speakers maybe this is
just the The Foreigner humor what do you
think you guys find it funny though
right
it's funny it's funny yeah
yeah no I thought it was funny awesome
it's funny I okay good good good good
good good
yeah I'm rarely this funny I I think I
deserve an
award so this is a rare special moment
and I deserve an award oh oh oh oh what
what
what and the award for funniest tweet of
the week goes
[Music]
to
uh Tak
K
woohoo thank you so much thank you thank
you yeah um it came to me immediately it
was just right there I had to take it
just like how I had to take this award I
want to thank kfp and myself obviously
thank you to uh everybody who believed
in me and every everybody who laughed
with me or at me I appreciate it thank
you so much have a nice day
goodbye goodbye New
York oh
yeah thank you so much oh my God stop
thank you so much
now that's the vtu award we create for
last minute new category go go go
go oh
man oh
man okay gaming
[Music]
time gaming
time Jesse's going to be at the Awards
on the awards what which
Awards
ah
streamer no wait that just happened game
wait is game awards
today it's
tonight
oh
tonight no
[Music]
no had I known this when I made my
schedule maybe I would have considered
staying up for it for a
stream but I guess now I'll just I'll
have something to watch after I'm done
streaming huh can't stay up too long
though how long does it usually
take if it starts it starts 2 a.m. I
thought 1:00
a.m. 3
hours P doing a watch along it's a
pretty decent time for
her it's
like 10 I think for her roughly
a.m. three hours including the pre-show
a well if I'm awake I'll watch a bit
huh a damn it okay yeah I I watched uh I
watched also something else of Aaron
Paul he's cool he's such a good actor I
watched the thing where he showed up in
the
office that funny coefficient watching
him pick cway wonderful
wonderful very that's the that's the
real watch along
there don't mistake Piccola stream for
the Picola watch along that's fake
the real one is by
coefficient or should I say p
[Music]
coefficient
Wait Don't Judge Me Oh wait I guess it
doesn't show
anything what whoa the chuo boys here oh
the lady is here it's my
Caravan ah coish
hello PCO ficient PCO ficient did
anybody call you that
before PE
coefficient no wait that was
[Laughter]
wrong come come come
[Music]
Coe sorry my voice is not so good right
now
com what's with my throat right now that
was on point really
thank you for the membership renewal
took you long enough come come come [\h__\h]
today's not my
day no I Can Do
Better got a throat in my in my in my
frog wait what wait wait what am I
saying wait what what
what wa wait wait wait
huh come pickle pickle
pickle TW Twitchy Twitchy I'm saying
twitch by the
way I need a broke we can't be doing it
like
this oh I only have the old loky melted
fro candies right now oh no oh
no oh this is actually
fun ah [\h__\h] I dropped it now it's got a
lot of hair on
it I'll have a cat in my throat next not
a
frog wait I'm picking off the hairs from
my throat candy but there's so many it's
like like sticky cuz I already had my
tongue a little bit on
it
no no should I just go for it no I
shouldn't I shouldn't I shouldn't
I'm picking I'm picking off and looks
looks pretty
[Music]
good going
here [\h__\h] it
okay it's in my mouth
now okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
come come pickle come pickle now maybe
it won't get better today than the first
tryle
[Laughter]
comle comle come
[Music]
I can't get the raspiness
today no it doesn't hurt my
voice oh yeah maybe a little bit more
strength there
comle
t
no rough rough one rough one
we could try again at the end of the
stream
maybe some part of that was P some part
of
it you have no idea P
ficient yeah you have no idea
how are you how are you so ready for
that I almost want to keep the chat on
although That's The Whispers right would
be funnier if it wasn't World
chat probably shouldn't do that
be sorry I'll give up I'll give up
uh last time we just finished a region
um I have a question in terms of
like game
length uh if I do this stream and then
another stream I I would think that I
would be at the end of
it for now um but like uh
sorry right um
unlikely you kind of zoomed in oh what
I'm zoomed in
no no not
really I mean the game window is
properly
sized Al there Sixx yeah yeah but six
acts in the full game right I mean we're
talking about only the the first couple
of Acts that are available during the
Early
Access right that's what I'm talking
about what what there's six acts
already the first free repeat then you
can go into end game what they repeat
what do you mean you go into hard mode
you redo the first free ones I don't
know if I want to do that for for me I
think it will be over after the first
threee oh right that Diablo did that
too wait why would they do that if they
don't even have the full
game first R is already a lot of yeah
that's what I was thinking too so if we
think of only the first three without
redoing them in hard
mode uh death it's doable in this and
next stream
right had the level so you aren't on the
level for end game and well now I have
to think about that God damn it could be
it's possible God damn it I was going to
plan out how long this stream should be
and how long the next stream should be
when I should end it today so that the
next stream is like a good length you
know not too short not too long but but
now I don't now now you're tempting me
now it feels like the right thing to do
is play all acts again and then do end
game I'll think about it after
[Music]
today the collab collab the repeat oh
true that could be
fun yeah
possibly the repeat act could be
collabs
yeah okay well uh use the desert mamp to
travel to the SAS and travel to the
halani gates wa what do I do first I
guess the
SAS are the helani gates at the SAS
welcome wait what to to the trial of the
second oh for Glory is that the same
place got to do the trail first the
trail the trail of the
trial oh oh yeah the helani gates are
after the trial or no wait no I have to
go to the halani gates
though act two is brutal I'm already in
it wiu wiu wiu is
here wiu is it you is it the real
[Music]
you you don't have to start the trial of
second but it gets you your ascendancy
what's an
ascendancy what is that pride and fall
of Bal Bala so wait we were here
before no wait wait wait wait
wait I'm
confused wait I'm here
what wait I'm
confused right I now I just followed the
quest
marker now I'm just back in the
Caravan pick the ah the next
Waypoint
uh uh this
one helani
Gates oh
a yeah here is where we
ended a couple days
ago ooh the music here is pretty cool
how do I fight again I don't
remember fck mashing [\h__\h]
mashing
okay uh is the sound too loud when I
fight oops o summon a
hold them back while I open the gate W
I'm fighting with the hot lady
woohoo game sounds
good these enemies are so
[Music]
clingy all right I'm going to ignore are
all the white items I
think
fire yes Minion fire build or originally
I didn't want to do any fire though cuz
we are still playing Diablo 4 on the
side and I am a
fire lady in that and I don't want too
much repetition
but it is what it
is how is she fighting I couldn't even
look at her fighting
style she's just a normal boring sword
fighter seemingly
chest
yippee
oh this is the basis of assault I I was
making ch
this is the basis of a solid meta minion
build so you're good wasn't meta enough
it
seems it's your fault
yeah no no
no they are kind of strong
here oh give them that
got to take some
[Music]
distance and I that's good I'm getting
back into the
groove pain pickle pain
pickle oh
no no that was that was wrong
again vocal warm-ups featuring hea
pickle but they're cute the way it's
like a not a hermit
crab it's a stone stone hermit crab very
cute Boulder ant oh it's an ant damn hug
ant
okay that chest I already
took oh that's another chest whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa oh pretty what a
pretty Beetle mini would love that
Beetle are these going to move those
statues are they real
people hello oh
oh terra cotta
Soldier save move
indeed and what about you guys in the
back no you're not going to move oh look
at these
guys Greater Life
PL take Take Ah the usual
issues not being able to pick up
items I don't trust these statues
oh take take
it they saw what happened to the
other true those few ones are the Smart
Ones thank you for the Super Chat super
D you know that didn't s started copying
that because
like in like shops and stuff like the
museum shop for example I would just say
super D when I was
like uh or like in the restaurant when I
was getting the bill or something like
that in German we
say sometimes we add like super than you
super to the d word or other words
really but it's just like a great
thanks yeah and then she started copying
it so
cute she kept on repeating it and then
she said it to the German speaking
people IRL and they
chuckled cute
yeah like a little parrot she should
have been a a
bird she should have been a bird but too
bad device is only
humans I say that now even though I was
also
relieved honorary
H she got some parrot
je some carrot blood in her veins
she does like talking right them carrots
like talking too are you going to go and
live yeah yeah yeah yeah let's go come
to
live cool very original I feel
like very
unique speaking of woo oh oh he's a
special boyet
oh my God I'm pulling so
many oh he's so fast oh he's so fast
he's got a constant like blur around
him very
dramatic oh there's another fancy
one okay okay I cleaned up let's go oh
this one has two slots I'm taking that
and I'm going to salvage that oh wait
he's still
there wait no oh yeah he was still there
oh did he go back because I pulled him
too far or he lost track of me and he's
not fast enough even though he's still
blurry can't even keep up with
me
[Music]
lame ha
very rare mob
nice I killed a minion what do you mean
I killed a minion a minion of
his very good I'm the only one who
should have
minions yeah speaking of unique did you
guys see cop's new
[Music]
outfit it's so cute I can't wait for
people cosplaying it
so cute the hair is so cute and the big
puffy
jacket I love
it so cute as
casual surprisingly I guess the first
casual outfit
cuz
yeah did she not have a casual outfit
until
now surprising if we can allow the
my Warriors will SW Hunter so
cute adorable my child she would look
good next to your ' 80s outfit yeah I
thought you were going to say in my 80s
outfit keep her away from my 80s
outfit next to okay wait I'm going to go
over there because apparently that's
where I need to go so I want to go back
and back trap image
image way she says that Callie also
started playing huh she couldn't
resist saw us play and she was like I I
want and she's playing the same class as
me right because of the
skeletons
image how does she like the Sass has she
commented on the Sass of this
lady oh
checkpoint you guys Co
up you guys say that about
everybody oh forward command
T oh oh there's a Impaler
person oh my God oh my God what are you
doing leave me he has some ow kind of
Aura how did I not get hit by that
woo trying to hit her with my charged
arrows here and there whoa whoa whoa
whoa
ow there we go good one good one
strong W was strong so let's free the
free free the impaled corpses I'm sure
they'll thank me for it
yeah Takami I've been thinking you know
would be cool to do something with
Takami
again well she she would have to catch
up to
me I don't like the charged Arrow I like
the damage it does but it does take a
while to charge it so that it's
efficient and a lot of bosses are really
fast so you got to catch them off guard
oh
well coming up the 24hour stream that's
not really coming up like as I said last
time like we might want to plan that one
out a little bit more before
we before we do that oh is that my
Caravan going through ah cuz we opened
the
gates Co that's so cool that we can see
that oh look at it
yeah we should do the thing where like
one of the Caravan does a thing with a
pole where they jump over the like up to
the bridge and then they wait they wait
they wait for the Caravan to go by until
last minute until it even like already
passes but and then then the people on
the Caron would be like hey what are you
doing jimy come on stop joking around
and then like then he jumps and like on
the very last little edge of the Caravan
he lands
I have the vision yeah yeah I've seen
that both in like videos from Italy and
Japan I
think yeah both in their own
style
funny waste of my
time so
sassy oh sorry that's my own
where you going
lady running off on her
own this actually probably has my
favorite final area huh oh okay Al you
mean like your favorite final
boss I'm
scared today I don't want to stream too
long but I also want to make
progress hard choice because I I I kind
of need to do something behind the
scenes a little a little prep for
something special for Christmas for you
guys a little prep I say but it's a it's
a big prep I think not you think
not
oo I need to um use my toad
portal 10,000 I have over 10,000 gold
now let's go can be spent at vendors
thanks I wouldn't have thought so
no not Advent calendar stuff Advent
calendar going really smoothly though
I'm really
glad I also got a few videos now in
advance just just a few girls um
submitted early
Hallelujah those
angels what am I here for oh
yeah how can I
be so it's going really
moovly
yippee
what let
you oh a
scepter level six discipline but that
our is obviously overpowered this one's
cool but we don't use
staffs too bad oh wait
Fe Phoenix and ring mail gauntlets it's
me those are made for me and they're
actually pretty good
looking
yeah I mean yeah more fire damage and
fire resistance yeah double more than
double the fire resistance than the old
ones would have they're not that good
they're decent okay I'll have you
know they're decent they're better at at
least and they
are uh carrying the Phoenix name so oh
come
on how could I not wear them you
know I'm glad you
agree so I'll just I'll just no I'll
stay okay into my statue
go ah
yeah okay back to the toad portal I'm
coming it's lowkey worst
what the serious is not I don't care I
don't care good enough it says Phoenix I
have to wear it
it's at least not bad maybe it's a bit
worse in your opinion but it's like if
you would ignore the existence of the
old ones then you would think these new
ones are great if my old ones were worse
you would think these are
great
logic yeah I have to wear them ooh
golden chest
so yesterday was my day off I did again
a million things really my days off are
never days
off but it also felt good to get some
stuff done
again oh oh hello special special person
oh
God also I I so I did the C thing right
you saw that on my Twitter
perhaps I laid a long L
table that was just hanging around I
wish I would have done that before the
girls came over I forgot about that
detail I hope they didn't think like
anything of
it don't judge
me um but yeah I basically I I used like
these
tiny M what do you call them like it's
like
[Music]
um how do you call
them it's like like a like a doughy
sticky
little thing
uh uh
M blue Tack okay whatever that is we
don't call it that but maybe we're
thinking of a similar
thing but normally like they sell it so
that you can hang posters or so on the
wall without using like tape or
something but I use it to fixate It On
The Ground the cable the land table to
stay in place it works pretty well for
that
yeah like sticky pads tiny ones that H
fix yeah that you can like cut into like
the size that you
want like if you want to but yeah you
don't you don't have to cut them but you
can that worked
well now it's going along the bottom of
the
wall it looks so much more clean it
makes me happy and then I also finally
hung up the last person but you know
first had to
drill uh some
holes to put the the
railing oh my
God yeah there we go this is my power to
cuz I had I had one more room without
curtains Yago is at the game
awards in
person oh is he dare to have someone
personally take the
award wait do they know ahead of time
it's about time like I don't know if he
would go if he didn't know that he was
getting the
award ah the people would not understand
like in in our spaces when Yaga shows up
everybody's like woohoo let's
go but they will not understand that
they are in the presence of an
idol Pi that [\h__\h] up thank you
watch show don't tell people that that's
right I would think so
but what the voting ended last night oh
so last
minute
H okay so maybe he doesn't know him
maybe he's just uh hoping and also just
thinking oh cool event might as well
go have a good reason for an O overseas
business trip to ride off my might as
well go and have fun in La I
assume I
[Music]
assume yeah just casually
attends yeah I hope I hope we get a win
you
know would be
funny it would be funny oh what the what
the hell wo oh nice
doah oh I forgot my about my totem I
forgot about the existence of it of a
king Rock of a
king the man
will dodg it perfectly a second time
leave you to the wait wa what you what
the [\h__\h] was that
go go go
go you are unworthy chill oh very very
big
Miss will fall the [\h__\h] is that by my
hand look at that spicy thing over
there I want to I want to charge my
arrows but it just takes too long wa
okay uh-oh what how do you dodge do it
just have to roll I thought the I I I I
I heard that the roll doesn't have
invincibility frames though inside
oh hold back while I open the
[Music]
gate in the middle you say are
unworthy I shall Dethrone you and leave
you to the side okay inside [\h__\h] [\h__\h] ah
so
fast will fall oh God oh God oh God I I
I used to be better what what what what
what what
what I'm want to die I'm so
scared I shall de you second
I shall D you you two got issues why do
I have to be part of it oh here yeah
okay
okay you are
unworthy the micus will
fall barely barely dodged
it I shall Dethrone you SAR and leave
you to the you are
unworthy
okay I shall de you sear and leave you
to the side okay I'm
here I shall me a good opening when heg
that LE you to the
SS you are unworthy what yeah I shall
Dethrone you Che them up does he say the
same things for the same attack is it
like
matched I tried to seek peace wait what
what ah what is that what is that again
what what oh I haven't seen that
before
timeo my heal potion is also dead
no what the
[\h__\h] not
today we must not
Escape oh did I kill ra the corpse King
is running away oh he's running
away was he down to zero HP I feel like
he
wasn't
CL I was graceful nothing about that was
graceful but
FS ah okay yeah um if he didn't run away
he would have easily killed
me wait
heal I'll just take my
toone try to get an item with life regen
for when you out of
potions a yeah it would be
good do whatever it
takes what
this one the design of this one looks so
sick buzzing diet crossbow of these that
looks so
cool oh that also even though it's so
simple looks like a cool
Shield paint a tower Shield over the
S aged greater Mana flask uh 63 68
increased Mana recovered remove 50% of
Mana recovered from when from life when
used
what
weird sell blue gear I thought you guys
were always saying uh uh
disenchant blue
gear you should only Sage rare
ah it's fine we got enough money quickly
he cters the very s against US ah he's
just going to be worse now right where
is
he I feel like he's just going to be
more powerful Sandstorm we must battle
sorcery with sorcery what we fight sand
Let Us return to the Caravan andreat
dark wisdom we fight the
sand what what do you mean fight orcery
of
sorcery I can't fight the what do you
mean return to the
Caravan
BR what was that the right Quest Point
Sara what do I do how do I fight the
sand do I have to be one with the sand
oh this was not an ability he had in
life oh it must be born of corruption
corruption there is something in the
tales that could help us overcome such a
power it would said that the Horn of the
vastii could control the
winds I believe the Horn's location has
been lost to time but perhaps it is
possible that we can reconstruct it we
would have to retrace the steps of our
greatest heroine orala on her final
Adventure speak to
assala she knows the tale and where it
might take us let her know how you wish
to begin or you may seek my wisdom if
you have further questions she so cute
oh you may see my
wisdom if you want to
do not
Wonder uh
asala
aala
where she's not here is
she I don't see her here wait who's
asala it's not the lady that came with
me right was that aala maybe it was aala
are you a I only remembered your other
name sea or yeah
sea I her name is aella but I can't talk
to
her
hello oh and oh she doesn't want to talk
here damn girl I guess it's too noisy to
talk there the the wind is so strong
why doesn't it show her on the map
though when I ran over I guess I had to
go even closer okay ah yes yes the Horn
of the V Theon I know the T the ancient
city of ke the bad lands and the Valley
of the Titans we can retrace orala steps
in any order
create the Horn of the vasi use the
desert map to travel to curve use the
desert map to travel to the Mason
Badlands use the desert map to travel to
Valley of Titans for Glory for Glory
okay
great Theon we got so much to
do H where first let's see monster level
21 monster to level
21 Mon oh this time it's all the
same
H do you have a
recommendation for the trial side
quest trial side quest is uh this
one trial of the SAS
wait
uh
huh top right of map oh this one oh it
doesn't have any signs so I didn't
really register
it not
hold you would do it later or is it that
difficult okay I'll randomly choose you
H stop stop stop let me
out over here then
okay massive power boost oh but first we
need some more power I suppose a place
of ritual and Bone I suppose I should
retire here
someday oh how cute she sees bones and
thinks ah this should be my retirement
home I like it
here it feels just like
[Music]
home are you
doing oh my God
let me take this
out already
chaotic uh where are we going up
maybe you're
spooky oh you look like you can come to
live like the Terracotta
people woo
w w wow
wow
oh let's
see I want to
say ah I was in the middle of my home
[Music]
tangent that I got a lot a lot of other
things done
again my home so clean right now I
cleaned up I got curtains everywhere the
cable is properly
placed I did all the dishes and
stuff also I cleaned my water cooker
uh do you not say water cooker I forgot
again and then I even felt like fancy I
I turned on uh I lit some candles some
scented candles I don't normally bother
doing that also cuz I don't spoke so a
lot of the time I don't have a lighter
at
home or I forget where I put the one
single lighter that I have I'm like
where where did that
go but I I lit some candles and it got
so cozy I put two scented candles in my
bedroom and just
chilling with my
cats he's so
[Music]
cozy sometimes it's nice
to make your
home the most
comfortable that it can
be let give yourself the spa
experience BLS are
bone splinters are bone
Splinter a bone how did she say
it I don't like this place because uh
the enemies are like scattered so far
apart because there's so much
space see they only have like little HP
left and they're just running around
stupidly
oh no Splinter born
bar where are we oh wait I went back but
there's a cap here
no minions rise at my
call that's really like
face
V oh veterans I was thinking of vets
like a vet like a animal
doctor because that's the first thing on
my mind right now thanks to S
Goodman actually thanks to Mike I
guess veterans they like Open Spaces
more
what the okay there the upper ones are
ignoring me I need to fight these ones
first
now come on stop ignoring
me there we
go from B
I like these lost men raised from bone I
like these lost
men that's one of those sassiest voice
acting performances I've ever
heard I wish it was me
win oh what the hell was
that oh I also hung up like free
pictures but like the reason why this is
worth me announcing it to you is because
it was also effort because I couldn't
just use Nails the nails wouldn't go
into the wall the wall was too fix so
had to be drilled
super strong
drill also I got contacted uh by the
museum they had to like wait for stock
to arrive now they have the
stock I didn't answer yet though I
[Music]
forgot they're going to send me a big
picture that I wanted to buy
but they only had the single
one that was like just for showing
it so they had to I guess it was really
popular because it it took them a while
and there were a couple people on the
waiting list
seemingly such a popular picture I never
thought ever before about like buying
something like
that but recently I was thinking of more
and more want
some more nice pictures to show up in my
home and normally I would go for like
pictures that aren't printed I'd prefer
to if I go out of my way to spend a lot
of money on something on a picture on a
painting then I'd want it to be like not
a printed one but this one looked so
good even though it was
printed like really good quality and
really
big so I thought why not is it supposed
to not
move like
this B
Beed the frame for it no this one's like
on a canvas so it already looks great
without a
frame well not really like a real canvas
but yeah pick up entropy entropy where
is that
culture joob making home fancy for real
like having a piece of art from a famous
artist in my
home that's going to be cool I mean h
Straton is not as famously known as
rembrand but I can always explain oh
yeah this H Straton person was a a
student of rembrand and you he was
really good you're so
unsophisticated for not knowing
hen ew stop talking to me
ow uh where are we wait I I'm up
here so where is this other thing you
wanted me to go to it's probably further
away oh you put a jewel here
huh and oh here
too a
jewel he was second right no have some
respect he was so so cool it's bigger
than my TV it's close to the
[Music]
beginning how am I supposed to find ah
wait I can type in right what was it
called again
entropy thank God that exists where is
that what
what I don't see ah this
one uhhuh well if you say so who said
who said that I should get
that thank
you oh
okay hey this one might be nice too
though cuz my spikes do physical
damage this might be better
actually duration is nice for Raging
Spirits ah my my little minions true
true
true there's better nodes okay for like
my minion
duration okay I'll continue looking at
minion
stuff should we finish
this kind of want to go somewhere else
too you know what I'll I'll prep but
where are we which direction are we
going after that are we going up here ah
we could for this
node it's uh oh that can dance increased
evasion rating this atud minutes
oh a lot of damage damage Dam damage for
minions all bonuses from an equipped
amulet apply to your minions instead of
you minions more life life for minions
and resistance for
minions
uhhuh I see I
see
uh more oops more damage
more life more all kinds of things yeah
this one up here has all kinds of things
area
AOE reduced
reservation oh there's one here
too ah increased attack and cast speed
minions revive
faster more AOE more cool down recovery
more life this one sounds pretty good as
a
whole
oopsie is there anything any anything
down
here no no oops no
no there's one
here that's pretty
close uh minions revive faster oh lots
of revive fast I like that I like
[Music]
that more movement speed cast speeds
accuracy
o this one is kind of interesting and
not too far actually I'm already
[Music]
here I think I like that I'll I'll I
might go that way too at the same
time
[Music]
um easy to resp oh well done well done
well
done okay
what it was
here no I wasn't oh another
ritual oh wa W oh it's just a normal
enemy you guys try harder with your
summoning that could have been a cooler
enemy come
on okay it did some damage to
still fossil D Memorial
[Music]
whoa what's going on here oh check
pun arest with the Rembrant L has Ren
Spirits taking o taken over you
take take take oh in full
a oh also I guess I have an unused um
skill gem oh wait it ah I still don't
have what enough enough intelligence or
what oh okay then it's good that I
skilled into in just now I'll continue
doing
so
checkpoint should I go back to the other
one oh look at him steal eyes the surv
sural how do I say your name
sir extra CH
damage me
kfp skin would be cool how's the grind
grind's going
well H but cannot grind too much
today
sadly I need to get to
work I'm going to prepare a nice
surprise of course it annoys me don't I
look and sound annoyed when I click on
the items and they don't pick up
of course it's annoying
me but I tolerate it for a better life
experience quality of
life speak up speak
up so who else agrees on just selling
the blue
stuff I mean it doesn't really matter I
think at this point we have a lot of
transmutation shards
that
good
[Music]
okay wait I should have looked at
that uh increase life
covered remove remove Shana
uh Wonder it's snowing here in the
desert
crazy selling the blue stuff ah you guys
just saying I should sell the blue stuff
because I'm Heisenberg and I need to
stay true to
myself that was makes so much
sense y' if only Hank knew in that voice
message already that I go by Heisenberg
now poor guy he would have suffered some
kind of PTSD trauma coefficient did you
know Hank from Breaking
Bad uh I got yesterday I got a cameo
from
Hank it was so
sweet you saw yeah now my in-game
character is called Heisenberg because I
created it in the night where I was
watching the finale and I was like
so my my head was full with with
Breaking
Bad yeah so I go by Heisenberg now have
some
respect what's my
name say my
name say it that's damn
right I
aming oh blue blue
guy where am I I need to go back to the
other checkpoint I feel like
even though she kind of hated him
me no I mean honestly even until the
very end I had like some sympathy for
him for
sure how can you not have sympathy for
Brian
cranon whatever the name was you got to
love that guy
no matter how evil of a guy he
played he still had a heart surprisingly
I honestly I I was surprised I feel
like like I I was disappointed in myself
for
sympathizing with him at the even at the
end I wanted to purely hate
him
but I don't know maybe made it difficult
to have pure hate for him don't you
think yeah cuz when when it really goes
down and he like in the finale he gets
like separated so to say from his life a
goes down yeah you it's just like
consequences of your
actions people die
if uh
you do [\h__\h] like
that yeah
Jessie
Jesse I don't I don't
know feel like he came around too late
when it comes to Jesse he still wanted
to kill Jesse for too long the bone pits
is that where I'm supposed to go the
bone
Pits on which one am I right now
sh of ivory ah ah it does say bom pit ah
okay
ah well then this
was uh the right way that I was going
didn't have to go back to the other
checkpoint but now I'm curious what was
at the checkpoint never I guess I guess
just a I guess it was just
a random yellow enemy or so
nothing to worry about too
much monkeys AKA hyenas oh speaking of
monkeys my favorite show on YouTube jet
lag the game they put out uh a new
season uh this one's again in
Japan their second time I think that
they're doing it that they're filming in
Japan
looks like they filmed in summer though
I wish I could have like seen
them I love that like and so a while ago
before the new season launched they just
put out the first episode of the new
season on YouTube but a while ago I saw
there I think it was a community post or
so
um I saw that they were selling
finally a
a version of the game that they always
play that anybody could play anywhere
not restricted to a particular region
it's not too specific it's not too
region
specific uh and and it was like I think
early uh pre-order or something so I
ordered one I don't have it yet but I
ordered
one it's basically a card
game and you take it and you go
somewhere and then you play it outside
it's like challenges you need you need
friends to play it with I guess but I
bought it thinking
that if anything maybe this could be
used for a future
video
Vlog I would in that case I probably
would need perms for it though but I
feel like they would give
it or like I originally wanted to make
my own
version not just use
theirs but I don't know it's cool to
have so I just bought it before I regret
it and it's like not available
anymore where do you buy the friends
from well in fact there are some people
who offer their friendship for money
in Japan too rent a friend for a day
rent a boyfriend for a Day stuff like
that doesn't exist would they play this
game with you I don't know if you would
pay for the travel costs
maybe if you guys aren't watching that
show you should watch it it's free on
YouTube and the first episode was
already 1 hour 20 or
something was over so quickly though it
felt so fast they release a new episode
every
week game a bit loud
okay I lo it a tiny
bit monkey monkey
whoa whoa whoa
whoa oh was this the
way am I once again going the right way
no it's not the
way
FG when I see
fig I I think
of one of the kfp
names sound similar can you guess which
one no
yes yeah you
know maybe it doesn't sound too
similar bra
not going to get killed by no
names wow dinosaur is it a dinosaur it
looks like one
the
Hors centor
Hena Ena was in my dream too by the way
it was kind of weird there were like a
lot of people that I couldn't recognize
in my dream then there was one that kind
of looked like
Jesse then there was Dy who I thought in
my dream was a girl the artist who drew
the current members wallpaper like went
up to them and I was
like like I hugged them and and I
thanked them for drawing me and I asked
if they would ever draw me again because
I really liked it and I I I really like
the way they draw
boobs how can you remember your dream so
vividly this one I was about to forget
but the the Dai one I kind of remembered
randomly throughout the day like oh
right yeah I dreamt
that Ena was also in my
dream it was weird because she was not
really going along with a joke that I
was
doing
somehow apparently I was from the
future but like the way I accessed the
past was through the dream like I was
lowkey
saying like I'm in the dream but not
really I wasn't as a aware as that
sounds yeah but so then I saw Ena and I
was like hi past Ena and then she stops
and looks at me and is
like
[Music]
hi and
then yeah I explain to her yeah you're
I'm I'm wa from the future you're Ina
from the past
yeah cuz um I I don't know I was trying
to explain it I don't really know what
exactly I
said but she just looked at me after my
explanation and then just without a word
walked away really
disappointed she just had this
disappointed
look she didn't even question the whole
past in a future she didn't believe me
that I was from the future
I know man was
sad she just ignored
me bro this was so
aggressive oh yo was that
stop if that one if they if they use
that same enemy and make it a golden one
that could kill
me maybe
maybe bad end my they hate each other in
my
dreams yeah she didn't take me seriously
she wasn't listening to
me well
well do be like that sometimes and I
know there was a checkpoint there but I
always like to walk away from the
checkpoints cuz I still have so much of
the map
undiscovered there we
[Music]
go is it just me
I'll go back though I need to control
myself my my RPG senses tell me that was
the right
path oh you can teleport between
checkpoint now do you have to be at a
checkpoint to do that
that would be cool where was this
checkpoint I think it was up
here but there's more un unrevealed map
here I need to see it
all oh yeah yeah yeah that's that's
unrevealed map oh wait there's a door
here wait is that where I came
from is that where I came from
Master wait yeah that is where I came
from right masteron bad
lands okay I kind of circled
back oh they adding that later okay
so not
yet my throat kind of feels very
scratchy I think in the beginning or so
of the stream I
screamed and now it hurts it's not
because of the peka stuff
though some screamed that I
did [\h__\h] it up how it hurts
it's not the pcka boys trust
me I can
tell madon are like mammoths but
[Music]
smaller oh this is where I needed to go
I I knew
it I knew it and I didn't want to go
maybe another fro candy could
help oh we're
full are we though are
[Music]
we how big is that
uh uh wait
here
um
oops look at
that but I'll still go back now I
think for a
moment water yeah I need to drink more
I've been
sipping
siing what was she
[Music]
and oh life
regeneration this one also
[Music]
Califoria gos were
Unforgettable Dy bikinis on
top West Coast represent put your hands
[Music]
up what is this sunclan Relic by the
terms of the first pack the sunclan
agreed to never again attack the mara
cap Quest item oh wait several
can't take it there you go find a use
for The
Relic
H you say it
like with
no hint whatsoever what the use could
be
okay very vake whoa
[Music]
meteor that's a bug what's a bug it will
be a apparent later on them not saying
what I should do is a
bug that's crazy if that's a
bug ah two dropping at the same time and
maybe it's because um I didn't pick up
the first one right away and the other
one like they just drop until you pick
up
one just making sure
wait did I oh that's connected
too okay I can go back although what is
this path up
[Music]
there oh another dead end this place is
cool
[Music]
too wow
all these little little nodes it's just
like the oh it's just like my skill
tree oh black bird black bird black
GB what what what what what what the
hell are
[Music]
you oh lots of electricity here
huh do I have anything with like
electricity n right now oh my God oh my
God
stop
[Music]
ah where are my minions
there ow ow ow I feel like I can barely
move around
oh he's doing that
again which one of you is doing
that I need more
[Music]
minions okay actually never mind it's
it's it can be pretty chill this bite is
okay
I say and I'm probably going to die in a
moment
ah but it's it's pretty chill
though pretty
chill I just I it's just hard to find
some space
sometimes oh
also I'm running out of HP uh recharge
so that's
bad I should focus on one maybe maybe
that's the Strat I I I I didn't know who
to focus on
honestly I'm
dying almost could have done this first
try but I think now the chances are low
ah did I
miss
no oh I'm in ah it's
feasible yeah maybe maybe maybe first
try
I won this
down you've got napping on me
now there you go first try
it I am your
NE nice
Caster yeah maybe I I I really should
have just focused on one in the
beginning but first try so no
complaints what no
space wow I ripped off the
tusks how big is the great
[Music]
hammer damn what do I do
yeah no space no matter how I Tetris
this
one I mean maybe maybe
but go to your stash and use your UNC
support gems to put fire infusion and
Marshall
Tempo what have you learn a
these tasks are truly wor I to go to her
anyway
thanks can you turn off like other
player special effects they're kind of
annoying me visually they're just too
much my uncle which level do I have to
be
only at the moment no
no
what ah that sucks if you can't do
that only level one
okay to I'll try to do what you
said g was it G it's not g is it
[\h__\h] e go
away a
help
a it's been a while and then what uh
raging Spirits
right
H uh I can't
one more strength okay H did I just I
thought I just had a level up I guess I
didn't next skill point okay I'll look
for
strength I'll be on the
lookout the change nah it's okay go to
all gems and search for Marshall Temple
oh you think I can get that
one Marshall
Tempo by the way guys I saw it in a clip
apparently on my first Poe stream I did
accidentally show boobs but it was so
fast that not even I
noticed speak up
I show baa yeah some of you guys noticed
that
amazing you were like ready for it you
knew where to
look
um what was it
[Music]
Marsh all right well I had nothing in
there anyway
so good to have something
now
25% so what this is going to be faster
I guess it feels
faster anyway wait was I I still have to
find the use for The Relic within this
map wait the horn that just dropped was
is part of the main quest to make the
Horn of the vtii right and TR to use for
The Relic that's an extra point I
suppose a separate Quest
thing you notice that in
the hopefully off
stream what's going on
here another Zone
oh maybe the entrance to the other zone
is like somewhere here though or am I
just completely in the wrong
place can go back to
town
a number one k player I don't know about
that I'm sorry but I don't know about
that I also I got a DM from Han a couple
days
ago
with a
video spicy video
of her in a feite la
crossplay kind of like doing a workout
and
stretching
and doing
like
yeah uh workout
moves like professionally filmed
[Laughter]
she just she just sent stuff like that
to me bless
her wait so I'm done with that part
where where do I where should I go now
should have been
me yeah well I'm special I am literally
me so when she cosplays me I have a
right to
see norf again
and back to Desert map
okay re still here we chilling
around her merch previews are out out
yeah H they look beautiful she looks
beautiful mama mia what a woman what a
[Music]
woman I'm so glad mad that she like cos
blade me
again and it's always such high quality
it's really nice to
see she's womaning all the girls are
Girling Girling all the girls are giring
Girling all the girlly girls where
should I go what do I
[Music]
do I just go
here myu besti
now you guys know the song so from my K
so now you should know what I'm singing
cuz you heard it in my K
recently unless you
didn't wait wait wait a second I'm doing
am I doing it wrong again no lived and
died here Valley of the Titans their
demise W they're tall
oh
tornado wait there's a there's a yellow
enemy already right here not wasting any
time huh Shadow
wither he's like the Wither from
Minecraft honestly pretty similar maybe
they were inspired by him skeleton the
Wither is a skeleton after all kind of
flying
around Shadow you know with it was like
dark so makes
sense those are some big dead beads but
they just turn into tiny little scorpion
thingies for
me more
beetles I like them they're cute
ah uh who here is going to
AWA have you guys been practicing your
water water ring
skills about to head out oo have fun
have a safe
trip wanted to put didn't work out maybe
another time but that's too bad I a
[\h__\h] hell a tornado killed
me um I was just going to
say I was I I'm I want to say
something to the AWA
goers to the AWA
kfp you might want
to
watch the cheering guide
again understand understand
I can't Pi it
up I got it I got
it I'm
glad oh by the way so one more tangent
that I wrote down so that I don't forget
yet it
seems
my visitations from L and ren were
successful
propaganda for my
Austrian tourist guide travel
Services I have received a request to be
a host for
number
two whole live Japan
members not like right away but sometime
already like a month was mentioned in
2025 it's it's some girls that I already
have a connection with so I'm glad
obviously I'm very happy
going to welcome
them I'm
surprised I guess you know it's good
like L and radden we we showed off off
our trip uh in the Stream and like with
pictures on Twitter and stuff they must
have seen
that was good
promotion very good
promotion I think especially the 3D
pictures that chy put together for
me by the way I I drew like sketches to
show chy how I wanted
it maybe those pictures that those those
must have really had good good effect I
think this area is kind of rough
difficult need to focus even for the
smaller
enemies not I'm not doing my bestest
that's for
sure but there's two blue ones
bro
yeah it's going to be going to be fun
and maybe like now those two hit me up
about it
just yesterday who knows maybe there'll
be even more like it has only just
begun maybe we'll get even more
requests I mean it's obviously not said
in stone yet
but seems pretty motivated about it the
girl that asked
me she was like Hey can can we visit you
together like in this month next year
really want to go please post
us go away
tornado I hope it will work
out now we got possibly the Mal's trip
saved and we got
another uh couple of girls coming to
Austria oh ancient Seal Seal of the
shaki let him see let him see so he is
able to forgive oh oh wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait it appears they
fought here what did I died put in the
place uh
the other green
thing the the big green thing I put in
there huh cool he's face
palming wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait do I do
something they want WWA so bad are you
imitating
gigy there's more BS I did it already
okay okay is there free seals of
that oh wait so wait wait wait wait
wait they obsess shut up they're not
obsessed with
me but also I've been I've been like
recently I've been also reconnecting
with Mat
andai made me ah made me happy
too we made a date for next
time I'm in Japan we're going to what
the heck are
those going to hang
out
God bless our
God they want me so
bad yeah I'm going to have a one-on-one
with God just talking
about all the Unholy things have done in
2024 all speaking of Unholy F uh no
spoiler at this point uh fuok was Advent
calendar yesterday I think uh did you
guys watch it they did the same thing as
last year where they
um judged in place of Santa who was
naughty and who was nice and just like
last year they put me on naughty again
and so the moment I heard that I dm'd
them back I was like why am I naughty
again and I listened to more while they
were typing out their
apology uh and then it said like oh
because you know my my spicy outfits and
and my performance at nissa's birthday
wo I was like yeah never mind makes
sense 10 seconds after was like why am I
naughty again I'm like ah never mind
makes
sense I feel like the year before I I I
I don't know if that one made sense I
don't think they even gave a good
reasoning the year before why I was
naughty I don't think they had a reason
this time they gave a proper explanation
it makes sense I
guess mostly yeah mostly not always
they're not always reason
those
doggles but I like
the I like the idea there oh [\h__\h] I'm so
far I like their little
um you
know Advent calendar
idea this time they brought the receipt
yeah good still not good Mama
Mia well heab BB had nothing to do with
it
apparently heisen BB did nothing wrong
I swear I can fight
better but I'm just uh especially for
the non boss fights I I I'm just like
chilling
today uh um I'm just chilling
I could try harder I I
could but wait are there like how many
Blues are here there's like free all the
tall
ones what are you this is
insane branded oh my go oh my oh my oh
my oh my oh my oh my God granted uh last
stream I was like
fighting more efficiently because I was
using my my totem Po and
everything all the time even outside of
boss
fights what the [\h__\h] is what what what
like going on here why was this so
difficult
well
damn lacking some damage
maybe they had energy Shields yeah I
notic this I no this but for some
brandles they were pretty damn
strong squishy well not squishy oh
another special one
bro
die Mama M
where ah by the way I had a level up and
I needed some strength
here I think we got to go up eventually
anyway so I could take this
one
yeah what is this a charm grants
immunity to bleeding used when you start
bleeding oh oh completing this Tri will
you to choose your ascendency oh take me
to the trial of the Sig as I will serve
hey hey hey hey the Jin the
Jin oh
what is this what I needed in this
region
how can I
advise hello no there's
more dense giant wait these are bigger
aren't they dance giant Mana flask of
the
medic uh increase recover rate 23%
chance to gain a charge when you kill an
enemy m
that's the bigger one right uh 165
yeah this one bleeding huh I don't even
notice like I surely have bled before
but I haven't noticed it I'll just put
it in here for
now and these do I have to carry these
with me they're small so I'll I'll do it
I'll carry them with me but uh I need to
do the
thing
uh
uh fire infusion nah was it
that
what yeah fire infusion okay uh
supported attacks gain 25 5% of damage
as extra five damage and deal 50% less
cold and lightning damage oh well yeah I
don't use that so that's
fine
okay good use of
that wait I I forgot this whole time
this whole time I put a candle here cuz
I'm in a candle mood now I guess I I
wanted to turn it on
here but it's already like so low it's
hard to reach the the thing okay it's on
fire fire fire light the
fire I should buy more sended candles
the few ones that I have are like empty
now
basically time to buy one I could just
get one like right now in this season
they sell all the ones that like smell
like Christmas
right all the Christmas flavored or
scented
don't eat don't
eat should I go up or
[Music]
down we
are it's a foot it's a
foot see a foot statue like this is
exactly what I was hoping for good I
would build in Minecraft all this time
look how great it is look how wonderful
this is this could have been yours GAA
but alas you didn't realize the
greatness of my
idea look at that and maybe
reconsider oh number
two yeah oh he's like screaming
these statues look really cool like uh
also good that I went down I suppose now
I go I'll go up let's
see a little bit to the
left can I ignore them just this
once no oh God all right I made a
mistake I made a mistake I made a
mistake
roll roll fight the power a the
tornadoes this life is
strange oh the other ones
disappeared I think for
now need more minions need more minions
out of Mana no
problem Y what the
[\h__\h] why am I
so I I've noticed my um probably because
chuny wonky was walking over my mixer
and changed some audio
settings feel like I'm peeking a lot
today hey I'm aware of it I can hear
it w [\h__\h] ice the ruthless you look
cool oh
purple oh and the a blue one is also
lurking
around is he dead oh he's already dead
he died so
fast H hello hello
for once I'm not complaining about
peeking is it usually you really let me
here HH well I don't know I turn myself
down a little bit so I may sound a bit
more quiet to you guys right now ah ah
ah now I still hear
it
huh weird it's not like that different
from my usual settings I I
thought I thought
so y go add Awards why you bringing it
up now did did he post something
oh we already talked about
it on Facebook what Yago uses Facebook
Facebook well okay there's still some
countries which use Facebook very
actively I don't think Japan is one of
them
though I know that um I think Thailand
is one of the places oh generally like
sea countries a lot of
them don't laugh no it's funny to
me wow wow wow wow wow
BR that's kind of crazy
my
bone flinters are bone that's how she
said it I think I nailed it this
time nice
drops
um be down
here no
did you turn your audio back up now you
sound kind of low I didn't turn it back
up um I turned a little bit lower cuz I
was peeking
but yeah I don't know what's going
on uh uh
I don't know was that button always
press ah ah ah ah no sounds the same to
me oh yeah that's that's something else
entirely uhoh
what
the wait I changed a lot of
things
damn uh I
sound louder
now ah Ah that's that's peaky peeky
peeky peeky
squeaky h
there goes your wine glass what did my
peeking destroy
it uh uh uh
uh or your surprise from my
peeking pick it up pick it up thank you
whoa what is that
guy I was reading your name and and and
eyeing your
coolness don't do this to
me I die a lot to simple things today no
I'm so
far no I'll try to run
through no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no
no no no no W what is the
statue those skeletons yeah they they
they're pretty strong and then the
tornadoes seem to be pretty rra to yeah
I hope some of the ones behind us left
[Music]
please
die is so
[\h__\h] Tuco from Breaking Bad be like
Mur so [\h__\h]
Kawai I love murder
ha oh this one looks
pretty to tole that crazy bastard
ah ah come
on no it's a quote from tuu tuku
literally said it himself he said murder
is so
[\h__\h] what have you
learned nothing I've learned nothing
from my mistakes and
actions o
looks so pretty I wish I could do the
thing that I can do in Diablo 4 of like
copying the looks of an outfit into
another one
transm compact giant Mana flask of the
Copus increased amount recover
covered
48 and increase charge is
[Music]
35 I don't know I feel like this like
getting a charge when killing an enemy
ah actually that's not good if you in a
boss fight cuz some of them barely spawn
any other minions
[Music]
someone could use AI to make him sing
that song that would be lovely why has
that not been done
yet why do I have give why do I have
give why do I have to do give everybody
the good
ideas I don't know if it's really better
but stay inside it can't
hurt stay inside did you just say stay
inside oh she does not support the
touching of the
grass a normal item to magic with one
chaos
[Music]
modifier touch
floor floor is
nice floor is good
ah the cool enemy is gone
huh no he's
gone oh it was a rare spawn
huh He's So Gone
m l game
loud okay sorry for the weird
balancing how about
now I just turned down
game oh brass slash that's another cool
one although the other one was cooler I
wish I could
have bought that
one charge and go
[Music]
GOI game super quiet my whole stream
quiet now okay game back a little bit
well I'll just try not to scream too
much and raise my voice again a little
bit about
screaming I don't know I had a meeting
today two hour
meeting about my next
3D
life cuz they're making the 3D stage
now and when I did that when I had the
meeting chunky wonky walked over
my she just walked all over it and then
suddenly life was not the same
anymore uh I see we have something here
huh what what is this on the
map just fancy
thing there's like a hand here but I I
can't do anything with
it need to press the last button first
oh okay is this the what opens when I
have all three of them activated
oh
oh there it is which one is
this this one I he's holding his head
his bald
head oh
no he seems to be very very troubled
oh what's happening opening up the Titan
grutto let's
go it's a sore
subject the
baldness
sumori this was certainly off limits to
Mortals how exciting
this voice acting I wonder if the others
the other characters also sound so
good you tell me Chad
e burn it burn it burn it with fire
Warrior
myth
really not as sassy ah she's the best
she's just the best huh
C is great
[Music]
hammer cult you
say are we dealing with a cult here oh
there's a huge
bat he after
Rion also very interesting and all these
huge ass statues here that are like I'm
not even paying attention to all of them
it's a waste to not pay attention to
them see how they're all like built into
the back here like a whole
head
broken super
nice over here too wow
design
K whoa spider spit
stinky got to stay away from
it I'm not sure those are statues what
what what do you mean of course they're
statues
or do you think it's giant dead people
dead
giants made into
stone Leu again we push appr it we need
that I need that need to sell that to
me I wonder should I go left or right in
my skill tree now I have both Taps
still so many
possibilities stop interrupting me
okay let me look at
it we could still finish this one which
by the way looks like a skull now that I
look at it or I can continue here
minions revive faster minions increased
life yeah I'll continue
here increased life let's go
my I don't know I feel like left was not
the right
C but that's exactly why it is the right
PA because it is the wrong
PA yeah my toad is a cash shop
purchase my to is beautiful in it you
want it you want my
toad my toad is my toad my
toad only belongs to
me whoa what the
hell no one one I'm sure you could get
some kind of cool
spicy um toxic poisonous big toads in
Australia on your own you don't need my
help I'm sure you have plenty of toads
over
there Toad from Luigi's Mansion no I do
not trade with that
toe that is an evil toe
nobody likes that
toad I would consider a Toadette
maybe Port
trade can I really go down or this is a
waste of time
I pass by an uncut
SCH you think I'll be in need of like so
many of
them oh my
God where is it I shall backtrack a
little bit
here oh this one's level
seven okay okay
okay I'll take it woo
actually it's good that we backtracked
anyway cuz it just feels like this is
the right
direction I can sense it oh no it wasn't
okay but like
roughly back up instead of down where I
was going I think
so over here
I saw some gameplay yesterday of
the Ranger or Archer whatever it is that
looks pretty fun
too oh wrong
again IEM
filters oh changing the color and L
A that sounds good
is it a mod or a cash shop
purchase I'm playing Ranger pretty
strong and fast yeah it looked looked
pretty
impressive by the way when they release
the rest of the game do you have to
restart from the beginning or can you
continue with the character you created
before
ah no
Wes I hear
mixed
answers they'll try not to oh huh
they're not sure yet they will add six
more
classes
O then I kind of I don't know depends on
what classes maybe I do want to
oh maybe I do want to like play again
but uh I I wouldn't really want to spend
all that time on stream
to
um level all the way up again
need more intelligence
bro it in that case if there is
a uh like boost a level boost how can I
advise I might even consider
it if I can go like to the level of my
choice which I guess probably not
there's a level boost okay damn it then
I have to play the
whole maybe maybe maybe maybe I can uh
how much longer do you think it will be
I feel like you told me before but maybe
when the real game comes out I can like
have my mom
play she would love this she loves
Diablo so she would love this I'm going
to have my mom play up until the point
of the end of the ark that
uh where this end
The Early Access and then I'll
just uh continue where she left off then
I don't have to play it
twice I feel like she totally do
it and then I I choose a class and say
mama you have to play this class
though especially if it like kind of
lines up
with me
being in Japan then she can take care of
my cats and
play but then well while like when it
releases while everybody is already
starting to
play I might not be playing right away
because my mom needs to first level my
character but we'll see it depends on if
there is a uh a loss of characters or
not really depends on that
oh
nah if we get the plus level one level
to all Minion skills again on this one
cuz I can still put the what was it was
it this one no the other
Stone then it might be
good might be pretty
good Vengeance hoof iron
Greaves oh no movement speed but
but lightning
resistance which is good in the current
region I
think and overall I think I should wear
this and it has a it has a slot
even oh I have a I have a thing in here
too how do I get it out if I sell it do
or should I Salvage this
one I
assume can speed over everything
be way more
[Music]
important okay damn you guys have some
standards you guys have some what about
this one though we need
um
uh this one right
a Regal
orb
orb what does it look
like ah this
[Music]
one too bad
hello
goodbye I will tell your tale thank
you okay all
right back
again next time we'll get him next time
time uh where were we over here finish
painting the base for Tiger waha p
w tiger and pan waa is what you're
drawing a
combination let's
go guys do you want to hear something
crazy you'll be happy about it
Wawa Wawa has been focusing
on releasing original songs for the
longest time and I'm currently working
on two song
covers
simultaneously luckily I what's going on
here luckily I kind of found some Gap uh
like I was originally going to oh still
okay I guess we fight oh great great
start I was originally going to can I
restart man n
n uh going to release a new song around
this time in combination with the extra
3D life that I would have
gotten if it wouldn't have been delayed
again while I was already planning it
um but then it was delayed quite a bit
so my original song also gets delayed so
I mean I could have still released it
but I wanted to time it
with
the uh with the 3D Live you know oh
oh so now I'm like okay
well coincidentally there's some song
covers I wanted to do
and they're not me
alone they're both collaboration song
covers
ow a
[\h__\h]
yeah wet PS
what the [\h__\h] was that
shaky are you cutting that wait wait
wait wait no you're not
okay oh
[\h__\h] ow that's iy
so yeah exciting
times working on it commissioning art
and stuff behind the
scenes who who whoa who
who just need
to uh I think one will be maybe out yeah
I've been tanging too much one will
maybe be out in like
January and the other one maybe February
March something like
that he always starts in the middle it's
not because I was there
okay stay close to his hand he won't
attack his own hand
interesting I shall test this
science for science
just walk under his AR interesting feel
like I was in his
line oh
spicyy oh
I feel like they could have made this
boss better like I feel like I'm getting
oh see right now again I feel like I'm
getting into his range a lot for his
attacks oh okay okay
okay no but for real like his um what do
you call it again his H box or my hitbox
I don't
know seems be a buggy right he's weird
with minion build builds you mean he's
weak to minion
builds o stabby stabby stab
stab
oh oh
spicing oh
and why did I run in no one will ever
understand thank you for the Super Chat
yeah song covers honestly
like I already told you about the like
original songs aren't very profitable I
will
say son coverers are even less
profitable because usually you can't
um you
can't uh monetize it but the art and the
like there's just costs it's just minus
but I'm doing these because I really
wanted to do
them one has like a lowkey
Sentimental reason behind it
so what I I don't understand the aim
like hard to register where I'm aiming
towards yeah like financially they're
not really worth it but I I think it
will be really
cute and I think it'll be just worth it
from
a different point of view fan service
service the
bone yo he's so strong why does he have
like 5 million HP and why can't I aim
this [\h__\h]
better I thought it aims where the mouse
is looking at but uh seems
[Music]
not oh maybe it's confused by oh holy
[\h__\h] where the enemy is
that one was right
ah no don't run
to I'm here I'm here see why didn't that
hit me stronger no complaints
but
ow okay okay okay we're good we're
good yeah he's so
bom oh he's so
bomb
[Music]
Oh so much time to [\h__\h]
up it's relatively
easy so bomb
how did that not hit me how did that not
hit
me he slam dunking me so
much and this angle is
perfect no no my HP thing is empty are
you kidding me charge back up please
otherwise it's all
over it's going to be
so heisen has been slain halfway through
the boss holy
[\h__\h] I need to kill enemies for it to
charge yeah uh you forgot about your
raging
Spirits uh I need to
kill what was it enemies for Raging
Spirits we should we should only use
flame
wall why oh I guess yeah well there's no
minions so but I thought une Earth is
still fine as an attack even if I'm not
Reviving anything
am I just too weak
maybe I feel like up until now I was
always levelwise
fine it's not doing a
lot foress is good
onal damage
SC the work and focus on dodging that
will take five years you might need to
ascend class first
got to do flame W
okay
well I think having this one out is also
good right although still
now does it hit him
though well hopefully now it does
oh what great start great start can we
restart now I'm I'm in yeah okay it
looks like holy [\h__\h] wait it does look
like it does a lot of damage
look how it's going
down I mean my Mana too but I can heal
that Spirits
arive not the spirits the
minions man this seems a lot faster
my fault my fault my
fault what the what what what well that
was a burst
what's he doing is he doing the the ulti
again yo how where do I go to dodge
maybe behind the
sword maybe behind the sword could it
be oh cool
ha but I still kind of survive standing
here I I won't risk it next time though
I'll try to see behind the
sword is that it no only if the sword is
out only if the sword sticks in the
middle
does my totem work for my spirits too or
only for the minions they're separate
right is it this this hurt
him sometimes it looks like it's not
really touching
him Spirits are minions
okay please first please I'm so far
you're not going
anywhere oh oh
[\h__\h] please
[Music]
please
what I red to the
void please kill kill kill kill
oh yeah this place is a little bit
buggy holy mother of
clutch I like how you guys are riding
clutch to with double ch
ch you've been working on this
[\h__\h] for almost 4 hours what
what class are you are you underleveled
for me okay it took me to understand
understand that my raging Spirits are
op at least against this
man
yeah didn't realize how shitty playing
melee
is but I was basically Ming this guy too
I was standing right in front of him the
whole time he resisted
fire that's with resisting
fire oh then we could have done it a lot
lot faster if we had a different element
or if he do have the resistance can you
please pick up the items I swear to
God no
no there we go and now mine
yipp pretty
feel like almost threw up in my
mouth now that I look at it I just now
noticed that this
floor has like
beautifully um iridescent
Reflections
pretty I just noticed your character's
name
I'm very proud of this one yeah can I
roll into the void again oh [\h__\h] yeah
yeah I
can maybe I can speedrun the game oh
like
this uh what's the company behind this
game oh behind this
game can we show them this VA oh oh my
God [\h__\h]
scary
um grinding gears look at this look I'm
I'm bug testing for you grinding
[Music]
gears can someone clip this on Twitter
so I can like I don't know if they have
a active Twitter
account oh Sho no I'm in it I'm in I'm
in oh [\h__\h] I'm gone oh
hi oh let's show this to
them I'm
chilling good fight though good
fight surely this is not just a me thing
surely this
is you know Common uh we can get out of
here now
right is there a bug command you think
so oh oh wait wait
please post any relevant information to
the bug reports for n I'm no that's M
sign I'm just going to post it on
Twitter I probably reported already huh
careful boss Twitter's toxic why do
people get mad for uh posting bugs of
Poe are they bug keeping the game
no
okay I still want to post it even though
somebody already probably reported it I
want to be a a good game tester you know
I I I'm I this is my job this is my job
I need to be good at it I need to do my
job
yeah so wait am I done here give the
flame Ruby to zaro looks like it let's
go I always press t
trying to portal to town but nothing
happens
weird yeah I have my QA Arc right now I
feel very proud of
it it's my destiny Zara what's up look
at this this Ruby is beautiful and quite
haunting Perhaps it is simply my
imagination I almost fell into the deep
deep void for it something staring
kind of did from deep
inside if you want to know if you're
done in an error you can check the world
map optional stuff is there uhhuh
okay did she just give me a level one
support
gem I don't understand the
logic what
why why would you give me a low level
one give me a seven
like an
a you'll be at
sore you'll try to investigate me at
sore well then I'll just ban you from
entering I'll be in a suit and have a
sign out to indicate that I
press all right
then you've made yourself very known
young one careful though don't get too
cocky should I
try uh putting a
third or it's not maybe it's not worth
it the base isn't nice little eight
discipline
nuh no no
no okay do not wonder do not Wonder not
Wonder
okay what now
uh I'll look at the map I still want to
find the use for The Relic can I not
finish that I want to finish the use of
The Relic
thingy got to go here
still as scent girl is your
time The Relic Quest is in the Giant
skeleton
area
here that Valley of the bad lands where
Mastodon bones rot Under the Sun for all
time is proof that a culture can vanish
entirely if the world changes don't
worry about it for now I will not let my
people diminish and disappear the where
do I find the second one
it's from CF oh wait didn't I just
travel to CF am I traveling to CF right
now I think I am yes
okay then I'll have my eyes on the
lookout I want to eat a chocol
little one
chocol the skeleton city of a once great
culture how adorable
adorable does she say that
sarcastically is she sarcastic right now
why she likes skeletons why does she
need to be
sarcastic
yummy the weary traveler has reached the
end of the path welcome to the city of
seven Wat
Bounty Springs Behold our Lush Plains
and verdant forests blessed to feed
Empires far and wide eat drink and be
fat at your leisure so long as you take
word back to your homeland of of
death
okay but it's a dead city right
what what are you oh immediately breeded
by a yellow
enemy it's so need oh my [\h__\h] [\h__\h] off
[\h__\h] off [\h__\h] off [\h__\h] off minions
somebody hello hello [\h__\h] up leave me
alone leave me
alone one small Speedy bug Boy versus a
powerful dead Reviving Phoenix who would
win who would
[Laughter]
win what's wrong with him well now he's
gone probably right
yeah it's just the normal
one well can't say that I missed the
other
one can't say that I
do that was an evil bug should I report
that bug
actually wait wait wait wait um grinding
gears grinding gears hello hello hello I
have another bug to report the one that
you just saw that's an evil evil evil
bug it kills
me do something about
it would you call this a bug I think
it's a
bug oh my go oh my God I don't like
these bugs I don't like it no what the
[\h__\h] leave me alone no I can't don't
leave me alone they're tickling
me me alone
what they're at the end of me I can't
deal with them they can't up with me too
fast they won't let go they want me so
bad I hate
it we might never get past this point of
the game now is
a come
on stand strong while I stand strong
survive don't let them take you
down okay okay I got a million minions
what do you
want Oh my
God it's just the
bugs only the bugs are a problem
you know those games where the the genre
is literally to just like kill massive
amounts of enemies what are they called
again sometimes this game feels like
that well not m i I mean like the actual
genre
name I can slash M no I mean the yeah
the Dynasty Warrior I think that's the
one the the one where also there was a
Zelda game
too the
ba uhoh uhoh I'm in trouble oh [\h__\h] I'm
in trouble I'm in trouble I'm in trouble
I'm in trouble I'm in trouble
give me more minions give me
[Laughter]
more wait wait wait we can talk about it
we can talk about it we can talk about
it we can talk about it we can talk
about it please let F
[Music]
about
no I can't de they want me so
bad oh my God
I I I I I I can't with those
bugs I was so
stressful that was so
stressful I should respect some points
into in so I can level my
gems
uh
ma do I have to how do I
respect oh you're still
here sorry the bug scared me
away the hooded one ah yeah
okay will it like respect the whole
thing and I have to redo the whole thing
or can I unsp particular ones
[Music]
oh one point
per one point at a
time oh the bugs but I'm ready for the
bugs this time although they're just
normal on
so they are not too dangerous once
they're
blue or yellow
especially yo if the boss of this area
would be a
bug it'd be so over for
me oh no oh no there's a yellow one
there's a yellow there's a yellow one no
way
no
[Music]
no look at that [\h__\h] look at that
happy [\h__\h]
damn I that is the scariest thing in
this game those bugs to
me that's the the worst thing the worst
thing in this game that's the fourth
time or so that I'm respawning here
because of a bug this game is so buged
no respect
time quickly time to
change okay but like
what what are we going to get rid of
this one I have on strength the question
is just like if I get rid of any of
these won't I ruin something else that
where what I need the strength and stuff
for or should I keep the attributes the
strength Etc and get rid of one of like
these ones
instead yeah see your build maybe maybe
you had troubles with that boss that I
fought pretty easily but you don't have
troubles with a
bug you hope I don't need that
press G first to see what you need
currently oh
uh all of
it I can't really give any
away you should fix your skills and
items
um but but if I get rid of one here in
the middle is that even possible because
like I need the one in the middle in
order to get to the other ones
right ins those small minion crit nodes
towards
wheel minion
wheel minion is that a
thing minion wheel which one's the
minion wheel oh this one H this
one this how you call those things with
the big noes at the
end
uh
um uh like one of
these what did you mean a spe speciic
one okay you say like get rid of the the
crit
ones
really how
many oh wait but ah how can I advise I
must keep
calculating if I if I take an attribute
now right we would want to go towards a
direction where we'll find something
that we want
[Music]
straight
up yeah that wouldn't hurt I at least
maybe although yeah here are still some
Minion
things evasion rating
dexterity increase damage one more yeah
critical
I'll take one of
those what's with the
jewels uh first you unlock it and then
you put a jewel
in I could also P this way from here
like that I think that's better going
from down than going from
up cuz on the way there's a lot of
attributes
yeah in that
case maybe I'll I will take this one
back for now and put it down here
instead
um but that those are only two extra
intelligent well in total 10 I guess but
should I get even
more good night thank you
Sky I might have enough for my
skills now
oh uh yeah seems like I can at least do
something flame wall
upgrade
no not flame ball
why I've been using that
no get bone cage stop the B well I
already have that actually but I just
haven't been using it much
recently your
spirit okay
it doesn't make a difference if
I that's a
four do I have a five
no safe travels let's
go I know that's thck I'm I'm yeah I can
skip levels I know that but I was
thinking aren't those more expensive in
terms of in I don't really know exactly
how it looks but
don't I need even more int to do
that oh no never mind we're fine
still okay the
arsonist
really I hope that's what you want
guys and then I could try fighting them
with the bone cage
I can try um but also the pain offering
I'll
[Music]
upgrade oh here and yeah bone
Cage have another one yes I have so many
I saved them up on Earth perhaps
two on Earth is a
physical I know what it is
thanks also well I don't have much
Spirit left
H would be cool if I could add another
arsonist or sniper or something
well I
can't some
warriors uh ah here
few archers get a bonus fire damage from
passing for firewall
oh oh you know what we can
um take one more away from arsonist and
add it to
sniper sure why not do you think this
will make a big
difference H H oh what do
it oh it's a shield I thought it was a
helmet oh I didn't identify do not
wonder how can
I
hello wait what was that zoned out okay
thought it was
scepter need just knees I will tell your
tale okay big difference
no uh wait where's my to did I sneeze my
toad
away huh
what's my wasn't my wasn't my toad down
there oh if the if the bug gets me again
I'm going to
CET they're real
bullies big
time man
I already feel a bit
stronger come on come on bring it
on no bugs
yet oh [\h__\h] poison
though and lots of Mana
usage oh bugs normal bugs normal bugs
are okay I can handle normal
bugs I was going to go the other way but
now I feel tempted to go this way
go WWA wa go to
AWA a
w oh she's she's really suffering from
lack of Mana now what did I do am I I I
I guess I'm spamming the firewall
more this one could be nice if I
identify it come on take
so far so good but it might just be the
lack of
BU go level up let's
go big big big big big
big I'm just going to go straight ahead
put that into intelligence as well I've
started to realize those
attributes can be very important must be
prioritized over the other fancy stuff
sometimes this
I think I just saw an action the the
snipers wait where those oh wait if the
enemy
snipers uh shoot through my firewall
they're they don't turn into fire arrows
right they don't okay
H anyway I should put that skill point
somewhere uh we were doing stuff
here putting on heal bars on
friend no but the fact that I have the
the health bars on the enemies should
already make it easier for me to tell
them
apart it generally does
oh 47 months of other race when when can
I get
one thank you for watching them did you
watch them as
BS hello my dear Gods Watcher W on the
man
wa wherever you wanted when you wanted
wa on the
man the hitbox for this kind of annoys
me for the Reviving
unearthing it feels like the edge the
end of the une Earth has to hit them
even if I go directly over the dead
body often it will not revive
them when you need cute and comfy too
one oh wait there's something up there
stairs is this
perhaps where I shall go actually wait a
second what was that the check ah almost
didn't get it need to touch the wall
need to hug the wall well if your Archer
and your AR have a special skill you can
AC you canb the button like extra
power oh look this is just a
little wait I can't even open these not
even treasure that I can
have huh maybe for later
put sniper poison in your skill bar it's
in combo with
firewall
sniper sniper poison
what what
Oh I thought I have to pull it from here
to
there I don't see sniper
poison but I found explosive
demise gas
Arrow oh
okay h I don't know if I'll be able to
multitask so many things for my minions
though oh oh no blue
bug shoot shoot shoot shoot
stuff oh it was just that one bug okay I
thought that was a bigger
fight an
amulet oh pretty plus six to all
attributes plus energy shield and
strength yo wait we have uh this one
right now I would say plus six to all
attributes is good better
you can Regal it too
oh yeah uh when I have the stone then
okay is that
it that's
it yeah no more in
starving yippe
I'm pressing the buttons but I can't
tell if they're actually doing it I
think they
are do do they shoot it at what my mouse
is currently
on the cursor okay gotta get good at
aiming 100 gold give me
that a yeah okay now I saw
it oh yeah yeah okay okay Ah that's so
much to do they should just do it on
their own whenever they
want they should have a will of their
own they want
we have a number
seven
oh do we like any of these detonate dead
causes a corpse to Violent violently
explode damaging surrounding enemies
so the ones that are already dead like
really dead on the ground or my
skeletons
those are corpses too
no violently
explode I had upgrade your
minions upgrade your minions skeleton
archer to seven oh okay or the
arist oh wait my sniper is only on level
four
[Music]
well the sniper definitely needs an
upgrade does he need an upgrade to level
seven is another question but the cost
goes
down if I level them up their cost goes
down oh yeah it
does from 41 to
35 I
[Music]
see whatever we'll get more we can we
can do everything
okay those skills are kind of
fun wait a second that's what I need
right
no okay the the golden one the one with
one golden
face Freo
okay nice
that's crazy I was like smashing mashing
those
buttons it's a lot going on I think not
I think not I don't want
to yes you will
the combo is passing wind first and then
fire n that's not going to work for
me left Mouse could be G ah left mous
could be left Mouse could be gas Arrow
then you have the whole combo on
Mouse
[Music]
oh wa what what what did you gas and
fire nice AE d
te feels kind of far
away but we are kind of moving away from
unearthing huh
so damn let me at least put it on r
e r
r
r okay gas and then fire there what is
it going to blow
up
what I
will wait they not I guess it takes a
while to
recharge H wait they already died
oh it feels like it's
exploding if it has a cool down and I
can't spam it
[Music]
uh
uh okay okay then I'll just go back to
spamming uh the
firewall until the cool down is over
always yeah I still have something to
spam
whoa how long like 5
Seconds
stinky stinky explosion
I feels weird to get to you to get used
to new
button
[Music]
combinations it doesn't feel as smooth
now the Venom
pit
[Music]
oh I've got my own kind of Venom cabala
oh cabala is
here a fellow Corp oh [\h__\h]
oy
me oh what the
[\h__\h] when I'm not quite used to my new
way of attacking yet
where's
my
there oh she's dead okay she was like a
smaller
boss he revives them as little
snakes
[Music]
cute wow GR two weapon set passive skill
points
what what
what n so
generous thank
[Music]
you should I still go into
I still go into
intelligence
okay we've reached the
node
yippee I think
not okay I'll
teleport I'll be
back thumbs
up plenty of De is the amulet now true
that's a cool amulet huh
quickly I love my new amulet it's pretty
to
design so
cell uh cell cell cell
cell reduce poison duration on meat I've
never seen that one before but
cell oh Golem
Crown accuracy rating ah it yeah as long
as it doesn't have the minion thing it
can
go increased amount recovered 44%
increased charges gain 31% uh this is uh
life no I want to keep the life on the
minions I think
okay I want to check one of
those this this away this away this
away here we go drum roll
please uh evasion
rating I think
not sure that's all right
rip could be
better wait can I put in a new one
yet
yeah
arist bone storm even though I haven't
been using it much right now but I use
it in in boss
fights and before I changed all my
buttons I was using it also in normal
fights I can still use it but I'm I'm my
focus is somewhere else right
now
what oh yeah one is a spirit gem one is
a skill gem
[Music]
uh I don't really want to deal with a
new skill until I get used to my current
skill set so I'll continue working on
what I have I think pain offing is
always nice will impale one of your SK
so we improve
that and what about these uh raging
Spirits it'll now be
oops it'll be what will be better it
will
be I don't know it will just be
better
good do I have anything else we still
have a few level
one well that's it
some good upgrades
yeah scatter shot really good yeah I
have this like leftover scatter shot
right or don't I wait I don't no I guess
it's not it's still
somewhere it was already nerfed
twice damn I would have liked to use it
and it's
Prime my raging Spirits my firewall
already nerved twice okay where do we go
from here or am I done in this
region I'm currently in in Kev right
find the entrance to Kev buried
somewhere in the Sands no okay we're not
done is it up here or down
[Music]
I out the walls but like this looks like
it's just straight
connect with here too I don't think
anything's up there
anymore I was here
[Music]
before wait I want to check over
here please tell me it
continues
yes yes
okay oh oh
oh the one last remaining piece of the
puzzle of the map the lost
city yes I am reading chat so much I
sometimes still mostly Inta overwhelmed
with
sand
pretty I think she doesn't like
sand oh oh oh I forgot I don't I have
some something else on my left click now
I
for
uhoh oh there's more coming
oh there's a big bug but this one's
pretty and it's so slow it's like a
turtle
bug
will I'm still trying to figure out
things oh God oh God oh God oh God like
trying to remember where where my skills
are now God so used to
it okay okay clear we've cleared
it the map looks so pretty
already and of course the real situation
also all the like designers of this game
are just
cracked that's pretty oh that's such a
pretty
detail them fighting for their life here
and I'm like oh they so
pretty where is my
CST Crown in
Gold I sound I still sound quiet
compared to the game sound really
like when I look away from the
microphone it's not as uh
properly
um not equalized was
equalized as I feel like it should be
how long why is it recharging so slow
yeah also just quiet cuz I'm out of
tangents quiet in terms of I'm just not
talking
much W focus on
[Music]
game wa today not not [\h__\h] posting about
hats but I saw some of you guys on
Twitter
have um taking the Hat tangent very
seriously some KF have been comparing
their hats let's just say it that way
because that's exactly what
happened comparing the size and the
length of their collection of hats of
their hat
Stacks you love to see it are you guys
going to wake up yeah I thought so but
only only after I completely walked
through all of
them
oh that's not even all the hats I have
jeez
oh good Flex good
Flex a man of many hats
yeah I will un you many hats and many
secrets I'll go down
here actually let me put my point
somewhere into increased attack and cast
speed oh that sounds
lovely e e
beautiful
Bridge
ow she also likes to play with fire but
you shouldn't when it's so stinky around
here I wouldn't recommend it oh
Treasures
Treasures excited for Game Awards I mean
yeah I won't be able to watch all of it
I could I could stay up really late
maybe I
will maybe I
will depends on how much they bore me
with their
ads I feel like there's going to be many
ads wasn't there like a good amount of
ads last
time maybe let's see where when the
category
is for pic
do you think they will be early on is
there already like can you already
know open chat like past
a oh then I yeah have to make my stream
reservation
early but the I guess that stream
reservation I did want to meet
relatively early anyway
my basically a giant ad
yeah especially for um
Kima giant
as that's what that
is and
award and the best ad for award goes to
what
and the best award for best ad what the
the award for best ad go or the ad for
best award that one that's fine too
makes perfect
sense
[Music]
W your
what do you
[Music]
want
whoops the best ad for ad go
to congratulations you won and
AD
honestly not bad
ads are for the advertiser that would be
a good
win have you noticed I really haven't
had troubles with bugs anymore so that
was that was a good change that we did
overall
they patch for me life
[Music]
patch don't let these bugs stop you
never fur Fury Fury Fury rattles excuse
me for saying your name wrong you don't
want I'm sure you don't want to be um
whoa
I'm sure you don't want to be called
that that's not
fun wow then's not doing any damage on
me bro you need to Respec
maybe you should consider
respecing
beautiful chain tiara
oops maybe go to the no face guy he
could help you I'm
sure did I pick it
up for my amulet didn't I already do it
on my amulet who whoa whoa
whoa I already did it and I didn't get
anything particularly good
though but I yeah what I picked it up
right
yeah
see but I want to pick this up too so I
can salvage
it Heisenberg said
no what have you what have you done care
for a Story Jesse Jesse what have you
done speak
up W this one looks
cool such a nice Warrior coach reduced
ignite duration on you oh I see this
more these kind of Buffs more often
now chaos
B we moved on from
chaos movement speed movement speed
movement speed gold increased Rarity of
items
found
oh
oh that's
go
s
absolutely sadly no minion
skills but other than that holy [\h__\h]
that's a lot of a lot of
stuff yeah yeah yeah more more golden
loot
hopefully oh this one also has increased
Rarity of items if I wear that with
those shoes
ooh Salvage gold for reg sh
yeah
hello a wait Salvage Salvage oopsie
oh
no not work Salvage you mean disenchant
okay that would have been the first I
will tell your tale I was one guy
okay you you one guide me you out of all
people I didn't expect it from
you look at them kissing
look at them is this a frog looks like
frog frog
and what is this cat
no than
keep I'm sorry it's okay you've been so
helpful other than
that uh
should use
can find the alar of the relics in the
map of the titans of oh oh those are the
two that oh where I needed the second
one
oh the one where I was waiting for okay
let's do it after after I'm done with
the current area remind me remind me
remind me where I have to go cuz I will
forget exactly what you said just now
there's no way that I will remember what
you
said whoa who whoa you guys look so cool
okay but you died so fast what the
[Music]
hell what's up here probably just a dead
end
mhm what's going on
here spicy Sparks are
flying already dead they're already dead
not is that worth
it wait there's
more thanks for the free
exp and yeah I think I think I got
in into whole life I
checked I think
I think I did
it how did you get into all life and I
auditioned
D who who whoa who who who
when will you deut yeah I'm an indie
right
now I actually shouldn't be telling you
about this I'm under an indie
aim look at those F hiding there oh I
feel
bad I just wanted to be bugging around
in peace and I'm disturbing their peace
man this minion Spirit
life is pretty smooth
going no don't terminate
me oh buried shrines here we
are let's go what's what's down here oh
yeah I saw this new Indiana Jones game I
watched a little bit long forgotten
Shrine of your my YouTube Ori playing
it but first of all I don't know if we
would have if we would have perms of it
but right now the little snippet of it
that I saw didn't really speak to talk
move oh not too late my stink BMP was
still in
action but apparently it's really
good
right but somehow it looks more sci-fi
than I thought it was at least from the
snippet that I
saw and I don't really like I thought it
would be more like the
movie that I saw that means I know
there's many
movies i h i don't
know just just a short impression that I
had maybe that's not it at all what did
you
see I don't know I don't remember
anymore I erased it from my memory
immediately my memory card is too full
I don't know where to go it's such a
maze might be fine to play um might
still need to check with
perms like they might give it very
easily but it might just not registered
yet because maybe nobody requested it
did nobody play it yet
then none yet hope they give you guys
Prim such a good game really yeah I mean
even the overly critical don't
tend really liked
it even though in the part that I
watched he was like dying a lot there
was some it looked really difficult in
the part that I
watched like he was some
where kind of stealing around
and they killed him so easily so
often just look really annoying if I
would if I was struggling with with that
I would
rage skill
isue what do you
know what do I know
maybe the stealth section is also a
wrong
impression fast simulator I just came
out with the Clementine family I don't
know anything of any fast food simulator
is that a multiplayer
thing it's easy to shake up enemies if
you
[Music]
get I don't know right now I'm quite
happy and I'm also quite busy with po
po and
diabo and stuff other streams like
cooking stream
that kind of got my hands full with
games right
now dance hey your niece wants to
dance uh hold pry dance in the like a
like a showcase or
so for school or like a little
group that would be so cute how old is
she
I hope she can convince them now I'd
love to see the recording of it she's
nine years old turning
T and she's in what like is the Dance
Academy like like a side thing in her
school or the school that she goes to
mainly a dance
SCH
imagine would be so
cute I see the checkpoint but I don't
want to go
there variety variet sure I know I also
would like veriy but we also need to
play Eden Eternal again we're not done
with it really but like we had to take
that little
break because I think shiy was gone and
I think she's still kind of like I think
over the rest of December we probably
won't get together but I was also
thinking of maybe playing it in members
a little bit maybe for one stream at
least but then the other girls will have
to do that too to catch
up but in any case we're not really
done mind
room she has to join it separate from
SCH because you what that is so cute
your 9-year-old niece join Dance
Academy because of me and cie
does she say she wants to be a YouTuber
when she grows up does she say
that did she say
that I need to know the answer Nicholas
Anthony tell me
she's squealing over is she watching
right now what's her name if you don't
have to tell me
but hello Isabella that's such a pretty
name I had a friend called Isabella a
long time ago I used to call her like
Isa or
E which maybe is weird in English in
German it worked German always
works he
oh I hope I hope my when she's listening
my swearing doesn't rub off on her
Isabella you shouldn't swear too much
okay don't become like me English is not
my first language so you can excuse my
swearing but it's not good for
you E I wish you best luck with your
Dance Academy that sounds so
fun you're starting so early so you're
going to be a big star
I know it oh all of these are going to
come to life all of them all of them all
of
them what's Happening Here
yum scary wa I want to talk more with
Isabella can we
collab
alive focus focus focus oh yo yo what
the what wait wait wait wait wait wait
how do I not die how do I not die
okay okay oh we're good we're good we're
good we're good I got it under control
somewhat look at all these
bodies okay big enemy
spam I expected it
any
more a bit
more only a
bit did I miss anything scroll scroll
scroll don't see
anything don't
die
oh hi K uncle's letting Ty I'm the
tallest in my girl I'm trying to get
hold to dance for my group Rec and make
for
treat you can do
it hey how big is your dance group how
many girls are
you are you like the exact
number of
five maybe one day you can also learn
like you know my original song dance
like Mirage me me me me me Mir you me me
me me me me
you good
luck you'll do so
good I'll cheer for you I'll be cheering
you on you have a nice
Uncle around eight my
ah around eight okay so you'll have to
arrange it a little bit so that it
matches for that amount of people
interesting you learn my dance too
[Music]
yippe can't
wait so
cute so do you want to be a YouTuber one
day like
me where do I
go down here maybe I'm not done right
find the essence of water somewhere in
the C okay
but a bajillion all up what does that
mean wait what does that
mean trying to
decipher place I need to go is Northwest
nine more years of Sheen audition wait
was there a minimum age I
forgot yeah makes sense but you know she
could be in Indie
Northwest Northwest
like what about here though I still
didn't check out this very bottom I'll
go there before it's too late before I
go too far
away I don't think I got a clear answer
guys I will not be able to sleep until I
get
one I need to know Koba just turned
eight sure she did sure she well at
least she does behave like that
sometimes okay there was nothing down
there I guess I'll go back back
up guys if I missed the answer then spam
it for me
please I'm like looking at everything
right I'm looking at the map I'm looking
at where I'm going I'm looking at the
chat I got my eyes
everywhere okay yeah there is there's a
path here that I for
that looks
comfy
ah oh I can't
see but already dead the golden ones
we're really really really really
powerful right now that those few
changes really made huge difference also
I'm like barely using my unearthing
anymore maybe eventually we we're going
to stop with our spiky spiky attacks and
just focus on the minions and the
fire like the Raging Spirits are
plenty now I'm mixing in
the attack
ohel I love your part in nonfiction h
[Music]
thank
you the
[Music]
dance see for Isabella for Isabella I
really need to push harder for them to
finally get us to release a new horor T
song I've been pushing for like a
year it's always like yeah yeah you're
right you're right we want that we want
that
too we're working on it we're working on
it have to continue to push
I'm pushing
hard or
Isabella or Isabella I'll tell I'll tell
the producer that's behind it about
Isabella the tale of Isabella a young
girl in the dance
group young 9-year-old girl trying to be
like to to okay I might making up some
things you know to exaggerate to make it
more dramatic to make it seem like her
career is just like it it hangs on
the life of honi if hori doesn't
continue it's it's just devastating for
her putting words in her
mouth the little Isabella she takes all
her
motivation from H dance every day every
day for the past year she's been dancing
H dance every
morning I don't know I I I'm not sure
how to twist this further
into an emotional story help me out
guys please Bing over her please
consider her feelings de bringing her
biting chill I long for it to producer
son for the Wonder I felt as a child to
grace my eyes once more but the last
winter that brought such beauty was 200
years ago now it cannot snow in a region
where it does not rain true true the
city is
quiet the city is
cold the wind whistles through stone
columns unheard by the living I ask
myself why I am still here I ask myself
why I will not let my tired bones
rest and I ask myself whether I truly
believe halani will awaken do you I do
do you I
do I was waiting for that I was waiting
for
[Laughter]
her oh offering of lightning oh what
should have waited a moment and thought
about that I didn't
realize that this was a choosing
situation but but but but but lightning
resistance in the
desert sounds
logical and intelligence 14
[Music]
I mean not better than the other ones oh
actually a no lightning damage what was
the others was it Fire and Ice or
so damn
it don't have yeah I don't have an
augmentation right now but I was also
thinking of augmenting it we might we
might need
the uh lightning resist more done one of
these like other
things oh you're in Australia you're
from Australia wait a second it's oh
it's early morning right
now oh but today no school so Uncle let
me watch your stream thank you so much
for inspiring me
K you're inspiring me
too cute I'm also from
Australia no I'm not close enough though
we're we're neighbors B
basically yeah o that looks fancy in
there Australian
kfp
youngling
wow I am
inspired I'm very
inspired where do we go more up
there oh what Shadow slicer still alive
what are you
doing ah yeah even though in those
trailer the time zones are
very ver buying
right you guys have quite the range to
okay I am going to go through my toad
portal wait re redo it here Isabella do
you like my toad do you think this is
cute I think it's like pretty
cute at least it's
pink it's one of the cutest things in
the game I would say I
mean what do you think what does a
9-year-old think about this I want to
hear your opinion
now just kill this froggy wow true true
true true but I didn't ask
you are you 9year old Isabella
no I'll go through it's a very useful
toad but maybe you've seen better toads
in Australia
what have could
be I'm awaiting your judgment anytime
now young
one I will tell your ta I will your
T hello
[Music]
reduced attribute requirements oh I
didn't know that was a thing either oh a
nice
[Music]
staff not for me not for
me accuracy
rating so we're going to do the
thing she didn't say anything
about of course
for such young people it is very
important to always
clarify that you're soon getting
older that's very
important I think I used to also feel
like that um I maybe 1 but I'm 14
soon cute
cute cute cute cute cute Regal orb let's
go um is that the right
one maybe it wasn't but it gave me
dexterity and intelligence which
is oh [\h__\h] ah I
swore I need to augment first can I
still augment
no so wait did I just lose an
extra like thingy oh I still
okay I think I'll switch with the
reliable Iron Ring of talent at Le for
now while we're in this
region too expensive to
salvage level eight skill gem I think
that's a
[Music]
first
whoa incinerate
no that's like that's like in Diablo
4 that's the same thing no is it not
tell me it's
not I've been having a lot of fun with
it in
Diablo flammability is a
must Flim Flam
should I just should I just
uh
oh that attack is underwhelming in to
Okay click the video oh yeah right I
forgot that was a thing hold down the
button for incinerate launch a jet of
flame and your
enemies but I don't think I can walk
with it in Diablo
yeah I wouldn't mind putting it into
flame wall but last time I leveled up
flame wall somebody was like no I'm like
what
why curses all Targets in an area after
a short delay lowering their fire
resistance okay this is passive right I
don't have to activate it or or do I oh
no ability is I know I makes your
enemies more vulnerable to
[Music]
damage I don't want anything else I
don't want to push anything
else flame wall starts costing too much
M oh oh you want to keep flame
oh okay
okay
uh then if you say so I shall improve
the
the bomb guy for
now okay I do want to get rid of those
things in my inventory soon
are we going to see the boss soon this
place is so big we've been here long
enough I
think looks like the map is giving me
hints that it's ending soon I feel
like this looks
like it could be the
end oh halani
Shrine I didn't find the essence of
water
yet oh left a child to die meeting place
of the Seven Rivers huh he
holds I didn't let I didn't leave a
child to die what are you talking about
oh you're talking to the water
gooddess you never
come where are you
near
F okay here we go we got to fight now
ra corruption
whoa now now Aron is go what did he just
bug was he just standing
around holy his HP is like way less than
the previous fight we had and I'm not
even trying that hard right now of
mother
ow right
sniper Dole I want to
shoot oh wait I probably shouldn't walk
over that fire area looks too spicy
hard to get out of
that and that's it already really
really that was the easiest boss I
fought so far is there a catch are we
fighting the water goddess now or
something I didn't even try that
hard oh no is that a goddess baa she is
breathing still that is impressive when
you're cut open like that don't look
Isabella don't look this is
not this game probably is not for your
age
group Uncle you got to do something at
last m
please end my suffering shouldn't you be
blue I think you should be blue my
followers are long since dust and I am
but
parchment my veins dry as sand what
happened here none remember my name and
none think of
me I awoke from my long Slumber unable
to
move my time has passed
I ask you mortal to use that one element
that may fin she know that's my
specialty
opposite fire but my other specialty is
Raising people from the dead so I could
kill you which ends your suffering and
then revive
you which you'll be
fine he was not my son not the one I
knew corruption held his mortal soul in
thr and you have finally given him peace
the big the big
guy some essence of water Remains the
last drops to be found inside of you or
what okay good
boy ignite the oh even I thought I would
just firewall her but no oh no what
we're going to ignite the
goddess oh
man
halani I pay my respects to you I'm
sorry but like a phoenix I'm sure
especially as a goddess we shall
revive in the most magnificent form
better than
ever a
oh goddess skeleton
hot
spicy by your request come on come
on
no
revive it doesn't
work this is what I
needed it doesn't
work that was the easiest boss
weirdly a lot stronger than the one
before even though the one before once I
did the whole firewall spam it also went
very
smoothly is am I suddenly overpowered or
is there some kind of curve that goes
downwards the bugs the bugs were out for
me they they just really wanted see me
suffer time is
short there was a goddess of water lying
at the heart of
K I wonder role in the past in
cold it is my sacred duty to keep our
Tales but I know nothing of this goddess
damn should have asked her questions
before we killed her Mar have forgotten
something so important mhm impressive
young one
now we have everything we need to
recreate the Horn of the vaser game gets
easier as you build better take a bit of
carving okay guess we have done the
right thing I think the flame Ruby goes
here imbu the essence of water with the
if my fingers were more Nimble I could
have done better this won't blow aale
across the entire veery but it will
serve our purpose nice that's all I need
here take it you retraced Ora's Journey
so you should be the one to Sound the
Horn guys maybe this whole
time Isabella didn't answer my main
question if she wants to become a vtuber
because she's already under an
NDA maybe she's already under an
NDA that's huge come on that takes up so
much space blow beautiful though
Yago is preparing her right
[Music]
now oh why am I disenchanting oh well
bone
blast ring of the Thirsty chaos
resistance should I keep
this or just sell maybe just
sell stay in sight and now let travel to
the sandstorm and ah the sand sand storm
ride we go back to the
sandstorm okay okay okay okay it all
makes sense
now
Shard okay do we face a big enemy
immediately I
wonder I hope so I want to be challenged
here wait where
here yes looks like it oh asala what's
up it is time to use the reforged Horn
of the V to open the way through mhm
prepare yourself war is n maybe I should
use my skill point before doing that s
move
swiftly either increased attack and cast
speed or increased attack and cast
speed I'd prefer to have like one of
these
here okay tough
choice this is a risky one the illusion
of
choice
okay I'm I'm I would think this one will
be more difficult than what I just would
hey will you let me
out wait a second
huh why won't you
yes okay let's
go how did I know how did I know I
spoiled
it nowhere to hide now sweet Undead
King I am hesitant to allow you access
to Sacred dish I thought you were better
a single Jing than an army of spiteful
enemies our city of the Dead must be
protected no matter no Tex you about to
turn op a really I'm glad cuz there's so
many
choices but if only we turned op
before wait we travel to
thisa is that
the to dis
off wait wait
where's what where's dis
sh we should do the Relic Quest first
okay now we do The Relic Quest
okay uh now now it's your turn to repeat
what you said
before where do I
go here right
here right
I wait that's Desa okay good to
know bottom left of the
map Valley of
Titans ah for like the relics
we'll find a use
here they remain where they
slept
well dying where you used to
sleep or where you're usually sleeping
seems rather peaceful
so I see nothing wrong with
that they seem more faster than
usual cuz the game doesn't tell you okay
thank God I'm glad to hear that most
people get lost with
that and need
help to find their
way I'm like obviously I'm extra dumb
I admit
it I need extra help to find my
way
places of
us Yi we can be extra dump together one
brain
cell together we will have several
thousands of brain cells that's
impressive you
know but the smart people okay here's
the thing the smart people are smart
enough to go on about their lives on
their
own and they think they're cool with
their normal amount of brain cells so
they don't think about the op thing of
collaborating your brain cells
and working
together and so they will never achieve
the greatness that we're
achieving if they combined all their
brain cells they could have millions
yeah but we're they don't want to do
that because they're like
cocky they're on the high
horse me alone
bug but we need each other so we combine
each other and then we are stronger than
them you know what I mean those people
who already have power they don't they
they want to like prove that they're
powerful on their
own they don't want to admit that they
need help
what are you talking
about well you would understand if you
tuned in earlier that's your fault no
I'm I'm not talking nonsense I'm making
perfect
sense
SK I'm giving you guys the re top for
Success you guys think I should go up
with a checkpoint
was avoiding
checkpoint I don't see I don't know I
don't want to know
out what I ran into the tornado not a
good
idea
yeah did I go there but here we can
still like level a little bit we might
need the the
level N I do feel like the mobs here are
strong
once again even though we've kind of
faced these TS
before
okay okay I'll go
back retreat
why is the tornado still there I thought
that was like something the enemy
was uh
creating oh
ah all it's the Bol
guy wait I did all of this before
I already I have to reactivate
them oh yeah I maybe I can
go
wait no
wrong
know no but it's
similar we need to find a specific totem
oh
okay it's not the same place huh
no it's my first time here I I think so
no way
point oh is it right in this game they
uh delet the maps for you right when you
you haven't been here in a
while oh okay was my second
time but then that's why I thought I did
activate because if I was here before I
did activate all of those before the
bald guy I activated him before
I see a check
coint wait the stinky explosion thing
doesn't work so well
here does
it oh my God
[Music]
damam okay we get it we get it you can
spam monsters we get it
so there was a checkpoint here is this
the right
[Music]
one I feel like probably
not or maybe it
is nothing
spawned should be next to a way point oh
okay I'm just going to
run a little
bit they do
eventually stop chasing
me so
run a way
points all
right thank you thank you for chasing me
I
appreciate your appreciation of me oh
this is a yellow one agon
to dental pain poor boy
another to
serve I've been taking my vitamin D
properly by the way for like a while
now so I'm doing quite well I think it's
working I think it's
helping but I switched to one that also
has the the k something
think big recommend you guys should take
it to in the winter but I see a bunch of
you
do
lightning wait should I Salvage
that oh pretty
stay
inside okay oh wait what am I talking to
you for as we approach desar I feel I
must ask something of you once more M
there is someone I care about let us
leave it at that is it me I have learned
she went on Journey to the SP three
moons pass and she has not returned did
she go to slay the SP this for there was
neither sickness nor injury
involved understand I simply wish to
know the truth of what happened to end
the pain of not
knowing it's been a while since I went
on a lone Journey to the
spires if you happen to find lum's body
in the blessing we'll see if I find
her it would have to be a
coincidence
okay
activate insert The Relic
oh oh like this oh they don't face each
other a that's not
cute what now
oh oh
what I
shice oh I can switch around
here huh I think uh charm charges
maybe look at my
skeleton I think that sounds
good oh it's like a blessing and that's
why the Waypoint is here so you can
quickly come here and switch and then go
back again where you
were oh out was the button
I
can't Al alt doesn't seem to work
here M because drums are kind of useless
until later oh
really I had another message oh here
uncles are FK so I took their whole life
dragon jackets it's a bit big for me but
I like it PA have dragon are we talking
cute you are under full control now of
the
computer CH is the thing that goes in
your
belt a this ah
ah yeah okay both is kind of lame
okay if I go back now wait should I do
the trial now that wasn't the trial
right if I were to do the trial I
[Music]
go
here I don't
really how long is that going to take
nasty oh 10 to 15 minutes really trial 1
hour hey very
different
statements you will get a death after X
damage regardless of healing so avoid
damage at all
cost what insta death
what a death after X damage regardless
of healing avoid damage oh oh after how
much damage I
take so if I take a certain amount of
damage even if I heal back up I will die
interesting might take a bit long nowh
you now
okay ah a separate health bar mechanic
[Music]
um
where
here do I start here what 18
27 the levels are
weird oh on the desert map okay
did I get something new
what
no stay
inside well do want again this is for
the trial is
it okay
here let's hope it won't take too long
cuz I think I'll end it after that after
the
trial as I said I I'm not really I
should not stream too
long I have work to
do skip super chat today maybe
yeah yeah we're totally fine like I I I
can still easily let's see what power is
offered here catch up to
wait there's a book there or like a
monument The Proven grounds for The
Sisterhood is complete though it broke
many bones and some backs the Triumph is
ours to behold zerok has been the most
helpful Aid he came to us Atari but now
he is well it probably only broke many
bones and backs of the slaves right
that's why it doesn't matter to you
I
suppose like altar stash
oh
interesting oh oh one's
gone Relic Locker decoration now
available in your hideout I will
serve oh Bala hello Jin we have met in
battle but not in peace
I am balbala ony traitor long a sorrowed
prisoner Asin here I shall serve as the
lording anime is now in Austrian Cinemas
for at least a week we shall prove
ourselves what was it roim
one honor honor
resistance place it at the
start place this item on The Relic Al at
the start of the trials go with the
winds
here
okay augmented
first yeah Wicked too I want to watch
Wicked and and I guess I'll watch the
war of the
roim
roim you guys probably just say it like
roim lame you need German
pronunciation
augmentation increased honor
restored can I do it now
Ruby charm what I should put it in
there
charm where I have a ruby
charm I'm
good no
you test of
strength okay so uh Dodge as much as
possible
right I'm
scared we might
die but it will be worth the
price is the checkpoint here when I
die stay really far back let me work
okay I have to admit I'm somewhat
enjoying all this is this the honor the
this hello hello sand hourglass survive
waves of Monsters ah we have some
monsters okay until the timer expires
killing rare monsters reduces the
timer
huh y it
he'll surely get a lot more difficult
continue Press Room on oh oh it's Oh I
thought it would be all in this
room okay how many rooms are there
ah trial up interactive select the trial
bronze
key Awards a sacred water fountain
afflictor of leaking water skin wait a
second are we doing all of
this Awards Bron ah this is what I just
did
word silver keyboard afflicts you with
leaking water skin on
Entry so you just one path Until the
End middle or bottom is good
really it's like latest fire
TR Warrior sucks but this shouldn't be
too bad for you we'll see ah uncles are
back thank you for speaking and
interacting with you made her day and
weekend going to get second ah I'm glad
I also had fun talking to
Isabella I hope I can hear from her
again have a nice
breakie
mate thanks mate
[Music]
um I don't know I really don't
know what's leaking water Lo 20 SEC
water the resource you find within the
trial
um I have Sacred Water right
now we'll go down like
go
no we the
stairs like a
currency is this a
trial wait what's that part over there
is
it a
shortcut don't hit
uh
okay is this a
trial I ask
again there's no timer here though
right this whole thing is a tri
defeat the ritual castes close to the
portals
easy okay uh
there
go not too
difficult oh my poor skeletons
ah they can deal with it they're fine
ritual has been
disrupted I heard lesbian in that
sentence the lesbian has been
interrupted did you hear it too
same I got sacred water for a
sip and I finished that one okay now I
saw someone say don't do Gauntlet trial
and then somebody somebody also said go
back up then uh afflict you with winter
draw on Entry lose all sacred water on
floor completion
whatever probably is fine
right middle one
okay sand Hour Glass oh it's a timer
again
survive until timer
expires let them hit
you don't let
you oh oh oh oh
[Music]
easy trial
complete
magnificent you know it girl you know it
I slay and you
pray for forgiveness
isy go
next I
take sippy sippy sippy why ises it break
when I sippy did I drink too
aggressively I can either get a silver
key or a bronze key or a silver key I
don't know which one I
want fish you're still here really
you're a lot thank you
I think my gaml almost was better last
time but my build is better
today plan two rooms
ahead ah after that I could only go back
up Awards a pledge which can be accepted
to change the trials
parameters
okay I want to do this brain empty
mode chalice kill some Elites where does
it say that
try to avoid gauntlets ah okay I see I
see I see well then I'll go up and then
hourglass trial avoid the shrine to
restore honor afflicts you with spiked
exit on
Entry ah take 19 physical damage that's
not too
much bottom one but then I have to take
the gauntlet trial
honor damage it hurts your honor but
it's fine I have no honor
left wait what's so bad about a gauntlet
trial
thoughtless traps can be
[Music]
hard I don't know what to
do try
[Music]
it
conflicting opinions
the feel R mon in the area to fill the
Chalice
uh oh oh you're showing me the
way
done drop the little ring even
wonder if I should just go back to the
middle or going around here on the
outside is
fine looks fine not too much
trouble oh here's
the granite collector
explosion
please okay a great challenge over hiala
what's
up you're watching me but not
helping I don't need your
help that damage was friend insane my
damage oh look it's overflowing woo
yeah this is first try still you think
I'll fail I got the
key now I guess we go gaunet trial I
better not regret
this it's on you if I regret traps you
say like out of nowhere or can I well
that's just that's just enemies oh ah he
hit
me ah they hit me
die oh oh there's a there's a yellow
one no I don't want to get
damage okay traps uh not but if it's
just traps like that that it's not too
bad
I'll always be extra
careful yeah
[Music]
fire fire don't run in there Budd
no so I run
in and then I go to the
right oh
God
okay will you
okay left or
right I guess I'll go left for now I got
Sacred Water from
them oh I turn back around but there's a
lever oh no oh no not not good why did I
turn it
what hope did it also like maybe help
somewhere else because that didn't seem
very
helped okay oh my minions are always
already going over to fight I I'll I'll
be there in a
minute
uh oh God oh God wait wait wait what
I'll go from here
I'm taking my
time oh oh was here I
was it should open a door you need to go
through
okay following the fire
again no
problemo oh
wait no my skeletons are on fire as long
as I'm not on fire oh but they're taking
damage come with me come with me oh oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh and another
lever here we go here we go here we go
follow go with the
flow take the money wait for a moment
and go go go go go go go he what didn't
I come from here oh maybe the lever
opened something again wait why did I
Circle back to here does that make sense
oh yeah maybe up here now where am I
here okay okay okay okay I'm on the run
I'm on the run I'm on the run oh ah this
door yeah that wasn't open
before Oh trial complete I that wasn't
so bad does it get worse later because
you guys were like trial Gauntlet no no
no no Gauntlet trial
no choose to take a pledge in the
[Music]
cour
ah ooh
I get something good but I also gets
like something bad really it gets much
worse later okay maybe it's good then
that we took one of the early
[Music]
ones trade offer K polite these don't
look so good skip it oh I can skip them
too
why yeah I mean before I take something
that's bad for me we got another
Gauntlet trial or we got a chalice trial
awards are pledge which can be accepted
to change the trial's power meters
inflicted with hungry fangs on Entry mon
us remove 5% of your life man and energy
shield on
hit
chalice okay is it just another like
survive forever
thing all rare monsters okay
doable wait I think it's down
right M mhm no hit
baby is there only two again I feel like
I saw
fre three of those weird Flames go by oh
I'm back already let's let's
see please give me a sign
chalice okay okay okay I did the lower
one Warriors have to be overl I hear a
lot about like struggling
Warriors feel bad for
you you guys need a need a buff
easy easy easy
easy I'm actually
full
a this could still fit yeah gy gy can I
teleport out and sell or I guess I guess
that was a stash
so I'll just use the
stash
ow we're close to the end of
it what do you say about these pledges
chat gain a random minor Boon glowing
orb hungry
fangs
but versus these don't take
trial fails if you teleport out oh from
The Trial map you can leave the trial
return
oh gidy gidy means like almost didn't
make it or
so or barely it means
barely wait wasn't there a stash was a
stash only in the
beginning uh I guess I'll pick up no
more items
damn okay we're almost at the end anyway
um ah two Gauntlet trials
[Music]
no oh and you guys said they become more
difficult
later I want to pledge or Awards a large
sacred Waterfront I don't understand
what that even
means
but should I go with the upper
one if I'm careful then it's shouldn't
be too
bad okay
water water it
is I'll just be careful although that
fire was kind of intense
previously what's going on here I feel
like this later I have to come back here
when these doors are open and then this
fire will be
turning
spikes oh
mhm fire wait skeleton don't do this to
me should we go right side left first
what is this what is this by the way
that's sus is it not a
trap apparently not okay a door closed
door here a closed door
there
okay then that wasn't the way
okay here we go here we oh wait here we
go here we go here we go here we go yby
yby
up uh maybe left
actually wait wait
wait okay sorry sorry
sorry sorry for the the peeking scream
freak me
out no don't close the
door oh well yeah this is the beginning
now now it has fire
mhm I feel like I didn't properly check
this area of
them where do I go where do I go where
do I go here
okay
okay now we can go from here again I
think that's a little cheat
yeah always got to weigh your options
Pro Gamer
moves of
course only the best skills at displ
here a couple of chests are the chests
also traps I've never had that before in
this
game but what if you're like going to
get attacked by like taking the greedy
uh Choice only one way to find out not
here okay oh Earth R thank
you huh well I don't have space for it
honestly so
whatever hello welcome I'm on a trial
right
now I'm doing pretty well so far far and
I'm almost at the end of it this is like
the the last point before the
end am I correct in going up here now oh
yes door open
now oh looks like the end of it no not
yet not yet not
yet is this it oh that was
it why you you crying guys like it is it
like a war
cry you need a hug your
mortality do you need a hug a work cry
will help I guess for this final battle
in this trial contains rattle cage Earth
Breer so it's just a normal boss right
nothing can go wrong
now except if I die so well yeah if I
die I fail and that sucks
I hope it's a
decent boss not not too difficult I'm
scared I'm
scared I should probably let my minions
do its thing mostly watch out for Slam
at the start okay
balala what's up you just going to
appear and say nothing and
disappear great thanks for the
motivational speech was she supposed to
say something
oh slam slam slam
slam that that was a slap oh that oh
that was a
slap he wants me so
bad go over here too huh
oh he wants me so
bad also maybe fire resistance would
have been good
here whats I want to hear Earth
recreating that
voice Splinter on B
oh he's
easy oh b b what are you doing here get
out of the
way got him poison of
what no problem
chica [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] the first time I take
damage do something skeleton
yeah I almost space space
scary I almost did it with no
damage
almost oh he been watching Mirage and
Kim on her iPad after second cute
[Music]
oh man he I need to I need to get like
some some convention appearance in
Australia now for real for
real kind of salty because I struggle so
hard what
aluda more like a
[Music]
loser do I want to bring these things
with
me maybe maybe the Mona flasks are
decent the seal Relic sounds
special uh
wait do you think I should keep the
stone and iron Rune the wisdom scroll I
can throw away I got a couple of these
actually they take up so much
space the rward is at the
end okay oh yeah do I have to put it in
my inventory
though Ro foren I'm sorry
oh oh that is that what the keys are
for but why why why does it look like
the gold one is available oh no I guess
silver it it looks grayed out but just
because it's
silver wait I I don't know I don't
know let me put some stuff in here for
now what a hle click the alter of a ah
right I heard you
guys be all crazy about that no no no
that one in particular I don't like
click the altar wait which
altar oh this
one power awaits me what that looks so
cool expected what am I in an infernal
sounds about right or blood Mage you
search for Power uh your search for
Power took you on a journey inwards oh
it's like got it's got extra
nodes you seek power at any cost and
there's no price to I to be infernal is
ah this is the only one that works for
Summoner oh
okay I'm a Summoner
right
cool looks like a blood
elf about the ears
though I don't know also the eyebrows
are not crazy enough I guess but
Ascent to
infernal
oh look at
me burn I'm more sister they tried to
burn me I think now I shall Pay It
Forward I think now I should pay it
forward wait I didn't realize my my legs
were so
spicy my my my uh tights oh cockroach
hello my tights look at those tights
since when did I have those on
fishnet but
like yeah spicy I think they're uh out
of like metal stuff though
cool wonderful is this my way out should
I wellit let's talk to balala it is done
you are no longer a jing you now carry
with you the spirit
of I am finally free but I find I do not
wish to rest just yet use my key but on
which
one now it may take another thousand how
can I use all I must rest does the same
key work for all them Glory should you
need me use that word bronze belt Mage
boots Warrior
H one keeper I thought so I have are the
keys in here
no oh I have one bronze one
silver ah mysterious gloves boots
Royal what's in Royal
one but can I do the the trial more
often and then end up uh opening all
these
chests rless Jewels um use Forge for
more
keys oh it gave me a bronze one oh
that's all I could do only
once m
well Warrior sounds like it might give
me a weapon that's not for my class Mage
feels like it might give me a one a
scepter but it might also give me a
staff
right boots I have really nice boots
right now so I don't care about the
boots belt though we haven't switched
our belt in a long time a new belt could
be nice look this one's required uh
level four
Mage belt and silver Ro yeah I thought
of the belt
too are they always just
white cuz this one I guess we also made
ourself wait I got so much [\h__\h] in
here I'll clean this out another
time o RG that was just unlucky
what well that's super lame super lame
super
lame what are these place this item on
The Relic altar at the start of trial
uh start off the trial
anyway oh it did also give me a scepter
but level seven
malice do I want any of
this you can use these on the next R
okay I thought so
okay and for silver
I don't I don't have a golden
key
Royal a ruby and a
sapphire well that sounds like it's at
least not a big
fail I already did
Ascension check your skill tree to get
ASC uh what's the button again for my
skill
tree whoa whoa it's in the middle now
what was here before
nothing so well I don't have a point
right now
wait
what I don't have a point though do I oh
I have two what I'll
passive I do didn't level
up you can get the doggy
dog dog where
dog
dog dog where do you see a dog H this
one loyal
hellhound
ah
[Music]
oh why not spicy flamy
cat oh is it not
here what
I
here oh he's always
there
oh look here I want to see your
face not a very Charming
dog but surely he'll be of good help and
support and this assist me in my
travels camera shy not not not the not
the prettiest dog uh but he has like
pretty big
um what's the
word
oh person that's not what I
meant Isabella back from breakfast after
I can chat to you freely uncle's
vacuuming unsupervised at his laptop oh
no the uncles are just letting
her do whatever she wants let's go
freedom
freedom well I'll leave this place
now that was great we did that uh I
won't do it again for
now once is fine right
once is plenty where is the Caravan can
I go back onto the Caravan through
here I'll just take my portal next one
is an act three okay I am so
hungry and I still got work to do
so we're going to call it a day here
unfortunately sorry
[Music]
Isabella it's time for me to go
Time to Say
Goodbye uh that was fun though I wish I
could play longer I should start these
streams
earlier is this considered ending early
not really it's almost midnight here so
it ended up being just the normal length
Stream 5 hours 44 minutes so much for
streaming a little a little bit less
today but my stream tomorrow is pretty
late at
[Music]
least and yeah tomorrow we be doing a
hand cam cooking stream where I will
also show off the viite products that I
have I still don't have all of them
unfortunately it didn't make it in
time um but Vite seems to want me to do
the cooking
stream early so I'll do it as according
to plan and I'm really nervous about it
but
it'll be fine it'll be
fine game words in one hour for p yeah
all of us
will pickle pickle pickle pickle pickle
pickle even if it was just a while thank
you for the
stream thank you too I hope you can
catch maybe some of the W
too if you want to thank you guys for
watching I hope you had fun thank you
for helping me a lot as always helping
me get the right build become super
powerful yeah nothing can stop me
now more Poe next week I
suppose
uh yeah I I want to finish
the wait so one question
uh once the like second part of the game
comes
out uh
like is is the whole thing with like
repeating all acts and then doing the
hard the the end game what you guys said
is that just for
now or is that still something I'll have
to go through at that point when the the
other
acts oh that'll be gone that's temporary
ah just so that people have some more
fun some more stuff to do ah okay okay
good to know good to know so then I I
don't think I will want to spend my time
doing
[Music]
that so people can level to end game end
game when there is no end game I don't
understand end game why would you do
I someone explained that to me there is
endgame there is
but is it this is it going to be the
same end game as when later when the
other
acts
appear yeah well then wouldn't it be
smarter to reach the end game
properly instead of grinding through the
same act experience the end game by
doing the the acts 1 2 3 4 5 6 properly
people would be mad if there was no end
game damn hard to please an audience of
[Music]
Gamers po vets oh those po
vets those po vets hard to please they
got some standards even though this is
only the second
game it's like they got the PO develop
developers on a
leash and they're whipping them you got
to do this and that I'm a vet now I
played the first
game make all my PO dreams come
[Music]
true and G
G they're like yes tantel uh yes po vs
I'll do what you want just just please
take off my handcuffs it's difficult to
do
things please let me go I'll do what you
want don't hurt my
family don't hurt my
[Music]
family stop toasting the beds what are
they going to do fire
me that doesn't make
sense doesn't make sense
okay in German we
say look forward to the Advent calendar
later in one hour byebye thanks for
watching
[Music]
oh
to oh
[Music]
maybe no Queen stream
tomorrow cuz I just got notification
that the remaining
merchandise could be shipped so that it
arrives by next
[Music]
week
yeah hard to hear me
can you hear
[Music]
me no I mean I could still do it but I
also would prefer to do
uh you know why is it so quiet here why
why is my mic so quiet
here yeah I think I also would prefer if
I could show off all the merch
[Music]
no and you know I'm I'm always very
nervous about cooking streams so I don't
mind pushing it away one more
[Music]
time push my obligations away from
me I could I could do a test run until
then like privately
[Music]
yeah then I'll I I think I'll do that I
I'll play something else tomorrow I will
decide when I wake up
though go put a placeholder frame yeah
cuz you guys want the reservation to
have a chat I see I get
it have a finished dish ready to show
nah what what would the cooking stream
be for Oh you mean like have it already
finished but then cook some more ah too
much
effort okay all right all right all
right goodbye no no I don't I won't take
the day off no no no no I'll stream
something but maybe something shorter
hopefully I I'd like a smaller game cuz
I I actually like the cooking stream
worked well with the fact that I had a
lot of work so it has to be a shorter
stream so that I I can get my work
done like this fire usually isn't that
[Music]
short typing up the Des well we can
discuss in the waiting room goodbye
goodbye goodbye goodbye
[Music]