n
[Music]
o
he a
[Music]
K uh wait starting
tweet yeah we reached
500k let's
go let's
go starting
now
Mario thank you thank you thank you I
guess I'll upload the
video tomorrow
maybe thank you so
much yay that means next Milestone is I
think the
O um Coca-Cola excuse me the the only
YouTube
short yeah let's go I'm on time yay me
too I ended up not taking a nap I was
trying to I was so close to falling
asleep uh and
then alarm
alarm but it's okay um I should be
okay
probably I'll be fine I'll be having fun
I'll wake
up yeah did you eat something yeah I had
a snack a little
sandwich made a little
sandwich so I'm fine no no no no now
we're going to play seven days to die
and
I wait a
second
I okay goals for today I think I'll work
on making that thing I think was it a
Bellow whatever that was for the
forge and just questing and skills
[Music]
stuff
um
yeah new
armor only if I have a significantly
different level I can make them in I
don't want to waste too many armor
kits but but that's one thing that would
be good to generally GA gathering many
many resources for armor kits
M
well will this show on
screen here we are now cled have a good
night and don't let the zombies
fight huh uh chat uh not chat um
[Music]
game game
come
on oh there you go punch obligatory
punching in the
air at least not against someone oh bi's
here I think FAA ended here too last
[Music]
night girls are still muted
oh there she
is
[Music]
um where where are
they the Discord images won't show
up
hello hello what's up good morning good
morning how you doing
I'm doing good I just woke up like IRL
you mean
yes good morning what a great time to be
awake yeah with my friends here in a
zombie
apocalypse getting need to
survive it's the best time to be
awake what's the plan today
Chief um Chief I'm the chief
uh no I think uh personally I just want
to gather a lot of basic materials for
armor kits um and then also increase my
Forge improve my Forge by making a
little Bellow for it and just making
some doing some
quests yeah yeah do you have the the
special quest for the Trader at the
bottom
yet uh no I don't have it
yet okay a well you you might get it
soon since we have been doing all the
same Quest together so you probably I
think maybe like once a couple of us
have that Quest we should all go down
there together yeah yeah for sure cuz
that's another that's another
inventory to unlock maybe some good
stuff oh okay yeah then well JMA just
closed
JMA so when she opens up we can get one
or two more tier two quests I would hope
that that does the
trick one or two
more wait oh yeah I guess does trador w
close at the same time too yeah they
should they should have different
opening and closing times business
baby I guess we can collect materials
while it's closed yeah just like raiding
random houses maybe oh there's a coyote
over there
coyote
coyote can we can we T the doggle no you
like bones you like bones or something
do you want a bone do you want I he'll
kill you
yeah where did that one come
from all right beautiful blood explosion
why did we lose so much HP for nothing I
have one HP now oh God
oh yeah can I get a party invite please
oh yeah shut the I hear more zombies
what's going
on it's just in my
brain oh oh he's up there oh oh he's
coming oh your father was one of
us I'll leave it to him I'll invite you
to the
party party thank you yeah seems like
today we be a pretty small group
again uh so I probably can do like
everything together in our small group
hi okay shall we go like towards some
houses maybe oh fa has a quest oh fauna
has a quest the tier do that yes yes oh
wa is tier threee okay no
[Music]
problem fa wake up
wake up wake
up it's morning
now her glasses are shaped like a like a
beetles beetles
eyes do you know what I mean like Beetle
glasses yeah so are yours I guess
so they look funky on
her oh oh press F press f for
what oh flashlight oh oh yeah I have
night vision goggles
I hope they will come in handy sometime
that's cool black and white though hello
hello good morning good morning
sunshine wait why do you know I was
asleep well you you just standing there
with you know we just assumed like you
were you know asleep standing up mhm I
thought you were listening to me I was
talking about how I was taking a nap
right before this so
we heard I just woke up
too did you yeah I
did but maybe it wasn't a nap for me
maybe it was just a sleep a whole a
whole beeping sleep
yeah oh oh what is this music well I
hope you had a good nap it was kind of a
non restful nap same I feel like naps
are never restful for me
that's that's not like I have to I have
to sleep a whole sleep a nap just makes
get your full R cycle yeah exactly yeah
understandable uh we were thinking of
first of all you have a quest over there
still and jenma is closed so we might as
well do your
quest um and I sounds good yeah I can't
do tier free quests yet so I just got to
rely on you you guys for now help this
one tier three oh it is yeah scary we
can do it and besides that I just want
to you know gather some basic materials
for more armor kits like duct tape duct
tape Duck duct tape and I have quite a
lot of glue oh yeah yeah we need all the
kind of basic stuff and yeah I said it
to people already but it seems like
we're going to stay a pretty small group
today from what I've heard so we can do
a lot of quests together have fun
[Music]
does anyone here have any
farming oh
skills guess
not the only farmer was sh maybe yeah I
was thinking about trying to learn some
farming cuz I feel like we should get a
big farm going yeah maybe maybe we
should we you should also learn farming
hello Domo
hello how are you I just got into the
game I'm good I'm trying to join your
party so I can see
we are at the
like desolation area yeah maybe maybe a
rule of thumb is to have two people on
on a skill each so like one backup one
and then one other for like when they're
not online so yeah you can take up
farming I'll try to get a farm going all
right I watch the video well actually to
be precise I watched one minute
of that's good enough
okay and hopefully we'll find more
farming magazines to bring you up
quickly yeah yeah yeah there might be
some at the house because I don't think
sh has looked in the house yet so we
might might be there okay yeah I think
it'll be okay cuz uh the farming perks
are in fortitude which is what I've
already speced into
so to easily get the
perks okay um so this well
I already said it like twice to the
other girls now but um uh today
hopefully we can find a lot of basic
materials to get more armor kits so duct
tape glue all that kind of stuff uh and
and fabric yeah and we're just going to
do quests in our small group I guess cuz
we're probably not going to be that many
people yeah find magazines for FAA and I
want to at some some point I'm going to
make a Bellow for my Forge to improve it
the forge
yeah just basic you need books for that
or just materials no I already it's just
a couple of materials oh I'm dying of
hunger me too I I'll give you I'll give
you food if you can kill me what why
would you do that why because I'm at
like 20 HP and I don't want to fail the
quest oh oh you fail the fail I guess
before you started we started before you
started oh oh oh oh oh okay a request
please set me on fire y sadly you were
not on fire what food do you got
now uh well only raw food I
guess but I have I gave you a can of
stuff a can you have to share the one
can
between that's not possible is it why no
I'll eat I'll eat one raw meat or maybe
maybe two raw
meat maybe three raw
meat oh really point is pretty far away
there she comes running yeah we're we're
pretty far wait you came oh is that you
wait oh there you are you're fast did
you come with a helicopter or something
no I started running immediately from
the old house wow oh wow you you went a
long way oh yeah I did then let's go to
fauna's Quest cuz she's the only one who
has one it seems okay is it kind of is
that the one that's really far away it's
not that far no it's not that far it's
just up the road let's do it ibody have
any tea oh I have tea do you have
diarrhea yeah maybe I should have eaten
the raw meat the raw meat gives you
diarrhea too good to know you
go that's why the cooks got to cook it
yeah oh maybe I can try making a mini
bike too
today dang maybe I'll learn some cooking
think we should have three Cooks oops
sorry yeah maybe yeah I think I don't
know we could consider like mobile
cooking like bringing a a cooking grill
with us and
then that would be useful where's the
issue really that we don't have enough
cook store is the issue we don't have
enough cooking stations to make food at
the same time uh efficiently I think
that and I think the issue is we're not
home enough to food and we don't have
enough ingredients should we make a home
next to the tra or just for food cooking
I think we should make a home next to
the fourth the third the new trador that
we're about to get okay okay cuz that
want's way more down south too are you
getting poked by the bird fauna
yeah dear can I hit it no not with the
bicycle it has been tested already i'
love to shoot him but a he's he's going
to get it eventually oh that works
too I missed all my shot dang it oh no
is it here well the fact is that you you
tried and that's what
matters well yeah kill that bird
focusing on F isn't so helpful when the
bird can fly huh
yeah I'm in trouble I have an infection
by the Zombie by The Bird oh no oh my
gosh maybe you should
die maybe it's time to die FAA I guess
so I guess there's not XP debt after all
is there
apparently hey bio you're a knife guy
right yes I'm a knife guy here this is
for you this is called Knife Guy I think
you're subscribe to this thank you
you're welcome wait should I die is
there p no there's no panel you kill you
yeah okay cool all right here go be
swift I'll make it quick
okay that wasn't very quick
wa wow you can do the splits fauna oh my
gosh been pring
we can Farm exp like this apparently
because we get exp by each
other no that's just wrong that's just
cheating I do not support that
strategy there over level six penalty
but I think that they we don't need to
I'm just saying it's there okay I feel
so good now keep your options
open okay let's go to fun house
fun okay
on a quest house let's run
it big tall apartment
no it's a little further into the
neighborhood
oh Kelly have you been in this
neighborhood already little bit you know
we dabbled around here but nothing too
much might be good to get a house here
though yeah multiple
houses yeah or in the as people said
probably I guess at that point we can
just make it in the next area yeah oh
true maybe snow CU I I already have tier
three the new trador is to the South Way
South of us is it this house I don't
know which this
house maybe it's just a
garage oh I'm
starving oh no it's not this one this
one is four stars so it's
okay oh yikes oh angry dog oh oh they're
coming oh very angry dog oh yikes oh
jeez doggy oh
doggy's dog wait Hammer is too big oh
there's a wolf uh-oh
that's those guys are really hard to
fight it takes so long to my hammer be
careful
are no the wolves are really hard to
beat
what difficulty
Spike think it might have been a random
wolf it's because we went into the four
star
house that the four that the house over
there
gave those wolves are really really
really hard that's
crazy yeah we met those W the other day
oh God you did still there oh oh my God
please I need imagine the XP will get
though if we kill I know yeah Quest
failed that's I think I can kill it if
where is he if someone distracts it I
can kill it okay oh gosh he's right
there oh oh oh terrifying terrify no no
no no you died on top of
me my leg is
broken oh no oh no get him
is he dead did he die dead oh he died
did I not get that exp because I died
immediately oh
no dang it always risking my dang life
for what for nothing for nothing oh he
just gives drop some loot bad meat not
the best ammo for you guys some
chili at least Parts explosives
legendary Parts can I have those please
wait why am I picking these up uh we
already have about three legendary Parts
I just need them to make the best
baseball bat on the
planet oh he dropped legendary
Parts yes so not surprised wolf these
next level the shotgun shells enemies
are going to be dropping legendary stuff
good to
know thank you I will use them well I
will never ask for legendary Parts again
probably until we start finding a lot of
them thank you I level up
oh okay so no quest for us so I guess we
can just ra as
normally might as well yeah that's rough
I have a
point oh
pumpkin oh wait 4:00 a.m. it opens again
oh you want to go back let's go back go
back let's all grab quests from that
Trader so we can like do like four Quest
yeah that' be a good
idea going this
one I'm getting upgrades
what kind of upgrad get upgraded 20%
faster punching
ooh from the bar brawling book oh we're
going the wrong way oh around around
around I'm almost finished with bats and
shotguns on my skill tree wolves drop
legendary Parts oh is it
specific yeah oh I guess it was a w wolf
I think it's a Dire Wolf is what chat
said they're called dire wolves
then I would like to see more of these
actually are you kidding me yeah more
legendary part okay you I mean we can we
can kill them you
know snip
St we're more way to get them is like
just stand stand on a car or somewhere
high up and just blast them maybe could
it be that it only showed up because we
started a tiree quest and it spawns due
to that oh that's a tier three Quest cuz
it never showed up
tier 4 no we were in the we were in the
tier four house like we walked in the
tier four House's territory and the
enemy spawned from the tier four house
the house was tier the houses have tiar
the house next to us was like four skull
four and a half oh that's what you mean
oh okay makes sense
yeah oh wait hold up did you guys finish
all the tier two Quest did you get a car
no car a car that's lame I think cars
are quite a bit later probably cuz first
maybe Mott
bikes yeah you guys are a bit ahead of
me I went to go help the others
yesterday so I think I only have tier
two right now sorry about that but I'll
try and take some should get there able
toal job opening trade route did you
guys get
that yeah
yeah bad
news okay well I accepted it yeah you
should see the new Trader in the map
then cool have you guys met him yet
nope oh maybe we should go meet him then
we can do more
finded clear is oh I chose that Quest
too it's
the like stronger infested zombies show
up I think oh well yeah we can go do the
clear first of course I wonder if Bob
will give us a car I think call if you
want to catch up to us maybe later fauna
starts a farm and I do some other
crafting stuff then you can go do some
solo Quest some solo Quest okay yeah
true sounds good sounds good I'll do my
best to rush them them you don't have
I'll help you I like healing things sure
if you got nothing else to do B you're
definitely welcome for me I'm just I
just want to get experience and level my
combat since I'm focused on killing so
and looting houses looting houses with
stuff so
killing is about the only thing that I
can do as well right now though I'd love
to learn to cook a little bit
more got that zombie maybe I can figure
that out next oh here f i here some
dirty water I really like how we get on
bikes it's
just look at
that yeah
yeah I need to throw my trash
away the Grim Reaper that checks out
yeah Grim Reaper loves killing oh the
tier free quests are in the different
region oh are they oh
go well I took do we all have opening
trade route should we go
down yo mine is really far on the uh
west side towards Traer re
far home in a part where I don't even
have the map yet it's like on to the
left you see it
so far yeah I think me and Faun took the
same Quest so we have it in
yeah um what should we do should we go
oh I see there you do you guys all have
opening trade route though no okay let's
go to final one first then maybe me yeah
you guys took some tier one missions no
I took a tier two cuz I don't get tier
three it says tier one clear oh those
are old maybe yeah old ones from
tra ah yeah the trader r quest we can
have simultaneously I guess
[Music]
oh okay well you guys lead the way I'll
just go where you want to go look at how
we're such
nerds here look we're the nerd
gang we're so strong though yeah you
better not mess with us yeah they won't
be laughing when we punch their faces in
no no know when I B feel their bodies
full of lead
yeah oh I wonder will she even give me
tier threee uh if I don't do my own tier
2 quests but someone else's tier three
quests I I'm thinking that that won't
count to
my we can still do your we can still do
your tier 2 class just so far it's okay
we can head over there yeah on our
bicycles yeah of course and then we can
all open the trade route together
yeah mhm be
nice scariest bik of gang oh yeah scary
super scary zombies fear us women love
us but I got to imagine us on one of
those like cute bicycles with the
tassels and the pink handles
and yeah yeah yeah like that so cute how
do you do that x x x yeah we're all
ringing the bell yeah imagine if a ton
of zombies come find us now cuz of the
Bell they're all attracting the sound of
the
Bell oh shoot I don't really know how to
ride this bike proper whoa I just got a
lot of exp because I forgot to turn in
my
challenges yeah right forget it's a nice
surprise there's a
hole there is a hole
there oh my God enough had enough
bullying
today fortitude and strength away with
you
zombie are you kidding me there's no
way just I'm running into everything did
I forget how to ride a bike all of a
sudden I thought you don't forget that
kind of stuff exactly I forgot for a
second that you're supposed to use the
mouse never mind to steer I think you
can switch to the other steering to
too yeah
man fair so I didn't learn how to ride a
bike until much later in life me too oh
God ladyes I never learned as a kid I
learned later nether I learned as an
adult um you're right what what
bye I fell through the world for me too
me too me too lagging well we have the
we share our experiences we're so
connected into twine our Destinies wow
incredible as newbie bike
drivers at least we didn't die though
that's cool yeah oh I think the server
is
lagging that must be it as long as it's
not on me cuz my IP has been really bad
today too I might drop out like
accidentally here and there uhoh you
love
top yeah be like that so rude get in
here
bike what a nice little
house oh you guys found it I'm on my way
yeah it's close to where you are
mountains these zombies are crazy the
burned ones Prett strong to that is a
nice house if it was close to the i'
want to take
it can you imagine living in this kind
of house like just out in the middle and
nowhere no one to bother you and it's
like a nice pretty chill house this is a
very high level I'd love I got it we got
this I just realized I think the bi me
gang we never cleared out our inventory
are we also pretty full I'm
pretty a couple things hey really yeah
wa let me let me give you some stuff
then um sure I don't want to throw this
away because everything can be useful uh
here I feel I put some things down um oh
there's an upstairs you can go from the
garage oh there's birds watch out thank
you okay thank you all right you're
welcome let's kill him
hello
hello I don't know why this game
continuously makes my sound cut off my
Discord sound that's a good
Str I hear them I don't see them yet oh
I see them now oh Ratt rattle
him hello oh well oh hello oh that's a
big gun nice he's
dead
ah
curtains I need to make it uh hobby to
get rid of the curtains cuz I need those
fragments oh yeah B beds too M all beds
too yeah oh gives me wood and
cloth and cloth
Furniture yeah yeah yeah yeah oh yeah
punch it punch it hello get rid of those
Cy
cushions oh why I bike huh bike thank
you you're welcome I don't know why it
said bike that was weird you use a
wrench you get pipes and springs too
wow oh
hello oh there's a zombie right behind
this they do Be Here There and
Everywhere Boo this knife is probably
you probably have a better one but I
have this knife oh I'll take a knife is
he dead no he's not he's living on the
floor anymore oh I don't see it kind of
Blends in with the
floor here mushrooms spes I'm good
in front of the fridge front of the
fridge did someone put put a bed roll
there is it glitched I can you yeah can
you pick it up I don't see
it oh thank we have to break these
spikes if you break them once they don't
hurt you right spikes just once I don't
know if that really works must test it
out well let's try and move through here
I bet there's still some zombies in here
oh you found the easier
way oh there's a hole in the floor here
a oh yikes wo wo wo
wo another one ah he's dead nope he's
not he's still
crawling
oh okay going down ow if you're brave
enough
secret
tunnel secret tunnel oo get him in the
head rattle him he's still
alive yay he dropped loot what' he drop
he dropped a lot of stuff I'm going to
take the baseball mag if you don't mind
and then can I please have the athletic
outfit please yeah everything else is
you guys oh you're still wearing the
Primitive outfit go get whatever you
want thanks got to get
fashionable oo I'm looking super
fashionable that seems bad oh gosh
there's zomes in here w w oh yikes how
you where are you how did
you we can take him okay
through yay sorry we're kind of late to
the party sorry about that no problem we
got it
a bit late oh black dye that seems like
might kind of nice mm wheel for a bike
maybe oh does anybody else want their
their weapon to be have a flaming
tip that's cool it's pretty useful I
think you can do it with your bat I can
give it to you really you can try here
you go try it I dropped it thanks uh
let's see where it is oh thanks let me
see does it really work for B there's a
bunch of stuff in here a locked
chest oh I have lock
picks let's
see oh never mind I don't have lockpicks
well just time to break it I guess this
is a schematic I can read about
it okay maybe we can make
it car parts tools think I have these
things we can try and make
this we'll make it when we go back to
the house
he's working on
it here we go do be working on it this
is why we want to learn
lockpicking I have lockpicks you do you
yeah I got six I can I can do the
lockpick thing I think I have points in
that here you go thank
you good luck
50 gas cans I have 50 gas cans I have
more than
that I I think I'm out of skill points
chat but I'll yay it worked what's in
there let me see we
got boots oh here's bullets for cie
thanks oh the shotgun shells
is anyone doing Salvage
tools uh yeah I think I am yeah okay
Salvage tools yeah I have
14 all right here is this and vehicle oh
thank you I also put some ammo that's
not for me onor and some armor ooh ah
thank
[Music]
you bam bam bam what's this
o and we don't need a helicopter prop
hats we flying with these bad
Bo I I think um if I make the nerd hats
on a on the maximum level they're going
to look even crazier I mean right now
they look crazy at all yeah but they're
going to have some weird like
construction around it later
on around the whole body it's exactly
what I want we got to crouch to get out
of here I
see oh I love that where was this this
is just a little Underground bunker
where do we we just down door over here
I think we might need to yeah break open
a door should that just go back to where
we were though I think so are we trapped
down here should we build a ladder or
there there must be a lay out there has
to
be maybe a ladder or something almost
almost
open um oh H it's it goes in the oh no I
go for that there stairs nice yeah but
more locked
doors we can open
them what happened why did I get hurt
did I hit you there's no way uh it might
be a way it's fine it's fine you know I
also accidentally HD people a lot let me
see if I can activate the same Quest if
I hit your health will be much much
lower it's good it cool down the same
Quest yeah yeah easy same class oh then
we can't do it right away probably can't
do it right now though it's available in
30 seconds oh okay okay easy yeah you
already know way around we missed some
keys they had some keys for us well oh
well you know we're a bit Savage we take
things into our own hands yeah Kelly do
still have some
space I think so wait let me see I'm
holding some useless items like u i
don't use these so are you sure it's
useless it's like yeah just some 50
bones I'll take the bones cuz I think I
had a stack no I didn't have no the
bones is what I gave to you oh you gave
me the bones okay I'll hold on them for
you does anybody have any small stones
yes I
do here oh yeah on the
floor thank you what are you making I'm
I'm going to cook some potatoes with the
stones o Stone potato rock potato you
need bones to make glue and duct tap
GL make glue out of Bones yes but you
need water which is the issue we don't
have a good supply of fresh water
yeah I
see but yeah everything's useful even
the things that might seem useless we
got to collect it all I I I mean the
only thing I don't really know is what
Rotting Flesh would be good for besides
getting a sick true oh it's for farming
oh okay there you go see everything
everything's useful
does anybody need some food right
now I'm good for now okay I have one can
of
chili I have a lot of money I probably
should use it yeah I've been buying food
at the Traer we're so desperate okay I'm
going to start it now NE do it it has
star head we fire no what I know what
happened what what they despawned My
Fire
potatoes my
grill no maybe we'll come back when the
quest Quest is finished I don't
know
no hi bird they dropped hey it gave me
more potato car if you want to try it
again oh my God it's so noisy up
there it's gone
well now we know yeah now we know man I
purposely put it on the like the lawn
cuz I thought it would
be no that's still
apparently part of the
area that's
okay we learned a
lesson can't figure out where the next
area to go is is it
oh we down this way it's up
here oh yeah I'm over here trying to
break
wires H you can just come up here and
there's a way down you don't have to
break the wires nice upstairs no but
next to you come back hello hello I
thought that was a weird mattress or
something what the heck
oh yeah down smart
ah
sorry might be right next to C you took
all of my health
away let me give you a med
kit oh no wait oh spicy oh you scared me
I hit anything with the bat all right
hold up I got a
kit I don't I don't have one kit it's
okay I have one I have one okay dang it
sorry two hits baby
yeah one it's gone though I may have
given it to somebody else that I
smacked oh found armor parts nice and
Raider boost I'll take those yes Lether
iron too wow everything's useful God I
destroy this whole
House's going to wreck the whole now
we're thinking like
apocalypse survivors hello it's an enemy
right okay yeah that's an enemy
I have the for the
Hat I really got to make sure it's an
enemy yeah look for the propeller hats
the main thing means
friend yes friends how you guys got in
there do you go
friends ouch
ouch
uhoh I fell down the hole oh everyone's
here ah I finished again yay yay yipp
there's a lot of stuff in this room
again and more loot again I think have
to get
out oh
well oh I got
bag got
somea Planet the Hunter MOD well I'm
cucumber but these things look good yeah
me
too see I'm going to wear my reader
boots make sure to get all the good good
stuff girls yep oh yeah loots
loot oh just kidding this is much better
than the Raider boots wait can I wear
the Raider boots of course you can drop
them for you you almost have a full set
then or do you
already I think I need the gloves the
gloves I'm makeing for you this is
better than the my primitive armor is
better than the the athletic
outfit really oh you made a pretty high
level one primitive
outfit yeah it's level four I see we'll
make you something else at level four
when you give me armor kits okay well I
found armor parts so I'm adding them to
my collection I am totally cucumber but
I have stuff for people
um I'm outside but yeah after this Quest
maybe we go back to our house
first get rid of stuff and
then maybe we can do do the Wawa Quest
that's really far away M yeah did I read
this
already
oh y apparently apparently I I learned
water
purification I don't know what that
means
but big yeah
make the Clean Water right yeah I don't
know what that means but I think that's
good for us probably wait could you not
make it before no it's a diff it's a
book that I haven't read before so I
don't know what it
means we love pure
water we
do oh I can I can create pure mineral
water pure mineral water
that different I guess
so tasty water
gang B why you walking so slow I'm so
encumbered she's being deliberate oh it
looks like maybe you also need to go on
an idol meeting really
urgently water from Rock level two water
oh is that b water M oh I guess so yeah
it's it's bottled pure water so I guess
yeah we need we need hold on we need
water coal Golden Rod flour and
crysanthemum for it kind of expensive M
we only need one of each
though
okay let's head back shall we should we
turn the quest yeah first to the trader
then home and then after a while maybe I
mean I can do that Quest also alone
probably but maybe with c yeah we got to
open that Trader at some point too too
M yeah oh it cures diarrhea and gives
you stamina regen so it's good water
pretty good
water
nice almost to beast mode oh yeah we get
a mini bike next I think is what I found
out
M so we want to definitely want to get
want to meet Trader Bob and do some
quests does he give it to us or do we
have to make it I think you have to do a
bunch of tier three quests
and he'll give it to you Hees it to us
there's no point in making one myself
yeah we got parts or some of us got
Parts
yeah well well want a mini bike also
apparently the water is good because it
qu is 60 per 60 thirst so it's a lot
more maybe they say you get a box for
some mini bike parts oh and then you
could craft it if you have the skill it
seems like I do have the skill for it so
I'll be making many bikes it seems I
didn't get many bike parts did I miss it
I think you took the nail gun right a oh
I guess it didn't stand out have a lot
of parts a lot of car parts true enough
you got to decide what you want I'll
keep that in mind I'll get the mini mini
gun is
nice that's a nice
weapon help B do lots of that water it
is the best water source in the game
oh okay know nothing compares to water
straight from the
pond right it just feels so wild drink
as much as you want I like to feel wild
and we can get a if we can get a flower
farm wa we good with everything else we
need we need Golden Rod and [\h__\h] that's
[Music]
it the hard part oh wait did I go too
far but the chrysanthemums and Golden
Rod they grow a lot in the wild where
used to live yeah oh honestly I think we
have some seeds anyway for that yeah we
can plant it when FAA gets farming
Harvest a bunch of them fauna stays true
to her name after all makes us some some
flowers and stuff getting to work with
the plant in wow I didn't think you had
it in you I've started to remember the
Road fa I I don't need to check the map
I know which road you go to the right
you turn it the creamery that's what I
remember people said that one's really
good does did anybody get and learn uh
the shamway secret recipe before I did
okay good cuz apparently that's the one
of the best foods in the game really
sham wait but if for example sham
sandwich that that's different that's
different is sham just bad or I mean oh
apparently what is it what is sham you
use the rotten flesh for that oh good
use for wait really what we're eating
rotten flesh that's why it's a secret
recipe they don't want you to know it's
[Music]
zombies yeah it's zombie meat zombie
human meat
oh o
yucky guess I'll get
these I think it's off brand spam maybe
oh K I'm dropping a book for two books
for you
well interesting I'm she she wants me to
she gives me like a nail gun potentially
but there's no optional like mini bike
parts yeah that's what I got that's what
she did for me too so maybe that's
separate maybe the mini bike parts are
at the next Quest person like not her
but someone else does someone like rifle
world
uh shotgun AP slug ammo maybe I should
get this one guys can I use this with my
shotgun are these the the good rounds ah
I got the opening trade
routes we should go and we should first
go home I think yeah yes yeah
penetration yeah vehicle expanded
seating mod
schematic this work for bikes I bet it
will should I spend $2,000 on
this sure for the truck a little fetch
Quest
clear super rare I'm dropping a book for
you f your inventory ma'am oh thank you
a couple first aid
bandages got a lot of money oh shotgun
weekly steam packs there's three did she
just say buy all these did she just do a
Fallout reference or stim pack an actual
IRL thing St Pack's a thing oh yeah it's
real a looking to stock up on
supplies but maybe that was still a
reference cuz she's like oh we still on
half stim packs go somewhere else ntim
packs are in Warhammer
too but the way she says it for the
emperor for the
[Music]
emperor
excited buy as much as I can
player vending machine oh wait something
you have to learn here to help a player
vending machine that's awesome I want to
sell things to people can you do that
yes player vending machine
6,000 6,000 do you think that will be
worth it will we buy stuff no we already
give things free to each other yeah
we're we're a we're a good Society we
share everything for free free in a
different
world I have to go to meeting I'll be
right back okay okay have
fun see you ooh s off shotgun mod I'll
buy
that ah B
yes um there you
go thank you make things go boom make me
proud yes I will that was really fun
when you were throwing Kaboom things
around the last grade Kaboom thing is
really
strong so I'm I hope before the next R
I'll just make a bunch of explosives and
I'll help sounds good what is
this nice double barrel shotgun quality
3 we can make a stronger
shotgun uh chat this work with my fire
Sledgehammer well I didn't realize
yesterday that you had to hold the left
button to throw it farther but now I
know how to spell it so do that it'll be
less of an issue yeah it did always go
pretty close huh yeah it apparently you
just you can't tap the button you just
got to hold it to SL but now I know
thanks for the business okay we're open
from dawn to dusk since all right I'm
going back to to our house new
house okay and I'll probably do some
sorting and try to make the Bellow and
then I might need some help uh as well
with making uh well maybe I can I can
make the baseball bat don't worry about
it uh yeah I I think like weapons I
don't know if I'm like specialized in
making weapons it's mostly
armor uh but if you need like for the
baseball bat if you need any iron or so
it you can take it from the
forge okay but Chad I'll let you know
let me know Chad if I'm wrong if I
should make her bat I don't
know I'm back oh I can I can make level
three bats is the thing so maybe I
should focus on that
I have a thing for you to learn oh the
the expanded seating for vehicles is
like a re okay you want to give it to me
now or at home yeah I'll give it to you
now okay since you're the vehicle master
I'm seemingly the master of so many
things I feel the
pressure but you know things I want to
make sure I'm here every day so that I
can be of use so I know yeah right I'm
very committed to this now me
too what's the stuff on the
ground uh uhhuh it's nice to have a
handful of us who are like strong so we
can carry yeah which way we feel that
responsibility we're strong and we can
carry but we are directionally
challenged yeah no I had no clue where
we're going is this the right way to the
yes whoever whoever's in front is going
the right way good we can go figure out
the trader uh later on the new Trader
yeah I want to take some time at home to
just figure out some crafting stuff yeah
I want to try to farm a bit okay so
little Quest break yes yeah Mor might do
a quest solo though so I can catch
up we need a mountain bike
Oh no you're fine I thought all of our
bikes were going through the world again
or something no no funny that was a
blonding moment oh I think everyone's
Frozen for me oh uh oh server lag oh
yeah Callie looks Frozen to me too I
just Road P okay I'm going into the
ground now oh okay
refresh yeah we hadn't seen a ton of
server lag in the beginning but now it's
kind of starting to pop off a little bit
more yeah wonder I wonder why like
there's fewer people playing so you
would think it wouldn't be is there such
a thing as like a just like a reset for
the server router everyone's ping seems
okay
oh yeah it because we're like exploring
new areas I don't know oh yeah they're
saying new
chunks I'm excited to see what the new
Traders area is like is it going to be
snow like a desert like desolated no
well it looks yellow from from Little
preview at the bottom it looks
yellow the swamp yellow
SW could be this area is a little
depressing yeah I'm tired of
this but Trader Jen is there and she's
so cute she's only her place is good but
I'm tired of everywhere else yeah yeah
even though I haven't been in that area
for that much and that long but I feel
sauron's gaze when I'm there and I just
don't like
it the
I yeah he's watching all of us every
single step no oh I'm
home good two workbenches who's going to
f all those trees when giggy's not here
I know where's where's our our gigg our
Beaver wife flavor husband
Krypton repair kit is iron and duct tape
I need to make some repair
kits oh yeah me too soon
see is there any duct tape around you
can make some uh I have one here I'll
just drop one for you
thanks thank you thank you need more
cloth
this huh oh there's two farming books in
our
house oh I'll read
them any cooking by chance sure let's
get some stuff started yeah we have two
Cooks in here
today yeah I think we have always have
two cuz we're always here yeah we just
need ingredients yeah where did my iron
go well if I can use the iron I'm going
to help myself to some of the iron mhm
go
ahead okay I'm just going to grill a lot
of meat cuz I feel like we have
plentiful of that that's
true yes please wish we had more eggs
though I
know oh I think I collected some on uh
on my way outside me too would be good
some raw
eggs
nice can always use more food
so you can make forged Iron by putting
regular iron that's like in your
inventory into the forge yeah yes that's
cool as long as the fires are
lit nice okay yeah they're already how
many do you
need um oh I'm just throwing them in
there I just have so much random iron in
my pockets that I just threw it in there
in this melting oh kiaha you should read
this too I think okay unless you already
have read it oh I might have already
read
it oh no I guess I
didn't all right we're duct
tape should I hold on to my own Iron
parts or should I contribute them make
it a like Community thing hold on them
right we can make it a community cuz I'm
just I've just been putting my iron
there everybody needs iron thingies so
we can
just uh I'm I just like when you put
iron in there you still have to go into
the menu of the forge and then um click
forged iron and then craft them it
doesn't happen automatically but I just
put 100 pieces of iron uh forged iron
into the queue so now it's cooking up
okay but yeah any any leftover uh forged
iron can of course be free to use
there's some in the chest right next to
the forge
C okay thank you I need to remake my bat
so I'm just going to take one duct tape
need more clay control
oh where's the
clay need
iron craft wrench
why and leather I need leather
too
clay how to make
clay yeah have leather right I have I I
dropped some off I think we we have who
house so ah uh how many you
need um I think for my bat hold on just
a moment I want to make a baseball bat
um hold up if I want to be level two I
need one leather okay I put some back
into the chest thank you what was I
doing 30 forged iron that's so
much well I'm I'm cooking a lot of iron
there's a lot that's cooking right now
yeah do I put it in there there's the
leather
just need more
iron I can make vegetable
stew feel
good yes
yes smelt the clay
really
okay do I have
to pumpkin bread
nice wait I'm going to try and make that
tip that fiery
tip wait I have one you don't need to
make it I have
one like I have the actual mod not the
schematic hold on CH the okay I leave it
to
you there we go I don't know if it's
worth using beer to make pumpkin cheese
cake wait is that really something you
have to
do I think you should keep it to to use
it for your drunken fist I think that
would be more beneficial oh I can make
pumpkin pie with no
beer I'll make two pumpkin
pies yum
yum me disassemble my
bat
oh there we go
uh I'm crafting oh yeah I want to try
making the good
water oh
yeah
[Music]
H Golden Rod
flower iron mind if I take this forged
iron oh we have so much yeah take it I'm
crafting a lot right now also do we have
coal uh don't know we did at one point
oh we do we have a lot okay I can
actually actually make quite a few if I
have plain water I just made an item
that makes our Forge 50% faster oh
really yay let's go can I put it in oh
do I need to make a better Forge to use
this turn off the forge ah ah okay okay
okay 50% faster let's
go woo don't be zooming that's nice
Kelly what are you waiting for right now
more more
iron U I'm waiting for my bat to be made
ah okay okay it's just going to take a
couple
minutes all right much
faster oh I was going to say thank you
for frogy waa frogy wa please treat her
um nicely cuz somebody was saying froggy
W plushy arrived treat her
nicely but this base is really solid
with the forge and everything wait sham
is is made of horrible ingredients what
out of I don't think I want to tell you
is
theh one component yet is it also made
of like dirty water well
no murky water maybe you got to tell us
the truth rip the B it's made of Bones
animal fat and Rotting Flesh
wow make a ton of it yeah make one yeah
make it make it what we what it takes to
survive
a It'll be such good food the virus or
something I don't know it'll be so
useful maybe maybe if we you know eat
the parts of the zombies we'll grow more
and more immune kind of like a vaccine
sort of thing oh true right have the
infection in our
bodies yeah I can see where you're
cooking see we it
I can put my magazines so many nerd
magazines we don't have anybody learning
robotics though oh I'm learning it oh
really why
put oh thank you cuz nobody else was
learning it so I thought yeah nobody
wants to do the nerd stuff but if you
want to do the nerd stuff go for it I a
nerd at
heart yeah go for
it my armor level is at 89 out of 100 oh
my gosh I can almost soon make the level
seven the maximum level armor wow you're
going to have to help us all out with
that yeah but all for all of that first
of all I I will need more armor kits and
legendary armor parts oh yeah that true
so it won't be that easy legendary armor
parts I want to make the maximum
baseball bat with the legendary okay
moloto aren't that bad to make I should
make some molotovs those are nice
oh and pipe bombs are bad to make too
okay that's good here's my baseball bat
okay
modify oh yes Soul faithful wait that
was already level three is the
die oh
well oh wait that not mine oh that's not
mine okay I see my okay it's fine
baseball bat check it this too
baby this is exciting oh my gosh I can't
wait to kill more people I mean to help
my friends and get strong
[Music]
yeah pommel Pete once took on 50 zombies
with just a club and he would be proud
of you clubs deal 50% more damage
attacks do 200% more damage to stun
enemies power attacks have 100% chance
to knock foes back down this is
big oh that's going to be big I want
that what should I do next
guys yeah I may need to run a little bit
a few quests on my own I am game stage
44 you guys are
oh so I'm going to go do a
quest but let me know when you guys want
to go to the new
Trader okay
for what mechanical
Parts wrench for what what do you use
the rench for cars
maybe I wish the new trador was a cute
girl but his name is Bob he might be
cute in his yeah Bob might be cute you
never when I think of Bob I think of
like a trucker you know hopefully he's
nicer than trade direct though he's got
to be right he's got car to take them
apart
pray
there breaking down anything electronic
or mechanical
okay anyone take the cloth oh yeah for a
moment uh but I'm putting the them into
the chest next to the forge okay
oh here I have a schematic for you you
can craft headlights oh for cars okay if
somebody wants a headlight for their
car will be useful for sure does anyone
have a car yet no not yet in the future
be great when we can get
one ah on the microwave okay anything
elute I just don't think Trader Bob's
going to be a cute trucker that's all
I'm saying here we sure the the if you
need the cloth fragments they're back in
the Forge
chest
okay thank
you got to make some
explosives what is this four grip mod
schematic yeah we can all get in a car
and go to missions together it sounds
like fun
yeah road trip with a car it might not
be so problematic anymore if our house
is very far from the Traer
[Music]
so that be great craft his item can't
wait to throw Molotov out the window of
the
car
violence always go to
violence I was going to
you guys said I had this grip yeah for
the
sledgehammer is getting a little
late is there a better version of this
chat that I already
know let me
know
gosh every time every time solo
Adventure I just want to hear my
friend's voices in the background while
I
Traverse the grant you courage thanks
Big up for the
courage if anyone has handgun parts
please give them to me I feel like
there's some in the old house gos yeah
yeah yeah there's uh in the in the armor
chest oh
desert the uh armor ammo in the new
house oh okay don't think anybody needs
that going to get rid of
it it's pretty cool at night I can make
a magnum gun
now hit by a
cactus quick before you start getting
fast I'm going to try to make another de
collector but I don't know if there's a
better way to collect water um so what I
assume is there are mods to mod the DU
collector on the right side if you look
at the Duke collector you can buy those
from the Traders um so might want to
stop by the trader and see if they're
selling any of
these I see things that help it good to
have more anyway though but I will see
about mods
long I'm so did drop a lot of stuff
though oh a forg steel that's big put
the stock on your rifle the stock
ah I'm getting so
strong I'm going to steal these people's
curtains
are you raiding
houses yeah just a little bit just a
little house killing time huh need some
need some cloth you know mhm wait for
stuff to
cook oh they all came back to
life glue as well I mean now we have a
good amount of cloth lying around but
glue
the bird we have 34 glue in the oh okay
that's pretty good yeah de I'm going to
make some duct tape out of it that's
okay yeah I think that's the best use
for
it oh hor is
good you oh a okay do not stand on the
forge oh did you catch on fire
yeah they've got a
Pelon wow fancy I know they are fancy at
the
[Music]
Harrison motor tool parts that could be
good oh hello oh hello I need something
to
drink you're dead
no
drink there's some coffee I think yeah I
just want to drink pure water I'm going
to go to where you are cuz you're by the
water you're by the coffee or the fancy
water the bi boo made no that's a waste
you're literally by the water I'm going
to go to
you okay okay where what there uhoh
that's
bad some w
there's a lot of them oh that's a lot of
zombos byebye oh God that's bad that's
very bad what are you doing Kellie do
you die don't die no I'm alive I'm alive
do you oh
Jesus oh he threw up on me I might die
oh the vomit guy that's not good dang I
was feeling so cool I'm going to die eat
the vegetable eat the vegetable eat the
vegetable no
oh dang I thought that they would make
the zombie number go down a little bit
maybe for me oh were you trying to solo
a quest huh yeah I wanted to solo Quest
I got pretty close I wonder if it's cuz
you're in our party that the level I
don't but you're the only one who
started it right so yeah maybe I don't
know can you make Ste I had a really
cool moment though um uh possibly I need
to check when I'm at the forge I guess
but uh
Quest I can do it my bat's very strong
oh hello hello sir oh yeah I mean it's
just um you kiding iron and
Clay so if you can make about 40 steel
for me I would be in your done yay when
I'm home I'll put it in into the cube F
where are you I'm by the water me I'm by
the pool by the pool oh we're drinking
pool water it's extra delicious
I might as well finish getting
loot did lure all the zombies out so
I'll probably just loot the house and
leave oh
nice yeah getting a wrench was a good
idea
oh pool
party
yeah Hat
Point and I'm going to go down down to
the Traer the new one smells like fauna
wait we should go together to the new
one okay you want you guys ready to go I
want to
go Yeah I broke my lock I'll go back to
the house one more time to put the stuff
in the queue thank you guess I got to do
this the hard
way Zip Zip Zip Zip Z okay we got it
that's enough thank you so much I appre
apprciate it let me wrench dang we got
so close to unlocking it is this going
to explode oh oh dog dog dog dog
alarm Okay F will take care of
it it didn't explode lately
yeah it
didn't you have loog pick I wonder if I
can make loog
picks I think generally brute forcing
things open is the way to go o
I had enough though I almost had enough
I was one pict
short well let me wrench the thrilling
game play Chief
thrilling o oo wrenching a car gives a
lot of good material yeah it does do you
have a wrench too F I do
oh I found one really early oh really I
made one level free
branch no l
there there we go o feels like Minecraft
now we're almost halfway there wait can
you ask the bird nest for
eggs is that a thing for eggs can't you
just open it normally well I don't
always have
eggs
oh maybe you can smack
them where's my
bike see I'm a shooting
does nope doesn't work well maybe it
does where's my bike
o x does more per
second watch the loot be
terrible okay I'm coming home again okay
I'm just looting some houses nearby
while I wait for you guys
[Music]
okay
um I wonder if it's still worth it at
this point to do the tier two Quest at
all or the one that I have or should I
just I think maybe we should just do the
tier three I think it's it's worth it if
we keep just yeah let's definitely do it
in a group though I feel like we can
steamroll if we're in a group but uh one
by one's a little difficult at least for
more
[Music]
yeah we really need more water mhm yeah
we should quiet these
days next time next time I see the mod
or the the tools for the to help the
things go faster I'll buy them yeah I'll
look
to
uh wait what's Crucible
required do I need ah I probably need
this do I need
this what is
this um the thing under
steel oh that's called a Cru Oh I
thought it it meant I need something Cru
Crucible isn't that a
word uhu oh crucial I I I can't make
forged steel yet because I need my
workstation level to be higher
by quite a bit so it's going to take a
while
still almost got it Lads dink dink
dink I will just look for Forge Steel in
the field then yeah or quest uh reward
could give it
too what no Repair Kit Repair Kit won't
work on
this on
what on my axe oh it
should who what's this music so
ominous when's the
next ra ra raid zombie raid
28 28
probably
okay how long do we want to play today 4
hours
again hit the sweet SP with the 4 hours
okay that's probably fine just need to
keep our eyes on the day so that we know
you know what cuz the 28th is the next
Rush right yeah feel like if we play for
4 hours it'll be right about there at
that time so we'll do probably need to
do another
one well then uh I don't know maybe
until ingame
Day
26 or or
so
nice and maybe that would be
good all right I guess I'll head
towards
the trade Quest opening trade okay I
will also go that way
okay I can buy the 15K oh maybe I
will H is it always at the
trader if we get some uh what how much
money 15,000 that's a lot of money I'll
need to get some donations from the
others too 15,000 for what what did you
me The Crucible if I buy The Crucible I
can make the forge steel way earlier I
have 8K 8K okay I have like 9k but
that's my like all of my
money if we put a few KS together we
can buy money too
yeah there's I have some money as Weller
cash
here I'm actually really close to the
new Trader okay well I'll take my money
if the trader sells crucibles I'll buy
it with some combined monies is that how
you make a car no uh maybe as well
indirectly but with The Crucible I can
make Forge steel yeah Forge steel is
probably the higher tier of weapons I
also found some forged Steel by the way
in my ratings
would like please wa what's a good path
towards the new
[Music]
Trader maybe that way um just come where
I am it's in the desert yeah but I don't
see the roads on the map because they're
uncovered not not
UNC I'll find my way
Crucible um what I'm doing is I'm going
to go to the path to Traer Jen and go
past the road there that's what it seems
like it's pointing toward
oh okay I
see
Anvil oh Anvil I can make soon four more
workstation magazines I feel like I
haven't read a workstation magazine in a
while yeah they seem rare mhm oh
huh excuse you I'm bringing a bunch of
food I can't hold anym I can't hold
anymore I can anymore right now that's
smart breaking the food well I'm cooking
a ton of
spam spam we'll have lots of spam hey
what about the Sham way stuff sham I
mean ah
okay
yummy hey I want to see how much better
that is than the other food I don't
think it's better I think it's just
cheaper so you can make more why is
Trader Bob not friendly behind well he's
mean yes School showed up when I got to
his house
huh what's wrong Trader Bob you don't
like us is it because he's
closed I wonder oh he might be closed
it's like let's ride together
okay maybe I'll just kill a bunch of
random zombies to level up that might be
helpful it's dangerous to go alone
for it's dangerous to go alone take this
oh I need to focus on repairing my ax
right now
Bobby goodbye jenma we don't need you
[Music]
anymore we always need you through
yourself yeah I do I do really need her
but she wants me to move on so I guess
I'll move on
no quite
literally I finally am being pushed to
move on to a new manager did you girls
know after all these years with
JMA oh yeah fin you were thinking the
same they're empty oh no restock
restock but good
thinking very important always have to
check yeah those are the the best spots
for magazines oh it is a desert
area not the swamp no it's not a swamp
unfortunately get CA juice what is
that oil shale GMA will be
remembered she's still still doing a
little bit of stuff for me but mostly
it's PMA now I have named my new manager
PMA yes because she's pretty pawn p n
yeah very Pawn she's cute though whoa
dog oh it's a
fox wait I'm scared the new area show
surely there will be more werewolves and
stuff running around oh God steal their
part oh yeah there's a lot of scary
stuff here be careful
Kelly Kelly stay
hidden hang on I'm almost there
no please don't die I'll be fine I'll be
fine it's just the bird where's the
bird sick of these birds and then I'm
walking into the spot
oh God
uhoh out when I put my Bat Away
awesome the music is getting scary too
I'm going to
die not bleeding anymore I'll be okay oh
no won't sky is red yeah I've suffered a
concussion I'm almost there please
please oh hey we were riding for the
night if we came earlier they the Bob
probably wouldn't even be open but now
is perfect time
through I I like this kind
of it's
pretty I heard I heard a wolf woof wolf
wo that's rough buddy these cactuses by
the way the cactuses do not play
around okay I won't punch
them though I want
to pop and
pills yeah that place looks like it
would have yes laser site mod or yeah I
guess like antibiotics and stuff just
lying around would be good I got a laser
sight mod by the way can I have it
yeah laser sight here you go wow oh the
sunrise here is beautiful thank
you what are you doing for it's a desert
after all getting more spam
ingredients you should open
soon all right I'll also keep an eye out
for spam ingredients he
appetizing
wo you sounds friendly
enough they're stealing those sound from
show me the sails Bob the
Rings what is this just uhoh oh
uhoh one
these what's
uh he doesn't respect the AF okay yeah
dang it I was looking at my inventory he
does have forged steel so that's
nice what I like the music here do it's
chill right mhm not a lot of really good
healing
stuff oh they don't like fire they run
away cut off a little bit yeah I'm dying
my internet is dying oh
no I'll be back hand magazine boo oh
thank you uhoh doesn't look like there's
anything for the forge though
sadly I wish it's not selling the what
was it um
[Music]
hello
hello hello hello man hello please hold
on to my
hands
otherwise the Lord will suck me in again
I don't have I don't have much room in
my inventory but he is selling the stuff
for water collection oh I can buy it
maybe depends how expensive it
is can make some room I could probably
give some money too if if need be oh do
you have the steel Callie yeah hold on
here's five forged steel oh thank you
hopefully it'll help you out that helps
a
lot my chat's still not Reviving hello
oh no rise
come on help they're so
dead chat where are you I'm alone
robotic drone medic mod o sounds good a
flying field
medic I can't afford it it sounds good
though it does sound good I don't think
I'm at that point yet
yet a battery here I see you Let me
refresh this if we do end up making a
car there we go heara wants hammers yes
hammers Hammers and workstation
magazines nice okay I will will be back
in the game in a moment momentarily okay
we will await you with anticipation yes
he has an anvil he's selling an anvil
but I could make one if I get three more
workstation magazin oh so you have to
you can have a drone and then you can
put this mod in the Drone yeah but I'm
not close at all I need uh robotics
level 76 and I have 13 so oh 76 wow
yeah you
car
B ikim my shell
Quest failed what do you mean Quest
failed oh because I'm not in the
party oh yeah I got to get you back in
the party one of you is the leader
now someone's got to be I'm not the
leader
[Music]
it's make sure you invite
guua
work die
die I received the party invite
all right but there's so many monsters
out
here got to get inside I'm
coming I like how they respect the
boundaries of this place because they
don't walk into the very widely opened
doors oh I like the music that's playing
oh hellad over here let me check the
guys Watchtower egg please where is he
egg
I found
egg can you break it and get more
eggs Central Area
um yeah I heard
that ah oh I missed him wow me yeah talk
to him he's nice he's not like
wrecked could
work that potato looks like a rocker I'm
not taking
that it's a baked potato though isn't it
re there's a restore power night only
Quest interesting sounds too complicated
I'm curious about those yeah it's not
night I took a buried treasure Quest
though I have a shovel which Quest I
just took a clear Quest did anybody take
an infested clear Quest I think I did oh
hello um I'll take a fet clear maybe huh
you must have more guts and you can hang
on your
fence oh he is selling for steel if you
really if you really want that
steel I think I'll just wait and see
Stones small stones we can just loot it
somewhere yeah for
sure would you guys like
food I would always like food fauna okay
I've got lots of food I would always
like food come come get some okay could
buy
this after I pick up my last Stone I'll
come get some
food one more Stone have I learned
this no I can make a
shovel okay Chow Time what's for dinner
fauna how about some meat stew ooh that
sounds good wait what kind of meat is it
the it's it's pork I think or maybe deer
or maybe something yummy it's not
zombies with a stick
you prom I promise if it's okay promise
Clos if it's closed I didn't learn it
yet
okay shin and grilled meat wow thank you
so much I do love I do love some yum
yums up early today
what I'm holding a lot of stuff though
you have
bandages have a bandage not but I will
take a bandage I got vehicle very
cucumber does anybody you want me to
carry some stuff do you have any cloth
or fat or bones well I have cloth please
carry my
cloth oh I have an extra bone bone knife
sword
thingy need this oil we have plenty of
oil back at the
house thank you very much to carry the
oil you can carry it um
ready oh our quests are kind of all over
the place take this oh okay thank you oh
thank you this oh thank you you I have
magazines oh nice for the quest shall we
start with the ones that are towards the
north okay Soo Calli and mine yes
okay kaha where' you go you want to
start
the furthest uh away so Ki is first and
then Call's and the mine okay you will
read this you read this you will read it
are you learning wiring fauna robotics
yes I am here you go that's for you
thank you you're welcome oh wait let me
wrench this
thing F let's wrench it together okay
we'll be faster yeah that's how you
collect the car stuff huh yeah mhm
wrenches why are you hitting
it hold that's not how you use a wrench
what it worked why do you use it
differently that's weird does it not
work I mean I guess a Power
Attack you have a different different
technique it still
works I guess so shall we go to um Mor's
digging Quest or we're going to go to
kiaha and then work our way to the right
sounds good
iara mine is really far away I'm sorry
about that that's okay Quest is a quest
I actually have two tier three
clears oh oh is one still from J one is
pretty far too
yeah we love questing yes more Quest
than marrier and I brought a cooking pot
and Grill so hopefully we can have some
snacks maybe yeah just keep it away from
the lawn keep it away from far from the
house yes I wonder if we can just go
straight this
way do cacti carry water it should like
I really do right yeah wonder if we
break the cacti if it gives us water
probably not well that's a big fact I
only got fiber from it
sadly oh oh wait how spam ingredient
yummy yummy for
dinner I dinner can't wait for for
tonight yeah they drop Yuka fruit I
guess when you smack them nice oh here's
some more
dinner no not roadkill not again please
the chefs are
crazy our chefs are insane making us eat
roadkill it's the only way remember how
hungry you've been this must cure our
hunger oh you girls found an actual
street that leads have digity the right
way I went for the Wasteland like I
didn't even take a
street oh W this is this is the max
amount of skulls like oh my God oh my
God is this our Quest no no no it's not
our Quest okay
yeah this is where they're making the
Sham they're dogs be careful they are
dogs outside look more
food it's a little scary here though I
feel like we should keep
driving really strong zombies here
there's lots of food
everywhere oh bye-bye
zombie what this is the real Fallout
right here yeah it doesn't give me
Fallout Vibes that much you don't think
so I don't know not the desert gave me L
Vibes the desert this gave gives me um
oh a dog that game where the Wawa and
the iris and the gobba daba is in in the
game now oh EDF yeah this EDF part I'm
looking at right now gives me EDF Vibes
oh yeah yeah I see what you're talking
about
yeah someone said be careful for
landmines scared there's a bear land
yeah land mines it could be honestly
I've heard there there's like traps the
f get in the game I have a perk where if
I step on it I don't activate it so I'm
not
scared area pops off at night though
okay I have
arrived more or
less let's see how strong the enemies
are oh she's excited to see
me zombies are strangely fast did you
check
these newspapers you I was about to you
guys scared
me wo it's kind of a high level Place
yay find something good found I found
more more handgun Parts I need like so
many I wonder what's for
dinner stop right there lady I need to
stop you right there point we need to
talk about your bicycle riding skills
you're in danger
people oh hot lady watch
out is she back hot lady back hot lady
any Ro meat
no okay should I start the quest she
blew ready all right here we go ready
let's do
it we got this ladies oh
hello
green that rad mod might actually be
good to use here
I installed something oh gosh strong oh
she's
alive when your friends start oh he's
not dead and there's a bird and inside
there's a
bird boom head shot oh they really want
fa understand the in the bathroom uhoh I
hear oh there he
is
nice dead I'm going to check the toilets
for oh yes there is water
here nice I brought the pot so we can
all drink water
nice yo are filled there's a lot of
action here do these very very infected
oh God he's oh God the Hulk is here
people the
Hulk there's so much
action we got him
I just still alive he's still alive uhoh
oh gosh some green
ones oh oh oh fa you here thank
God there's some fake fauna cosplayers
trying to give me hugs Faun the green
ones the new green ones but I can tell
them apart I know who's the real
one oh you know you know my hair is kind
of this exact color yeah in the
game oh nice the prettiest I've ever
seen I got him really
quick o do we
have did C
is might be
upstairs yep my catch is
upstairs oh we're looking for supplies
huh I oh yeah oh oh this takes a while
it is really dark in here I'll go inside
oh are we
stuck
outside oh we might have to forcefully
open the
door oh around bash is head in I'm going
to follow on you I'm going all the way
around let's just try to not exit the
boundaries
hello oh gosh wait there's scary people
out
I how it get the
other I need to repair this
soon glowing where from where there it
lit up in here even though here don't
worry I turned away right at the right
at the last
moment there's thing oh here he is
hello check
hello ladies how did you guys get deeper
in I want the door it's it's an alien oh
God oh God an alien oh God it could be
oh are they fighting each other oh that
would ni each
other y y he seem this is not a place to
be at night you seems
strong guys found your way up here oh
nice they found their way oh no just
kidding that's B
why is there there's so many
spawning I feel like ah for here maybe
for the toilet stuff is there a door oh
I see
door there must be like a go around I
guess it's less fun I like breaking
through I'm
scared you have to buy stuff from the
vending machines here can we just break
it Wast yeah who who's buying stuff
I'm
losing maybe now it's not the time but
repair it when there's always the time
it's always the time to
loot uh-oh will they spawn endlessly
until we find our loot no clear area is
a condition so I feel like oh there's so
many watch out wait come back downstairs
come back downstairs they outside
they're they're outside the door
okay they're all stacked on each
other
e
uh-oh yeah yeah nice good one bi boo
okay the area is still not clear though
not clear though what okay don't try to
ow ow ow ow ow don't try to wrench the
vending
machines it gave me an electric shock
you silly my goodness you know I was I
was going to try to do that too you know
I'm not giving up on this door I did it
for
you so um there's something behind this
door I'm telling oh thank you for the
[Music]
help we're almost done it's better with
two it's def better with did anybody
bring a repair kit I have one can I
where
you um after the zombie can I get the
drop o uh he dropped armored up enforcer
gloves you guys probably would like this
uhor for sure yeah I know you probably
want that so you can grab that ooh you
have to parkour up here there's some
there's some loot for or there's
some actually do I need this old money
and some corn seeds
hello taking pot shots at him uhoh oh
gosh there's a lot of people upstairs
oh
yeah um um did you go for the
outside I parkour up okay ow
jeeez I'm bringing them down hello
okay
o
thanks that door is locked I can
probably go around though
beautiful good job ladies
oh I don't want to shoot oh did I punch
you I'm sorry oh it's clear now can I
get the repair
kit I got one oh come here thank you
there's stuff up here that we can loot
though I think hold up
[Music]
yeah
Ma look there's there's so many sham
food
boxes whoa this is a totally new area up
here right for the Looting
rooting tooting looting rooting tooting
looting
shooting oh oh tell me if you find
anything good that maybe maybe you might
be helpful oh boy all right ladies is it
time to break the chest no I'm unlocking
it I'm unlocking it don't cough drink
some tea cie with honey I'm doing my
best uh let's see there are a bunch of
44 Magnum rounds in here Vio in the ammo
okay
y double barrel shotgun here I'm going
to drop that for you oh really oh I got
a saw off shotgun monster does that
sound like a Dropbox loot box probably
give this to crony actually cuz crony
wanted to do shotguns I have oh okay
wait are you not doing shotguns I am I
am but I my shotgun is level
uh okay I found my Satchel let's go oh I
have armored up also
will need those I'm dropping an armored
up as well thank you did you guys all
find your satchels I did I have
Hammer I found my satch I have molotovs
be those oh yes
please seems wrong to just throw them on
the ground but I'll pick it up from the
ground hopefully they won't
explode I think this Satchel also might
have something in it if
somebody hasn't gotten their goods we've
all gotten our Goods right oh I have wa
I dropped have some I'll pick it up and
drop it here maybe yeah I guess we're
good
then good on good oh uh f i here some
[Music]
farming thank
you oh should I learn this D are really
raging this was a fun one yeah lots of
stuff here was we going to get a lot
more like these I
think I feel like we might be way over
the other girls' levels if we
to so many quests uh oh my leg didn't
break I'm good oh watch out there is a
zombie down there though I killed it
we're good just kidding shot Nice Shot
get him get
him
yeah getting out might be a bit of a an
adventure in here yeah oh just jump out
the window are you sure Chad don't you
get like stuff more often um that you
put skills into so if I'm not the one
opening boxes and so on the chances of
me getting workstation magazines are
lower like if the other girls are
opening it so I should open things more
often too right
yeah oh here it
is God it's like a rush during the day
ouch
bad oh gosh there's a lot aren is yeah
there's a lot there a
lot ow
ow don't die don't
dieing almost shot almost shot
FAA it's okay I deserve it I deserve it
there more there's still more I've hurt
you many
times oh boy um hold on I'm trying to
heal okay we good we good thank you
thank you
for a panic drank my beer uhoh but I
don't know understandable in this kind
of
[Music]
situation
uh um um oh fine now here you go take my
dirty water I searched all the toilets
for you thank wow
sweet that's how you know you got a
friend I can purify this if we need
it
oh oh I brought um what is it I brought
all the ingredients to make the really
good water so if you have like the
fireplace oh I can make I can make the
really good water do you have some food
for
me yes thank you
Mommy here you go pumpkin pie Mommy
Mommy
o
uhoh god it feels so good to do
that oh she's
alive sure um look good shall we go to
the next Quest buried supplies sure oh
okay let's do
it oh is this the mor Quest I
wonder I think it is by the way I know
we're all like uh loot
goblins um if I I I think the past few
quests I was always kind of lagging
behind because I was destroying curtains
and stuff U but I won't get workstation
magazines if I don't open any boxes uh
and you girls don't get them either cuz
you're not Skilling into it can you like
maybe keep like one crate or so if you
see something for me to open like one
well just every now and then if I'm
lagging behind because yeah I noticed I
don't get any workstation magazines be
rampant thank you thank got a sh caring
is it all uh what it is it all crates
because all the crates have like
specific um like this is a food crate
this is a does it specifically I don't
know any specific crate or like any
crate not sure where it would show up
there's no bird bird please I feel like
it's been pretty mixed mixed bag of
things in those you find the workbench
ones oh oh it's a it's a crack book so
you need to look for cracka book crates
crackable crates so if it says that we
can let you open it okay bookshelves too
right yeah
bookshelves probably there also a supply
drop pretty close but we should get it
it's really close right yeah let's go do
that first also this bird is really
annoying
me do you guys see the bird yeah you see
him bullying me yes e vomit
dinner oh but I I I not no need to
always leave the boxes for me of course
because everybody's looking for
something just one time
maybe want to see if I get lucky oh God
that's how many skulls is that seven
sham way Factory D that's definitely the
scariest
one they get the quests are getting
intense for sure are but we are also
getting intense yeah I should check more
mailboxes
too and those newspaper machines are
really
nice yes we should check those every
day ouch okay found the CR no no no no
leave me alone leave me alone okay is
the bird still bothering you yes why
here K you want to open this one what
why is it there is that the supply wait
we made it back to Jen's house
oo oh it has a farm bundle and a
crafting oh God the birds
are the
bird nice yeah shoot him up the sky this
one for fauna
probably and this one for and this one
for FAA
weighted head oh I thank you I have one
of these I'll probably it's a
schematic oh it's a schematic nice
nothing much interesting just some
blueberry pie and the magazines and
stuff is there another one or just one
crate I think it's just the one I think
that's it okay yeah they're a little
underwhelming not going to
lie well it was on the way you might as
well go check them yeah okay back to
buried
Supply yeah okay what's the best way
we're going west I don't to way I got it
it's uh just down the hill I think we
can take a left East East not
West East you guys are going west but
moris is moris is that way the way I'm
looking we got to go down the
hill are we not doing moris which one
are we doing I'm going to yours oh okay
it told me let's see let's just see who
gets where how yeah who gets there first
make your way over there I'm just going
down the hill how do you go down this
way bi boo parkour on your bike I I just
I rode down on my bike and it was fine
was it my bike only has
44% oh I have I have repair kits for you
if you need to repair your bike
okay I'll figure out my way down
somehow a birds following me again I
thought you said go
east it's not West it's East
West or are we going
sorth it's
SE SE yes oh Southeast yes
what ceased and cease and exist ceas
what's it called cease and assist ceist
CE what CE cease and assist what Cee
and yeah is that how you say never heard
of cease and assist before SE and yeah I
was just trying to figure out what it
was called
again English is a hard language don't
worry about it I get those letters a lot
in my mail for re saying really makes
any sense to be honest especially being
silly I get letters from KFC and Burger
King and McDonald's they're all sending
me those letters it's okay that's just
that's just how you know you're doing a
really good
job
right place where are we going yeah it's
right here we're
digging you seen holes
before
SE everybody is too far away I went two
SE oh kill him oh I had a bag no ah come
on I hate this yes bag the
bird whoa you Clue D I was playing
baseball right
there where's B all right we wait for
Bio I got to go wait maybe I should
cook oh yeah do a quick cooking session
before start Ione have small stones wait
there's some small st I have small
stones I have small stones yeah go
gather them I'm going to kill
surrounding zombies so they don't
interfere I'm going to I don't know how
far I need to put it so that it doesn't
despawn surely over here should be fine
right surely on the other side of the
street will definitely be
safe I would say he was alive
any you piece of garbage man oh he's
very strong he punches strong like f
is wait then I shouldn't put my bike
there no my bike will come back right
yes I think what uh I need okay I have I
have stuff to make the really good water
that's definitely orange I say so
chat anybody have spare healing eyes
actually I might be able to make one I
do have some yes I might love to grab a
bandage from you I got a
bandage a little Band-Aid M oops use
mommy band
make it better
please thank you thank you ma'am all
right use
this
[Music]
Bo which always makes it
better oh we're cooking this is far
enough
surely yeah
maybe I can't really cook anything good
I can make some water though that's
might as well while we're I'm going to
make
some oh do you have normal water okay
when you're when you make your normal
water yeah you can use that when done
I'll make the good water when it's done
yeah actually I could probably make
Spam
spam spam I mean I'm about to get a
cease and assist from spam everything is
made of zombie flesh oh my gosh I think
it's commentary
does that absolve you of any
legal I don't know it's a great question
okay Gua we're over here coming I found
a paint brush to paint blocks like
building blocks that's exciting you guys
see the yellow circle yes yes okay good
so the treasure is somewhere in here
treasure orang and the circle gets
smaller and smaller but every time that
uh you dig a certain amount of holes I
guess the there's a chance for zombies
to spawn oh be ready to fight so that's
what happened okay
we're oh my God a
jumper oh
really we can probably
leave area yeah people with guns going
to have to take care of the ones you you
can you can get out of the perimeter
like a few me
May oh does anyone have aair kits I do I
have one on I might need at least one
okay we got level thank you we can help
you
out oh we get clay from these digging
quests nice that's good nice what do we
need clay for uh for the forge as well
ah just good to have in the Forge mhm oh
it says you're getting close oh more
Sponge watch out
hello oh
God
[Applause]
jumper
yo getting too close for comfort please
stay
away I need eyes on my back I need a
back eye
I got
you my need work on my
stamina
ow has this always been here we're
getting close to treasure though nice
head thank you wow FPS Pro
Tak rip ball
BL yeah Sheriff need a little more
cardio I think I heard oh yeah oh
hello I just one just one guy
got one gu one guy it's always one guy
beep that one guy yeah one guy beep him
yeah
him we're getting close the treasure
there's a lot watch out
[Music]
watch oh W okay oh
gosh I'm oo low HP
oh God it's chaos they're on fire that
girl is on
fire yeah let's make him a grave B here
in the Tren P push the bodies into the
grave he died in a very seductive
pose looking
good noise very close I
think so close I'm hungry I'll eat some
Aon is cooking oh yeah get in there yum
yum rest in peace Yum Yum's right there
rest in pizza oh
Pizza I have one piece of pizza in my on
oh I'm going to invite you to the party
oh no yeah yeah yeah not don't noce
no oh oh nice one yeah shotgun oh
boy the shotgun feel too e not as much
as a b that's the best you're stinky go
shower smelly smelly cob
man okay this is in
peace I
know we are a great
team oh oh they can't mess with
us yeah I think for tier three they get
pretty deep
shovel they said we're getting close to
the treasure so they said that like 10
minutes ago though look you're getting
close more more
uhoh leave us I'm running low on
[Applause]
HP oh watch out watch out
jump oh God did you get hit no I don't
think
so yo the hole is as big as the
Circle I
know yeah we must be close is we have to
be that box doesn't appear past Stones
does anyone else have any repair kits I
do F come
here here hold on I got you than uh
where my repair kits go no wait a minute
oh hold on I had one oh no that's okay
you gave me the one I think I had two
but I may have given you I may have
two sorry about that but B has one we'll
make a bunch
more thank you get back to the
house not that
expensive we must be getting close we
must be right oh we getting close to the
treasure oh oh wait is
this I think so hold up
fast right
now oh no no the bullets
you oh God
e oh wow I exploded his whole body that
was
wacky he dude that man is in pieces nice
one B this one's
scary up I got him she's
scary what she's just a cosplayer
she's
scary be sad that you're saying that
about her she's inspired by
you she she needs to learn some con
rules about
interaction wearing deodorant and
showering
please it's a public service
announcement I have no be this way I'm
oh I'm not doing so well
healthwise my my leg I know my KNE stay
don't worry about the Battle we'll take
care of the
battle no no
no
gaha have to protect and
attack getting close to
the wait they're here they're here
again oh they're going the hole oh God I
don't know how far we can go this is a
hard Quest I can't switch my
weapon why is it
lagging oh I'm
bleeding I'm a Bandon I got it's okay
it's I got one I got one a thank
you oh yikes oh
man
fire okay okay okay okay that's okay I
deserve it I've been hitting my friends
all day it's
fine I can take some bullets for my
friends
y oh this lady's still alive hold
up nice okay I'll I'll stay out here now
because I'll be ready with my machine
gun okay you want to protect it must be
close it's got to be
[Music]
somewhere oh that it oh there it is yeah
that must be it sech
the oh what's this
but
was you you could have was it one for
everybody it should be one for everybody
I think it's one for everyone uh o armor
triple pocket wa they're back they're
back
magazine oh I don't want to die in the
in the digging Quest wait before you Lun
there's a lot of them okay uh you guys
can look through there oh sorry I think
I I shot
bi uhoh oh they're all down there oh
they're all in the hole oh they want the
treasure
too okay actually that's really good
yeah they can't attack us down
there yeah
dummies um there's some interesting
schematics in there kir if you like
making like armor and stuff like that I
think I'll check it out armor
scha no no no no no no
take what more
more I think it will stop if everybody
takes the chest thing right take take
your chest take yourest I couldn't yet
oh God I'm going to die wait no I just
took everything out if we can look at it
later yeah look at it later okay I got
it it's over it's so over in a good way
OU ouch ouch it hurts everything oh we
got like a like a last rush or what is
going on go away
oh no oh god oh no no
no do we fail the quest I don't know we
already got the
treasure
free I think we finished it as long as
you
grab no no yeah we should be fine well
that's kind of crazy we're still
here oh my God that's rough
every time someone takes their Quest
item it spawns zombies
[Music]
apparently that'll do it oh dear oh it's
so hot oh no there's a lot of them still
um we it's okay we still we still
finished the quest cuz we got the item
yeah are you guys around I'm I'm oh I'm
oh my gosh hold on just keep hiding keep
hiding keep
hiding okay
this is like the worst enemy ever why is
it so hot
now I already wear my clothes wow he
wasn't flinching at all with my with my
bat hyper powerered
zombies still alive oh nice got some
loot
gosh oh yay I have some be boo ammo oh
yes please I used a lot I leveled up
again got a very very powerful schematic
not schematic mod I wanted to tell you
about it's it's pocket three which
increases your carrying capacity by
three I just feel like it's not a
schematic no it's a mod you can install
it into your armor I feel like we should
decide who gets this somehow cuz it's a
very it's a very good mod yeah I know
maybe we have I already have pocket too
so I don't need it you're good
you can have it for now like yeah is it
okay we'll find more we'll find more
take this one yeah we'll find more
always if it's okay with you guys I
would like to install it if I can but
are you are you uh taking down the
cooking
station um why oh wait was it oh just
because we all died so we almost all of
us died so we probably don't need food
the water ah did you guys get your
supplies
yes I'll make some food maybe oh can I
can I have the water for the uh pure
water yes you can cancel the Sham if you
want I'll cancel it oh my God my gun
already almost broken at all these nerds
gathered around the
campfire isn't it okay I have a I have a
Bandelier mod what's that
bandier uh reload 15% faster oh wait
it's a you have to read it and learn how
to craft it we crafts like weapons stuff
I can have magazine extender mod
schematic okay I'll learn those I think
that's handgun stuff I'm pretty
sure I need to get the next level of
shotgun I hope I can get that oh I have
four skill
points oh yeah skill points we we
leveled really fast with those tier
three Quest like I'm
already in well well into the next level
dang all right we can uh come back for
the fire I made a marker on the map so
okay we can go do another one another
okay uh there's mine to the right to the
E chat is there anything for like
getting more magazines for workstations
or is that is there no skill point that
uh would
like connect with that I have beast mode
strength I almost have completely maxed
out strength that's
big big boss thanks
CH you can become the Beast of Darkness
okay there's one quest to the east we
can go to and then come back into
it y I'm leveling I'm getting closer oh
I need more repair kids does anyone have
any more I have I have two left I you
one one Kara here's an armored magazine
I found it in a pile of garbage there
you go thank you welcome wait my bicycle
is the other where is it yeah the other
way I'm on my way soon but yeah I
repaired my my machine gun like 20
minutes ago and it's already about to
break again
soon yeah we can craft a bunch at home
right not stage
80 what the heck yeah I don't know like
we really don't need to do so many
quests we could like work on farms and
stuff yeah I need to do quests but
still I personally just need to level up
I'm going go hit that Traer it is pretty
late though oh what should we do the
well I'm at my tier three clear already
we can do that and then we can head
back Oh you mean late in the game
already yeah day 2 four
uh oh but no 28 is when the raid happens
right comes yeah oh we're fine still Yes
okay I'm going to go to where bioo is
then I want to
help threes kaha you should open this
mailbox okay there's a mailbox here but
I think I realized why I'm barely
getting workstation magazines myself I I
still need to put one skill point into
the particular
[Music]
oh but that's oh this is four star okay
four y it wasn't bad we did we did a all
we done this one no we haven't done this
one
should know I'm scared where is he
anyway
uh huge for me yeah pretty good
Quest okay it has started we really got
to try and enforce the base better I
think with like Cobblestone and stuff oh
they're coming out of the graves they're
coming out of the graves oh I've done
this this is the one I did and died what
on your own no wonder hello
doggy
oh he might die
too I can tell you what's going to
happen
um spoiler alert bad in the house
there's a point where like 10 zombies
fly out of a room so okay we'll watch
out I was about to say get excited how
did you survive this outside part in the
first
place watch out jum watch
out
a yeah so it's in here I broke down the
door last time but maybe there's a
different
[Music]
way peacefully taking there's a
cooler with murky water in it if anyone
wants murky water uhoh well I think
we're past murky water at this point no
we're not no are you leaving behind no
no no the cooler by the by the campfire
outside get ready they all come from
that room oh there's a big guy
what is
this looks interesting get
ready they're coming oh okay should we
fight them outside outside might be good
oh who we outside it might be
better
beautiful okay okay okay okay the popo
guy is still alive almost dead oh you
guys destroy it was just two people yeah
it was that bad why did I get like 10
zombies then that's not fair did they
maybe sent less outside towards you oh I
have a
workstation uh book here you go yeah
workstation let's go you lucky
bastard nice where uh you lucky people
there you want to open this that's uh oh
yeah that's the right one let's go
there's polymers in here that
there's this you can
open handgun
ammo oh there was a roaming horde I
guess I just got unlucky really oh no
yes well we also
have I was someone doing sled Hammer uh
yes I was I am oh okay I'm going to drop
it in the bathroom uh fauna in this box
is I think you do you do no wait who did
electrical traps I do electrical traps
here's the get hammered magazine on the
floor next to the toilet ke thank you so
you can get hammered oh you
CED I'll get
hammered yeah only you can do it being
hammered is my St standard stance right
now uh there's a lot of stuff in this
vehicle there's vehicle Adventures um in
this chest
um there's there's Miner gloves for
heavy armor if anybody using heavy armor
it's Miners and and kiaha ammo in this
chest thanks oh sorry the chat's been in
the weird place the whole
time
[Music]
sorry
uh wait uh uh we didn't open
this oh yeah the lock chest no no the
passing gas oh no it's open it's open no
the passing gas wasn't open oh the one
below wasn't open oh
did she logged in don't C
bike
uh I'm so
cucumber okay I guess I'll take this
um yo is there a doggy outside I heard a
doggy I like it he goes oh oh there's a
there's a hord coming in uhoh Yik from
the front Watch Out
uhoh
Boy that's a new one one here you
there's more there's more there's more
Dr something
[Music]
good
nice minor boots minor gloves we have
almost a full
set oh I can't move
oh I am hurt yeah nice one Kiara burn
him yeah burn him to a chis so we can
make more Sam sandwiches oh I got a
work awesome why is everybody getting
these now I don't know you need brass
for Stuff uh probably can somebody take
this drop loot I'm so I really can't
move anymore there's Pistol Pete I bet
that I bet you could use that Bab thank
youa go here's your book Thank
you see we're so strong
together
yippe there's cloth in here as well as
harvesting tools I don't know if
anyone's using harvesting tools
but no I right I'm not
really Skilling into that oh okay I'll
just take it I got a ble hello you
welcome yay yay I found it on the
floor party more
coincidence Hong Kong Hong Kong press X
press x x yay y
[Music]
why can't I change some setting chest
chat I can't switch with the mouse wheel
anymore
weird for even more Quest I'll probably
have to go back to the new house cuz I
have to drop off stuff I'm pretty much
ready to drop stuff off okay I want to
hit the trader first first it's closed
right now oh it is closed should we find
like a residence to like because we're
so far
away yeah
maybe C wait you use shotguns cie me I
have ammo I found a for head was it you
oh yes yes here you're getting so many
now wait oh damn it I'm going to run
back to the fire that's on the way oh
yes oh the fire you mean that fire um
campfire Oh I thought you meant the can
fire fire a canned fire yeah there's a
fire full there's a canned fire over
that's fine oh this house is on fire too
what the heck
oh wow lot of fire sorry I was stoning
out we we are looking for a house
now um we probably should like close to
the Traer yeah close to the to the Bob
we should probably find a house to like
start hunkering down over there cuz it's
really really far now we make bring the
like Kitchen pot and stuff yeah let's go
sounds good did the water finish yes it
did yay nice would you like some or all
yeah I'll take some I made it for
everybody okay there's some thank
you this way this way okay back to
Trader B yeah well should we set up a
new house like I guess we don't need to
go back if we make a new house yeah we
need to set up a new one let's go near
the trader and see if there's a house by
there
Al I feel like then all of our like
resources and items will like be so
scattered again and we'll have to go so
far to pick something up is why we need
to get a helicopter eventually yeah
yeah I I'm going to still try to bring
all my supplies to the new
house okay okay
yeah it is tough when all your stuff is
all spread out I wish we had like ender
chests in this game yeah maybe there's
maybe we cars have big
trunks there's so
many cars should have huge trunks we can
put a bunch of supplies do Supply runs
and stuff M that' be great I wonder if
we can make cars at this
point we can make many bikes I suppose
but I don't think we all any of us know
how to make a car yet
would that be fun yeah at what CH at
what level can I make a
car cuz my vehicle skill is at
31 that seems pretty good decent start
yeah I think you need three to make a
bike so you
want oh I can make a mini bike right now
so
motorbike what do you mean to make
it wait let me check in a moment
is it no you can't just repair your it
requires a workbench to craft from
scratch mini bike well Two Wheels One
minibike ches mini bike handlebars
engine and elite car battery it's not
too bad I handlebar old house we have a
couple of those things yeah mhm and she
also uh or Bob somebody will give us
mini bike parts it seems as a reward
right yes uh oh there's a diner nearby
the uh we can hunker down here maybe the
greasy spoon oh actually I can I can
craft the the parts as well it's a it
looks like a nice
reinforced place they got
AOH watch out or
not burgers fries
said I love
fries yucky versatile you the fries no
no somebody the dude was burping at me
oh oh okay maybe I can repair it
here oh wow you cut her head
off it's pretty
impressive holy all right we're taking
this place over
no so such a beautiful sight to
behold oh watch out I stabbed you you
might be bleeding oh I'm going to die
uh-oh no oh no if you get hit once by me
you're you're going to bleed out that's
rough I hope my quest didn't go away it
shouldn't if it didn't if it didn't
start it won't it won't go away okay I
can't carry anything does somebody want
to take these things out of these chests
I don't have space at I get for trying
to be are we going to set up here at
least a temporary yeah let's put some
boxes down okay I'm going to make a
fire honestly I might just put the food
in this cabinet here you can put the
fire in the kitchen and then it's like
real RP yeah ooh ah it works again will
I get electrical shock let's see
no o Lumberjack oh I found three armor
parts that's huge nice nice
better than my current
boots yeah better stamina
regen does anybody have wood for
crates yes okay aat I will also there's
a shamway shipping crate mhm oh maybe we
can use that crate for storage yeah we
can oo
oh yeah we can okay we'll just put stuff
in here for now why did
we ah don't forget the land claim box or
the stuff might despawn that's right oh
yes how do you make
that oh I can make
one the land has been claimed by FAA
there's a murky water in the soda
fountain eat some murky water we boiling
some
water I have a shotgun thingy Kelly is
active shotgun I'll take it like a
shotgun magazine shot my fave here thank
you to
you any more repair kits on at hand
ladies oh I don't think so we might need
I I have one but I might need it to
oh shoot I might need that for my
baseball
pad I'll try and make one I go back oh
if I had duct tape I could make
one blue I blue and cloth I have extra
kniv I I can actually give you mine I
don't need it that soon thank
you m my machine gun is on zero thank
you appreciate it oh if I could only
pick it
up need cotton we won't find that in the
desert one cloth fragment I can make
duct
tape oh it's good it's fine 9 mm ammo on
the floor if someone needs it oh I need
it thank you yeah it's about to be
morning go headit up the traitor ah yeah
he's going to be open
soon oh I hear zombie I got him hello
big tummy zombie I got medical
journal thank you
yes okay I'm I'm going to the
Traer Trader Trader Trader traitor turn
in
stuff oh
gosh in quest I'll help you thank
[Music]
you I knew that would get me thank you I
live to
protect I was just exploring there there
were zombies on the roof you'll be
protected
they were on our
house oh there's a after the
traitor open up Let Me In when do we get
to meet Trader
Joel Trader Jen let me in open open open
you're late he needs to announce he's
open first you're late he's waking up
he's brushing his teeth Wasing his face
faster get 5 minutes later
out
ah
unel fixing to show a good
old it's about time he seems to be the
vehicle man oh high power Magnum ammo
that's pretty good but I feel like get
Magnum ammo you'll get offered that
maybe yeah you don't need to take it
from me I can take
it can I make two of these 10 lock
picks uh infection might be
better I'll take the lockpicks wait
water purifier mod allows safe
consumption of murky water o oh that's
that's the hat that F has definitely get
that more hats in it more magical
hats this a freaking Katana that's crazy
a what a what tempered blade but you
might get offered it too I don't think
it's a katana though
let's
see what does the number in the right
corner in the bicycle mean what says 27%
27% of what oh it's your bicycle's
durability you can heal it using repair
kit
okay going to
break feel music armored up
I have a hammer one for here I'm going
to drop the magazines here that I don't
need hand got magazine early
today thank also for you thank
you oh shotgun crafting skill anyone me
okay I need that
awesome
yay I can make double barrel shotgun
quality
6 with the legendary part maybe I should
have given that to gigy oh well next
time oo she has like a monster truck in
the back here here's your handgun
magazines oh thank you does anyone want
a shotgun duck bill mod schematic recipe
maybe I could take that cooking
magazines anybody's a different option
Mor's going to learn how to cook really
learn how to cook yes I'm going to learn
how to
cook okay I can make grilled corn and
baked potatoes ree good now I can help
thank
you okay all right I
will take a job but I will not do
it I think I've got a few I have armored
magazines I was about to run away
explosive
magazines uh that's um B bio I think b b
yes B Mama boooo boo boo baba I can
drink dirty water oh thank
you
cute H okay what armor level am I good
question think he's got that tap 100
armor level
[Music]
100 I can make legendary armor if you
guys give me the parts y yay
YY whoa what did I just
do I ripped out something let's freaking
go oh I leveled
up ready he loves Vehicles
huh he's got all the nice vehicle stuff
also I took some
quests some to if you guys want to run
through quests
what did I
do oh you're very quiet right what did I
do oh now you're
better I wonder
why oh I can make steel KN wait can I
make steel Knuckles now somebody else is
looking at their inventory I can't look
through it oh I'm looking one
okay uh the was is it he
has batter up volume sa Club have a 20%
chance to rag doll enemies if you're
interested that's big here I'll let you
look thank you I definitely need
that big hits
okay batter up volume six that's
huge okay thank you very much for
letting me know B yeah I'm going to he
does have repair kits I think buying
those might be a good idea I bought a
couple yeah buy repair kits that's
always
good check for Crucible is the guy
selling any crucibles right
now Crucible I don't I didn't see any
when I looked right I didn't see any
[Music]
either we buy and sell vehicles
mechanical Parts you're looking at the
right have any okay I'm going to new
house probably not going to do any more
quests today just going to clean up
stuff and do like productive
stuffie
doie I didn't realize almost been 3
hours right it goes like so fast I
know what the heck I didn't even realize
time is really flown I why when you're
playing this
game
okay do you help
with um I I I just bought a rep kit
because I was like oh no what if I
bought
the
bicycle um I don't really have I have a
good like um gear or weapons so that
might be kind of nice do you do you want
a a shotgun double barrel shotgun it's a
pretty good one yeah fire twice and then
I'll give you some ammo for it here 25
and I'll give you a little more hold
up there go thank you it's so far
thank
you let me put that here oh there it
is that should help you oh the mini bike
PES is
expensive mini bike but I can make the
parts too um it's not even can you craft
the parts yeah the parts and the mini
bike itself
so I don't know if I can make one for
everybody with our current materials but
I can check
I'm on my way Wawa armor
shop oh this is a quest place I'm going
to try it once I'm spending all my money
oops you want to try on
me do you want to
try yeah why not okay okay can you jump
here around and be a moving Target okay
okay okay try to catch me try to catch
me this is like a video game tutorial
try to catch me
T you missed you missed Miss then you
got to
reload ow oh you didn't miss that time
oh I hit you you did hit me do you want
me to kill me though yeah actually kill
me cuz
yeah oh one sec I need to
reload that awesome good job yeah
yay well Kara wants to go do some
housekeeping would anybody like to run
on a couple more quests with my just
because I'm a little bit behind I'm down
yeah I can't really that much but now
that I have a gun I can shoot a bit yeah
we got stuff to do yes we have
responsibilities
farming well I also can't get on
tomorrow um so I'm also kind of like
maybe I should try and level up as much
as possible oh you'll miss the
raid it's tomorrow yeah should ah dang
it okay well that's too bad I'm sure you
guys will be fine but the last day I
think that we should play all the way
through until a raid
happens okay do you want to do this
clear tier three clear North that's your
quest kie yes okay we'll go
there I I think it's yeah North
Northwest yes yes I'm so fast we're so
fast look at this so fast
[Music]
faster than
you
loser that's not very
nice next time I stab you it won't be an
accident wa does that mean that tomorrow
before tomorrow Ra was an accident
before and then the next stream will the
next stream after the tomorrow stream
will be the last one with like two
shifts combined basically yep okay yeah
I think tomorrow since we're timed a
little bit oddly the
The Horde will be in the middle so then
the last day will be a little bit longer
than the others but not like six seven
full hours
yep okay last day let's make a count
yeah but we got to look into uh if
there's any way to keep the server alive
until we want to do season like keep the
characters I don't know if the server
has to be kept active so to
say or if there's any other way to keep
the characters cuzz I don't know I don't
want to lose all this progress yeah
right
yeah as long as we don't like AFK play
and stuff we should all keep our stuff
right then we can ask them I don't know
because they probably have to pay for
the server and I don't know if they'll
pay for it if we're not accely playing
if the server gets like temporarily like
put on hold wipers yeah we'll have to
check that out if there's any yeah yeah
we should ask I feel like they should be
able to save the server like even if
it's not online hope file should be okay
yeah be we got we got pretty invested in
it
too me and
Fa yeah pretty also got really into it I
play yesterday not yesterday
tomorrow I have been playing every day
so far but tomorrow I just cannot sadly
that's fine you need a break too by the
way are you crazy like playing Dark
Souls and seven days to die in one day
when you have scouring in your
lungs what no I I like Dark Souls yeah
but do you really have to play two times
in a day
girl I can relate I
understand but bibo do you have scarring
in your lungs
no well well I did I did play Elder ring
that one time without a voice but it's
just it's just the you know the game it
just makes you want to you know gamer a
game doing another stream today I
thought about doing another stream today
but I decided not thank God I'm cooking
tomorrow for some friends
say cooking cooking let her cook they
wanted to eat like really healthy stuff
so I'm doing like chicken with like
really delicious sauce and like bunch of
green
vegetables a bunch of veggies and then
ricotta cheese salad with
walnuts and then yuck Dingle for dessert
which is like uh it's like fried apple
with Raisin and cinnamon oh yum yum yum
yum yum yum I'm always hungry when I
play this game cuz I I don't eat dinner
before it and you are the Cook I you
don't have you don't have to it's over
here oh and there's a hole in the ground
too let's go oh oh okay yeah that's
easier there's a hole try to take it
easy I wanted to play tomorrow so bad
but I can't will you take it
easy when spoiler she does not
take I'm just having so much fun you
can't be helped
same oh I hope we get to play again we
should make a chest only for car Parts
cuz it's getting a lot we should yeah I
do kind of want to organize our chest
yeah we need
more what how to I bet we have having a
bunch of hidden stuff we can't find it
cuz it's all over the
place
what creepy lab where they're making
pills that's nuts oh fun I got a I got a
knuckle magazine for you thank
you on a punch
water there's a guy in a radioactive
suit what does it mean know he's dead
fore I got Forge ahead Ki Oh okay I'll
bring it to you yeah uh how do you name
a
box uh hold e and then drag it to the
naming option
ah kill it dead kill it dead
ow dead sorry I did not see that i' hit
you in the head oh
boy I mean I don't know know an off one
though what is car
part
Dead Oh up here Up on the Roof oh
baby oh there someone there is he alive
there must be dudes are you alive ah oh
that was you scared
me oh yes there's a lot there's a lot
get
ready uh we've got so much
sham oh they all have they look weird
why do they look like that these are
crazy zombies
who uh these are kind of wild okay did
not expect like
that I got minor boots and minor gloves
I wonder who might like these Sky yeah
maybe oh gosh I'm Radioactive radio
no radioactive oh
okay he's very strong I was going to be
careful
wait killed him oh there's another one
oh not done yet though is it oh it's not
in there I thought it
was a great stash does anyone have a
um lockpick oh I do there's a box here I
got 10 actually I need to use this o I
can make the fort bites now these are
really nice for Buffs fortnite
bikes fortnite bites fornite for bites
maybe I don't have the
lockpicks oh I'm lockpicking it all
right you got it B you got this Kelly
are you carrying your legendary Parts on
your own like inventory or did you put
them somewhere I am I haven't had a
chance to go back home oh okay cuz
there's some here an our chest what is
it a Time charge I have like a time bomb
oo a time
bomb taking time bombs
yeah the legendary Parts though
everybody's eventually going to get a
weapon that they're really really good
with they might want to upgrade to level
six and if you want to upgrade it to
level six you need legendary parts to do
it so I kind of want to see if we can
hold on to them if
possible indeed okay the area is not yet
clear by the way carry anymore it's not
clear there's still zombies around oh
and I still need to find my supplies too
okay
let's see I
wonder where did we miss somebody oh I
also have to do for me it gives a check
mark but uhoh oh no we did clear the
area I just need to find my supplies
okay oh okay it's confused I I
see you think I'll get break my leg if I
jump yeah probably yeah I got hurt
yourself nice oh I'm
done nice CE did you find yours no I see
it on the map but it's like hiden I
think behind some of these locked doors
probably a little bit organized I don't
know what this is for sandwich in your
dreams car parts you need help break it
open a door car parts car parts no I'm
just trying to figure out what level
this is on
Parts bye
oh apparently we can do this Mission
Again somebody took the same one oh it's
it's K classic oh ki's Mission oh oh
yeah I'm not there so yeah okay I'm
going to leave the we we can go to the
other one though we go to the yeah if
you guys want to yeah not there's one to
the I'll Follow You Vio for the next one
okay
[Music]
does anyone have food oh actually you
can kill me oh I do you want to die yeah
I died earlier it's fine kill me oh
really okay end it you sounded so
excited about that she's like yep leave
it to me I'll kill you I was a bit too
happy I can't believe I don't know about
all
that um trying to make some space I feel
like the do collector is still so slow
even with two
upgrades come on do something maybe we
have to like make a bunch of them or
something yeah I'm guessing it's it's a
beginner item so we just have to make a
bunch of D is there no better
[Music]
one okay I'm I'm back I'm fine I'm
alive all right B will Le the way okay
you're 100 on Armor already right Kiara
yes okay I'll just learn them then I
can't get over 100 right Chad or is also
learning armor as well just for my own
self just a little bit we can share
them can't go over 100 okay too bad okay
we're going to the Nast if I were to I I
why am I lagging it's going
insane yay new weapon for me oh God they
look
terrifying nice new steel
Knuckles
oh that bike definitely needs repairs
maybe I'll make
one I wonder what's
necessary for what for bike repairs oh
just a repair kit oh really oh this nice
let me it's one it's it's one of the
options when you hover over it like with
e just got to click repair you did it
yay thank
you
yes uh you don't have your Rader gloves
yet do
you um no I don't I'll make you some on
level six level six yeah well we'll go
all the
way
a
e let's go your level six nice sorry for
tomorrow fored iron
for okay it's this one this place the
food Tru stop Diner oh oh this one has
four skulls so what we definitely want
CeCe to be here with us I think CeCe I'm
right here hello
here watch out for the barb wire fence
bird oh nice shot nice shooting text
than I'm very
cucumber B do you have some more Forge
steel
[Music]
somewhere might be good at
some this
chest do the Traders sell steel for
steel yes they they they sell Forge
steel it's kind of expensive though but
it's like 150
per I see
we need to oh there's already a doer
coming out I bet he'll reset though when
we start the mission yeah hold on I
am very
heavy okay it's getting cleaner
here I'm going to
start you going to started yeah okay
okay it has
started hello ladies could make it a
little lower level that also needs Ste
it's a
diner well I
mean
yummy for now okay I'll make it on level
five fauna oh that's horrific okay thank
you oh I found a big Treasure Chest oh
he's
alive that's horrifying a skelan
zombie don't oh oh oh there's a bunch of
them hard yeah bring them bring them out
here it might be easier to fight him
alive it's not a time to leave there's a
lot of guys please move sir behind you
get ready lots and lots of guys in
there I wonder if I can solo the boar oh
jumper jum soloing the boar I want to I
mean that's awesome but you him you can
do it I want his meat I don't know I
though we have yeah that dude just won't
die oh there's a bunch
the door with the rad gloves you can
probably kill him did you run I mean
definitely better than what you
have hello there's a locked Crate by the
way that I found oh okay don't here okay
I will unlock it look at the ammo
there's some good stuff in
there medical I'm going to read the
medical journal use one of these just
for funsies
well they buff my
damage not that
far yeah you find in there and you have
a full
wa what's in
there measure hunter that gives exp
bonus oh I got iron Knuckles do you use
iron knuckles
for um not
anymore okay oh she's upgraded I have
upgraded I found on the forge head too
nice cloth we're always need a new cloth
hunting rifle that seems like it might
be
good a
crossbow or is down here didn't we have
a chassis chassis this might be a bad
idea no you got this okay we have plenty
of easy just like talk to him like say
say taunt him taunt him what there's
more freaking
Bo this
one wait I like three shot him wait
never mind I just stunned him never mind
never
mind not quite
a they drop oh I killed him shotgun we I
do I can make a p a pump shotgun now
guys y Pump It Up also there's some loot
over here bi Boo full of ammo for you oh
okay mm it's uh right in front of the
counter there's a yellow bag yeah oh 40
night look
shoes that's some drip that's some drip
I think yeah we completed again good job
team oh shy can make
a I guess
not I got to make this how many can this
hold I wonder
cat it up why your feet on the I wonder
if we shoot this everything's going to
explode which one I will make a pum gas
St do we try
out wait wait wait wait let me put my
bicycle somewhere
else wait oh it has hold on hold on hold
on
[Music]
a oh you guys exped the whole place it
did
work ooh crushed
sand don't know what that is but hey
maybe it's useful this one again crushed
sand let's just take everything okay I'm
going to tra to turn and then to clear
my storage oh
bunny easily distracted go the Traer I
might go back to the
house make a
couple I'm kind of a menace now I feel
bad tra come here let me make you even
more into a menace okay I'm just getting
some food for us lots of food where the
gloves
go wait am I still drunk I should fight
them while I'm drunk
drunk can fist
brawling oh this will take a while do it
faster no I have too much monkey W
that's
me that's
you I'm making a mini bike right
now I'm excited to see what it looks
like yeah wonder how fast it's going to
be no Zoom
around
Zoomies I'll be the fastest in these
lands for now I'll make more though I
think I can make a couple
maybe Ranger outfit that looks
good let me see if I can make some
bandages it gets laggy when I go into
that it's generally laggy here weird
need a little more
oh it's a little better for Max Health
Wheels oh we might not have so many
wheels didn't we have more can you craft
a wheel there Wheels all over the place
all around the desert it seems like but
can you actually pick those up or do you
have to
like I'll see if I see another one out
yeah for science
please oh I feel so bad why why why I'm
killing pigs that's
okay thiry they're cute though no
they're not even radioactive they're
normal then they're probably sad and
thirsty and taking them out of the I
guess they are probably sad and thirsty
yeah must be
it okay I think I think tires only give
plastic if you beat them think they give
Tire tires okay no problem I found a
couple
more and we can make Wheels ourselves
with a oh quite a oh it takes a few
quite a few things a lot of stuff around
here bags oh I lost the bicycle I don't
know where I put it
no isn't it
borrowed you shouldn't lose it um where
did it
go oh God it's gone
a bicycle I lost it uh do you see an
icon like a yellow icon for the oh yeah
I do I do okay okay okay okay I found it
I found
it make them like you course they can
like you the every day what am I
doing sorry guys I'm all over the
place that's okay me
too probably go back to the house pretty
soon
is is very far away but it can't be
helped should take the B well you can
you can use the new house to temporarily
store some stuff yeah temporary little
base yeah it will be too good huh let's
use that for a real car
o any is fine
okay this is all stuff that's good for
bioo but not for me oh
I'll take it still for generators are
selling oh interesting thank you visual
magnification here we
go mini bike is being crafted right now
[Applause]
y maybe I'll make one more I think I can
make one more for
[Music]
sure e
H what's
that a furious fist I got a bunch of
good stuff for you guys so I'm just
going to go back to the
house this point duct tape I want to
throw stuff away why is it always a duct
tape bike wait the bike well it's fine I
got enough
stuff a dog what the dog doing a dog are
you going to attack me dog doing it's
attacking me I'm going to have to kill
it did anybody anybody here in this VC
learn how to make an EXT wait was it me
did anybody learn how to make an extra
minibike
seat I thought you learned did I I gave
it to you did you use it I got a vehicle
expanded seating mod but is
car I don't know I don't know does it
not work for the mini bike did you use
it I didn't use it I I used it but I
didn't make it yet Ah that's it okay
okay that works for bicycle b mini bikes
too it seems mini bike we can ride
[Music]
together then we'll save I mean we're
always going everywhere together so we
don't need two B bikes huh eco-friendly
e friendly with the bikes
awesome okay heard who's killing dogs I
just heard a very sad dog s there were
sad dog noises happening the whole time
at that diner for some weird reason oh
we're in the desert it's strange it's
just they're trying to go for the scraps
and then I taste them like oh this is
disgusting wait what am I doing then
they run away
again let's make a
couple yep I'm only roed up for seven
more minutes so I got to hurry up and
get home so I can put this stuff
away oh wait oh it makes two at a time
now I think do I put the fuel into the
bike guess
so how much I wonder does it
take
fun look at
these thank you
I wonder what bonus you get oh but ah
you're not wearing the top but you have
the top I know is it worth it to get the
bonus to sacrifice the
XP maybe not on Hite
% not sure they do say that the set
bonuses in this game are not like that
worth it mixing armor is better but
reduces the chance of critical injuries
by 20% I mean that is pretty good yeah I
think it's less complicated to just wear
one full set so why not yeah that's true
I look pretty scary
one, gas
wow surely we have more
elsewhere oh hold up oh no
coughing I'm okay I definitely wasn't
coughing that not
coughing definitely not oh I collected a
lot so
far um
Yos okay I think I can make this one
more bik look at that building look
crazy wa wait you're not behind me I
thought you were behind me oh me no I
lost you let's go I'm in the I'm in the
Traer guy oh okay okay okay oh gosh oh
where
giant giant building
looks like a
factory oh God be careful there
hey what is that scream that's a crazy
scream oh she's at our window she's in
our bushes whoa you guys got a screamer
yeah no wonder they're called
screamers be careful there's another one
coming a she'll punch them it'll be good
punch him with those new gloves yeah
M I'm feeling strong you are and it's
[Laughter]
hot e do you have some extra claw
fragments yes oh hujjah wait another
screamer here you
go where are you I'm almost home in the
the bathroom the former bathroom ah
thank
you zombies I will will defeat them she
closes the door behind her I'm on my way
stay back I'll take care worry guys whoa
but but it sounds like a lot are you
sure I'm strong okay that's true
probably let me just drink some beer
ow oh there's a zombie in the house uhoh
uhoh that's bad I I'll take care of the
one
[Music]
inside was it oh the door was open oh
the door is gone
door is gone he's throwing up oh it's a
police one inside the house are you here
too yeah you here oh
hi
hey welcome home oh he's out oh there's
a
okay yeah we need a new door in the back
uh that cannot be
safe is it over
I think so think so okay I have some
ammo for you
Ki thank
you oh gosh I have so much stuff this BM
is kind of cool they can keep this
running oh yeah I put some Furious Fists
uh in the books thank you yeah books
chest what am I doing ah G
[Music]
powder all
right two
bikes crushed sand I don't really know
what that's for but I'm going to put it
in here maybe give to
bio hey you didn't hear it yet I found a
car battery
bio yes I shall donate to you the
second uh bike because I'm sure you'll
enjoy it y yay thank
you I will not crash it into a fight
actually I think I can also make an
extra seat for your bike so you can also
take people with you I'm coming
home I ah oh if only I had more if you
can bring me more cloth fragments I can
make you a bite an extra
seat okay I'll Che I'll check if Jen has
one
well
done there's some good stuff in here can
i d the bike surely I can I want to put
some color on
it to make it
distinguishable wasn't there some
Dy
okay I guess I'll make it Pink iron in
that Forge or can we have yellow dye
yes there is yellow dye oh then you
should take the pink dye bio should I Dy
your B your bike pink yes
please it'll match my bike yeah it's
more it actually does look more purple
than pink so that's perfect o where was
the yellow
dye uh let me check if can't find it dma
has one oh wait I found it I found it
I'm blind
got to make some duct tape do do you
want any more yellow dye cuz she does
have some oh no no no
need do we have any clay soil
ugly clay uh I think I put most of the
clay into the
forge dang how do we get more clay um
digging the ground gave a lot of
clay like any where yeah I mean when I
did the digging Quest it gave me a lot
of clay just from
[Music]
digging wonder how many shotgun parts we
have do we have a shotgun parts ladies
maybe I'm trying to make the best gun in
the
world where is
flashlight oh I'm outside I'm going to
dig can wait are you behind the house or
where I'm behind the
house 40 forg Steel can we sell stuff to
we can sell stuff to
her maybe we should just focus on a new
bat
instead wait wait
wait where's the
seat wait did I leave this ah wait where
is this wait for
uh one
second CE I have armor for you for me
yeah for you
are you giggling where are you let me
see I I'm coming back home
so okay we got to take a test ride maybe
not shotgun parts in
here get on fa wait it's
locked what how do I
UNL maybe we got to be in a party
you got to unlock and gas it up oh how
how
to
[Music]
wait unlock and let me put some gas
in this look so gross the bottle on the
side bye
suckers out of here [\h__\h] this apocalypse
oh my
gosh here they go
onto our honeymoon Sunset yes we need to
pick up gigy somewhere I know a we had a
third
seat no I don't think so this is pretty
romantic I look like your
bodyguard your scary bodyguard is this
even significantly faster than the
bicycle I guess so it better be if it
uses fuel right yeah you would hope
feel pretty fast this is me on I think
maximum
speed nice there much cotton before now
it's gone speed of seven b this is speed
seven bicycle with speed
five
oh wait wait wait that's race one sec on
this Main Road let's see all right how
big the difference is oh okay but wait I
I can give you the new bicycle
although it doesn't have a second seat
on it yet need to make the second seat
oh no I wanted to see the difference
between the two the normal bicycle and
the bike all right
speed
okay all right you got a head start okay
3 one
[Music]
go I'm coming for you
oh here we go oh it
lagged I'm taking
over okay okay try kovski a hole Yeah
chovi Cecilia
[Music]
IM messed up that is messed upy should
not be taking rides anyone in
Taco always end in
[Applause]
[Laughter]
pain uh
oh oh not so technologically advanced
anymore are you CC
me no I I stole this bike so what can I
say engineering genius
takana robotics I I'll make oh I hear it
I hear the engine I think you're robotic
thing has I was told something uh fauna
is replacing your robot or something oh
is this it what what was that I don't
know chat was saying something
huh should take this
CeCe you think I can steal from ra yes
I've been stealing too have you
yesterday
steal thank you we're not really
stealing it's way better than what I
have nice big water drinking B I'm going
to put you a purple bike outside for
now once I get more cloth fragments I
can put the seat on
uh where is it here I have five there
you
go I think you have to ah wait you have
to uh put some gas in it press e and put
gas and also unlock but uh you probably
don't have any gas right
now oh it's locked yeah oh I guess I
have to unlock it for you there you
go oh is there gas in it there's 2% of
gas gas in
it am I always carrying the gas does it
not go into the bike guys is this my gas
right now let's give her a
stack
um oh
yeah so ladies can we make a limited
water now okay um kind of guess kind of
cuz I'd love to make more glue if we
could we have more water it's just very
slow
oh I see glue we can make more de
collectors and then buy the upgrades but
o that might be a good
idea what do you need duct tape or what
yeah I'm making duct tape how many do
you want uh let's see I've got four so I
just need three more for the pump action
shotgun okay take from uh Forge
chest are you having fun I am having
fun fast let's go
sorry sorry there you go wait do you
take damage when you drive into people
uh try driving over here I took damage
when I hit a
[Music]
[Laughter]
tree we should put like a speed on the
front and then you can impale the
zombies could have swor we had shotgun
parts
somewhere possibly
[Music]
how many cloths do you need for that
seat got to take these level two
ones how many what how many cloth do you
need for a seat
[Music]
um uh in total 100 cloth
fragments okay M
so hit curtains and hit uh sofas and
beds everything
uh what am
I I think I can make two more
bikes you got
really have any any shotgun parts in
here I wonder if at the old house
there's any shotgun parts that might
be search I do I need more steel ow
I thought you were
dead is gas usually coming back for more
huh yeah there we
go going to the all
house is there even a point in dying in
Black
[Music]
mind these are empty could check the
trader
H oh
tomorrow if only I had handgun
Parts yeah it seems we're all looking
for certain weapon parts I wonder if the
Traders have them though we might need
to just go check the Traders yeah I wish
they had them more
easily yeah a bit hard to
find seven shotgun parts is just a lot
oh that's a lot yeah yeah yeah that is a
lot this chest
look for a pump action level one oh yeah
yeah oh there's 39 cloth fragments next
to the forge yeah I know but that's not
enough that's the only my remaining
cloth put some in too we're at 58
now we need 50 more just just a few more
um so I'm making two more bikes um but I
guess today we're ending soon so these
bikes anybody can use them
tomorrow uh and then the day after to
like whoever I'll just I'll probably
make more bikes tomorrow again if I have
time crafter thank you thank you no
problem everybody will have bikes at
some
point yeah no one bike should definitely
be Callie's bike but Callie's not online
tomorrow so that's just you know what
I'm thinking maybe I'll die this bike
black it will be yours but tomorrow
somebody else I guess can use it how
about that okay sounds fine to me I'm
just very
[Music]
grateful oh okay whoa that's a a golf
bike more yay golf bike yeah love
that my fav color after yeah let's go I
think your bike is very recognizable
like a like a lawn chair taped to a lawn
mower wait it doesn't even look so black
in reality what the
hell lame I'll unlock it
and okay uh your bike is outside and we
only need 24
24 oh
nice didn't know we had so many parts to
really make so many mini bikes yeah I
made a couple couple parts uh the the
white mini bike needs some gas so it
might not work right
now but yeah feel free to take those
bikes and have fun with them don't break
them hey thank
you I'll go try finding
some clo
and yeah
gas gas yes uh I'm going to Quest maybe
oh dear oh dear I can
help we've got
food who who rode bicycle bicycle
me cute bicycle bicycle
bicycle yeah we're really we have a good
stock of food so far very nice yeah I'm
cooking some stuff
too I want to be helpful oh there are
tons of car batteries back at the old
place too oh there's a lot of stuff here
oo um kind does the Traer closed like is
it already closed I think it's already
closed
okay if you find gas and cloth M please
bring it
gas and cloth you got it gas gas if if
the old house also has more mechanical
parts or Springs or electrical parts and
short iron pipes uh or even headlights
any of those kind of things would be
okay I'll bring them helpful I mean I I
don't need them right now but headlight
all
right oh not gas as well yeah and
mechanical Parts electric parts this all
that kind of stuff okay
if you're doing a quest I'll come with
so I can find some stuff okay um it's a
little
bit far though
vehicle we can we can raid houses on the
way to find stuff okay
okay I'm just looking for supplies right
now anyway 10 more yeah I think it would
be nice to have like Gass and stuff and
just have a
good and the chair is probably also
really handy because then when we to
when it's more than a couple people
tomorrow then or on the last day then H
H boo in your inventory there's like a
lot of stuff like handlebars and then
take it okay how about the forge steel I
know you want Forge steel though uh I
need four Forge Steel's I can give you
four oh d d oh okay well done if you
give me my four you can take the rest
thanks okay I'll get i'll gather it
together for
you I don't have any
corn I find that unusual
mhm
water a mark your water
uh oh I hear something
outside yeah he goes Raw
oh no eggs
either I think there are eggs here at
the old place let me see if I can take
them oh there's one one
EG
egg yeah okay let's let's loot this
public school oh heck yeah
okay we can jump over okay we jump over
oh we can jump over oh yeah we need a
new back
door before we
and oh I can make a lot of steak and
potatoes yeah make a ton of baked
potatoes people push me oh okay go
intact cars okay okay well I was just
going for whatever's
close is it
working it'sing here here climb climb up
this this I I'll push you down the slide
oh okay okay what what are you doing
did you get playground I'm ready I'm
[Music]
[Applause]
ready takes a while okay let's go into
the
school it's a dark I can't see anything
this one's open I'll to the left okay
let's loot the
school loot School
oh clo fragment oh
yes think we're going to oh
hello
nice oh I'm bleeding oh oh I stabbed you
I stabbed you that was my fault that was
I in front of you oh take a bandage
it'll stop the bleeding see if anybody
else this shotgun
parts I made it just in time I used it I
used it y
you didn't kill me this time don't
worry yeah cars give so many
resources did I not learn how to make
beer oh I need the I need the
thingy night we did not some I do hear
oh they're they're by the door they're
in the door this okay well it's locked
so I don't know who this belongs to wait
oh they unlocked it oh no a chem station
beer
a I mean oh my gosh it gives me 300% can
you make it what the C station 300 300%
damage wow W that is crazy
uh oh it's workstation level 50 oh oh
okay leave it to me I'll get there
eventually no not yet but hopefully soon
parts do you guys know who has who owns
the crate in the basement level of the
first house I think it's from M
I'm not the one that's in their bedroom
though it's the laundry room I'm I'm
dying oh oh are you dying
a five bottles of chemicals which are
kind of hard to find oh to make the
workstation for the
chemicals tell them I wonder where you
get those I should have been saving my
beer I was chugging it for for nothing
going to need that I have one bottle of
beer that I'll gladly give to you I'll
shoot them a message and just oh there's
so many you if they they do want
to yeah it's night time so it seems like
the ones outside are also coming oh
there's a giant bear oh my God there's a
giant bear
oh what it's like two people big be
bear it's like as big as the boar in
that other world a bear a bear a zombie
bear take a eye out surprised that's
kind of
horrific duck oh my God I see it oh my
God I see it oh my God you're having a
good time you think we can kill
it it's chasing me no
my leg is broken uh oh
no any spring I'll keep a lot
of e e oh God I'm Radioactive radio here
we go
again it's better for the environment to
use my bicycle when I can
electrical parts oh it's Day
26 it has just begun boy so yeah I mean
I think we were going to end in like 20
minutes
anyway
yeah see you okay yeah I'm behind you
I'm trying to get this bird of you okay
I'll just keep
King keep kiing him but you pulling way
and way more enemies I
think stop stop cting in a big big
circle Okay small circle small circle
okay okay okay okay I'll I'll start
shooting I have to heal thank kind of
see why they weren't cooking takes a
long
[Music]
time ow oh I have a watch out watch out
it's
over okay no it's okay they're
distracted eating my body quick I'm
going to get them all die die die die
die die
never mind uhoh uhoh that seems rough is
it worth it all that death for nothing
well we got some good
stuff find any shotgun parts no dang
it I just need four
more right
oh God oh my God there's too many of
them okay I'm going to ride away I'm
going to kite them on my
bicycle my bicycle oh my God okay yeah
kite them kite them on your bicycle I'm
going to take them out one by one okay
I'm going to do a line back and forth on
this big
road do a
line they back and forth rather than a
big circle
oh
no oh
[Music]
no
uhoh one bread fed diet in this house oh
yeah pumpkin
pie a Yi the door's back
[Music]
they so
slow make some more cornbread come
on we better get hecking exp for this
nobody needs those
right cor so
yummy uh oh it's over
it's giving me Minecraft Vibes right now
sorting these
chests or are you sorting there's a lot
to sort through there really is oh man
oh there we
wow that feels nice to click that sorts
all of it for
us can you
makeus what this crafting St no
[Music]
it's so
over seems
tough yeah we had a we had a hoard
hoard okay it's only like six left seven
eight yeah we got
it I almost leveled up so that's
actually pretty good I can't be there to
help I'm cooking cornbread right
now it's okay cornbread is important as
well oh
yeah oh is that a
[Music]
recipe secr
recipe secret
recipe I already know the secret recipe
cuz SP its to of
me secret recipe oh for for sham sham
for sham secret recipe I guess I'll make
that before I end it
today e what is that
sound oh my God why is
it is it yucky
sound my shot's broken I can't I can't
help
anymore I guess I can hit him oh nice
yay level I'm getting just so
distracted ow
no I want to stab them while they eat
you yeah get them sneak up on them give
them the old one
[Music]
too I can't make those I think we're
good can I put any of them
if I scrap this oh leather get six
leather from scraping Furniture that's
awesome yeah it seems like we really
need cloth right now mhm and Le honestly
lever to everything every material in
the
world old house should we go back inside
and get some more cloth
yeah it's daytime now so hopefully they
won't spawn so much yeah let's just
ignore the giant bear CH wait cotton
crops that get you you
cloth
M we could make a cotton Farm
too oh my God that be a good idea I
don't know if it's worth it I don't know
more cloth more duct tape
yeah I got eaten by giant dog oh that's
messed up there's a giant dog in the
school so watch out in the school schol
yeah they went to the school that's
right okay okay I'll
just ah yeah that's where they went oh
I'm oh it's
over dirty cloth
uhud puddles on the ground can be I
wanted to but I think I didn't have
enough materials especially now I don't
have enough steel
but uh could definitely work towards it
legendary parts I was going to take
one but Forge steel I still can't make
it myself and now I used uh a little bit
maybe for something else I don't
remember but yeah I think I used a
couple for the no did I no I maybe I
didn't I don't know but we still need
more so this maybe next time I don't
have to be so Overkill yet I think I'm
fine like for the part of the game where
we are at I think this is fine look for
broken vending machines for steal oh oh
if they're broken I can wrench them okay
okay okay I
see I okay so I did use some steel for
Fess gloves honestly worth it I'm glad
to make her a present anym I'm kind of
useless so oh do you need to repair kit
yeah let's get out of here
[Music]
couch it's 4:00 a.m. I'll go to the
Traer really quickly
ow
ow my mini bike I don't know maybe we
should get out of this neighborhood and
just like find a solo house okay
okay
oops gas
pumps
no okay uh I guess we can pick up the
car pick it up just try to wrench
everything storage that I can find well
this won't give me steel right these
things I'm going come on the little
train that could you can do
it well if that bike is waiting for me
maybe I can go yeah drop stuff off
andc waiting for this area is also six
six maybe you might want another friend
there to help out yeah we just we we
we're riding on a road and there was a
giant hole in the middle and we fell
into it
oh do you have your bike I have it okay
okay
okay let's
see I'm going to put the forge Steel in
the crate next to the
forge
um okay I'm going to put all this stuff
I'm back on the
seat
okay what did I come here for I'm com
for you watch out there's another hole
in the
ground okay
okay does he no road rage people
please okay let's go to the east we'll
head to the oh here okay
clay what do clay
become farms and forg
right yeah very useful everything's
useful nice what the
spring put the mods
somewhere
okay I'm good to
go there's so much in the way here
people keep
driving keep getting
stuck we need we need a monster truck
yeah we just put it big big truck yeah I
want like a school bus so we can all go
together yeah schol would be good that
sounds cute
okay well I'm
coming he had so much steel I I bought a
bunch of Steel what a steel black mini
bike I think this one's mine yeah that's
yours not really zero gas maybe I should
put some gas in it e
really yeah oh there might be gas in the
is it the wrong one in the uh car chest
at in the kitchen oh I think chest okay
is there yeah there is here I'll add
some more uh one one
full one full tank is uh 1,000 gas
apparently 1,000 and that will get you
through it for a while it seems okay
thanks I
doing prob me load it up first yeah you
know how
yeah I did it no worries
okay I'm going to go find them okay I
repaired my gun it's fine okay I only
have seven ammo though yeah I R I'm
running out of ammo
myself let's L how do we can can we make
ammo yet is it still I can make oh you
can okay okay there's a lot of couches
maybe they give cloth and the curtains
as
well so I'm going to yeah the cou think
nice oh yeah the curtain give a lot of
give some as well okay damn it are we
out of duct tape again yes probably no
we're we're getting there though I'm
going to work on getting a cotton farm
and
then uh our water production is much
higher
now nice but we're still honestly if you
ever see the water purification Parts if
you can buy them we can always use more
water I think H water purification Parts
okay yeah seems tap justes don't give
where do I quickly get duct tape chat oh
screamer armor parts and springs he got
everything I need
dispenser um do you have a single cloth
a single I do not
oh believe we can look we have one more
we have enough for your chair there's a
back pack in here no o be careful behind
oh one more gas you saved me I like 6 hp
right now okay okay okay one hit and I'm
dead she's
dead Springs are pretty cheap o let's go
upstairs yeah I mean is it even worth it
to make a farm cuz it's so expensive to
craft the seeds I guess I'm like
confused on the ratio here I feel like
maybe C's is something that we have to
like find mostly or maybe if it grows
once it keeps growing I don't know you
think when you when you use it does it
go
away uh I think it goes away then I have
no idea that's weird maybe you
need I should make you a level five
farmer set that will make things behind
you behind you better oh oh yeah maybe I
should wear that if you can get me armor
kits I'll make you a farmer set but I
think we have one piece of the pharmac
set already just should wear it not the
best level tra are selling armor parts
by the way are you in a Trader now yeah
can you check if he's selling duct
tape let's see du you see
that no I'm going to go check out Jen
though
next who
that's nice look so cool oh be
careful don't run into it uh I found
serrated blade schematic you want that
oh
sure cuz you do sword knives I
mean oh I think I already learned it oh
okay give it back here you go maybe Bob
has shotgun parts he
might is that better I think it's better
uh to which Traer did you go Kelly wed
I'm going to Jen now okay so w didn't
have any duct tape no duct tape sadly a
lot of armor parts though maybe like
four or so but I I have 15 duct tape I
can give you five I just need one oh
okay yes I can give it to you that's big
yeah do I need wait let me double
check do you guys know if like if you
have an item two I need two
okay I can give you that thank
you ah also Kelly if you find a a
crucible let me know okay I'll check and
let you know thanks what do we need we
need one more cloth you said singular
cloth a singular cloth okay I have a lot
of cloth but I'm not at home but I will
bring it home chest we're struggling
with the simplest
things I'm going to go check Bob
first and then we can head home Bob has
some stuff we
need I'll go to
Jen she's cute but I like
her yeah she's nice Bob's not bad though
he's friendly
enough oh yeah I guess so on the ranch
oh compared to what's his
name don't know his name terrible
terrible custom of his I wonder who the
next tra is if it's another cute
girl I hope hopefully oh I have fingers
crossed I don't know how often like
stuff respawns in I think it's every day
maybe
w uhoh
b party fou party fou for
B apparently Crucible pretty expensive
so we might need to do a bunch of quests
to get a bunch of coins yeah save up but
he doesn't have it right I don't know go
check the other Traders
okay with your sick
bike yeah that's right I'm fast
[Music]
now duct tape duct tape duct tape this
assembles your
bed hey who said you could do that just
Kidd kiding disassemble away oh did I
break a bone can you take Quest from Bob
CeCe um I think so well I'm just giving
back quests so I must be able to right
oh yeah yeah yeah good I don't think
I've ever taken any from him but maybe
through you
guys sprin the
leg oh he's giving me a
bicycle I don't need it anymore hello
need forged
iron oh fored irono crafting
bundle no she got shotgun
weakly
see there lots of armor parts but it's
about okay I can't take any quests but I
can't see his in oh maybe it's because
he's busy oh I am I am talking to him
currently okay I do that first
I don't think that she has anything that
we need okay what are you guys looking
for I'm at
Bob shotgun parts for me what do you
need Kiara I just need one duct tape
right now and then I'm happy I have or
two two yeah two yeah I have that are
you coming home soon I'm coming
okay it's so far are you on your bike or
on the bicycle yeah I got a bike let's
go home see
actually maybe I should fill this one
up she got steel
though oh wait I have no
more ah Crucible yeah but I don't think
any Trader has a crucible Now shotgun
part okay Bob has shotgun part he does
how many let me
see uh let's be
big I have no money
though I'm going to have to do a
quest she's so nice even when I don't
buy
anything I'm looting I'm getting lots of
stuff I might have a problem my bic
broken he has five shotgun parts I can't
afford them though oh that's okay that's
as much as I need okay I'm going to go
do some quests how expensive are they do
you know
450 okay I think if I do a couple quests
I might be able to get
it wait your bike
Broke
bike oh no splint is not needed it's for
breaking your leg let me get on my bike
and get out of
here take some quests with her tier two
quests tier two
quests okay you guys doing any quests by
chance no I'm following my own path
that's good that's good I I really
respect that I would like to do more
Quest cuz I'm broke
now but I'm going to go to kiaha First
yay thank
you
okay it has been about 4 hours we're
stopping at the end of day 26
okay
okay did you girls no um you probably
did but when you go to the challenge
window did you know there's a second
challenge window what you did you you
should you prob have a million oh my
gosh XP points oh I didn't realize until
now chat told
me thank you K there's a bear thank you
K I can fight the bear
no problem I mean you you killed the
boar very earlier this is a a bear well
is it a is it bigger than the boar I
think
so I think I think you can do
it oh I need three points okay I don't
want to drink the beer
though this could be bad the bear is
very cute oh the bear is
scary he's got more than I do uhoh I'm
tanking him fisticuffs oh no the bear
you can take him I'm clipping inside of
him ah There's a Zombie teaming up on
me uhoh
boy I'm dying oh oh
magic I just can't really Rocks come on
now
okay little solo clear for Mor surely I
can do it right oh wait
I
nice if you didn't start it yet we're
like heading over there we can do your
quest with you real fast yeah oh wait
here
Stones oh my
goodness I that was
exhilarating do you feel power
I do I killed a
bear that's pretty awesome oh he did
hurt my knee a little
bit hello give me
testosterone it's over here the
quest oh is fauna not in my team oh fun
you're on your own Journey I'm I'm
fighting bears in the wilderness in the
tundra f is fighting bears bear
fisted Hello's here hello let's do it
ladies yay mhm all right what I wanted
to ask IIA do you guys know if you have
like two weapons but one is higher level
like I have one five level five item and
one level three item how big is the
difference there the I
wonder the higher tier like the like for
example if you have a bone knife and a
hunting knife the hunting knife will be
better than the level five bone knife
but the if you have the higher number
it's going to definitely be better oh
okay
yeah but like a level one baseball bat's
better than a level six Club I think oh
yes yum watch out I'm going stab you
watch out it's
okay no worries and also we got to grab
supplies you forget the supplies just
one cloth just a single cloth you're
still looking for a single
cloth kind of one I think I have cloth
hold on let me check I don't I don't
apparently cloth is a hot
commodity we often forget about look at
this game I set up window set
up
oh I didn't realize they let you reread
books in this
game yeah they let you read book so just
make sure that it's not an open icon I
see I see make sure it's not an open
icon yeah if if the if if you have a
book and it's a open book icon that
means you read it already oh I
see if it's a closed book you have not
more attention to that oh he dropped
loot what do you drop shotgun parts oh
so batterup volume six I've already read
so I don't need that but you need to
drop legendary
parts so but if I read it I still get
exp it's just doesn't really teach you
anything new I don't know who else is
trying to do clubs but we should leave
it for them they really that bad in here
doesn't look that bad I wanted to do
clubs but I'm really liking this spear
so I'm not sure anymore yeah I got a
spear wait wait look look at it I mean I
can count get him wait I just saw you
where did you go oh this
way he's dead no no he's
[Music]
not he is wearing a helmet CU that's
rough oh wow he really you off the top
of the oh clear it's got to find the
supplies now
K kie look look look yeah look at my
look at my
no I like your spear it's
very robust and looks like he can poke
things really good I think someone's
Satchel is up here
uhoh how did you get up
there
parkour Hardcore Parkour oh there's a
ladder parkour there's a ladder
somewhere oh there's another bear how do
we do this get it I don't know if I can
take a second
bear can't take two bears the first bear
kind of wiped me
out my satchels around here I
think
oh that smoy oh my goodness she's like
shouldn't you be done streaming by now
hello
no movie is like it's late it's
early breakfast time breakfast time for
Smoothie all right is that a is this a
bookstore
H book store it's a bookstore like an
abandoned four and a half stars
but oh we did find River supplies oh no
just a
peek well it is time to end now yeah
is I just want to get the duct tape yeah
I I give you duct tap I just got to find
this stupid Supply I can't Quest real
quick
my
oh yeah quest to then St so many books
though we really do need to do a season
two it's just too fun it
is seven days isn't enough yeah
yeah what are you talking about we've
been here almost a month yeah 21 26 days
I can't find this stupid smovie says hi
back I don't know how I'm supposed to
two oh okay I got it I got it okay I'm
done hold
on mine's like super close but like
where is it
oh it's raining C on top of
it yeah he'll he'll have the shocka oh
dang it he'll have them tomorrow but I
won't be here tomorrow oh it
resets it
does you think he'll have shotgun
parts when I come back it's
G I hope so can I mine the carpet
no somehow Furniture keeps on
disappearing in this house oh and walls
too
oh you found I found it yeah nice okay
now I'm heading back for the duct
tape where are we anyways oh my God
Traer
J oh this
isless my
here back my so many books you guys are
going to be so happy y oh boy f with the
book hey yo when that restocks we should
go together again
tomorrow more book hauls I'm going to
leave I didn't explore the whole place
cuz I'm a little
scared good careful I got a bunch of
books good good good and I'm really
slow let's Park this
bicycle actually that's a good parking
spot anyway but can I make it stand
up okay where
the okay wrong
way is that the why is it can I give it
up is that the cik why is it
Kelly you're on your bike right now
right I got off of it oh I'm just
turning in a quest real
quick
okay can we name
bikes no wonder that would be cool that
be nice no we can't I'm
confused well the colors will be a
giveaway whose bike is whose
but this one confuses me let's see I
don't want to this is it is Call's bike
right yeah where did the other bike
go I I have mine right you have the
purple one I have the black one all CeCe
on the white
one uh I have a bicycle G's bicycle
where did the other one go sell
these I mean it's my my my bicycle my B
I don't mean oh there's one right here
yeah yeah that one's from Cal it
seems I think no Callie has her bike
doesn't she with you
Callie do you have it on you yeah I have
my bike with me oh okay never mind then
that is the extra bike okay okay here
you go tap thank you'll go really fast
too being so excited about duct tape I
know the simplest things this this game
makes you appreciate the simple things
in life it does
real uh
I'm two
right and
then last but not least so last thing
for today are we still one cloth short
from a seat
CeCe I have lots of cloth oh I also have
some more cloth now yay I'm coming home
too okay but you can make cloth from
plant fibers I should do that m least I
can maybe I write a recipe no bikes
allow in
here and then for making it level seven
how do you do that guys Trader Bob he's
just down the
road Trader Bob is actually really close
to Trader
gen doesn't exist oh
please um what time should we play until
you guys uh like now we should probably
end
it probably I'm almost home let me drop
off the books at
pleas of
course yeah I'm just going two shot
parts and then
I's for four more
hours I could I could totally play for
another four hours more
hours that's why I thought maybe the
last day should be like a super long day
or something but I also know you guys
have to sleep yeah no I don't mind I
don't need sleep I think um storywise
it's probably fun to end it on a on a
horde
right and one long episode I think it's
fine having the last one be longer 4
hours it does feel a little bit
short I know right I I thought that
seven days would be the perfect amount
cuz JP days everybody
oh books
bookies brought a ton of book in the
book
yes how many how many hold on I'm going
to take a knife
Guy and
um and a handgun okay thank you also you
girls wanted me to make the seat right
with the cloth yes please okay uh drop
the cloth off and the chest then I shall
make it the forge
one uh yeah okay oh I put 70 here
earlier uh yeah they're with me don't
worry oh okay okay I'm going to the rest
in there I put I put more in the crate
okay thank you he does not have shotgun
parts does you only have them for
certain
people B wait no why am I learning that
I'm
Max yeah B Bob had Bob had like three
shotgun parts but okay I'm like stuff
for everybody don't worry guys dang it I
think they are
gone uh what am I making seat
right your stock changes each
day F take it Miss opportunity I'll just
have to check tomorrow Springs Springs
oh what if I can make a
h oh
oops
cool thank you for the books my heart
Bob thank you thank you okay I'm going
to jump off guys it was fun than than up
I won't be there tomorrow but I'll be
there on the final day
okay same with me sadly but I will I
will be back I'll be
back back back byebye we'll see you
around by the
finale yeah see you guys for the finale
then uh hopefully I won't be too
underleveled but it'll probably be fine
call is there something that we should
be looking out for you in terms of items
tomorrow shotgun parts shotgun parts um
need shotgun parts and forged
steel yeah we yeah everyone needs forged
steel
though but we have a few but yeah mainly
that shotgun part s really need shotgun
parts for the for me yeah okay I guess
that's it for me all right I'll see you
guys on the last day
by bye everyone
byee bye bye and the extra seat is
finished y now we can have even more
people on the bikes uh people do you
want it on your bike in the house yes
please okay yeah I'll be outside did you
I'll I'll give the part to you you can
modify it oh okay I think you can so uh
there you go thank
you
my you guys realize I can't find my bike
anymore how do you know where
is our bike
can you get on I just want to test it
yay uh it's locked have to
unlock oh do I have to do it no okay
it's unlocked let's
go look at those
nerds nering together let's go oh ow hey
careful you have a passenger on
[Music]
there thank you I love that there's a
drink colder there is there yeah oh yeah
there is that's so cute what what all
the duct tape is for is the light even
working in order to build this bike I
had to put in a light part but when I
look at it it honestly doesn't look like
is there a button to to turn it on no I
don't think
so or press F press F oh F turns on my
night vision a hm maybe maybe maybe no
maybe it's just our own light all right
cool awesome thank you we got a lot of
stuff done I have one armor piece that's
levels the maximum level level six only
one it gives me a lot more uh space in
my inventory too oh really yeah that's
cool awesome oh yeah so now um I have a
level three Nomad outfit that somebody
can inherit from
me h maybe we need another chest just
for armor stuff because this chest is a
mish
mash yeah I wanted to organize but then
I went fist for fa I'll put the fist in
the fist or the magazine box thank
you um where shall I put
uh I feel like we're in a pretty good
place yeah yeah
tomorrow horde shouldn't be going down
yeah although I don't want to get too
cocky about it
yeah lots of food
cooking how about like bandages and
stuff like first aid
bandages how we looking on
that we could use some more probably we
use more we need Aloe really I think
o which I can also work on we can also
use some more ammo parts so I can craft
more ammo so we have plenty for the
hoorde yeah I'm just waiting on
crops oh aloe is in the desert maybe I
can go collect
aloe next
[Music]
time and then I can collect cotton to
make more Co cloth for bandages although
we don't have much time until the The
Raid oh okay let's log out okay I SC
this but I never use it let's
go okay
byebye bye had fun with you
girls see you tomorrow see see you
tomorrow byebye bye
bye
pun okay I'm I'm I'm I'm out of here I'm
out of here don't
worry I'm really productive we got a
couple of mini bikes um with extra seats
even oh look at us again extra
seats
and uh some sick armor good progress
there
yeah I mean we're realizing how much
importance even the simplest things have
being constantly low on on well all
kinds of things not just duct tape but
yeah the nerd bik
cooking we're so cute yeah no self say
today 100 armor is insane hopefully now
I can get more workstation magazines I
want to go to that Library maybe if I
open things there's a higher chance for
workstation magazines there too I don't
know not sure if it's just with crates
or also with those bookshelves what do
you think do you guys know
I'm surprised you got so much I was
locked in I was very very focused
especially now in the in the house at
the
end I'm the opra of mini bikes yeah I
hope the girls who weren't there today
but will be there tomorrow will be
impressed by our progress and by the
mini bikes what was the question if if
it also matters for the bookshelves that
were like fauna just went into that
Library who opens it like cuz
workstation magazines somebody said it's
more likely to get those from the crates
or whatever but is there like a
certain place where I I'm more likely to
get those like can they show up in
shelves or is is shelves like a lowlevel
kind
of oh okay they're they're also
influenced by my skill Dres okay good so
I shall go there and open some uh
[Music]
shelves construction sites and built
houses everything techn depends on who
opens it okay
okay yeah you think I've been helpful I
hope so I don't think I've ever been
like dis
involved
and like of so to say importance in
anything before like in Minecraft I
wanted to be with uh phoenixon but
phoenixon wasn't really used much by
others not to this level uh people
didn't need it so much
um but I was quite proud of
that in myth one block yeah myth one
block I mean I just had the overview of
everything and was organizing stuff and
yeah I think in myth one block I I was
quite helpful too
but this is this is on a different level
that's why I want to make sure I'm there
every day but I'm also happy that it's
like ending um in two streams because I
want to take a day off and I feel like I
can't take a day off as long as this is
running um you know
um yeah and and as long as as much as I
like
this like having to play it every day
for a whole week is a bit rough uh so I
am craving the day
off craving
it oh yeah I'm I'm I'm happy I mean our
group seems to be getting smaller and
smaller but let's see who will show up
tomorrow let's see
I like our group though very motivated
uh individuals gigy will surely come
back tomorrow right she's been missed
today but it's all
right no I do want to stream my PV
because I can you know ask you guys
questions and stuff and you guys tell me
tips when
I sneak peek over to the screen
yeah I love our
group it's been also just really great
to you know hang out with
fauna we we didn't
really over the past three years in
general we haven't really done much
together and this has honestly been a
really nice experience very grateful for
that that we happened to just like kind
of bump into each other naturally very
early on and then just stuck
together yeah I did kind of like
sense this feeling that I had with her
too like wanting to separate into a
little bit of a smaller group and you
know I feel like we're on the same
wavelength when it comes to this game
and
collab so yeah a little bit introverted
a little bit overwhelmed but still very
motivated and still very uh goal
oriented yeah I get it I get it I like
smaller groups too which is why I am
enjoying this smaller group today as
well it's just chaotic and I start
feeling bad when there's like 10 people
in the VC I don't get a word in I don't
want to force my word in either um I
don't want to
like you
know like there if there's so many
people streaming like whatever I want to
say doesn't really matter
to uh them usually so sometimes I mute
myself and then just talk to you
guys yeah yeah uh I I really don't like
that honestly on the first day when we
started out how many people were we in
VC
very many and I you guys remember you
notice probably I didn't get a word in I
was
like yeah we were like 12 really wow so
in that beginning that went on for like
2 hours or so I feel like I was honestly
thinking already like this might not be
for me maybe I'll not participate that
much at all but then we split into
groups and then it was okay then I was
like okay never mind this is fine
this is fine it might be
fine yeah I'm glad I stuck with it
too shy too yeah people don't believe it
I mean I don't know not necessarily shy
I just I don't know it's weird feel
uncomfortable not shy just
uncomfortable and anxious very
anxious yeah
but so is it I wonder how hard the
zombie raid will be
tomorrow should I be scared should I be
intimidated uh oh by the way you guys
saw probably on shi's schedule that she
published that there will be a collab on
my channel some of you guys may have
seen it U but she didn't write what it
is and with who uh I already like one or
two weeks ago wrote to a couple of
people um thinking ahead of
time for Mario Party
collab because I want to play Mario
Party the new deree Mario Party On
release and so I actually have two Mario
Party collabs cooking right now with two
different groups because the first group
I wrote to most of them were were like
oh we don't buy digitally we we I I made
a reservation I don't know if we'll
will'll arrive on the release day and
the other one was also like oh yeah I
buy in the shop I buy physical so they I
was like
what I buy like literally every [\h__\h]
game digitally it was like I didn't know
so many members buy
physical and then it takes them some
time to get the game um that's crony yes
l is crony one of those members was
literally crony so that's the later
group
um yeah um but the first group that I'm
playing with this
week uh next week I mean or this yeah
now it's this week it's Monday for me
already uh I can already spoil it for
you it's me uh Shi bi Boo and
gigy uh at 9:00 p.m. my
time on Thursday the
17th yeah we're going to play the new
Mario
Party yeah it's an unusual group I think
it's a weird group I just randomly threw
some girls together who said they can
buy it on release
day yeah and then a week or two later
I'm having another
group
which let me
see where's my othero group oh
which um Al also might include
gigy I might kick her out because she's
in the first
one um but it's uh narissa and crony and
giggy and me but yeah I might kick giggy
out that's because giggy was like first
I I wrote to these girls and giggy was
like yeah I can buy the digital one I
can play on release day but the others
said they can't so then I brought giggy
into this other
group no no no it's not it's not like
that it's not because I like her that
much I mean I like her but you know it's
not because of that it just so
happen keep her in she's fun I was
thinking you know two oranges and two
blue ones it's going to visually be very
appealing but I don't know please don't
don't kick her out okay okay I think she
has a very um nice energy she brings a
great exciting fun energy to collapse so
very appealing to
[Music]
me I'm thinking like me and giggy
chaotic loud orange ladies and then
neriss and crony are the mature cool
blue ladies in that collab but yeah the
first one is is bi Shi me and
gigy giggy stay okay
okay um the
sponsorship oh wait what do you mean
that it's out how do you know it before
I'm saying it what my sponsorship is did
they tweet about it wait ah what how do
you [\h__\h] know they tweeted oh yeah my
sponsorship at 6:00 a.m. on Sunday is a
tribe 9 it's like a Danga
related game the company okay cool
thanks I appreciate that then I can make
my
schedule have you heard of it it's
apparently free to play and I think it
has a gcha element to
it uh I think so yeah CI also has a
sponsorship with
them yeah I'm glad they asked me I was
interested in it because I did watch
dangan Luma and I like the style
so good luck in Mario party thank you I
will lose again and that's
fine I will be momentarily salty about
it but I will be ready for the next
collab
already CU I have two lined
up takam
dang
yeah I usually Avo gotes but we'll check
it out for you thank you yeah download
it I think it's on Steam for
free if I understand correct
L Tri n yeah it's free it's free what a
[Music]
deal tri9 is an extreme action RPG where
groups of teens will endure multiple
losses and devise strategies to overcome
formidable foes dive into a crazy
adventure with unique characters in a
meticulously crafted world with a
variety of art styles by the same
creators of the Danga NPA
Series yeah it looks pretty cool I'm
interested that Yum Yum Yum and I think
it will be longer than an hour stream
they they asked to play until a certain
point I
think is there referral code I don't
know maybe they'll give me
one not yet though so then you already
know a bunch of next week because the
first two days will be
uh uh seven days to die
um then oh actually it's ending a day
earlier than I thought it would it
seems but no never mind it no that's not
true it's not ending a day earlier than
my father would seven days seven seven
days to
die so that's like Wednesday officially
for me but more like
Tuesday and then yeah
Thursday oh I'd love to take the day off
but well I guess I do
have more than a 24-hour Gap in
between yeah so uh thur day is the
collab and then Friday I'll take the day
off yeah looks like no place for members
watch along
unfortunately I
think but yeah Saturday I want to play
Zelda
and Sunday early in the morning tribe 9
and then in the evening I'm going to
play The Voice
mimicry game see already already you
have a
[Music]
schedule yeah I'll upload the member
bloopers thingy rebroadcast yeah I'll
I'll try to put it somewhere in there
too although I feel like I don't know I
almost don't want to rebroadcast it
I don't want to open up those wounds
again for the people who will be
watching
it I don't wanna feels
wrong no I didn't finish Dela
yet do it the pain was
fun has it been re-uploaded
elsewhere What on YouTube or else
elsewhere
yeah I don't I mean it's like a free
stream for me to do basically but is
there a need for it is there anyone here
who missed it and really want to hear me
sing sad songs only for 2 hours or
so your singing was great yeah but then
again the audio mixing wasn't so good
though me me really yeah really
o okay but it opens up wounds are you
sure you missed part of it okay I'll see
where I can squeeze it and it would be
um probably placed in an NA friendly
time slot or no sea sea friendly time
slot because I did Europe slash na kind
of friendly time slot before
I think it should be sea friendly
mhm so I don't know where but it will be
in there
okay I might make the schedule now
before I
go you know last night I I my schedule
is like even more uh um moving
towards yab territory my time sleep
schedule last night I was up till like
10:00 a.m. I was trying to I wasn't
tired enough I was in bed since like
maybe 9:00
a.m. but I didn't really follow asleep
until
[Music]
10: now it's halfast 6:00 a.m. I still
have to eat my dinner but won't take too
long recently these past days I've just
been making small sandwiches and making
really simple stuff it's kind of lame
but I'm not really motivated to cook at
the moment
and it just feels weird to cook dinner
in when it's dark outside I don't know
it's weird but that makes no sense
actually because often I cook dinner
past midnight but I don't know I'm
making weird excuses it just feels
[Applause]
wrong I don't know shut up I don't know
it makes no sense I know I know I don't
know but I'm I don't know there's phases
where I don't want to cook okay now it's
one of those phases
yeah my my eyes and my head are kind of
uh exhausted right now so I think no
super chats right now but yesterday we
really zoomed through it so maybe
tomorrow I can read some maybe maybe
what if I start my stream like an hour
early and read super chats before we
start a little
bit I'd rather started early and do that
but rather than doing it later
actually I
think although then again the final
stream will be I wonder how long it will
be um tomorrow if we play like 4 hours
again we'll get through the raid then I
wonder how long we need for the final
day 6 7
[Music]
cuz we're really close to the raid now
if we play four hours tomorrow we might
be able to you
know five to six yeah I hope not more
than seven cuz more than seven will be
very rough for my energy I
[Music]
think
yeah I wonder if I can ask if they can
start another hour earlier like 1:00
a.m. my time for the finale if there
would be a problem with
that depending on how long it will
go doesn't hurt to ask
right I'll ask if anybody has a problem
with it
okay good
good ah yeah uh Japanese gang J Japan
gang will be a little bit early
[Music]
than well I'll ask first like what how
long we might need need for it I don't
know I'm sure CeCe will be thankful too
yeah
yeah too bad the finale couldn't have
happened on the weekend oh yeah for me
it's fine but I guess for the
viewers for me it doesn't matter what
day of the
weekness well
yeah Japan yeah I mean
what8 1 plus 7 8 a.m. isn't that bad
that's not that bad I
mean sacrifices have to be made and
especially considering that we didn't
have a single EU time slot in the end
yeah yeah yeah I
mean geeki found geki wrote something
really um
RP
is
oh oh that was just about like her not
being here
today let me just quote one part my
beautiful precious wives and beautiful
apocalypse survivors dot dot dot I will
join you all tomorrow in your quests dot
dot dot I think of you all very fondly
in my heart but tonight I must do this
and that I'm not going to say exactly
what she's doing I don't know if she
wants me
to I miss you all
dearly cute she's so cute oh right C is
still like chatting in there let me
quickly write it uh one question since
we didn't have a single e time slot
and the finale might be kind of long can
we start one
more hour early and then recently I
found out how to do the time slot thing
on
Discord the time stamp
converter um that would
be what day would that be Wednesday 2 1
a.m.
one one one one one one where is one one
one okay I think that should be accurate
oh Kelly says she's fine with
that she's so
fast
speed Unix amp for Discord yeah you
can't do that within Discord right I
always open up this like website
this time stamp
generator I don't know how to do it
within Discord can you
oh well I guess if you that that looks
complicated what does this
mean it's all external oh okay use
hammer time what do you mean hammer time
oh is that what the website is called
mine is the one I use is
free R.F free.
fi funny name
website hand
time I wish they would implement it into
the webs into the uh program what the
hell
please okay yeah leave it at that I'll
go make my dinner
breakfast and sleep and then no wait
I'll make the schedu two I guess and
then tomorrow when I wake up I'll upload
the choreography
[Music]
video
yes yeah I'm living na time soon it's
over two more
streams in thank you so much for
watching
see you tomorrow have a nice evening and
day thank you for watching two streams
today two
streams yeah in total we streamed like
eight hours good job Wawa thank you
Wawa good night waa good night waa wait
you don't see her guys she's there
she's right next to
me I'll be nothing
[Music]