[Music]
so
you
oh
[Music]
you
do
[Music]
you
ah sorry one more moment please
one more moment please
[Music]
so
thank you everybody for waiting sorry
for the wait
sorry um
[Applause]
good evening hello
jim
hello everybody let me turn turn on some
more
music do i have some music do i have
some music
oh
wait let me get it from my audio stock
collection
how are you doing
sorry i was preparing i was uh turning
all the snacks into pngs
um
trying to
make everything around it transparent
yeah yeah sorry that took a little while
and i was watching russia's concert on
the side where you guys watching too
russia senpai's birthday concert so cute
she's so cute
i just moved something oops
[Music]
what could be
fitting maybe this
a cafe cafe no
not quite
not quite how about this
that's kind of weird
[Music]
it doesn't fit either
we'll put this
[Music]
you missed the concert from lucia senpai
you definitely missed something we're so
cute
this is actually pretty cute but
[Music]
that's actually good i think i used this
bgm
during my outfit reveal of this
particular outfit
i think
i might have used this when i was like
shopping for clothes
maybe you feel uh like you've heard this
bgm before and that might be why that
might be one of myself i'm sorry i
wanted to get some hyper chat going
because otherwise the chat keeps on
breaking and falling apart from me
are you gonna use handcuff no i'm not
gonna use it today i thought you know um
it's way less stressful to do it without
and that way i can do it pretty
comfortably
so
yeah it's not really necessary to have a
hand camera maybe in the future but uh
this time will not be using it so
oh it actually doesn't loop so well does
it
does it
um
yeah we're doing we're doing a new
series starting from today i mean we
already did like a little kickoff a
testing session in my members only
streams
you know
was like an international one it was
like a mix of all kinds of countries we
had some like
american snacks we had polish snacks we
had uh we had pocky we did have pocky
um
i just realized that made one mistake
with uh
the making something transparent
wednesday let me fix that one really
quickly um
oh yeah yeah before we get started i
guess
i guess you guys want me to say
something
uh yesterday
i was on an official stream
i was on an official stream on the
official whole life channel and i told
you i told you it would be worth
checking it out you should check it out
live otherwise you're gonna get
spoilered on
twitter probably how many people have
you got spoilers on twitter after waking
up and not watching the official stream
how many of you got spoilered by the
news um
i was on a plane where that's okay
that's forgivable
uh
i was watching your life me mimi
i saw you guys were spoilers
yeah i knew it was gonna happen i knew
it that's why i said you guys should
watch it live
it's not f that that that had way more
impact
actually um
so me and putin senpai and eof his
empire uh together with eichen
we were um playing a game that was so
much fun i kind of want to like uh
steal the idea and do it as a collab in
within whole live english
um
[Music]
uh i was floored
why are you a floor
no i understand yeah that game was a
super fun we actually had more topics
like more themes prepared but
um just two took so much time that we
were already
at the end of the stream after two
topics um
but it was fun what we were doing was
like uh we had a theme of like creating
a certain type of idol unit
uh with three members and they gave us
specific members to choose from to fill
in
the
roles that we were trying to fill for
example like a seiso pure pure idol
group you know girls who don't swear
perhaps girls who are very pure um and
they gave us like four choices and but
if if uh one of us
chose the same girl as someone else like
if i chose the same girl as botan tempe
um we would find out afterwards and then
we were not getting that girl to fill up
a slot in a idol
group
yeah one of the choices i made was ina
uh i mean
don't you think that you guys say so i
think they know you know it's uh the
most say so out of whole live english a
whole life myth but
well i think it's uh i guess it depends
um
yeah i think united states yeah yeah
yeah i mean
she doesn't she never really swears
swears and uh
she
even just her voices say so
i also had the choice uh to make whether
or not i would put bana into a cesar
unit
uh i was it was a difficult choice
because
on first look and i think for most like
japanese bros if they look at fauna if
they listen to her for a little bit i
think she say so like you can be um
deceived by her but honestly like you
guys tell me also that she's not say so
and i guess she did a little bit of a
yandere here and there but me personally
when i talked to her
i have not encountered much of her
nonsense
yet
so
i was just really speaking from
what i know but not necessarily what
i've experienced personally yeah
i meant i think ahmed was mostly safe so
i'm it
[Music]
can i say so yeah i guess
ahmed doesn't need to be safe so she's
perfect the way she is
yeah who said that
i don't know about that it's i guess
it's a
an open topic for discussion um but
anyway um do i have a
let me let me show you an image for
everyone who missed it did anyone miss
it does anyone not know what's going on
uh let me show you
guys
[Music]
uh
careful
so it was revealed i mean until now uh
this this concert and expo was already
known that it was happening and i think
everyone was
pretty clear on the fact that
um uh whole life japan would be there
but yesterday it was announced that the
first gen of en so myth and the first
gen of indonesia uh would also be
performing on at the concert yeah yeah
and
actually all of whole life
uh production so
uh
i indonesia second chance and uh ian uh
hope and uh
council uh and all stars everybody will
be at the expo and by the way
you guys if you'd
never seen the venue before never heard
of the venue before the venue is huge
i've been there before for like this is
where tokyo game show is being held and
many other big big big events
yeah it is huge i mean um
there's like several uh parts of the
halls that you can use i think not even
tokyo game show uses
did they use all of the holes actually i
forgot
uh
but it's a huge venue whether or not you
use all the halls or not um and then the
concert will be like in a in a separate
hall that is like
uh there for like concerts
and also maybe you've heard of it before
the uh nico nico
also happen here at least that happened
in the past year i've also been there
i've been at tokyo game show and and uh
tokyo uh
party i've been to all of those events
before i've been to makuhari mesa so
often so for me it's like super exciting
it's like huge to be there it's like a
insane venue like so many people can
enter and then it's not only the people
who can go there in person but also you
guys can watch it online
what
um so uh you guys are obviously very
curious and asking any questions however
i cannot really answer your questions
i know i know i'm usually the one who uh
goes into detail about things but i
cannot um but i can tell you we are um
performing at the concert we're not just
like i don't know an announcement voice
or whatever no we we are going to be
[Music]
uh do doing something in one way or
another
[Laughter]
so just uh look forward to that and you
can uh i'll be on i'll be on day two
like
will be on this day too and then gura
ame and ina will be on day one so i'm
actually thinking
um i'm actually thinking about doing a
watch along on the first day perhaps um
review guys yeah we can do a watch one
because yeah you know i said
i was thinking yo i'm in this i can't do
a watch along but now that i think about
it i'm not in it for one day so
how about we wanted to go it's always
fun to
to watch these concerts together and it
could really get us hyped up about my my
own
a day how to buy the ticket um
there are tickets on spawn
please just uh i already linked it on
twitter you've retweeted millions of
things on twitter you should go to the
whole live home page or to the twitter
it's everywhere right now yeah um
it's called whole life super expo
uh
expo is the whole event that it will be
like i guess i guess it's probably
comparable to
into like uh i don't know to a
convention but it's all about uh
life whole life
production yeah
um
and uh
and this one is the concept where not
everyone will be there but as you can
see these are this is the lineup for the
concert i'm so excited
the trailer got me
um to like oh my god i was i was tearing
up when i um saw the trailer because
and they asked um when i was at the at
the stream at the official live stream
um they asked if
if we want to watch the trailer
beforehand and i was like no
now i want to be surprised i want to be
surprised
um
yeah so it was really really um
emotional to just like suddenly
additional cast and then
we show up that was beautiful
[Music]
yeah yeah there will be a live stream
yes yes yes yes uh you can watch it on
spawn s-p-w-n
so
that's it for now that's uh all i can
say for now i think uh yes yes yes yes
i'll put it here
is
[Music]
i was waiting for this to be honest like
i was also
you know because of um
things um i was also
worried that
it would it would still take much much
longer until we we ian would be included
in something like this
um but thankfully
the dream
uh came
true and
now we are part of it yay oh my god oh
my god
i really want you guys to watch it
um so i'll be talking and reminding you
guys probably a lot during uh the next
couple of
weeks slash months it's happening in in
march
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah the comic was so cute
yeah it was it was beautiful the comic
that christina manzanita post it anyway
we're here for a different reason though
i've been already talking for um 15
minutes
yeah um yeah yeah but i think i think
all of myth and and indonesia first gen
we
we've been waiting for an opportunity
like this and we deserve it and we're
gonna do our best and it's gonna be
exciting it's gonna be fun
and i think all of our um fan
communities will come together cheer
together and be like super happy for one
another yeah um
yay
the final we were part of it for the
other concerts i was always watching and
it's like
oh when
when will we be part of this when can we
do it because you guys know um
nevermind okay i can't i can it's
dangerous if i talk so much for tangents
so much
um i will stop myself
[Music]
i'm doing a korean
snack box review
[Music]
come up come help me papa go papa
i ordered um
online
and i i i ordered a korean snack box
uh
i apologize
already
if the snacks in it
don't real really
represent
korean snacks in your opinion
i
cannot really
judge that
yes i i just
said all of that
that was me you saw my mouth moving
right
[Laughter]
yeah yeah yeah okay okay okay okay
there's quite a lot of snacks in it um
most of them look rather
cheap i mean well sweets are usually
cheap i suppose
ah
okay let me show you
um
where did i put it where did i put it
okay
so do you want to see it take a look
inside the snack box first uh you will
see a few things but several layers of
snacks
so we start out
oh
and speak
now this is uh
the first look inside the snack box
[Music]
this is how it looks like it looks
pretty full
yeah
maybe something already looks familiar
to someone oh
okay okay but that's spoilers here i
don't wanna i don't want too many
spoilers where do we start um there's a
lot of small ones like uh
uh like orange
[Music]
here these are like
that
this is the
the tiny tiniest thing in it let me put
it here this is this is according to the
real size
connect size of
this some tiny baby baby snacks but it's
i think it's like uh
candy
hard candy
uh the ones with the cow look really
cute i'm not gonna eat all of them i
think which one should i eat the one in
the cow i want to try it's probably like
milk
uh oh you oh you candy
will you candy let me try i'm gonna try
the one that's uh
the the brownish cow
um it's probably the caramel wait that's
not hard candy it's like kind of soft
candy
i think
i guess this is probably like a milk
based
candy
wait i'm trying to open it
[Music]
oh okay it smells
smells good
wait dude
durian durian
wait is there you gotta warn me before
i'm eating some kind of durian candy oh
[\h__\h] no
there's no durian in this right who said
durian please no
wait it's so sticky i can't get it out
of the tiny packaging
okay i got it
that must be like caramel
[\h__\h] i got cat hairs on it
okay i'm digging into the
uh middle row right side
[Music]
ah
good stuff
it tastes like those hard caramel
candies
but it's soft
mmm it is with peanut
i don't taste the peanut
[Music]
um but it's good it is it says peanut
um what about what is the top left what
is the orange one
let me get my hand
what is this one
[Music]
that's peanut
and that's the peanut one
oh i was eating
i was eating this one
i was eating this one now
well eat this one
my fingers are so useful
okay
now let me try we're starting with small
things
hey but peanut i'm not a big fan of
peanut what is uh what is this one it's
just like
like some kind of
what this is anytime thing you know
bint
what is this one
[Music]
this one
what
that's how is this also peanut the green
one is also peanut
the koreans really like peanuts
no that's not peanut the bottom right
one is the green one is peanut
the packaging is deceiving i would have
thought it's something else
[Music]
okay
wait so we have mint and peanut and
peanut and
caramel and obviously grape
okay
is one of these not a hard candy because
the hard candies they take so long i got
to spit them on
you know what let's do something else
uh
i'll leave them i'll leave them on my
table
i want to try something else uh
what the hell is this
kore nani
what is this
sorry my shitty
shitty um
photoshopping what is this rice rice
cracker assembly
okay let me eat where is it
oh there it is okay
i hope it's not spicy it shouldn't be
spicy i don't think i made it spicy
i wish
[Music]
a rice cracker and it's falling apart
okay yeah uh i'm digging in
topping us
[Music]
oh
interesting it's kind of sw
not sweet but
it's not
it savory a nice crunch to it i like it
[Music]
it doesn't taste like the the sand base
the rice crackers that i had in japan
doesn't taste like that this tastes more
like
it doesn't taste so so
um adult it tastes more like like anyone
can eat this
[Laughter]
[Music]
it doesn't even taste salty it just has
a tiny
tiny sugary sweet
taste to it but not as much as you know
my chocolate rice waffles
[Music]
oh i should be writing oh yeah i forgot
okay
we'll start braiding them starting from
this one mm-hmm
that's what children mostly eat
i hope that the the snacks are not like
totally random snacks i hope there's
some popular snacks in here is this a
popular snack in korea
i want to eat things that you guys need
[Music]
i don't know see i can actually continue
eating this is pretty good
yeah oh really
oh a lot of people say yes oh nice too
nice okay popular but old i can imagine
popular for all the people
you mean like
what
60 year old 50 year old people
[Music]
has a long history yeah honestly the
packaging
the packaging looks uh
not as good as it tastes like the
packaging
is
like kind of boring it looks like
it's not really meant to
make people buy it
yeah it looks the packaging looks old
like it's maybe designed 20 years ago
i'm sorry but the graphic design is but
we're not reading the graphic design
we're rating the food taste
and the taste is good
okay i'll give this
[Music]
actually
i'll give it an
eight out of ten
[Music]
it's it's totally edible it's it has a
nice crunch to it
it doesn't taste weird so even for
someone with european taste this is
totally
fine i could even give it more snacks
but it's not blowing me away voice good
yeah eight out of ten pretty good rating
i think what was our highest rating in
the members only stream
we had like one good one decent snack in
[Music]
ah 10 for the soda okay but that doesn't
even count oh speaking of we should
probably
um bring out the drink there is one
drink in here that i'll be drinking
throughout do you guys know this
[Music]
this
is which i'm so excited about because i
love pineapple
oh they're laughing about it it's old
it's old
i love pineapples so and pineapple is
good for the throat
so that's pretty we should we should put
put all everything away from my table i
mean let me get rid of everything um
[Music]
i know
where's the best bus mug
here
okay okay made some space
made some space nice okay where'd you
get that well i i ordered a korean snack
box online it's yeah i ordered it online
so this is what i'll be drinking now
this
uh
okay
i hope
uh i hope it doesn't like um
if it has uh bubbles and i hope it
doesn't overflow when i open it but
listen up
listen up guys
oh
it smells
very sweet
[Music]
okay i'll drink it
good stuff it is a little a little
bubbly
a little bubbly that's 50 years old what
the [\h__\h]
am i only getting old snacks i see
[Music]
very sweet
it almost
it almost stay i guess this is normal
with pineapple juice but it almost
tastes like um
you know when you get the pineapple
rings out of the
out of a can
um
and you open it and you take out the
pineapple rings and there's like
pineapple juice left in it right so this
is
i guess
what it tastes like
but it's not bad i mean
it's just this is pineapple juice yeah
it's good i like pineapple juice not
expired no no it says made in korina
expiration date is the 12th of july um
[Laughter]
i will give this
[Music]
9 out of 10. so far holy [\h__\h] this is
pretty
pretty good sorry i misspoke this is
pretty good
nine out of ten i'm not being extra nice
this is really just actually better than
the other snack box that we had
yeah okay okay okay i'll go again holy
[\h__\h] there's so many snacks man um
what should we do next i have also no
idea what the hell this is uh
wait wait where is this one oh let me do
let
[Music]
what is this
oh
confusion in the chat i don't know old
again
[Music]
okay you guys can't really help me with
it huh you don't know what it is
there's a kanji
on the
here on the side of it uh
the bottom country you don't even see
but it says it's the i think it's the
kanji for laughing and the kanji for
luck underneath
for whatever reason that's so much
really sad i don't know what this is
i don't know what this is
i'm scared
it's about
um
it's about the size of my hand here uh
approximately uh uh
yeah about the same size as this okay
realistic sizing you don't need you
don't know what it is even though you're
korean okay well let's let's open it up
uh
okay to go oh my god oh uh okay it looks
like crackers
but probably because of the
um because of mailing it
to me um a lot of it looks
like it's falling apart
um
oh
[Music]
huh
i'm trying to get a good smell
but my nose
it smells
it smells nutty
[Music]
is it peanut again i don't know i don't
think it's peanut
it's uh one two three four five six
crackers
uh in in there
[Music]
and
uh interesting um
the crackers are like they they're
layered
okay i will try this it doesn't taste it
doesn't smell bad so
i shall try um
[Music]
can we have a picture oh let me try i
mean it doesn't look so good because
it's falling apart wait one second
[Music]
let me try
i'm gonna take a picture
[Music]
um
it actually tastes good too
maybe they purposefully picked snacks
that are
um that seem
like they would be uh
edible
for a foreigner is this safe to show on
the stream i think yeah it looks safe
looks safe
looks pretty safe
[Music]
wait
uh yeah it looks looks safe looks safe
looks safe to me
okay
[Music]
this is
this is the inside
uh as you see it's crumbling
falling apart but i i wouldn't blame
that on the snack i would blame that on
you know the
um
uh yes
uh delivery um
it's falling apart
but but on the left side here you can
see the one that's broken i i broke up i
broke off like half of it you can see
that it's like kind of a layered
layered cracker
let me take another bite
[Music]
oh you remember now
oh
it's good
what is this taste i think it might also
taste a bit caramelly and i really like
caramel so
um
actually you have it reminds me of those
famous uh lotus lotus
uh caramel
uh crackers snacks uh cookies you know
that
l-o-t-u-s
reed and crumbs yeah we're birds we like
to eat crumbs
[Music]
it tastes like that yeah although the
lotus cookies taste a bit stronger i
think um
[Music]
yeah you should eat this with um coffee
or tea
i think it would fit very well
this snack 15 years ago
so far i'm only eating snacks that are
like super old what the [\h__\h]
but don't worry the expiration dates are
fine
okay i love that dish
also
an eight out of ten not bad it's yeah
it's a bit sweet but it's not
overwhelming it also doesn't taste too
um
too artificial like one problem i have
with a lot of snacks that i ate in japan
is that they tasted very artificial to
me but so far the ones that have eaten
uh from korea they don't taste so
artificial but that might change quickly
okay
c or c
or c
okay
boomer box okay maybe i have something
that's more um artificial and more um
modern now
um
this one this one for the packaging it
looks pretty um
like for like it came from this age it's
it's not a boomer snack it's probably a
zoomer snack
it is a very long boy
um it's very
long and flat i don't know what it is i
suppose uh there's a lemon on it and
there's a coca-cola on it
um so i think this is like a sour snack
something like
ah it's one of those long
jelly
thingies with sour
stuff on it i think
it's approximately
much longer than this snack
it's about
uh let me let me turn it around
um
where did it go
where is oh i flipped it where did it go
here it is okay okay
oh perfect
okay i shall eat this i i used to love
sour jelly when i was younger
um
when do i open this
yeah so coca-cola and lemon perfect
i'm opening it up
[Music]
oh
are you supposed to
[Music]
tear them a cardinal
oh it do be sticky
[Music]
oh
warning
oh it's not that sour
[Music]
i love that
it's not even as sour as i thought it
would be
[Music]
i like it
so far
pretty good snacks pretty good stuff
y'all
[Music]
um
but honestly i think we would definitely
have a similar snack in
in austria
[Music]
i give it
eight out of ten because it could be
more sour
um i would actually like it if it was
[Music]
but
the
the choice of um
flavor is good because you can't go
around with coca-cola flavor
okay okay
for some reason my my my my hana mizu my
my nose is running
all right uh we have another weird one
and i don't from the packaging i have
absolutely no idea what it is
[Music]
there is some uh kanji on it
no no no what is this
huh
oh the people seem to at least know it
oh god snack
gosumi
kosomi
kosumi
what is it
similar to what i ate before i see
it's about
oh this size
[Music]
i love beauty yeah
that is what the kanji says
uh
it's it means going to sue me
what
ghosts go
i see some cracker
it's a nutty taste okay
uh let me open it
i think it's crackers again yeah
okay
oh oh yes a lot of small crackers
they do smell nutty
[Music]
and they have i think salt a lot of salt
on it probably
okay i'm digging in
[Music]
um
it's not bad
again it's not bad but
not really not in my taste i don't like
nutty things that much
it starts off it starts off pretty good
but then once you start chewing
it comes together as a it's a nutty mess
and um i'm not a big fan of that but
it's pretty good that's pretty good
but nothing special
i give it a
oh five out of ten it's not bad though
this is kind of boring
let me drink let me drink my
my pineapple drink
with my pineapple drink
yum yum yum
okay
going well so far
um
let's try
these ones i couldn't turn into a png
forgive me
what is these it looks more traditional
this looks more like a traditional snack
doesn't it
[Music]
what is this
they're laughing
very traditional yeah yeah i think this
is the only thing that really looks
traditional to me let me put it here
um i got a lot of these they're very
small
actually they're smaller than that and
they're like one like this size
[Music]
korean traditional juice
floor flour and flour flour and honey
okay
oh
[Music]
okay wait uh it looks the shape is cute
the shape looks a little bit like a
flower
um
the
smell is
[Music]
it does it does smell traditional
like it doesn't it doesn't smell like a
modern snack
okay
okay i'll try
um i don't know what this is
[Music]
hmm
it's not absolutely disgusting
it's not disgusting
but it doesn't really taste
good to me
um
[Music]
this is the first snack that i don't
like um
i will give it um
a three out of ten
and that's still me being nice maybe
i kind of saw it coming with like
traditional
uh snacks
yeah
you know i like my sweet snacks and my
very strongly tasting snacks yeah this
is our lowest snack so far
it's very weak on flavor as well like it
doesn't have like one particular
flavor that stands out to me
which with which i could describe it so
um
okay okay okay okay okay moving on
moving on
um
ah let's try
what is
this
it looks like something with apples
i like the design the graphic design is
decent
it is uh where is it
it is about the size
apple cookie so many cookies okay it's
about
this size okay apple cookie
fresh talk
talk saguaro
sakura cookie i remember the word for
apple
apple cookie
well it tastes like apple a cookie that
tastes like apple
that is interesting to me
oh sure
[Music]
okay the smell is all kind of weird
makes me think that
apple is not really something that a
cookie should taste oh wait it's
supposed to be like probably like
it should it should remind me of like
apple pie probably
from the looks of it
it reminds me of it i guess the visuals
remind me of an apple pie
um
it has like
a cookie base and then on top it's like
a apple jelly
and then and then it has like cookie
crumbles i guess on top of it but
it's like a pretty thin cookie
and there's two inside
okay i i'm not liking the smell of it
but you never know you never know i will
i don't really eat it now
happy meal
[Music]
uh
[Laughter]
oh that's an unpopular snack yeah i
understand i understand
um
ew
um you
that's getting um
a one out of ten from me
i know i know it from the smell it
doesn't really fit well
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's worse than the traditional snack
ew i don't like to have to taste either
ew get it out of my mouth i want my i
want my where's my what's my juice here
ah
um
[Laughter]
how does it compare to pop-tarts
oh it's pretty close it's pretty close
to it
this one is pretty close hey we need
something good again we're doing so well
and now i've been so unlucky two bad
snacks in a row
okay
next up
we have
this what is this
what is this
it says butter and it's again a cookie
uh
i think it's with oranges
maybe or i don't know there's some kind
of fruit
a butter coke oh that's bad i don't like
coconut at all
and
coconuts
[Music]
i really don't like
i don't like coconuts but i'll try it
it's about
this size
[Music]
uh yeah you can already
you can already see uh already know that
i will not like this coconut butter
cookie
[Music]
maybe the coconut taste is not so strong
okay again there's a lot of cookies in
there and it just looks like a normal
cookie
um just like a plain cookie
[Music]
okay the the coconut smell is only
pretty weak so
it might not be that bad
my favorite snack really
really with coffee very good okay boomer
boxes
my favorite snack was born in 1990 when
this is from like 1990 nice
these are some really old snacks huh
actually i got a booklet like a pamphlet
to go with these snacks and they're all
like explained
pretty cool but i don't have it with me
right now
let me try uh
[Music]
i
i don't
taste the coconut
[Music]
maybe a tiny
a tiny bit but only such a tiny bit that
even someone who hates coconut
might have no problem with this
it just tastes like a butter cookie
which is
nice but a bit boring
um
oh no
[Laughter]
but i must i must rate it as whether or
not it's edible and if it's good um so i
will give it
um i guess so
oh
it tastes like live blitz cookies i'll
give it a 6 out of 10.
i guess
i guess i don't want to continue eating
it because it's
nothing special
yeah it's kind of bland
but it's not bad it's not bad yeah 6 out
of 10
[Laughter]
edible out of 10.
okay okay let's get some good snacks in
here charlene
let's eat this mmm you know i love corn
ah cold ice cream
popping corn chips sweet and spicy spicy
look at that big corn on the packaging
um
[Music]
i love corn
wait it actually says
since 1983 on the back end but at least
the graphic design must have been
updated since then because uh the
packaging looks
like it's kind of modern yeah
okay wait this is uh i've had these i've
had
this snack before i think
um
in a different country as well
so it's it's just like i guess the
korean version of it
yeah put it on your fingers yeah you put
it on your fingers
let me open this
ah
i don't think you can put these on your
fingers um they have no opening
and they
smell weird right now but i'll give them
a try you know i love corn i love me
some corn
there are triangle shaped and a little
bit puffy and they don't have an opening
so no fingers no no no you bubby
[Music]
okay
it's really delicious okay you guys like
him so
the koreans like him so i need to
like him too yummy okay
it's spicy yeah it's so spicy on the
packaging so i'm a bit worried about the
spiciness
digging in
[Music]
hmm
the aftertaste is a little bit spicy
but
i can handle it it is sweet and spicy
indeed
it's good it tastes much better than it
smells
um
[Music]
there's like air inside so when you bite
into it
[Music]
it has a nice
nice crunchy feeling to it um
you hear that crunch mmm
nom nom
yeah i can continue eating these these
ones are like i like
you what what do you mean it says spicy
in your packaging but it's just not
spicy no it's not that it's only a tiny
bit but i guess for
for koreans maybe this is like they
wouldn't even categorize this as spicy
because they're used to much more spicy
things
that's just just a small bit
okay
but
even for someone like me who doesn't
like spicy things as i said it's really
no problem
[Music]
i do like these
the corn taste
[Music]
it works really well with the sweet and
spicy flavor that they added
[Music]
good stuff
good stuff okay let me put that here
and drink a bit from my pineapple juice
again pineapple soda
rating i forgot oh i'll give it
giving a nine out um ten
nine and a ten
nine out of ten
okay
okay now
don't tell me this is an old snack again
i'm gonna cry
next up is this
it's a chocolate bar with some puffy
rice in it i suppose
[Music]
called
kicker it old again they were laughing
again
it's about this size
looks good
very new chocolate oh really
new ruin road
zoomer oh it's neil
[Music]
it's actually new really very new really
it looks like a chocolate bar
[Music]
okay
it's a ducky moss
[Music]
no
the chocolate
is boring it tastes so bland
the chocolate tastes so bland um
it doesn't taste like super artificial
but it just tastes
so boring
i don't even care about the puffy rice
in it it's just the chocolate is boring
maybe maybe i'm too
too
spoiled by
extraordinary chocolate from europe
because we have lint and we have milka
and we have veritas pot and we have all
that amazing chocolate that just tastes
so good
so i might be spoiled by that
too used to yeah high high standards
from uh from europeans to uh chocolate
so good hell yeah
um
yeah sorry no it's not no no
i give it about
three
3.5 out of 10.
very specific
okay
next up this looks very much like a
children's snack
[Music]
uh i thought those were bananas in his
hand for a moment
do you know this oh
what
since 1981
it even says so in the top left
[Music]
yes
uh
it looks like little chocolate uh little
little um
a little little crispy cookie ball swift
chocolate cream inside
it's about
uh
this size
it's recently popular uh-huh
tina me suit takes coffee flavor oh no
i'm not a fan of coffee
so this will probably not get the
highest rating for me
um but i see okay
i know it's a baseball glove for a
moment i thought it was bananas
that's bananas
[Music]
this is not the original one oh what's
what's the original taste ah i guess the
original is uh chocolate taste and this
one is what
tiramisu
i can open it
not true cream it looks like uh
let me show you a photo
[Music]
sashi no toro
shukurimu
hi smoovie hi
it's not for you this is not for you
kitty cat i know it sounds like it when
i open plastic packaging it sounds like
i'm giving something to you
but it's not the case
okay here we go
it looks like these
it's like really small balls and uh
they look like shukurimu
[Music]
they look like a sugar shoe
shoe cream shoe like the the french ones
but
they're not as soft as them
they are uh
that actually have like a
[Music]
um
hard
cookie texture or whatever i don't know
[Music]
the smell
already smells bad
probably because i don't really like
coffee
and also smells artificial okay i'm
gonna try it i'm very picky guys i'm a
very picky person
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
you're such a kid that's a shut up why
if i was a kid i would like all of these
snacks no
um
i don't think this is only me not liking
tiramisu
i think i just also don't like the taste
of
you know the artificialness of it maybe
i don't know i don't like it no no no no
no
zero out of ten
i'm sorry
i'm sorry i'm sorry let's eat something
good how about this one
[Music]
peach flavor
a peach flavor
this looks like some kind of gummy
[Music]
yeah let's put it in front of my
nameplate
we don't like that flavor too okay
it's pretty small it reminds me of a
pucho
from japan
let me see
open it up
oh mama
the smell is good
[Music]
what it was pretty
pretty chewy
hmm
[Music]
oh
oh this is high too
this is hot the same does it say hi to
just in korean
i [\h__\h] love haiku
wow that that peach taste is so good
[Music]
japan has the same stack it calls is
it's called haichu and this one is
called
are you kidding me
that's why it's so good
[Music]
i really like them
dumb
the peach flavor it tastes very
realistic um
[Music]
um
hmm
it just takes a while to
get it all
chewed away
my rating um
[Music]
for what it is i will give it um
a 9 out of 10.
i mean
i don't usually when i go when i go
sweets um
shopping
i usually don't really pick these things
um but uh when i do then
if it tastes like that and that's
fantastic that's amazing
[Music]
we still have a few
more now about the next one i'm a bit
worried because i don't really trust
these kind of snacks
[Music]
when they come in this kind of packaging
but that's just me
next up we have this one
[Music]
a spongy soft cakes filled with rich
custard cream
i don't see a single korean font on this
one i know
it's all english since 1980 what
1989 why does it all have some kind of
stamp on it to prove me that it's really
old
see i just don't really trust these kind
of snacks because when it comes to like
cake cake-ish things
when they are like packaged in a way
that it keeps them edible for
years i just i just don't trust them
i always like twinkies
[Music]
it needs more custard oh you already
have eaten it before
okay
okay let me try oh
oops
[Laughter]
i opened it and it fell out of the
package
uh-huh
okay
okay um
it's it looks fine
let me like break it in the middle
[Music]
oh yeah
the custard inside looks like uh
egg yolk
from the texture as well
but it smells good
okay i'm trying i may need milk eat with
milk
[Music]
hold up
thankfully it doesn't taste as
artificial as a firewood
um
[Music]
it's like a cake spongy cake
or something with a little bit of
custard cream so
it's not
bad it's not bad but i wouldn't choose
it as a snack
hi smoovie hi hi you want some custard
cake
um
i shall give it um
meow indeed yes
i will give it all
let me pet my cat
meow
i will give it um
[Music]
four out of ten
maybe four four point five out of ten
[Music]
okay okay okay
yeah sorry
it's not not really oh convincing okay
now we're getting to the end of it
wait which one did i not eat ah i think
only two snacks left
ato
which one should we go first maybe this
one
or
maybe this one
okay next up is something like a potato
snack
that is not a potato
[Music]
what is this
it's so old
well the expiration date is fine
um it looks like nuts
a rice snack korean style popcorn
classic goblin aha okay okay okay
okay okay
let me actually uh put down my hands
okay
uh kiana froggianna there's no space for
you anymore
uh
okay sorry no more space for you i need
to put my snack there
[Music]
wow the whole table is filled with stuff
[Applause]
okay
is this gonna be good or what oh
interesting
um
it doesn't look like popcorn
[Music]
what is that
what the [\h__\h] is that
[Music]
that is such a weird experience to bite
into
right now that i
[Music]
wait a second now that i'm eating it it
reminds me of one thing
[Music]
did you hear that
no it's not layers but it's just very
interesting
[Laughter]
into milk yeah this could probably work
well
as a breakfast cereal with milk
i feel like i've eaten something similar
before that's just a bit smaller and
yeah but it has it
kind of has the same
has the same texture what the hell
[Music]
no it's not a toothbreaker it feels like
when i'm biting into it feels like it's
like uh
the texture is like
[Music]
what am i
maybe i eating
one of them
yeah what am i eating
well this is
it's fascinating
eat with milk
you mean in a bowl with with milk and a
spoon
so literally like breakfast
it's very spongy yeah but then it has
like
something
oh i don't even know what it tastes like
although i really wouldn't i don't think
it would be
yeah it feels like stirrer for him for
foam
yes yes yes yes thanks for saying that
it feels like it but it's not like it
tastes like it obviously
um
interesting that is korean popcorn
that was
an interesting experience but
hey
i don't know what to make out of it
just to be cool
i will give it
a question mark out of 10
i am very confused by this snack i i
cannot judge it is question mark
[Laughter]
[Music]
out of ten huh
okay we have one more snack
oh
this feels like jelly
the packaging seems rather um
new
my table is a [\h__\h] mess right now
here we go this is the last one sorry if
you feel like this doesn't really
represent it but um they did say like in
the order in the description they did
say something like it's it's
edible things like it's not crazy snacks
in there nothing too crazy you know
okay so this is like a grape
um gummy candy
we know what i'm missing here is that
what was it peppa doll pepperoni where
the [\h__\h] is my pepperoni
where is my pepperoni
pinot pedal i want to pedophile the
pepperoni
[Music]
wow what what an artificial oh smell
that is wow
very soft though
very squishy
oh my wow that grape
smell is so overwhelming
i do like the texture
it's very soft to touch and very soft to
bite into
[Music]
the taste is not as quite
artificial
and overwhelming as the
as the smell is so the taste is better
than the smell i would say
[Music]
the texture is very soft yes
as a gummy would be a jelly gummy
[Music]
i give it um oh by the way what does the
what does this 60
mean
what
and 20
up what
what does it mean
what do the numbers mean mason
what does this mean
not durian ah grape juice 60 grape juice
oh
so they upped it by 20 maybe
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow
20 more than before
not bad not bad
not
that was pretty good too i will give it
um
5.5 out of 10.
okay that's all the snacks that i had
today i didn't eat all of the little
small tiny candies that we had
um but yeah mostly that was it yay
thank you
um i i do want to try more i'm sure
there's way more snacks that you guys
would recommend to me
then what i have on the table right now
[Music]
yeah yeah um
oh i want to make an austrian slash
european chocolate
uh snack box and send it to the myth
members because holy [\h__\h] we have some
good snacks here
but i am uh generally by average way
more um
positively
convinced about these snacks than i was
with the snacks that we had in the
member stream we had an international
snack box
in a members only stream
um and those were mostly disgusting
you should have tried choco pie i had
choco pie in japan before is it the same
thing
it's probably the same thing though
what a fun stream right yeah thank you
well next month we'll actually have a
russian snack box um
russian snacks i have no idea what to
expect out of it but yeah
so these are my korean snacks
it was pretty tasty i'm going to
continue drinking the pineapple drink
oh yeah pineapple they know what i like
it's good for my fruit
please no doriando no
i will never eat a durian no there's no
way they would send me a durian
[Music]
ah
yeah
but but my dear korean friends
i want to go shopping and eating
in korea
this year
[Music]
that was me speaking
i already told
yesterday i met um rmt my old roommate i
met her yesterday and we went shopping
and eating together and then i told her
you know i want to go on some trips here
because we're going on a trip on a
skiing trip um
in february and i told her i kinda wanna
also go to
uh
dusseldorf for um eating japanese there
again i want to eat tonkatsu and
yakiniku there and dusseldorf and she
was like oh i want to come with you
let's go on a food trip and then i was
like okay okay oh my god what do you
think about going to korea
i kind of want to go to korea this year
yeah they i don't think they're as as
strict with um entering the country as
japan i mean honestly i have no idea but
i'm just kind of guessing it um and i
always wanted i never been there before
and i kind of really want to go
fashion shopping there
i want to buy clothes i want to buy
clothes and eat food food so
um i might i might go with rmt she's
she's pretty open for it so
that's exciting
yeah
we're gonna
eat a lot of food together
yeah
[Applause]
yeah i think they're probably more open
[Music]
in germany i've been there before but i
want to go there again i've been telling
myself i'll go back there because last
time i was there
my favorite and the one and only place
that makes proper tonkatsu in i think
all of [\h__\h] europe
uh or at least the only place that is
somewhat
close to me i mean not really because i
have to fly there but the only tonkatsu
place that i know uh in europe
um it was closed the last time i was in
dusseldorf for dokomi for
for a job it was closed and i was like
[\h__\h] are you kidding me they even have
honey toast there which is amazing
yeah will it be a fan meeting no no no
just going there for like a
one day trip or two day trip just to eat
food
yeah
nine nine flinging this field billy guys
please try the good snacks in korea yeah
yeah when i
go to korea i will report to you guys
what i have eaten and uh
what it tasted like
if i liked it where i went i will give
you a full report just like i did with
my paris report
[Music]
street food oh yeah i guess korea is
well known for their street food as well
i did see a lot of videos on youtube in
my recommendations about street food
yeah now that you say it i remember
i watched a bunch of videos
hell yeah
they make some really
fascinating stuff with
korean
food what did i see
oh oh
oh
whoa
the corn dogs look good
oh what is this
[Music]
you don't even know what i'm looking at
but everything looks great oh
oh yeah i was wondering about the
youthful burgers i i saw this video
about korean street food that's about
youful burgers
it's fascinating because the bread like
it looks like a ufo and it's completely
closed and it protects the the inside of
the burger from spilling out i guess
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
they have like their own they created
their own toaster device
and it like closes it
is
schweiss than burger to summon how do
you say it's a salmon spice in english
yeah but i need to try like the more
traditional things as well i'm just like
kind of scared uh that they're too spicy
[Music]
uh it fuses it together yes i guess so
or it seals it together perhaps
look it up it's called ufo burger in
korea
[Music]
yeah so that's that uh i hope you
enjoyed the the snack review we're gonna
be doing more of those
every month i think i will be doing one
yeah
um
[Music]
every month different one
until it circles and we go back to the
same country and then i'll just stop
yes yes
wow i'm excited to see
what weird snacks each country has
many many calories for me but don't
worry i usually only take like one bite
it's kind of a waste but
um
[Music]
my favorite i think
i don't know if i gave it the highest
rating but i think my favorite was uh no
i think my favorite was this one
[Music]
where is the layer for the long boy
no that's not it
this one no that's not it
no no
no no i can't pick it up
i don't know which one it is
eight number eight ah this this one this
one and the pop popping corn chips
i think those might be my favorites
um
the the long
long sour boy
hey
thank you very much for the good food
i enjoyed it actually um i do have to
say the the the
these ones were not that evil these are
pretty good too yeah
they're tasty too
i have two of those so
gotta eat them
should i read some super chats
should i read them while we're here um
[Music]
should we keep all the snacks
here as well
[Music]
however you feel like oh yeah we should
read it because tomorrow after holo talk
we won't be reading it but holy [\h__\h]
what a mess it is holy crap it's such a
mess here let me clean up a tiny bit
ah
[Music]
it's
all on my real table let me clean up but
i'll keep the rest
on stream
[Music]
queen job
i do want to say though
i think i might have said it during my
uh international snack box review but
you know you get used to the snacks of
the country where you grow up
at
so
when you eat chocolate or anything from
a different from a very different
country then there's a chance that it
might just taste really weird to you but
a person from that country if they were
to eat chocolate from your country
chances are that your chocolate that you
like so much will taste weird to them as
well so
i am not
saying that you know the snacks that i
rated low uh with a low rating that
they're really disgusting it's just to
me
um i'm probably used to a different
taste
and
if you if you tried yourself you might
actually really enjoy it obviously
everyone's tastes are different and uh
even more so when you
come from a different
uh
a different
continent i suppose
thank you i'm glad you enjoyed it i will
read super chats now
uh
let me you know what let me put it on
let me put this
um
super chat reading now how do i say
let me say that in korean
hey
yummy now
[Music]
how do i say it in korean
chat goes too fast
okay one problem i have with hyper chat
i don't know if it's just me but it
doesn't stop i can't scroll
whoa whoa
i i tried to copy something but i
i don't know what i just copied
i think
i think this is it this is it right
bring froggianna back you miss her
me too
let me try to find the space for her
oh frog
[Music]
and what a ball
um
and the glassware so on
there we go
here where you want to go for rocky i
need some space for you
[Music]
maybe here
yeah that works
[Music]
this one
what it's the same
no it's a little bit different
[Music]
okay
it would still be okay okay okay all
right it looks a tiny bit different
froggy olives hooray
hurry frog kiana
we only have to read super chats from
this stream so
i don't think it will take too long
let's start at the very bottom
[Music]
you know what i take it back it's a
little bit yeah yeah
is the btm okay
and also depends on my tangents mhm
[Music]
yeah that's no problem thank you for
coming anyway
okay
thank you for the pinky
can't wait for those uh two days concert
but sorry that for me it's hard to show
up in person but i will still give my
highest support in front of my pc oh no
problem no problem i'm i'm not judging
you at all i think for most people
of the whole life english audience it
will be
um
you know watching it online rather than
being there in person but if you happen
to be in japan um as far as i know
they're currently in the third round of
um
i think it is a raffle
i think the the system is a raffle i
might be wrong but from what i've seen
it's a raffle you can enter to try to
get a ticket and then you will be
notified whether or not you got it
[Music]
for like going there in person
and it's the third round some people
already have uh
the
like the confirmation
that they got a ticket and some people
are still trying
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah that's how they do it
yeah because i guess there's like a lot
of people trying to buy it and rather
than having it being first come first
served
you
enter a raffle and then you get notified
whether or not you got it
online
[Music]
wait i already know i have a phrase
she
[Music]
he said i want to eat street food in
korea one day ah
looks delicious man
yum yum yum food trip let's go
i'll i'll gain like uh 10 kilograms
[Music]
of weight
but no problem i'll lose them quickly
[Music]
good pronunciation and
when you mean this
[Music]
oh thank you i know my pronunciation is
so good
[Music]
i'm asking is my korean pronunciation
good
[Music]
very nice
all right
[Music]
i agree thank you lip syncing skills
well i have some experience with it
remember that tales of talk
not many people know but i told you once
and i actually had to re-record
my video part of that i had the voice
but i deleted the video and um after
editing it uh yeah i
had to re-record the whole thing
the whole interview with me just sitting
in the hotel studio and acting as if i
was
talking and i it was really difficult
because
it was like a one and a half hours um
interview
and
holy [\h__\h] that was tough
because there was no proper script i
just had to wobble wow
but i only told you guys afterwards and
beforehand no one had uh
the idea that this was kind of
off that something was going on yeah you
guys had no idea
yeah
a professional i'm a professional after
all
anyway
[Music]
thank you for the pinkie
the super expo announcement helped me
get my cold chimpkin buns out of bed
this morning yeah nice you were very
safe and i can't wait to cheer you on
still teaching irl but i'll get up early
to catch your snack box review oh well i
changed the
time so maybe you had to
get up um a little bit later i hope that
was good for you
[Music]
thank you very much
yeah i'm really excited about the
announcement finally we can talk about
the fact that we are proud of it as well
yeah
it's off of my shoulders wait that's
there's actually a second part to the
super chat oh and empress i would very
much like your
opinion on cocoon superchat before mine
i know it is a blue but katon is a loyal
chimpkin so i'm sure there's a nice
compliment about your files if i had to
guess
wait
[Music]
oh you mean it's not you you don't mean
the one that's like immediately before
you you mean like a couple months before
you
my or she getting thick with all those
snacks
tys i'm not getting fake i'm only taking
like a tiny bite out of all of these
also he wrote t-i-e-s on purpose so i
read t-i-e-s on purpose
i know i know how to say it by now
faking the chicken thickening the
chickening that's an old saying that we
had
pretty nostalgic thickening the
chickening
picking the chicken
um
i think from the point of view of german
speaking people um the way i say of
[Music]
oh god it's so wrong it's
my th pronunciation
um
makes it sound as if i'm saying
[\h__\h]
the chicken um
[Music]
i never really realized this
i think when i used to say this
[Music]
oh
dear okay this is the one occasion where
i wish um i could say
th properly
freaking the chickening
stick and the chicken
anyway moving on thank you pogba for the
two pinkies that's one kiss for you
thank you
thank you for your support thank you for
getting up today for the stream even
though it was really early like honestly
i don't know how you guys do it i would
never do that i would i would not have
the
determination to get up so early for a
stream when i could just watch the
archive
but you guys prefer to watch it live
which i understand as well
thank you for that thank you for your
dedication
drink it's monkey donkey ezekiel rama's
thank you
rainbow is a rainbow thank you
congrats on the concert already bought
the tickets first idle concert for me
and of course for my absolute aussie
that is the bestest i'm sure it will be
great also remember that you asked us if
we ever dreamed about you i don't
usually dream or remember my dreams but
i dreamed about you there was a new nsfw
kiana fan artist on twitter and everyone
was wondering who it was it was too easy
to find out because the handle was kiada
out legit
so in the next stream kf we tried to
expose you like you exposed them but
instead of denying it you started making
r18 art of kfp employees that called you
out that sounds like [\h__\h]
sadly i woke up before i could see any
not at all what kiada would do but still
the best dream ever love you
i'm gonna do a rainbow now but i don't
know what to say so i'm gonna go full
yonder they love you love you love you
love you love you love you love you love
you love you love you lovely
okay
it's you really dream that it was very
detailed
that is very detailed wow um
i do not have uh
an out
where i post r18 art i don't
let me just make that very clear
i do not
i do not no no no i don't even have time
for that
[Music]
yeah um that is a weird trick
but well i i guess it means you're
thinking about me
and and it means you
like me so thank you very much
oh man
oh man you don't have to even try
looking for that account it does not
exist
uh
no that is not cringe please watake as
much as you want from home
i would appreciate it trevor g dankeshen
for the pinky kiwamo congrats i'm still
so ecstatic over the loon i've already
put in vacation time and book my spawn
tickets you mean booked yeah
one more dream to check off the list
right so okay if people flock to watch
and cheer you on and link your fish
you'll have your own oh hand and
travel
oh and done instead of oh and done you
wrote oh hen done
that is so cute
oh can i show can i show christina's art
i need to show it because when you say
ohen done
all i can think of is that it's so cute
have you guys seen it on twitter
[Music]
it starts off like this
whole lives uh second best beyond the
stage 2020
uh 2020.
[Music]
i
i was i did not do a watch along with
that did i
that was before my uh
that was before my debut right
but you guys are already there you guys
are already there
i'm 20 20.
wait you mean 2021
[Music]
i'm confused but okay so this is me
watching concerts together with you guys
and
look at your chimpkins we're cheering
together
and then
[Music]
wait actually is this
wait i just realized there's actually a
chimpkin holding a picture of us
watching it together wow that's cute and
then he looks up and it's me give it
[Music]
tears in its eyes and holds
and then i ran oh god
[Music]
you see in the background uh the small
ones are uh this is moona and eofy even
oh
oh why is
so cute why are you guys so cute look at
you
[Music]
i love you guys
stop it
my eyes can't sit
my gummy and i
[Music]
christina
why are you doing this
why why why why
[Music]
why why is a four four kuma
manga comics so
so emotional
[Music]
it has [\h__\h] chickens in it
it's raining indoors
so cute
[Music]
okay
okay i'm good
[Music]
poof
yeah
i'm gonna be thinking of you guys
i'm gonna be thinking of you when i'm
in the concert
blue thank you for the pinky we're so
happy and excited for the amazing news
thank you for all the hard work you've
been putting in we're very proud of your
dental look forward to your performance
with chimpkins will definitely cheer
twerk hard for you
can you guys i want i want some of you
guys to do
like maybe there's some streamers among
you
can you guys still watch along i want to
watch somebody's reaction
i want to watch kfb's reaction
can you guys still watch along too on
your side and then send it to me
i want to have your reaction i mean we
can do a watch along
of the archive of my performance later
on but i also want to see your your
first time um reaction
i want to see though the first
time reaction not the second time
watch along off the watch long
yeah no i will watch it privately but
[Music]
do
i want to see your reaction yeah show me
[Music]
maybe you can post your reactions on
twitter as well yeah put a put a camera
in front of your monitor and then when
when kiara
is there then you go like wow
and then upload that on twitter okay
thank you
that would make me very happy
please
[Music]
look at it
embarrassed to show my face then i don't
know
blur it blur it afterwards i guess
that's okay
or show me privately somehow
send me an unlisted uh
youtube link
and okay koreans are tasty thank you
thank you
[Music]
um
i wish you the best of luck taka taka
tried to sign up for a ticket apparently
there is no no answer yet but let's wish
him the best one of the few kfp people
representing in japan let's hope that
the few ones that are actually able to
go to the concert that they actually get
a ticket
yeah
it's not sold out yet but it's a raffle
yeah so you need a lot of luck we wish
you the best all of kfp hopes you get a
ticket
oh for them online
go infiltrate the system tucker
infiltrate the system
[Music]
uh cruise thank you for two pinkies
i'm extremely excited for their
announcement and although i'm sad i
can't go in person to experience it live
i'm sure it's going to be amazing and
i'll be cheering with my stylish kfp
apron i got from the birthday match oh
speaking of birthdays it's mine as well
and i was wondering i could possibly get
a happy birthday song in german like you
did with risu it was extremely cute
thank you for all the wonderful times as
always love ya thank you
kind kitchen
so sweet of you yeah i i
i um i wish all of you guys could go in
person but obviously even if the borders
were open even then it would be
difficult for all of you guys can't
bring everyone there and
that's just the way it is but i think
you know when we watched my
um when we did the watch-alongs of
concerts at home together it was always
a lot of fun anyway you just gotta kind
of like
instead of watching it silently alone
you should watch it together with
someone get an actual pen light and
really get in the mood don't be don't be
so quiet just because you're alone at
home you should really just act as if
you are at the concert because then you
can cheer even louder and you can dance
even more yeah
who knows if they're even allowed to
cheer uh loudly at the concert because
like for some concerts they
um had the rule to not share with their
voices you know because of the sea thing
um yeah i like it quite well if you like
it that way then that's fine too but if
you want it to be more like an
experience as if you were at the concert
then i think you should
just you know be loud as loud as you
want yeah because whatever senpai's uh
concerts for the people who were there
in person they were not allowed to cheer
with their voices
so when we were watching it at home
together on a stream we were able to
share more
than the people at the actual concert
which is a little bit ironic but
yeah we went all out i went all out and
it felt like uh i was pretty immersed i
was i was pretty immersed yeah
go watch it on a big screen
yeah it's so much more fun yeah if you
if you're like really getting yourself
into it rather than just watching it
silently i think it's more fun um
[Music]
when oh that would be dope yeah
but
maybe in the future maybe in the future
there's like vr tickets who knows
i mean cover
cover is a company that started out with
vr so
i think so um
i i think
that we are already doing vr stuff like
the the cinderella switch
you know that do you know about that
it's only been done by japanese talent
so far
um but it's something like like there's
two japanese talents for the people who
don't know there's two japanese talents
for example let's say toa senpai and
pakoda senpai so um you can
like buy a ticket i guess um and then
you go into vr and you cheer for example
next to thomas advice if you choose it
that way then tula senpai will be next
to you cheering together you can look
over and she'll be there and she'll you
get you guys to give a cheer on piccolo
by his performance so that's what
cinderella switches and then you can
turn it around and you can have piccola
at your side and you can cheer on toast
by on stage
and it feels really immersive because
you're obviously doing it in vr
yeah it's fun
and and the the member who's next to you
they will like kind of interact with you
as well like she will look over to you
and be like yeah yeah
i mean i never i never actually watched
it
properly but i kind of have a an idea of
what it's like so
yeah
it is really cool i hope we can do that
within yen as well at some point it
sounds like a lot of fun
there's a lot of possibilities yeah
i heard there were headphones ah yeah
there might have been headphones
[Music]
i would love to share with you and ollie
ollie would be great for cinderella's
switch
as a as a viewer oh my god yeah both me
and ollie i guess
i get i get very hyped up sometimes as
well
ollie would be a great choice too yeah
she will she will scream endlessly
[Music]
oh that would be amazing
oh i forgot chris i i tangented away oh
please let me sing for you happy
birthday
fan club
[Music]
special day for you
treat yourself
treat yourself to some cake
and
i don't know i don't know how you like
to celebrate everyone likes to celebrate
differently but
celebrate yourself
yeah
today's also my birthday i felt that
what happy birthday
uh
wait i can't scroll the name is gone
wait
happy birthday
[Music]
treat yourself
and okay so this is so slowly but surely
where the korean super chats start so
it's going to be a lot of translating
um
park park in
[Music]
they're my glorious and presentation i'd
absented yesterday's collab because i
forgot the schedule and it streams for
another channel ah but
you missed it i reminded you guys i even
did a community post did you see that i
felt like that community post was kind
of a shadow band or so and i did a
twitter post i reminded you guys a
million times on stream on twitter how
could you still miss it
ah and then i absented two days ago when
can you playing snake game because i've
fallen asleep how lazy can't be am i so
send the rainbow for my glorious empress
you are going to the usual room how can
you miss it when i'm reminding you so
often
let me read the rest of your super chat
uh
in addition when the link of zelda part
2 broadcast i misunderstood what time
tantra said i swear i never tried to lie
or glorious empress i understand my
nickname korean word meaning what so i
translated it to the boss
ah huh okay but you were you're late a
lot these days
how could you miss them the stream on
the official channel it was even a good
time for you
it was a good time for korean viewers
[Music]
bad chimpkin
go to the usual room
[Music]
hmm
it's not a question anymore though
i'm not asking you if you want to go i
am saying you are going
[Music]
yeah
um one week
minimum
yes
ah but thank you thank you
a case for your function
optimus prime
park comes
[Music]
oh you were supporting you were cheering
on changgoon
oh how nice are you besties
well you won't see him for a while
because he'll be in the usual room
you're on your own now
[Music]
thank you for the rent super chat love
you too
thank you soon for the support
yeah
another korean name
[Music]
thank you
thank you for the wonderful news denzel
it will be a glorious concert you've all
been working to make this endeavor as
successful as your other projects and
kfp will be there along with all the
other fans i hope everything goes
smoothly glory to kp thank you glory to
carefully indeed thank you
it will be glorious i think i hope like
i wish i i want to um
i want to check out the expo itself
uh
i don't think it will be possible but
maybe maybe some cave people who can
check out the expo
will uh send me pictures
and videos yeah
yeah
i want to walk around the
expo
makuhari
get to work kfp
for the kfp
uh
why are you doing something for the
expert well i mean if you look at the
expo picture you see all of us there so
uh
we all will be there in some form but i
cannot say any details more details will
be revealed later on the expo is more
like an expo so it's not a concert but
uh
every whole live member will be there in
one way or another
[Music]
cannot share details
thank you
please watch the concert
uh online if you can dr jack i know you
will i know you will
thank you soon for your love and support
[Music]
i will i will i think i will do the
watch along the question is just
you know will i do it a lot alone or
should i should i maybe i could
i couldn't buy kelly
but the thing is when i invite someone
else to watch it together with me i will
probably hold back
a lot
uh
yeah uh cause like when i watch
something like that alone
i'll i'll be way more like
excited and sing along probably but when
i have uh
someone with me i'll i won't be singing
along because that's kind of awkward
uh
yeah uh
well i wasn't there for the whole time
so
it was uh at least sometimes i could
sing along
um
i don't know maybe maybe kelly uh
is gonna even watch it
in person who knows
i don't know what her plans are i'm
thinking about it but i feel like i can
be more open and excited
with
kelly together what would be
with alone sorry alone but what would
might be interesting cannot speak
english anymore what might be
interesting is if like uh
me and kelly do a watch long on the
first day and then i may you know do a
watch long on the second day you know
whoever is not
uh
performing on on one day is doing a
water long on that day
wouldn't that be
interesting
[Music]
perhaps that wouldn't that be nice
maybe i'll ask them if they want to do
that
[Music]
okay
okay i'll ask but don't get your hopes
up
maybe they want to watch it privately
you know
but it is a special
special
uh
special thing so
special uh opportunity special uh what
what am i looking for what's the word
occasion a special occasion so
ah
yeah yeah
cheer each other on
wouldn't that be nice
[Music]
and one more thing that was kind of
awkward though when watching a
concert together like last time as well
was that there is kind of a delay
it's not it's so hard to get it like
timed perfectly
i remember with ina we had quite the
delay
so even if i am singing along it might
get like so annoying because it's
delayed they might have to mute me
[Music]
i mean
you mean the the the comic the manga
yeah we also cried about it here
it worked out in her favor
uh
actually already has a ticket
and he got it for the second day he got
it before it was announced that we will
be here so it's perfect he got it for
the second day and i'm on the second
date
[Music]
how lucky is he i think second day is
also vatime and those are his two or
she's me and vatamin
how lucky is he
yeah
holy [\h__\h]
i don't think he knew uh when watame
would be performing when he first um
uh entered the raffle though i don't
think you can choose which day you will
just be assigned to a day
as a day in a seat
[Music]
a ticket hopefully hopefully you're
getting one
um
i am uh squeezing my thumbs for you
[Music]
thai duncan
thank you
[Music]
me
weird pronunciation that this lady is
giving me huh
so fast what
magic autumn yeah
ramsay duncan
[Music]
let's go
let's go let's go where are we going i
got the tickets immediately i'm super
happy and you mean the online tickets
nice i'm so proud that my cute idol
aussie will be performing a concert
stage is the natural habitat of the
phoenix after all
thank you yes it is it is it is where i
feel like i need to be
yes i will enjoy it as much as i can
i'll try to make the best out of it
um
[Music]
thank you
it's it's actually finally completing
one of the few goals that i had left
on my
on my list from my debut
debut
[Music]
no
a few more goals off of my list how
exciting
yeah yeah yeah
thank you unity chad and you'll be there
too
to witness it
yes
the very moment
brandon wood thank you yeti logistics
function
[Music]
boom
there are many old style snacks and
snacks that i've never seen before
attention good luck oh man
i feel like this is often the case when
you buy snack boxes like this there's
like
often snacks that probably are not the
most popular choices when going to a
supermarket and i suppose a lot of very
cheap snacks
yeah
but i mean if i could i would get you
guys to put together a box for me and
send it to me directly but that is
unfortunately not possible and if only
if only i had a whole life member in
every country of the world and i would
get them to make a box for me but that
is also not the case so yeah i gotta
rely on these snack box
services there are several ones this one
i ordered from a different one than
before
um because i missed out on the korean
snack box by one month from that uh
service so i bought it on a different
uh service hmm
ask reina for indoor snack ah that is a
good idea yeah yeah yeah
for indonesia i could ask uh the
indonesian girls yeah
that is true
old-fashioned snack yeah
i i did get the feeling uh
when i was looking at the packaging the
packaging already looks old-fashioned
for a lot of them
why can't we send me a p.o box oh
because
sending food is ng and sending presents
in general has been
completely
um
cancelled
by her life management a while ago like
we can't take birthday presents either
it's only letters
for safety's sake
[Music]
but thank you jehovah
thank you don't worry there
i i do not think that this is all korea
has to offer not at all i'm sure you
guys have even more um really really
yummy snakes
snakes snacks
what the [\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
foreign for the rest of the chat thank
you
oh it's partially korean partially uh
ah
which one was the superdome again one of
the first ones
i don't remember which one was the
soporo
polo
[Music]
the middle one is it uh
was it
no
what is this one is
this
one
i forgot was it good i think it was okay
i already forgot there were so many
there were quite a few similar ones like
a lot of cookies a lot of brown
cookies that were
that tasted pretty normal
so it was not bad i was i was worried
that there would be more like weird
tasting things but it was actually
everything pretty edible
thank you
a kiss for you too
crumbly
cookies doppler stained vancouver
the taste of the shippers seems a bit
outdated their products currently being
produced but some are unfamiliar
familiar to viewers yeah yeah it feels
kind of outdated they have they had this
pamphlet i gotta take a look at it at
the end and i'll say what it says
delusional dreamer
thank you
thank you i have the most friend
michael that's what she said thank you
hjj
you 89.
thank you
oh there is a word for boomer box in
korean
oh my god really
[Music]
it just says a box
it's just a box according to papago
oh there they're laughing
[Music]
huh
don't say that
oh man
oh it i got deceived
bamboozled
oh yeah
[Music]
books
i don't know if it's a good sign that
they're laughing
dentures
what
literally boom books wow okay old style
box bad words wow okay i guess it's like
a
muhammad i feel i understand write some
free dancing
kind of makes sense they send all the
brands next they survive in the industry
meaning that they're generally popular
in the country and not a quick comes and
gone when people forget in in one year's
time
right so free are you are you okay
that's
the way you wrote
that sentence
feels like you were a little bit
confused but you got the spirit and i
understood the message
thank you thank you
[Music]
sorry ryzza free for roasting you
i have my problems too
i have my issues too and speaking
english
no good gentlemen
run out of space no problem if you run
out of space you gotta go watch sana's
streams a bit more unui
now for the red super chat wait what
does this mean
[Music]
yeah one of the snacks i think is called
kosomi
thank you for the another red super chat
thank you so much you apparently really
enjoyed this wait you sent another one
after that too
another rant super chat that says that's
the most favorite snack of my grandma
so what are you saying it's not my fault
i didn't order these specifically
give me give me more modern consumer
snacks then please
oh man
i can't help it that's not my choice
they just put random things in there
thank you for being so generous though
[Music]
thank you
yeah you missed the box but you can
watch the archive if you want
kylie
comes
on
[Music]
my
um
[Music]
i like it though but it's literally
dedicated to the ancestors during the
traditional festival so it's super old
for real yeah yeah yeah i understand no
problem i i
i kind of
expected it to taste like that i know
like the traditional snacks from japan
are a bit similar like
they obviously don't taste
like
like tradition like newer snacks from
nowadays
don't worry about it it's kind of what i
expected it to taste like thankfully
it's not like the whole box was filled
with traditional snacks
thank you for the membership thank you
welcome
um so thank you max
thank you for the pinky very nice of you
thank you for supporting my stream
traditional food be like that yeah but
when i think about it
i i really like the fact that they have
traditional snacks to begin with because
when i think about it i don't think
austria and germany really have
something like that
we just have the snacks that we have
there's no like
differentiation at least there might be
old snacks but nothing really that we
would call
a traditional snack
or traditional sweets i
i wouldn't be able to think of anything
i think like also
doesn't the same apply to to you guys
maybe from america or from canada or
australia
[Music]
i wouldn't
i wouldn't call anything traditionally
like like like these ones like there's a
big difference between traditional
sweets
in korea or in japan
to
non-traditional ones
pop-tarts
that is not the same
are you kidding me no this is not no you
can't
pop-tarts are not your country's
traditional snack
it's not the same thing
[Music]
get out of here get annie i'm going to
take your [\h__\h] pom-pom and i'm going
to throw it on the ground get out of
here with your pop-tarts
oh man
are you going to offer pop-tarts to your
ancestors are you are you gonna offer it
to the gods or whatever you're gonna go
to a church and lay a [\h__\h] pop-tart
in front of the uh grand altar
that's what you're gonna do it's [\h__\h]
disrespectful they're gonna kick you out
of the church and you're gonna be
unlucky for the rest of your life and
you're gonna end up in hell
oh man
[Music]
london
donuts and timbits are pretty
traditional for us you guys have no idea
what i'm talking about are you
you don't understand it you don't get it
you don't get it
[Music]
are you doing it on purpose
get out of here
[Music]
it's hard to pin down one specific food
for the us because we're a melting pot
of different cultures
i guess i guess
[Music]
i would offer
i think in austria the only thing that i
would maybe call
a traditional sweet is smart marzipan
[Music]
although i mean i think that's not
it's obviously not an austria only thing
but it's uh
one thing that gets used
specifically in austria a lot for
um
in in for like
sweets and cakes but i don't like it but
yeah it feels it feels kind of
traditional i think
anyway i gotta read super chat
uh yeah mozart is
[Music]
mozart might be someone who i would
consider a traditional existence but i
think the mozart chocolate
was probably invented kind of later on
so i wouldn't quite say that one is
traditional either although although it
tastes
it has marzipan in it and that makes it
a bit if if anything that would be
something i would put on the list
anyway
my german is so good well that's because
my first language my first my mother
tongue is german
[Music]
why not cakes
i wouldn't
i wouldn't call
christmas cookies traditional i mean
not in i mean yes they're like a
tradition to make each year but i
wouldn't
again i wouldn't categorize it the same
way as as you know differentiating here
these uh
traditional korean
uh
sweets in comparison to non-traditional
ones but okay it's really difficult to
explain this but so whatever
taco bell
you got
thank you for getting it
i'm glad it finally arrived
at your doorstep
huh
i can help
[Music]
wait
foreign
[Music]
it's very important to say that in
before a meal i i respect that but i
didn't know the word until now i should
have looked it up beforehand
they like to say
uh thank you for the food before oh wait
is that is itadakimasu right it's not
kochi so
do you guys have a word for kochi sosa
madestra as well like after the
after the food
because in japan i always they always
say itadakimasu before and they say
afterwards
i'm digging in and then thank you for
the food
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
get that soup
i'm gonna get that soup nida
look
get soup
i just literally just today before the
stream i watched the seinfeld episode
about the soup
uh
they gave him a specific name i'm not
gonna say it but the soup the soup
episode
you know the soup episode
[Music]
soup
the soup guy
oh man no stuff for you
no show for you
i i became a big soup fan after going to
a restaurant chain in japan that's
called the the soup stock
it's really good if you're ever in japan
go to the soup stock
you can order like a menu with an
amazing soup and then a curry with it
chicken curry with rice
and soup
[Music]
really good soup gets is it cheap it's
normal price
[Music]
i'm at the soup store
okay i need to read super dance sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry kai come san nida for the
pinky
[Music]
i don't know who picked those but you
really need to punish him or her
[Music]
whoever picked those sweets needs to be
scolded apparently
it wasn't really that bad like i i at
least thought most of them were
edible so
no problem don't worry about it
thank you though for the pinky we don't
need to punish anyone no no it's all
good
we're on good terms
thank you
for watching today yeah super junior
sorry sorry sorry sorry
they do a funny dance with that song
they touch the the back of their feet
first they first they make a fire
they go from one side to another they
make a fire like sorry sorry so with
their hands they
they
rub their hands
sorry sorry sorry sir and then they uh
with the right hand they touch their the
back of their left foot and with the
left and they touch the back of their
right foot and then do that dance i
remember
[Music]
i know i know it's a funny choreography
oh they're washing hands against yeah i
am
[Music]
my favorite snack is luaker
what is that
let me look it up
oh
they're from here
from
italy or south to rome which is i guess
yeah uh
i've seen them before oh
yeah
korean bro likes uh south tarolian snack
a lot although they're not i don't think
they're that popular here
and there's very similar ones that are
more popular more well-known they look
the same they're called mana schnitzen
if you like those then you probably also
like mana schnitzen
m-a-n-n-e-r
that's a
the brand the company and they make a
lot they make those cookies and they
also make like
recently i've been drinking hot
chocolate from a manor
powder a powder that they make
[Music]
it's a very popular souvenir for people
who go to austria and if they don't get
mozart kugel then they often get mana
schniten
[Music]
it's like a
simple
waiver chocolate waiver
but they have a
um very
they're the packaging they have a design
that stands out a lot because it's like
kind of like
like a soft
pink
yeah
easy to find
it's everywhere in souvenir shops it's
everywhere
ah yeah
uh
[Music]
mushy
my
[Music]
so
i i knew that word before but i forgot
i used to know more words before when i
was watching that korean show about
babies
ah one word they said a lot was
[Music]
maybe i should watch the baby show again
and then i can remind myself of some
words
[Music]
why does she say so fast what the hell
yes
sorry that came out of nowhere oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
it's like hearing that
he's like someone sneezed so i had to
have you guys say kiss on that thank you
thank you taskario next yeah
[Music]
oh my god
uh hakuya second tea danke sans
seventeen p forty two donkey
[Music]
oh
write something into the text box next
time it's an empty pinky we don't accept
that here
you gotta write something in there what
am i supposed to tangent on if you don't
write anything in it thank you for the
support though thank you
soon
[Music]
what
um
[Music]
for your lovely generous support
fox spicy
and doppler stain
can't be nuggets
wait what does it say in korean
[Music]
will find the person who put the
malicious inventory and file a formal
complaint
they they are so wow
korean viewers are so passionate i'm i
wasn't even unhappy with this you should
have watched my members only stream
with the international snack box you can
write write the the complaints
uh to the pop-tart uh company please
instead i'm not mad at the korean snacks
i'm not mad at all wait i guess you guys
are just not that
happy with
what i got here i guess they are kind of
i mean just by the looks of it they
don't look that exciting most of these
snacks here i i bet you guys have snacks
that look more exciting than this like
look at the packaging
[Music]
i think they have more exciting things
than this
yeah pretty boomer snacks
[Music]
cereal companies getting complaint
letters from kfp
you did rate the korean snack zero out
of ten ah yeah wait which one was that
again ah was the chocolate bar
wow i was really mean to the chocolate
bar was it the chocolate bar
i know it was the the little puffy this
one's right these ones i did not like no
no no no but the chocolate bar this one
was not good either
yeah
i think yeah the it looks like
the cookie based ones
and the jelly based ones i liked but
once once any of these snacks had some
chocolate in it which really was not
many of them i did not like them which
shows me that yeah maybe the chocolate
taste
is at fault
thank you for the pinkie dough sally and
duncan
thank you
[Music]
i think it i think the pebble would have
been in the other korean snack box that
i missed out on
i think it would have been in that one
unfortunately
[Music]
now i am actually really lucky when it
comes to that friends have and beat me
in the past and you might as well but i
actually have a really stable weight
for my whole life
i
i eat a lot of shitty fast food
um but i never really gained weight from
it even though i don't do sports and
i don't do anything
i eat a lot of snacks and i eat them at
really weird times don't don't you say
that like if you eat after midnight or
whatever if you eat late at night it
makes you fat
it doesn't really count for me i
wouldn't say i have one of those insane
metabolism
uh
it's just normal but
yeah
maybe it's because i
at least don't eat
too
big portions
and
i think also when i eat then i usually
eat like i eat like a little bit of
breakfast um usually like one bowl of
cereal for breakfast
or one
one croissant
unless when i'm in a hotel or something
i like to eat as much as i can from the
breakfast buffet but usually i'm already
here done with breakfast after one
croissant or one one piece of bread or
one bowl of cereal
and then
sometimes i eat like maybe a sandwich or
something for lunch but not really lunch
kind of late lunch not right away
not much though
something small
as a snack in between
and then
late very very late at night i have some
dinner but you guys might know that my
portion size is really not that big
yeah
um
yeah so i would eat like i don't know oh
sometimes
you know the frozen pizza that i eat
that i uh eat a lot i can totally eat
that alone but when i order pizza
holy [\h__\h] i could never eat that up
sometimes not not even like half of it
[Music]
and then afterwards when i'm like
already lying in bed for except about
for example i did that yesterday too
i was lying in bed and at like i don't
know 2 or 3 a.m i was eating ice cream
in bed so
and i snack a lot on chocolate and stuff
uh in between as well i don't eat many
veggies and i don't need many fruits
either
although i love i love fruits but
uh whenever i buy them they
go bad so quickly it really annoys me so
i rarely
eat fruit because
i buy like four bananas
and on the second day they already are
so brown that i usually only need one
out of four bananas
[Music]
yeah
yeah you might be skinny but i don't
know about healthy that is a good point
that is a good point put them in the
fridge i tried that before too but it
didn't work that well either so then i
bought like a banana
holder
where you can hang the bananas
buy some green banana but then i have to
wait usually when i buy a banana it's
because i want to eat a banana right
away on that day but if i buy a green
one then i have to wait like one to two
days until it's actually good
so i usually buy bananas when they're
the perfect
flawless
yellow color
no
anyway
cover the top of the banana with cling
wrap
clean wrap you mean the transparent
see-through wrap
i think i've seen that tip before
another hotel
ah did you just tell me a life hack
yo
[Music]
um
i am blessed by
my metabolism
i suppose hooray
hooray
[Music]
you you again
uh i know you're in the chat right now
tell me how to read your name
you're translating for me ah
sora kusasana
that's not how you want me to read your
name right i think you told me before
didn't you tell me before i'm so sorry
oh my god i forgot i forgot how do i
read your name please help me
please help me please
you told me last time i think
[Music]
if you want if you don't want me to
forget again because i would probably
forget you can you could change your
name and add a english reading
next to it that would help me
so much
yeah and if you if you super chat like
that to any other
uh girl in her life they will probably
also
read your name incorrectly
if you don't add the english reading to
it
[Music]
please thank you
that actually counts for
everyone else who has a name in uh any
language that is not in using english
writing
and if you have a korean name or i don't
know any any other
uh writing that i cannot read
then it would save me a lot of time if
you could add that to your name
the reading in
alphabet please
please thank you
but you don't have to you don't have to
like this that is amazing
that is amazing
thank
you thank you
brandon
minutes maid thank you
most of kanji in packaging is nothing
but only for design because korean used
word from kanji but only use hunger
imagine only hiragana japanese yeah i
thought that was very interesting um i
noticed that too some of these packages
were korean packages they use uh
some kanji but
uh like um i think they are supposed to
be read in like
chinese reading i guess
yeah but you just use it for decoration
i guess
interesting
[Music]
yes that is
interesting
[Music]
i didn't know there would be no choco
pie your bet was that there would be a
choco pie
ah i'm sorry you lost the bed
unfortunately but as i said i'm pretty
sure if you mean um wait let me show it
choco pie
because they have them in japan as well
i did eat them before you mean the one
from there
[Music]
it looks like they have them overseas as
well
you mean like these
i've eaten them before i think
i don't quite remember
how much i liked them but i like the
idea of them
orion one is better than lotte i see
those two yeah yeah
they have a happiness pack
oh
is it this this must be uh
this is the korean one maybe
[Music]
oh
strawberry version looks so good
packaging looks so good
[Applause]
oh
look at this
strawberry sakura version oh
20 20 words why did they not send me
this huh it looks cute even the
packaging looks cute
oh
[Music]
so now i'm pretty mad see what i missed
out on
damn
boy
[Music]
i feel so regretful
damn it
i'm sad
thank you for the red super chat
next time choco pie
[Music]
is trying to get a ticket for the
concert another one of my
rare
japan brailles very rare nowadays but
they are still here they still exist
um okay okay okay wish him good luck you
must get a ticket kfb bros represent
yes
i think the seller should go should we
go to the usual room because he sold an
old-fashioned box also there's no steady
seller snacks where's cole book chip
where is original chocolate taste home
run ball where is choco put home run
ball
i mean the ones i have here but in this
one but in the original taste are these
actually popular
only the original taste huh we had the
same problem with the pop tart
uh in their international snack books
they sent me a weird tasting one and it
was disgusting
and then everyone was like okay but
there's actually good tasting ones as
well kiwawa
yeah
maybe maybe because this was a special
flavor and or a new flavor
so that's probably why they wanted to
push it
it's okay i will try to visit korea in
and then i will try all the snacks that
you guys recommend me
okay
okay i promise
i promise i will try
if i can get there i will do my best
um a great human can't be done
[Music]
great human
i don't think you need it to write dad
was unnecessary i know where to go
i know where to go
um
right idiot
[Music]
you are a purple
is he still here did he get the message
[Music]
my mom is still here not pablo
i'm saying he's a baka
a sassy butter
sick thank you
sick is it okay to say she's sick or
yes
[Music]
okay let me refresh because we're at the
end of my list at least from
uh from this point
okay
so we go to p90 scroll scroll scroll
scroll
oh [\h__\h] you guys
sent
so many oh man
i thought i was close to the end
oh no mike thank you for the pinky sorry
for turning up blinky while i will watch
the vlog by the way i just started
picking up german as i was enrolled into
a german university
what
do you have any tips on picking up
german for english speaker any good
reference books
wait you enrolled into a german
university where i suppose they teach
all subjects in german
but you
start out with no german knowledge
you're gonna be
having a hard time man
that sounds
like it's gonna be rough
well
any tips on picking up german for an
english speaker any good reference books
well honestly as uh
as it is my mother tongue
no
i
i i don't have
any any books to recommend i just
learned it from my mama i i guess i
could give you
my my mother's discord uh
maybe she can teach you like she taught
me as i was a baby
uh
nope that's probably not gonna work
either oh
[\h__\h] well i recommend you to wait do you
are you also like moving to a country
where they speak german or are you still
living in the country where you're
sending the
super chat from um
because
if you if you actually also move to the
country like germany or austria or
wherever or or
switzerland maybe
then that alone will already help you a
lot
but
if you live in a country where they
don't speak german then that's rough
buddy
[Music]
you gotta
work and study hard german is very
difficult from what i've heard from
other people
i wish you the best
i wish you the best and in german um
i wish you the best here write it down
right now ich voon
[Music]
all good
no we don't say afrida not yet we're not
there yet
[Music]
and
don quixote food in pink and super chat
[Music]
thank you
personally i don't recommend it the er
the youthful burgers you tried them and
they were not that good really but they
look cool they're instagram food yeah
i just wanna eat it for because of that
and hi
thank you for the pink super
[Music]
welcome to korea the nation of delivery
manager kim anna your pronunciation is
good so don't worry try delicious korean
chicken too
um
i found a restaurant
uh which has korean style fried chicken
i don't know if it's really
um like the og but i might give it a try
that looked like he lip-synched it no i
didn't i that was my voice that was my
own voice excuse me
excuse me
[Music]
should i prove it i'll do it again
see i even closed my eyes how
i i didn't obviously i wasn't even
looking so that's myself
sounds legit right
impressive
that is me
i sound like crony crown is a little bit
lower i would say
lower voice a little bit
i think it's the robotic
charm that makes you think of pruning
um
charming
[Music]
congratulations dante are so excited for
the news i can't wear the kfb apron by
your birthday merged the scene
unfortunately but i will support you
online see that's the good thing when
you watch it online you could watch the
concert with my kfp apron or you could
watch it with the omo cat merch or you
could watch it naked in your underwear
and then right on top of your
belly you can write i love kiara
however you want to do it you can
support me in any possible way
get into the mood yeah by wearing the
merchandise
or not wearing the merchandise becoming
the merchandise
it all works
yes
thank you fava here's a kiss for you
i'm so excited
i hope i hope you can stay hyped until
the concert oh my god it will be amazing
you're welcome yeah today's stream was
early for uh so that korean viewers
could catch it i think in the future
when i do
other country snack boxes i will always
try to do it at a time that is suitable
for
wherever the snack box came from for the
people there
so for the russian snack box i will do i
will try to do it at a time that is good
for
russians mm-hmm
yeah
i know
i can't use my handy because of my job's
rule let's take my light and so we clean
the doors for tea
oh yeah you you're using the word handy
which i think uh is
a good point did you guys know that in
german
we
took we say handy
uh to the mobile phone the smartphone we
call it handy so we're like i'm gonna
buy a new handy or i'm gonna buy a new
and i'm gonna i'm gonna go get get my
handy repaired um
[Music]
yes
it's it's an english word but it's the
word that we use for it in german
[Music]
because it's handy
exactly yeah or it's a i think it comes
from the you know being a handheld phone
like a hand sized phone or so that's
pretty handy
it's handy and no it's
[Music]
hand-sized
yeah makes sense right
now you learn some german but it's
english
[Music]
well good luck learning german uh as
well to you you will not need it in my
stream though if that's why you're
trying to learn it because my stream
language is english so you better learn
english but your english seems fine as
well
okay
oh
[Music]
um there's no problem with your name but
i don't want people to
like uh
make something out of it
uh
so i will just say
i don't want people to record that and
cut it into something it's not
[Music]
thank you
one
[Music]
that's me thank you for your ransom
thank you
and congratulations on your 3d live i've
been
oh
thank you for
congratulating me but i can not
say
if it is bad
i've been waiting for it for a really
long time
of course i probably waited less than
you when i heard the news on the
official broadcast i almost cried but i
put up with it i will cry on the day you
do the live
thank you i will too
[Music]
keem ida
thank you for the red super chat uh
details will follow
thank you
that is still a question mark for a lot
of you guys i know
uh
i cannot say
i
i am
[Music]
i am a dangerous
dangerous phoenix
i cannot
say anything
[Music]
[Laughter]
the information is classified yes
one after another take it easy take it
easy
genma don't hit me i didn't say anything
in genma they implied it i didn't say
anything
hey cake thank you for the rest of the
chat
[Music]
with all the languages again man he's
following up with some
[Music]
foreign it says manager great job
where's the snack good i hope you
enjoyed it i couldn't watch it live but
i suddenly want to eat snacks
understandable with so many snacks on my
table
how could you even hold back classy
fried oh that's a good one
thank you hickey cake for coming by
and yeah the archive will be available
shortly after so make sure to watch it
thank you so much as always
thank you for your generous
[Music]
can't wait for the concert yeah
me neither oh my god thank you very much
please look forward to it get some light
sticks ready
yeah
get a t-shirt
get hyped
study study the whole life original
songs and all that of ever remember
because you never know what they're
gonna perform
but you gotta be ready you gotta be
ready
thank you i'll see you there hopefully
faithful must keep down mummy fried
phoenix spider shin thank you for the
pinky love you thank you i'm watching
you forever glory to the kfp
thank you
thank you very much
you say you'll watch me forever that's
gonna be a long time because i'm an
eternal phoenix are you really up for it
are you sure you can do it
i'll be watching you watching me
[Music]
so
um
i will read this super chat but it once
again implies something that i can
neither confirm nor deny
uh congratulations on your 3d debut
i hope that this concert will increase
the number of kfb employees
can i leave the usual room now no wait
why did i bring you there anyway i don't
remember why are you in there you can
leave when your sentence is over
oopsie no tabbed out oh no
well
well i mean
uh
there there has been no
no
date or confirmation uh
or announcement about our
3d debut uh please don't get confused to
chat
it is known that we already have
3d models
uh
but
the debuts are
uh
not not
not
uh
anyway
[Laughter]
thank you very much for your super chat
[Music]
[Laughter]
mr
[Music]
thank you
i saw this dream an official channel i
always fell in asleep in the middle of
the stream what but do you forgive me
thank you for having been here well and
will be here with us why did you fall
asleep that was so funny and
entertaining
i don't recall okay i'll say that
yeah uh thank you for watching the
official stream it was a one hour stream
how could you fall asleep during that
huh it was a good time for this person i
think definitely yes yes it was a good
time for him
wrong with you go go
one week
[Music]
delusional dream i forgot to give you a
kiss i think today here's a kiss
[Music]
for the pinky i'm so glad i will finally
get to see my auntie performing on stage
i'm so proud of your tangio
i really wish i could be there in person
i'll be cheering for you as loud as i
could behind the screen love you always
thank you
yeah i know a lot of you are probably
wishing for that but don't worry one day
maybe maybe maybe maybe i can come to a
convention
um that is close to where you live and
then you can come to the convention to
kind to kind of kind of see me in
at a concert in person as much as in
person it can be as a youtuber
[Music]
yeah
um but i think
even if it's not in person even if it's
just online i think it will still be
very very special yeah it will be
streamed yes it will be streamed on
spawn
you must watch it if you consider
yourself a takanasi kiyaga fan or
a fan of anyone in myth or anyone in
whole life japan
then you must watch it you must
and it's a two day event it's so
exciting and finally it's on the weekend
which is also very special having this
huge venue
venue on a weekend
for whole life is a big step in the
right direction yeah
hell yeah
i guess so in time for the super chat
reading sorry i could have been here 40
minutes earlier but big cattle was lying
on top of me and little cotton was
curled up against me under the covers
you know how it is that is 100
understandable if you ever need an
excuse
[Music]
why you can't be here
there are no excuses that work except
the the excuse of having a cat on top of
yourself or so or
yeah being like stuck with a cat that is
always
for me
the only legit excuse
but if you don't have a cat and you keep
on using this
uh excuse then i might get suspicious
and ask you for a picture or video of
your cat and if you cannot provide that
uh sufficient proof then
you might be going to the usual room for
life
so be careful you know what's back in
time i know i know i trust you
i trust you
thank you for coming anyway
i hope you gave your kitty cats all the
love all of it
you you beeping bubble bubble
bubble bobble
[Music]
what if i get a virtual cat that does
not count
that does not count no no no
thank you
[Music]
helping me out with some korean yo you
also know a lot of languages don't you i
respect that
thank you
and we're gonna call thank you for the
pinky that announcement was unexpected
but i'm so happy we're finally going to
see kiara reveal her true power on a
different note i don't think i can trust
tangie's taste on anything after that
cats watch long
eh
you mean my taste regarding food
but
but you can't
compare my taste when it comes to food
with my taste when it comes to movies
that's
different
i would say
eh
well i don't trust your taste either
i don't care
[Music]
well then order the same snacks and try
them and then tell me how much different
your taste is not that i care but um
thank you thank you
very much
[Music]
thank you
you have to add to that it says stable
weight terrible cholesterol and heart
issues please take care of your health
my doctor did not say that my
cholesterol would be a problem and you
guys know i have a very very healthy
heart
uh
heart rate when i put on a heart
monitor
so
i think my heart is actually doing well
but uh
i suppose what is not doing so well is
my lungs maybe because i can't breathe
well
[Music]
and
we're almost done guys
i need to prepare whole duck anyway
[Music]
i love tomatoes jun thank you for the
red super chat if you don't mind would
you try
to humor it's based on fumuhumu but made
sticky rice it's so nice thank you well
let me try to translate what is this
a choco pie
[Music]
it's choco pie with like mochi inside
wow
oh
interesting i didn't know that exists
it sounds nice
[Music]
but i don't think i can get my hands on
it at the moment um
today's my birthday happy birthday
[Music]
thank you june here's a kiss for you
please take care of your throat well i
do stream every day for over a year so
it is almost inevitable unless i
stop streaming um
but
i will i will go to the doctor as i said
because i'm already worried about it but
i almost feel like
i must make the same announcement as
iris but i don't want a camera
put through my nose is there any other
way to check that
[Music]
could you use a more relaxed voice well
maybe sometimes but not always because i
am kiwawa and
i don't want to completely change who i
am
thank you for the thinking
and yeah
depends on the issue
i think your vocal cords are fine i
don't think there is a way that you can
tell just by listening to me
nose camera doesn't hurt
[Music]
but
does it feel like those uh
cool
tests that you do through the nose like
like poking the the swabbing your nose
when someone else does it they go pretty
deep don't they
and it feels so [\h__\h] weird
is that how it
feels to have a i should ask iris how it
feels to have a nose for your camera a
camera for your nose
i should ask iris yeah i don't want it
i don't want it
[Applause]
through the nose why not through the
throat i don't understand are your vocal
cords in your nose or what
[Music]
your nose does not have a gag reflex
interesting i see okay
but i have a sneeze reflex
[Music]
just thinking about it i hate those kind
of things
i can't i can't even think about it
nobody gives me goosebumps now just
thinking about it
name thank you perfect
absolutely marvelous thank you thank you
soon
um
[Music]
and
uh wait
oh dear
oh dear you guys
pathetic engineer down cause you're here
from your dance quickly mustache thank
you for the pinky i don't know why
you're laughing though
what's going on thank you though check
catch monkey thank you for the pinky
just wanted to say congratulations on
being part of the concert this year yeah
i'm sure everyone's been looking forward
to this forever i sure have i might not
be able to catch both days but nothing's
gonna stop me from watching your day
live thank you
you know i
i have a i have a dvd of
uh one of the previous concerts
and it would be so nice to like have
something you know
like properly
uh how to say
um
like
something recorded for
proof
so that i can look back on it and say yo
i was part of this
something tangible yeah
yeah
like okay i have a million streams but
concert concert in a huge [\h__\h] venue
with thousands and thousands of
people there and watching it online too
i want proof of that i want a proof of
that
[Music]
oh i expect there to be some kind of dvd
or blu-ray afterwards there usually
always is it's most likely not announced
yet and i don't know for a fact but
i just expect it to happen
yeah just my own uh
uh
guess but yeah
ah
so thank you take it monkey gonna see
you there i will try to hear you
cheering even if it's from far away i
will listen closely
thank you thank you soon this is my
imagination that the super chat is
getting stacked even more while you're
reading it that is true
it's your fault because you're also
stacking onto it while i'm reading them
thank you for the pinky i'm enjoying the
streaming i also want to eat snacks but
i don't want to miss uh
streaming for a moment so i can't go to
the convenience store and you should
have bought it ahead of time
and you streamed early today so i don't
think i need to go to work and sleep at
work tomorrow
yes yes yes yes i have a good streaming
time for you guys today and tomorrow as
well i think holo talk is always a
decent time for
uh s-e-a viewers
[Music]
oh for your support thank you soon
sick night thank you soon believe me for
the pinky you know what for the holofest
happens on my birthday what
the first day or the second day guess
who is
guys from heart attack oh my
we're throwing a huge birthday party for
you buddy
is it the day one or day two
buddy bunny bunny bunny second day is my
birthday squared you as well oh my god
first day oh second day for d squared
first day for body
oh
big party for you guys
that's a nice birthday present let's go
oh
well i will not congratulate you yet
because it's still far far away but yeah
that sounds very exciting
[Music]
don't don't congratulate him it's it's
january this is happening in march
esperanza
ah why are you doing this
what are you
what are you doing this for huh
why are you changing your name trying to
make me pronounce things
[Music]
why are you doing this donkey shin for
the super chat
understand what you're trying to
do what are you trying to do
huh
it's car names that's a car name
oh
i like hearing you say car names that
sounds like a
a weird fetish
i think you're doing a wonderful job of
keeping things secret
really really so don't worry too much
about it by the way did you train
i'm not gonna
i'm not i don't recall
[Music]
anything who am i
what am i
what
who are you kaku where am i what is this
what's happening caitlin dankeshen thank
you i'm your aussie oh love you thank
you
who am i
uh anyway that's all the super chats i
think
no one
no
[Music]
no and
andy andel
and
no
no not no
what
no
book book thank you
i don't know why i always um yawn so
much at the end of my streams even if
it's like this one is pretty short like
why do i get so tired man i think i
might be the winter time
maybe i'm even more tired than usual
because it's winter
[Music]
what
what is that is it a thing
maybe it's also just because there is no
air in my room
no oxygen have love
pavlova there's a dessert that's uh the
shape of a cake
it's a russian dessert
named after the ballerina anna pavlova
it has a crisp pressed and soft light
inside usually topped with fruit and
wood from that looks and sounds
delicious
it looks and sounds delicious i love it
i wanna eat that holy [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] is this
people also search for baked alaska
what is that
that looks amazing baked alaska also
known as bombay alaska omelette
norwegian omelet surprise or omelet
siberian depending on the country is a
dessert consisting of ice cream and cake
topped with browned meringue
holy [\h__\h] looks amazing
why why did i come here
what happened puff
puff papaloovian response
[Music]
pablovian conditioning also called
classical conditioning a type of
conditioned learning which occurs
because of the subject's instinctive
responses as opposed to well
i don't know how that would apply what
do you mean
[Music]
what do you mean
how did we get here
what
[Music]
[Laughter]
do you know why bicycles can't stop on
their own it's because they're too tired
oh you're so funny love azalean thank
you
for
[Music]
it's an instinct that i get tired at the
end of the stream ah
sorry for this deck ariel thank you
concert concert concert
yes
concert this
usually tied up the last one
i don't think that's what's happening
but
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
sorry i i almost
sang away from my chair
um i'm melting so
uh thank you everyone for
watching today
uh we'll do more of these and tomorrow
is whole talk with the one and only
young girl
you guys wanna i wanna spoil you guys i
wanna guys
[Music]
should we save it don't spoil it it's
okay
oh man recently it's really tough like
no it's the same opening but with jakko
uh i i'll i'll keep it why do i have to
keep everything secret guys it's tough
kiwawa can't hold back information
this is a tough time everything must be
kept secret thank you unseen thank you
oh it's killing me
it's killing me
i will go now
i'll go now
he can kick what are you doing
that's dangerous he can't kick you crazy
real crazy
cake here's a kiss
right so for your dog
why here cake cake you should call
yourself young young young
because i young young delusional dreamer
thank you for the pinky what
forgive tantra i always fell asleep in
the middle of the street again
but i watch for archives okay
one of these sounds you're making
as long as you watch the archive
eiffelgeep pbnk donkey shooting 17
ah learning japanese did why are you
guys coming with these super chats now
i
i i learned japanese pretty fast because
um i i spoke uh i communicated in
japanese every day with japanese people
so
if you do it that way you'll be very
fast with it what what what what why do
i read this now i have to put it into my
translator
oh yeah
[Music]
wow
she's not coming
[Music]
wow
i'll see you tomorrow at whole talk and
uh i might i might stream on monday too
because i'm not really streaming on like
tomorrow it's re pre-recorded
so
yeah i'm please do not do me a favor
this time and do not spam the chat with
zipper recorded that was funny before i
don't think it's funny anymore
i might just ban the word uh
pre-recorded
or the word life for the time being
because even if i tell you guys there's
gonna be a lot of people who
uh come from somewhere else and then i'm
gonna spam it then the whole chat will
be is it pretty quiet
[Music]
yeah
driving into the ground until the end of
the stream last time it was from
beginning until the very end
even when i pinned the comments it was
still until the end everyone every
every second
chat message was is this pretty
recording
and some of them they are doing it as a
a joke and others are doing it on
purpose
uh and now i'm purpose but like they do
it because they really are asking but
others are just like making fun of it
pudding channels shut up
thank you soon everybody for watching
today
uh
yes
good night everybody
see you tomorrow in german we say alvina
sand
oh hi
oh yes
belly scratch belly scratch
[Music]
kick
i saw that
wait a second
oh my god
oh kitty little kitty
[Music]
what does it say what does that say
uh
what does that say
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
bye
[Music]
thank you
oh
[Music]
so
smoothie
[Music]
oh
i know you can hear me
otherwise what i really call them
smoothie and chunkers huh
think think chad pink
[Music]
nah chunkers is still here she's just
lazy
she likes to stay comfy
for as long as possible
[Music]
it's so hashtag relatable
i'm gonna go cuddle now
[Music]