[Music]
w
oh a
[Music]
T out
no I don't know if you were there when I
like previously said you're the one that
I saw like in a non vtuber related
stream in the
[Music]
chat I was like oh yo why are we
watching the Stream
[Music]
do you not like
attention do you know what stream I'm
talking about
[Music]
though some crazy crazy ass stupid
Australian stream
[Music]
the guy who didn't want to sleep
remember do you
remember on the 21st night of September
[Music]
yeah I know I saw you were spamming
that it doesn't count it doesn't
count it's
[Music]
over can't believe you watched it that
much to know that he fell asleep several
times I did not have the patience for
that
anyway guys did you see the
the YouTube
short it just uploaded like 10 minutes
ago I uploaded
it me me me me me me you me me me me me
R
you
yippee
[Music]
yipp yeah
oh I'm
shy F just a you know where um
wait do you see wait fun is in VC with
me there's like uh we split I was alone
in a VC Channel and the other girls are
in the other VC Channel but everybody is
muted but I was just like muted alone in
this VC and the others are muted
together in the other VC but father just
decided to join
me to be muted with
me she's like a cat right
now yeah we muted together it's so
wholesome
uh where is it where's chat here
okay chicken salad not soup Okay the
reason I've been starting earlier these
days is because the server like
everybody enters at exactly like the
hour mark and every minute counts in
this game um I want to be efficient and
and all that but I also need to Yap
there's so much I need to Yap about uh
so if you haven't seen in the community
board or on Twitter Etc I put up a a a
visual graphic of the challenges not
challenges Milestones um I just I just
thought you know I wanted to make some
dance shorts because K-pop brain rot is
strong uh and I thought well if I'm
making so many dance shorts why not just
pretend that I'm not going to give it to
you unless we reach
Milestones like I would give it to you
anyway
but uh making it seem like this whole
challenge to reach 1
million sounds fun and seems motivating
and I thought that's PR let's go we love
some
PR so just now since we're already at
420,000 views we are at crony's dance
show that I just uploaded and so close
with 500k you guys get the full dance
video and then I've decided to just
spoil everything cuz it's kind of hype
um you know I I I chose to some girls
who I thought you know uh would be into
participating and who also um I don't
know maybe some unusual pairings and so
on so uh Ollie Ollie was so excited at
my proposal uh of course she was you
know got a got a reward Ollie for being
such a
sweetheart
um where am I
here uh
and then yeah M Senpai M Senpai as well
and then Iris for 700k car for 750k
fauna for 800k then we'll put up an
Acappella and I I actually have a plan
for this one you already heard the
Acappella how to make it a little bit
more special I'm going to try to make a
video out of it too I'm going to map
something just something simple but just
to have a visual and not just the audio
so me and chagy will work on that to
Yosi I'm very inspired right
now and then uh then Kobo dance short
and then Ki dance short yes yes another
Japanese member here too and then last
but not least for 1 million we're going
to do a 3D stream don't know what yet
but we're going to use the Mirage model
for it yippee so there's lots to achieve
I was going to do all of these things
anyway but I have real realized I I can
if nobody helps me to do PR then I'll
just do it
myself and I've also opened up my Tik
Tok account uh it has apparently jenma
made my Tik Tok account two years ago
and I I wrote to her just now it's like
oh Jemma by the way uh if I wanted to
make a Tik Tok account how long would it
take does the company have to make it
for me and she was like well actually I
already had one ready for you so cuz
just a thinking that you might need it
so I already have it ready here is the
login data and then I logged in I was
like perfect nothing to do besides
uploading a video so the solo uh dance
video is up now and I'm going to upload
the crony dance video like tomorrow or
so and basically I hate Tik Tok I hate
the Tik Tok culture but
um ladies and gentlemen we I got to do
something you know I got to try I got I
got to put some of my baits out got to
fish for some catfish to bite on my bait
I just watched this jungle survival
video before the stream um gotta see if
I can catch some fish you know
gotta swing out all of my fishing rods
and see somewhere it has to bite so
that's the plan that's what we're doing
uh you guys don't have to make a Tik Tok
account you don't have to the content
will be the same I'm just uploading
shorts um trying to spread my reach and
have to grow the Tik Tok account first
probably we'll see how it goes if you
have a Tik Tok account please follow me
I put up a screenshot on Twitter I'll uh
make a community post about it later
maybe as well H yeah it it was very
spontaneous now so um you'll hear more
later about
it um exciting uh I I did not take a nap
but I'm drinking Coca-Cola
mhm had a crispy chicken before the
stream from Burger King and realized
this tastes way more bland than I
thought it did is it just me is it the
burger is it me I don't
know but yeah yeah we'll see how long it
last today is apparently 4our session
today is a 4our
session let's see we're starting off for
f uh there's CI bio cilia ra and the
other VC uh although ra is also muted
Cali is not streaming today apparently
cuz she's sick I feel so bad she she's
she caught some [\h__\h]
man um but yeah let
[Music]
mehh don't know how loud this will
be but yeah I'm very hungry
great uh okay yeah hope today will go
well I have some goal o goals I guess
I'll take a little bit of food if they
have something
edible
oh yeah um
howdy she doesn't hear me um I think I I
I'm more comfortable in smaller groups I
think me and um fauna might just do some
quests probably to kick it off uh I want
to get magazines and uh especially
workstation magazines is this the right
way where the hell am
I
what I it's so far I thought it was way
closer for some reason um but yeah what
I what am I saying oh God I'm so hungry
and so
thirsty let me go back and get something
more gotta get that bike bike yeah I
guess so um
I watched a video on like armor cuz I'm
going to be the one making some armor I
guess eventually so I I I looked at all
the sets and what's like the best
combinations and stuff I mean there's a
lot of good stff I don't have to minmax
everything I think to be
honest there's no need actually is there
something
cooked there is
water that's good
SI
sippa
um yeah wait I had something else in
mind but I forgot but yeah we H want to
look take a closer look at my
skills and stuff I don't know
um why are you guys on day 15 hello
hello F why are we on day
15 I noce that it seems someone forgot
to leave I I had a feeling last night I
when I logged out I was like H like I
was one of the last last people to log
out but I was like I feel like I saw
someone afking there will it be okay but
uh but wouldn't the base be totally
messed up now then because that means
another Rush
happened maybe the spikes were enough to
hold it off the second
ra well I think if only one person if
only one person is there maybe only like
a few zombie
spawned isn't that exactly where she
logged out last or didn't log out last
night I don't know did she die I I just
saw a pink-haired woman standing on the
car being the last person when I logged
out wait should we ask go up and ask
what if they
noticed
um hello it's not like
hello no it's fine don't worry hello
hello if anything this is good because
now we know you know what happen now we
know what happened what happened then uh
apparently R stayed AFK I knew it I knew
it I knew it cuz I saw her think so I
was the second no I saw I was the second
as I was the last one before a to log
out and when I logged out I even said to
my chat oh isn't there someone isn't Raa
still AFK like in the server cuz I saw
her standing on the car I loged out next
to her I was wondering is she she looks
AFK but I'm sure she'll remember AFK for
S hours oh my
God something else wait so did a raid
come I wonder I think it did it probably
destroyed R over and over
again multiple times
no what unable to move but then we
missed the raid what does this mean for
us that the next raid will be super
strong
we're ready we're going to do it we're
going to destroy it's okay we strong
together I think that it also has to do
with a levels and stuff so since no one
leveled up I think so that's how it was
in the beta at least so I
fun we are so we are so well fortified
but that means today there is going to
be a raid then really right no but they
seven no seven days
21 so that was yesterday yeah the next
one is 21 so we're still on track
right it's literally the same just last
one week it's it it was calculated guys
calculated um oh my God yeah can you
guys give me like some wood if you don't
mind uh there there's a bunch of stuff
in the house go ahead and feel free to
take we there there's weapons in there
too as well so you can grab a weapon you
know
I even double checked like I when I
ended my stream I was still worried
about l so I checked like if I could see
if she's online on Discord or on Steam
friends and so on and on Discord it just
said that she's like playing Monster
Hunter or so so I was like oh I guess
that's fine but
no that's crazy I'm going to make you
some armor but hey R you collected some
water for us cuz we kept yeah thank you
for collecting water for
no I'm
not you already did oh my
God how much water was there it only
unfortunately it caps at three so
because
was well great you welcome that that was
calculated as a
mention
here and then wait hey I made some
coffee and some tea
[Music]
Tower I can't find wood okay CE here's
your team oh thank you you're welcome
it's level my God bless you do
itess welcome that is so funny she takes
care of
me here's your
coffee thank
you
yummy B can I get some of that tea oh
okay I'll make another
tea JY sorry Chef you're working over
time I don't want to give you the
XP
penalty I thought we don't have an XP
penalty there is a penalty how do I find
out tab second
tab there's exp penalty
was is okay my beautiful no
hesitation oh my goodness my beautiful
water 23
deaths what 20 what 23 23 deaths you had
so far but I see yeah it says deaths 15
where wait where do you see your Dev tab
first I think she probably just died
once and then just was in the respawn
screen probably and then
yeah at you dying a lot sorry I
understand why people have to die is you
know restore your health and I have
eight player
kills eight player you murderer
[Music]
wow well okay thank you I'm not thirsty
or hungry anymore it's so let's start
preparing for the third
raid
yeah yeah I'm I'm still trying to to to
find M well it not it will not happen
today but yeah we can take it relatively
easy
guess bab can you cook me uh some corn
or something yeah do you have
any yeah I do I'm cooking up some
cornbread I'm coming home not the
cornbread popping off I'm coming
[Music]
home yeah the cooks are going to have
get to work wait guys the W the toilet
the the some of the boxes here respawned
so like the toilet was empty right
because because it's it's it's the ra
cuz it respawn Stu it respawn
everything yay I so I have some work
water if you wanted oh oh because she
was
online well some positive
effects huh
only I was standing where you went who
were standing I'm I'm behind
you oh stairs here oh thank
you nice hi so far what if if you grill
the corn does it give you more Health
back or
more whatam call it more hunger back
lack of I think so yeah I'm pretty sure
it's more efficient as a food to eat it
grilled yeah maybe we should try and
search for food
too I know I'm no but we have like we
have 60 steaks at home from the Big
Green boar oh wait do we did we cook
them all not yet but you know can always
cook I think we might have cooked them
all really I think so I mean the steak
conversion ratio is so bad five raw
steaks to make one grilled steak wa wait
a minute I wonder if the green Bo
respawns so we can kill him again good
food farming place I
think uh I would hope that he wouldn't
respond cuz he's already in my
nightmares true that guy sucked yeah it
was too strong and too big was pretty
satisfying to kill though yeah a big
trees
respawned wonderful yeah so you never
know
yeah oh yeah if anyone wants to come
with me to grab the treasure chest
treasure hunting I you mean the no I
have a treasure map oh I see oh it just
hold on a sec what wait I see a drop is
is it the yellow thing bi boo
no there's a drop though you should get
the drop first before it goes away oh
okay and then we can get the buried
treasure wait where did the treasure go
the where my I don't know I only ever
saw the drop on the screen I saw the
treasure chest oh it might be the drop
maybe it must be
okay well let's let's go over and grab
it yeah already I'm going to head that
way I'm home oh if anybody wants to come
let's party them up yeah get in the yeah
can you invite
me well I'll invite you me too I want to
do the treasure chest thingy it sounds
fun
okay oh yeah I see the icon the treasure
icon on the map okay I think I think
only you can see that then bio so you're
going to have to lead the way to that
but let's get let's get let get the dwap
the air dwop the
dwap uh if you guys have a stone
axe um and get some wood for me because
by hands it takes too long oh I have a
spare axe if you want it did I forget to
say k Kitt K
Kitty okay for people who just joined in
a little bit later
[Music]
um as I have thought last night there
was somebody left on the server AFK I
should have went back to like check but
what could I have done I think she went
too bed um and that's why we passed
another full week and a raid happened
but it was versus one person so it
wasn't too bad I
guess yeah it so funny I made one why
are some of the zombies super
hot their dresses because because some
people are super hot yeah so they turn
into hot zombies hot people become hot
zom zombie reflects the
[Laughter]
streamer wait can we go into the snow
area don't we freeze to death or
something we have clothes it should be
okay I love snowy area yeah ah it's too
bright my eyes
flashbang why would they why would they
put the drop here they don't even care I
the uses light
mode hello yeah she
does H what are you guys planning on
doing there's
a
God be careful are we just balling yeah
we're balling right now okay yes we're
doing class increasing our skills Loot
and loots we're going to build a little
house together oh people coming in
um you are the farmer you if you have
some time today can you try to plant our
super
corn yeah yeah I would love to plant
some super crops super corn okay um if
you uh the the the super corn seeds are
in the new house next to the fireplace
in the food and Medicine Chest um there
is free uh ear of super corn don't take
those just take the Super corn seeds
there's five of them and if we need more
with more grown ears of super corn I can
produce more seeds because I have some
recipe okay but for now it's just five
seeds here you question is will the FL
be at the new place nothing cool in here
um anywhere is fine I think I got I got
some magazines
though
magazin oh blade crafting I need that
knife guy I I have heard that the second
wave has already been finished yeah we
did
it we're
so we survived the second wave I'm
believable are we still going to be
using this house for another wave or are
we doing a different house now another
one use this house because it's it's
well reinforced right yeah yeah it's
very well reinforced
got to continue using what's good
still make the most of it oh my gosh
there are those lions or Tigers what are
those big cats mountain lions big cats
big cat a big cat means big
trouble oh big cat hurts oh that was a
bad
idea yeah I'm dangerous it better be
guys question right now are you doing
stuff at a new location
uh um bble has like a treasure chest and
we want to go here yeah I have a
treasure map that I'm looking
for um where did you guys go I left but
I'm waiting for you somewhere close by
okay well I'm going to go to the other
home so I'll stick in a a different VC
I'll see you guys later y I'm right next
to
you okay treasure is can you kill me
ah big cat I see the big
cat F hello f are you following the the
treasure people
or I will quest with you
yes awesome but before we do that can I
tell you a story of um my cat please do
yes okay so um one one of my cats has
this
really interesting way of forcing me to
feed her I wonder if you can relate
so like when she when she's really like
losing her patience with me oh my swe hi
giggy if you hello G you have to listen
to my cat story really quickly okay okay
so smoovie one of my cats when she loses
her patience with me and really wants
food and then wants to show me she wants
food she will purposefully wherever I
can see and hear it look for plastic
because she knows she can't eat it it's
not allowed to and then she will like
nibble on it and lick it and make these
noises these plastic noises forever yeah
and I push her away and she goes back to
it she does it again and again and she
will not stop until I even leave the
room and then she follows me and she
finds a new thing to nibble and eat or
until I give her food relatable
relatable really oh my
God I relate to the
cat relate to the
cat relable plastic when he wants my
attention a oh no I didn't know that was
a common
thing they definitely know when they're
not supposed to that's so bad so so bad
mhm but it also makes me think
maybe then she knows also since she
knows she's not supposed to and she's
just like kind of like annoying me with
that she knows at least that she's not
supposed to swallow it and that you know
at least she's that's she knows where
where the the line is I guess uhhuh good
it's not like she actually wants the
plastic she just wants your attention
yeah cute so
wise yeah I would eat plastic for your
attention
too no no you already got it you already
got it
oh now we understand the meaning behind
the FEA put it
down oh the feathers no
no you you all have my attention we're
going to do quests it seems the
Clementine okay yes I'm at the tra
Clementine is is cute a cute name yeah
right the
Clementine is there any food I am so
starving also starving I feel like we
might need to figure out a food yeah I
have 60 meat if you can cook you have
the 60 meat I will I have 60 meat okay
I'm on my way to the house that's where
the B meat went no oh no I found it yeah
where where you find it I killed two
pigs and I took it off their bodies oh
wow okay okay nice we need that yeah we
do all right send that to the to the
slow
cooker okay um and do you need
seed crafting farming magazine um I
think yeah I already I feel like I ate
one okay I will put it in the chest we
should make a Farm by our house yeah
because we're struggling with food
yeah well I did tell Shi to take the
Super corn and and and play uh plant it
sometime today uh but if she doesn't get
to it I don't know I so making seeds and
farming are two separate skills right oh
are they it it seems to me like it yeah
I'll put the meat in here and I have an
egg
oops okay oh I am oh I am on zero oh I
am striving to death right now I'm going
to make a bunch of bacon and eggs how
fast yum does that finish um Takes a
Minute 20 each okay I'm coming over
because it's death or life situation
right
now wow I can make some grilled corn
okay anything I didn't know it was why
does it go down so
fast an apocalypse are just so hungry I
know they don't know that we have to
parkour for
food uh how long usually until you
starve for real for real I don't know
why are we all starving how did this
happen h so
hungry maybe because the we loged we all
logged out right at the apocalypse and
we were just so so exhausted from the
apocalypse you're cooking at our home
right yeah yeah yes okay good good good
good I'm
home hey e ay
M oh thought you were eating the food
that I was supposed to eat now welcoming
you home ah one corn is that grilled m y
Yum Yum Yum Yum ah
salvation a little
bit Yeah okay we'll fill our tamies and
then we'll go questing
okay gy yesterday without you we were
quite efficient too but I think with you
we are we are even more efficient we
will be three times officient I missed
you to my beautiful lives I feel like
I've in a coma for two
weeks yeah I think you have
been fauna got so distracted so often G
but she's also so Mo motivated she runs
off into random houses all the time and
punches things cuz she's the Fister yeah
my fisting has gotten much
better I I I'm gone for a week and a
half and you're the strongest
Fister it's true it's
true she definitely is I did some
research into armor by the way like I
watched this whole video on every armor
set and so I think I found out which
armor set will be best for you
FAA oh which one is that it's like
there's I think there's two heavy armor
sets and one of them the one that's like
that looks the most hardcore that's the
one you need ooh the tank armor yeah see
you already like tanking I
do awesome I found Assassin outfit do
either of you want this a whole is it
just the top assassin now I guess do you
want a
kiaha um I mean I uh I think you can
have it
too okay what does it do it gives sneak
Effectiveness plus 5% medium armor
rating uh something something stamina it
lowers stamina a little bit and it
lowers Mobility a little bit but not I'm
already
starving why do I have a backpack over
here did I die did you die I don't
remember dying why is there a backpack
icon and not know why maybe I did not
die yesterday on the way did you did you
the no I didn't why why am I why is
there a mysterious backpack
harvesting
harvesting how do these how do these
magazines keep on appearing in these
chests so
magically we're so good at finding them
they just
appear um it looks like everything
respawned so we should have like a bunch
more nice loot nice yeah I see loot in
these
cars uh
ah Salvage five repair
five cook
faster eat one right in front of your
face
e oh this is rough maybe maybe when we
do quests we'll get a lot of
[Music]
food
farmer hi everyone Welcome to our home
our abod it's very comfy we've got bacon
and eggs cooking if you're hungry than
God oh you guys ever searched a
toilet oh res
respawn oh they respawn I see yeah all
these cars are um unsearched again all
right uh this is the new base for
protecting right so we should put spikes
here I think we're still going to
protect the old one keep the old one as
the base for the next raid until it's
completely run over
okay uh the farm is still at the old
base as well okay um it has not grown
despite it being a week later the server
oh actually in while you're here maybe
maybe you could grow the super corn next
to this house I don't know is that I
need to get um I need to get Rotting
Flesh nitrate powder and clay soil
rotting flashh is also in there and
maybe the other stuff yeah maybe okay I
I'll work on it then awesome thank you
so much thank you
[Music]
no oh you got a spear stuff I'll take
that take what you want it's fine
anything but I think we really got to go
questing soon to get like to find food
and stuff it's night time oh so we can
wait just accepted the quest while I was
out there there is a quest oh is it GG's
am might be mine yes is my name tier one
clear I feel like we could we could do
that we should do that oh can you guys
invite me to the party so I
XP okay I'll work on the farm in the
meantime okay wait thank you oh you are
in a party I think I I sent I think I'm
the party are you oh oh thank
you w this is so confusing ah okay I see
all right I'll set up the farm here
since like I'm already
here nice thank you no problem hopefully
this grows within the next week
apparently it needs
water have you watering
it uh I have not been watering it I
don't have a watering
can oh that's old also something you
need oh no yeah I thought I was hoping
the rain would be enough you know mother
nature and its finest I would think so T
to grow how can the rain why why doesn't
the rain water our plants cuz it's
Arizona the rain is
alive
Twilight if only this was the Pacific
Northwest only there was
vampires m protect us I
know I feel God what I was looking for
Stones I was talking about this with
Nissa yesterday um about Twilight in
Arizona do you think that Bella's first
time seeing grass is when she went when
she moved to
Forks do they not have any grass in
Arizona they got we I don't I don't
believe it there there's some grass
right if they do I don't believe it
maybe fake
grass I just remember she took a little
Cactus with
her that's
not it's
PL do do you have some Stone Arizona
plant I have stone please share I will
come and give the stone after I hit this
tree timber
timber all right here's hoping that the
GR uh the corn grows yes super speed
pray for the super corn I put it in the
chest oh put it to the side of the
house I heard that super corn is not a
food but rather a fuel no no no no most
of the high-end food is made with super
corn oh is it like super corn meal uh no
like several Foods also just grilled
super corn is fine too I guess but yeah
I don't they they listed me a couple of
things in chat before that you can make
oh maybe we can't use it your cooking
might not be good enough yet but yeah it
it will be good enough at some point no
no your cooking's great though I
appreciate your cooking bacon and eggs
are
delicious yeah better than
charred thank you I've been working
hard Chad what else do I need all right
you guys want to prioritize super corn
right what about like Yuka and hops
whatever that is yes Yuka I heard is
good too I forgot for what but Yuka is
good okay I'll take like two yucas then
[Music]
mhm all right seven days to grow let's
go seven days s days to grow coin yeah
once I can make armor I'm going to make
you an a farmer outfit there's a farm
for Farm buff oh Yeehaw Yeehaw I like
how the farm plots kind of it's hovering
well it works pip pip pipe pipe pipe
pipe pipe Peter Pipe piper pepper
pickles oh we got one more
slot pipes I bet we can do the quest
even though it's night time of course be
a little dangerous though we're strong
no we will do it yeah we're strong
enough good luck you guys I'm going stay
here and farm like a house right in
front of me I wasn't ready for
it oh yeah get him you're so good at F
it's like the shown in anime Arc where I
time skipped I'm like that's so much
stronger how much did I
miss I've been
reading up the ways of the Fist I'm
going where you girls are let's go to
the quest oh okay I don't think I'm
anywhere near the quest I just went to
this house
okay yeah it's really far turn around
okay
anywhere is there more food that's done
cooked there might be I would like a
little bite to
eat one more just a
little I'm also still hungry and thirsty
but what can you I can eat this egg in
this
economy I'm tting these raw eggs do we
have any
water m you can wear collect you're
right as long as you're with us we can
just drink from the the sea that's
wonderful thanks your hat from the river
yeah with her hat if you put it on oh oh
can you make more hats like that then no
I found a special part that lets me do
it I see I see see FAA because of that
hat is actually the real reason why I'm
sticking with you
what what about why just kidding oh it
was only for the Hat yeah sorry it's all
about you know materialism and and using
people for you know my
advantage it's not true it's not true
it's not true
F I can't believe this after
everything that a
zombie nice die potato seed let's go oh
nice all right the farm shall
expand okay should we yeah go to the
quest Point yeah yeah
yeah maybe we'll find food on the way
yes I believe so
hopefully zombies zombies
yippee y m
exp yummy
I made it to level 10 I need a better
B something powerful okay okay I'm going
to Club it in the head
die wait I think you're lower level than
me now aren't you don't worry I can
still protect you
die okay all right I'm going help I'll
hop to a different VC since I'll be
focusing on this stuff I'll see you guys
in a bit okay
okay all right giggy lead the way um I
believe it is this way 1 kilomet West
okay gy have you seen bibo's bicycle yet
no I want it yeah I was thinking of you
and she got it like you would love that
bicycle the way you're zooming once we
do our Quest we're going to have the
coolest bikes too we'll be a biker
family oh yeah we can have matching
outfits matching jackets The Clement
yay Ed
bedazzled on the back like those
families at Disney World wearing masing
shirts a we're Disney
Family oh
noie careful never mind you don't need
to be careful punching him mhm oh my God
you're so strong I'll put him on
fire thank you I get strong to impress
you guys that's my whole reason for
getting strong
consider me
impressed I want your attention so bad I
want to eat
microplastic
no show me what you have in your mouth
what is open up open up Ro playing as a
throw throwing cat throwing
up I've noticed actually my cat doesn't
only do that with plastics she also like
when I'm still in bed and I'm just not
coming out of bed to give her food and
there's no no plastics around then she
will like sniff on the mattress and find
all these little like fur balls that
have accumulated and accidentally get
them stuck on her nose nose and then she
like accidentally eats it and she can't
like get it out of her mouth and then
she forces me to pull like pull the hair
out and then I'm like this is so
annoying okay I'll make you food that's
an accident yeah yeah it's definitely on
purpose she only does that when she's
hungry they're too smart
yeah is this a fetch Quest or a clear a
clear Quest huh it's a clear Quest okay
okay get to punch stuff yay exp let's
see if it's like a repeated Quest once
again or if it's something new oh yeah
I'll repeat it looks to me it looks new
it's not on an area of my map I've been
oh yeah new area at least for me
true and also remember that neighborhood
that we found yesterday
FAA we should go loot yeah we should we
should look in the mailboxes yes
especially cuz that was a lot of nice
looking houses there
[Music]
mhm steal their books I heard there are
book stores oh that guy's scared that
guy's got red eyes and he's
fast to me it look like a jumping beer
just now you literally one shot I
thought he was going to be
scary the scary maybe maybe the enemies
got weaker because of laa
being oh she kep dying over and over and
then they're like it's time to be we
maybe oh level up I'm level nine oh
nice I'm getting addicted to this game
want to level up same
BS where is parkour parkour there I
heard parkour was good got to get one
point in
parkour parkour what is that Ender um
the the foot
icon so I one one like life hack Quality
of Life Hack That parkour gives you is
that you can jump higher and then you
can for example you could put down two
building blocks on top of each other and
now you can jump that high so you jump
up there and the zombies can't jump up
there but they will go towards you and
you just stand up there they can't reach
you but you can reach them with a spare
or so and yeah you just kill them like
that what the
hell D noodle D noodle I'm sorry Father
you into my
sledgehammer you just run up and punch
it snake meat no it's just normal sake I
did get meat yeah but it's just normal
steak huh it's all the
same ow the NOP
rope never seen a nope rope before in
this
game nope nope nope nope
nope we are almost there 80 M away let's
go I see it oh oh this looks familiar
but I guess they all just look the same
everything kind of looks
familiar oh my God Golem Golem get
houses from the same company F there's
Golem that's literally
Golem give me your ring give me your
ring he thought you had
it okay started the quest howo is this
you okay yeah I've got the ring that's
why I'm so strong
my
brushes my
shs in
German have you watched the German
version of course that's like the first
time I watched it it was always in
German like growing up mhm mhm that's
cool yeah nowadays I would watch
everything in English but when I was
younger the First Choice was still uh
German German oh god oh de oh two of
them
my clown
smack stamina
help there's more upstairs of course
there
isting
them my Stam I need to
eat soup I found no no no
no help
[Music]
help oh my God they're coming in from
outside too oh no I close the door I'm
cleaning I'm going to die no no yeah I
have also all kinds of debuffs right now
broken arm fra trying to use my bandaid
and I died oh God oh God oh God oh God
it's so over no no I'm still alive we
can't fail this we can't fail this I'm
still alive not for long
okay oh my God the last hit saved me 8
HP I'm out of stamina they went so fast
oh God what how is this
one did it get harder because it's day
16 it might have yeah but it's still
just one
skull
yeah maybe we just ran in too fast
no I have food by the way if anybody
needs
food I guess
yeah like one piece
is already okay a
start there's some bacon and eggs oh yum
thank you but did you actually die F I
died yeah the EXP I found the cooking
magazine all right can I read it yeah
although it's not there's still zombies
in here right cuz it's not
cleared yeah I think upstairs still
probably in the
closet I'm too I'm I can't go up
there
where are we downstairs too I still have
one skill downstairs area which one was
the one to heal naturally again this
one
just ouch ouch bird a b out of all
things now the birds are coming and
joining to kill us yes please are you
downstairs or upstairs or outside I'm
upstairs I went downstairs but there's
nothing down here
[Music]
H Tech junkie Tech junkie a farmer
outfit Farm outfit yeah oh we got to
give that to
Shian awesome too much junk in my
inventory so much junk in your trunk
really empty bookcase empty oh I found
the zombies they're downstairs and
chilling okay are you ready to fight
them yeah as ready as I can be right now
I will come down
there okay if only I had
ammo he I still have ammo I can stay
behind oh they're right in this okay you
ready yeah where
oh my
gosh came from
outside she dead there's one on me I'm
BL you blind it's just so dark in
here I thought that was a debuff too
he's fast I know I so fast I 18
HP oh you're so strong you're so
powerful some bandaids here take a take
a Band-Aid thank you do you have another
one one yes here oh let's go wrapping
myself
up oh I have
shells Oh
yay we are also oh we've cleared it okay
but let's take a look if we missed
anything there's an ammo pile here
random
Shotgun If you see 7.62 let me know
[Music]
okayy not that much cool stuff was there
a a
mailbox do you need armor crafting yes
yes I it's crazy I already have so much
in armor
crafting where are you I will drop it
outside I have
24 oh my God you're almost 25 here you
go 25 now hell yeah let's
go yippe okay then back to Trader
Chan
yep yay and if we see shii sometime we
got to give her the farmer outfit oh
yeah we should drop it off I have too
much stuff I should drop stuff
off okay me too me
too I'm picking up everything off the
ground on the way okay
oh I'm infected oh yeah got to find some
honey oh there's there oh do you guys
have an axe cuz I didn't bring an axe
can I have honey in my inventory all
right I have an axe oh like not a a
spare but I have one where are you oh
I'm with
son there you you look like a zombie can
you do something about that I can't I
can't I need new outfit and we all need
me I wish I had the one
outfit H nobody put on the Assassin's
outfit oh I haven't put it on I put it
in the chest in our house and I was
thinking giggy will put it on oh once we
get back I'll put it on all right wear
it I found that just for you you know
for all the sneaking I do mhm but I will
say the Assassin hat together with the
nerd hat are the top tier hats in the
game oh there's the nerd hat yeah the
nerd hat gives you ear XP buff ooh
actually yeah I want a nerd hat but but
the thing is like the nerd hat is best
to to use during the raids cuz that's
when you get all the XP oh yeah and the
Assassin hat is good because I think
it's got something with
looting and that's better for like
everyday life in the
[Music]
game I'm going inside this creepy
building uh this Three Star Building
yeah are you sure there's a zombie yes I
don't know we'll survive that we will
survive I will survive that car looks
like a clown
car look how strong FAA is oh thank
you our dear
wife such a Demir wife punching
everything are the mere patient kind
wife
oh you're breaking everything what else
is up here oh the floor is not very
strong be careful you'll get stuck with
just your
leg are you up there yeah nothing's up
here just
[Music]
trash some snack how to go down a there
you go why are we the animations man
they have no climbing animation at all
they're
running oh we going in there's a dead
person in here yes there is a
dead two of them
even there's two dead
people why is it why am I weak does that
mean my armor is almost broken yeah I
think
so I hope I can make some armor soon
need a
workbench this other one just fell down
on the ground after breaking those
things on the
Shelf he's dead no he's
not missed both my point
shot books
please they got to have some good stuff
here come on yeah this is a three star
area
oh it's a little foggy in
here in here out here everywhere foggy
in my mind too
that there three of them
there can't reload F than that oh it's
still over oh
no I tried my best with my gun so good
why just take two it's biting her legs
they have on them oh they only have
Rotting
Flesh zombie dogs damn dog zombie
dogs that's why I'm a cat person you
know exp depth let's go I know I have a
debt too actually I might have recovered
mine already I'm not
sure it does say beware of dog right
here chat what is that debm the 1 hour
39 what is
that it looks weird I've never seen it
before it was so foggy how are you
supposed to read that
far fatig need Vitamin oh do we have
vitamins at home yeah I have one vitamin
on me too oh I'll put it next to your
bat thank I want vitamin I need I think
we go inside from the window over here
oh there's somebody in
here you putting them out of their
misery
yeah let me
in ow do you want Sledgehammer crafting
skill yes okay I will drop it when you
join here it's right by the window oh
dear there's the doctor oh the doctor is
out um almost there something else in
here some glue yummy does anyone want a
blade crafting
skill I think bi Boo likes
those
okay this SE
bag
oh popping
pills popping
bottles too
okay oh my God I have a book for you do
you see this you should take
that I drop it see
it thank you wait where are you girls we
went inside just going through the
window 20% extra damage to knocked down
and stunned
opponents I'm getting so
strong which
window can you show me oh
yes maybe just ate a potato a that one
found it
okay
[Music]
whoa is this a hospital mhm hospital at
the golf place I guess it's the ranger
station hey armor
magazine oh there's one in here too uhoh
oh die zom
zomie it takes me
like the whole time until you kill him
until I
reload I thought he was
dead there's
a armored oh let's
go more more more more almost 30 now two
armored books here
too what is going on that's the fourth
in this room cuz I found one too
sure button it'll let us through oh you
got the keys yes yay 29 baby dead in
here
29 oh okay okay
okay almost shot
for I'm always up in the
action what do we got a dog
again but this time not
dog anybody in here for sure definitely
in the
toilet
def oh let's go okay I want to I want to
uh wear that what' you find let's go I
think that is the Assassin Rog Hood the
good one of the loot bonus ooh let's
go that is one of the top tier head now
we're now we're suddenly finding so many
armor things what the what is
that this person is dressed differently
than others
yeah I'm always so hesitant cuz I don't
want to accidentally shoot you
guys I don't waste of bullets
either so much exp from
him no why did I drink it that was
accidentally nice Community Kitchen
about to two pumpkins in here oh wait
don't eat them oh I just ate all the
pumpkins don't eat pumpkins eat this eat
this so zombie we're past eating raw
ingredients
so
hungry open bacon in
eggs anything else in here um no dead
end guess I can leave then
[Music]
okay noise now to head back home oh we
can open this door oh what it was oh
touch the keyack I've just gone in a
gigantic Circle oh you can go up
there think there's zombies up here nah
they can't
climb oh they can they can climb stairs
at least they they have no idea what
they're doing there's a parkour
situation up
here I have just skilled into
parkour it's just like parkour
civilization parkour can you explain to
me what that is cuz I don't know um it's
a world where parkour is the main
currency yeah like a Minecraft world
it's a Minecraft world and then they
only Exchange in parkour and then you
start off as a parkour Noob and uh when
you're a parkour Noob you either go for
the CH or you go for the
bee kill k
[Music]
beef or
chicken yeah chicken gives you two
hearts of health and then beef gives you
three hearts of health and you go for
the chicken every day you can never rank
up to be a parkour Pro so you either
live in complacency of being a parkour
Noob for your entire
life or you try and become a parkour
Pro you're so strong die
running low on stamina though ouch ouch
ouch I missed the point to blank
arrow
whoa we did it we did it sorry
ow we got to be more careful my
club there's probably good stuff in here
though it looks like
it passing gas sealed shipping
crate I actually need that
my pockets are so full I know me too
mine too but I don't want to skill
into the pack mu trade there's some good
armor that um like gives you more
inventory and
stuff lot of medical
stuff there's a magazine for medicine
what Med medicine um yeah two people I
think
does anybody scale into bow
crafting I will do it okay wait then
I'll leave it in this uh chest here this
one
okayy oh there's a reinforced chest
should we break it open it only takes a
bunch of hits yes yes yes no one knows
lockpicking
huh oh no I'm sorry it's okay just try
just trying to find a good spot
is this a good
spot
yeah ow we're almost
there I'll let you I'll let you do the
thing I don't want to die not by your
hands you would feel too
guilty
oh there's some 9 mm ammo and bullet
casing here on the table I'm out of
stamina oh I'm going to drink beer this
will help will it help are you drinking
again G I Can't Help It 8 a.m. is the
best time to
drink we need to have
disc this no I I just ever since we I
lost my job because of the apocalypse
really hitting me
hard same same we're all in the same
boat girl
yeah I found this lifestyle to be really
fulfilling you know yeah grow our own
food it brings us back to Our Roots you
know yeah I'm just so sad I can't
provide for my wives anymore I don't
what do you me you do
provide I'm not providing the life style
you deserve Gucci prod bags every
[Music]
weekend I don't get a bonus
anymore sometimes a simple life is
better means more than all that
stuff long as we have bacon and eggs to
eat that's all we really
need you're right I found a new
perspective on life I'm no longer
drunk I see the light that was fast just
a quick 20 minute 20 minutes drunken
session just just feeling the buzz a
little bit
I'm still out of stamina though I know
me too I'm fatigued too I need
vitamins what unbelievable okay I have
vitamins I have one vitamin you vitamin
can I have it yes I'm just trying to
parkour right now would you do you think
you would be able to build a building
block
perhaps I want to go on the roof okay
and I'm trying it with this chair
inside what's inside we have vehicle
Adventures does anyone vehicle
crafting I'm going to scrap and there's
ammo for you yeah let's go and some B
here you can look inside
yes vehicle crafting let's go nice ammo
I can help again oh I don't have any
wood what's time I have some wood it's a
bomb here take this
okay uh I I shall take because I want
the
block
building building
building
uh uh here take this armor crafting oh
thank You magazine another one another
one okay I'm putting down the wood again
because I can't carry this much but
thank you okay I will take my wood back
my 1,000
Woods oh actually I guess I need one
more
block Uh Wood lady can you build one
more block and put it up there
okay oh and
vitamin thank you vitamins are very
[Music]
important they are thank you okay there
was nothing up here
good good we just had to know
yes all right then we shall not get too
distracted and go back home I guess yeah
I got to drop off all our items and then
do another Quest yes and another one I
failed this time uhoh broken
leg how did I not break my leg careful
careful L maybe it was your parkour
yeah save you it could be it could be I
knew there was a parkour God out
there she protects us parkour goddess
thank you so so
thirsty oh we could go to a lake and
drink oh yeah is there one there's not
really it's behind us should we
behind howsty I'm quite thirsty it's
okay I'll make it okay
but what about a nice picnic by the lake
you know with a we can make it to the
one right next to the trader that'll be
beautiful
okay I love picn but my stamina is quite
low because I am dehydrated take it
slow you can drink my Molotov
cocktail no no more alcohol I thought we
discussed this that's why you're thirsty
you're dehydrated my
alcoholism the 9:00 a.m. beer I can't
help it life is so rough but my wives
are here to make sure I don't fall back
to bad behaviors that's
right even though I just offered the
molotov
cocktail the devil and the angel on my
shoulder I just tested you and I'm
impressed by the results of you
resisting
thank you that's my man I can have
uppies later
upes you're into uppies I didn't know
can I have uppies later up J Slaughter I
love
uppies I've been here before let's in
here there's another zombie I'll punch
him two
stamina L you're so good at doing that
amazing I just leled up my punch this
zombie was just a van life YouTuber and
this is what you do to him van life
YouTuber all his subscribers will now be
wondering why is he not making any more
van life videos whatever subscribe to my
channel instead P life but are you going
to bring out the same content I doubt
it oh I just had this feeling I heard
shod what the
hell oh Bo
voices in my head she's been soaking up
our XP this whole time yeah it's okay
we'll
share the mushroom Mining Company our
favorite led to many broken
legs I saw a clip a perfectly cut clip
from your PO fauna when I was falling
down oh
no that was nice
and giggy you missed the most dramatic
fight ever yesterday with the boar oh
yeah the boar have respawn I haven't
thought it I looked at it yes you want
to go
back for maybe not for
now we were so much meat from it we died
a million times but we kept on coming
back we're stronger now and we got the
supern also stronger yeah we did Super
corn supern I doubt it stronger it
wouldn't learn from its mistakes yeah
doesn't have the capabilities of
learning M I don't want to see grace
anymore no no no no yeah is the Bo's
name
Grace name I named it I think so
experiment or whatever Bob from Bob's
bores Bob your Bor she's
massive experiment success
successful but also failed I guess that
they didn't want it to be that big and
aggressive but the tiny boyss I felt so
bad for no tiny we kept accidentally
punching them when they were
just they were so exhausted I'm
sad you're so
thirsty here where says you I am also
thirsty you're pretty thirsty on twt
Twitter as well borrow I can't help it
when you show us your your your I I
can't say my
but yes where am I supposed to look when
you show us your butto I must dropped my
hat it's okay you can you can look at my
buttock all you want your hood is
getting washed away into the river it's
following do you have can I drink what's
happening do you have an empty hand oh
here we go is there strings attached to
you
GGY
yes strings
attached so
thirsty you're spam spamming the button
you falled under that hat yes I feel
like I've never seen your face in all
the time we've been together
not looks shaved not bald I like it oh
Kiara you're your mask it's so cool too
oh really yeah I think I've have
drinking enough do you need some Kiara
um the blue one is the the first right
the your okay I'm fine I'm fine it seems
okay I don't know how but I
am all right
continue oh you can finally move
normally again gy yeah I am regening
normally
oh what that's your St no I'm not
looking at the stamina bar I'm looking
at the other blue
bar that one right
[Music]
there what is
that have a lot of bars bacon and
eggs you know who else has lots of bars
fa she does I'm spitting them yeah I
haven't heard her spitting
them you didn't see her
ram my
oh yeah I guess she spits
occasionally when I'm feeling passionate
about something when she does then she
really she really spits those
bars no joking with
her all right traitor
[Music]
serious hello Trader
wrecked I think I'll take the
[Music]
magazines magazine
gotcha I wonder maybe now he's selling
the magazines that I
want oh level up level up level up
oh my inventory is so full goodbye
sewing kit mine
too wait is sewing I'll take that oh
it's on the ground
now I'm too much of a loot Goblin I'll
just crawl home if I need
to there's a buried supplies 400 m east
oh he's selling workstation crafting
skills books oh threee of them that's a
good start you have
[Music]
money not enough I can only buy one
right
now but I'll sell some
stuff you hey girls when you look into
his um in his shop does he sell Forge
ahead by any chance for
you let me I will
check take a look don't expect me to
through can probably get he's not
letting me
shop can only one person shop at a time
I don't know what no I thought that was
debunked oh well he's not opening his
shop to me I think you just have to
stand like in the right
way so evil for
that
um oh I might need that actually oh
well I don't know what to sell oh wait
maybe this gets me some good stuff
too oh
okay all
right I have unlock home to get rid of
everything he can you bring some
money okay like maybe 500 so I can buy
his workstation magazine
stock I will bring it oh he does have
Forge ah head he has two do you have
some money
wait two for you and Two For Me Maybe we
have the same like if I yeah maybe has
the same inventory oh so if I buy it out
he won't have any more for you too okay
maybe how many do I still need I think
let's see
um I still
need
uh
six I think right CH hey where am I
going oh 10 in order to make one right
yeah okay six I need six more so these
two and maybe he'll restock while we're
playing the next Quest is really close
to our house yeah it is
awesome I want to make some snacks oh
but birds Dr off bird supplies chest uh
quests are often bugged it seems
yesterday we just failed one when we
started it really no this one will be
better
it's not too far so it will be
okay all
right I should also go home and drop
something off but I want to buy the
magazines well gy are you coming back to
the
trader I can come back with the money
okay can you just buy the two magazines
and then give them to me um it looks
like there's
only oh there's 2,000 I have 400 oh here
we go oh my gosh we're rich so
rich of course we
are We Are Born to Be
Rich we're supposed to be rich we look
rich the richness is calling for
us it's our destiny to be rich very
aspirational thinking I like
it oops water in
here come on
[Music]
stamina come
on if you play this game for seven
ingame
nights uh oh no never mind where were
you pass that is there no there's no
maximum right this is like
endless yeah I think so
oo you can keep going until you get
tired tired of playing this
[Music]
game oh I wonder where Shi
is oh she left our party oh she wants no
more XP huhuh I see
yeah I'm going to put her outfit in here
yeah we should tell her there's a
farming outfit she can Farm way more
officially that
[Music]
now wow farmer outfit looking
good I'm going I'm just going to go tell
her in voice chat yes I'll be right back
she'll be
delighted
ah gigy you use 9 mm ammo I use shotgun
shells oh okay I I just added I don't
know if that is is that
different I I think they're called
shotgun ammo oh okay oh Assassin outfit
forgot to take this Assassin outfit oh
oh oh yeah right we found that
huh okay I told her was she
happy yes she was delighted oh we love
to make people happy
yes okay I'm going to buy the
the items yes
okay I'm running
off you go you go do
that
oh is there
glue there should be I just put some in
there oh I just want to like add on to
it is it a the bottom chest oh yeah well
is there like a theme between these two
chest no but I was I was just thinking
there should be
[Music]
maybe well that will be difficult to
achieve at this
point yeah we got so many bones can we
make something with the bones I don't
know actually can make a bone knife oh
yeah many bone knives mhm potato seed
corn seed
pumpin SE okay
purchasing which one Southern farno V
makes what do you want H the what was it
the the workstation
magazine I feel like someone might have
purchased it hey there should be two a
she Callie just bought it for ahead see
wrong chat wrong chat bought
it I need this urch Le did ni right from
under my nose yeah I walk past
her then I only need four more then we
can have a workbench
finally I feel like it's taking forever
to get the workbench like it's crazy
like a workbench is like the most basic
thing in like rust and Minecraft and all
these other games but here it's like a
whole Miss apocalypse it is it's like my
life mission MH crazy is she going to
come over to us I
wonder she is at the Traer oh I'll come
to
you Trader where are
you that I never know when we leave our
house is it left or
right left right up it's up up wait yeah
it's it's up from our house when you
exit our home it's up yeah it's where
you coming from right now right yeah
yeah yeah okay how do you name a box
again I think it has a button and then
you can click on
it uh oh e hold e I'm going to try
digging the
thing wait wait no you have to do it us
okay okay I will wait is it is it on the
way kill someone oh no it's just over
here it's oh okay uh okay right here is
where it's at Wait f can you come over
quickly yes I'll see what's
around oh we're really low on
food wait is this the farm okay hold on
don't don't get
distracted don't get distracted
just quickly going to dig this and then
I'll go over to
[Music]
C get this tree there yeah this area
this biomi is
scary okay wait I'm not here I'm here
okay dig dig dig I'm digging do I have
yes I
have this show me where your goods
are is it usually like at the very
center
of the I just randomly down oh I found
it wow oh that was fast yay can you get
out of there wait is this a thing where
we all have to find our own it seems
like we all have to find okay yeah it
was like that with the ow oh no they
zombies I'll try I'll try killing them
okay oh there's a big one well there's a
big one what what that he's Bing
is that the cop zombie oh God yes he's
spinning
ouch W our first cop jump what's
happening oh I'm dying don't don't don't
SP behind you behind you behind you he
just
exploded
ouch is this because we're uh digging
right now I know
yeah it's prob of the quest kind of
crazy let us dig in peace
please I think you might have the same
one Kiara if you search down there is
there there
yeah it looks like butter okay then to
the TR what the
hell many all
a are we running or finding I'm running
we can we can run goodbye
run bye I want to turn in the quest
yes I feel like digging quests would
probably be like not such a big reward
could it
be hello oh
hello kie told me that you you're very
far on for Forge thingy K in the old
house if you go to the second floor
there's two magazines in the box if you
want them is it the ones that Cali just
bought or SE separate ones from the ones
that CI has or no those they were mine I
told you yesterday I think that you
could have them but I don't think you
heard me oh ah so there's four in total
there four in total maybe maybe that's
the ones Callie is talking about I'm not
sure okay well yeah call at least two in
the old house okay I'll see I'll see if
should and we'll see if the trainer
still has two yeah gy did didn't you
check oh it's the Traer doesn't have
anymore goodbye byebye because cie
bought them from under my nose yeah
right yeah she was like looking for it
though okay now I'll check in the uh
main house or I'll check later I guess
cuz we can just go do a quest
now oh so there is two extra four in
total I don't want and just get bacon
and eggs from him but I'm so hungry no
resist take something more
special okay how difficult is it to make
ammo has anyone learned how to make ammo
yet uh no I don't think so I can get you
I don't know should I get this shotgun
shell but we don't know how to make
ammo requires a
workbench all right reward
with the Malone residence no no no not
the
please we I know we can't be there okay
I've taken the Malone residence as well
did you yeah can I take a different one
can we get multiple quests try taking
one and see okay I'm going to take
Sean's sh he's giving me 109 mm ammo but
that's not the one I want oh I have some
ammo for
you I'll just take the 9mm ammo and
hopefully someone will make use of it I
guess
aell out okay just double checking if he
really has no more but I I want to buy
these
maybe all right later thank you let's
go I'm so hungry should we drop stuff
off and then go
okay I oh I have some food for
you you I have what kind of food soup
stock and can of chili o I'll eat that
actually maybe they have food in the
main house I got to go there
anyway we're going to take some of their
food oh the the main house is kind of
like where the like on the way no the
fetch Quest is on the way to the main
house
Won't Anyone think about the Clement
we're hungry too we are well we got the
super corn
growing yeah it will it will one day it
will serve us well and everybody will
want it we should try to get a du
collector too maybe yeah I guess so I
think it's not that expensive we just
need what is it duct tape pipes and
plastic oh easy we have that's stuff
yeah maybe we should make
one wait someone's saying I can already
make a forge now a forge yeah but not a
workstation right what can I do with a
forge maybe I should make a forge yeah
maybe you can make some stuff with the
forge I don't
know it seems I can make it with the
right
ingredients maybe with that you ah I
smelt stuff with it okay and with the
the ingredients that I smelt I guess I
can make the arm too perhaps I see I put
the food in the food
chest thank
you wait I'm coming to our house too I
would also love some
food hungry by
default
um hold on how do you make the
do
collector duct tape iron
pipe we only have one duct tape
nah I'm sure we have more it's just not
organized yeah I have two duct tape but
I think I need for the forge oh yeah for
the forge I need free duct tape and
threee iron pipes Etc okay we can make
the the forge
yeah then I need there one more duct
tape here's duct tape thank you wait you
can make duct tape somehow oh wait I can
make duct tape oh so
talented what else I keep on forgetting
uh one woodlock how do we get a whole
woodlock because I've only
seen that we can Harvest like wood um
like
boards oh I can make one oh okay yeah
it's 10 wood for wood log oh
[Music]
ah and you need it TR
now yeah let's just make it
now do you have any more cloth kiaha
cloth's my wood if you see something in
my chest you can take it
okay I don't see any I'm just missing
cob St Ro okay if there's nothing in
there then I don't think I
has that's okay I will find it is it for
the water
thing yes
H oh we have stuff up
here a
forge Forge ahead
wait can I actually cut up our couch to
get cloth well maybe I should cut up our
couch sounds possible sit food we can go
to their house and take their
couch oh this thing is huge should I put
it inside or outside maybe inside could
put it upstairs if there's not room
downstair I'll get rid of this I'll get
rid of the kitchen table
yeah this is a good space for
it
whooo
here
[Music]
wow where is
that redeem the Harrison have to have a
couch right yeah rip
apart this house next door must is this
the a pig house oh it's Bob's house
Bob's house is kind of
scary I don't this house is so nice
though I don't want to destroy their
stuff wa let's just destroy Bob's house
I'll make sure it's Bob's house safe
over
here pickup truck turn on the forge oh
it's a leather couch they're two fany
they have a leather couch leather
couch uh
uh H do we have something useful I've
got ceiling zombies
here expected of such a bougie home I
know do you can afford ceiling zombies
too a where' It Go
what is
around pile of
books fishing
book wait where are
you I'm in um the Harrison's house oh
okay just
raing yeah I'm looking for
cloth how do you take apart their couch
do you need a tool for it I don't know I
just smacked it with my uh my ax but it
didn't give me cloth only leather may
maybe this one's made of
cloth okay I'm at Bob's house looking
for a
couch why are we so desperate for cloth
right now we need duct tape to make a do
collector
yeah it is true it is true Bob I am
going to kill your pigs for
food sorry Bob
curtains are also good holy cow I just
one shot it oh I'm so
hungry ah don't worry I just killed a
pig if I can oh no oh
no what is this room for oh my gosh
there's just a folding chair in the
closet it's the timeout
Corner let's see I'm
[Music]
starving okay oh I better get home I'm
starving I'm back
homea your presence is missed is there
any food in oh I already searched in
here I think there's in our home there's
one can of
chili okay and one sham
sandwich maybe I could just get this pig
you'll have so much
food it's true he died in a cage and I
can't kill it why are raw eggs in the
output of the cooking
pot shouldn't it be cooked
eggs you can put them back in the food
chest oh I just put them in there for
storing
oh can we not just make boiled eggs I
apparently they're
[Music]
bad okay take water I guess it's better
to just make bacon and eggs a aen aen
bags Ain bags Ain and
[Music]
Bon bacon bacon you put clay in the
Forge smelter then you can forge it put
clay in the Forge
smelter I got you clay clay clay clay
clay clay clay I saw it
somewhere clay clay there clay in the
Forge smell
in the ah oh is that why nothing's
happening oh wait do we not have
microplastics I have some do you have
some my
tummy no no macro
plastic so is this number the4 five and
so on is that um like the iron being
smelted and like possible to use
I see so if I fill all these oh I can
only put two at a time in right so I
can't have like brass lead Sandstone all
at the same
time but I could make some forged iron
for now right that would be
good always be I have 60 meat again
wa we're safe you are
providing once I let go of the alcohol
that was limiting me I can finally
provide for my
wives I dismantled our
car I hope we weren't going to use
that okay uh I want a quest I want to go
questing we can go to the area do you
want me to come back so you can make
food first though yeah I really want
food I think if we have food and then um
if I can get just a little more plastic
I can make the water
collector okay okay and then the quest
I'm going to is um the their house is on
the way to it we can also get your your
Workshop books once we do it yeah yes
it's more like the quest is on the way I
feel like
it depends on how you see it I
[Laughter]
guess then I don't know I feels like I
feel like I'm not doing anything on my
way back can you get plastic plastic
from just a random house I don't know
anything let see what I can do you can
dismantle cars or tires all right
um we might have barely enough let me
see check my chest again chest chest we
need nine more Plastics wait is there
some
upstairs trash has plastic
okay we need we need two more
Plastics ah that would have been
good oh I see I just went to their house
on accident I was not following the
correct
Arrow oh I was like who are these people
are they raiding or questing yeah
they're going in the house together I
thought it was a bunch of really
intelligent
zombies oh I'm so
hungry were we not
princess why
there I thought we were above eating
Rock I didn't eat we're growing pumpkins
I found one duct
tape that's
good I'm scared there's weird getting
kind scary yeah yeah why what is this
atmosphere I just want
some is this
plastic
h no my thing broke my a
broke weird sounds in the
forest I have enough okay I can make the
do
collector I think oh really I think
so what's this place
again skers place
Box
egg I'm so scared to go into things
alone am I getting we be wait this would
be such a good uh base because it has a
water source right in front of the house
like its own little Pond oh that would I
know we probably should have been nearer
to water source but we're also pretty
close to the Traer though
uh should I go the lake is right behind
the
trader
yeah why is this so scary out
[Music]
here I'm back with the
meat yay I will put it in the food chest
here is 60 meat and six eggs go thank
you I will be right back real quick okay
I'm scared
mommy are you come home come home no I
must provide too okay you must
provide we've got a lot of bacon and
eggs
now you okay no I don't have the
confidence to ra
alone I'm scared I'm going back
I can come with you now in a minute it's
just like there's some kind of be Boral
audio going on in there when you
suddenly hear the zombies in your both
of your ears it's like ASMR but the
worst type of as AR don't my
it it is I have way more confidence with
you girls
around I'm running it's so like time for
me to get a workstation because my armor
needs to be replaced ASAP yeah we do
have repair kits if you want to fix it
oh I don't think it's even worth it I
just need two more magazines if you
think about it two is nothing we can
just luckily get those
maybe maybe maybe if we get
lucky two
at this chest and then another two
randomly
oh I see the water collector wonderful
yippee yeah we are so good at
this
mm what did I come over here for ah
food it's
cooking food and the sense of
[Music]
safety okay are we no longer
hungry it's
cooking one is ready here while we're
cooking do you want to hear one more cat
incident I had yes always okay so I feel
like this happens to any cat at some
point but chunky wonky she was like
sniffing stuff and touching stuff and
she touched something that had a sticky
surface some kind of sticker and she got
it stuck on her uh tail and the moment
she had it stuck there she freaked out
and like
zoomed through the through all the
hallways and back and forth and she was
like and I was like running after her
like stop stop let me just like rip it
off when she would just freak out and
not
stop it's so funny they freak out when
they have something stuck to their fur
immediately they're so silly they're so
silly they are silly they lose their
minds micro plastic eating
Rascals it's so cute
though I'm cleaning up the
place all this this trash on the floor
yeah we don't need all this stuff
there's no way but gigy did you see the
forge here look at this Forge oh my God
in our kitchen like a pizza
oven yeah it is the some good pizzas in
there to make a pizza wonder if I put
this in there would you put pineapple on
your pizza yeah always I love pineapple
pizza I do like pineapple pizza this is
our pineapple pizza
[Applause]
[Music]
resident let's
go it does this make sense guys what I'm
doing here Stone as well what happens
with
[Music]
stone oh but I ah I still have all the
iron in here ah it took it
all the meat got used so
fast I don't understand why it costs so
much meat for two bacon strips and one
egg it shrinks a lot in the
pain especially cuz they don't
differentiate the stakes we get from the
Big Boar versus the vulture for example
or even the snake didn't the snake give
us the same meat yeah
[Music]
crazy oh whole first eight
kit I'll take one vitamin just in case
sometimes it's handy to have one at
hand handy to have there's an armor book
here too in there oh there's we have a
book chest I didn't realize yeah I
wanted to make a book show but I didn't
know
time to get
reading I think
I seed CRA why
not
ah robotic didn't I have something in
robotic
maybe harvesting
[Music]
tool free
Salvage
11 armor
33 I can make real good armor already
that's like the I bet that's the highest
skill anybody
has
so yeah I just asserted dominance I said
give me all you got Senai tax you cannot
say no to me I am the most Senpai out of
all of you except for Cali cuz she's she
is two hours older than
me she was pushing real hard to get out
of that
stomach yeah it was like we were a twin
bth I'm pretty much ready to go okay
okay those two hours make the difference
tell I have three bacon and eggs for
people who are hungry
okay I think I'll survive for now but
it's good to have yeah I think I am good
right now all right so one of you has a
quest right or do we uhhuh okay I have a
quest all right too got two
quests then we shall March oh somebody
fell a tree me I'm a Timber
deforestation hey hey hey no
deforestation are you punching a
boulder getting rid of everything in
this Forest I feel like the con rocks
are not safe the Conant of videos that I
consumed today on YouTube will change my
algorithm completely for a while because
I watched a 2hour video of like jungle
survival alone with no tools and then
another one I watched today was um some
guy uh building uh like his his own
office under his stairs and failing a
lot the one where where like he made the
chair like he couldn't get the corner
right yeah yeah yeah but then he was so
happy about the brass Det
why did you watch that I don't know it
looked
intriguing amazing that was so
interesting he used chat GPT to do math
for him and it did it wrong can't trust
chat GPT with
everything yeah I really liked it
because like a lot of these like videos
where like people build stuff they're
like only successful but he had so many
failures and learned a lot of stuff too
just by
watching it did kind of make me want to
like make something right me too I felt
so confident watching that working yeah
it's like oh even if you mess up you
could just slap some bronze on top of it
then again then again that guy he has
his whole like workstation room and
everything he has a lot of experience
with that so I don't think we could do
it that easily huh yeah no we could we
should have a woodworking Club yeah we
can whittle a horse for each
other what you know like the wood
carving and we make a little statues for
each other
oh statues of each
other what if they turn out really yeah
oh I've been here the Malone resident
Malone leave me they're here oh oh well
we'll they're doing the wait yeah we
can't do it at the same time we can't
they're doing
can't what's
up it'll probably be done soon right are
you guys almost
[Music]
done it seems like they're pretty done
they're all swarming out
yeah or are
they okay got to wait unfor maybe they
just started do you have a the other one
you yeah where's your quest yeah it's a
little bit far but
it's there's a deer over there we have
to kill it it's so active though a deer
yeah we kill it we can have meat can I
punch it it's going into the Frozen
lands it
runs oh
[Music]
go I I feel like the Frozen lands are
still dangerous because of the mountain
lions we should not go mountain lions oh
it's the National Forest
the water and drown that is
like a zombie I've never seen
before oh yeah
e yeah uh where's the other Quest try
snipe it oh CeCe has a forged ahead
magazine she said what more in the chat
I think so
whoa enough so that's free I haven't
used yet
yeah why haven't you used them a to the
Yol a to the
Yol oh wait do you want to go pick up
the other mag yeah we can oh wait are
they done oh are they done now no they
said they can't oh okay now they
done I can't hit this deer it's so good
yay
yay y yay who is this did they already
clear it out
too I
guess are you still fighting the deer
yeah I'll get it I'll hit it soon
soon I I miss missing I missed 10 arrows
on it no it's running
away run di
run oh Mis so soup they left so much a
potato oh isn't the like cuz when you
start the quest the enemies inside and
uh respawn does the the loot respawn I
have a feeling it does yeah so if I loot
it now we can get double loot maybe no
there's a zombie get away from my deer
stop
that's my it's my deer KY come
on the zombie is eating my deer I killed
the deer the zombie trying to kill my
deer that's my deer for my
wives get off that deer
she no no it's okay don't don't worry I
got it I got it there's a wolf over
there you better be careful I know at
scary oh God I hear something really
really t terrifying next to me it's a
zombie leave my deer alone you better
get out of there I need this
steer it's eating my deer there's a wolf
walking towards you glowing red
eyes isn't that the one I want to make
for
CR I think I found the the helmet that
belongs to the heavy armor that I want
to make for you fauna oh it's very
terrifying looking it's not very
Charming good good but the crazy thing
is this it's literally in an in a house
that has no skulls no
zombies why why is something so good I
have a forge ahead what another one yeah
I found it randomly gosh what then after
I pick up the CC ones we literally have
a workstation anyway here's the Rader
hel helmet fun your prettiness will
still be underneath there somewhere
Quest not available until 4:30 3 what
what time is it 3:45 oh they need to
restock the
insides they need to put more zombies
inside they're all they can just loot
everything around all paid
actors it's not real zombies AR
real wow scary you look very
scary I will miss your green hair it
made you so easy to recognize yeah H
should we go get your books then yeah
let's do it while we wait let's do
it um where is it where's that
way uh that way do you think if I hit
the wolf it will kill me do you want me
to help you find it what does it
drop
meat it has red eyes though doesn't that
mean it's like really dangerous nah I
missed three of my arrows on it
he looks really
dangerous I hit it I hit it I hit it
[Music]
sad what about now is it sad now now is
about to kill you it is sad oh my God
it's really large oh I'm so
thirsty I'm sorry I'll find water down
maybe oh it died oh that
did you resurrect it did you just use
necromancy it broke my arm I'm about to
die not dead he not dead yet it's still
alive he's running after I can't believe
my arm
broke no don't worry he's out on me
now my leg oh no how am I going to punch
with a broken arm oh I just realized is
that that
my party's HP on the top
left you're so
dead what did we
die oh my god oh
no why why does it have so much HP I
don't
know ow oh my I have some help
your egg speed up you girls got to be
more
careful oh
nocking up the he's really
tanky I told you the cold lands are
dangerous I want to kill him I want him
dead I want to know what's on his body
you know what you can still kill him one
day when you're stronger you just have
to strengthen yourself I'm good today
today is that day
I hope he's still there he's still there
he's eating your dead
body oh he's still mad he's still mad
but I'm
healing uhoh no he broke my arm
instantly he's so strong I can't he this
don't worry don't worry I'm alive now
I'm going to shoot my arrow in my
arm you die second time paa look at your
HP he too
strong okay okay okay I'll kind of I'll
kind of I'll distract him we have to
find him together if we're going to find
him oh no I'm staying out of this I'm
just going to go get my books and get
smarter meanwhile the girls are down
only I had shotgun
ammo that' be nice huh you're scaring me
I'm running out of ammo oh
no is he still there yeah don't worry
I'm kiing him over these two
broken no it's
not let's get some water and some
food
[Music]
hello I'm sure he'll give you so much xp
you won't have any debt anymore will he
ow he broke my
leg f is it worth it is it worth
it we Su cost fallacy kill
him I'm having a feast here it's like
Thanksgiving meanwhile you girls don't
worry he's resetting our it really
hurts oh I feel so good here broke my
leg he's dead he's
dead maybe some more of bacon
eggs so easy what did he drop um BS
steroids um do you want tea I have
shotgun ammo and
7.62 ammo I'll take that and
Mining I will take the art of mining do
it here do you want is whatever's here
chest I'll take the
steroids my poor leg let's go work
broken
too
what at least we have broken legs
together two broken legs between the two
of us
yeah okay I real time we'll try to make
a 1 hour 24
minutes please no we need a
splint
yeah kiaha you can come back and we can
start the quest oh to you girls
okay yeah
[Music]
yeah okay and then when after the quest
maybe I'll uh or oh later is fine too
sometime during the night when we are
not doing any Quest I'll make the
workbench or when we got when we're like
reloading stuff or so whatever when we
have time and then I can make armor
what do I need for making a workbench
anyway
workbench I will need mechanical Parts
duct tape nails woods and forged iron
perfect I think we have all that oh is
our our doctor left wait did she
leave the
doctor
doctor she's still in a VC but is she
offline
M why do you need something from her I
need a splint
doctor well I'm also a doctor in
training if I could get a few more books
call
911 mhi
MOSI could probably infiltrate her
VC I'm worried she logged off for the
day I don't know I don't want to bother
her if she's not streaming yeah why is
she alone in there yeah maybe she just
needs a moment this job is
stressful true he smoke break on the
job wait maybe I can make a
splint you can it in duct tape I think
you can do everything fauna that you set
your mind
to people say Cece's done for the day we
have broken legs I think I can make I'll
with wood and duct tape doctors off have
two duct tape do you have wood can I
have your duct tape I have 1,000 wood
here for you a lot of wood I have
another thousand in my inventory don't
worry she's always chopping those trees
I have five cloth fragments I'll make
you a splint I'm glad we could at least
have broken legs
together there you go thank you for this
try try that out
doctor I'm Healed I have a 40 minute a
now I'm healing recovering wait let me
give you your wood
back that was worth it I would say yeah
we got so much xp
steroids yeah a
book
yeah
um soup
soup
te so much barel extender mod
schematic I don't know what that is do
you want that I have no idea I'll carry
it for now that sounds like something
for a
shotgun increases damage range and aimed
accuracy for my shotgun
I'm typing the Bible no no no
barely
barely what's in
here
CH it's going to disassemble their car
don't need it anymore almost there 100
[Music]
m what does Callie mean I should make
the ammo or is she saying she is going
to make the
ammo um how do I interpret that I think
she's going to make ammo oh sick I don't
know cuz I think I'll get i'll get real
busy with the armor making probably yeah
all right I'm here where are you oh
there right here
okay let's
begin wait wait wait oh okay okay we are
get
it Chang it's blue now
how that
happened
oh trying to get up here to search this
pile of garbage I wish they would give
us different quests we're always going
to the same
places yeah maybe we need anymore better
oh there's a guy up
here oh I why did I why did I why did I
do
that don't wor distance oh there's some
more guys I can take them even with a
brok
leg our healing leg I need to distance
myself from these toxic
interactions no no no no I said distance
distance distance
distance dead dead
okay soon to be dead nice shot in the
neck
giggy yeah he's dead now no he's will be
dead soon he can got the jump sounds
like there's some stuff going on down
there there I'm just loing the
attic no it's calm it's
calm yum
yum I'm just babying my
leg I'm going into the basement Who's
down
here anybody
beautiful somebody hear someone me
too oh I see him
now meow
meow there's two of them in there is the
kitty kitty there no there's just like
pictures of cats really yeah who's cat
finally cat pictures I thought they were
only dog pictures and bird pictures but
finally some
justice oh I found a stash
I forgot we were doing a
[Laughter]
quest you just get so into your blood
lust I know I'm just here to punch
things oh I know I like how it explodes
once you're done looking at them the
pictures are photos of the death's pets
oh we have the confirmation I knew it I
knew it
thank you those are
cute
NY where the rest of them wow my carrier
s oh someone else's I think it's really
badly H like hidden in a way that I
would normally never find it no I found
it by accident is this someone
else's it's not mine oh yeah I forgot we
to find supplies here up here maybe you
forgot you were on a quest too I thought
it was a clear Quest is that yours oh
there's the kitties I di meow meow oh
they're cute two of them two of them oh
I have a medical journal for you soon to
be doctor thank
you got to keep an eye dangerous hey
have you been to the attic yet yes okay
I don't think there's anything left up
there you can go if you want maybe
there's a cour satchel though oh true
there might be
wait you you forgot an important thing
F you didn't open the shipping crate
there's a shipping crate I'll take
it oh there was just ammo that I can't
use oh this is a different attic than
the one I was in this is not my attic
it's not my I wouldn't ever miss
something important like that
get hammered I will thank you or their
cats yeah for us
now tuna
I'm where is my career
Satchel is it
downstairs I'm also very
cucumber does somebody want to take some
of my stuff
I am also very cucumber I am also
consolidate though uh how heavy I wonder
our
magazines one space Oh Oh It's about
spaces not the weight yeah oh wa then F
read my cooking
magazine oh I would love
to it's about as heavy as 1,000 pieces
of wood here in this cooking magazine
you will learn how to make Austrian
Schnitzer pumpkin pie
no or kaisman how about kaiserman
pumpkin
pie not P I learned pumpkin pie in
Kaiser
yes what is this shotgun Messiah volume
free oh shotgun I don't use
shotgun giggy use shotgun I use shotgun
then I think this magazine might be good
for you
ooh and then have haven't I already
given you a bow magazine before then
take this one to build onto it yes more
bows wow sharing is caring because we
care so much about each other in the
Clementine family yes that's so
beautiful and there's a wait I still
haven't found found my yeah okay
uh it should be maybe behind you I don't
know it's like does it show up on your
map uh yeah I just tried to follow it
now but could it be
outside Maybe not
maybe no wait it's that way it's moving
maybe a zombie is carrying it is
upstairs or downstairs
M well it must be right above me I guess
if it's moving around like that yeah or
or below me
cuz I checked the attic but I didn't
check the fauna attic oh yeah there's
another Attic in the garage but yeah it
wasn't in the garage yet let me check
out the garage the garage
attic um so many why does this house
need two
attics I know save some for the rest of
us yeah my house doesn't even have one
attic that's good though atcts are kind
of scary it feels like Monsters be up
there or rats is there Satchel up here
kiaha I found another one that doesn't
belong to me so I found two that don't
belong to me this the one that you found
is is it on a
shelf why is it over there oh okay wait
then it must be the one you you saw
living room living room it's on the
ledge upstairs or come to the garage and
go up the ladder the garage and up up
the
[Music]
ladder I broke their sofa and got cloth
do you need that
mhm just break all their
stuff that's a living
room through here through here damn
zombies you live like
that across you see they they're hidden
so
mean what if I break my
leg okay you'll be just like us yeah
we can make you a splint like I saw that
one over there but this one you kidding
me we can
match
yeah okay we're done ladies
okay we can go back to the trader how
far is your quest
fa I don't
lad come on now we're not amateurs
anymore I have
a we have the walk back our poor legs oh
I know oh oh still oh
no we're 21 more minutes oh that's not
so bad I have 28 I don't know if I
jumped maybe I did is is all of that all
those broken legs are from your little
Adventure out there in the
snow no we were in the snow we were we
were at we on the street oh
yeah we were in the street yeah not in
the snow well since you girls are
walking so slow I'll check out this
house good I'm going straight for this
car murky water I'm assuming no you
probably got a decent amount of XP too
kiaha for our our adventure I'm not sure
I wasn't paying attention did I get any
XP chat it was
1,000 for killing that wolf really I
hope I got some I feel like even if
you're in a party when you're not
participating in the battle or you're
not even close then I don't think I
don't think think
oh can I be sneaky playing scary music
again it's daytime what is there to be
why is it playing scary music I know
only got beautiful birds disguise wow
broken legs
mhm you look like a zombie Bei just
walking I'm so shambling cucumber when
you see a zombie in the distance and it
starts hitting a tree there's a lot of
money all right I got I I killed one
zombie in that house and I got 300 coins
from that really damn that Zombie's Rich
that was the only person in there
wow now I'm walking slow
too I mean how bad is
sprinting it just makes it go back up
what happens I'm going to hover over
splinted
leg oh your max health is lowered by
13.5 so we keep sprinting we are missing
13 Health well I'm still at 100
yeah it's not too bad Rich
zombie all that money is not going to
help you after your zombie what are you
going to
buy do you notice how we spawned in like
completely naked with no belongings
isn't that weird that is weird what were
we doing before the
apocalypse don't ask questions you don't
want the answer to I think this is
protagonist syndrome
protagonists always kind of start like
that don't they it's mysterious but you
know scientists are still doing studies
about it and just not figuring it out
yet but they're getting there we're
slowly Gathering more information I have
caught up to you oh
no Grace We're next to gra more minutes
this is so cute you two seem like like
two old married like 90-year-old people
who are taking a a really slow hike a
really slow hike should we visit gra no
we're we're
cumbered we're
cucumber although I would love to check
find Salvation there I do wonder if the
Boors respawned oh I killed a few so
they might not have respawned but the
big one probably big oh yeah the big one
is down
there oh not I did not try touching it I
just
left that is quite the
cliff we're just making our way one step
at a time why is there a cliff when I
have a broken leg you're rude consider
it may maybe somebody did a digging
Quest right here and they just couldn't
find
it looks like it dig up a home Mountain
yeah just can't I can't believe it's
like 30 minutes of real lifetime I know
you don't heal it two hours of real
lifetime will you now maybe rethink your
choices and regret your actions and
learn I'm happy we killed that it was so
worth
it it made me feel really accomplished
like I achieve something yeah I think I
would do it again if I saw one I'm
shooting me too I'm punching next time
maybe I'll help you so that you don't
have to suffer so
much oh wait wait you have some shot
some some sh some 7.62 or whatever for
me right maybe when you catch up with me
you can give it to
me I have
26 awesome I also got 66 9 mm but you
don't use those oh no
I never find anyone use N I think so
yeah I saw some girls m but I never get
shotgun ammo drops never now where the
shotguns
at crafting
[Music]
skill I know I wanted to make you a nice
shotgun when you came back but I I I
couldn't
I I wanted have a GI for welcome please
Angel we finally have this a workshop 17
days
in well can we minus seven from that 10
days in oh
crafting have you also been reading
Knuckles crafting books or there's
Knuckles crafting yeah for the guess I
should you should I have two
oh thank you oh let's go armor and I got
handgun crafting book this for you thank
you oh F I'll drop you the Furious Fists
books three are exct I awesome thank you
welcome oh I can get new weapons
yeah let me talk to talk to this guy
going
home okay see you home open these three
random crafting
books what do you get and now he's
giving me like good stuff like too much
good
stuff here's two armor crafting goodbye
thank
you I'll also buy one just for
fun he's selling medical
journals get out of oh
do I have
money I have $100 only we have 2,000 at
home
wow
nice um um bad news the fetch Quest is
in our house so hopefully those zombies
don't break our stuff oh no but we can
maybe cancel that Quest and go do a
different one so
easy no that's what I didn't know that
could
happen why would that happen that's no
that's crazy don't it might not be maybe
it's no I li it's the house next to our
house than God I guess it can only
happen at houses that have skulls to
begin with right and ours didn't have a
skull yeah yeah yeah we just have a
random house okay you shocked me gigy
you shocked me you scared
me all right I'm also on my way back I
took a quest by the way just in case we
need one later after
yours okay I have mine too it's a little
far though okay it's always good to have
some Quest it's by that big lake to the
West oh also oh wait the fetch Quest
maybe after the fetch Quest it's so
close then I'll make a workstation after
the fetch Quest
you're still so slow I'm over cucumber
and I have a broken leg and nothing is
going right wait what's wrong what's
wrong I don't know let's talk about it
scary about this cruel world is it your
midlife
crisis I just don't understand why when
we loot a house and we think we're doing
so good that everyone respawns and then
the door gets magically fixed right in
front of us how does you know what would
help you and fulfill you probably
alcohol no
alcohol no no no in our house build your
own office Under the Stairs will that
help me dad will surely fulfill you I
feel like God is Playing Tricks on us
though do I need brass for that we can
we have brass we can use brass we can
cover up the
mistakes it's going to be fine geky it's
going to be F okay I guess I'll build my
own office Under the Stairs yeah when
when you're like sick of our yapping you
can hide there I would never be sick of
your yapping a I'm sick of what God has
done to us oh no we could have had a
beautiful wonderful life without zombies
and starving why did he put us here this
is true but it's a challenge and we we
have to go through it we'll get stronger
out of it we'll be stronger connect
in this world where we don't have to
worry about co-workers and
bosses
and and
offices
coolers the one that we robed and we
don't have to worry about the
HOA
yeah that's true I haven't paid our
water bill in like 17 days wait we're
here now let's let's make the work St
okay do you want to help me gather
things together cuz I forget I can only
remember one thing at a time what do you
need how about four duct
tape do we have that I can make that and
a
Nails we have that's a lot of nails 91
Nails oh wait I have maybe some in my
chest
too I I have five nails so we have 96
Nails wait how many
f h can you make nails almost home I
have one
nail okay then we have 97 out of 100
Nails we're so
close well give me give me the ones you
got for now yeah maybe try tracking the
recipe then it will show up on your
screen
oh amazing you can make nails and Forge
all right
I wait why does the DU collector make
dirty
water oh it wants you to boil it
yourself why is the do
dirty wow yeah I think B has also been
doing that the whole time don't ask
questions God is testing us the acid do
oh no wait cruel where are the
nails they're in the bottom chest bottom
chest thanks I'm just dropping stuff
sorry if I'm putting them all in the
wrong chest oh do you know about the
deposit button yeah but it taking my
five billion
Stone stop taking my five billion
Stones I do need my five billion Stones
uh what else uh this
[Music]
and I need a few more of
those weird these ones okay
four duct tape four Nails
more we're so close to a workstation oh
my God I'm so
excited it's very
expensive I have an
engine for our car
yeah and the
headlight yeah I've been uh like
collecting some car fings and throwing
them in there because I also have the
vehicle crafting skill relatively High
oops so we can be the first ones with a
car on This Server oo yeah like a
minivan for our family
yes would be so cute how much duct tape
do we need
four okay I will craft
it Yum Yum
Yum I'm sorry I'm very excited wh been
working towards this for a while
[Music]
yeah I need to look up what some people
might be able to make nails oh I already
got Nails I can make them in the Forge
okay I already made them like the forge
can make all kinds of stuff can it make
forged iron yes I've been forging a lot
of iron you have some oh yeah how much
you need um I
need 12 easy take in front of
Forge thank you I'm going to get brass
knuckles so strong what about the duct
tap what about the duct tape oh duct
tape there you
go this is the
moment work table workbench
oh bunch of girls already logged out huh
what did they it's only CI and L up
there
oh I need
food do we have some food for Sho some
food we have
some come and get
some it's so
slow okay which one's the Sorting button
get this one move items to fill
B
hey
[Music]
hey we need to be a little bit more
organized it's hard to find things we
do sorry I'm just working so hard
getting us all the wood that we could
possibly need to start our life
together yeah why are you I saw even
your title says wood why are you so
focused on wood
I just love hitting trees then I would
you a lumberjack
armor oh I am a
beaver cute you
know Timber I have 3,000 wood if you
need any wood that's that's a lot for
sure where did my some more don't
worry where did my workstation
go is it in your inventory
no no where did it
go where where did it
go it was down
here oh
wait did you find it I was looking in
the Forge for the workstation crafting
thing but it was just in the normal
crafting thing in the normal crafting
window oh I'm so
confused I'm so
confused it's like as if you're looking
for your building block in your cooking
pot I would find a block in there in my
cooking pot just got to dig deep
glue let me put some
glue it's it's already been almost 3
hours we're supposed to end it at 4
hours I wish it was
longer even though it's so
late I
know I'm making my iron
Knuckles wait if you're Gathering so
much wood uh yeah wait wait sorry do you
need it for something specific no okay
good I I just like having it good it's
it's useful for the forge cuz I need a
lot of burning
material okay I have 3,700 right now no
no right now it's fine there's still
plenty in there but good good to have
wood at hand
anytime oh
oh oh I can make a
glue baked potato is that
good IRL baked potato is amazing that's
true I would like a baked potato
IRL I wish I could like type when I'm
looking into a crate I wish I could type
in like the name of what I'm looking for
you can't right oh no I just drank the
murky water that's
fine what did I need
again I always forget chat how do I
know pipe
thanks it's always the
pipe did y'all find your supplies what
does she mean what supplies does she
mean I don't know
I guess she's talking to us right oh in
the quest that we did
maybe you mean our
Quest repair there we
go yeah we did do you want to kick us
off the
server yeah you trying to kick us off
right
more
please
done
[Laughter]
yay yay thank you boss why can't I make
a a baked
potato do I not have the skills to make
a baked
potato it's ridiculous oh I don't have
fuel G can you put of your your
wood my sweet
1,000 oh thank you so
much don't worry stand back kitten I
have so much wood you're the
best okay I have to go to an idle
meeting I'll be right back okay okay
g hi I'm going to get more wood your
thumbnail is so cute by the way I know
the person who drew me as a beaver is so
cute it's so cute oh to be a little
Beaver oh I got the
workbench yay this is the Glorious
moment workbench achieve best moment of
my
life oh ah Kiara
sweep no what happened I placed it
wrongly now it will stay here uh oh cool
hey get your hands off of that thank you
so curious what's in there yeah I can
make armor can
I all right oh I'll need a one two armor
crafting kits for every every single
thing I want to make that's crazy I
think I had a couple already acquired
one there must be more
elsewhere like what else would people be
using those
for uh
what
what do some does the old town have any
spare armor crafting
kits I make those
never
mind never mind you got it
AR just got to remember the basics
sometimes um okay armor parts seing kit
duct
tape all right we'll be needing a lot
more duct tape and swing kits
[Music]
nice my leg is going to be healed at six
minutes finally it's been so long glue
and Claw glue
glue GL
glue
cloth I feel like yeah I saw
[Music]
oh one second maybe whenever somebody
wants a specific hi whenever somebody
wants a specific armor they shall
provide me with two armor crafting kits
for each piece they want and then I can
make it hello what's going on
Gamers
hello yeah hello helloo
the work here yeah it has been completed
but uh you should let me craft things
because I have the highest skill um yeah
you're the one that can do it but every
piece of armor needs two armor crafting
kits and then 10 claw frag fragments I
have a couple of these things but barely
enough right now I see especially like
armor crafting kitss and I can make
armor crafting kits but then I would
need uh uh like more duct tape for
example I need a lot more duct tape oh I
see so if you guys have either duct tape
or I think I had some duct tape in my uh
chest in need of duct tape though to
make a baseball bat or just the
armorcraft buy it the armor put in the
Discord server so we know what to give
you and we'll we just put in your box if
you could label it okay you were doing
vehicle too right I have four vehicle
magazines o no ni we can make I see that
um there are some legendary Parts in
here you actually need those to craft
the strongest version of whatever weapon
you have so the strongest version of the
club level six you need one legendary
part and then the basic Club just so you
guys know what that's for I'm going to
make a baseball bat so I don't
necessarily need a legendary Club but
I'm just letting you know that's what
the parts are for
okay yeah oh shotgun weekly let's go
where are you in the house there yeah
take magazines if you need B do you want
to go together to base again to drop our
CRA or do you want yeah I'm going I want
to go to I want to go back to the quest
Quest or not the quest Quest the new
house I want to go the new house I have
oh am I
muted here I hear you hi here yeah I
have uh something for you I think want
this oh you do oh well I give it to you
now that you're here for Where I Leave
oh I am not I am not at the house yet
you can put it in a chest though and
then I'll grab it if you if you it does
says that you right there next to oh no
wait no no sorry that's wor never mind
yeah I'm pretty far but you can put in a
chest or something okay okay what is
it h no it's nothing it's just like a
Knife Guy the magazine
and she's going to shake even harder
people where are you right now I have a
I have some we're at like the the desert
or something coming we're coming to the
the the new house
though I got stuff for you too Kiara
hold
up you in the house oh yes oh good gosh
why is it so hard to control a
bike by the way how does the bike take
damage is it like if you fall or
something no I it's it um it gradually
reduces its durability as you use it so
you're going to have to thing I wanted
to give you I think I don't know thank
you oh no that's awesome helps you I
know you you like I've never taken care
of a bike
before oh wait how do you do that I'll
press
x what was that yeah I hear screams
there's some Screaming people screaming
ladies are coming watch out oh small
raid maybe yeah it looks like a small is
coming oh already I'm
blind yeah there are a lot of them I'm I
use I will help
you I'm go let's do
it hi beibs
hello look at us having a nice romantic
bike ride together yeah in the forest R
together
Canada yeah
on freaking
[Music]
reloading oh yeah do it's a peaceful
peaceful existence in Canada and uh she
just killed
someone so
peaceful yeah the most peaceful o
loot yeah I wonder if these guys drop a
ton of loot I got one
they're not really dropping much at all
except exp which is good drop something
you
fools H behind here yeah hit him c yeah
I got him with the BN stick they out
I'll park my bike next to yours there we
go oh
okay I'll leave it hell un who that lady
looks like she crawls out of t
all right this club is extremely strong
now okay I lock
mine I think I need to go now everyone
so thank you so
much playing thanks for playing byebye
byebye
next okay you made everything respawn so
course all our
loot
yeah byebye everyone see you
byee oh Callie you got a bicycle too
yeah I got a bike and we met the new
Trader how do we still a new Trader oh
yeah yeah she's nicer too as she kisses
you she say that she could kiss you if
you if you um um what is it if you get a
bike and tier 2 quest uh you can talk to
the guy and he'll give you a special
dialogue to say like special Quest and
then he'll give you a quest to visit the
new Trader oh o yeah she's got more
stuff I made a bunch of bandages you're
blocking the uh the entrance may want to
do this Quest FAA yes okay I'm at the
start Point okay should we go a failed
list oh it took too long I'm just
looking do we not have any leather at
home a lever maybe I have to make it
craft one you're so smart but
no I have stuff for you okay here's
vehicle oh leather we do have leather
right um here's rifle thank
you I have 100 leather there you go nice
yes please I'll give it to you in just a
moment I'm I have to run to the old
house really quick to get duct tape I'll
bring my duct tape too okay do you have
a storage uh in here Kiara yes mine's
over here uh in the living room up
ceiling okay I'll just try find it as
long as it's named here here it's not
named okay okay how do you name it I
I'll name it for you oh thank you got
it no problem wow the archiv are doing
archiving Things
ariv o by the way we did um plant the
super
corn yeah yeah it's planted it should be
growing or done growing
hopefully I think I might have messed it
up cuz I punched it and I only got a
couple
seeds it though you get it or not but
you should punch it
Right Punch
yeah I mean you don't seats aren't
guaranteed it's like 50% depending on
your level
probably so punch away as long as it
says it's not
growing for now should we all get into
the same party do you think okay yeah
there's about less than six of us I
think maybe about six you're leader
right now so I think you can do that oh
okay yeah I made a lantern
do we have a crafting table down yet or
no yes yes it's in the kitchen in the
kitchen okay but yeah if you want to
make armor then you should probably
leave it to
me I think I can make weapons with it
too is it scary outside probably it's a
little gloomy it's night time it seems
scary ah she's
running oh wait I was going to put more
ion here oh yes our spiky house spiky
house it's very powerful
very hard to get into for
zombies and
R
ra no sh is already wearing the farmer
outfit as far as I the farmer are you
yeah yeah yeah I'm wearing it good it's
scary in
here here I'm coming I have candles here
I'll put in the mood lighting I can
I can make ammo wait are you girls doing
the fetch Quest right now I I can make
Supply Quest I'm coming over
okay the clear the area Quest oh do I I
the supplies Quest
oh well I'll just go where you are yes
okay I can make I can make all types of
ammo
now really how did you do that put uh I
I have the skill for it I guess
[Music]
oh ammo for
everybody oh
look owie guess you can only put on
surfaces well you didn't start the quest
yet did you no just killing them in here
okay
okay almost
there so
easy I have such a strong Fister on my
side that's right
oops a pumpkins there's some good stuff
in these
cabinets I can make pumpkin
bread pumpkin bread looks so good in the
game that I went out and bought
ingredients to make pumpkin bread in
real
life this is the guy with the it made
you so hungry it did I had to have it in
real life can we come over and have some
that sounds so good
yay send a photo of your pumpkin bread
yeah you guys
s he's
fast oh you're doing a quest I can join
you yeah yeah I see um most of them
there too by the way uh my don't you
have to add everyone to the same party
I'm trying to I sent the
request okay SP and join theirs
whichever works we're in in a quest
right now so you'd have to wait yeah
okay okay I'll just uh join that then
yeah let's merge and Quest together
since I think there's five of us one two
three oh crap I I failed a quest oh it's
cuz we dropped the party I guess yeah
uhoh oh that's fine that's fine that
happen the find our supplies I found
also one Supply not mine so there's a
biker gang in here oh I forgot my bike
I'm already running they're all
upstairs I'm hungry so anywhere I
started
blasting get him oh can you guys add me
to the party me too please oh I think
mid
Quest what you mean our should we
waitting until after this Quest yeah cuz
you guys location as I am okay you're
sker Place yeah yeah oh watch
out a six zombie she's wearing a white
dress red
one hey you too what a pretty lady the
corner there's a courier Satchel here
one of yours oh it might be
mine oh I just got not
mine think mine upstairs I forgot we
were on a quest
again and punching I think there must be
an attic cuz I think mine's
down all right I'll wait for you biibs
okay I'll
coming yeah you still got to get the the
invite
[Music]
anyway is it in here look at you in your
bike I had to walk here just like the
old days I thought you had a bike is
that a I left it oh it's just there I
left by
accident oh okay think already started
oh something went flat in there yeah oh
uh
Sor shipping crate oh mky water nice a
kitty there's a cat picture in here a
different one the same as before a
different
one A orange cat
[Music]
behavior oh New Stone spear
oh okay found
[Music]
mine oh that my God what a cute cat I
know is there an attic there has to be
I'm so upset we can't take the cat
pictures and decorate our houses there
yeah I was going to steal some
lovecraftian
thing I'm not sure if yours is up here
too but in the Attic that where we were
the dead person there's a um oh not the
attic I me sat I meant is there no no
downstairs oh a basement yes sure oh but
I'll check upstairs again maybe yeah
it's like on a really high shelf you
might have missed it oh weren't we
merging since there's like no I think
they already started so we have to do W
for them to finish their
Quest okay there's like a respawn time
when we were trying to do your quest it
made us wait like 2 hours 2 hours in
game yeah that's should we do something
else then besides this
one
um you see have I don't have one oh I
see yours okay yeah I see yours I don't
I have to break it
what where are you just do this one I
have to break the kitchen to get my
Satchel oh you found it yeah found it
yeah we can we can do this one for you
after they finish and then we can merge
yeah okay how about we do yours yours is
like right there and near
Mory oh true we are pretty
close ladies still have the Hat f for
drinking oh yes please let me drink some
here you go nice we can also join you
guys on your quest now we just finished
ours I didn't even put
this can invite you guys have you turned
in the quest to the trader yet no not
yet to do that or else it'll make your
quest I think you gave me your Raider
hat or did you switch how about they
invite us so that way they still have
the
quest oh I want I think that might
affect it I'm
worried
yeah okay we can
wait okay I'm at the Harrison residence
if you want to do your thing just
uh that's my bik i a b it's my bike it's
my pink bike what a cute bike thank you
ah empty hand
[Laughter]
forgot don't look look okay now you can
look I'm watching I'm
watching I'm watching I'm
watching pretty good pretty good pretty
good drive skill yes watch watch me
drift I'm drifting I'm drifting look I'm
drifting wow I'm watching I'm watching
I'm watching I'm drifting around the
course I'm drifting Go she's crazy I'm
so crazy look at that wow she's driving
on the inside yeah she's um uh tracing
Ray Tracy Ray Tracy it's so long she's
not disgracing
us I'm intimidating you just wait I
think you just wait cuz it goes up okay
I my hat no no no wrong
way the green
one you can't wait know you do have I do
have my hair out I should be yeah I know
I was just I no I thought you were
behind G or
so all right let's give back the quest
should we yeah and then we can combine
mhm okay yeah we can head
back well we'll wait to start any Quest
until we combine so that way we can all
do our Quest together yeah yipp I'll
have toas bat ah by the way Kelly did
you like wait was it Lev or
I'm going to go ahead and end it here so
I'll see you guys like next time
byebye see you next
time byebye where did you say you
brought it to Celly it's in the chests
in the new house the ones that aren't
labeled I put leather and duct tape it's
only six duct tape though that's fine a
bunch of leather thank you you're
welcome do we have any food I'm starving
yes where are you um in the forest I I'm
coming to
you I'm inviting you you want a level
five Stone that's funny a
what yes who uses make it who uses Point
44 guns me or I will be using them cuz I
take this Stone ax I have a funny
magazine that if you like magazine go to
the shop with your gun you will get
cheaper prices oh that's so funny yeah
like you're threatening them
silly I'll keep it have magazines for
Kiara and FAA yo magazine stalks are
[Music]
rising Fist and rifle I love
reading reading is good for you reading
and
fisting
yeah mostly fisting but also reading
about fisting it sounds wrong it is a
deep deep science there's so much to
know about I don't think it sounds wrong
you should embrace
it okay I too love reading about fisting
not only the act of fisting but reading
about it watching it I love watching you
f like
heart oh my Lord and the chest inside
the unlabeled ones should have leather
and duct tape duct tape oh nice lots of
leather here's your fisting magazine
thank you waiter waiter more fisting
please okay out I'm getting so
[Music]
smart okay I'm going to go make my nerd
hat my baseball bat looks so strong oh
my gosh I can't wait to kill things with
this melee for the win
and
then I have two skill points huh I don't
remember what the other stuff was that I
wanted got to look it up again
later what was
it ah the preach outfit was a like the
best uh
preacher yeah the preacher the preacher
you have the Hat of that I think yeah
the preacher outfit is the best um
what's not heavy not medium what's that
light armor light armor the best light
armor
set out there
[Music]
so Raider sent for I want maybe like I
don't want to just make stuff on my own
for people and force it onto them they
should tell me what they want screaming
out there we got to deal with
her glad down where is she now
now ra that'll be no more screaming out
of
you there's a bird chasing you watch out
a
bird there's a
bird out here is it the bird that's
screaming I think it's the bird that's
screaming
so
loud the dang Birds put it away from for
now I keep telling them to do so oh oh
there he is
oh okay and gunshot just start shooting
at it Bird's
dead it won't bother us
anymore how do I take back
ah there's my bike
[Music]
okay what you making me yeah I made oh I
made a nerd hat which I will wear I I
feel like I might want to make nerd hats
for everybody because if you wear nerd
hats during the raid you will get so
much
exp we could all use that
tomorrow oh
yeah Oh there's uh shotgun shells and
stuff in the output oh yeah I was making
those ah I accidentally took the 7.6 to2
did you make those for me
yes nice you to nice you're
welcome you're welcome how far am I from
making level threee stuff
chat and how funny do I look
now so fun like nerd look at
me you can see my orange hair at
least oh
nerd am
nerd
wedgie I give you a swirly Kiara yeah oh
you I can't chat not oh
CH chat if you want to see how it looks
like because chat is covering myself
just look at me I don't I look like a
nerd my life today looks like a nerd
right come on it's just like you wait
I'll show you
CH what a inconvenient place to be for
you here can I turn this
no what know what I look like from the
Sid do I have like a ponytail or so
Kelly tell me let me see hold it uh
Ponyta uh let's see yeah you got a
ponytail I got a ponytail long ponytail
kind of bushy looking frazzled like you
don't take care of your
hair you know some days busy studying I
can't find my brush yeah she's reading
up on those
books and like the side of your hair is
like growing out of like the side of
your glasses and like above it it's like
a big bald spot it's kind of weird bald
spot no yeah there is sp I don't believe
it you're messing with me bald bald no
bald bald there's nothing wrong with
being bald bald there's nothing wrong
there's nothing wrong with being bald I
just don't want to be oh Trader is
opening up so let's go give the quest
back we go
yeah Bol to
one day we'll all be bald okay never my
head will be full of hair forever do you
need wood I have 6,000
6,000 that's the max stat
stack 6,000 for my wood you make another
stack yeah I'm making another stack I
think I can solidate my wood now what is
it you need wood just tell
Gigi I have so much wood don't even
worry
worry man that's a lot of wood I heard
if you're wood if you have wood for more
than 6 hours you should see a doctor
good thing you're training doctor doctor
can you see my wood
please guys are freaking
mes my God sweet Jesus Joseph and
Mary nurse nurse I have so much wood can
you count my wood I don't know how
to I'm quitting I'm getting my medical
license revoked I'm turning it back
in when you get fired from I'll practice
so you don't have to look at my
wood um change of topic does the other
trador have like better quests yes yes
that other trador has tier two Quest as
well so the quest you guys got going on
right now that you want to
join is that a tier two yes no oh let's
go finally oh I have I have I have two
tier two uh Quest let's do it then B
would you like a tempered blade
schematic a tempered blade yes okay
might be
good all the Traders will give you the
max tier Quest you're eligible for oh
okay I'll get tier two here too once I'm
there okay all Trader showed here to
okay okay
okay
um what's happening Quest started oh
here do you want armor crafting right
here oh you guys aren't on my party yet
oh yeah one sec one sec
[Music]
um see let me
see uh
fun yes do you have um 200 coins
yes I actually how do you know exactly
how many coins I
have wait did you drop those magazines
for me too oh that was from someone else
oh oh I'm getting all these donations
from these
magazines all right I'm just buying the
last magazine he has now you can go [\h__\h]
yourself oh well thank you sir I'm 42
level 42 armor now nice when can I make
the next tier I
wonder all right I'll uh leave
the group and then I'll uh be open to
being
invited okay how to leave okay me me too
all right I am single and ready to
mingle
okay let's mingle I'll mingle with you
I'm ready to be invited as well yeah I
invited you wait Quest failed is it the
shared Quest you just accepted yeah
it'll come back when you when the person
rejoins the party don't worry all right
all
right okay doing me a
concern oh go I have joined tier two
Quest let's
go please I'm starving thank you you
might need to go accept it in your there
we go go oh I have two workstation
magazines I'll bring them to you kiaha
nice oh we're meeting up anyway aren't
we
yeah towards the quest I'll just go
towards the quest and then which place
are we going towards I don't know
there's one being shown to me follow me
okay I think it's the same I am
following yeah we got to climb a
mountain we can do it
way we just got a Skyrim horse it you
know easy yeah I'm pretty goat like oh
we go clear you're my goat Gigi that's
for sure oh
really you really don't have to make
those
noises you're pretty good at
that not bad
B goats are crazy it makes me happy
nuzzles into your hand and licks your
finger looking for some hay I don't
really know if that's necessary
I'm just emulating goat behavior is that
not what goats do wild yeah you went to
a petting
zoo do something scary um flashes you my
demon goat
eyes I I have passed out onto my back as
goats do out of I begin eating your
liver oh wow they're talking in asteris
asteris asteris beinging with words oh
it's the boore barn
Fields oh
no we gotb this
wait it's on the other side of the
boar thank god let's run it
ladies all right let's go big
[Music]
party
hello we can take them oh the oh B oh
there snakes snake too snakes there's so
many danger
noodle nice don't worry
guys yeah these guys will be easy small
potatoes what's wrong with oh never mind
I got to the angle on it
this is all happening so fast oh ceing
zombies worry not guys I am skinning
this warar while you are
fighting yeah get his goodies
oh there's a lot of falling from the sky
wrecked he's dead they jump so
high I want to fight too but there's no
zombies in my way
yeah is so fast they're lurking they're
lurking about they're falling from the
sky oh hey there's even another ladder
to
climb oh can we get much
higher oh I didn't die I didn't break my
leg I was so
scared crippled again for 2 hours Golem
[Music]
sh shells cooling mesh mod there's some
goodies over here guys if you guys want
this stuff some Amo for Kiara and Vio
let's go yeah I I failed going to where
you were so I'm giving up on that cigars
boo
what cigars boost your strength increase
your butter ability and make you look
like a sexual tyrannosaurus
what that's what it says
what okay I I want to be a sexual
tyranosaurus I learned it tyranosaurus
what even is that I don't
know Tyran
t that is definitely what I
want you sure yeah on the I respect
it huh oh
I want to be that that
person I'm
okay I'm
fine tyranosaurus
SE full of gas for when we get
cars so I'll hold on to him for
now at least I said it for you
guys I muted myself uhoh why because not
everybody has to hear such
things what
things no I'm curious of plays of words
I see I think that's just what the game
was getting at
[Music]
so are we done with this Quest we're
done how is this tier two it was too
easy I agree it was very easy I want to
find the big boar
again you want to fight him again maybe
that wolf again we lose our
Quest the quest in the quest first
quests are are
better do you want to do you want to do
my quest that's like right nearby sure
yes I see it I see it wait maybe I wait
where I'll just go where I'll just
follow
you what's this one also a clear Quest I
believe
so clears are easiest cuz you don't have
to look around forever for things just
kill all the zombies how did I still we
have to turn in our current Quest first
right no it multiple you turn multiple
at the same time just don't die this is
so fun um on my way hopefully I don't
break my leg again I think if you've
cleared the quest and you die you can
still turn it in oh really yeah as long
as you've cleared it I think I don't
know I might be lying I hope so I think
you can it's true as long as you clear
it yeah as long as you clear it
yes no I wasn't lying I was not lying oh
gigy are you joining us yeah okay I'm
head it over okay I'll
[Music]
wait this is a nice
residence I hope the
B are those bors your source of meat
this whole time so you were getting the
bacon from get the
allall I have 16 meat right now I need
another board oh wait that's pretty good
though that's a good handful of
meat okay we let me see let me I think
we're
complete okay we are complete let's
go let's run
it yippe
oh oh just run and start
shooting you just blasted them
oh I have a magazine for you I'm GNA
stand right here while I'm dropping it
this magazine for you thank
you a beautiful
flow you look good I'm sorry ow that was
not my intention looking
ladies me go up I wonder hey hey hey hey
oh right that we're already in
there a sham
sandwich don't eat it it's a
sh I love
sham my tummy is
fine oh there's an upstairs oh
hello let's
go oh she was working out wow
respect when she turned into a zombie
yeah uhoh so all that tells us no
working out working out not good for you
a nerd you found a nerd me I'm sorry I
ended up clipping
you please be nice to my new friend ow
the club the club it hurts this baseball
bat is so
overpowered kind of laggy I can make
iron tools now
we did
it Hunter's Journal Barrel exender I
want these gloves I'm taking them from
me what gloves pill sealed shipping
crate no uh here's some
shotgun stuff on shotgun
shells yeah there's GG do you also use
shotgun yeah but I am using my bow
mostly right now so if you have a good
shotgun you can take
it okay
M thank you there's um what did I find
here oh I have some bullets for Kiara
here go thank you some what what does
anyone use knife magazines I do I use
knife
you're thank you let's and here
Sledgehammer if someone wants to use the
sledgehammer cooking magazine oh I do I
do
Hammer I do the hammering in this
househ what what whe revolvers right B
yes I will be using revolvers later okay
I'll leave these for you thank you your
chotic I'll put it in our home later
okay good job team that's it a it's so
fast when we're a big group it
is it's good we all get the reward not
fighting for my
life they I like I like steamrolling
enemies cool nice house is this good to
drink sip sip let's see really
nice well it is it is not good it is not
[Music]
clean see you're drink water do you need
my hat what it's too late for me I lost
I'm going to get I'm going to get bab
diarhea do you need do you need tea I
have tea oh there's more toies here I
want hungry
sandwi oh wa I have F oh no oh thank you
Kelly I love how you just come in from
the
side this guy looks like he's an
Outlast yeah guys look like he's going
to
explode G
me okay fun
yeah let's return the quest tra yeah
okay go turn in some
quests good job team good job job good
job team no
casualties I feel like we could take the
boore we could probably yeah I mean we
we finished the quest now so you want to
take the board let's take the
board all right we've definitely leveled
up a lot since then thanks to the raid
and we have stronger weapons partially
and more
people
yeah if we go in all at
once yeah I guess we could be
strategical about
it oh wait this we just hit each other
until something happens we can all hit
each other each other wait um somehow
we're close to our home I'm just going
to drop off some things really quickly
cuz I'm cucumber me too
cucumber I have so much stuff in my
inventory oh you're here already same
fault yes cooking magazine in magazine
chest thank
you should I just learn all these is
anybody using hey chefs you guys making
anything delicious for us or yes you
know how to make the
hobo Hess Ste you really want that hobo
Ste huh how to make hobo Ste
one day we'll we'll get we'll get
experience a delicious pumpkin pie see
that's what I'm talking about fauna
makes the best pumpkin pie in this land
the most
delicious oh I'm going to get you home
cooking
weekly thank
[Music]
you oh I can I can get a bicycle now oh
yes join the bike gang yay so now we can
go meet the
girl I want a bike me too oh I got to go
to the quest to give it back he do you
have to give back the other quests at
the like right uh Quest person or can we
give back both at the same
person
bicycle I'm going to go back Quest
I will
get if you girls are going to the board
let me know okay I'm going home first
okay step by step
very why is there a hole
outside who dug this yeah that's kind of
not very nice for them to do that my
bike keeps getting locked in there I
just want to check the video again that
I watched to see what armor combination
was best again there was this video and
they said those two hats the nerd hat
for the raids and the Assassin hat for
like everyday life but the rest I don't
remember I want just look it up again
the whole like set combos they are
apparently not as good like there's no
point in wearing a full set apparently
and otherwise like if you don't know
much about everything then you'll just
go for that and you'll probably be happy
enough but yeah now that I'm the armor
person I kind of want to mmax that at
least for myself
no there there's set bonuses but
apparently they're not even that
good so yeah I want to look that
up behind you oh sorry sorry sorry I was
muted I was like talking to my
chat what's what's going on problem I
feel like my server is lagging or is it
oh maybe I have armored mags for you oh
thank you the beep is just endlessly
running for me oh I'm in the I'm in the
Traer
yeah but you're like running on the spot
oh I don't know
why did you buy those for me
fa um I got them as a reward gave them
okay okay okay I don't have wait
actually I do have money now you gave a
lot for that
one uh does anybody use like uh bows
even nowadays in our I think you do yeah
I think and Cecilia also do I believe
and sh I'm also going to drop some
magazines by your oh but is this
magazine Chad is this a magazine that
you only learn once and then that's it
because this doesn't seem like
a yeah yeah okay then I wonder if she
had this before so if it's a one time
thing I know I'll take it for now oh
wait oh another one
whoa burning sh use the
bike uh you have to you can't place it
in here you have to leave the the Traer
area and then you can just place it down
and then press e to ride it and then
hold e to pick it back up again oh oh
I'm in the
hole I immedately went into the hole
watch out for the
hole oh dear I think that's someone is
doing this to us on purpose I want them
arrested whoever dug that hole of a
bike the bike the world is my PR x x to
ding ding
X I didn't see the bicycle I got a
bicycle
too special jobs he gives special jobs
now yeah that's the trader that's the
trader Quest the
Trad I urge you all to accept
oh let me go we can meet her
like okay I can show you where she is
yes please I wonder everybody accepts
the special job we can go she would have
a different stock for magazines I
suppose yeah she has a different Stu
than the guy such Scholars here how to
put down big readers
ouch my bicycle is red no now it's green
ah oh oh never mind it's but once we
find this new Trader maybe we want to
get a new house closer to the new Trader
yeah
maybe you can see me now you can see my
hat oh it's so
cute all right uh are we all going to
the trader gen yeah yeah uh I thought
that'd be cool which
direction that way south east right yep
only about a kilometer
away with my my propeller hat and the
bicycle I feel like I can take off
anytime fly nerd I'm a
helicopter this is the only helicopter
we're going to be able this
game truly no we'll be we'll be able to
get a helicopter after by the end of
this we'll be a take off in the sky yeah
yeah shoot them from the helicopter
now there's a supply
drop oh I hear it I hear it I hear it a
PL me
away I'm going for it okay let us know
what's in it wait it's in the scary
Forest I'm still going for it oh the
trader the trader is in the scary Forest
anyway oh
yeah yep the supply crates are kind of
underwhelming though I'm not going to
lie there's not a lot of great stuff in
there maybe they get better also
depending on how far we are with the
raids I hope so after each stage maybe
better drop I hope fingers
crossed who are these Supply crates from
anyway yeah um Trader Jen doing it for
us cuz she wants to kiss us so bad
there's a oh she did want to kiss me
earlier I'm on my way to watch you oh
there's a big hole I'll give you back up
there is a big
hole Yeah I don't know where it's going
to drop you think it'll drop in the hole
no it it it disappear from the map did
you collect it no no it's coming down
how it is is going in the hole coming
straight in the hole it's coming in the
hole what's in
there first shotgun shells that's all I
wanted there's a baked potato there's
if you want to take the
magazines I'll take the
coffee what kind of magazines let's
let's open these and see what magazines
it has um it has handgun and armor
crafting assault rifle and workstation o
workstation for C oh yes I need both
armor and I'll bring those to you thank
you is the trader lady like on a weird
path up a mountain
yes oh yeah you got to take a swirly a a
swirly path yeah I'm on it right now
it's not hard though it's
fun I'm on my way over to her Duty
witch wait that sounds familiar Dy wit
why is that um I'm going to her house by
accident is this a dead
end what does Judy want from you I don't
know it's kind of
ominous does it go last name witch do
you think that means something that's
why it's
ominous it does the swirly Road go down
again weirdly like yeah it doesn't go
straight it's a bit up in the mountains
this is
confusing yeah that's why we need a
helicopter am I going back helicopter
helic Miss where's a
snake oh you guys should have seen we
went to go find B treasure and then it
was we went into a snow place and
everything was super overleveled M yeah
and we died a million times I can
imagine I mean they probably saw the
messages of B died Callie died B
died it was intense it was crazy oh oh
I'm tracking the wrong
Quest oh here how do you can you change
which Quest you're girl you're tracking
you can you can uh set a wayo with right
click oh
fast what is this
path yeah it circles through the
mountains a bit but then afterward I
just went down very steep I just kind of
mountain goed it all the way down they
could totally place a
a roller coaster here this is
perfect place it is very
swirly I think
I did I make
it goting our way up here yeah we could
do that or we could take the biking path
there is
one I got lot my legs are not strong
enough to bike up here my C pedal pedal
work those I'm trying working harder I
am a mountain
they need to put down some signs I keep
on taking the wrong
turns but now I think I got
it yeah it's just a little confusing
yeah I went the total wrong way but I'm
on my way now you got this we should
have gone together I know yeah I could
have showed you guys the way sorry about
that got distracted by the air drop air
drop what six shotgun shells woo
I'm almost there on my bike wait how do
you get off a bike
e e and if I leave my bike somewhere
does it ever despawn or so uh so hold e
and drag to the hand symbol to pick it
up into your inventory
okay H okay
noise
wow oh lovely in here you made it here
hi hi you made it just in time it's a
church oh so you took the bike path and
you're already there you're so fast yeah
I'm on the mountain get lost two times
easy just jump
down just down the degree incline W
closeup of her upper body okay didn't
need that that's what I said you just
you just like have a front view over
chair
[Music]
your health is my
priority now I'm motivated to get there
fast I got to see this she's spting with
me she was like glad to see her face
oh is G but I want her to FL with
me we
like 15 more minutes before today's
shift ends I'm so
sad it's fun isn't it it's so fun maybe
it would be good to accept some quests
she has so that I don't have to come
here all the time I guess no never mind
we got two tier two quests at the other
guy too
still yeah we he only gives you one
Quest at a time okay I think I'll
bicycle my way home so that I can maybe
in the last minute let's figure out
where to put my skill points and if I
can make one more armor piece
sure sounds good shees I'm going to head
off for tonight thanks for playing guys
yeah thank
you thank you same time Tom I guess yeah
same time I think okay okay and then we
have the raid too so we'll have to get
ready for that the the raid's going to
happen like pretty early right cuz it's
already day whatever
mhm yeah it's on the 21st just get ready
or three hours I think yeah we can play
a little after though so it's
fine yes I want
to let's do it for sure okay see you
later have fun thank you so much byebye
bye bye take care of yourself oh she's
already
gone I may have taken the wrong way
again I'm in the mountains
oh no are you biking through the
mountain I'm biking through the
mountains are you biking directly up the
mountain wait kiaha is here no not
directly up if you see you see me
uh if
you go that way here around here right
side then you should you should get
there wait where did you go gosh I think
I'm going up the
mountain
legs is that
GG no I don't know how to get out of
here I can get down here I can climb
this is it necessary to go through the
mountain no seems very difficult she has
a really nice
place
yeah she does how do you repair your
bike uh use
a she's a little did did you destroy it
no I just fell down the mountain oh yeah
you just need to repair up repair
okay she s
some boobs when was night 14 uh we
missed it chat we missed
it it happened while we were all gone
but that's
[Music]
okay people probably keep on coming into
our streams like and they missed the
beginning where we explained what
happened and they'll be like what did I
miss like did I sleep through it what
happened I must have
did you guys take a Quest from her no I
didn't I should have you can um it'll
just
one oh you want me to help you with your
leg oh my leg is okay right now my bike
is not very okay she'll be fine
though don't worry I'll go up the
mountain again and
then well I don't think you need to go
up the mountain to I think you should
just say
it what is this view of her I don't even
see her face you don't see her face you
just you just stare right into the good
it's a very welcome
bug I don't think I don't think it's a
bug I think it's
intend an intended view learn an
Elixir
okay m D do you know what video I was
watching actually let me I have it in my
history the quest I got so close I don't
know if I want to do it
though how long I can I can do it if you
want I can do it too where are
you
Northeast it's the tier 2 Clear G right
wait yeah yeah going to do a
quest yeah let me go
where it's one tier two GG okay I'm
going to try to get there
ASAP is it up the mountain or no no it's
not out the mountain
okay don't break your legs that way I I
helpes we I don't have to like end
exactly at the 4H hour mark right cuz I
just want to spend some time looking at
my skill points no just don't AFK for
seven hours yeah yeah I will
not I'm just picking up stuff on the way
there's a lot of zomes on the way okay I
need Commando Bo and NAD chest
yeah oh M oats brother may I have some
oats zoom zoom
zoom this place is scary I know who
lives here dead people so scary that
dead people live
here oh we have two quests do we we have
a lot there's like three around next to
each other whose Quest is this one it's
two of mine okay we can do all three of
these actually oh okay we're fast yeah
I'm almost there okay
BS I am really
thirsty is there
a here take my coffee thank you does all
on your
bike
huh be dying right
now 250 M almost
there please
wait no problem um Wawa is on the
way soon I'm there oh the signs are
telling me to go
slow ignore them it's an apocalypse
who's going to enforce them this looks
like Fallout New Vegas it does look like
New
Vegas I can't believe with gy and me
we're all playing New Vegas
yeah funny danger noodles okay I I am so
here oh yeah two I have I have stuff for
you me too I have lots of stuff what all
for me yeah it's Christmas dye orange
dye watch out there's a zombie W you can
dye your bike or whatever else you want
I will dye my
cloes yo so many magazines you guys are
amazing it is good that the whole server
knows what magazin all of that you want
this knife thing oh I would like a knife
thing thank you scary scary welcome
snake o for
Gore
yes oh I have armor magazines
too you guys love me too much hammers or
explosives Sledgehammer thingies I do I
do okay there you go yes yes yes
yes
lovely I love how you girls keep on
getting magazines that I
need okay what's up hello
baddies eating a can of pears just
starts blasting
everywhere oh I buy Stu here all right
let's help out a little
bit I will help by opening
things oh we just started
blasting I will regret this but I will
go
upstairs well I'm behind you oh there's
another upstairs
too in here I
ow oh she's got yellow eyes mhm orange
eyes
spicy it's getting spicier here in this
area things are getting a little bit
more difficult dangerous
[Music]
danger that's good I was kind of getting
sick of all the same places yeah it was
too
easy sorry guys am I giving you guys
motion sickness
is
upstairs there's a
box oh a forge
ahead let's
go more more more magazines here you
go M yummy yummy books I amako I like to
eat
books oh there's some here
hello ah he's so fast he's on fire wao
Sauron is this
you or is this one of his babies
yay we still haven't finished what's
left there there's more somewhere maybe
oh there's more
un
un on the roof yeah all the way up here
dangerous dangerous dangerous
careful don't fall
how do I get up
here
un
un is still not Co did he not die from
the fall he did not he was
chilling
damn good job level 1
woo Commando outfit excuse me what
outfit outfit oh that's I think a pretty
good
one
Yeah medium armor oh no but you my
little pretty lady will get a heavy
armor
set oh I use uh
medium I don't know that's or not but
there's many different medium
ones do you have any cool armor right
now B boo I just have
the scavenger outfit right now you can
try this craft something
better my armor is critically broken
right now uhoh uhoh it's getting a
little bit
yubby well wait do you have a good good
outfit not yet one day I'll hit these
arrows okay I'll just wear it for now
and then once I got the one I really
want I'll put this back into the armor
chest and somebody else can have
it okay thank you thank you oh I have
ammo for you does anybody use assault
rifle uh no I use machine gun okay waa
ammo for you over here where are you
where are you FAA
F where are you
oh behind you huh I'm jumping up and
down we got to do like hot hot cold
cold oh oh thank you oh what is that
armor parts ah armor parts that's smart
that's what I need too all right second
Quest okay let's go this one harder
right this is fast got to find an item
it'll be so much easier but everybody's
got their own item again breathing
spikes oh god oh oh it's
do behind us oh they're twins w
I feel like we're bullying them uhoh
there's a cop in
[Music]
here wow juicy how does he have so much
range boom head theama goes
crazy is this a developer
himself yeah who is this guy
painting oh blue babies I'm not sure if
this is one of the developers
though
hello they're I think they're in the
closets and yeah yeah behind the door
okay okay
okay oh
whoa
reloading I think I accidentally stabbed
you my
di I think you did accidentally stab her
you you killed me it's okay I was
bleeding as a any no no no no no no no
not not
purposefully uhoh oh wait I failed the
quest then no oh I think I did too it's
okay no but the other one's still there
guys you guys are still okay so keep
going I'm feeling
hot cloes apparently you feel
hot it says You must find a shelter
where am I going this
way Arizona
baby is this does this all look like
this because of forest fires I think so
unless the zombie apocalypse did
something what did I
everyone's dying now what did I what did
I
die it's the spikes it's the spikes Why
didn't it make
noise I didn't hear it
spikes but that was mine right I found
survivor's guilt now don't feel guilty
get that reward get that bread also
there's two up
here oh cute
I
may home
upstairs maybe that would have been my
career
Satchel whoa gy I thought you were a
zombie but like a really pretty one
watch out for this [\h__\h] I'll protect you
I'm a Zombie coming back to life Quest
Limit Oh yeah you DA's uh Quest have a
daily limit oh
oh so I guess we can go back to give
back the
quest right I think is it are we are we
done in
here there loot here
yeah I have a medical
journal oh I I have some ammo for you
Kiara and oh I got a brawling for fun o
thank you oh we forgot
this so scary oh here you go there you
go thank you oh my goodness
sick oh I can drink beer
now don't do
it but it helps me punch better did you
go go into the attic and found crates
yes okay okay okay good
good oh now you can you can be like
drunken fist you know like the kung fu
people drunken
fist conf here's the medical journal
thank you some steroids thank oh
wow wow my armor level is at 54
now that's half of the
maximum wait I accidentally got a
medical Journey Journal I dropped it
again I think I can make first aid
bandages
now our second doctor yeah doctor are
you licensed now I am I didn't give up
on my dreams even
though can you please check something
oh what was
it
um yeah let's go back I quickly want to
you know take care of everything make
some shoes and
stuff do we have to talk to the same
Trainor that we got the quest from or oh
wait since since the three of us failed
uh the quest let's do this one right
here that's mine so fail's the last one
that we did
too so we can complete this one maybe
okay
I'm so far I just I bing oh you were
fast huh yeah I just closed my eyes and
started
biking she's in the hurry I'm on my way
back there's a quest here bab yeah I
have a clear Quest
here
what I don't see it I don't either but
I'll see the you don't see the bouncy
exclamation point yeah normally we would
see it sweet maybe we can't do it
together for some
reason hopefully we can maybe maybe we
can't cuz I can't even press f on it ah
it's because we reached the daily Quest
limit is that why no I don't think so
cuz we failed we failed ours so I don't
have a it should say if you have a limit
but do you have at the bottom left do
you have a exclamation mark a red
one no uh
[Music]
uh is that the one that says you're done
with questing FAA do you have it I have
it yeah we're done with questing for
today I don't have it yeah you're not
done oh start no I can't start it I
think it's bug so we can go maybe you
can start it because we're in a group
maybe alone you can do it maybe well I
don't even see it for myself okay so
it's okay let's go
home and end our days slowly
yes I'll probably the quest first go to
the trader yeah I follow you girls I
don't know where to
go I feel like I actually have to learn
the maps
now like before I just run around but
now there's like roads and terrain we go
we go up this road we go we go down we
go up we go we go up we go up you're
right you're
right C on him what are you
saying and then I started
biking are you saying I was reading the
wrong uh books or did you say are you
saying I should read more of those I was
just reading those cuz people kept on
giving them to me but I thought I don't
use assault rifles but okay I I can make
you
some sorry I was muted to tell you that
yeah no it's not the same thing or is it
is it the same thing oh
it my voice in
there b bike she stole your she stole my
[Music]
bike what about this one did she Chuck
it outside this pink one did she throw
this oh did she did she Chuck it outside
I yeah she might have thrown your bike
out I see a go does this not work
oh I guess that was nice of her to
do
she's yeah just just cuz she's closed
doesn't mean she's heartless
nice we'll figure it out later
chat all right well I guess this is
where I will stop for today okay okay
yeah me
tooe bye bye I will stay in game just to
quickly points and stuff but I won't
stay too long and I will not stay
AFK I will not don't AFK I want level up
to I have a point wait where where's
home where is home byebye that way
byebye
[Music]
byebye boo hello I'm just leveling up as
well it's so hard to think about what
you got to level to but apparently
there's a a way to Res skill you can
reset your skill points but it's kind of
expensive oh you can mhm the trader
sells an item for
it if you really messed up you can buy
it I wonder if sneak is useful we
haven't really been sneaking anywhere it
is if you like raid houses like a little
bit more carefully if you sneak onto the
enemy you do like way more damage and
can kill them way
[Music]
easier Quest failed ah okay that was
geek's
Quest no but if you if you if that's not
your play style then maybe not depends
on what you want to
do stealth
build shared Quest tier one that's that
that's not the one
that I still have the the one
right the one that I didn't
fail can I check that
somewhere and this one this one should
be
fine don't go
backwards ah than you for the gigy raid
the beaver
raid oh it's 6:00 a.m. in my
place it's 6: a.m. good
morning yeah I've been completely
changing my sleep schedule for this
project but it's worth it I'm having
lots of fun yeah it's so fun it's way
more like there's way more stuff in it
than I thought it was going to be like
skills and stuff well I didn't really
know what to expect but this was yeah
great I love how we all like have
different like roles and stuff too yeah
exactly it feels like everybody has a
purpose and they know what to do now and
now at least like we have a we have some
Cooks we have some first aid people we
have me for the armor we have the farmer
shielding we have killing people oh
yeah I just like to kill people and cook
on the side M what a nice lifestyle to
have yeah I don't know if the evening
GST Time s will ever happen at this
point it's kind of like I would normally
join it but then you know when
everybody's in the na times lot it
just it didn't happen last night right
or this yeah it was cancelled because it
seemed like not enough people are were
like interested what's with these
trees
what trees
laugh at those oh like I I I am finding
an
unusual wall of trees in front of my
house that was never there
before and I was just like this is like
I'm snowed in but it's like treed
in but apparently they were planted by
gigy okay nature is healing nature is
healing this is some kind of
fortification
all right a there's trees in the
house what that's a lot she loves trees
she's such a
beaver okay do I even have enough kits
for what I want to
do surely these birds that are following
me won't follow me all the way back
right uh no I don't think
so okay um uh track I'm seing kit and
duct tape duct tape please please only
one oh I have to I'm crafting okay okay
[Music]
okay are you doing vehicle too by the
way yes I'm quite far with it too I
think
okay I'll save those for you please
build
motorcycle yeah and then car I'll build
all the cool stuff and then
helicopter although I don't even know do
you build cars and all that also on the
workstation
chat I
wonder what else oh the armor parts hey
welcome welcome in the other home oh my
gosh yeah right Tre trees
everywhere it's so
green what do I need what about here
okay oh yeah all more parts are also
very
useful let's see what did I
say I need
[Music]
Commando boots need forged iron armor
free armor crafting
kids Mama Mia well I can make a couple
here
okay Commando are you still streaming
bio yes okay hello hello people on the
other side hello people on the other
side are you still streaming
yes hello people on the other side hello
we should like this is this kind of
sweet I can talk to your Pebbles you can
talk to kfp hi
kfp they're saying hi hi Pebbles are say
hello hi Pebbles D they give you a colon
d a call and d and the smiley face the
col and D on the typing board ah Co and
D Co coland D col D I don't know what
that words but I know what you're like
you mean the smiley the laughing face
yeah
nuts colon a a double Punk double Punk
is that wait oh how do you say it double
Punk d d Punk yes D Punk D Punk oh
that's cute D
Punk the two dots ah I thought you were
saying some some weird magical word
okay
leather and forged iron leather un for
we have that we have
that oh I have leather here here here oh
it was it in that chest I dropped oh two
it's only two yeah I should have a uh
more it's okay I got plenty in here too
and
then guess for iron is over there I need
to make a chest that has all of these
things that I need for armor stuff cuz
it's usually always the same it
seems where did it go where did it go
guess there's also some in the
Forge it's
not ah I need to make
more but I'm sure we still got some
ah so blind I wish I could just type it
in okay making armor command the boots
yay this will be really nice to have and
they're level three so I can already
make level three armor
ooh and then the other thing I think was
NAD NAD chest and preach can you make
medium armor uh I can make heavy medium
and light all of them and all of them at
seemingly level three now oo nice but I
just need a lot of armor crafting kits
and
stuff okay I'll be on a lookout for
those what's this can I not make
this more cloth
fragments that's where it
is stinky boots
finally exchanged my old
sandals and now those scorpions can't
bite me
anymore cloth cloth cloth cloth clo do
you have any cloth on
you I I have cloth fragment yes yes yes
oh okay
those oh
awesome thank you oh more oh oops that
was mine okay wait I give back where did
did it go oh I got it oh
[Music]
nice we're just in the process of Min
maxing right now yeah we're getting
ready but don't worry won't we won't
stay on for 7 hours no no no
no uh
craft and then maybe no I won't have
enough armor crafting kits
for for the chest piece
yet uh armor armor
crafting I but I can make more I just
need more duct tape and duct tape was
glue
and oh my God so many cloth
fragments oh you can make duct tape okay
here's glue yeah oh the glue I have uh
it's more like the cloth fragments but
I'll I'll take you glue
anyway
go ah thank
you claw fragments why are you so
elusive more elusive than I thought you
would be can I make that too don't think
I can
oh
cotton you make them with cotton that's
not too bad oh there are like cotton
plants everywhere and you can get seed
everywhere
have I ever put them
somewhere I feel like I've picked up
cotton sometimes but got a punch of few
cotton I'm going to do that before I
leave because that shouldn't be too much
it's hard to leave my house now there's
too many trees
here okay cotton cotton where is cotton
when you need
cotton this is something
[Music]
else I should just use my
bicycle if you craft ammo is it just
like one ammo at a time like One
Singular bullet you're cting if so
that's kind of lame um I think you can
like if you have enough ingredients you
can like line line the queue up and it
will craft more I'm pretty sure I
haven't tried crafting ammo before so
I'm not sure
there were some in the chest what cotton
or cloth
fragments let me see if there's any
cotton here though 17 ah in the food box
I had a feeling it would be in the food
box oh well what's
this okay I'll go
back yippe
F should have many clo frag use hidden
curtains oh I should make that my new uh
pas time if you get cloth fragments
easily
then curtain
harvesting radio schematics
what o don't like this
noise curtains and beds are great for
cloth do you need any
more s
622 cuz I can craft it oh I mean how
much do I have right
now oh not immediately but I mean
tomorrow for the rage maybe am I the
only one using the machine gun I think
so huh okay well right now it's not that
important I think okay I'll hold off on
making bullets until we meet it yeah you
can save your materials cuz I'm sure we
do collect a lot
yeah okay yeah
cotton cotton how much cotton for one oh
just one okay I am prepared now so I'm
going to head off byebye byebye see you
tomorrow bye PE see you tomorrow for the
for the rager for the horse let's be
ready
byebye
byebye I'll use it all up okay now it's
is only me
left I will just finish my outfit and
then I will be
satisfied this is trash can I oh oh wait
I can scrap it oh you get grass cuz I
made it with grass I'm so
hungry I had Burger King before the
stream it was not very satisfying
I forgot I had a mod on
here take it
back
complete
scrap or should I have not scrapped that
was that okay I think it was okay we
don't need that armor anymore and then
my where where's my where's my claw
fragment is it all
finished learn the fire what I have to
learn it
ah I'm so stupid I thought it was just
like
apply so it's for the sledgehammer only
for the like just for like I guess close
combat stuff wait oh I just learned it
so I can make it now I
guess wait the dye can I use the dye on
my body part when I make my body
part for anything with a shaft uhhuh the
flashlight yeah the flashlight oh I have
to learn that too
oh schematics are to
learn o so will that be on my
workstation or here flash
light ah this icon I guess tells me I
can only build it
there oh that's not so bad I think I can
make that I was just thinking like
currently doesn't feel like I would need
it oh 4:00
a.m. but um
maybe oh I was collecting that for the
duct tape right
um uh what was I saying maybe like later
maybe will be in situations where it's
really dark and I might need the
flashlight I don't
know fire sled flashlight no the
flashlight would go onto the machine gun
I would
think okay take and then what was it um
keep on forgetting let me
check uh
Nomad chest I think it's the last thing
I'm making oh yeah The Nomad
outfit ah
wait can
I I need two
more okay I can actually make one more
even damn this is really really
difficult to get even the simplest
things but it's good that there's always
a good use for even the simple things I
had a feeling in the beginning of the
game that even these simple things you
want to collect it all and now now it's
like ah don't have enough of
anything many steps of crafting yeah
right
okay uh I'm missing one forged iron
okay there we
go I'm doing it level threee Nomad
outfit that's pretty that's pretty
pretty
awesome
so um can I put this on something by the
way armor rating plus two so from three
to five would would that is that what
would
happen where did it go
here can I modify
that oh it doesn't work here is it only
on specific parts
can I Dy
it
that's that just looks like someone put
orange over the whole thing in Photoshop
and used a specific filter
mode doesn't look so pretty but okay
wait I'm so confused I want to see what
it looks like so this can somebody can
somebody else can wear that now wait
it's not orange I ah maybe it only shows
up like for other people but like in
this window though it doesn't it's not
viewable maybe maybe if I go on a
bicycle uh what else am I wearing
everything okay so now I
have
um carrying capacity Plus free stamina
Mobil Mobility noise incre okay I'm I'm
pretty loud and stuff but Undead damage
plus 30% that is like pretty
good and then
and what was the good thing about this
outfit I don't even know but I just
believe what they say and then everyday
life I'll be wearing this for loot bonus
or this for exp whatever I prefer in the
moment yeah Undead is like 90% of the
enemy who's not Undead I don't maybe V
bors I don't know H yeah run speed a
little bit faster Mobility no I don't
know I don't know why this is so good
but apparently this is a good
combo ah snakes Bears yeah true and then
so before I go I wanted to look at my
skilles I just can't focus enough when
there's people around and I just want to
ask you guys cuz although I looked at a
video too like what skills are
recommendable in the beginning um but I
already
forgot uh I don't
know oh
no do I have to deal with that now
do
I I think I have to deal that now where
are they I hear them but they're hard to
see I just want to look at my
exp what are you doing here oh
reload wa I'm alone on the server right
now please go easy on
me can you believe was AFK for freaking
7 hours but I feel like she may have not
really properly died if she was standing
on that car the whole time or did she N
I guess they could get get up on the
car cuz it's um it might be two levels
High two blocks high where she was
standing but there was like it was still
accessible uh I hear something still Oh
Oh I thought it was over of course not
I want to save on
ammo ah
please hot lady
incoming don't know why I scream so hard
just
now you dead okay are we done now
no I think
I think maybe we're done we're done can
I look at my skills now thank you I just
want to look at my skills and log out
cuz I can't focus when people are like
and I and everybody's like doing
stuff uh everybody's like doing quests
and running around and I'm like oh God I
got to I got to keep up but I got to
look at my skills for a
moment um okay I can't forget about the
fact that there's like these basic
skills up here too what what what should
I do what should I do
nothing here right um continue to defy
gravity and keep standing deal 220% head
shot damage and have 15% chance to
dismember with fists and machine
guns focus on a strength tree you're
using strength weapon you mean the
sledgehammer I only use it when I have
no ammo or when I want to save on ammo
but
deal shotguns Club sledg tools but no
what about what about
my let me see if there's something else
interesting uh clubs no sled him oh wait
this is ah how do you ever get this one
do I just have to wait to be a high
level fortitude for machine guns
fortitude just this General one oh I
think I hear zombies still what the [\h__\h]
hello oh maybe we're
fine oh that's a vulture I think can I
just stay
inside uh oh
God will they destroy the house ah oh my
God all the
sadles the TV
ladies I saw you on TV
okay okay stop now please stop stop it's
early in the morning drink some coffee
and
chill please where are we I can't
focus how about with the lock in the
menu will'll tell you oh okay well
uh well this wouldn't be bad right in
any case one point
here oh I hear sounds [\h__\h] can somebody
take care of these enemies while I'm
looking at my
skills oh this item needs
repairs I think I might just log out I I
might I might
just I can I just log
out I'm looking
bye I just I'm I'll do it tomorrow in
the beginning of the
stream nobody's online now so so nothing
will proceed anymore right I'll think
I'll watch some videos again and think
about what to put my my skill points
into so that I'm ready and just I'll
throw him in quickly in the beginning of
the stream yeah [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] I'm
out I can't focus man keeps on
interrupting me m m Mia give me a
break yeah two days to prepare for the
raid yeah do we have two days I mean
we're probably going to be fine again
if the raid if the house was fine with
just laa standing there and doing
nothing but probably because she was
alone they didn't send as many zombies
but how did she win by doing nothing
it's a it's a mystery to
me
yeah now I thought it wouldn't take so
long if if would if zombies would just
leave me alone I can just put in my
skill points and be left alone but they
kept on interrupting me so I give up I
give up it's just a few minutes that I
wasted this do not do not make me feel
guilty about a few minutes when we
missed a whole
week it's
fine you should be fine day 19 right now
what what
what two days should be enough to prep
oh yeah yeah yeah I think our prep will
be fine fine we're all becoming much
stronger too and the fortification still
stands it doesn't seem like
anything's like
gone yeah and we didn't even go all out
last time I think there were still some
people chilling
inside and I mean we didn't even have to
go outside at that point we could have
just waited it out with the we just went
out there for
fun now we will maybe go out for
not so much fun but more for actually
protecting you know be a little bit more
serious we'll see we'll see but we
didn't have to go outside yeah and for
exp and
loot spikes I I know i' I found out
there's a
trait that if enemies are killed by just
spikes they will still even it was
either about loot or about
exp I think
exp that you will still gain exp if they
die by spikes but I don't know what that
um is it one of those magazines the
onetime read
magazines that give you that oh it's an
intellect perk oh okay so not a
magazine armchair farming yeah that
would be so sick imagine just sitting
back and letting it all happen I mean in
the end maybe that's not the best
entertainment in terms of streaming and
and going out there and fighting
yourself is of course funnier but I do
think there's a certain aspect of
funniness to it if we can just sit back
to that that was funny to me last
night a good mix of everything we just
Flex that we can do
it the car I made yeah uh when how I I
was collecting some carps I I collected
like a wheel before thinking oh I might
need this in the future I wonder how far
I am from making a car or maybe I could
already make one at this point I already
read a bunch of those magazines do you
guys know could I already make
one is it in the
workbench you need four wheel I figured
do I really I mean it would make sense H
the wheels are kind of rare but maybe
you can also make the wheels yourself
watch the video to figure out Vehicles
well maybe I
will you could do a make you could make
up mini bikes oh yeah mini bikes would
be fun for now I guess rather than
cars but now everybody's getting
bicycles you know like let them have
some fun with their bicycles
first mini bikes are unlocked oh okay to
craft a car you need level 75 oh okay I
think I'm pretty far from that
still a I think I'm still under 50 with
cars I'm over 50 with armor I think
that's pretty crazy at what level can
you make legendary armor cuz I did see
that you can make legendary armor I
think it was like level seven was
legendary and right now I'm making level
three
armor oh I got to I got to hit 100
exactly
100 okay well I'm not that far off
anymore especially with everybody
knowing that I need those
magazines I hope they'll keep on giving
them to me it's like all the time people
are like k k I have something for you I
have something for you I have something
for
you it's like Christmas all the time
wow isn't it wholesome everybody's
giving each other
stuff while like you know we all are
like loot goblins and looting and
looting and Roo and tooting but we still
end up sharing whatever everybody needs
and we share the money too it's really
nice
like rust wasn't like this rust was
wasn't like this because it was PVP
there were some groups that grouped
together but in the end it was PVP so
people didn't share
really I like this game because it
really encourages team play and feels
very rewarding and motivating and yeah
I'm surprised I like it that much I'll
be honest like before the project
started um like when we first had cie
ask us about it I was like okay I'll
sign up for now and see how it goes but
then there were no time slots known yet
but when they were planning to do it and
once once they said that it would be at
3:00 a.m. my time starting and then
maybe end at 7 a.m. my time I was
like I want to drop out but then I was
already on the art that c Commissioned I
guess so then I was
like I don't want to like drop out when
I'm on the art I would feel so bad
so I guess I'll stay and I'll try my
best to be in it but I won't guarantee
that that I'll be in it every day but
then I messed up my sleep schedule for
it anyway and I'm having
fun and they were going to organize like
different time slots that would work
better for me but those for this whole
week of seven days to die it would have
only been on two days and then if I
would have only participated in those
two days then I would have barely
participated so I kind of need to
participate in the na prime time slots
but if I participate in those I'm
already [\h__\h] up my sleep schedule
what's the point in joining the EU time
slots especially if others aren't
joining those either so you know in the
end I'm here and it's fine I I'm I'm I'm
here so I it's not like I could fix my
sleep schedule for one from one day to
another anyway so
I think now I'm going to
be participating every day I was I said
to kfp that I'll be playing Zelda on the
weekend because I'm also really [\h__\h]
addicted to Zelda right now um but I
think I'll continue focusing on this
until it's over because I really
enjoy the bonding that I get to do I I
missed out on GTA because you know I
didn't want to participate in that
because of timing and everything and Ian
Rego I missed out because I had my Moab
recording on some days and you know I
just missed a lot there too so finally
even though it's a shitty time for me I
I get a chance to be with everybody and
have fun with everybody and have some
like rare bonding time with people that
you guys aren't even expecting that I
would bond
with so I want to make the most of it
yeah it feels nice to be like relied on
too I feel like now that I'm you know
doing all the armor stuff I want I want
to be there I also want to be there for
fun honestly I I I I feel like um I want
to be there for
her geky too but I don't know I think
fauna and me were currently kind of
attracting each other um because of
our um feeling of being overwhelmed in
bigger groups like just today when I was
alone in the VC and I was just muted and
and there were people in the other VC
Channel but she chose to be with me Beed
together with
me you
know I think we're
always
like China trying to yeah be loners
together right now
so I don't I I don't want to miss a
day and not be there for her we're just
so dumb like you know she's fine without
me of course but I don't
know if I can be any kind
of you know assistance to her right now
I would love
that cat ladyes strong Clementine family
strong we have some history now in this
game we're family I can't let my family
die alone without
me I may have left them to die in the
mountains in the snowy mountains but
they needed to learn their lesson I was
still mentally
[Music]
there the Clementine
family yes we will hold
together now I've been having a lot of
fun hanging out with
them I did want to hang out with gigy
like for a while uh anyway like in Ian
REO I also was kind of trying to stay
around her because I wanted to interact
more with her cuz I'm really vibing with
her gy geky seems to Vibe with everybody
she's like doing so well I'm such a
proud Senpai she's really really social
and really extroverted
and we don't have so many extroverts in
our
Branch she's very adaptable and very
talkative and Ting and
funny H people love her I love her too
I'm glad people love
her my my orange Gremlin
kohai
yeah an actual extrovert and does she
that's the thing though people call me
an extrovert too and I'm just like
thinking to
myself I'm not but I know why you think
I am no I wonder if G actually
also thinks she's not an extrovert but
people just call her that because she
just knows how to talk to people uh
quite well like especially to introverts
I don't
know yeah relative to
myth or like relative to the rest of our
Branch it's just a
easy to be misunderstood as an
extrovert I'm just really good at
adapting to
social
situations yeah and I hate awkward
silence not going to lie I was kind of
nervous with bioo alone there like she
was I was I she was so quiet and I was
like
uh uh
[Laughter]
I I felt bad cuz I I would love to have
conversation but I'm also trying to be
quick and focus on my on the last tasks
I wanted to do and then get out of there
but she was also focused yeah I was
like cuz I don't really know her as a
quiet person either I was surprised so
that's why I asked are you still
streaming or not because I thought oh
she's so
quiet I don't think I ever heard her
this quiet
before you think it was fine
okay we were we we were both trying to
get our stuff
done uh so yeah okay I'm getting tired
cuz cuz I didn't have a nap today and
it's half past almost 7:00 a.m. actually
but I'm going to go I don't know to the
bakery hit the bakery
o who hit the bakery you know yesterday
I was so lucky cuz after the stream I
don't know what time was it I don't
remember but after the stream I still
had like I made myself a sandwich or
something I had a no I made pasta quick
pasta I made a really quick
pasta uh ended like 6 a.m. so I was
making pasta at like 7:00 a.m. or so and
then was eating it and about to head to
bed or so but at 8:00
a.m. I'm is on
delivery yo perfect timing I would have
been so pissed if that came at like noon
or so while I was sleeping I would have
probably not opened that door I was so
excited
to open the door like welcome Amazon
welcome you are so welcome right now I
am not even in my morning robe no I'm
wearing clothes I mean they are pajamas
but normally when I open the door for
Amazon it's like messy
hair uh eyes are like half
open uh maybe morning robe and I'm like
like pretending to not have just woken
up at 12: noon but they know they can
sense it even when I'm like slapping my
face before I open the door and I smile
and I'm like
hello you know how you know what I mean
you like trying to not seem like you
just woke up but this time I was really
not just woken up even though it was so
early
[Music]
but yeah I'm hungry and tired actually
I'm going to eat something
small and I'm going to remind you guys
before I go you probably have hope maybe
you haven't seen it oh cuz I uploaded it
just before the stream more or less um
the crony dance sh is on my YouTube's
right now oh crony wasn't here today so
sad uh thanks for the Super Chat come on
H and the crony dance is up now it's
it's spicy we're holding hands it's kind
of
illegal yeah it's cute
though and and then we're already on our
best way to the full choreography dance
video that I showed you the screenshot
of the sneak peek um but yeah as I said
I'm I was just you know hoping to
relieve my K-pop brain worms because
these kind of collaboration dance
challenges are very common in the K-pop
world when somebody releases a new song
and they go to these Korean music shows
then there's other artists who just
release a song and they're all promoting
it so they always collaborate by dancing
each other's songs together and putting
it on each other's channels you know and
it's always so interesting to see these
like different groups paired up like oh
my God Le seraphim Sakura is Dancing
with twice's other
know or I don't know wow amazing it's
just brain
breaking so um yeah I was thinking like
within hono people have been doing dance
shorts like mostly alone where the heck
is
saki where the heck is
saki where the heck is sucki
[Music]
I'm an otaku
bestie yeah I was saying um yeah in Holo
like there's been like solo shorts so
far mostly solo dance shorts and and
then you know some girls have been
Distributing motions and stuff to make
it easier for people to do dance covers
but I
thought I'm going to do it differently
I'm going to invite a bunch of girls and
do collaboration dance
shorts that's the spicy stuff oh yeah
I've opened up a Tik Tok I know I know I
feel the same way that most of you do
about Tik Tok I do not like it and I am
overwhelmed I don't even want to look at
my feet I'm so far I'm not looking at my
feet because it's I don't know what the
[\h__\h] is going on I'm not going to follow
anyone besides H life either I
think uh I'm just going to re-upload
whatever I put up on my YouTube shirs
I'm going to put up there um old ones
too probably eventually and I'm just
hoping that the algorithm will strike
you know why not like work on that on
the side and see what
happens yeah I don't know if I'm doing
it right though I don't know if I'm
supposed to do something with the sound
like I'm using the sound directly from
the
video file I don't know if I'm supposed
to like I don't know I don't know how
this works
I need to ask my friend I have a couple
of friends who are into Tik Tok I kept
on calling my friend today like trying
to get her to explain me Tik Tok while
I'm uploading this Tik Tok but she
didn't pick up so I was kind of
lost I guess biu could help me too but I
don't know if she does she even upload
Tik toks like does she have a bi boo Tik
Tok account where she upload
stuff no right she just uses it to watch
stuff and then talk to you guys about it
ask
Ren raden's dance kind of went crazy I
just I don't I just want to know like
the basics even I how to did I do it
right I sound like such a
boomer sound like such a boomer oh my
God yeah if my friend doesn't pick up
the phone I'll ask one of the the Holo
girls but yeah as you can see Oli Martin
Iris KY FAA KOB COI and honestly like I
might make even more after 1
million I might make even
more I'm having
fun
yeah yeah if some more girls want to you
know if some more girls are expressing
their interest these ones I've just
invited them personally um I just you
know some of them are unexpected right I
just felt like H maybe maybe this
combination would be interesting maybe
this combination would be interesting
you
[Music]
know I dedicated Tik Tok man I would
just love somebody to completely take
control over my Tik Tok but for now
because it was a very spontaneous
decision to open up my Tik Tok uh for
now it's just going to be me doing it
laas no I don't know laas
I don't know she's kind of Mia to
me I wonder what she
[Music]
thinks
yeah PMA PMA is a bit of a Zoomer yeah
she might know how to use Tik
Tok but it's okay at the same time I I
feel more relieved if I have control
over it
myself small cookie bear where did you
suggest that I didn't even see it did
you suggest it in her stream in a Super
Chat to her you didn't have to apologize
to me I didn't even know about it thank
you for the red super chat if I ever get
to your super chat with my Super Chat
readings I'll read it properly that
time yeah
um so yeah watch the crowny dance sh and
keep on streaming Mirage on YouTube and
on streaming surfaces if you can if you
want um
yeah W PR
department is
cooking a Yago dance
short I could try to ask but that might
be difficult
like like he's not even modeling
merchandise cloes anymore although that
was really like getting a lot I can
imagine he must be going to the office
each day and they always must be like
hounding him like yagan yan yan please
we need we need uh pictures of of Kaki
beu merchandise uh please please we need
pictures of uh Rin virgin blah blah blah
blah please can you put on this shirt
can you put on these slippers please can
you hold this weird dakim makura or this
opai mouse pad please can you hold this
uh I love fauna hat can you please hold
this or put this pacifier in your mouth
I don't [\h__\h]
know
Pago he has been released of his
duties yeah I would love to like um do
like dance collaborations with like
K-pop girls
but I'm not on their on their level of
Fame they don't know me they don't know
I
exist I wish I could one day yeah maybe
you know if I keep on doing this maybe
eventually for the next or the next next
song or
so I could ask guu if she wants to give
it a
try but guu also kind kind of Mia
somehow haven't been able to reach
[Music]
her mnet debut when I know right please
I'm working my way up there with my k-
up releases one day the capb world will
will see
me as worthy but it's not like only
famous groups are on those music shows
honestly it's not that there's less are
known groups too totally um but I think
what I really need is like a label to
get me those kind of opportunities like
as an indie so to say so to say I am
when it comes to music I'm kind of an
indie I'm just doing like even all of
this if I had a label my label would do
this [\h__\h] for
me yeah
am I really going to push what what do
you mean I'm already doing K-pop style
I'm not pushing for
it but like within kop I'm doing
different genres like Kima is pretty
different from Mirage and I'm already
cooking the next song which is also very
different from Kima and
Mirage didn't tell you yet but I'm
cooking the next song
already yeah
yeah yeah I don't
know when we'll release it though
because yeah things are kind of
complicated right
now I might just like we might just
finish it early and have it lying around
until a good opportunity arises a
sponsored stream this week no it's next
week it's next week
let
me let me
see yeah it's next week
next um Sunday it'll be a shitty time
for me like 6:00
a.m. originally they wanted me to do it
at 4:00 a.m. but at that point of
time uh this seven days to die is over
and I'll be the process of fixing my
sleep schedule so actually I don't know
how the [\h__\h] I'm going to get up at 6:00
a.m. I can't switch it up that ear fast
but I have to
try they it seems like they want to get
like the na Prime Time time slot but
that I don't usually stream at that time
6:00 a.m. is rough but I'll do my
best I'll do my
best Kelly should keep this going I
wouldn't mind but if it's more like a
long time frame it will be difficult
like people will want to play other
things too and then it's like okay on
which days you know but I wouldn't mind
it coming back for season two maybe we
can keep the server and our
characters like I don't know I guess you
can't keep the server running forever if
it's not in use and we have do we have
to pay for it I mean I don't know but
maybe like a month later after first
season and so to say maybe we could do
another one like so far I think
everybody's having a fun time and would
love to do another one too I would love
to do another
one like if it remains if the server
doesn't get like completely closed down
then it will probably
remain yeah I I think like one week get
a time is fine like having it go for a
full month it will be difficult to get
people um log in
consistently you know what I mean like
people will want to play different
things too and then there's only one
person on the server on one
day yeah could you you could invite ID
Girls I'd love to I always love to do
things with ID girls but honestly I
think the like amount of people in our 7
Days to Die group is like a comfortable
amount I don't know maybe it could be a
few more but h
it's like now with the amount of people
we have it's like easy to overview who's
doing what who needs
what stuff like that I still like a good
balance I think
yeah it's so like it's a
family this whole family like we're in
this apocalypse together we're holding
strong
I like
it yeah I don't know what that Forest
game is I wonder what that
is is that
similar by the way this whole time
there's a wa behind me it's kind of
scary it's because I'm still in voice
chat let's get out of
there so scared my head hurts all right
I should go um tomorrow same
[Music]
time stream Mir rage thanks for
watching is that it is that all I have
to
say
yeah what day is it Saturday now well I
mean I played for the night it's really
just Friday but then again then again it
the Saturday it's both Friday and
Saturday in my mind
damn
okay okay thank you for watching have a
nice evening night day whatever uh
Europe gang if you stayed up with me big
U you crazy
noodles uh if you're SCA gang have a
nice day guess you stayed up too for me
huh did you well you woke up early for
me if you're na
gang have a nice
night good night have a good
dinner
yeah love you
guys see I'm getting behind on super
chats again cuz there's no way I'm
reading super chats at 7
A.M we we we'll get there guys we'll get
there bye-bye byebye bye-bye J say a
Fe yes yes
yes C yes yes yes
yes H
sleepy oh sleepy sleepy
sleepy oh I think today or tomorrow
might be the last day for the myth
anniversary group
merchandise just saying as a
[Music]
reminder oh in two days
again thank you for the support
[Music]
you saw me on a Mir I told you
walk to do with this
[Music]