sing out boldly again continuing this
Odyssey we'll start this new refrain
raming with memories and when the cloud
of Skies become bright let's be
night ready baby I would say today's
broadcast on slight delay out the stuff
is really enough Stu I'm buffering
endlessly well take it easy what do we
learn start a fire in their hearts on
the PC burn optimistic focus on a quick
fix teach new dogs alliv her old trips
still going stronger than ever and never
say you die and I'm aware it's their
running through where the freaking lie
dreamers to streamers to entertainers to
I'm not losing to you young people it's
a mid crisis spanning New Dimensions we
can bring another mystery to R planning
our Ascension dancing in FL we
join us while we're celebrating in the
myth that we're creating there's another
story waiting through this world and
beyond our distant dreams have brought
us here a strong unyielding Bond guiding
us endlessly will bring us moment back
we hold dear Time Rushes on and no these
winds may scatter us we'll keep this
promise when the moments finally ride
we'll always find the way to reun now
I'm ding again now it's time to sink or
swim let's try the deeper R could you
hold my f vibing with everyone let's and
Ponder pun tat them have fun nobody
escapes death and I know that it's more
that is coming go I'll still pretend I
got this killing thing sort of listen I
want to look cool but I keep on tripping
and falling guess I'll keep playing the
fool to hold up the calling you
countless leted us to this day Triumph
and sorrow hope for tomorrow we'll
always find our way
Come
in every Universe we were always meant
to
meet a lead bound this search we will
never know
defeat my wings will guide your hands as
the faithful base go by we will C the
path for NeverEnding
Sky drawing us together I can sense
another wish is coming true each typhoon
we weather strengthens our crew me and
you sing that again the cloud and skies
give way to clear we'll start this new
refrain briming with memories another
story starting right
here keep forging ahead to make us s all
a home whichever fast we tread steadily
journeying we know we're never really
alone if we believe wherever F may find
us our love will find us every epic
chapter we might will set us on the path
to
reunite
a