[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
assistant
business ES
[Music]
foreign
guys I
I have to use the bugged app today
because my movements are completely
inverted and it's really confusing but I
guess for you guys it might not make too
much difference if I'm just playing a
game
um yeah but because I need to use the
accessories and the one that is not
bugged uh the accessories don't work
um we have like you know two different
ones and one you can put pngs on and any
other one you can't
uh yeah
I know it's weird but yeah why are you
in trash I'm hiding
I'm hiding no I cleaned the dumpster I
cleaned it
for this purpose
so much
I love these assets thank you to my
beloved creative fans
um so the thumbnail once again Christina
matzanita drew me as a thief thank you
and then my other assets I used last
time as well are from blue and then this
dumpster is from Skye right yeah yeah
thank you I love it so much
quinoa of the trash bin what is your
wisdom
okay
you are sometimes more trash than your
own trash
so let's treat the trash
how you want to be treated
yeah um I hope that was wise enough deep
yeah I mean if we want to go deeper I
can I can see I can dig in my trash can
see what I find at the bottom of it
maybe some banana peels
it was a compliment good yeah
um
um it's also was General it wasn't just
for you specifically it was for
everybody hmm
sorry guys for being late I was I'm like
stressed out I'm trying to do things
um like uh between you know the stream
and so on but I'm also like kind of
stupid because I spent like an hour
making muffins
they're really yummy I like them more
than my blueberry muffins
but I just I don't know I woke up and
the fact is I'm seeing friends tomorrow
and I thought
well I could make muffins and then
because last time I had so many left
over I couldn't eat them all alone but
then you know I felt like at this time
uh if I have leftovers that's actually a
good thing
yeah because I can just I can just give
it to my friends yeah and hopefully they
didn't like it but yeah I made chocolate
muffins today if you look at my Twitter
but you know what I'll post it here let
me post it here let me post it here
[Music]
some people commented like I don't know
what I'm seeing on on this one I thought
it was absolutely genius especially
especially if you think you don't know
what you're seeing
this picture I put the icons to fit
perfectly on the egg yolks because the
egg yolks were particularly reflective
but have you I this is the moment where
I realized
icons are just egg yolks with faces
more or less trying to censor something
but that while I was doing that I
realized oh the Emojis are actually
perfect for that usage when I do it on
an egg yolk
they look funny and they're round and
they're yellow and I mean but did this
look to you guys like egg yolks though
did you know that I was covering up egg
yolks with Emojis
the first time you heard of a reflective
egg yolk wow
yeah they are very shiny yeah okay
[Music]
they are very shiny yeah so I was making
um uh chocolate chocolate muffins
chocolate chip muffins and I was kind of
lazy I I also really like you know those
muffins that have like really big chunks
of chocolate in it but I didn't really
find you know those I guess you just
when you make those do you just cut up
up a big bar of cooking chocolate
is that how you make those usually but I
felt like I didn't feel like cutting up
a big chocolate bar
um so I just I just chose the tiny
chocolate chips that are already you
know
already chocolate chips yeah
for me yes I cut up a big bar is that
how you make the extra oh no there are
extra chunky bags as well really they
didn't have them here
um I couldn't find any of them but I was
like I mean in the end I'm using the
right the same amount of like grams of
chocolate anyway so in the end it took
me the same amount of chocolate it's
just not as aesthetic but whatever
so so and then and then I had this
lovely idea to top uh top it with with
cute vanilla chocolate
heart-shaped chocolate because like last
time with the blueberry muffins I was
experimenting
um I'm really excited guys I know this
is a simple muffin but I'm really
excited because it's my first muffins
this one the the previous blueberry
muffins are my first one and I'm really
excited about it so so so let me just
tangent out of my trash can
so so so the blueberry muffins were
pretty good I gotta say but um I felt
like they were not sweet enough actually
um but my brother tried one and said no
I think this is perfectly fine it's
really good but here I ate it when they
were already two days old I when they
were fresh of course they're like extra
topped here really good yeah
uh criminals can bake too yeah
and then and then uh yeah they were
really warm when they were good they
were really good when they were warm
and blueberry yum yum yum but I I think
I prefer blueberries when they're fresh
but they were good so then I thought
okay next time I'm gonna try a chocolate
chip muffins
but the chips are so tiny that you can
barely see them right
um no you can't really I mean I know
where they are but you could they're
just really blending in with the with
the dough oh and this is the first time
I no my brother what are you saying no
he really likes them
[Music]
uh what was I saying oh yeah I for the
first time I found out that there's
cooking cocoa baking cocoa oh I was just
gonna use like normal like you know for
drinking hot chocolate
um that kind of cocoa I was just gonna
use that but oh the recipe said baking
cocoa and then I went out and I couldn't
find any I was like in at the shelf or
the cocoa ones and I couldn't find any
and I was like maybe they just don't
have it and then I just I I was like
whatever I'm not cooking I'm not baking
it today anyway I'll I'll just I'll just
use um eventually I'll just use the
drinking cocoa powder should be fine
right but then a couple days later uh I
went to the supermarket again and I
accidentally found the cooking the
baking cocoa sorry can you guys follow
me I accidentally found it even though I
wasn't even looking for it and I already
thought I'm just gonna use the normal
one but turns out that the normal one is
sugary really sugary it really has sugar
in it so you're supposed to really use
the baking cooking cocoa but I don't
know it doesn't really make so much
difference I don't know because I didn't
try because I ended up finding the
cooking baking one so I uh bought it I
was like yo I found it they only have
one like type one brand but I found it
yeah it's really hard to find something
one thing yeah I didn't even want to ask
them
the the the the staff the people that
worked there because I thought they were
they were gonna think like what the [\h__\h]
is she talking about cooking cocoa never
heard of that what the [\h__\h] is that
yeah but apparently it exists it's it's
a thing and I bought it and I used it
for this so yeah
um basically I use the same recipe as
the blueberry muffins I just added in
the cocoa powder
and chocolate chips instead of
blueberries and the rest was pretty much
the same I think
and then and I had a bit of these cute
decoration chocolate Hearts
right are really cute they're so cute
and and so with the blueberry muffins I
tested out some of those sprinkles
because they come in one sprinkle
container yeah and I tested them out and
was wondering oh they're probably gonna
melt and just lose its shape completely
right especially if I put them on top
where all the heat gets to it and it
turns out it wasn't that uh it just it
kept its shape mostly uh it did like
melt a little bit but it mostly kept its
shape the last time so I was like all
right all right then this time if I put
these hearts on the muffins they're
gonna stand out because they're white
and they're gonna stand up because
they're cute so turns out they didn't
really melt at all yeah
they kept its shape and your cute hearts
yeah yeah so
sorry I'm so excited about my muffins
even though it's just normal muffins
right but they're sure they're good so
here is finito they had the perfect
texture inside they were warm and fluffy
and outside they had a little bit of a
crunch to it you know
[Music]
um
they look like volcanoes and this you
can see the hearts I mean a lot of them
slipped over to the side but uh there's
a couple the one on the bottom left
especially they stay straight in the
middle mostly yeah
shape
chocolates are bad for chickens don't
eat them but somewhere around in Phoenix
you should know
um
I surpassed you no way can you not bake
muffins anybody can bake muffins I've
realized it's so easy it's so easy and
it's fun with a kitchen machine
especially it's so easy because I have
no little arms so whenever like recipes
needed me to like make a dough I was
always like oh [\h__\h] dying when trying to
mix it with my hand
um
yeah new challenge these these turned
out so good I like them more than the
blueberry muffins they actually have
like the perfect amount of sweetness I
think and I'm just for Aesthetics I
thought it would look good with with
some sugar
powder on top but I mean I feel like
without where you can see the hearts
clearly they were plenty aesthetic I
guess
uh
well well oh well
nah I have I have I have a KitchenAid
mixer with three different
um like attachments the dull hook that
looks like a Captain Hook I used that
with that one for the pizza dough
um but for this one I just used the
normal like swirly not swirly no
um you know the one that just looks like
a mixer like a hand uh you know not an
automatic one just a normal one yeah
oh wait Sky yeah wait squished that's
what's it called yeah whisk just a wicks
uh whisk
oh whisk uh If I Stumble over my words
and I combine whisk and mixer uh it
turns into a bad dreaming word so let's
not do that
[Music]
[Laughter]
I like this picture it's actually like
it's like so instagrammy and perfect I
love it
um yeah so that's why I spent like an
hour making my breakfast but it was fun
and worth it and tomorrow I hopefully
will be appreciated by my friends for
bringing muffins
yeah yeah yeah yeah unfortunately they
can't eat them warm
warm they would be best but I I just now
took a bite from one that already cooled
down and it's still good but warm is
best
the muffin bringer is always appreciated
now now I'm finally type of person the
type of friend who who can bake and
brings their friends baked goods isn't
that nice I was never that kind of
person you can't microwave them I don't
think so I don't think that's a good
idea at least not in a microwave I was
wondering if maybe if you like baked
them for like I don't know 100 degrees
for five minutes or so maybe maybe that
could work but you can microwave them
once really I feel like in in the oven
it would work out nicer
um
but I don't know
oh really really maybe I should do that
tomorrow
I'll think about it but they're nice
cold as well maybe I just warm it up for
myself for breakfast because I'm
probably gonna eat two for breakfast
again I ate two for these for breakfast
two of these for breakfast can't talk
um so besides this tangent I must say I
can't stream too long because I need a
little break before the crony stream
which is at 11 PM for me which takes an
hour so I'm done at midnight but I need
to sleep early and before so that means
that before that I need to eat means
that I even have to cook before but I
don't know that's so stressful because I
still have some things to do before
um so I'm probably just gonna order food
and then have my brother use up my hello
fresh recipes
um yeah I'm really not gonna stream long
I think
until 8 PM so two and a half hours from
now
8 P.M then I have two hours to order
food eat food finish some of the things
I needed to do
yeah no three hours three hours three
hours nine more like two and a half
because then I need to be there for
crony
um before the stream you know
um okay stressful I'm stressed out but
at least that means I'm kind of like
hyper right now
ah yeah maybe maybe I don't know I said
three three hours total but man I don't
know I don't know I don't know
ah
calm down calm down
I I I was gonna get a energy drink
because I felt like I didn't get enough
sleep I felt pretty tired
um but turns out
turns out the stress is making me Hyper
so we're good
will we do with the rest of our days now
do you not have any streams of koala
that you need to watch um
you must have something oh also I still
need to record the like those cow carrot
just sent me the script today
I still need to record that but it
shouldn't take too long I think
and still need to record that so that
you guys have a little video on the
weekend from me
um
we can just rewatch all streams yeah
yeah please do please do we watch them
all immediately voila really all caught
up but I do have things I need to do
anyway all right okay that's good then
what do you have to do what are you
doing what are you doing huh did you
make those plans after knowing that I
will be gone or would you have had those
plans anyway even if I was streaming on
the weekend then you would have missed
me wouldn't you
oh I just filled up my cup of water to
the very brim because I was partially
not looking but I didn't know what flow
it's like it's like higher than the cup
it's higher than a cup but it's oh I
need to I can't even
[Laughter]
oh
okay surface tension test cutter yeah
thank you so much surface tension for
existing is that physics is a physical
thing right
oh okay okay guys
let me show up a little bit more here um
just for you
surfing is really difficult for me but
at least I could slurp like you know
water like that but like I really can't
slurp Ramen or noodles or so
I don't know why
anyway hey wait maybe maybe I should
maybe I should train that like while
drinking water like this and then
immediately afterwards like remembering
that technique technique that I just
used and slept notes like that is that
how you do it do you use it the same way
slurp training yeah
is do you slurp for the people who can
slap ramen noodles do you slurp it the
same way as you would slurp like just
normal water
never use the straw I use straws but uh
I have no idea how it's done yes kinda
kinda hmm maybe maybe I can train myself
like that then anyway you're right okay
I have no time but I played a little bit
off screen afterwards last time because
it was so much fun
um I don't think I hear the game audio
if there is any audio let me let me see
oh God can we I need to [\h__\h] calm
down I'm gonna get a heart attack I'm
going to get a heart attack
laughs
is there some music hello
is there music on the loading screen
normally
wait
I don't hear
uh
um
let me see let me see let me see let me
see
let's see let me see hello hello
I don't hear
why
it's my headphones I am well I hear
myself
okay myself
um windows
Sunset things why why why why
uh
oops your Muse how about this one
my my [\h__\h] sound settings are so
annoying man
they're never like it's so weird because
like I don't even have the Elgato
attached right now and it still says it
still always goes back Elgato sound
capture even though I don't have a
gobble attached I really I will never
understand this and I change it and I
deactivate it even in the devices but
active reactivates itself you know it's
so [\h__\h] weird I I just I don't
understand
I don't understand where is the sound
sorry guys I will I will I will fix it I
will fix it
and we'll fix it
I'll fix it
it's so haunted yeah
and to be haunted it to be haunted
why is it not working now
Thief simulator oh I see it like in the
bottom right you know when you open your
sound devices on the bottom right just a
small window I see Thief simulator is
making some noise
um
now let's let me cook yesterday I had
this issue with
with karafon but that was like a
different thing
um
come on
don't be so stupid you stupid computer
is the game itself no no that's why I
just said I just said I
[Laughter]
[Music]
will sound I see it literally
it's okay
that's it
[Music]
um
ah
don't ruin my mood now computer
wait can I hear like YouTube yes I heard
YouTube when I opened my own stream I
heard it
huh like what the [\h__\h] is going on these
days huh
music is overrated is it listed under
the correct device or is it still in the
wrong one it's always under the wrong
one normally what I do is I just at the
output selection I just choose a
different one it will still show that
it's Elgato sound capture or so yeah
even though I just selected something
else but usually just by selecting
something else it will then work
normally
um
let me restart the game
let her bake yes let people
maybe we should just worst case just
make it into a tattoo into a trash
dumpster that's a
h
one of those games I don't like wait is
it do I have a controller attached no
but you know what let me de-attach this
because I feel like maybe it's messing
with my mouse
okay
oh yeah
um
a restart again
sometimes you know when I have a
PlayStation controller attached it kind
of messes with the sound I didn't have a
PlayStation control attached though
Papa
game audience
[Music]
okay
I hate it
I already changed the default audio
device million years ago it's still like
I'm cursed by Elgato sound capture
I have the default device as like
something else but still you know and I
I like purposefully I click on the
Elgato and I deactivate it
and it's still okay now it worked but
it's still like showing Elgato as the
device that it's using
okay
there it is
just have to always like a million times
deactivate it
and then switch it to different ones I
don't [\h__\h] understand I will never
understand it
I want to write a formal complaint to
Elgato it's like a virus to me Elgato
sound capture is literally a virus
sponsorship lost
Barbie I'm not sponsored anyway
[Laughter]
okay okay so what did I do off screen
really nothing important I just I think
I am I think I learned one more thing
um off screen
it may have been this one no wait no it
may have been this one I think and then
I I used that to rub
something
uh but you can't see what I did right oh
and I bought some info on some of the um
some of the these houses these these
three that are together 103 104 106 no
104 105 106.
um
and I tried to clear up one some of
these thingies
um at least the ones I could find
um what did I do
I don't know
they didn't take a lot of the things and
I wanted to give them I need another
triple candle holder and then I realized
I also want the single ones
um
ah
wait there's okay I have one no oh yeah
so I I'm done with all the 104 105 106
thingies
I just couldn't stop myself guys but
next is 107 and 108.
we gotta break toilet break window break
wine glasses still decoration and then I
realized holy [\h__\h] it's getting really
difficult now because
um
where can I see it
the I saw the tenant routines I hear
I was I was actually forced to Rob
um
a house
while they were in I think which one was
it
which one was it
may have been
I'm not even sure anymore but like time
schedule wise I think it was this one
because the only time we're in those
these two hours when they are both gone
and that is basically just two minutes
and that's just not enough time so since
she this tenant is in the kitchen for
three hours before that
I I did a risky thing uh the overlap is
too short so I just went in already at
like uh this time as soon as the other
tenant was gone yeah
and just robbed it while she was still
there
and it went pretty good because when I
wasn't streaming I was able to stay
pretty calm most of the time
speaking clean yeah
and sometimes they found me or like
noticed I'm here and then I would just
hide in the in the closet for a while
but overall it was pretty chill
so I got oh I got some stuff here
uh oh another saucepan I guess I wanted
to maybe sell that because they don't
need that anymore do they a landline a
John muscle receiver toaster I don't
know if I should keep this one maybe for
the future maybe they needed the toaster
wasn't there toaster
okay can I not run in this game no there
we go
different from Minecraft Minecraft is
Ctrl and this game is shift for running
confusing
uh wasn't there
no microwave radio had said these ones
the the more expensive ones probably
don't show up yet
but these ones remember if we're seeing
a microwave we gotta take it
Jeff and Carla
no no no no no no no why why would you
think that it's not Jeff and Carl in my
bag no
uh what Ctrl [\h__\h] you
[Music]
all right
um I guess let's go I feel like I I need
to like you know get into my groove
again
but now wait I want to buy info I want
to buy info I want to buy info I want to
buy info
I want to buy info I want to buy info I
was also just trying to make some money
off screen which I did
I make of much money but I also bought
some a lot of things like the
information so that's why it looks like
I don't have so much money I will buy
the 10 routines because we're going to
the Wilsons and loot location I don't
care and maybe oh these are expensive
but I'll buy them okay
attended routines there's no one really
no one home there's only one person okay
okay see sometimes
it's just rough
wait
eh oh okay okay this one
we will definitely have to deal with
someone who's in in the garage and
toilet
muscle's the time here
that one's rough this one okay they have
a three hour overlap
and if we want to go a bit earlier we
could go at 7am to the kitchen
okay we've got free jobs there let's go
to 107 then we have to break the toilet
we have to break the window
we have to break their wine glasses oh
that's good cash money that's good cash
money do I have a criminal Elliot I liar
I lie earliest uh no not yet
what should it be
what what what does what what makes a
name sound Criminal
great planning right yeah evangelism yay
wrapped right on the toilet my greatest
fear
still Chill La Galina was dead
um Kiana the crook
um
why why did you think it was that
he had a sassy
why does it sound criminal doesn't it
doesn't chicken snatcher oh I am the
chicken snatcher uh had your chickens
now I'm coming for them oh they have a
skill point remaining oh
didn't I already learn this I feel like
I really learned it well that's weird
did I not save or what no I did but what
Vinnie what's up
Waits way too much time in front of the
TV
hey neighbor and help them out that's
weird I feel like I heard that before
hmm
uh okay I'm assuming 108 needs the
electric pick thingy
now I feel like
look I don't have money for that yeah
wait that's weird I feel like I already
bought tried to buy one before
oh but I did buy climbing gloves
off screen I think
all right all right let's go to 107
hopefully they don't need the electric
one
hopefully
Elgato
no I don't wanna
its own word but I don't want the name
of Elgato which keeps on freaking
torturing me
messing up my audio devices
I'm as good as a driver as ever
all right all right oh haven't we look
kind of looked at 107 before where is
the oh there's parking right there
oh wonderfully located
uh we're we're a bit early
that's okay I want to get mentally
prepared and look at the house
and remember how to play this game I'm
just gonna open this up already
free parking
the guten burglar
oh they know me as the Gutenberg from
Gutenberg oh
but I am not Sarah guys
oh oh they're outside okay interesting
that's actually easy
yeah the wine glasses
what do you mean what do you mean who
are you anyway
you have no right to tell me and where I
can go okay [\h__\h] you
I'm gonna call the cops on yo
what do you think about that
I'm gonna take out my phone and I'm
gonna film you I'm gonna harass you by
feeling you yeah yeah yeah yeah and then
I'll show that to the police
oh what's gonna do what you gonna do
sorry excuse me
I love those I love and I also hate
those dramas like those real live videos
that people take mostly in America
where like two people film each other
and they're really pissed at each other
like they they're filming each other
because they both are are like really
like
offended by each other and think they're
in the right so they're gonna film each
other for evidence right because they're
both both people think that they're in
the right and the other isn't
it's so funny yeah
Americans forgot what the escalation
means
maybe oh man I actually you can also
know those those videos do you see those
videos in social media where
um like in Planes
some as some things escalate
uh the other day I saw one where I
absolutely didn't know what the [\h__\h] was
going on and then today in social media
I saw another plane video where I
thought oh it's gonna be another one
like that but this one actually it just
so happened to be a positive one for
once uh some some huge seven foot uh
tall guy
didn't have space in his seat so a Karen
looking lady gave him uh her seat that
was like the emergency exit so that was
more space I was like I was expecting
some drama what's going on
incredible okay do they need the
electric lock pick here
DIY simple lock pick okay
for this store maybe for the entrance
door they need a different one
I wonder
yeah yeah okay
then we are soon leaving
people being nice and playing that's
right it really seems to be rare
chances of meeting a true care in the
wild are low
um have I ever met
someone like that
who makes like big drama in public like
that
it's a good question
not sure have I if I had then I probably
told you the story about it already
maybe I haven't
thank God
thank God I mean at work in oh no I
definitely had Karen's like talking to
me in my hotel job
oh yeah
there were some stories like that
oh yeah yeah
and and just coincidentally I think most
a lot of them a lot of them happen to be
American but also others
many others too don't worry
they just don't want to accept the way
things are all right she's leaving ER
wait should I hmm first here in the
bedroom
he's gonna stay in the bedroom for a
while and then go to the toilet and then
wait no wrong wrong where am I 107 here
kitchen
any retail customer service jobs will
let you with plenty of care and then
but also not only Karen's but what do
you call I think I asked you before the
male equivalent
many many male equivalents as well
throwing things at you even like pens
a Kyle
really I don't remember it being called
a Kyle interesting
Kevin yeah I think I think you guys told
me before it's a Kevin
Kyle
interesting Kyle
well shouldn't it be like I know I can
it's either Kyla Kevin you barely hear
that though that's so sad all right
um
all right all right all right I'm gonna
I'm gonna we have to we have to do it do
I remember how this works
it's been a while
there's someone coming
he's not looking though
oh
oh he's just sat down I thought he was
coming over here I am
a bam Bambi all right okay I'll I'll
wait oh wait after
wait
Taylor Wilson
she'll be in the garden okay if we break
the wine glasses first then we don't
have to be the garden and then we can do
whatever we want in the garden inside
while she's in the garden afterwards
remember to look at the nearest dumpster
oh can I hide in this small one too
no there's something inside
it's a closet inside
worst case I went 24 hours until they're
gone again and repeat their schedule
okay okay 107 is not so bad hi
what
wait what what do you mean
oh come on
I want now I didn't steal anything like
legit you're gonna call the cops on me
and they're not gonna find anything on
me I didn't even manage to open the door
did I
did I actually manage to open the door
and I just thought I broke it again
I can't even find I'm losing time
losing time oh man but they can't find
me either
as if someone like me isn't like really
easy it isn't like really easy to find
I'm literally dressed in burglar clothes
I'm calm again
OH police car is over there cook
you will never find you're not gonna
you're not gonna report me are you
oh
[Music]
go away
I'll have to sleep until it's that time
again
oh [\h__\h] hell
no no no no
[Music]
[Laughter]
no no no
[Music]
um
whoops
how are you calm playing offline
yeah I I think it was on the same day so
I still had you know as in the flow I
knew what I was doing
and I don't know I just get more
expressive when I stream
all right same thing again but we'll
sleep probably
no I didn't play like this off stream I
was calm
really
it was quiet
I didn't say a word I didn't scream I
didn't panic
always calm I'm always calm guys
who do you think I am
ah okay so what time
we wanna be there
at
uh
7 A.M
okay but I won't open the door until 8am
I think because I'm a little chicken
right now
I need to
I need to just
take my time today
I need to take my time
someone please replace the music in
Psycho stabbing scene with Kiana Screech
thank you
[Music]
I don't know if you're gonna get the
desired effect from that why why is
everybody's car blue maybe I should make
my car Bluetooth to stand out less
why did I all have blue cars
weird
did you guys come to my unarchived
karaoke yesterday huh everybody who's
here did you watch it
anybody who didn't
if yes then why
did you not
is
love the Papa Roach ah thank you
no I'm sad
but I will stream it again okay
[Music]
nothing to discover
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
foreign
I did open it before I think
The Sounds leave mud here
oh
I love the money for that okay I I can
get some quick money if I just do the
wine glasses first and then another time
we won't have that uh you know we don't
have to do that
[Music]
nice
let's take them with us
how's my oh I brought some things in my
backpack
oops
I brought some things wait what about
here uh mini electric lock pick okay
is there anything else I can feel
through this one
there's people
what about the wind wait I could no it
needs a glass knife
mmm okay
it's okay we already got money for
breaking the window uh the the glasses
yeah no I can't even open the windows I
can't smack them
gotta make some money
I'm gonna sell some things
can I take this
I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna
go now
ah don't call anyone please
don't call anyone please
I didn't do anything
going back
[Applause]
so I'm gonna sell some things
and then we're gonna buy the new lock
and I'm gonna try again
hey sorry
nothing to see here
if you don't want to sound or seem less
suspicious guys just go with la la la
la la la la la the least suspicious
sound you could ever make is
[Music]
oh well amazing uh give me a shitty rank
this makes no sense I only went there
with the goal to take I'm gonna destroy
the wine glasses or something all I
wanted to do
can I sell the
no
I need a pot so I can complete this one
um
I'm glad I took it yay okay
now the rest
and I guess I'll sell let me see
we need money urgently
um
why they want an old toaster but I have
a toaster that's so
come on
all right I'll sell the things I have
right now hopefully that's enough
to get to 1 200 or so I think
[Applause]
he keep it until it becomes out that's
the plan I guess no
no let's see how much we can get from
that
huh
oh
I have a small TV that you want 120
noise
a new toaster a saucepan
the wine
how much do I have now oh
maybe need to just
um
go to a different hospital I noticed
that if you steal something once it
doesn't come back to the house
so
I can't steal the same things over and
over again but I mean I still left some
big items in some of the previous
buildings
so in theory I could go back to those I
guess
that would be a little broken I guess so
what if you spend too much money and you
need more money
uh
wait how much sorry sorry sorry I keep
on doing things again what was I gonna
look at I wanna see oh yeah one is
really one thousand two hundred damn
damn
so I even sell something cool
but I have the bass guitar is so special
I'll sell
the Golden Goblet surely that I already
sold that several times so
we broke
we're broke man how can I be broken
if I'm the top three of the street
AKA I'm the only one
and they don't even sell so well what
and I need a couple more bucks okay it's
time to steal whoever it doesn't matter
I'm gonna go to the ones that I'm pretty
familiar with
don't advertise that what
what stealing I mean it's a peep
simulator obviously stealing in real
life is not good
don't steal things but I mean in the
game I have to I'm in character you know
um I know they're they're up there
are you still in my heart
sorry I'm not giving it back
ever it's mine but I will take good care
of it don't you worry about that
here's my favorite hiking spot
yeah I'm gonna get ready for picnic
meow just a picnic just a picnic let's
see who's home
oh
go to them which one is that 106.
she will come back soon after but I
think no not enough time she's in the
creature now okay I'll go I'll go to
I'll go to her
let's go let's go let's go let's go
gotta be fast
bro first time I'm doing this today
gonna be faster
don't have so much time or they're both
gone
how do I crouch again okay
see
so scary
I'm so scared all right all right
I am here where's she
gone
can I take this can I throw this out the
window it should be possible
oh sick eventually we can come back here
to crack the save
she gone now that door uh sound was her
being gone right
so
what was that was it me
gone oh headphones
maybe I just stay in this room
I mean with the painting
oh Mouse that's probably already enough
promise not to break them yeah I'll wrap
your hearts in bubble wrap okay
what's that oh a hard drive I haven't
had that item yet
[Applause]
okay
good so far she's really gone now gotta
be gonna be fast
I'll see if I can still find something
small but yeah bye yeah bye there's
really no time
[Music]
something something something something
something something
camera
why are they so loud okay uh
yeah bye
okay I'm leaving
where's my painting
oh yeah okay
what what can I leave the painting here
okay yeah yeah wait wait if I just if I
just
came back right
yeah
I thought it was safe my heart my heart
you gave me a heart attack I'm gonna sue
you for giving me a hug me a heart
attack
where are we now like what time where
the call
which house did I go to this one okay
we're at the same we're just gonna do
the same thing but we're gonna leave
earlier
[Laughter]
don't taste me
ah I'm allergic they saw me for the
window yeah I was I was too careless
can I do
there's someone coming
from the clock are they gonna see
what what do you mean what do you mean
what do you mean what do you mean what
do you mean what do you mean what do you
mean what do you mean I'm just a law
abiding citizen just like you are you
are you maybe I should check up if
you're a law abiding okay
threatening always works
I'm gonna take the painting again
and some of those other things
but going outside actually wasn't that
much worth it I think
okay
actually what I should just
open from the bottom
and I don't have to close them
sorry am I constantly looking up because
my am I I'm I'm inverted does it look
weird
do I look funny
I don't want to look funny
not at all
how many times do I have to tell you
shoot
okay
that's it that's all I'll take you have
we have to Rob them step by step not all
at once we can't be too greedy
okay
they can't see me they can't see me okay
now we just have to bring it safely
two oh
okay she's going that way okay I think I
can bring it to the car go go go go go
go
as if carrying the painting is really
going to slow me down that much
this is as fast as I can go
that was close nah I've been in more
close situations beforehand this is
nothing
all right let's go hope that was worth
it
let's go
let's go I'm going
The Perfect Crime
let's go to the pawn shop because the
painting
I don't think the shop had anything like
that
what
I think that's the first time I got an
ass rank with exclamation mark
I was pretty fast and really like goal
oriented
stole plenty of things too all right all
right all wrong
13 bucks for painting
the [\h__\h]
that's weird I gotta sell like pretty
much all of this I hope I won't need
these things later
the hard drive yeah okay we have enough
money now
why is everything worth more than this
shitty painting I guess because it's
shitty well it's not that funny I've
actually kind of like it
it's probably fake it's probably just
printed hmm
what's on the HDD maybe we can check
no I doubt it
okay we got some money
very important to get this but
Swan unlike the others I can use
several times right I don't have to get
several of these per
lock right
that would be crazy
1200 each time oh they doing it
wait that's a different one um they do
need another hard drive so good that I
didn't sell the hard drive
I was about to sell it
guitar guitar that those are new things
the guitars are new
okay remember guitar and an old toaster
and a pot
that's some things I still need
oh and skill point
um
that would be good
more space
open saves no but um I feel like
I feel like no need for that just yet I
think I'm gonna put it into the agility
first
already did the turret when you lock
pick oh no I didn't
oh yeah this takes two uh SP anyway okay
I'll take I'll take agility and then
next time more space
let's learn
can I learn it
oh
it's not even on here is it do I not
learn it
the same way
huh
okay maybe it just works like
automatically thanks for the membership
you're one beautiful Thief
thank you
okay let's go
you're gonna get a visitor
oh
a little burglar a cat burglar
hide your cats otherwise I'm gonna steal
them too
I hope they don't miss their painting
maybe it has sentimental value to them
oh well then you should have secured it
better
put an alarm on it or so
I'm sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
traffic
right
107. what time are we
oh we're okay we have to sleep
otherwise would be a little bit too
risky
[Music]
7am
was the time
okay
okay here we go I don't have to do the
wine Quest anymore because we already
did that so that's
that's helpful
we have to break the toilet and break
the window on the second floor okay
very comfortable sleep
um
I personally I can't sleep well in the
car
unless I can sit in the back and let go
sideways but even then
could be very cool as a fifth to have
the power to control time I mean
obviously of course
yeah we need very same same
most people don't sleep well in the car
I'm just so jealous of people who can
sleep immediately
that's such a such an overpowered op
skill
remember saying thank you
sleep like a baby in cars oh really I
used to be able to sleep easily in the
car not anymore
I sleep on the bus both ways daily how
when do you how do you know when to get
off
aren't you scared to miss your station
recently I missed my station so often
even when I'm like awake
I can't open immediately this guy I
gotta wait for him go faster
walk walk walk that walk go go go go go
go go go go go go go go go
okay
risky risky risky scary scary this is
[\h__\h]
there's someone on the other side of the
street
unlucky
[Music]
come on now I already lose so much time
and I'm losing all my
lock picks
I know I have seven more no two more
simple ones yeah
I might run out of them
why are there so many people walking
around right now
can I reload
oh
what is the checkpoint the last time I
slept or when where where do the how did
I decide
the checkpoints what
I guess it's like after I woke up huh
but the same people are still walking by
um very unlucky unless I I I'm able to
pick the locker really quickly here
that's daylight robbery for you yeah
it's
it's so
it's kind of um cocky of me to do it in
the middle of the day but what can I do
don't have a choice
sleep to the list okay good dad good
idea
maybe we have better luck
on the next day
um
wait why am I
see
what is it 7 A.M
seems so but it's a different day right
I didn't go back in time yeah okay
um
all right
hopefully by the time this guy comes out
these two people also are gone this this
one there's one over there
right
car time machine yeah
the almost all time machine I'm just
sleeping on it I'm a good sleeper
even when I'm not tired I sleep for the
greater purpose of stealing things
did you see uh Marlins stream with Lena
by the way
just before my stream they had a stream
a collable and off collaborina is in
Japan right now why is there so many
people in Japan right now huh why why
why why sauce
yeah they did like a t-shirt thing a
t-shirt judging which t-shirt would you
take
if you weren't able to read Japanese
with like funky Japanese on it
oh oh there's two more people no
they're on the other side
oof
have to wait for that one again
oh and that one
oh come on
I have no choice
I have no choice I will wait
afterwards they're just in the garden
anyway
there's another one coming
wow
okay okay
yeah I called in like I was watching the
stream and they uh once I commented
Martin was like oh oh maybe we should
call kihara so she dm'd me and then I
called in they believe that gouda knew
what the shirt she chose man I don't
know which one which one shows I was
watching kind of at the end only
which one did you choose
please please please please please
please please please please
oh thank God okay
um
I'm gonna try to enter from the side
um hey what is this how's this work
let's just take time
yeah okay
scared I'm so scared oh keep it open I
guess
or should I
what am I stealing what am I doing break
the toilet break the window on the
second floor
okay
um
whatever you want should I take the
coffee machine
teapot saucepan
oh a printer a lamp
um um where is it where's the stairs
huh out here
are you told her okay
she's not gonna report me is she
oh guitar
ah it's not the one they're looking for
I think
uh what else what else
uh uh Brandon we're not on the second
floor which one
done
can I put it in my bag oh I can't okay
then I'm just gonna I'm just gonna take
it
coming back soon
one of them is coming back soon
okay
I'm Gonna Leave
um maybe goodbye
they're gonna catch me if I leave like
that
all panic panic I can just walk for the
front door still it's fine it's fine
[Applause]
okay
ah we did the quest let's bounce we can
come back but for now
we're gonna leave it at that because I'm
gonna sell the things they have before
someone comes and then
gets really angry
um you have to know how to control
ourselves
and not be controlled by our greed
this is S rank job you think so I don't
think the game is going to see this then
took too much time I think B no not bad
not bad
bad
I did the
boom your scream scares me for no reason
sorry
I don't want to scare you
it's that microwave okay next time let's
try to get a microwave I think they had
one
oh and they want another saucepan and a
pot ah because I sold the other one
maybe
Taylor Guitar Washman guitar
okay
new Quest okay 108. we have to still
break a decoration and steal the
painting Daisy
hmm
okay
I should probably buy some more simple
lock picks
you would think they would later on not
have the simple lock specs anymore but
no they definitely do
we definitely do
and the simple locks I mean
one more
breaking the toilet is such a random
request yeah these themes or at least
the Vinny guy who keeps on asking me to
do these things as well like oh they
they have a TV let's break it to teach
them a lesson they're like they have
weird fetishes
weird things make them happy
yeah it's not like they know them
personally either
not everyone thinks to upgrade their
looks
um
[Applause]
all right let's go
My Cousin Vinny's such an anti-anti yeah
he just woke up and he decided he wants
to see the world burn every day
every single day
on here
sorry I'm late
no problem
welcome to the Stream
we're doing great so far I can't stream
for too long today oh but
everyone my bag still have a good
question why what's why didn't I oh I
didn't sell the things okay let me put
them in here for now
no problemo
no problem we're not gonna be able to
steal like everything anyway
yeah let me out
let me out
wobble on the second monitor ah it's
okay thank you for having me
even when you're busy with work
she probably wouldn't even notice if I
would break in right now would she
but we're gonna look at 108.
promise oh with 108 right now
there they are
not home except for the garage guy
but
that's kind of risky going in now
uh starting from 11 A.M
nah
the living room
is rough
try
right now he's
now of course now you go to the toilet
where's the toilet
[Laughter]
why do you need an hour on the toilet
anyway
toilet garage toilet why did you go to
the top so often he must be nervous he
must know
that something's going on
can I do it as well he's there
oh God that is so risky
what am I doing
I'm I will have to prioritize something
so scary
um
[Applause]
break or steal big TV break or steel
decoration okay once he's like
once he is
uh
outside again in the garage
oh that's the daisy painting
makes it a lot easier pick
is there money in there pendulum
I'll just take a couple things for now
it's like this one
oh
when their electric guitar they're not
looking for that but I'll take it
okay I feel pretty safe right now
alarm clock I'm inventory full
okay let's break or steal a big TV
where is where is the big TV
and break
who the [\h__\h] saw me
what the [\h__\h] Sammy
it's gonna be fine right
okay it's gone it's gone it's gone
ah
so nervous okay now
right decoration like what for example
this which what decoration what
decoration
what decoration
I want to leave
I'm gonna come back
okay
wait wait wait it's okay it's okay it's
Keep On Moving
run run and play that music please while
you're at it
the music that starts playing when real
guns until nervous I gotta go I gotta go
I gotta go I gotta go TV didn't count
what I felt like that it worked
I still got time
hey I have to open it again
no way why
all the luck probably
[\h__\h] hell
what
it's gone though
I I think it did count it just doesn't
right away show it like that
wait what the [\h__\h] what is he doing
maybe I just have to
okay I'll look for another TV but
he's now in the kitchen I gotta come
back
kitchen
it needs to be bigger where's the bigger
one
and where's the bigger one
where's the bigger one steal up the
painting though I did
and did I steal a decoration and let's
go home once and come back uh maybe take
down this
second floor
I never seen one I saw like uh
a lot of other things though
and it's twice as big as mine
your TV very small huh baby TV
cute
bubble bubble TV
bedroom TV okay was there a room that I
didn't enter at all probably I was so
very nervous my first time in that house
I still need to orientate myself
uh let's go pawn shop
didn't have to do them like that oh
Daisy okay Daisy okay Daisy okay
I'm gonna sell Daisy to you I think
10 bucks
pendulum I think was not asked for the
hard drive though yeah we needed the
second one oh no that's still the first
one is it
the wine you can have and the guitar yes
good money
I have these things to a coffee machine
router
I'll just sell the phone for now
50 bucks for a Nokia
damn
nowadays definitely not a realistic
price how much would you get for
those old Nokes now nothing nothing
right maybe just for Nostalgia like a
buck or so
what was your guys's first phone I don't
even remember what my first one was
where am I where am I
oh God
I can't go backwards
Nokia
mine was a break what
[Laughter]
mine was probably a Nokia Motorola oh
lots of Motorola's those aren't around
anymore are they
mine was Blackberry was Blackberry oh
yeah many blackberries too
Samson Erickson what's a roll of flip
phone
an iPhone 4S it was a hand-me-down
iPhone 4S
when was that a thing that seems it
feels like not not so long ago
oh yeah
Nokia Nokia Nokia
oh Nokia Nokia 2011 oh that's not too
long ago is it 10 12 years ago
yeah you can see people's age when I
quit but not necessarily it also has to
do with how strict your parents are I
guess but
um these days
they get their their first phones way
faster don't they
um
okay Washman Taylor Watchman Taylor
Watchman Taylor
um
and the decoration okay ah
the vase would count for example okay
okay okay let's go back
um
I'm a store
the hard drive
okay
kids don't get a Nintendo DS to play
Pokemon these days they get an iPhone to
watch Elsa and Spider-Man videos
yeah back in the day the Nintendo DS
was so such a popular thing to give to
your child I guess and I was playing I
was playing a lot on my Nintendo you
know
good stuff good days those were the good
days Nintendo picked the chat yeah I was
never able where am I going I was never
able to make my picture chat work I was
always alone in the picture chat I don't
think I was ever able to properly
connect the Wi-Fi connection I didn't
realize that that was what I had to do
um and I wonder if I would have
connected it like could I only chat with
the people like close by or is there
like a was there a server
yeah you're showing your age
no Phoenix
been around for a long time I've been
around in in the 60s too
it was local only
oh yeah four people Max
wait local only what do you mean local
so that they have to be like right next
to you
mm-hmm
I'm Marie Antoinette Young
oh okay but did you also still have to
be connected to Wi-Fi
where are we going
this one right
so
11 A.M okay
11 A.M
no Wi-fi really oh okay
but if you can only do it like when
there's someone in your room or so
it's kind of boring
that's kind of boring
but probably better this way
just wireless connection from TS does
yes but I never got to try that
[Music]
came way too early
pizza was fun the school bus
School
bus wait you mean like actual school I
never was in an actual School Bus
we just had you know normal buses
for me the answer is
good at it though
when I was in America I saw some school
buses like standing around my fog damn
this looks like little Simpsons or so or
like I don't know any kind of like
American sitcom with like a family and
children
yeah that's fascinating for me
absolutely fascinating
they look so cute all in yellow
it's real
it's just like you know seeing a thing
in anime and going to Japan and saying
the same thing wow
that's because school buses are real
yeah apparently
American school but still iconic yeah
sorry I can't think I'm waiting the
thing is you can't do like half past
something or so and I I want to be ready
right away when this person leaves so I
gotta wait a little bit
oh yeah now this person left
I hated the school bus
side looks really wow American sidewalk
well
on the grass whoa American pavement wow
American Earth soil everything wow
American
hello
Hello nice to meet you oh
interesting that's what an American
person looks like well fascinating I
must inspect further oh let me look let
me look at your pores are they different
from mine
well sorry sorry excuse me I'm just so
fascinated by you
American Dad oh American lady
cute clothes actually oh she's wearing
thongs
or do you call them flip-flops here I'm
never sure I call them flip-flops
do you speak
a language with me lady do you want to
talk talk to me talk
totally and just uh I'm just a thief who
wants to have some company
please
oh person left I think or is leaving and
on the ground right
they're gone okay
let's go let's go all the TV is there
when you're outside you can still see
the signs easily okay and the other
thing is there
let's see
do not get caught under any
circumstances
so you got a new TV congratulations
right in here in here
currently
down there
on the toilet so I wonder if he would
hear it oh lots of money
I'm inspect here
hi friends
let's go
that's exactly what I needed oopsie
I'm slowly open slowly open slowly and
open
what
what thanking all the hard drives this
thief has a thing for hard drives you
see it still there
let me wait a moment
Joe Master receiver I'll take it I feel
like that might have been
in the requirements
foreign
come on get a hold of your bladder
break this one
maybe not
okay it has to be I guess this one
now
together
vase
Wick away raise
these these
can't open this yet
anything else I should bring what's this
anything that's on my list
oh small little paintings why not
no more money
okay maybe I still got time I still got
time
is that
alrighty another radio you found a
rather already better than Cooper
and I can take another one what
another guitar they restocked these
I thought they don't restock I mean I
don't restock everything
just certain things
um
he's on the toilet again
I might just go
um
oh okay sometimes it says you're hurt by
the tenant but they don't react to it
thankfully
I'm gonna go
scared
money
let's go guys it's time to leave
why is this door open again
oh there's someone there
yeah bye have to wait for that person
or I can walk behind them and run
but I got some good money I got 2 200
bucks now hey
I think I have a talent for this I'm
good at stealth games um you guys told
me that there's um
like a better game than this when you do
the same thing a lot of other a lot of
you guys told me and don't worry I saw
it I saw it
yeah Hitman
oh this honored design was always like
kind of interesting to me yeah but I
don't have perms for that I think
I wanted to play that back in the day
when I was playing the other game from
the same publisher
or you don't want someone to see their
own necklace at the pawn shop
break it down first
okay
break it down okay what are you talking
about learn appraisal okay
um
yeah but Hitman apparently Hitman would
be something for me
who do
free hard drives for the 60 bucks hmm
okay okay okay okay
I really still need the microwave though
okay
too
fauna and Dana loved it
at least I have perps for that one yo
no jobs right now interesting I'm just
too
progressing too well
in terms of like skill
I feel like
I'm like
really good at this game so far
oh not Dishonored um hits man yeah for
Hitman we got perms
not for Dishonored otherwise I would
have played it a long time ago I think
at least not not as far as I know maybe
by now we have it did somebody play it I
don't think so the only Hitman
um
it's also payday free which is Co-op
payday 2. Co-op
what and you you you you burglar you
become burglar with Co-op
Payday for the like GTA Heist
but then in GTA you can also call up to
heists right
just didn't do it because I wanted to
play a game Payday 2 really
huh
oh crony plant player too really
good I wants to play it well I wouldn't
mind being her
her buddy for that
payday is more Bank let me look at it
wait I want to see really quick
Google
paid payday 2.
oh
they have like clown masks that's so
scary
that's scary
is there a non-coop mode first that that
I should probably play first to get used
to the game
some multiplayer game
it is more like the heist from GTA it's
more of an FPS
you can play solo I did crony play it
then I might watch like how crony played
it a little bit to see if it's something
for me
you can practice solo
oh crony did it as a collab too
a
um
apparently it's not a stealth game not
not that much
I'm gonna sell
uh extra hard drive what's the baby
what's that
a cell things
when you play the foreign
did she not play the solo mode on her
own at all
does somebody know did she just jump
straight into the co-op mode
welcome if she can do that then maybe I
can you know manage to do that too good
money 180 bucks BB
hard drive six books okay cool cool
good stuff just a co-op
was it not difficult
when you just jump straight into the
club I feel like I would struggle
jumping into a game like that without
any knowledge
hmm
it's fun as hell with friends either way
oh all right
okay I wanna see can I do I have a skill
point I do they want me to learn
appraisal level two
disassembled generally with special
tools
I never even used this thing in the
first place but okay I have to learn it
for the story
I did it Vinnie
[Music]
seven don't like our protection plan our
protection plan I hope nothing happens
to the jewelry in their bedroom
what's our what's the what's that
supposed to mean
okay we have to do something with their
jewelry
what does that mean that sounds so
threatening
our protection plan what's that mean
s
it's scary
extortion
we protect them from us
I can't do this unless wait I actually
have the money for it what the hell
yo I thought I wouldn't be able to buy
it
new tutorial jewelry tools allow you to
disassemble jewelry before selling it
okay
I tested out here or what
oh no I have to bring it here
seems so and disassembling it before
selling it is better be just because the
owners will not be recognizing it in the
pawn shop is that what they're saying
because they talked about the pawn shop
okay okay
I probably won't fall from the pawn shop
anyway okay
ah behind my nose so much cat hair God
damn it
[Applause]
guess we're going back to 107 at least
that one has a time frame where
everybody is gone
at some point
I think
let's go ah driving like this only
reminds me of GTA I just probably just
because I don't play games much where
you can
driving the car in first person mode
it's very rare for me but it probably is
a thing in many games not just this one
ah the Wilsons the Wilsons are gonna be
gone
um
7 A.M 8 A.M well if I'm just doing the
jewelry
oh and then Garden okay I'll come at 8am
your trucks
okay I guess I'll finally play Zero
truck simulator as well
the time has come what did I say 8 am
Wilson lots of Wilson let's go why you
guys you guys why why is why does zero
truck simulator make people so excited
what is it about it
y'all
I'm in baby
um
generally in the bedroom Julie in the
bedroom bedroom bedroom bedroom look up
there
let's go let's go
where's the bedroom
heirloom bracelet
sorry for taking that
you can find it again in the pawn shop
damaged you phone a mouse baptism I sold
that no I have that already
nobody wants it
he said oh I can hide oh
small TV
trespassing no no no I'm not trespassing
I'm just bypassing
the law
[Music]
I got so much time let me steal some
smaller things
is there anything here to steal
nice one
let me think about that TV
and let me check the kitchen
[Music]
sauce pounds not the teapot am I grip I
mean
finally
a pot
okay another good stuff good stuff I'll
bring the printer actually because I
never brought the printer before
I'm gonna go right
after after that one person
walks by
yeah you need to be able to make
yourself some hot water
otherwise what kind of person would I be
um yeah bye
is this yeah bye yeah that's pretty yeah
bye
um holy [\h__\h] oh holy [\h__\h] will she see
them well she's Panic will they panic
when I see the yeah
come on
give me something Shady no
no no no no
no no no no no
oh look away
stop looking at me
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
all right drop this princess so often it
probably doesn't even work anymore
it needs maintenance but it's okay it's
okay we'll tell whoever buys it uh that
it works just fine and once they get it
then we'll have a rude awakening and I
will say wow that's just because you're
not very good with with I.T stuff okay
not my fault that you're not
skill like that skill issue
printer it doesn't want to be with this
family because they're not using it
anyway
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay nice nice we got a lot of stuff
better and better
hey yo
level up soon I'm gonna break down the
jewelry okay okay
we'll go let me try this out
uh select wow it's so fancy
this is sample do I need skill for this
um
they're attaching 58 oh okay doesn't
really seem like there's skill necessary
you just
gotta do it a couple times
I don't know if this really makes it so
much more like un noticeable that it's
their own
yeah it's pretty easy
I did it
a professional knows how to handle a
real thing
oh there we go it's safe opening time
baby
what skill points for that that's uh
2sp I have one so we have to save it for
now or we invest in more backpack space
yeah we're talking real fifing now the
big league hell yeah what did I do with
the jewelry I just sell it
we check real quick here
the big one
wasn't there a big one in GTA
I remember yeah
let's go that wasn't even there before I
feel like
voice noise
I feel like the old toaster is not gonna
be in the new houses that I'm going to
it must have been like somewhere in one
of the first houses the first two
yeah the big one I'm in CTA two my three
wants that during the weekend yeah it's
a long long play through but I I know
you guys really enjoyed that one I hope
I can repeat that like somehow with a
different game or
I don't know with another GTA game or
something similar I know you guys really
liked it and I really liked it too I had
a good time with that
um today it was fun for me too Red Dead
red dead yeah you guys keep on timing
it's kind of similar
but it doesn't seem to have the like
iconic
reputation as GTA does it seems but I I
want to you know play it anyway
eventually
it's just hard to recreate something
like the experience of streaming GTA hmm
San Andreas yeah I feel like I checked
if I have perms for that and it was a
No-No but
800 wow
you think it's safe to sell the printer
I wonder if it will show up in the
requests later oh well
yo we got so much money again yeah
I'm doing so well and I barely get
caught ever
I mean
I never get caught I'm such a pro
what I should learn from my playthrough
so good that's the spirit big money
today it pays to be a Fame
they're working on a new GTA oh
what they are how long will that take
is there an estimate have we seen
anything of that before
what That's so exciting haven't you
heard no not really I don't know
they've been working on it for six for
ten years what
what
why don't they finish it two more years
or so no please no
a couple years more can't they speed up
a little bit should I send them like I
don't know my Harvard student Canto to
help
maybe that will make them go faster
um
they're still making money with GTA 5.
ah same
same thing I guess as um
as
as the switch
them not releasing a new console yet
even though usually by now they would
have
or Mario Kart ate the X the Mario card
that has been around the longest without
a uh
why is the grass going for my car
my car is leaking
[Applause]
I still have things in there don't I
oh router Yamaha guitar coffee machine
[Applause]
Skyrim Google improve your lock picking
skills my lock picking skills are really
good now I'm I even already have the
electric one so
I don't see a problem there
[Music]
um
that doesn't mean a good price and
they're not they're not looking for this
one right
no no no no
ah coffee machine wow 350 bucks damn all
right
I even look like a professional burglar
yeah because the way to you know
recognize it whether or not a burglar is
professional or not is if you see them
in a dumpster that's like the most the
most professional burglars bring their
own dumpster and walk around in it
with their legs sticking through at the
bottom
and then whenever someone walks by they
just Crouch and disappear inside the
Dust
haven't you seen you guys should check
when you suddenly you know you see you
want fire Street and you see a dumpster
chances are that there's a burglar in
there and it's a it's a mobile dumpster
[Laughter]
oh man
funny funny
which house should we answer because
that right now we have no requests but I
just want to steal some more things
maybe this one no even though
and this one the guy is like always
around
I feel like it's easier
than the other one because I have I feel
like I have more time in this one
you must steal your money back from the
Austrian government
I don't think I can do that it's like
it's not like I can like you know take
something physical like that
I wish I could
there's vines in the front
wait which ones do you mean you don't
mean the thick bushes right
wait what Vines
where did you see Vines
there's a garage I never checked the
garage
I could just walk in there careful
carelessly a bit
of it
by the door
oh oh but I mean I can reach that window
up there anyway can't I
well now I don't want to go they're
almost coming back
yeah I didn't notice the vines
hmm
okay that's how I'll enter next time
what time again
12 p.m okay
what am I doing
ah
I'm still always so confused in the car
how are you on time
um
I think we'll go
oh I mean the game we can play maybe for
half an hour and then I'll read super
chats for half an hour and then I think
I'll leave it at that
so that I can get some food
and you know
do some more things that I needed to do
all right this way I guess we don't have
to pick the lock
um what do we want to get just all kinds
of things I guess
whatever they have left
yeah Valkyrie with crony
does this fit in my bag no
this fits in my bag so
hurt by a tenant oh
but it's okay I'm gonna take this with
me I'm gonna take this big ass TV I'm
gonna sell it
all right I'll pick that up in a second
um
what's what's worth money
oh
fits in my bag selling it again perfect
I hate the router too
okay okay I'm Gonna Leave
um
I'm a delivery person but when I try to
deliver the tv oh they changed their
mind because I just it just turns out
they thought and they needed an even
bigger one this one wasn't big enough
for them so
I'm gonna be back there soon bringing
them an even bigger TV don't worry
I I don't look back lady don't look back
you don't want to see what you will see
when you look back
that's like that's the biggest TV I've
ever carried carried before
oh baby baby
um
but second I thought the radio was like
a policeman talking to me
when you [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] do you
think you're doing
um deliberate person just delivery
person
that voice
of radio voice
all right
um checking once again
well I got a cheese man too much
television is bad for you and it's even
for wealth redistribution wow
such a good person
oh the never level up which means
another skillful point which means we
get the thing we get this one no wait
that's that's the one we want right
right now on it because we already got
the appraisal
wait don't we do we not have like a
quest right now
uh yeah no he wanted us to learn this
one yeah yeah yeah okay okay
all right hey
Vinnie don't you want to call me
come on call me call me
I'll buy the tools of unnecessarily
glass knife oh and to say
why is the safe cracking tool a
headphone
am I gonna call to save and I'm gonna
ask it more singing you want to play
some Xbox games with me
I need both of these things right
he's probably not gonna call until I
have them both
I need a bit more money maybe we can get
it with a TV and all that kind of stuff
you have now let's play Uno
there's no quests oh 101 when I'm free
oh really we're switching neighborhood
again I mean same neighborhood but like
different houses
um
[Music]
all righty it's time to move on it seems
I'm not gonna buy that stuff yet let me
see what we have here
I think I really need to go back because
the new houses I've been to now don't
seem to have any more candle holders
those were the houses that I did in last
stream that had the candle holders
and
yeah I feel like if I get rid of that
from the list they're gonna ask for new
things at least from the newer houses
so that's one thing I should be doing eh
it's on sale for what that's like
nothing
that is basically getting Dishonored for
free
but that sale might just be for Europe
huh
not for everybody probably
and these things where do you get these
things
are they just
way later in the game because I mean
they they do bring so much money these
things as well or maybe in the safes
maybe these things are going to show up
in the saves
got it for free from Epic
[Music]
good for you
probably in the safe oh
all right okay
still uh gonna sell
[Applause]
let's see how much we get for the big
ass
700 all right I think we're gonna be
able to afford
um
the rest of the tools just fine
when when the guitar
and they keep on restocking the guitar
too so I think those are like easy
money makers
the big books
hey 2500. oh
that's enough I think I think I think I
think
I think so
yes
it's enough
oh now I don't have money for the tenant
routines though
all right let's train this one here what
hold the rotate Direction shown by the
arrows until the tone of the sound
changes then carefully press the proper
direction until the combination is
accepted
oh okay
after that start rotating in the
opposite direction okay what I don't
understand
did it change
yeah
was that okay was that good
that's the proper direction until
combination is accepted so 66 okay
oh what
I understand
slowest wait do I have to type in 66 now
I went too far
ah wait so I know it happens around 66
so around there I should go slower
because it's like immediately over
ah
and now that's ah okay okay
well this might [\h__\h] it up again now
I have to redo it right from the start
so let's go slowly
how far
I didn't even know that this is how
saves work I've never like in hotel
rooms as well there's always saves but
I've never used one before because I
have no idea how how they work how do
you even set your own code
hey
66 78
Havana High School in high school we
just had you know simple locks
you had safes in school
for your locker
what
like this
no combination I know I mean I have
combination locks you know sometimes
just a normal simple key one and
sometimes with like a three different
number wait this is the same principle
okay so I guess so yeah but just with
less numbers that you can choose from
oh
[\h__\h] what what was that anyway
[\h__\h]
it didn't write it down
same concept oh
I wasn't looking
this safe [\h__\h] is gonna take a long time
the things are inside better be worth it
and the tenants better stay away for
their own safety
caves are hard to crack
it seems so
what oh because I was going backwards
I thought we were still
um not there but that was like passing
80 I didn't realize
are you still intentional no no
[Music]
no no no I'm not doing anything
suspicious
how dare you
assume that I am just stealing something
okay and then and then
where did it
where did it uh
two okay
I've got a feeling it's in Greenview
102. 102. be a good debt slave and check
it out for me yep Slave oh that's why
I'm doing all these things because I'm
his depth sleep
cool
wait let me look at my tools do I have
enough yeah okay
all right
one or two did he say I already forgot
it he just told it to me I already
forgot it
they got me out of prison oh I don't
even remember that
well then you see all of this that I'm
doing I'm doing against my will you guys
have to help me
oh
I'm being I'm being like basically
taking hostage I don't want to steal all
these things from these people
I want to be good I wanna after prison
time you know I thought I would I want
to change my life for the better and I
wasn't gonna do any of these Shady
things anymore but I'm being forced to
do it you know
where can I park my car
it saves the no longer safe
true
that is true seriously why can't I put
my card there's a parking spot too far
away can I can I really only put them on
the parking spot
let me try to
anti-debt slave fund thank you thank you
thank you that will help me
I wanna change my life I wanna just
together
the normals want to be normal
is there someone here
what the [\h__\h] that's a children's room
if they have a child
um there's a oh I can enter from here
and there's a dumpster over there all
right let's see is there a child in here
that's so scary but
oh man I'm not gonna hurt your child
don't worry
oh there's someone there
uh how do you how do you unlock
um
until
a person again to know their routine
middle click oh
[Music]
I waited so long
don't don't look
there was a person out there looking out
of the window don't tell them that I'm
that I'm in here you didn't see anything
otherwise I'm gonna steal something from
you next I know
I got caught
the police would tow my car oh okay
let's just load the checkpoint who would
have known that the car was the one
that's gonna
get me in trouble
who would have known
uh one out of two okay well
what do I do about this car
what if I'm like here
it'll still tow it won't they
I just wanna I just want to check the
tenant for a little while because I
don't have money for getting their
routines
um
okay this one I just covered on the side
wonderful
don't look
don't look go somewhere else mind your
own business
oh ah
I I I I I I'm sorry what if I just say
I'm sorry
mommy
the police hurt me please brutality man
it's really getting heart attacks man
all right let's just bring my car
elsewhere do my uh the Discover tenant
routines count even if I reload my
checkpoint probably not huh
okay I'm gonna bring my car down here
even though it's really a far away
just wait till you play a Payday yeah
is it is it much more difficult
it's not a good way of selling me the
game guys with promoting it to me
I want to feel like no really
I want to feel like I can handle it
get to shoot the cops oh okay
I have to protect myself you know
marked
all right
lady let me just Mark you that's all I
wanna do
[Music]
foreign every single time this [\h__\h]
this [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Laughter]
they react so quickly yeah
oh
but
oh man
thank you for the membership renewal
she has a sixth sense for real
crazy
all right one star is gone
they do come with some nice music yeah
it's just weird that it always so
abruptly ends
even though I'm still being looked for
oh no it's okay
lady please let's just oh
take clothes supplies
nah can I open them
all of them
at least on the first no way I lost my
last mine too can you guys tell me
which what they do during the day like
what are you here for your eyes always
open
you look suspicious anyway you must know
something what are you not telling me
what are you not telling me
tell me the thing
god dammit
I'm at least gonna take your headphones
um
[Laughter]
that's all I can take back here [\h__\h]
hell
yoink
do they have Vines too
while I'm here you know I might as well
no
but they're kind of chilling at home
right now
remember not to bring up you know me and
Juliet
I don't even remember what that was
about
kind of want to open
quick
ly
oh when I'm just back here again what a
waste of my tools
[Music]
um
I feel very angry that they do not give
me a chance to do my job
you need a key for this one
I mean I need a key for it
can't break in
hey I guess I have to go through a
window in this case but I can't even the
the blinds are blocking me
[Laughter]
you know there's shitty working
conditions man what the hell
what
can't believe it the way I'm being
treated here in this neighborhood and
they wonder why I am why I break in
their houses if they don't even give me
their key if they don't give me the key
of course I'm gonna break in
I'm gonna give them one star
for other thiefs in our platform you
know I'm gonna give this house one star
because they need a special key for this
one where do I get it from the nerve of
these people yeah
how else
I really have to go for the window
all right you know what
while I'm somewhere here let's go to one
of the
super old houses which one which numbers
were those I think it was 9 10 11.
around there
and find an old toaster
one of them had like literally never
anyone at home
um
which one would have a toaster this one
maybe
let's just open is there someone home
this is the third coat is that a toaster
I want to go for the for the window
now
leave me alone
where's someone who went home here ever
toaster finally I got the oil toaster
it was eluding me is that how you say it
don't know what its problem is remember
when I first was here and I was like
super scared of everything even though
it's like really no big deal
because no one's home
okay you can't even take much so I'll
take this too
that's it that's all I can take
that's it The elusive toaster I'll take
the saucepan too
next time stock up your home a little
bit better so I can get something out of
this okay
your home must be worth breaking into
otherwise what am I supposed to do
much
oh
there's someone actually here
okay not worth it I'm just gonna bring
back my toaster
ah
I need money though I need money
oh discovered well
which houses are these have I been on
this one before
108 oh yeah wait it's The
107 108 ones
I'm familiar with these houses right
this is getting confusing
I've been on this one before I think
your toaster or your life
the whole they left behind was a toaster
I wonder where they went must have gone
to some vacation home or so in the
Bahamas
I got the huge TV from there
um
okay
I'm gonna do you all a favor and leave
now
[Applause]
I'm doing you
do you do you
soy milk soy milk say soy milk
feel the same
you know I said cooking will take so
much time but I kind of want to eat the
thing that I would cook today apparently
my recipe that I would be making today
would be
um a pulled chicken burger with some
kind of saute
uh dressing or sauce or so or something
like that
sounds really yummy and interesting
but hmm
effort required
pulled chicken yeah I'm gonna pull you
apart
I need the candle holders to me I should
go back to that house
that had the candle holders
we're done with the kitchen
okay let's look for these vases remember
this guys
remember this vase and these glass cups
they want some more
and The Tear trophy remember all of this
place
I saw your trophy in one of the 107 or
108 as well I think
but I want to find one more candle
holder triple and two single ones and
maybe the vases as well
remember it saute really tasty yeah
wasn't that something like with peanuts
thingy I ate that in Indonesia didn't I
didn't like
[Applause]
wait what was that sign on my on the
street
wait a second welcome do they have
they
there's no way
that
they have Patrol police patrol now
um
what is it son
what is this
what does it mean
what do the what do the icons mean Mason
don't worry I'm not gonna
go to 108 10 no wait not that one what
am I talking about I want to go to the
houses that I did last stream
because we have the
couple of the things that I'm looking
for like the candle holders
okay okay
no I need the money right now
I'm broke
I ate some saute from an Indonesian
stall today
um
that sounds delicious street food city
oh yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum
Miller's
[Music]
I wonder which one I should go for
this one the Jones
or the Jones here
bedroom bedroom bedroom bedroom bedroom
bedroom bedroom
kitchen bedroom bedroom bedroom garage
oh
gosh I'll try
I don't know which one has the
uh
that was a thing but oh well
uh sleep
what was it 8 am
I tried making the peanut sauce from Ali
no but apparently it's one of the one of
my recipes from for this week
from hellofresh beep
oh okay oh yeah these houses they're
tricky they have three floors all of
them
what
I am not a newcomer here
this isn't my first rodeo yeah
apparently it is
um
go back in
what did I come here for uh
for the thingies for the thing is
those the single one's nice nice
was this the base that I needed as well
I think so the tall one though not the
wide one I think
lady is where is Lady Lady down there
aren't there both of them there
should have been only one
why is there a dinosaur here why is
there a T-Rex there
that's dangerous
what is that
camera
okay
it looks like they're like two people
out there but must be from different
house
very confusing
an affair oh Nani
can I get oh interesting painting one
more
vase please
wait a second let me check really quick
ah scared uh Jones
bedroom bedroom toilets kitchen bathroom
okay
uh okay okay I think she didn't get up
because of me
um even though she heard me that was
just her routine
yeah because she's in the toilet now
then she goes she's going to the kitchen
um
kitchen wait isn't the kitchen upstairs
is she gonna panic when she sees that I
opened the door
um we'll see I guess
um
where is she she's still standing there
she's she should be coming up next for
the kitchen
oh she's so
she's so supposedly well how long is
that minute
oh I'm playing such risky games
[Music]
pocket money
still doing toilet but ours should be
over soon
what
wait
no it's a downstairs kitchen oh
wait there is no kitchen here
kitchen here
okay I might just come back here
um
another time I'll take the speaker now
can I put two speakers in my trunk
at this point you know I'm I'm just like
you know
I'll just take whatever I can't give me
that
no no no no no
broken speaker not nah don't worry
anything can be fixable can be fixed
anything
ah
it's so refreshing such a nice day out
perfect day to do some beefing our
fingers will fit both of them
[Music]
gotta pull inventory I can put my things
on the card uh the Box inside and maybe
go inside one more time if I still got
time thank God these cars don't count as
Patrol
the right weather to break the law
exactly don't you also feel like that
sometimes
today this is today no I can't
uh
not too bad okay
that's unfortunate it looks like it
could still fit but okay logic
nah you know what I better drive home
once so I can
sell these things once sorry driving
over the speaker
what oh it's your purpose for my car oh
no oh no oh
um
can someone push my car please
once someone please have an innocent
Fame
oh God they're gonna report me for
suspicious activity
wait wait I'm gonna drive for the trees
there you go
right now every cent matters
I'm broke
okay loopy feet no I'm not new here
anymore these are my streets I own these
streets
that's really well that I took so much
time but I guess I also took so much
home
yata
uh all right here we go 240 for that
that's really good
uh we need another one of those vases
and we need a triple oh baby a triple
nothing new in kitchen
nothing here okay
ah yeah I want the tenant routines from
the valley Williams eventually
because I gotta go to the Williams in
the 101.
okay
well
how was your time
what do you mean
my crony was my crony I guess I'll find
out later today
love feeding all the same if you know
play the game
houses all locked up inside what how
does it go on after then
hahaha
play the game I forgot how my song goes
welcome even though I sang it a million
times by now
is this the immediately the chorus
Golden Goblet yeah landline yeah camera
yeah the faces I'll keep
at least the tall one
I'm feeling uh sick right now why am I
being sick
ah
let me eat my muffin
um
it's so good
it has this self-made taste to it but
it's like a good self-made taste
oh
maybe some stressed yeah
oh first sick
I copied the muffins I always eat [\h__\h]
like this I'm used to it
hmm
um
what the hell
what am I doing next
let me just
I know we don't have much time here
what I really want
the second base
that's all I want really
don't tell me what you wanted
what I really really want I wanna I
wanna I wanna I wanna I wanna really
really wanna Really Wanna Get That Base
oh
hurt me
she's not gonna come checking right
now
oh yeah where was that base
originally
was it somewhere here on this floor
was it ah it was here they don't restock
it
um
Apple face I'll take it
they don't restock the face that I want
ah
that is very done then
very sad
in that case
take the receiver
oh
I've been to this place a hundred times
by now
off screen too
it's just too easy they will never learn
what the [\h__\h]
even when they hear me they don't come
looking for me
so weird
I never take the globe I wonder
three bucks now
really free box
hey
maybe you could leave a note of what
things you want to see likes yeah maybe
they'll be considerate about it when I
take the kiss wait how much did it say
it's worth
put it down
okay
70 bucks
um
I don't know for an item that I have to
carry like that
maybe there's a better option
[Applause]
can I take the car yet why can I not
take the car yet come on it's time it's
time
don't no time to waste
I just wanna
move on with my life become an even
better Thief
cheeky
very cheeky all right I'll take it
I'll take this one
silver plant you can steal the plants
it probably wouldn't be worth that much
all right if this is 77 70 bucks this
one's oh
I kind of praise the speaker why
it's detected
oh okay we're good it was just that one
that one person
huh
where's my painting
okay
well no sometimes they're just hard to
see ah there it is it Blended in with
the scenery
no no
no not leaving without this painting now
it may not bring the big big bugs but
still it doesn't matter
I've made up my mind
once I Got My Mind Set On something
I will not back
uh up what back down
it brings some bucks so
better than nothing
all right
going back again
no I think I actually already met my
um
time quota
didn't I say I would be super chatter
Super Chat rating now
you guys
why do not remind me it's already time
oh another asprank I keep on getting us
ranks now damn
no vase though I don't think I can
get anything right now
addiction too fast
all right you is it really my addiction
too fast or is it your addiction to me
guys now
Chad kept asking about the time
I I didn't think that 30 minutes would
go by that fast what the hell
both
ah welcome
we're in sync
oh
candle holder why do I sell I got ah I
took them again didn't I
holy [\h__\h]
I guess we'll leave it at that for today
that's that was almost three hours
[Music]
um
do still feel kind of weirdly sick what
is it well why am I why I've been
drinking water
I've been drinking water what do I need
to do I need to cook
I need to get ready
yeah it's probably better if I ended
here give myself a little bit more time
even if it's just 15 minutes
ah
I wanna Thief more but but but but this
game is becoming too easy for me maybe
we really need to move on to like Hitman
um
I'm too good for this game
although I wonder
how far can I get in the game like
what's what's the end game
and what how far am I from finishing
this game because I wasn't planning on
finishing it but
is it possible to finish this game like
the main Vinnie storyline or so
there's an end
I wonder how far I am from it
um
I gotta look it up you will be the one
the first one to finish it
that would be funny
I I I I don't expect myself either to
get so deep into it I really just got it
because it was so cheap I didn't expect
to enjoy it so much oh God the more
attack I feel the more sick I feel
oh
I hope I'm not like actually sick that
would ruin my weekend
um please just move on to Hitman what
what's the problem with this game
it's good
fun
yeah I will skip the Super Chat reading
though
oh what's your problem with this game
there's a sequel coming out yeah I saw I
saw
I'm gonna I think lay down a little bit
maybe four
an hour
no not sleeping but just laying down so
maybe I feel better
um
this game is getting a sequel yeah I'm
gonna play it Fifth simulator two
when it comes out I will play it I'll be
the first one
maybe he's just hungry low blood sugar
can make you feel nauseated I'm gonna
get something to eat something proper
or cook myself I'll think about it
maybe I can
freeze the chicken
and then cook it when I'm back because I
do want to cook it myself but not today
[Music]
um
when you freeze a chicken what's like do
how should I freeze it is it okay to
freeze it now I wonder because I had it
in the fridge for a couple days but it's
still
still before its expiration date
I think I'll take it out of the very
gently think I'll take it out of the
plastic though first right it has like a
a plastic
bag that's that it is in and it's like
I wonder if I should take it out first
and put it into a keep it in
but then how do I
oh I guess if I want to unfreeze it I
put it in the fridge to like slowly
um
deep freeze follow it
okay okay
if you had eaten something a week old
and feel sick do you really have to ask
why you randomly feel sick huh
what did I eat that was a week old
I don't remember did I say something
what do you mean
who's that Dad
giant mod
wasn't the chicken that old what
chicken
what chicken
you mean the chicken I'm talking about
right now huh
what what I don't remember there may
have been something like that like with
two three weeks ago or so when I
mentioned
something did I
the muffins that my brother brother ate
were only two days old and they were in
the fridge for most of the time
they weren't a week old
I've got one guy over your food
yeah there was that there was an egg
right that I um put into the burger that
I made
the burger patty
but that's like
it's quite a long time ago and nothing
happened after that yeah
[Music]
that's like two weeks ago three weeks
ago
well maybe it felt like more recently
the egg pass it that is it did pass the
water test and for my muffins I used
fresh eggs so pretty
I just didn't want to waste the
the older eggs
okay I'll go get some food for myself
and I think I'll put the chicken in the
freezer if the other ingredients are
gonna
be able to keep themselves for a little
while
alrighty sorry guys I need to rest
I don't feel so well I'm gonna hide and
sleep in my dumpster if there's
something you need just knock on my
dumpster okay
but try not to trying to relax in here
okay and then German we say I'll be
dancing thank you for watching I'll see
you on chromeo's channel and um next
week hopefully on Monday
okay
I love you guys I'm gonna miss you
bye bye thank you guys so much for the
assets too I love them
bye bye
what's up yo
Mata okay
bye bye
uh
comfy getting comfy in my dumpster
[Music]
foreign
all right
all right nice movie
no
no why um
[Music]
hello
wow
talking to me telling me a story
[Music]
good story
I love cartoon
[Music]