[Music]
[Applause]
me
intoxicating DJ keep play
[Music]
dancing so emot
feel it R me
[Music]
feel R me
me
there feel it right BR me
[Music]
oh
honey night is
[Music]
feel it R for me
like
intoxicating DJ keep
[Applause]
playing dancing
emotion
[Music]
feel it rush through me
feel it
R feel it like me
I
[Music]
e DF e DF
ef
ef KF p e
DF EF KF B
EF KF B
[Music]
louder I can't hear
you where's your motivation
Cadet that's
[Music]
right oh my chat is
weird
K wait what's with my
chat
o
oops K Kitty what's wrong with
this K let me try this
one this one this one's better k k sorry
for the wait I had problems many many
many problems I think it's fine now do I
sound normal I think I sound fine I
fixed it ah welcome to sponsor stream
this stream is sponsored this to be
clear but I am very very happy and
honored to be sponsored for uh such a
funl looking game oh my God Earth
Defense Force 6 it's apparently been
uh you know quite a few additions by now
and I am I am honed to be part of this
lineup with go AKA
gura and
Iris i i as you can see here in the
[Music]
screen uh well one question before we
get started I have my controller ready
but is this is this better to play with
uh with keyboard I actually don't know
I've never played this
before should I play this is this okay
with
keyboard on PC yeah yeah cuz I'm on PC
and if you guys are keyboard is better
okay good okay okay then let
me disconnect my controller um what was
I going to say oh yeah so uh today we're
going to play some solo but well I'm
also going to be playing um with you
guys hopefully uh I hope it
works um but it's a PC version I think
if you're not with the PC version you
might not be able to do it oh is chat
kind of weird
no yeah so I hope you guys got the game
ready to help me are there any
experienced Earth Defense Force players
in the chat who can give me advice and
everything
it's not
competitive is not
okay we keep disappearing yeah I don't
know what's wrong with chat today I'm
having too many issues here and
there uh I can give you encouragement
shouldn't I be the one giving you guys
encouragement uh it's Co-op yeah yeah
it's PV not PVP oh yeah yeah yeah but
still I don't know it's still
intimidating
so as you can see uh in this picture
there is free oh maybe I should let you
hear the music it's so loud there's free
little decoys that you can get with the
pre-order uh early purchase bonus early
purchase bonus doesn't have to be
pre-order
um sure and I asked for the date how
long it's available apparently it's
available until uh this year's
Christmas
midnight local
time midnight Christmas so you have
still some time to get us a lot of time
actually uh looking forward to having
you guys play the game with me
apparently uh some of you guys already
are on it and it's really cute because I
recorded So Many voice lines for this I
want you guys to hear it we'll get a
little taste of it today I think but
yeah it's been finally released I think
two days ago uh and yeah let's get a
let's get a taste for it but if if chat
is so broken anyway should I just do
full
screen
maybe maybe
maybe oh I didn't do anything
yet okay let's hide
this where is this what is this hide
this
hide chat and hide
this whoa I'll make myself smaller
too wow today in 3D where where's a good
place to go maybe here I think Iris was
here Iris was
here how's this work call sign what's a
call sign is that a military
term and
gaha usually I go by Wawa but today I go
by
gaha what is that a big gecko
okay so uh I want to get used to the
game controls so I'll first play offline
I think solo start offline game one
player gather items strength from the
player character and clear all the
missions tutorial mission available at
the beginning okay I think we have to
play the
tutorial uh okay let's get into it solid
frog first missions tutorial okay in the
year 2022 that's not so long ago a
cluster of spaceship suddenly appeared
in the Earth's orbit Humanity soon
learned that they did not come in peace
the first strike was premeditated and
precise in just one day half of the
world's military bases were destroyed
leaving the humans all but
defenseless but but there is defense the
Earth Defense Force W happened two years
ago maybe I'm a little bit I'm later
with the stream than I thought I was
they were visitors from another planet
people called them the pride primers oh
in the struggle that ensued it seemed
that it would only be a matter of time
before the human race was wiped out
until the Special Forces team storm
destroyed the alien mother ship and
admidst the chaos the primers left
earth
oh they
left that's good right huh yeah peace
has seemingly returned seemingly the
past two years of war had ravaged the
planet reducing the human population by
90% what that's barely anyone left
civilization was on the verge of
collapse nevertheless the survivors
struck out upon the road to recovery
soon another three years passed oh so
we're in 2025 now quick math quick math
sooy oh okay you guys really have to
help me I have no idea how to play this
uh uh do I just start Mission do I have
to do something here I I think I have to
be a ranger uh to to use my
decoy I think that said yeah yeah
Ranger but were we already Ranger
anyway should I change something here we
have a broken PA 11 Broken that will get
us far a grenade launcher okay a nice
backpack and no support equipment really
oh
no is this the ranger explanation change
the backpack I don't I don't have
anything else for now I think infantry
Special Forces Rangers are combat
experts who can handle a wide range of
weapons they are also licensed to
operate military vehicles on the
battlefield oh we can drive vro scroll
over oh
[Music]
oh oh the backpack is
me menu Scrolls
horizontal kiaha y we have gura Irish
and kiaha level eight uh-huh we start at
a higher level cool this Soldier class
is the easiest to use and has the
highest combat strength ooh if you are
playing the game for the first time you
should start out by choosing this
Soldier class okay can I change my color
to Orange oh I
can what is this ah okay okay cool I'm a
bit more orange
now adjust
armor what's this don't know what that
is orange and teal M I wish I could
color everything but yeah like this it's
not I don't know if I don't know if this
is teal but something close to
it oop okay
okay Wing diver no Ranger okay so I
chose the Ranger and now start
mission base 251 reest for
reinforcements from base 251 head in
their Direction
immediately okay can we stop with
easy winning battles of breze in this
mode um but you're unlikely to find any
worthwh weapons select this mode when a
mission is too hard for you can I start
with easy 10% of normal damage your
attacks don't knock your allies down oh
okay oh here we have friendly
ah oh no there's friendly fire damage in
everything but this is like still the
least Troublesome we'll do normal next
time first baby
mode I once said long ago there is hope
oh
Iris I'm sure she felt like they were
speaking to her there and it's true why
because we are still here we
are idiot idiot
idiot you're not going to say it oh
hello you kept me waiting don't worry me
like that sorry I know I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry sponsor s for
being late move by pressing okay yeah
this is uh intuitive oh they have they
have drinks over
there how do how do I move the camera
angle you just got here
huh yeah well you made it just in
time okay let's good ah there we
go oh what are you what are you
selling oh I can climb up there
oh do you have ice
tea okay I'll follow you that's a lot of
boxes what's in them whole life
merchandise they should make the
EDF girls uh our our figurines our
little thingies decoys they should make
them into real merch figurines
sell them sell them not acrylic stands
no figurines threedimensional figurines
please thank you for waiting for me at
every corner you're so nice what's
What's his name
anyway bobbleheads they got a wiggle
true we're kind of
wobbly I already saw like previews from
when you guys started playing it two
days ago and it's really
cute it's really
cute nice base you got here
guys hey I want to move I want to
follow I want to follow you here come
this way yeah I was trying
to why did I stop following
you cool music by the way you made it
out
alive do you have any idea how relieved
I am a H he likes me and you were on the
front lines the whole time yeah I guess
so I can't believe you surv I I am I I
am a frontliner not only
that you really outdid yourself this
time but now the music is getting kind
of you shot down a command romantic and
saved the
world do you have any idea how relieved
I am that you're
alive I'm so worried about you made
serve you well H maybe it's broken I
think can you repair it
please we have much to
discuss where to begin at the
beginning who is that is he going to
Captain has arrived Captain my Captain
we'll have
time okay oh why around scum scum line
up that's that's my
line oh oh I I actually have to oh over
there over there yeah okay all
right this is base
251 here we are currently dealing with a
major issue
honey the fact that you're the captain
and not me we're short on Personnel what
I should be enough for 500 people we
don't have enough soldiers and it's
affecting our ability to complete our
duties D so we contacted a few other
bases and requested that they send us
their elite soldiers I'm Elite no am I
not good enough for you and how did they
reply they sent us you maggots instead
huh not an elite soldier in sight this
is not how you talk to a c Beo number
one you lot aren't even soldiers at all
I will fire you once I get to a rank
where I can fire you tell me what
pitiful jobs you worked up until
yesterday the frer kitchen management
sir you were a cook
wait he's also starting today what about
you what about you I was a research why
am I not online a scientist I like how
he uses fancy words in to to sum it up I
enlisted five days ago sir up until then
I drove a truck for you a truck that's
enough what don't disrespect the truck
driver soldiers you're not soldiers at
all didn't ask me you never shot or been
shot at you can't fight let alone
protect yourselves useless cowards
that's what you are H you know nothing
about me sir
nothing but Beggars can't be choosers
we'll take what we can get so mean I'm
so insulted if you're useless then we'll
just have to make you
useful you guys would be nothing without
truck drivers who would deliver all this
stuff here
huh starting now we're going to reform
you inres thoroughly thly
do you understand
yes sir yes
sir the Invaders backed off EDF saved
Earth and humankind
wonderful do you know what that
means no our forces are necessary to our
people everyone wants the same thing a
peaceful calm existence where they
aren't constantly being threatened the
people depend on us for thatat
threatened difficult we are responsible
for countless lives a heavy burden to
bear yeah you need to be ready to face
hell woo in this life and the next to
fulfill your duty yeah do you understand
I
understand 3 years ago civilization was
on the brink of Destruction now on our
recover covering planet we are the
Defenders of peace on Earth never forget
this sworn Duty
never yes
sir defend the city defend its people
are you
ready will you carry out your duty I
will carry the duty will you carry out
your duty I will carry the [\h__\h] out of
it then let's go let's go
wow nice intro very motivating can I
shoot my friend we will teach you how to
shoot a gun oh I can't shoot at all some
like you should be able to pull a
trigger oh I know I know how to pull a
trigger I know I know let's go let's go
why do I go last run run run run run
where to go go go why do we start in the
middle of our
bunker oh
can I shoot from here no not yet I'm
using the broken PA I guess it's not
that broken after all
oh come up front me sir yes sir now
him why not
[Music]
me did he do
it you're last come on just like in the
spelling be I'm always last
always have to watch
everybody destroy four doets
okay what what it's so inaccurate wa I
destroy completely ah okay okay
okay it's inaccurate cuz it's broken
maybe hey thank you not my first time
this rodeo Oh R to
reload more wasn't that already four
press Mouse wheel to switch weapons what
the [\h__\h] is that grenade launcher W wa
thought it was a red
lasso
W destroy all Targets okay I miss kind
of hard to tell
H oh no what I think the circle is
around
it
okay okay ah going I get it now Okay
Yahoo Yahoo oh
n use backpack equipment with f key
wa oh wait there was no Wawa move left
right and SP perform emergency
avoidance what does that mean Dodge I'm
a
natur la is a
grenade press left shift to
dash oh he takes a moment though put
down your weapon during Dash focus on
your Fe what focus on my
[Music]
feet I like the zomies I'm having the
Zoomies okay I'm lined up how do I
switch weapons again mouse wheel right
that's enough for today eh I was just
going to
excited a
bit you will become soldiers Defenders
of humanity am it's anable job however
it comes with Duty and responsibility
why is he fighting in a suit s s
sir why is he fighting in this enemy
Invaders damn
punks time to work get ready where where
where where I'll take care of these
Invaders scum don't worry it'll be an
easy
job dress for the job you want
wa oh miss C already
cool okay that was tutorial Mission easy
to
tutal nice beginner
friendly I got nothing from it okay uh a
second let's go normal then that wasn't
even necessary to put it on easy in that
mission cuz nothing really we didn't
have a real fight time to take out the
invad trash come on Invader trash
okay where are they defend the city do
your duty I'm will not only defend the
city I will defend the world the earth
the earth I love Earth ass Earth s s I
love
us wow oh no the
reality the Invaders are here find them
at a oh I see them on the map I guess so
the Red
Arrows you really think you can do this
oh I need to stay with them huh IED at
the base doco where are
you not much of a city left
Y what city was this do we
know oh no oh
no
what take them out it's a huge get go
simp if they look like they'll put up a
fight shoot them wait where did it go
out there it Blends in with the city I
don't think I can reach it from
here can we reach it from here with
the them oh I
can oh oh oh oh oh oh but how do I how
do I rolling
a
okay they they bleed purple
no fear I am not scared ah
kill oh yeah let's
go is he dead yet let's get this one too
oh no I missed I missed oh yeah
yeah oh my God there's
more I'm
stuck I'm stuck
how much ammo can I run out of ammo 114
P oh my God y juicy
meat uh what where are they shooting oh
over there let's give another big big
bullet in your face get out of my way
wait wait wait wait wait wait where you
going
don't another one yeah oh the buildings
are falling a part two unlimited ammo
except for your Maxine size aha okay
okay so I will not run out but I have to
reload okay okay
okay uh wait there's another is still
alive oh now it's dead oh this is
fun I like how they
explode very beautiful oh first aid and
armor do I get to keep it for the next
fights
too let let me pick that up might be
valuable
oh oh it's
dead we did it you never get used to war
no matter how many battles You'
survived I can press f for wcoy really I
already have W
decoy but maybe I think we're done oh no
there's more okay there more but let's
let's get to them and then we could
place it probably I'll
try show the invaders no mercy
understood they don't even understand
Mercy they don't speak our
language you're so far I could Dash I
think dashing like this will they also
Dash that's why they fight so
desperately
okay wait F
doesn't talk to
me you can do it I can do
it B Believes In Me B cute elimin all
enemies eliminate all enemies can I make
her
louder I'm already here you don't have
to recruit me while I'm already
recruited the moment when I was born I
was recruited by you
waa waa protect me do I have to throw
them like
EF is it okay if she's further away
EDF more please all right if I see
anybody under ah underneath you what you
skirt why would anybody do
that we got respect for our tal right
guys we wouldn't look under the
skirt oh get him get him get him get him
get
him I think I think he's dead I think
he's dead
oh big one big one big
one I can barely hear her it's too
chaotic can I make her
louder is there like a
decoy uh maybe if I lower bgm a little
bit is she C SE e or voice volume voice
volume is like
maximum if I up
this and low
this I think she's voice
okay then wa then what I can do is hide
get the master higher and the rest lower
basically
but why is bgm still so
loud
okay
okay I don't know if it changed wa I
can't hear you where are you waah wa
T P I need your
motivation cheers oh no
there's one close to her I
her I hear her it clear T General Cadet
we are looking for you yeah she's
looking for me only for me oh no she's
getting
shot he Y where is it it's like behind
or on top of this how do I how do I get
it can I shoot through here oh the
a y y y where am
I I got stuck I had to shoot myself out
of
it oh okay okay okay they're coming for
me oh y it y
it drop me some health items
please wa wa
wa I think she's dead
she's
dead
[Music]
wa okay she may be dead I have
to help my other recruits
Cadets ah I have her back okay okay okay
wait I think this battle isn't so long
anymore
though can I can I reach ah
[Music]
close again
again she protect
me let's
go let's do this they don't have a shred
of Honor I did it we're currently
seeking candidates yeah download the
game now install buy and install again
now go go go let him know
the can I carry her to the next location
don't let them taint our city leave no
one behind she says but I'm leaving her
behind start battle ah how do I bring
her or do I not have to bring her
monthly pay is being increased now it's
a good time that's not true that's not
true guys don't trust her monthly pay is
not being increased
can speak them on on
soldiers to reload
her okay I got her back in the inventory
now I need to wait for her to recharge
okay okay okay
okay I hear the aliens
talk that's
freaky Invaders
detected there Invaders I see them
very
clearly although that one went down from
the
roof can I
reach yeah I think
so no oh
nooc here we go yes
sir now we
go oh yeah oh yeah let those limbs fly
oh you brought your
friend maybe we can reason with
un doesn't seem like they' listen
anyway protect the are the blue dots on
the screen something
hurry keep theage to
Min friendliness ah okay can I see
Health packs on the map maybe not oh the
green ones ah okay the green
ones are you guys okay
what's wrong with you
guys don't take a break
now we're almost
there
beautiful don't expect much support look
at those legs I'm not the best Marksman
is this what happened to frog cut out to
be a
soldier will be shocked at this sight in
me who believes in you we can do this
yes cute Invader activity detected
placing bait better than any eliminate
the Invaders and restore peace to the
city who's this who's this cute
girl what more wa wa come with me I'll
pack you up packing you
up now she's in my backpack again how
such a big WWA fits into my tiny
backpack I don't know this is just how
game physics
work do not question
it what the Frog's doing we're going to
fight right of course oh no they're
attacking they're all going in One
Direction what are they what what is
there can I
[Music]
reach oh right
baby on
my the only civilians that seem to be
left alive is us
anyway
oh come
on oh when I killed him right here in
the middle I can make Ro uh hot pots cuz
they're already
falling like cut up sliced up into the
soup we just got to heat it up and then
we have nice
spinner yummy
[Music]
yeah I got his
foot y but they're dropping all the all
the like Health stuff and and so on in
there aren't they uh-oh let's kill one
on the
outside then maybe he'll drop something
for
me did he drop something yeah yeah yeah
yeah let's go move that leg out of the
way ow there's something else there I
think but I can't see
it take me in of take
me give me some of that I I'm I'm
guessing I should not touch the water oh
I don't know pretty
[Music]
good okay
she looks
happy yes I can shoot myself let's
go nice work are we done saf in the city
citizens can rest easy here we
go
yeah
C she is happy to be there I'm happy
that he's
there y
[Music]
amazing you don't take environmental
damage in this game oh okay so I could
enter the water but I wonder how deep it
is nice very
nice the city is empty yeah it's just
us what does this mean I got a new
shotgun Slaughter
E20 okay I I I I like the one I I had
though that was fine too Cascade zero a
new rocket launcher but you yeah I
probably want to use the the new ones I
have
right old shotgun got better
uhhuh pick up the green chest to get
more
weapons it was a bit chaotic here and
there so I couldn't see uh too many of
them especially when I was cooking all
the frogs in the in the hot pot water
uh let's
see so we can switch to
this oh almost
kfp
damage
a
[Music]
range this has an insane range oh cuz
it's a sniper
rifle a
rocket launcher ah wait I was using a
grenade launcher right I could try one
of
these hiana fried frog sounds perfect
that's what I'm
[Music]
doing I wonder which one's better this
has a lot more
damage reload
time blast radius h
capacity
two let's try it let's try it Grant is
good okay okay
okay do I have anything
here
no
okay then let's do another
[Music]
one standard Mission we're cracking down
on enemy Invaders we're keeping the town
safe because that's our job
exactly here we
go defend the city let's
go Earth Defense Force drive out the
Invaders where are they oh around the
corner you know the rules so do I
bastard shoot it you know the rules and
so do I the aliens are just trying to
survive on Earth do we really need to
fight them it why is he so I want to let
them live on earth too I used to think
the same thing until they killed my War
you wanted to let these huge giant frogs
live on
earth
themet
oh it goes like PE
PE your
home hello there you were hiding behind
your body I'm not going to drop Wawa
just yet
cuz this is just the first
wave not many frogs
yet it's a
shotgun wow it goes so
far okay he's
dead good job me Pat me on
shoulder good job me now we just have to
wait for things to get better did it die
on top of the roof
there we humans even fight blow it up so
I can get the items Al conflict is
guaranteed armor and health time for
work y'all let's go where are you guys
going oh up there oopsie what was that
oh those damn aliens we don't have time
for this crawl back to the we don't have
time for this that isn't this like all
we do all
day what else do we have to do besides
taking down frogs and making frogs we're
in no to fight fighting among ourselves
and ex why are they going the other way
how
foolish I I feel like I feel like
they're going the other way ow whoa
where is the Frog can't believe it's
come to this someone like me in battle
shouldn't I be seeing the Frog it
doesn't matter who you are as as you
FR ah there it is Target
acquired it's time to
die oh he's dead
without going
inare to I like this uh what is it not a
grenade launcher a rocket launcher right
I like it out of w did he just shoot he
he dead he's pretty dead but he's still
shooting very very motivated frog we
should recruit him good
work life is a so tough huh frog tastes
like chicken right it's not that weird
that in this in this kind of Apocalypse
world we can't fry it a moners has we
fry frogs we got to take what we can get
we'll be there right away okay oh my God
that's a lot with the Enemy Invaders
late the
moners wait is that the same
thing Invaders and monsters exterminate
the monsters wipe them out are they
coming
why don't they
Dash guys you're not letting me go alone
right be prepared they're so slow
bad oh
ants
[\h__\h] Roger oh
no reload reload that's probably it
doesn't need a it doesn't need a whole
rocket the mon spit where should I place
Wawa let me let me rep Place
her can I throw her like
that let's go that's me that's me that's
my
voice EDF
[Music]
[Applause]
EF holy moly oh my
oh oh w w okay now I understand why it's
so many because they're somewhat reing
to take
down oh my God they're like
[Music]
everywhere can I fry these
H H how do cute ants
taste what do they taste
like armor is there any green ones any
gun
thingies don't touch him don't touch
him is he gone yeah okay I protect you I
attack and I
protect e e e e e e e e e e e e if I see
anybody peing under you know where you
go
oh now it hurts yay believe in me they
we're really excited to hear
that if I see anybody peeking underneath
my legs you know where you're going yeah
usual room let's
go damn it extermination team slacking
again I bet it's those guys from out
east how many times have they done
talking to herself should I pack her up
you will take a test for listing
maybe the monsters are multiplying
faster than the extermination teams can
take them
out monsters there are more of them nice
the won't be sa until exterminate the
that's that looks like a whole another
bunch of
ants there are too many of them damn
extermination follow me
kfp competent we need to protect us the
monsters travel undergr
always otherwise laas will be very
sad this is our can I climb over it
sucks oh yeah it is what it is
Exterminating monsters is our primary
tastes like shell
shellfish I'm not a fan of the before we
lose any
citizens people didn't see that coming
huh that's good news here
W let's go let's go let's go attack
in the front
line all
along to All Enemies W and wa Dream Team
don't need anybody
else
reload oh god oh no oh God why are you
g don't touch it don't touch it don't
take her she's T stay
Al oh that's green that's green that's
green taking that
home Cadet where are you in these trying
times I'm recruiting all of you now you
see you see we need you you can't let us
Hing
now let me here you want to
get baby I'm not alone anymore they're
over there took you a damn
while what a
massacre nice aame moving closer from
here wait why what
that why what
that
no who did that which ant did that oh
who whoa whoa
whoa where were you when waa was killed
to the left got it I was on the
battlefield this why I ha if you weren't
on the battlefield that means it's your
fault nice
aim come on get
wrecked hey I'm helping okay
me destroying the buildings may not look
like the the smartest thing to
do uh but I'm
helping I wonder is there another wave
coming that I'm going to drop Wawa again
closer to the
wave I was stuck at
home closer you didn't protect me when I
needed you the most
now they know what we're made Y show
from monsters are emerging from
underground W [\h__\h] oh no the other
direction don't back down okay I'm
coming I'll be the first anyway probably
these damn monsters are planning on
nesting here not on my
watch defend the city protect the people
oh my
God call extermination team
extermination what I actually do does
she bu
everybody
ho I don't know what is Shing
anymore oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my God
I was a little bit too close it
seems freaking nice
explosion so
much I'm going to be bringing lots of
presents home
tonight not according to K
ah it's okay it's okay it's okay it's
okay it's all Kaku no this was not
Kaku what
happened did the ant get
you I made my oh no I must avenge
her okay but there's only two ants left
why did she have to die so so close to
the
end she could have made it if I was a
little a little bit
faster good job right let me pick up
thingss look what a peaceful City a
perfect place to
live really really you mean
that yeah Mission clear not a
problem
y
yippee oh I got a lot of new stuff
we got KF F50 mg1 grenade launcher um1
reverser new oh okay these are new these
are I don't know
upgrade oh we got something for a fener
as well blast hole
spare
yippee
yipp yipp yipp yipp y yipp yipp yipp
yipp
wow so we can upgrade again something
nicer uh
although burner and reverser gas burner
for welding
oh Special M special uh piece of
equipment that sprays Nano machines oh I
don't think I need either of these do I
what am I going to do with that no okay
I'll keep the the slaughter for now
then yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and and I
think also this is fine for now isn't it
do you guys want to hear go a little bit
yet I think if you want to hear iris's
decoy she has a a four four plus hour
stream so you can probably hear her a
lot here but I think
GAA has not been heard much
yet so let's do something with [\h__\h]
ball top priority extermination order
today's job is Exterminating monsters
you keep the civilians safe there's no
days off for this job got it I know it's
a 24/7 job I'm so ready for
it Go exterminate the monsters let's go
let's go
woohoo all monsters an are to be
exterminated I hope GA likes ants
because she will be surrounded by them
oh wait they're closer than I thought
arees than which way are we going guys
which way are they
going what is the extermination team
even doing uh we're already on
Route let's get some buildings out of
the way the Al and now we're monsters
when do we get arrest cuz I can't let
see we won one battle but it just never
ends monsters detected
oh what well what terminate
them where where oh it's
ants yo
Landscaping yeah yeah yeah yeah I mean I
can't I can't fight like this I need to
see my targets goodbye let's go over
time goby
use your Trident and help
me oh she slipped on the ant shoes you
take a
test for more information please your
fight no promoting now we need your help
we need you to
fight go go help me
ef
ef what happens if I pull that shark
tail let me pull that shark tail
[Music]
oh me what she died fast wait wait wait
wait wait that was not what I wanted I
was just tickling her a little
bit sorry GA I'll make it up to you the
people can't live safely like this
she'll be back soon there are more
monsters around here somewhere we need
to exterminate them all it's the arrows
are showing me to go that way uh to the
rest of the
team but that's not where the monsters
are mon I should be the leader of Team
you got that not that dude yes sir with
all due respect this city no longer has
any people she hates her day one day the
city will
be I don't as we keep I love her she was
teasing me yesterday wasn't
she but I appreciate it now I don't mind
her teasing me I tease her back we won
the war but I didn't do so badly did I
yesterday in the spelling being Humanity
will rise it seems like many people were
surprised about the aqueduct spelling
seem brighter it was so
funny cuz people were
like oh my God she's sabotaging crony N
All N all
uhuh why would I do that she say she
helps me I'll help her back you
know I would never sabotage Bry it was
so funny every time she spoke when her
little Muppet thingy uh moved it looked
so funny to
me I know my waterways I know them but
then I'm just happy I could help crony
you know that was oh my that was my
purpose there are monsters coming out
still kicking after 3 years oh do I
destroy that that must be a source that
old Relic destroy it I'm on it boss the
return of Sara that thing yeah me and
there is device it warps monsters in
from far away places C that means the
enemy can send we the only socks I think
they should have made us kiss those damn
primers they sure Left Behind Some
terrible paring
GI they're so scattered where do I throw
GA I'm just going to put her
there are they going to are they going
to spawn
endlessly if I don't
destroy the crystal
thingy GA can you hold the line
GA for the top can you hold the line go
up let's do this okay
but I don't trust her I I I don't know
if I can leave her alone like
this
don't wait wait wait wait oh no oh
no they want a piece of the shark tail
they want the shark juice I need to stop
them oh my God
nice shooting than this is
fun aiming is really not that difficult
in this game so I'll be the yes you are
she knows what she is is waiting she's
aware she's breaking the the
wall but decoy is a bait
right so I want oh there it is I want
them to go to
[Music]
her okay okay but but no I don't want
them
to what if she dies
again how much HP does this thing
have you got to keep on
shooting reload reload
oh there's still so
many noble
Sacrifice by the way since we were on
the topic of the spelling be I want to
say I never I don't think I ever watched
that movie with the super
calistic that's why I think you know I
had lower chances of spelling that word
correctly I know I know it's
unbelievable that I didn't watch
him I know I
know I messed
up who could have known that I would
even survive until a sudden death round
I didn't expect that at all
I don't think it's unbelievable it's
different word than a German D it's very
similar though oh it's still spawning oh
my god oh there we go there are more
tep smash them there's
more
where right let me clear this
area is it
[Music]
clear oh my God oh my god did it far
better than what I would have done
really I I I was um very surprised that
some of
the Ian girls spellings of words even
though their English is supposedly
better than
mine what was going on
there should I be concerned should we
send them back to school
should we start a a whole live school
for whole Live members who seem
to maybe need some help with grammar and
words and math
perhaps like a real
school [\h__\h] up on apples I can only
teach
languages but I wouldn't I wouldn't want
to be charge of teaching English words
oh there's the other one all right
getting ready to deploy and
shoot there's no enemies
here spot him spot him distract
me monly salary is being increased
randomly chose are you joking there were
obviously like not so random words in
there very
very purposeful and I didn't realize
until afterwards the spigot is seemingly
the tap that chickens look at as if it
was their
friends did she actually put that in
there for me to the materials knowingly
GA did you do that GA coming in were you
aware of that eradicate the enemies she
will not answer my questions General pet
we are looking for you
she doesn't seem like she wants to
answer the game was rigged from the side
the bonus will be paid 6 months after
enlistment cute God I hope it's
not coming
in I think we're oh no we're not done
you studied the materials right I'll
pick you
up study the
materials what are you still stuck in
we'll never give up this city spelling
be from
yesterday [\h__\h] study This Is
War who I got the rig ones though what
do you mean rig you mean because of
sprinkle sprinkle sprinkle little star
how I wonder how to spell you an
extermination team has been dispatched
I've also never heard the word before
this combobulate or what was
it is that where the word bambole comes
from bra sounds really
funny it's not okay where does bamboozle
come from
then what's bad are you okay
good accept your destiny as a
decoy Die With Honor monthly salary is
being increased do your duty
believe in me believe in
you is terrible we might just flip over
wait is there another one of those
crystals looks like this town could use
some road maintenance I don't see it we
need to make it over the trouble hold on
what the [\h__\h] is that here we go what is
that from
us I think it's from us cuz they were
talking about extermination team here
leave that's the extermination team
I surprised people didn't know com I
knew that I would have been able to
spell that one too I'm surprised I don't
know narissa at the end did say that she
just wanted someone else to spell it
because she did just didn't want to
spell it I don't know if I believe
that I would be relieved if that was
really the case if she didn't know how
to spell it I I hope I hope
so how do you not know how to spell that
where are they oh my God there's so
many I just don't see
them oh it's
me is she dead
again there's more over there need's
more anywhere they
multiply there's a mother she would have
spelled it with her spe
nah oh what the hell that's a boss boss
monster boss
[Applause]
an it's a charge
rifle it's the mother of all charge
rifles
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
go back go back go
back something go
back where's the extermination Squad
when you need
us no no
no oh nice nice hit nice hit now one
come on nice
I feel like I
shot payback for when she shot me
yesterday that was so cute this they
prepared it so while I didn't even know
about any of the
animations in the background I only saw
all of that for the first time during
the stream it's so cute the handmade set
as
well so
adorable good job am
okay Anything Green left oh yeah over
there can I grab it oh wait there's
still enemies only like one or
[Music]
two which one was your favorite
animation um the F
ones and the crony one because it was so
funny every time she spoke it seemed
like she was Rising us up
but the SW ones looked so
chaotic with the scribbly
eyes yeah and I didn't know I didn't
expect that gigy would be such a smart
lady
wow compl she was very like reliable and
stable with her
spellings I could show you some food
she's so good she didn't even hesitate I
think looks like you've settled in now
you understand our job what we must do I
understand better than
today that was
fun that was so much
fun wait we should play together now
guys I think I understand the controls
now can can we play together let's
figure out how
okay uh how do we play
together maybe back to the title screen
I
[Music]
think online mission
mode up to four players can work
together to complete a mission is it
this one then
[Music]
that's the
one okay I don't know how many of these
I can do cuz the missions are longer
than I
thought but let's see oh wait I'm not
signed in yet uh wait wait wait wait I
have an
[Music]
account what
oh epic
music but it doesn't show me the option
to log in with Google through here what
the
[Music]
hell wow I love this
music I'm already logged in I have the
program
Open oh
[Music]
um but it doesn't like on the website
when I log in it shows like sign in with
all of these different things like
Google as well but now it
doesn't now it does hide screen it's
like not showing the Epic window
anyway let me try one thing
[Music]
online
y can I log in like
this no
[Music]
I'm logged in in the epic games
tab but it doesn't recognize
[Music]
it this music music is so nice link your
accounts e wait I think aren't they
linked
already
a how to link how to wait wait
[Music]
wa uhhuh I'm I'm doing
something okay
[Music]
oops
okay oh
oh
uhhuh is it this
yes yes yes yes should be
this and then
this let me in let me in oh I think I
think they're letting me
in uh are they letting me
in ah okay okay okay okay
okay oh okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay
preparing for online gameplay whoa what
is
this I'll make a
room kiaba Squad cour no no can I
change
ksq
ksq Kias
uh
um uh
what's a a good word with F that fits
this
[Music]
fighting uh priv
private platoon oh
yeah oh it's too
long
ah P
Patrol
okay uh
mission five okay that's the next
one room type everyone but I think only
four people right that's I wish you got
you all of you could join right
away does it have a
password exceeds the weapon level limit
gooa exceeds the weapon level limit
ah oh wa wo
you guys are fast oh we have three
rangers and One Wing
diver okay okay okay wait I don't oh
no do I need to mute my
[Music]
microphone so wait they want me to
change can't use our deco
[Music]
boys oh weapons are also different
though wait that's that's the backpack
okay I don't know let's go for
whatever push to talk by
default okay but don't don't talk guys
don't use voice chat
okay I I I I don't
think you should talk I am the decoy
right true we don't need any extra
decoy okay how did you guys even join
where was the room code or the the
password how did you
join oh
no disable it
uh oh
[Music]
uh
where out of nowhere it'll be
[Music]
fine game settings I don't know it'll be
okay okay
okay it's okay I
trust
yeah oh we have air raid two air Raiders
now
what kind of class is
that I think Evan you have to press
okay still looking at the
equipment I win
Ean are they in the air
actually they have drones and air stries
wow arery support but they're not in the
air right they're on the ground
right woo
okay let's
go W decoy don't use me as a
decoy scramble they're laying eggs
everywhere like the place smash them
to let's
go
e check out this big ass egg a monster
lady oh egg they'll just keep multiply
we need to destroy oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah they're fresh
fresh hatchlings almost feel
bad right oh what the hell is that w w w
w w w
w we done here I'm I'm going to run over
there and do my duty those things attack
humans from the moment they're born wait
they should be am I blind ah theze of
these eggs they're still in the eggs
they're just chilling in
there loot Goblin loot
Goblin do we share our loot when we're
in online
mode the exter
team support is he dead
no I wanted the Frog kill
carefully this
sucks Lo
refor they should help let's get rid of
some of these
buildings
inad can't
see do we get like a score at the end
that tells us who did the most damage
and all
that that's true and the most
kills I'm envious of that too get that
frog get that bro
get oh sorry maybe I hurt
you are you okay I I shot a rocket right
next to your
face my sorry whoa whoo wao no scores
only share pick up numbers okay so no
try Harding then that's good rest
that's probably for the
best
ID there's one over there I'm blind
where is it
egg
away
oh okay I'll take out more it has been
eliminated
successfully let's go towards the
masses oh the extermination Squad is
here alien sighted
aliens are leading monsters
in no the monsters are leading the
Aliens destroy them both can you play
the extermination squad car can you play
with that I
wonder would be nice to just walk
through
here for that
thing what's your health H okay ni
there's
there I need healing where's my
healers you guys are not protecting your
decoy
correctly what if I die we'll take care
of the
rest you are they saying that to me is
that a command that they can say we
leave the rest up to you we won't be
moving for a while what which one is it
you leave the rest up to me or you're
helping you you you leave it to
yourself giving me Mi signals here there
Friendly Fire do you think you're
shooting me on purpose I don't think
so
no
wa who I gotot a
tle no I
missed
sh no it's okay I need some healing let
me run around
here leave me alone leave me alone leave
me alone leave me alone leave me alone
that's not
healing that's not
healing something at
least
wa
who it's not healing
either
cha [\h__\h] even the worst of us deserve to
live drop me some healing
no a huge hord Of Monsters And there are
aliens with
them enemy Invaders often travel
alongside
monsters close to the monsters for
protection but it's not full
it the top left that's my health
right could be more refined but it's not
really going up
though am I misunderstanding this whole
time no right that's help wait let me
take this okay okay now we're full team
just got these monsters riled up what's
happening what's
happening can anyone Take the Lead here
uh I'll take the lead which way though
there's they're in both directions let
me eradicate the these ones over here
they's still egg though maybe if you let
them sleep do they just continue
sleeping
under
wayos I think we have
to kill them anyway
right on a dragon thing hell
yeah okay nice nice the enemy is nice
nice good job
WWA pick up that loot and then we're
good
okay how's it going over there I'm
joining you guys now this magazine more
W backup
incoming
[Music]
ADF ooh there's a big party over
there
wa Nice Shot nice shot
[Music]
okay I need to
reload there's so many of
them I can't even count
them there's too many of
them on I don't know which ones are
dead and which one our line but I think
we almost got
it
oh right up there right up
there we have some very angry monsters
coming our way exterminate what caliber
is this shotgun I have no idea what that
even
means he's he's a spider hey take me
with
you can I ride on top of you and then
when you jump do I jump with
you wait wait wait let me let me
try oh oh yeah move do you know where
the enemy is move move move
move no
no okay it doesn't
work oh no
time oopsie sorry too much
impact there's a little bit over there
but only a little
bit oh but it's over extermination
complete got to be finished before any
civilians
died
idot
idot peace and quiet this city really is
beautiful good job guys you guys are
amazing we are soldiers bra and strong
[Music]
oh good job guys that's so good that was
fun
okay can you guys leave the room kindly
and let somebody else join is that
possible thank you guys
thank you thank you all right all right
all right all right we have cole Bob and
Alex yeah check your equipment and then
we'll do another
mission oh now we'll do Mission
six so kind now you can disable
VC what where
though it wasn't in here was it oh wait
[Music]
oh uh do I just
like
what is there a way
to
okay this is
faster okay
[Music]
okay okay okay
okay H should I change something
though minion Buster special rifle
should I switch to this this is new
sounds
fun minion I'm going to I'm going to
bust them all I'll be yellow juice
everywhere
but I'll keep the
grant
[Music]
okay I got support equipment oh I forgot
to use that I think I had it selected
though our miss this time is Monster
extermination colorful but don't worry
we're with reinforcements for an
extermination those don't take it too
serious oh what are you doing what that
we likely won't have much to do on our
end what is that they're professionals
just leave it to
them looks so Hightech so that's what a
powered exoskeleton is that like healing
me or buing me to make a designer weep
oh it's
healing who did that hey who's
sabotaging
EF ID
kfp just imagine it says kfp instead of
EDF I'm treating
to fried
defense
combo combo can I have a can I have a uh
oh never mind you can
focus let's
go running sideways shooting a straight
line of
enemies I I think I'm
hitting just yeah I think that was
efficient
[Music]
right pretty sure that was a good
strategy
why is this guy still here oh
sorry I thought you were an ant you just
more metallic
ant you won't reach him from
hereare mine mine mine mine
mine mine mine mine mine mine mine I'll
take them
they lined right up for me exactly beare
ofr going
to there's a one all the way over there
but seems really
far oh no it's not that
far entering we can get it you know
where the enemy is yeah I know where the
enemy is look at the
map somewhere there oh it's dead I think
okay where's the next wave finally done
where is the
next sear the rest of the and still
don't know the death craw is one of them
is that what you call that we should get
back
soon ah wait what press to mount the
vehicle H wait what's what's that button
what is the button for that
Al what is
that
wa w power you got to give it more
gas damn
it useless
idiots we're so slow is a be careful can
I not go faster avoid you the
tires Yes W oh it's I think it can go
like up upwards
walls oh jumping
SP but it jump backwards
I jump backwards it's meant for caves
moners Trav ground maybe I need to aim
okay okay if I don't just jump but like
aim forwards it kind of jumps forwards I
suppers but don't underestimate them
either it's still so
slow
monst our pre killing monsters always
Mak light him up light him up
a p through P
[Music]
harder what's
happening it's a trap I can't move out
of it f up if it's a trap help me help
me I don't know how to control this
thing capable of
[Music]
learning wobbly wobbly
controls what what do you mean you
request a powered EXO is that what I'm
inside
of are you requesting it back I should
probably leave this thing because I need
to oh I got heals oh thank you
move okay I'm going to fight normally
like again normally again like a normal
person I'm too far from
these power
failure I wonder does this do AOE damage
if I shoot it in the middle of a like an
invasion of these
ants I would hope so
that's that's some kind of AOE damage
right
yeah
okay really them down I'm injured uhoh
give that's what you get for slacking
off at least I remember to use those but
I don't think I hit
anything how about
now oh yeah oh yeah AR done that did
something
damage oh Calli R what was CI streaming
uh the the the game that everybody's
playing right now shouldn't name any
other games right now I think so I just
will not say
it okay okay stop saying it guys sayf
idiot idiot idiot your brain is only
idiot sorry I made you say it but EDF
EDF EDF EDF EDF the best three letters
besides I they're saying
ITF
ADF indeed well we did it guys our are
only making our personel
short is there more we
are our muscles will protect you
remember the lyrics cuz I I recorded the
voice line long time ago up your voices
in aatt
cry thank you for the r this game is so
fun should play
it that still exist here in
[Music]
Paradise Mother Earth we're ready to
give up our lives
right now it seems fight or we die bring
your courage shine your light for the
world that voice sounds likeon your
spirit burn real bright it's time for us
to fale voice sounds
like join us right I heard it a little
bit in
Iris I like is that I thought you didn't
participate in this
ERS will be real
[Music]
soony just naturally part of EDF it's
not even the
sponsorship she's just you know this is
her side side
hustle when she's not screaming she's
she's defending the ass
earth oh that was a fast one
we going to be stuck calling these
monsters
forever as I'm sure you're aware if we
stop Exterminating them is more their
population will grow out of control we
have no choice but to continue thanks
for the healing don't lose bring bring
me more give me more monsters are
exterminated give me more and for all
more more not the healing thingy that's
all I
meant you gave everyone hope take pride
in that thank you you mean me I we got
moners we need you here
let's go it's a busy day today let's get
to
work we are
soers our muscles will protect you
all take
cover there's no escaping
[Music]
them what's WR such a happy
song seems we've got more
welcome wa
hello you're very welcome right now I
just want some targets to
shoot well they're so depressed right
now my Army is so depressed what do I do
I need to send down a wa Decoy for
motivation game show but I don't have
one right now all I have is myself
there's one there
on no one knows this but life
y truly cruel get rid of these
bildings oh that didn't do did that do
it they're here
what uh what flying monsters huh what
sounds like a pain in the ass
what are these spelling bees are they
trying to spell something out for me
what is it is it deite Dev I am m e uh
no i n e n t v e h t h okay okay I get
it I get
it don't kill me kill her
be get watch
this for
oh they're juicy they're so
juicy oh my
God the ants have evolved into flying
ants okay we're clearing up
nicely one over
there and one here
you see there's one
left who can reach it you can
fly oh we did it
together to fly Monsters has been
spotted suggest there may be a nest
nearby is sty so British this has gotten
out of hand are you saying there's
more no are you
dead we did it who's this
nice it Bob isn't dead right they were
just chilling down there from spelling
be to killing
be killing the killing bees
wo
woohoo no I think I think they are still
alive I think the HP bar was
full okay okay okay okay we can do
uh one last
one last last so if you guys enter the
room they already entered it seems this
is
last hi cleanup
Mission seven didn't I already do
seven no I guess not okay we're looking
for the hi Nest the hi
mind it
all wait equipment should I check it
too y
y
oh oh I got I got some uh
armor T5 Mouse a small hand
grenade a large number can be carried at
once
H ignites upon
impact I want to take
W it was so fun playing with the wow I
youber
Alex I see thank you for fighting and
defending the Earth with
me my aiming ATT tracking has gotten
really my
aiming well I mean I didn't really feel
like the aiming is difficult in this
[Music]
game turn
oh weapon level in
the room
settings H I don't know I don't think
I ah I don't think I can
what go away how do I make this go away
I don't know go go go yeah it's grayed
out it's okay Wawa is right here
wa is right here in your heart and on
your second screen and
here looks like we're hunting the skies
today
team the monsters have no right to live
here step fo
our our home okay countless lives to
defend
we search them out can stop me except
for
offense you're right about one thing if
we don't destroy the nests we can't
exterminate the fers I'm on your primary
screen how sweet what a compliment what
a flattering
thing okay they are
immediately coming at
us all empty
oh wait oops see wait I want to do I
want to I wanted to do
a I can't say anything I can't do a
command why not oh wait that thing is
still there how do I get rid of the
thing on the
left how do I get rid of
that I don't know how I opened it press
left Arrow ah thank you
yes we are soldiers brave and strong our
muscles will protect you all from any
harm raise
upes
inry beautiful
we this neutral area isn't even that
destroyed yet but we're absolutely
messing it up now
don't flex your wings like that at
me that's one down you can fly in this
game better than me maybe but I out you
can't fly for [\h__\h] remember that we've
got Flyers yeah I got it I get
it it's like they're directly replying
to what I'm
saying it's as if they're listening
trying to
survive I'm starving
honestly people could still be living in
here this looks so relatively
livable and intact rest of humanity
still has
hope
hey I found it I found it I'm totally
the first to see
it w okay that's oness there's more
moners are oh there's another one
there okay nice nice
nice
nice W the screeching sounds of
amii someone stop I'm is
suffering oh um someone catch me someone
catch me someone catch
me
[\h__\h] oh they wanted to catch me right
you guys tried you guys were attempting
to do so surely it's just because of the
delay and the time in the
Stream otherwise you would have totally
been there I believe in you
guys I see it I see it Target acquired
oh two Targets
acquired where are you guys are you not
coming over
here uh-oh oh
oh ef
ef exterminate them for the future of
our planet come on destruction
okay okay okay
okay we need a song like the EDF song
for
[Music]
K I eat fried chicken every day it
tastes so good the
ah
as I don't know what rhymes of that
every What rhymes of every
day that H
Cod why is this not going away why can I
not destroy this
Come
On Come
On
never I eat fried chicken every
day and it tastes so good even if I
don't get
paid I just love the
W
honestly the moners will it's great when
you're as
P
[Music]
yay we Are Soldiers brave and
strong it's Canon it's
Canon s they already remember the song
from hard this is our somehow I I just
noticed I feel like this game I can play
pretty mindlessly even with turning my
brain
off that healings mine I've been hiding
I don't I don't even have to think that
hard about aiming and all
that pretty good that's the appeal of it
on normal yeah okay well you know it's
good to have an option play normal if
you want to mindlessly shoot stuff and
play harder if you defending the if you
want to have a bit more of a challenge
ain't easy huh but the world will be
better one day don't lose it that was
fast there's more right oh there no
there's not more
okay that was so fast we were so good
good job cadetes good job
recruits that was the last
one that was the last that was the
last hey time flies when you're with kfp
am I
right that's good I might actually play
this again
sometime although I don't know if I have
enough space to download this game on my
laptop while I'm
in so maybe we'll have to wait
until I'm back in Austria to play this
again it's a good collab game maybe
collab of good on IRS I think that's
planned I I think
so but it doesn't it can also be with
others do I leave this
here we can also do this with other
people whoever is in for it
so
[Music]
yeah oh my Windows Firewall was was
blocking some features from this game
but I don't know what what it was it's
seemed
fine let me let
me okay so with that everybody I I would
stream longer but I think for now we'll
leave it at that it was a lot of fun as
you saw in my non-online solo
playthrough there is some cute little
decoys one of them is this uh small wow
it looks small now but in the game she's
very big and she has a lot of things to
say so go get one for yourself uh the
she's available together with gobba and
Iris for the early purchase bonus but
the early purchase bonus don't worry
it's up until the end of the year 24th
December so you have a lot of time to
still get this little va big vaa big
wava with big
words please sell us the figures I would
be so
nice yeah and ef6 is now on sale for PS5
PS4 and PC AKA steam so you can get a
set of free decoys as an early purchase
bonus as is at and the PC version is
currently available for 10% discount as
part of the launch discount check out
that URL in the description for more
details yay thank you so much for
sponsoring this the free publisher or
Defense Force it was a blast while I was
blasting these monsters actually it was
fun
like I would really enjoy playing this
some
more and I hope you guys give it a try
too oh EDF gamer we have some EDF fans
in the
chat yeah check it out check it out
whenever you can enjoy enjoy the h live
collaboration that's going on and when
while it's still there get yourself
those cutie
patooties and in German we say Venus EDF
kfp EDF kfp EDF
KF
wooo I had fun see you again out there
when we
are ready to fight some more
monsters yeah what do you mean just 1
hour it's been 2
hours this stream was sponsored I played
longer but let's play again sometime
again
[Music]
byebye and once again sorry for the
delay in the beginning
I hope you had fun
nonetheless now get some good rest
cadetes and get ready for more purple
and green blood blasted at you tomorrow
when you're back on the battlefield
right every day every day you have to
protect the Earth after all it's our job
IDF carep
Ki
over I'm proud of you I'm proud of you
so proud of you
[Music]