[Music]
[Applause]
ch
[Music]
for
[Applause]
[Music]
ch
do
[Music]
[Applause]
for
[Music]
KY H daring
I'm
Tak it's us again yeah we're back at it
again kiisa your favorite pairing
Kisa Kisa thank you eating Mike Tyson's
ass for the
membership hello everybody good evening
welcome to Monday Monday a mundane
Monday so far maybe but not
anymore mundane is like boring right
yeah not anymore it ends now we will
make your Monday exciting exciting
indeed as we played The Sims for yes
Sims Julian B thank you from
Canada for the Super Chat uh we we we we
we will play Sims 4 it's been a while
since we have uh I have played Sims 4
same when's the last time you played
Sims um years ago years ago I I was
never my mom's really into the Sims um I
was into the Sims because of the vampire
expansion oh but other than that that
other than that I just like I don't know
the Sims I like the Sims but I've just
never does I hate that I can't make them
look the way I want them too the Sim it
just download more stuff yeah yeah
[Music]
what do it just do it make your Sim
dreams come true I'll try yeah of course
she was of
course seems like obvious that you liked
it because of
vempire yeah so okay I will explain
we're not just playing Sims normally
also you may be wondering how can they
play Sims together well the first of all
this is an off collab narissa is next to
me she's right next to me yes I'm
touching her hi she's not actually
behind and above me
no yeah a birthday mer R thank you yeah
I've been seeing a lot of arrivals noise
give the chicken a hug please
um kisses proof okay someone Che okay
loud that was a little bit wet
sorry I just ate so okay okay so uh
yeah I must say this marvelous idea
stems again from The Marvelous Ki brain
yes yes so uh narissa yes and I going to
be playing a challenge yes we're going
to fight against each other for this
sims's life or death yes basically and
Nara will try to manipulate we will play
one sim uh each person gets one sim day
at a time I thought might be good uh so
let's say we start at 7:00 a.m. Sim time
or whatever and then we switch again on
the next day at 700 a.m. Sim time so I
have a question yeah money hack money
hack no no cheats obviously no cheats I
mean you wouldn't want to use money
anyway probably you don't want
to money for what you want me to be
miserable you want the S to be miserable
you want us to be miserable yeah but I
can use money to help make that
happen cuz let's be real the money isn't
The Sims the money is our money you know
so we can do things yeah no no we will
start however with like the basic amount
of whatever the game gives us and I will
for example because I want the Sim to
fry if I will try to get her a job maybe
MH uh and does gain more money hopefully
but at the same time I I probably need
to fix everything you're doing in your
turn like you're trying to make this IM
miserable make me uh lose my connections
with friends and this and that and maybe
make me lose my job maybe and I
eventually you get an instant win if you
manage to get the SIM to die yes while I
get the instant win see on the bottom
left if I get the SIM married and get a
child to be born you got a youo yaho
so I don't know I hope this is
relatively like balanced um there's a
few more rules at the top here so no
easy murder as in like getting the Sim
stuck in a pool yeah yeah yeah that' be
so lame I'm sorry that would be lame
that would really make it a challenge uh
no cheating as in no cheating money and
whatever uh and also no throwing away
money like but like specifically looking
at you like if you if I earn money from
my job and you go to The Sims uh like
furniture shop thingy and then buy
everything so that I get zero simoons
that would be terrible we don't want
that okay so leave me some money to if
anything I want to hack in money so I'm
not going to waste your money okay what
okay you understand what your job is
right yeah but you don't understand
what's going on in my brain you knew you
you would also say yeah we shouldn't
hacking money but oh no okay okay so you
guys understand what we're doing we're
going to start by creating a little
simple Sim just somebody no resemblance
to anybody yeah yeah yeah uh in
particular um but I was thinking maybe
certain traits and all that might also
be important and interesting all right
will there be game sound I don't hear
any yeah wait I literally also don't
hear
any what the fck and what was
that where's the sim sound
ah there we go okay I love Sim's
creation songs is the volume of the game
off uh she kind of looks maybe
like bit similar to the thumbnail Sim
already yeah kind of a little bit um I
don't know the looks don't really matter
she looks pretty
anyway what do you want to do so um
where's the mouth oh there it is so
we're making her a young adult
yeah this is personality right no he
says in control now yeah yeah yeah this
is no voice this is the voice waxing us
for batisa
wal W Genie lay W Genie La okay okay I
like that I like that okay you like it
okay okay what hair color do we want I
don't give a leave it brown maybe
so it looks a little bit similar to The
Sim and the thumnail okay okay wo yeah
oh o o o o o la whatever you
want do you know you can scroll up also
I'm I'm trying desperately to scroll
it's not working oh my God what if we
make her look like a '90s anime like
Idol uh like not anime just in '90s what
does that look like you know like the
bad hair that all Idols had like this it
was like you sound so different to Thea
who are you oh I'm
sorry who who said that just you no I
said that but like look at this this
looks like the like idle
hair do it guess little
B okay okay well well well okay I guess
that's
fine this she sounds very sve
SW hey you sound different now no it's
I'm sleepy all the time kiata kiata
won't let me sleep at night guys huh
that's lies she keeps me up all night no
no no no no no no no oh this is cute no
no I let you sleep you let me sleep we
slept a lot we did sleep a lot night but
simultaneously not enough you
know you never sleep what what while I
was waiting for the food what was what
are you doing while I was watching
Netflix I was laying down playing on my
phone because I asked Kiana if we could
turn off the bedroom light because it
was shining directly into my Iris I said
no because I knew you were going to fall
asleep no no no no I knew you were going
to fall asleep so I moved to my room did
you sleep no I did not sleep
h i I managed to stay oh my god when she
like a mermaid mes VI that's exactly
what those two are exactly what we wore
in the mes yeah
coconuts and shells
coconuts coconuts coconuts
coconuts Cool N please it's not about de
creation can you like I know I'm I need
to speed it up I need to speed it up
okay yeah yeah I'm just trying to make
her look like really basic so you have a
hard time finding a romantic
partner care but yeah look at these
awful shoes okay all the rest of it can
stay the way that it wait no no what are
you doing this part is really important
okay so I want an
aspiration that is like kind of like
beneficial to me okay we'll just switch
off every other one how about so you
pick one thing and then I pick the
next okay okay okay okay uh I would say
for me either family or love I think
because that's my my life goal for real
for real okay uh this one soulmate this
seem wants to find and live a rewarding
life with the one this wants to play the
field and go on dates
although
yeah if I did
this it says wants to play the field and
go on dates with all sorts of
interesting people so so you
know not necessarily monogamous right so
if you ruin my relationship with one
person I might I can like easily go just
to the next one I guess that would be
maybe helpful for me uh
was a large loving
household uh yeah what do you guys SP
should I make her player you should go
with it that's what you want I don't
know I'm thinking uh like
strategically strategically that does
sound helpful when I ruin all your
relationships you cannot do that you
cannot they they will find me too
Charming okay next
yours wait so this one is likes and
dislikes traits these are all
traits um okay I'll do this and then
we'll interval with but then I only get
one trait and you got to you do tra you
can do tra do a trait this the likes and
dislikes are not that important I think
yeah that's true okay I'll do two of
these then
[Music]
yeah
wait sorry this is important if you're
going to be like looking there all the
time you should maybe like yeah
sorry there we
go maybe you're speaking differently
because you this time you're actually
hearing your voice for the headphones
cuz yesterday you didn't have a onom
maybe that makes you talk differently I
think so I'm not used to hearing my
voice this is really
weird are you guys believe it normally
she doesn't have feedback in her ears
from her own voice I don't know why you
want to do that only whole life member I
don't know anyone else who ever that
prefers not hearing themselves why would
you want that he why would you want not
hearing yourself as a streamer that's my
question oh
yeah you go what did
you chose mean these s become happy when
being mean or mischi to
others that's kind of like you get to
pick one train I get to pick two yeah
yeah but she just gets like you let's
say you do something mean cuz you want
to ruin my relationships in the end
you're just making the Sim happy if you
say so which kind of I guess like boosts
your mood which is good for me I think
in theory no but you're also ruining my
relationship
so it's a but a plus and a minus both M
mhm okay keep going keep going okay your
turn
are you choosing that next I don't
know I should probably do like something
like outg going oh no no no not
necessarily uh no these are not
important for this challenge how
about lactose
intolerant I happy when they finish R
tasks um
no
cheerful this these two tend to be
happier than others that's pretty good
Romantics tends to be flirty may become
sad if they don't have any romantic
social interactions with period of
time you're welcome to talk more narissa
oh yeah I mean I'm just looking at what
you're looking at you need to talk about
what are you going to pick pick hurry up
take so
long I didn't look at this one I think
actually oh did I no you did it's the
last one
[Music]
family or these
seems sad if they don't and can boast
about
family bro bro let's go like bro for
real yeah bro for real seems can bro hug
other
Bros gain confidence around other Bros
how do you know who's a bro though I I
don't know and become confident from
watching sports you're bro bro yeah
you're for real bro oh my God bro let's
go
uh neat is
[Music]
like not good cuz you're you're probably
going to leave everything dirty and
that'll be really sad what is child of
the ocean child of the child of the
ocean Islands these Sims experience a
spiritual connection to the islands of
sulani I guess it's a DLC py Islands by
part taking the culture m n
is there something that helps me with
like being less
hungry cuz this is this needs to eat
right oh oh can eat spoiled
food might be
good if I don't have time to cook I
suppose so maybe and there's something
around make make her a glutton make her
a trash
can but now no cuz you going to let my
sim hunger and then she's going to have
an even greater why you think I would do
that why do you think I'm so a bad
person ah how about just being
genius maybe come upset if they haven't
improved their mental skill no
no okay I'll go for I'll go for oh
what's this more confident I yeah is
confident good of course confidence is
good cheerful no okay oh God no cheerful
whatever okay okay I don't know if that
really helps at all but at least she'll
be more happy I want her to be
happy be
happy
children that's okay um I also wanted to
switch this one actually swiching no why
did it do
[Music]
thatf okay we just need to fix some
likes and dislikes it can be random it
doesn't really
matter
what he seems become happy around s
negative moodlets can laugh manically
and dis and become Ang when Interac with
good Sims okay okay select dislikes and
likes I don't really care I don't I just
pick whatever it doesn't matter yeah it
doesn't really matter yeah
although I mean I guess it kind of
matters I never really noticed it
mattering to be honest uh I think it
increases your ability to like learn
those certain thing so say you wanted
your sim to like learn how to play
guitar having that as selected as one
would make it go faster I think we can
just also just leave them hello my name
is I have an
idea
angle
deil
perfect okay did we do ah wait let me
take a quick look at the gloves really
oh my God wait that's such a cute like
tennis outfit but what are those glasses
they're awful get those immediately ew
ew Queen uh that's cozy so cozy she's
got girl s like yours almost not really
but kind of cute party outfit okay girl
let's go okay she's got an interesting
style I appreciate it I can respect it
wait I want to see the mermaid outfit
mermaid outfit isn't there one because
of the I don't see one not here maybe
but I'll
Chang and the hot weather outfit yeah I
mean why
not not
necessarily perfect wait how about how
about wow o o cute I love robers yeah
but the shoes oh it matches the
color those are really cute with the bow
do you like the Hat uh we can keep it I
hat okay she she doesn't want to
sculpt bur right yeah yeah yeah that
would be terrible and then what the hell
is that cold weather pleas please please
please okay that's my outfit of choice
thank you I mean it's certainly warm
yeah she looks really warm and happy
okay and then for fancy outfit if she
ever has the opportunity to go on a
fancy uh party or event you put her in
humo that's amazing yeah there's a lot
of different outfits like that nice um
what speaks to us
personally I kind of found this one to
be very elegant and I fashionable yeah
yeah I can see it but we can also put in
something more simple whatever you want
to do I don't
care I mean she probably never get to
she's evil so the red one you just she's
evil she's not evil oh look at her
trades you're evil you made her evil
well you got to set her main aspirations
so okay but how about how about how
about red and black yeah red R and black
yeah this one yeah yeah okay sure Queen
let's go change the shoes though to
proper collar here there we go okay I
think Sim is like whatever we don't
care
de this is angle de we can be your an or
your deil right and let's go where does
she move in though we need to get her
like a cheap small house like the
smallest one available you need to yeah
so that's I let her on the street
forever no no no you you have to you
have to let her live in the house okay
okay somewhere where there might be a
cheap proper maybe in the city there can
be
Apartments like I think the I I think
San m has Apartments cuz I've seen in
the other Maps they they barely have
like one like single
houses I have to like place them there
if I want some proper ones but pick the
cheap apartment that's fine yeah we have
to have some money to live you wanted to
cheat
money yeah of course why don't we buy a
giant house I don't why don't we buy a
mansion why don't we use cheats to kick
someone out of their mansion so we can
buy the Mansion where's the chapas ah
here is weekly rent
600 5 500 that's pretty big we don't
need it to be that big what about in
here
300 that's the best one on let's go
let's get it this place is incredibly
suspiciously cheap it's like the
landlord can't give it away a great
place to practice your hand oh a lot of
things will break in this apartment well
great that adds to the chaos we love it
we absolutely love it let's go makes it
a bit more difficult for me to furnish
yeah let's
go okay okay your day first okay it my
day first okay yeah otherwise I'll just
kill her okay so I have one
day why is she in the witer out I
haven't played in a while uh uh wait how
do I use okay P for pausing I forgot I
haven't played in a while what the this
dude do we have to look at him the whole
time yeah he's on the billboard he's
kind of sexy though so let's look here
we have a little one single bedroom oh
we have two
bedrooms that's un necessary but okay
for my future child of course got boy
what the is a TV's the living room
okay what where's this car someone died
there someone died that's why so cheap
okay okay
um
M what what do we say about like
buying additional things I think ideally
we shouldn't buy anything additional I
think we can live with this mostly I
mean I'll but I mean and maybe at least
a
bookshelf yeah cuz in case I do manage
to get a job and and get it longer for a
day without you get getting me fired by
not oopsie oopsie by not going to work
uh then I would like like to learn some
skills probably yeah okay thank you so
much for letting me have that here I'll
just buy a couple books I think that
works as a
bookshelf read H I think the skill books
I still have to buy extra first unicorn
the first
unicorn all right the do we need some
bgm because normally during the daytime
it's like maybe
unless I'm in a shop there's like not
much going
on yeah let's
play a little bit of audio
stock
audio no can't can't play that why would
you do that I don't know uh here I have
I have strip club strip club time music
strip club
time no that's not oh no no that's
perfect really but that's okay it's l
sish yeah that's what I called it even
okay I'm kind of nervous what where do I
even start
though what well first off she looks so
cute in that outfit I think it's perfect
I think oh she already knows someone
Miriam she's a friend no they're not
friends she just knows her I guess I
could get to know the
neighbors can I visit apartment
hello become my friend and ideally
immediately marry me wait did we look at
the time it just like 10 seconds passed
but let me look at the time um 8:00 a.m.
okay so you get to it
oh
ah hell go
here let me in okay there are many
different ways to let's learn the rooms
no no need okay hello can you marry me
can can Sims wait can female Sims make
female is preg pregnant by now I don't
know I feel like
chat yeah
yes oh nice I wait I could no I said
birth a child could I adopt a
child can you adopt people in The Sims
yeah you can you can adopt yeah but I no
we should make a baby leg okay well
flirt go on
intercourse yeah you got a you got a
yoohoo uh
um how s get pregnant I don't think I
can get a lady but at least we can be
friends and that's good where are you
going Ang Ang angle please nice me to
you're a nice apartment dag dag dag dag
dag dag talk
about cloudy
weather uh we'll be best friends forever
please please be nice to
me if I may be like very moody uh on
like on another day like
tomorrow please don't be surprised
okay I'm I'm I'm I'm kind of like Moody
you
know you just met this person and it's
giving you the option for a deep
conversation yeah but ask if mermaid ask
if mermaid please for
me are you a
mermaid are you mermaid or oh excuse me
are you a mermaid she's like what the
are you talking about mermaids are
not real mermaid she didn't like that
girl that's not my fault she was
insulted by it why would she be insulted
excuse me mermaids are Majestic I have
to fix that now I sabotaged
[Music]
myself pretty negative choices here
let's try to be funny well your
character is evil oh
no only if she follows what her evil
angel on her shoulder evil devil tells
her to do I'm an
angel an evil angel I'm an
angel maybe she was insulted
because implied that she smell fishy oh
maybe why would you
think you wanted to ask if she's a
mermaid yeah but why would someone think
that
think
well why would someone think that if you
were like are you a mermaid why would
they be like what do you think I smell
like
fish what what what do you mean why
would think I not I would not come to
that conclusion you literally asked are
you a
murder all right I'll get to know her a
bit more the first day is
like I should you need to get a job yeah
I should get a job um she has a PC I
will use her
to find a job all jobs are all jobs like
jobs yeah I think so that might be best
cuz like you going to get me fired
anyway so I just do like one time only
times okay big brain oh I think she's
laughing menacingly like probably but
the big head was dampening it so we
couldn't hear she's perfect the way that
she is ooh uh paid Beach cleaning
volunteer work ooh you love the beach
but wait needed by Sunday okay yeah
begins ASAP begins ASAP Sunday 6 p.m. so
all within today I think
83 H this is a one time Pan the others
are like by hour coconut milk real milk
Bob said that coconut milk wasn't real
milk but I told him it totally V so we
need a bird party to get us uh to go get
us a coconut from a tree that we way we
know it hasn't been taed with so we can
test it out do it no I don't know where
to find that
doesn't it ah I saw a Mermaid once but
nobody believes me and I haven't been
able to find one since I have a
brilliant plan and a fin suit that it
wants to wear on water looking for
someone to take pictures so that we can
prove to the world they really do exist
at the very least it should boost
awareness bro AA
let's dude that one sounds like fun no
but it needs photography level too I
need one like I love this
Emoji so I just got my nails down and I
have to pack some boxes but I'm pretty
sure if I try then I'm going to ruin my
manicure plus the boxes are going to be
totally heavy so I really need someone
to come and like do it all for me okay
pick it up I think yeah I think I'll do
that cuz it doesn't need any skills and
it begins right away okay and pays
okayish all
right um how do I begin this I've never
done this uh same starts 11 ah oh in
halfen she looking at the camera in half
an hour it begins so I'll be leaving uh
what how do I yeah leave your neighbor's
house uh which one's mine um the one to
the left I think there was like an
option to go home ah here I think this
one yeah okay ah so far so
good so far so good we're back home but
yeah so I guess I'll go to work I don't
know how that works is there like an
interaction to pack
[Music]
boxes um I anything else I can do before
I leave how my how's my mood oh my mood
is still very good maybe maybe my mood
is
good yeah let's just be chilling yeah
getting some okay fun from the
TV I love that she's in this outfit I
just think the silliest
thing I want to change it but I can't
cuz it doesn't work on the mirror I need
this all right but she's leaving all
right oh she changed clothes herself
yeah she realized she can't go outside
like that she should oh this actually
like a kind of job where it just happens
and I don't have to do anything I think
so nice time is passing nice when was it
7 or 8:00 a.m. I don't know guys do you
know you just came back so oh that's
fast easy wait wait wait Katrina was a
little high maintenance pactice here no
I want that in this box make sure the
boxes aren't too heavy even still angle
followed all of the instructions it took
all day but the packing got done and the
client was pleased and that's also all
that really matters isn't it oh also
money 8 $84 yeah that's okay for now for
now it's okay now I really need to
pee her her bladder is small yes that's
okay that's okay I'll I I I can support
a small bladder yeah yeah in my
lifestyle mhm hunger is next
8 a.m. they say by the way okay 8 a.m.
waking up in the morning I'll be cooking
simple
things you're probably going to get this
kitchen on
fire
eventually what's simp anything really
but oh something cheap too where I don't
need extra ingredients oh it all needs
extra ingredients oh wait I can use not
fresh
ah okay GR
grilled cheese it is let's
go maybe I should have made a bigger
serving to like eat it later but you
might just throw it out cuz you're
allowed to do that stop giving me
ideas yes you know I want you to be
creative fun you need maybe some
inspiration cuz you haven't played the
game in a while yeah you know it's true
you might be planning around there so
too
much it's it's
okay she's
insane she's so funny though imagine
you're making grilled cheese
yeah and you just start
maniacally
laughing my grill cheese will conquer
the world literally she's so crazy let's
go
girl let's go yes we love that grilled
cheese sandwich amazing now clean it up
clean it up she was going to do it
anyway good girl and then I'm getting
pretty tired but we're not going to
waste our time sleeping
yet I'm going to read oh yeah right I
need
to goodbye chunky wonky chunky wonky
let's buy a book how about we just buy a
cooking book so so that it will get
harder for you to ruin my cooking and
ruin my life ruin your cooking can be F
the P okay okay okay it will be here
read no no not read something
read a that's such a nice reading corner
like out the window damn yeah like what
a pretty view from bed too why is it not
moving
anymore keyboard CH ah because it's
nongo keyboard nongo nongo oh she's just
reading little standing why there's a
chair right there she's crazy
sh who will Shak a tees who will shocka
tees okay now I love the Sim language me
too it is so dumb me too welcome to the
neighborh am I getting free fruit
cake oh wait is she the one I just
talked to yeah yeah
yeah uh wait I'm going
to quick before she leaves
[Music]
what fruit cake the fruit
cake the fruit cake I need the fruit
cake it's going to be my dinner my free
dinner yay you them in wow is it really
fuit cake I think it
is yeah fruit cake welcome everybody
wait let a guy that's a guy that's a guy
you found A's your neighbor nice to meet
youba would you like to mate with me uh
please I mean your man bun questionable
but it's okay yeah I mean it looks good
looks good well well yeah he likes he
does his hair he likes fish cuz fish is
on his T-shirt wait it's hard to see
it's hard to see I want to talk to the
guy ask if mid no oh my God yes no I
need to
know well we gave him a compliment
wonderful order him to clean that's
compliment let's can I already like
flirt with him go Sharky
maybe this is too easy maybe let's see
if it's too easy for me I will also say
my child has to grow
up to like it's not going to be too easy
for
you yeah you think you're having an easy
time but just wait until it is my
turn wait stop talking to the others
girl stop she wants girl time she does
not care about him she needs she needs
to get
prante you need to give
what literally what happened play in the
rain she wants to play in the rain she's
cooking she's
happy good for her but what the it
oh
she's
o are you getting robbed no that's like
a wrestling mask go home you have gas
the Sim cannot go home right
now oh is this like
a is this like a what do you call this
like inter the actions that you do when
you don't really have control not one I
me
n skiping Nardo why is this happening I
don't
know why why don't we go back home girl
why did you
change go
home can't travel because she's working
I'm not working huh what is this a bug
go back home go home get out of my house
go home maybe next time no I no they're
leaving and my future
husband yeah you just told him all to go
home I kissed his hands I kissed his
hands and I liked it support his facial
hair oh my God he really likes me he
took my my flower what if I already get
pregnant in this first day you need to
get married yeah we can I mean the order
doesn't
matter we don't we don't we're not
that's not no don't leave why did he
leave cuz you sent him
home can I get home too please yeah
there we go
okay what is she
doing you sent her there no no I didn't
but let's uh where's the book by the way
is it in my inventory I don't you don't
have an inventory it's a Sims I have an
inventory girl what no
since when is there an inventory within
the Sim this is the inventory I can't
see
it this
is you've missed many things in The Sims
apparently guess she's just watching TV
now that's okay we have time to do
things but I guess I did she put it
back there it
is are you going to woohoo in the
costume no I would hope not I sure hope
so I mean if she can manage to do it in
the costume okay
then
respect cuz it's really really really
covered up it's like Mean Girls
musical okay there's a Mean Girls
musical yes of course there is I know
right of course there is and uh it's
cursed there's one part where she's like
she she hooks up with him in the um
mascot costume she's like like she makes
them wear the costume no they're both in
the
costume like woohoo you know oh in in in
a mascot costume spicy a lot of social
bunny wor things happen to angle today
open social bunny on your phone to post
about them what the okay that's
like Twitter since what is there a
social media app in The Sims a long time
you can even become a YouTuber in Sims
now
[Music]
yeah and one of the avatars looks like
me I believe it yeah you're blowing my
mind though what uh so we're going to
post a book review with a happy
narrative let's go whatever that helps
me maybe it helps me somehow maybe
getting followers will help me oh this
so cute
picture thank
you it's bedtime already wait wait
before you
sleep are you sure you don't want to eat
some of that fruit
cake hi chunky won there's no space for
you here sorry
chunkers Yum Yum
Yum she is just covering up everything
she's so
fluffy oh her butt oh you want to sit
here that's not going to work to see
anything okay that's kind of
adorable just adorable she wants to sit
between our
cameras yeah make some space for her
over there just wonus please that's so
weird like only when like narissa is
here she likes me I guess okay she's
sleeping cuz I couldn't control her you
and your phone the phone is used to do
much more than just call a friend it's
used to travel play games or call a
hotline when sad explore its features
and get rewarded okay thank you oh
there's like a no no thank you no
[Music]
quests a well this is good chunky wony
being here so that like when you control
the Sim then I can play withy
Mony so we at 800 a.m. okay it's going
to be time for you soon yes um I play
with chonus wonus I hope you treat our
our Sim well because we we're her
Guardians
okay yeah okay she woke up it's 6:00
a.m. wow woke up so
early let's eat another piece of fruit
cake yummy she already doesn't like it
what what did I just eat from eating
fruit cake does anyone really eat this
that fruit cake stuff come on it's free
food she doesn't like it she
said this
sucks like this cake Aida bought is
awful at least no why is she going to
the bathroom to wash her dishes just Sim
things just Sim things I'll take an
angry shower what time is it
uh down here you can see I have one more
hour quick shower and then we're at
perfect mood all is green all is
well and yeah perfect
perfect and leave the fruit cake here
for you if you in case you want to make
her
unhappy Dam you know you make a good
point okay uh 30 minutes oh oh she even
cleans the floor yeah cuz I I spilled
some water
here interesting
yeah cleaning cleaning my environment to
keep me happy and it's almost your time
20 seconds what she going to do put it
away nice yeah keep it clean keep
clean yeah I can't even think of
anything else to do except for calling
my boyfriend and telling him to not
believe anything I say
today uh where's she going I don't know
playing the rain she really likes the
[Music]
rain I don't think you have his phone
number yet
sure okay let's let you why she like
playing in the
rain okay here you go okay have fun one
one day n is in control woohoo chus
wonus you're very much in your leg okay
I don't know how to to do this actually
how do I move the screen um like with
the you drag it with the mouse or you
move around with
WD and how do I rotate
it
I rotate wait how did I do it how do I
pause real quick actually
okay wait how did I move how did I
rotate ah with uh Mouse wheel okay
cool what do you mean with okay I see I
see see okay Vera assuming Direct
Control it's devil time she'll try to do
you want to maybe get some space
here she'll try to destroy
everything what do you want to do I want
to
I want sorry I think that's uh not us by
the way I I know okay I want I want her
to come check dust level what does it
even mean you want her to come here yeah
just click again it said go here M or
you can always like press like go home
on her icon okay so oh she want she
she's in bath towel she wants to say hi
she's she's knocking in a bath towel my
neighbor she likes you decline shower
decline shower is she offering to shower
together no she wants to use our shower
oh what are you doing what did you just
do what is the
interaction um you ordering her to clean
P
yeah you scaring
her our friendship is stronger than
that no
oh I'm sorry I have two
personalities please forgive me like me
again tomorrow
no oh Mischief not so much angle doesn't
feel right about all these tricks and
Games should she turn a
new now we have Miss Chief
skill that's fine that's fine as long as
it makes me happy imply mother is a
llama your mother is a
llama going to yell at her I like you
come to my house you asked me to take a
shower why would I let you do
that belly
rub the
electricity oh she she she changed into
her clothes I'm going to Jer at her oh
my god do you hear the yeah okay dony
wony you're so ELC I can't see anything
over here Mony
hair not helpful I'll hold it down
um relationships you guys he it too
right yeah you come to my house and tell
me
i n n n what are you going to do what
are you going to do nothing
[Music]
oh good that you don't know how to play
this game so
much what is your plan I don't know what
is my plan don't ruin I couldn't read
your mailbox but I managed to throw in
the mail
oh okay oh that was Penny p is her name
oh I know her Penny pizaz she's got some
pizaz
you know you can always speed up too by
the way this or like one two three
basically one two three wait where is he
I said I wanted to travel to him yeah I
think you're traveling together now oh
so wherever you want to
[Music]
go let's
go Central
Park this is where we should have bought
a
house
why won't it work oh I have to the drive
yeah I think so I don't think we can buy
a house there why it's a park a public
[Music]
park here it here it starts here it
begins I see you are hey bro come back
here yeah run away run away run away we
can
[Music]
tomorrow
so more choices no no no delicious no um
mock facial
hair
no
no no
no yuck yuck yuck yuck yuck yuck no no
no I love him no you can't do this no I
love him so much impersonate
mermaid show me she jump into the
fountain oh they having a nice why are
they having tell stop it I think that's
not so bad right
now he loves me even at my worst moose I
can I can fix this
[Music]
J what does jir mean um I don't know how
to explain it I don't plus plus
relationship plus bro for that first
interaction
WF run run Aina
run you can't
escape does he like okay good
doesn't your mother is a
llama yl beg
forgiveness our relationship is so
dead Jack
sh I'm ruining it for you oh bro what
the was that why did he like that
no he didn't like
good trash and
Nim I
meanu
masu oh that sounds terrible I'll talk
to Penny
myself okay well our main goal of
socializing with our date was achieved I
mean yeah I suppose so oh oh oh we're
achieving more
goals why is she still here just go
home F you know yeah yeah so
over I'm so sad my heart just broke oh
no yeah fight
[Music]
fight I think we're getting our ass
KCK no we K his ass rang at least at
least we won the
fight they're still laughing how are
they still laughing oh yeah look at
this
confrontation I'm going to impersonate
mermaids I don't know what the that
means how can you be so mean when
there's chuny wony next to you who is
like so cute I
know hey angle you the she was saying
something Penny ass is
falling I don't care what she has to say
Ru your
[Music]
relationship FP guess I got to be more
aggressive in my next round um po Mighty
ask what his I'm going to ask him a
risky question he had a and declare him
my enemy
Andie can I fix this I don't think so I
look for a new man oh good luck guys
oh
anybody
volunteers um declare him your enemy
bro
AR they're all
enemies feelings he probably getting
getting Joy from it yeah you volunteer
you know that you're going to be dealing
with very very moody lady if you're
volunteering what do you mean that
volunteering to be the next
guy yeah you guys you guys want
this problem fake bad
news that's so terrible that's so
terrible he looks so
sad s thought I thought he was going to
be the one he was going to be my baby
daddy I don't yeah I don't think that's
possible at this point
okay then I think you can waste your
time with other things now okay one more
thing um and how do I go home Buton do I
press no on her icon no her icon her
small icon okay okay hey this drama
isn't my fault at least not completely
I'm allowed to feel bit about what's
happened between us yeah he feels B
about it then maybe there's still some
love in this hard for me okay okay this
little icon no there's a house icon in
the in my icon in the yeah here this one
this
one oh what does it say what does it say
when you H hover hover over it this one
you hovered over it for a moment what do
you me show me I'm so lost he says SIM
can to go home right now oh well I don't
know why why can't I go home maybe you
need to end the date with him
properly um like say
goodbye I don't know I don't have any
options click more choices more choices
actions disband group goodbye maybe
goodbye they'll never hang out with us
again want to flirt with your date have
Sims become playful Yeah well yeah I
socialized I did a really really good
job socializing hey girl where are you
you can right click on her then
lead you to her yeah okay what she doing
group is gone uh try maybe
like yeah pick that ending early okay
let's go home now I earned a medal hey
yeah a book we got a book as a
consolation prize hopefully it's I did I
did a really good job yeah I being a
deil yeah yeah good job being a
debil being mean and ruing my
life yeah go
home you're so chill about ruing my life
damn I mean I'm not really ruining your
life you know not
really what button was that one three
three you can also change the time down
here oh the speed
oh how do I stop it it feels like it's
your first time playing it's been a
really long stop it with p PE like pause
pee for
pause okay okay let's see so what can I
do in the house if you can't handle me
at my Resa you don't deserve me at my
wallet
exactly that is literally the spirit of
today checking dust
levels wow so
evil so
evil
um want to check my mood by the way here
the mood see how miserable I am no so
okay you're doing great your fun is high
you like to be evil I'm really I'm just
doing what the character wants
sure yeah goodbye cake cake
no no I do cake we didn't like him we
had a fight you think I want to eat cake
given to me by that guy no deep in my
heart yeah deep deep in your heart not
the fruit cake girl what are you doing
breing she has nothing to do her life is
boring and has no meaning her life is
boring trash before you try to eat out
of
it don't worry I don't think I
can I I hope not I don't know you picked
you picked the Glutton one right no what
did you end up picking M the nice one
being nice no happy just being happy
happy happy
birthday
okay oh oh they have a trash Sho that's
so
cool how do I buy things you don't have
to press all the time when you click
right click one time unless you change
the camera it will stay on her girl how
do I buy
things well if you paid attention you
would know that it's
here what do you want to
[Music]
buy what
hey
hey hey she's in the middle of her
business how do I how do I stop well I
won't tell you now you have to figure
that out
yourself we're going to be here this is
a
disaster um well I wanted to sell the
toilet no you oh here's the sell
button is that
okay can we allow this
what you don't need two beds yeah that's
true okay how do I get out of here well
do I hit the same but I'll tell you if
you give me back my toilet
no
okay oh she already finished going to
the bathroom this not a bage excuse me
why would you take away her toilet she's
literally in the middle of of using
it she's like where the did that go
did I hallucinate this
[Music]
toilet the Glutton Spiel gluten
Spiel sucks to P it was trial girl who
told you you could cook cancel
no keep on cooking let her cook let her
cook girl no one said you can cook I
didn't I and I'm the weird God
today you have no idea how to reset this
camera do you I mean I know but I'm just
liking it from this angle so I don't
have to readjust from this angle wink
yeah this
[Music]
angle just stop trying to cook you like
this angle but this angle is not liking
you right
now here guys can you look up for me if
women are an option for me by default in
Sims 4 I think they are can I get with a
woman in this game by default or do I
need like you
know
add-ons let me in your apartment even
though we aren't friends I can they're
not you made a baby with CI no people
are
saying I did I I guess
yeah I'll take this out of Contex guys
why is it not moving there it go
oh
okay oh that
s oh what are you going to
[Music]
do what
nothing I need
money oh you're going to get a job yeah
you need money well I need the money
okay okay she wants a job Mom okay she
wants money why is she
tense stabbed in the back yeah just like
how you made her stab people in the back
her boyfriend who made her cake to
survive I didn't do
anything I didn't do anything wrong uh
we literally caught you in 4k okay I did
nothing
incorrectly there's a lot of proof a lot
of proof no stabbed in the
gut not take it out of crotch text wow
wow wow guys
wow according to go you don't need to
have any much okay thank
[Music]
you you want to view the painting how do
I steal
things you can't just steal things why
can't I just steal things I think you
would have had to make us a kleptomaniac
God that's unfortunate
M what's that kitchen her smells funny
it
is that's how it is everything is so
sparkly clean it's beautiful you have to
talk loud or sometimes you cut it's
beautiful just like
you thank
you oh oh it went home she said I'm
getting out of here I think she needs to
go to that job that odd job that you
gave her that's probably true yay what
did you give her what job did you give
her uh she's doing some lawn work okay
apply Sor chunky why would you do that
you're evil to chunky too I just I just
I just moved my phone slightly I success
well we got we got 69 oh she said I'm
going to bed okay oh oh she's sleeping
early yeah go get those hours yeah get
those
is her mood is pretty good right now
narissa I I know I don't think I'm doing
a very good J well you absolutely ruined
my chances with that guy you're still
have 4 hours though
uh what ises that mean social
Bunny and social bunny you want to post
something you want to tweet something
yeah okay new post you have done nothing
that is worth your posting girl I worked
I worked to job I went on a date uh
maybe if it went well and you got a
medal a gold medal for it maybe then you
could posted about it like I just I just
had my best date ever I think I'm going
to marry this
guy yeah girl you can't be
eating you need to
stop she's like oh I'm so
hungry no I hope she's not wasting money
when she starts these foods and then I
don't know where this food is from but
it didn't it looked kind of green you
know so I'm inclined to think it was
spoiled no no no no okay how do I go
somewhere where anywhere where you want
to where you want to I I don't know I
want to look at my options
again uh you could if you want to just
go outside the apartment you can just
click there I want to look at the other
areas is there like a gym gy go work out
I think there's gym
I think you have to go
wa what
[Music]
again I forgot you got to figure it out
okay
oh okay let her cook question mark you
lactose free milk bread you're making
food
yeah
oh
why I don't
know begin to think narissa isn't the
devil no no she did she did plenty of
evil things I did nothing evil a he was
banned for you I was just helping you
why why what what's wrong with him he
was so he brought shitty fruit cake that
is
enough imagine someone comes to your
house and brings you the worst fruit
cake you've ever had he he was just have
he was he had good intentions
[Music]
okay okay you're going to read a book if
you just want to waste time you can just
also just you know speed up y why speed
up not work is my keyboard
no yeah I don't know when I tried to hit
pause earlier it didn't work either I
the whole keyboard I think the keyboard
disconnected okay
now just want to waste time until 8:00
a.m. yeah okay you're done with your
turn huh yeah you've done enough damage
I would I would agree with
that okay taking over in 1 hour AKA I
don't know 10 seconds yeah same
time clock is ticking okay she's
uncomfortable oh my
I'm here for you baby girl I'm
protecting you you can't do anything for
another 10 minutes I'm your guardian
angel three two one wait there's no
there's no the good thing is that when
they are low on um bladder they take
shower they often pee in the shower yeah
oh my God I think she would do that
would
she no she she didn't girl girl okay um
well I can just buy one you better not
sell it
again let me get the cheapest one just
in case you're selling it again so at
least I make profit I'll get the baby
toilet no wait is that the cheapest one
no I think it
is
girl the things you s than this is going
to be an issue I don't really think that
like items that are necessary for life
should be sold okay I'll let you have
it oh wait she's cooking right now oh
it's like oh thank God what in there
what is in there did she put something
inside it's aume
yesterday be faster with the toilet girl
resume the bread why are we making
lactose free bread
why what bread doesn't even have lactose
I was hoping that I could burn down the
house by cooking bread but it didn't
work I wasn't quite sure how because I
already brought up my cooking skill and
you cannot undo such a
thing yeah but like if I just leave the
oven on like what's going to happen Okay
so I wait I have an
idea is that a guy
oh my God that's a guy that's plenty
well I guess a girl would work too but
yeah you already ruined my neighbor's
friendship to me so hello you're my next
object of
Love he's bald that's okay looks a
little bit like a hip hipster no hippie
I you've got a point actually with that
outfit support Ken's facial hair I
support your faal K he is K enough he's
K enough for me yeah
of course he is okay we need to we need
to fall in love
[Music]
immediately why did I ask him oh my God
that was that's not goodboy Feer
hboy oh sh we're definitely not close
enough for me to sh my yeah sorry that
was kind of weird that I did
that no friendly let's be friendly first
let's strengthen our
friendship uh
where the did she go where empty TR
why did why why was that's what she want
me to do you didn't get his phone number
you're never going to see him again cuz
he has to pee freaking Sims man I think
is he coming up to my room call him over
no he's
gone zo
hi thank you oh my God this ah he's here
thank God okay he's in the right place
already okay Compliments are always good
yeah who doesn't love getting compliment
exactly exactly sit down girl you're
kind of weird for standing up like
that no don't
read joke I don't know joke about
politicians Sur he'll enjoy
that basketball career VM
interest
um small
talk let's get know get know is always
goody he's unemployed that's fine oh
perfect the perfect husband for you it
doesn't matter I'll take anyone he can
move in and be your living husband you
get a job we don't have a job either we
can't judge someone who doesn't have a
job if I don't even have a job I
guess but that's because she was L born
yesterday Ask Ken to pursue D dream job
cuz we know that he doesn't have a job
wow oh okay okay we're getting we're
getting friendly can we already flirt
yeah maybe probably you flirted pretty
early
on depends on the person loud he looking
good
oh I've learned this romantic
orientation a
break
but I'm not interested in type of
relationship that mean I don't think he
likes women does he is he I don't know
quink koip no
way so I am sending him home goodbye
goodbye I can't believe it it's over oh
who is this oh he's cute I'm in girl
hurry up oh hey angle we'd love to have
you join up across what do you what the
is that Hugo I don't even know who
Hugo is girl go go go go to the guy to
the new dream guy why is she just
sitting
there okay bye-bye chunky wonky it's
getting really intense so it's probably
best for you to leave yeah oh they're
having like a cool thing
here I'm in a hurry oh hi
AKA why does he not stop for me why why
am I have to go so far for love where is
he oh he's
cute I could support this oh oh
really but you
w y
Yi Peach tell dirty Jo I'm not ready for
that yet why is it giving you these
options so it's like suggestions because
I'm in a floaty mood I see okay hi B
compliment I'm complimenting his facial
hair ask him if he's a mermaid I need to
know no that was bad once it will not
work this time where theck is
he hey hey hey hey don't leave this
conversation we're having a good time
here and I need
you I hope you're ready to be committed
are you
sing good mhm that's what his love
like let's go let's kiss his
[Music]
hands that might be a bit much he liked
it
sex ask about abrupt b m
spe hang out by the way cuz I think that
makes stay with me and go to my
place oh oh like I'm loving this person
I met five minutes by the way if this
doesn't work out he's next you're next
then you're on my radar got my eyes on
you I can hang out for a bit okay
wonderful pick up line
[Music]
Ain cool cool how about
vanilla
o how about we embrace
I can't believe he said yes to that
first kiss is it time can we really make
it is that is is that is to exchange
phone numbers
[Music]
yay speed running romance
F I am attracted to you
mis at kiss it's not it's spring it's
spring guys try it okay whatever it
means I think she'll hold the mistletoe
above and be like Oh
mistletoe talk about
marriage ask to be boyfriend oh yeah
well I mean if I don't lock him in now
you're going to ruin this for me next
turn yeah if you if you marry him talk
about
marriage I'll try but that might scare
him off maybe I should scare him in his
sleep H marry him in his sleep hey hello
wait I I wait sorry
sir bro that was
dangerous no he liked that was kind of
positive yeah he got a woohoo with wait
yeah ask him to be
boyfriend
oh was that I don't it's G
now a case should I really go for the
baby I guess wait what why
is goodbye to uh our previous didn't I
already say goodbye let's think by
here ch ch ch the
train
lo oh oh oh make babies Oh expand on
family I have
to okay as to be boyfriend yeah okay
woohoo wo and shower I think I woohoo is
just you know uh it's it doesn't make
the baby happen so I have to
specifically choose try for baby okay
try for baby in the shower
y y we're going for baby first oh my god
did he say yes yeah oh my what just
said wait
no and the notifications Ang has learned
salim's woohoo interests so what are
they give me the
Deeds why am I running and he's just
walking so slowly am I more excited
about this than he is I think
so yeah maybe I'm running I'm so ready
I'm so ready I'm on a time limit dude
come up here bro he's jiling he's slowly
slowly
arriving speed up time okay there he
is that is not the
shower
shower yeah yeah I didn't choose a
shower oh why would you do that my
most sexiest
pajamas now this doesn't mean that I
really got pregnant I think I don't know
if this is still a thing but if there's
like a baby sound at the end then it
means I'm pregnant yeah yeah yeah uh but
they may have that that may have been a
previous Sim game
W it doesn't always
work and also
M it takes a while to yeah yeah yeah get
the child out of my
body why is it still
going these SS prar to love the presence
of children and become happy for yeah
thank you for telling reminding me that
I hate
children oh my God I don't know if she
realizes that she she just made a baby
can't be help is she is she pregnant
know we'll we'll find out but she
immediately was craving food so we're
eating the lactose free milk bread milk
bread oh that's why it's lactose free
thanks dude I uh can you ask him to I
could probably but that ends it so
soon it takes you a while to have the
baby yeah but then maybe I can find a
way to kill you tomorrow while I'm
pregnant you want to kill me while I'm
pregnant tomorrow
tomorrow damn he's chilling too well
yeah I should ask him to move in yeah do
you even have that talk about marriage
again give Apartment keys I know STS uh
H I know her to ask to move in
but oh oh that wasn't me that
was yeah but he can just move in that's
invite to stay the night are you going
to stay T
[Music]
night move
in this guy is very
agreeable
and he likes to be
led you he even brings some money oh oh
my God you wanted money you wanted money
go this
Samba this
Samba oh she's pregnant oh what she's
thinking about a baby thing and she was
feeling sick all right
perfect about
marriage say
Steve I love this guy you met him an
hour ago already like yeah I'll move in
with you baby girl but we're great
together oh I didn't know I had glasses
in my pajamas well you were like let's
make a baby and he was like oh hell
yeah want to be my snug I can't even be
mad this is so
funny it's it's a romance Show on
Netflix you're literally just watching
Netflix Oh I fell I fell asleep oh guess
I'm tired yeah um I don't know if I want
to you know get married run away but
then otherwise you're just going to ruin
this relationship and I'm going to have
no baby daddy for my
baby so but if I marry now then the
challenge is almost over yeah only
almost what do you think guys well I
mean your goal is overall to end oh by
the way he may have moved in but I would
say we shouldn't control him yeah yeah
he's his own person and we are only the
guardian angels of I'm just going to let
him do whatever I don't I don't care
about him he does help cleaning up the
apartment which is
nice oh I at him he's a good guy yeah
what are his traits though I want what
kind of person is
he go away see he's a bestselling oh he
wants to be a bestselling author but he
hasn't written anything
so uh he has a job as a blogger oh nice
he will go to work m
he has some comedy and Charisma skills
cooking oh video gaming four writing
eight oh he has an incredible skill in
writing he's friendly with a guy called
Malcolm lrab land grabs are famous in s
oh yeah and he's a creative bookor lazy
and the
muser musers get better boosts to their
skills when they're inspired why is he
so horny Kim yeah cuz I made him horny I
suppose so
how many days until the baby is born
baby born baby born I don't know well I
think there's a set term like C set
amount of time but I don't remember it's
not very long but definitely it takes
longer than a day like maybe three seven
days or four thank you for the
memberships so don't you want to join me
in the bed and snuggle D she's sleeping
just skip until she wakes up I want him
to join me but okay
uh you can assign the side of the bed he
just left what the what she doing I
don't
know
neana Carini Carini isn't this the guy
guy who didn't who turned us down Ken
Ken what is going on here you should
flirt with him does he have a secret we
shouldn't lead him but you should have
him flirt with Ken can
now what what is happening where did
they go okay okay they parted ways okay
this is still on the he's still my
man for how long I don't know he really
likes reading maybe you should try
riding if you want to be an offer good
job huh okay um I think I should get up
soon I I'll be awake all all morning all
night I guess which is
okay what should I do should I marry him
or not what do you think there is s yeah
you think it's you can still ruin it
after I yeah I I believe in I mean I
don't know how but I'm sure I will find
a way
H oh I can take a pregnancy
test we'll do that 15
bucks he's on the
Move am I I think if you do a pregnancy
test it immedately will make her
shoulder belly or was that was that not
a thing I don't
know yeah
[Music]
she's then it's confirmed
Wooh I
am oh they're so
happy
crazy sa
[Music]
sa let's eat that bread really quickly
eat eat don't talk eat eat eat we don't
have much more time I have if I want to
get married I have seven more hours Sim
hours he's going to go to bed is it no
no he reads another book okay what Fu
every day he reads about three books but
never writes one aspiring offer he's
just getting ready this is so crazy
I should just get let's do it let's
do it oh oh they love each other
so
[Music]
much for posing here this is the moment
you're barely
friends let's go
will
bro oh wa what does that bring so like
an eyeball
on I don't know what's happening it's
literally an eyeball
this is the ring it no it's yeah that's
the new one a weird a weird ring yeah
why is it on the on that thinging angle
why
heav I mean you could TI up right here
right
now why
not you can still get me divorced right
after which
is how do I push this baby out of me
right
[Music]
now it's okay it doesn't have to be the
same person you know I can have a baby
and then you know get a new
guy oh oh it's happening we we're We're
looping congratulations that's a nice
ring
love it first
[Music]
kiss
you you on
your are you googling how to do stuff in
Sims nothing I don't know how to do
things why are you
googling she's Googling something on her
phone the The Sims
hacks helpful how are you are you
googling how to I'm not Googling child
my child no okay don't let her cook oh
I'm dizzy oh no oh no she's not okay
that's cuz you're
fragante oh wait this thing is
broken as a pregnant lady I will not
attempt to repair
this so I still have a bit more
time I can Moon babe
boy I'm back
what why is she so strange I have to
make our relationship so secure but I
think it's impossible like if you want
me if you want us to get broken up in
the next round you can definitely make
that happen no matter what yeah yeah
yeah just like you can get married
exactly with no effort true true okay
right well my guy this will be probably
the last interactions together the last
positive ones at
least just know that I will forever love
you no matter what happens let's let's
it in the shower really quickly cuz I
need hygiene too oh my God it's
impossible you're too
on
by what did you do we're woohoo in the
shower
oh
my all
right by
[Music]
Ste okay okay okay it just keeps going
yep plap plap plap you're pregnant
you're pregnant you're
pregnant you are pregnant though am
pregnant yes you can't say
that okay they are
happy
link wonderful I like the the
towels okay I need
[Music]
to make some somewhat proper food
here oo Yum Yum Yum
PTO
vamos Amigos vamos Amigos let's do
some oh there a
funny oh my you can like play with him
that is so cute yeah totally
realistic oh speaking of it about toast
on toast or whatever yesterday I for
Nissa cooked eggs and toast with bacon
with crispy bacon buttered toast with uh
fried
Sun side up but flip eggs yeah and bacon
crispy ass bacon from
Nissa only the crispiest of bacon I
appreciated it
yeah was it good was it yum was it was
it was the bacon better than the males
bacon yes 100% yes you have a horn was
it crispy enough yeah it was crispy
enough you did a really good job thank
you thank
you oh no
maybe my husband should be cooking for
me but he's sleeping right
now thank you for the memberships
duction oh she's so DIY eat it eat eat
it eat you only have two more hours is
she eating yeah
eat why is she coughing is it the
bunny oh way hey you need to clean up
the dust feed dust step you are not
welcome
here no need the FX something
broke
husand wait what is she doing she'll
probably oh complain to
landlord yeah yeah we complain to the
landlord I don't know if that helps what
does it do I guess the TV can't be used
or something yeah yeah
yeah this is really bad
yeah okay please fixed
it since you're tenant in good standing
I'll take a look oh God
nice oh someone's looking oh thank God
this is
before make
her she's breant why would you make her
do that what what the what what why
is
this why is why is she just sitting
there
landlord she's going to take a look at
it can you actually do it please
please please you thank you we don't
want to see a pregnant lady get
electrocuted
today
terrifying Doo to bed Doo your turn
thisa in control
[Music]
now thank God I saved her life why did
why did you make her go to sleep when
you had like 2 minutes yeah because she
any any second
counts
okay I can't believe you did that oh my
God you're so mean you're so awful you
can't you can't electrocuter now okay um
how do I go places again that's we we
still need to find that out how do I go
places I think wait um I
think
I think no I
[Music]
think wasn't wait phone they're saying
phone oh yeah
probably okay travel okay um close call
for real for
real I don't need to go with anyone what
are you doing I don't know you have to
unpause good luck I
guess devilish Diva time
and the devilish
Diva where is the gym that is exactly
the gym nice first thing you pointed at
yeah okay let's go to the
gym yeah Little Gym
oh I think Little Gym time I think in
I I I think I know what you're trying to
do oh
[Music]
oh go
workout she's got evil workout excuse
me at least she looks cute while doing
it yeah in your tennis
outfit
no
woohoo what's the plan Nissa huh she's
working
out just look at her she building she
getting
gains oh let's sweat what a
rush the Boost of
adrenaline you should say yeah okay she
likes
Fitness no no no where are you
going where you going yes run run you're
G an antic go to hospital
don't use the toilet okay yes let the
baby flop out let it out your limits go
to toilet let it flop out what's wrong
with you plop baby
out one go push really hard just do it
believe
yeah okay she'll pee herself soon
probably good get embarrassed in public
stop oh she's uncomfortable okay I I
guess I have to let her go to the
bathroom come
on
no yeah she's energized now so she's
still doing very
well what's wrong with
you yes if everybody occupies everything
yeah
yeah no no
no I'm back in
business no my husband is calling me
he's like why the are you trying to
unbirth the baby why
[Music]
why at least we're getting good use out
of that gym membership yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah you know we pay we pay for
this
so I want the option to do an evil
workout again she's too energized to do
that
she's so
dirty well well whatever makes you happy
n thank you I'm
glad she should be there should be
someone to kick her out like why someone
who owns this place the staff should be
like girl you pregnant you're dirty go
home
no
she is really dirty
though even though she took a shower
yesterday all this dud is chatting up
that lady they're ignoring the pregnant
lady okay that's fine who what is oh the
towel people there's two of them why are
they like
[Music]
this Ken he's
like no stop talking to
people oh my God she's making friends at
the gym
this is
impossible future
husbands no you don't need any
husbands why is it why did it select
him what's his name hecking I can't
hecking believe it I love
hecking
so does this kill a sim
eventually I don't know you don't know I
don't know why would I know cuz you were
looking up things maybe that was written
on
there and the whatever you looked
at or you just want to tire her out
completely girl they
can okay I guess she I mean I think if
they're like everything is in the red
then she might be able to
die but n Nissa wouldn't do that
girl I don't care that you want I don't
care that you want to take a
sh no well her blad is your smallest
problem because even if she can't go to
the toilet she will just pee on the
floor so okay go girl where are
you m why are you letting this happen
angle I did my best for you to get your
life evil workout yes
finally to get your life on track and
now yeah evil
workout so evil oh my God terrifying oh
There She Goes she's sleeping you can't
no let her sleep girl where are you
going no oh she wants to leave she wants
to take a nap a nap like you like you
love she's like let me talk to people no
what was that person's name Jen no idea
was that
Jenna
Jenna almost oh my God it literally
won't let her work out anymore yeah
she's she on
FL ask for help clean J no no no
no you can't let make your work out
anymore she's done why that's not fair
there's a there's like they have logic
in their brain too a certain
extent
girl she just keeps
[Music]
peeing oh my
God a you have only one hour left of
ruining my life can't sleep through it
sleep through it girl save yourself
she's so crazy you'll have a happy
ending un
yeah my turn I can fix her I can fix
this first of all go
home go home go home
immediately She's So Pregnant
go go home go home she hello thank you
why is she so heavily pregnant it's been
days oh what oh I I had the life hack of
the the pregnancy test which just like
in real life I think immediately makes
you makes you pregnant very very
pregnant apparently okay oh my God uh
first of all we need
food oh
man so
close you tried I H it was hard to watch
because it was so painful what you were
doing let's eat some mac and cheese mac
and cheese do you like mac and
cheese yeah I'm fine okay
well do you want to say what we ate
today for
lunch H dessert dessert yeah say all the
can you remember all the things I made
we had apple strudel today with vanilla
sauce yeah with vanilla sauce and then
the other thing was like a bread filled
with I think also Apple it's a b it's
like a yeah fluffy bread with uh filled
with apricot and then also the vanilla
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah it was it was
tasty MH remember what we had
yesterday yes we went and we had a cake
and then we had um little like they're
not
dumplings like little bread yeah
to curd cheese uh dump like round
balls uh with strawberry sauce around it
let's sleep properly girl
all I need her to do now is get like
birth the
child love day that's Valentine's Day oh
they have Valentine's Day and then what
did you drink
today oh I had a lemonade but then we
also had that uh hot Punch Yeah The
Berry Punch which is very uh common in
Christmas markets yeah yeah yeah it was
very tasty I loved the texture of
it like he really just spends all day
reading h
an in order to write something he needs
a computer and we don't have one that's
true that kind of
sucks and um uh do you want to explain
why my phone works and why it wasn't it
working in the first place okay so um
you know the most's phone randomly died
yesterday which was really bad while I
was taking the funniest pictures of
you and so we're like but we're
like you know it's no big deal we just
go home we plug get into a charger it's
fine um we tried multiple Chargers we
tried different outlets in the wall
different blocks different cords nothing
would work I looked it up and things
were like okay you need to press these
button combinations to try and basically
trigger the like it to turn on and then
try clearing the cash um alternative
ways were charge it on a PC which didn't
work so the last thing we had left to
try was putting it on a um wireless
charger and we tried with my phone but I
was like I feel like my my phone
probably wasn't strong enough so uh we
decide Kiana's like obviously I need a
phone yeah so we go to the phone store
and you know how they have the wireless
chargers down like on the counters right
so um she wait did you say already that
we tried to charge with your phone yeah
yeah yeah yeah um so she puts it down
and the phone starts charging while I'm
already discussing getting a new phone
with because I don't have a he said I
don't have a warranty on my phone so if
I were to send it in I'd have to pay a
lot of money to actually get it repaired
yeah and while we were discussing the
new phone I put it on the table where
there's a charging spot yeah and no it
works yeah so if that ever happens to
your phone uh try a wireless charger it
is not the port guys yeah guys it's
because now it is like it literally
wouldn't charge now we were charging it
with the port because we got it to like
what % at the store and then we came
home and then we plugged it in and it
charged just fine like it's literally
it's not the port it's not the cable
it's nothing like that that's literally
just you know yeah but yeah it charges
fine on the cable now it just basically
I don't know how to explain the issue
it's a battery problem yeah and it's not
the not the cable it's not the outlet or
whatever we tried everything and if you
look it up it's a common thing with the
with that phone M it is what is it's
like the faulty battery thing whatever
yeahum sad just
oh so yeah now we have I bought oh
what I that that low on
bladder oh
well you on the floor
maybe W like it finally got drained
completely and that that was what it
needed but
I really need so apparently with with
the phone model that we have cuz we have
the same phone you literally it all you
literally are actually not supposed to
let it get below uh 15% I think is
what's recommended and everyone will be
like this battery you should not drain
all the way like a lot of times people
are like oh when you get this your phone
you should every now and then let the
battery drain to zero yeah that's not
the case with this one you were not
supposed to do that every single thing
was like that's dumb if you do that it's
it'll literally break the the battery
but that's also kind of ridiculous
because I mean it happens and it
shouldn't be like a no girl a death
sentence for the phone yeah exactly
because what phones are like thousands
of dollars yeah so to like have a phone
and to have the battery and again this
is like a common problem with all of the
Samsung S 2122 and 23 models um it's
just crazy yeah I mean eventually it
will die that just happens even if
you're trying to avoid it so like die as
and go to 0% and your off that's like
almost unavoidable at some point so
saying that never that it never drain to
0% is weird expectation it shouldn't
be yeah no right like and but it was
weird because they did you you've had it
drained to zero before and not had this
problem so it's weird because like it is
just completely random like to feel
baby want to feel your
child we met yesterday I'm already
heavily pregnant with your baby we are
also married can I go to the
hospital birth him are you trying to
force the baby to be born you can't do
that I'll
try I don't know if I can what is there
a bring bring AA too bring
bring and this could have been us but my
devil angel ruined
it I know if feel
[Music]
really subp vabi oh
subp
oh wait oh by the way it's funny cuz
when when the when the phone started
working the STA the guy who still wanted
to sell me the phone I'm like well but
yeah no it he was so I I mean I couldn't
understand obviously but he was like you
you should still buy the phone you
should still buy it and I'm just sitting
there and I was like no no like and like
again this is a common problem and he
was just trying to sell her the newer
model of this phone which also has the
same problem yeah like which still you
could literally look it up like everyone
has this problem with this phone so the
fact that he yeah I was like he really
wants that
commission yeah So eventually I said
goodbye we're fine yeah
no I know was there a hospit I feel like
I feel like I saw a hospital before I'm
sure there's a hospital I don't know
where excuse me yeah he lost his
Commission because you had already
picked out the phone and we're talking
about buying it kind of yeah like cuz
like he said if I want to have it
repaired the battery then that'll be
like 300 e and yeah maybe I should just
buy the new phone because with your
points and going into the minus with the
points and then paying some money it
will only be 800 for you the new phone
it was so insane because I'm like I mean
I think I've told you guys this I had a
I had a note five and I had it for like
over a
decade because it just worked it just
worked it it worked I never had that
many issues with it until it just got so
slow and it got to a point where like
apps wouldn't update on it um there's a
there's a a vet CLI
Clinic yeah where is the human Clinic
guys can you look it up on on the
internet I want to check if I can induce
birth oh yeah the notes were great
ones so it it really sucks that like the
Samsung Galaxy s22 whatever are like the
new notes but like they're not as good
Willow Creek they're saying
really oh I already check that let me
check again um
hosit that's a museum that's a nightclub
that's a gym that's a library
[Music]
libr doesn't look like Civic what Civic
what what are you talking about what's a
Civic Center where is
that bless you you can't they're saying
you can't speed it up without cheats oh
really okay okay let's go back
that's okay I wonder how much longer it
takes are you going to in the next turn
just do the same Sports thing again the
gym thing what's your plan lady I don't
know you don't know I don't know cuz
obviously that didn't work okay it took
me some time to regain all my greenness
mhm but
still didn't work oh yeah let's shave
let's shave like here while showering
you do that thank
you yeah no um the good thing I don't
want to get a divorce I kind of like him
thank you you know he's
great yeah but um you know I always get
ask like why do you have so many phones
well but in this case it was helpful to
have an extra phone and old yeah no I
was so grateful because obviously I
don't have Wi-Fi here so like unless I
use roaming data which is not not smart
um you can take family leave okay o
great nice cuz the baby's coming
soon she's
[Music]
happy at least for now my phone will
live a bit longer for a while but I
wonder if this will like every time I go
to zero if this will happen now well
just don't drop to zero it's okay cuz
now we have the the wireless charger
which fixes yeah well we need to figure
out how to set it up because when we
plugged it in it wasn't working so I'm
not quite sure what we did
wrong maybe we should have bought the
more expensive one the Samsung one not
the offbrand one yeah the Samsung one
was way more expensive the wireless
charger MH and I liked the offbrand one
more though because it's an actual like
phone SC you can like I could use it as
a you know know no same
yeah like I could put my my camera on it
too my appphone wow she got so good at
cooking yeah it's not fair it totally is
no what else can I do like I'm so happy
with life everything's great I got a
baby on the way actually I think I have
an idea you need to decorate a room for
a
baby no no cuz the the baby the moment
the birth is over the game is over yeah
but like you've got 4 hours and like
nothing to do so
I
[Music]
um just want let it out let it out let
it go here before she lets me suffer
again we got to keep those needs up as
much as
[Music]
possible I can't believe you literally
got someone to marry you within a day
but W you agree I'm just that Charming
you are thank you would you also marry
me in the day yeah y I literally kissed
you today because you asked me at the
beginning of stream she kiss the girl
and she like it the taste of her cherry
chapstick have nothing to do life is
perfect right now life is just a
Beautiful
Bliss why do they why they're reading in
front of the book and yet oh love day
and in front of the bookshelf and yet
they would with all the books here after
they're done yeah what's wrong with
them oh it's almost it's almost time for
you are you ready do you have a
plan yeah I've got a plan doesn't really
sound very confident I'm not but I have
a
plan ah it's over
okay okay it's nara's
turn what you doing
[Music]
you little
uhhuh no
no
no you're just going
to
no you're not just going to like burn us
all I don't
know I don't know how would I even do
that I will I no no no fire fire light
the fire no fire fire light fire
[Music]
fire I don't know if you can
even
no I would love to have a bench like
that that's actually so cool that is
pretty freaking
cool don't help her guys what are some
flamable objects I can put around the
fireplace fire fire
fire don't tell her don't tell Sparks
like the
Flames no you keep up keep up and go
your own way you can't do that to a
pregnant lady you you're killing two
people at once then at least let the
baby out first
no but put the baby the
baby okay what else what else what else
does that really work okay we got a we
got a rug what
else
no
um all my hard work of building a
[Music]
family no no no no no uh sofa chair oh
yeah
chair I don't even know if this is going
to work have
mercy no have mercy no no no have mercy
no don't kill
her what what remember how sad the guy
will be I don't care but you liked
[Music]
him maybe she's got them divorced
instead this is
murder doesn't this count this easy
murder no I feel like it kind of does
but it's okay I
guess you have to give let's see how it
goes let's see how it
goes okay um how do I stop buying
chairs no no no you can't have her stuck
in a room that's like keeping her stuck
in the pool no it's not it is well I
don't even know if this is going to work
so no you can't do that that's we said
no letting her die in a pool but getting
rid of the exit of the pool this is to
save me okay well nothing work it didn't
work so it might need some time guys you
lied to me it's in the
balls what's with the trash Oh Oh
kids
[Music]
guys you have to bring the door
back you can uh use this one and then
click on this oh that's so
cool put something in like that blocks
so no how do I flip it how do I flip it
yeah like just drag it
[Music]
over it is it because the trash is in
front of the yeah might be the trash
well how do I wa Okay click on the trash
and just move it somewhere not that one
the other one but okay that works too
probably okay door door door door door
door n the maybe move this trash I
you can click on
it h any door will do
anyway oh there we go why is it not ah
cuz this this wall is angled probably
that's
why um oh thank God guys it didn't
work it didn't work you
guys guys why did you lie to
me said chairs name a bush the bush my
work
that's way too
big I don't think this is going to
work whatever okay I'll help you how are
you helping me but pressing escape cuz
you don't know what you're doing oh
thank
you
so what you going to do
Nissa I don't
[Music]
know what is this
noise what was
that you just notice it now it's been
there the whole time I think it's cuz I
raised the volume too
much just some did some weird setting
here I don't know
why it's fine there's BM the people
won't notice it won't hear
it
[Music]
oh you meant a different sound you mean
the
the no it was like this it's just a
weird sound you
know and that's you can turn S sim
autonomy
off you
you by default it's always on we should
have turned that off no that defeats the
point that makes it really hard for me
because they won't do things that I tell
them to you just got to get controlling
your excuse in the end we're just
guiding our Sim but she still has an aut
auton me will I told you to do
something oh my
God sometimes the Sims or the humans
just don't listen to their guides in
their you're cheating then they're
saying and I think they're correct what
the one person said that and I don't
know what the you're talking about
how was I
cheating autonomy is just always on it's
just how Sims work and honestly that
doesn't really change much why is she so
evil it is kind of cheating sorry how is
it cheating mhm rigged kfb bet
tril how is it cheating how is cheating
because then uh they forcibly renew
their things so I can't be fully evil
and stop them from doing it she the same
way that you call that cheating it could
also be like a a demerit or a negative
thing for
me because like she could decide to do
something evil cuz you made her evil be
mean to someone because that makes her
happy being me chieus cuz that makes her
happy she could do all these things and
it could be a problem for me too and I
have to stop her too yeah but it we can
just stop her in that case mhm so it's
not really a big issue how do I turn
things I don't think it'll
[Music]
work just like
so I don't think it's going to work
anyway all my plans are
foiled because you're just too good you
get married in one
day I can't even like set the house on
fire even with the do so they can run
out I can't even start a
fire I feel
[Music]
like there may have been better options
for you in my life they I haven't played
in a while and this isn't like The Sims
2o you could do so much Cur in the
Sims tomb like the moment you stop it
stops the cooking process if you move
the
and previously previously in The Sims
you could you could start
cooking and then oops I should continue
with
it what she just stops to make out with
him she's like
oh but yeah you could do so many you
could like make a row of ovens and you
get one to start on fire and then you
turn them all around so they all ignite
and they'll all stay cooking but here it
stops if you stop paying attention to it
maybe you got to be more creative but
yeah definitely they there's not as many
ways to kill a sim and Sims 4 as in
previous yeah no there's not like I I
can't even start a chair on fire even
though you sang the song fire fire the
fire what why am I on him no wonder that
was you right you starting the fire yes
that was me starting the fire you did
start the fire but it's a small one yeah
it didn't do anything
it's just a really cozy place
now only Sparks can light the flame
Sparks light the
flame keep up keep up dude where is she
going she wants to eat and you gave her
a chair I did give her chair she
appreciates the chair offering from you
clearly Yum Yum Yum why you letting her
eat I don't know why would why is she
not doing any of the things I tell her
to do well she's just like oh I want to
eat instead oh I want to go to the
bathroom and I'm like girl you're
canceling everything I tell you to do
just we are supposed to be guns though
what guns what guns like look what is
she
doing she's just like I'm going to go to
the bathroom you could sell her I've
already clicked you her I'm going to do
it I'm going to sell I'm going to sell
the toilet it's because K is cheating oh
my God
how was I cheating she literally took a
door away trying to lock the Sim into
the room okay yes you guys are little be
bias I need to be bi this garbage is
bugging me girl what what is you
doing um maybe um she can't put it out
because the chair is in the way she
can't yeah you you have to move the
chair to put it out oh she can still
warm herself by it though
why is she coughing girl she she's sick
on things that's not good she's pregnant
that's that's not what she's pregnant so
it's the one who wants to kill her she's
pregnant but you worried about her being
sick well I don't know what to do all
the ways you can easily kill a simmer
like not able to be done in one
day and I don't think you can do
anything practice singing flaunt wealth
bit your pore
she's so crazy where's she going oh
she's swinging the Garb I will accept
[Music]
that what you have a lot of time
still why does she have a platee why did
she set it on the mantle by the
fire what she doing I don't know oh she
wants to talk to the neighbor
like what does that sound in The Sims uh
that's her mood changing into tens I
[Music]
think this is what you have to put up
with try to read some advice people are
saying a pregnant Sim can't die oh
you've literally got immunity M more
fireplace it would be really ethically
wrong to kill pregnan Sim so you're
right
um even taking away the ladder pulse
Doesn't Kill The Sims anymore they can
just get out easy oh my
God I mean that's just logical I mean I
can get out of a pool without a ladder
seems It's just getting better because
it's getting more realistic but that's
also I mean for for trolling I guess it
gets
worse what is that music it's just big
gem from the
[Music]
store
why does it sound like that guys there's
only one dishwasher they're like buy
cheap appliances I don't think you can
do that anymore oh what she ples what
with that before don't worry about it ah
electrocution is it backwards yeah you
can dra no you can like uh
uh uh
wait
[Music]
Kiana trying to help me destroy her
life what
right put this somewhere
else oh
yay how they have no counter space
though that's so
sad who needs counter
space you need to manipulate this place
anyway yeah don't give me
space order some
fireworks what fireworks
do fire fire light the fire fire fire
light the fire imagine what would happen
if somebody L the fireworks on fire in
their home in their apartment oh she's
heavily
[Music]
pregnant okay cook cook cook what are we
cooking chocolate cake in the microwave
all
[Music]
right got the
water waggle wagle like a pregnant duck
like a pregnant duck oh wait I saw oh
look she has like marks all over her
body cuz she's sick you see that the red
Mar oh God what is she sick with I don't
know I guess it's just her immune system
got cuz she played in the
rain
maybe can't upgrade
it or no no no I have a better idea
quick meal hot
water hot water
okay like they're like put metal in the
I you think I can just put metal in the
microwave I don't have the option to do
that the game knows what I want to do it
won't let
me we can we can try to think of
another like way of winning for you that
is not too easy not too hard working out
to death because she just kept forcing
herself to go to the bathroom and
shower
um cook something and leave it you can't
do that anymore it stops the cooking
process I
tried I don't know why the husband okay
I'll give you the option to kill the
husband I'm not killing
him I don't even know how I can't put
him in a pool you bought a house without
a yard so I can't even build a pool you
could
move but yeah the we have no
money and we have good amount of money
and when you move you get I think some
money back
too bro come
on what does she keep doing with all
these Waters that Mak
well yeah maybe you should have tried
those things before I got
pregnant the gym on the day one instead
of ruining my
relationship I didn't
know guys it's not
[Music]
breaking I don't know what she's saying
oh she's so S I kind of feel bad for her
wa this is so
sad oh e e i mean at least water is good
for her throat maybe Steve Troy
Troy the way she angrily slams open and
and closes the fridge she so angry oh
she peed on the
floor so now she's showering
dirty oh someone's calling her hey Angel
it's me oliana do you want to go out on
a date who are you I'm
married yeah but as a deil maybe maybe
you want to to cheat I want to
said no you don't want yeah you can't
kill a pregnant character even if
they're stuck in a pool or on fire
they'll keep generating gravestones but
they will not
die they generate gravestones apparently
well we could take that as a a does that
is that same
that's so crazy that's weird does it
also happen like in theory if there's a
fire yeah well you know what if you
manag you start a fire fire maybe I'll
consider that as a win maybe if you
start a fire and get her on
fire you could try that but I still want
to set the house on fire even if you
won't die I just want to set the house
on fire I need give a try I can't it's
not working you can't just give up
already
be more
creative guys help me how do you
actually start a fire in The Sims these
days this doesn't make any sense I can't
just turn the oven around so they can't
get the stuff
out what what's a new notification was
making that sound the spice festival is
in town spicy
spicy cook grilled cheese fail cooking
kiata saw to that to make sure it
wouldn't happen right away in the very
beginning
I had a plan I had a plan I guess we'll
see if we can visit and maybe order some
fireworks oh go kind of broken I how do
I break a stove I can't just you could
probably order it from your phone I
think but a broken stove no no the
fireworks
oh you pray for a bol to fall on the
house light a
campfire does a husband have cooking
skills we can't control him that's part
of does but
yeah we can't do that that is cheating
if you want you can control
him girl go in knock knock knock knock
we need to use your computer let me in
let me
in oh nobody's
[Music]
home
well go home Hey Nobody's Home nobody's
home nobody's home nobody is home I try
the phone yeah yeah yeah how do
I how do I try the
phone there's a phone down
there second one is a
phone social bunny Trend shopping okay
okay okay okay I don't want gifts wait
you're trying to buy firewalks yeah can
we not I don't I never purchased firew
before is that really in there I don't
know that's what they seem to be
saying I feel like it's just in the
normal
shop I you can only die from over
exertion with old
age oh
really if you stack playful happy moods
you can get a Sim to laugh to death yeah
yeah and you can also die from
embarrassment which she's right now very
embarrassed so you're getting there
as far as I know you can die from
embarrassment and a lot of you can I
think you can be scared to
death wouldn't that be nice yeah no
fireworks you can't buy here oh I'm
pretty sure fireworks is dying of cring
is real in in Sims it is yeah have you
ever been so cringed that you died
inside yeah definitely died inside yeah
yeah yeah any emotion on EX excess can
be Leal yeah including Joy anger Etc so
you can try to get like Mega Ultra angry
or whatever happy or embarrassed or
energized what if I just eat so much
food can you die can you eat yourself to
death is that a
thing who are you trying to talk to I
don't know who that is girl chill if you
want we can turn to
thing
off where is I don't
[Music]
know
yeah well she's so embarrassed I feel
bad for her well she peed herself how
can you embarrass her more I have have
some ideas but
[Music]
oh wait wait read let's go let he said
let's go embarrass our ourselves I'm
literally asking W can we embarrass
ourselves I think the baby will
literally be born
tomorrow that would be nice that would
be a happy day
okay oh oh yeah no B oh no don't be
oh you can embarrass yourself of a
shitty performance self-deprecating joke
that sounds
embarrassing damn that guy's Su is
amazing
yeah what would won't be embarrassing to
you huh there so
think don't really get
embarrassed about things I'm cring and
free so okay you you've you've you've
basically lived with me for the past
however long yeah so you know yeah I'm
not really I'm not really the type to
get I guess oh he got promoted
congratulations what a happy life my
husband being promoted I'm about to bore
bear his baby bro a so
happy so
fulfilled
Grio
girl oh that's my fault
how do I get her to go up these ah you
have
to click here on the then you go up the
floor wow fancy
place oh that's the wrong thing oh and
then here you can perform down there
okay let's um steal the
microphone practice acting that sounds
embarrassing for all these people
acting is terrible
yeah this person's not good either you
can die from a vending machine reliably
kick vending machine can what what I
that's what really is this person why
are they GL they're famous they're
Global
Superstar everybody who's sparkling like
that is Superstar or like a star can you
become a glowing
[Music]
Superstar tell some jokes yeah so
funny therea tell me a
joke why did the chicken cross the
road to get to the
KF that's not funny that's just
reality it's so noisy here it is pretty
noisy can you tell him to stop he's
embarrassing maybe
[Music]
um I think if you talk to him it will
stop
already turn off Fame
shine how is this a famous person they
guess you don't have to be
good oh thank God good
good did I
in front of everyone I did no no and
they're still just fine with it they
like
yeah is that our neighbor it is p
p no she's getting better M
Moby they like they like the joks
they're not really listening yeah I
don't think they're they're ignoring me
that's so
when you're so bad jokes don't like fail
just get IGN
yeah she peed herself in front of famous
people that would make me die of
embarrassing well someone says they
don't blame a pregnant Sim for peeing
apparently which I mean they do I do
hear they like to pee or like can't hold
back from peeing of the it just
like easier to pee so yeah because the
baby is pushing down on your bladder
stand
okay oh the talent showcase is finished
so nobody's listening though you just
want
to what's the plan
Nissa is there a vending machine that we
can try I don't
know she's like dying my dude she's not
doing very well she's not doing very
well she's very
uncomfortable I don't think there's a
vending machine here is there one on the
first floor I don't think so there was
like not really anything on the first FL
true except these
stairs okay let's let's ah
there's she's gone into labor she's
bursting
[Music]
no oh what do we do now well even if you
don't send her to the hospital she will
it will eventually come out yeah yeah
yeah yeah okay wait
so h no just click on her um I don't
want to go home I want to try to I want
them to tell us where a vending machine
is because she can't die while she's
pregnant I think someone said uh in
the uh what no in the in the Japanese
World okay okay okay I
think let's see let's see
here okay where is the vending machine
here
probably
[Music]
maybe yeah these are all
residential wait is it isn't there
another
one they got comini Park shopping areas
and such in here yeah what would I be
someone else was another one in the
skiing Resort
SW I guess then oh oh wait there's some
more up here uh what's this onand B yeah
guess I've been here
before okay I don't know maybe check out
the part yeah yeah yeah let's
go we're going to try to kill the
unkillables give it a try I have no idea
how the vending machine thing should
work I'm going to pause it paused yes
okay no it's not okay
um here we
go but you can't kick it oh yeah we have
to we have to get it to not work is what
you guys are saying
oh so like the like it would give
electrocution or what I think
so no no no no so it falls on
you she's going to pee herself again y
maybe this time when she pees the baby
comes
[Music]
out I want the melon soda going to buy
seven AR intrusive thoughts what's your
intrusive thought buying five drinks and
not drinking them
SS I shake it I have the option to shake
it but not to kick it
bless you thank
you well it says it's not working
already it's
stuck right
yeah she has proven Victorious against
her fold a stingy vening vending machine
only stuck items can now be found in her
inventory maybe now the vending machine
can sit and think about what it did it
says okay Cupid's cupcake that's so
expensive oh and then oh does it like if
it fails it crushes you yeah falls on
you well okay you have um six more hours
to try to make that work we just need to
like keep ordering too many things cuz
that seem to
work crushing an in
labor
lady
passed out wait dude is she wait did she
is there the baby is the baby out yet no
no no no it'll start automatically
in probably an hour now baby come on
yeah two hours baby born baby born baby
boy baby boy wait you want a Bo baby
born baby born baby born that's like
what do you want want a jingle of like a
baby
pupp I guess in in Europe that you can
buy it's like a Barbie but it's a
can
pee which is great
boo love day was awful says our husband
we have disappointed him our first
Valentine's Day together I mean what did
he expect to a person he decided to
marry the same day he met them much he
expected much I'm just saying that's $41
there grapes in there just grapes I
don't know that's amazing fruit vending
machine but they're so expensive they're
$41 yeah I think grapes are expensive in
guys how did I get so lucky that it got
broke the first time and get broken
again maybe seven is my lucky number but
you purchased eight now it's
fine knock it when you try it what do
you mean you can't just knock it you
have to you have to guess wait for it
bro I bought so much from the
vending
machine guess I don't have to cook
anymore new boo baby new baby is
[Music]
coming let it
out let it
out it needs to come out bamboo bamboo
it's
done want to see them no she did it
again she sucks she won again the
vending
machine may
maybe maybe the vending machine does not
want such a thing to happen it it
literally it literally we have to
go
oh you want to
bring we can only bring one
oh why can't I only bring one
person it's it's an intimate an intimate
can I ruin the birth somehow I mean I
was wondering this whole time why don't
you just divorce him I didn't want to
that's too that feels so easy you know
but I
mean okay I can't help you then yeah
like here we are in house I wanted to do
something more fun than just sabotaging
your cuz like you can build a
relationship in a day but then I can
break it in a day and that's just not
fun yeah but I want to try to find a fun
way it cost me time yeah it's true and I
may have a baby then but I'm not um
covering the second condition why are
they still talking
about marriage you're already
married well sometimes you got to talk
about marriage while you're married I
guess
oh
well baby incoming
outcoming show me the baby are you done
already I still have to Telly where is
she going oh because she she talking to
him now
what Saar did you click the
voice you
did you
did I was about to get my
babies he's still a part of our family
and lives with us
no my
man okay well now the
baby that's uh probably very shocking
for him like what the that's why B
what is happening what's happening with
the machine is it girl little boy oh my
God what if the machine kills her in the
end e that would be so crazy is that
Mayon what's happening put that
heart back
in oh my
go I'm so confused open heart
surgery bring the baby out this is not
what you should be doing why are you
surgery
her how is Bobby it's a girl it's a girl
what do we name the baby H I guess did
be days cuz it's the last name
m what do you think thinking
of what if we named her after a
condiment a condiment mhm Mayon yeah
Mayon May
Mayon I like it I love
Mayon twin well his name is ketchup yeah
what that's like beautiful what a what a
lovely what un believable we
can't handle twins alone there Isa I
need the
husband wait it's still your turn though
I know so good luck handling two babies
without a
husband he's feeling
flirty you can still fix it you can
still fix it he's still loves us
overcome your evil uh oh no he hates us
brain brain worms we can fix this
I don't know if we can fix this come to
the good side come to the bright
side he hates us abandon the Bad Evil
side Nissa come here love baby beautiful
Follow Your Mother
[Music]
instincts
apologize
a she's coming around she's she's in in
in reality she's not a de she's just
look she looks like like man oh but
why why are her needs did bth like
maximize your needs that's amazing I
think so oh I guess it's like a like a
high after having birth yeah oh oh are
we bringing the babies I hope so where
what probably are you going home did you
click go home no oh they kicked us
out baby doo baby baby is baby here yeah
oh baby we can make baby room and
[Applause]
may if I ever have
twins I will name them
this I'm so happy to hear it in memory
of our
collab I don't know if you should do
that oh no I love it may and ketchup I
don't know can you get back together
with the SIM after
you you can you can I can probably make
it happen pretty
quickly well you need to get remarried
so yeah that will be my final step cuz
now the baby it's not only one baby it's
two
babies look she was in labor he can't be
mad at her she's you did this to me two
hours you could try to kill me I don't
think I can new I to
fire yeah
cuz now I'm not married but I have the
baby so one condition is fulfilled the
other one
isn't I don't know what to
do there's
a there a E burn it froze into
the fire fire fire light the
fire are they just talking I'll give you
I'll give you instead of uh I'll give
you two extra hours cuz you're just much
slower than me cuz I'm better at SIMS
you are better at The Sims there's a
plate on top of the fireplace that's she
she put it there cuz she was
lazy yeah put that away so she can do
all
that ba guys but it won't it literally
won't it won't do the
thing but maybe it really was because I
mean I guess it would still Start the
Fire it's just like you know a lucky an
unlucky thing sometimes it starts a fire
sometimes not maybe I don't know yeah
there's literally a rug yeah I think
it's a chance thing doesn't always
happen
obviously fire fire light the fire I
want to see if you can repair this
relationship Miss
brismas I we can make if you if you fail
this now I will fix everything you have
to cuz now you're single with two
children I'll I'll I'll seduce him back
why is she in a flirty mood
is happy baby makes Happy
Mama what happy baby makes happy mom is
that is that it yes I'm it I can kill
her now but she won't
die Bae has joined our part will
just do over there
e e this apartment we're moving
after this
[Music]
real
finish can you take care the baby while
she's trying to you know yeah right like
a lazy dad do something he's too
sad he was divorced he'll get over
it get over it fire fire let
Polie
please light the rug on
fire I honestly I normally don't try to
kill my S so I really don't know if this
if there's an issue with how you're
doing it I don't know I don't know
either but it's definitely like a chance
thing it doesn't always mhm do that
so campire I think that's that's one
this one mhm rocks of fire you have no
space for
it
oh that's right where the rat is very
convenient let's burn the and the
Rats out of here that's totally what
you're trying to do right you just
trying to clean cl's apartment before
the baby lip here because you don't want
or just rats and babies living
together yeah yeah yeah exactly that
would be
terrible she has good intentions yeah
good intentions girl why are you sitting
down no let's go oh
oh
oh your turn wow I did say give you one
more hour it's okay it's okay she did on
fire so
close your kids are going to die if you
don't take care of them yeah no it's
okay turn it
off okay so we can't go well I I'll get
rid of it actually you you can just sell
the fireplace and on the chairs
yeah goodbye
yes goodbye fireplace this is now as it
should be a children baby
room mhm maybe you should have made a
nursery like I told you
to because now you're divorced the game
didn't end immediately when you had
kids yeah cuz you divorced me right
before which now gives me a little bit
of extra work de she was going through a
hard
time
she was going through a hard
time I understand it's stressful to have
a baby yeah I mean I can totally
see a situation where a couple well like
during labor has a fight oh yeah you
know okay good luck BR about baby ha I
had the baby that you gave me but now
you're not
[Music]
not what
a he didn't just leave ask if single is
a crazy choice to
oh is there like apology so I already
did so now you can just it was in deep
conversations um maybe Deep Thoughts it
might Deep Thoughts oh deep
conversation let's talk deeply about the
that just went
down ah no toilet no toilet how how does
this keep on happening where does this
toilet
go don't understand where did it
go it's by a nice one God a baby a baby
toilet
[Music]
baby it's mysterious it's quite
mysterious okay oh my oh my
first oh yeah yeah yeah just delete
everything like that nine nine
yeah get rid of this get rid of the
garbage too e oh this I can't can I not
yeah okay that's fine I mean with cheats
I could but it's okay we'll clean this
up
properly actually this is this also
works what I don't know why Sims do this
like waste your time with this this one
doesn't work
somehow okay thankfully our husband is
still ex husband is still taking care
he's being a very good dad to his twins
well I'm trying to you know that's my
dream to have twins the opposite gender
yeah mhm and call the Mayon and ketchup
no your dream came true
nista can you imagine all this time you
were trying to like not make this happen
but the game wanted you to be happy so
it gave you twins it's like oh it's a
girl and a boy
yeah crazy like I think when I
used to play Sims and all that in the
past past past past I think I even used
cheats to make twins happen yeah oh my
God I did too I remember there was like
different like woohoo methods where
depending on where like in the hot tub
or something it was more likely in like
one of the earlier swim s yeah I think
so too yeah but now it just happened
naturally to us it was it was it was
meant to be oh he's feeling
flirty let's get back together he he
just likes
everything he literally hates you and
he's like oh yeah you want post all sexy
he's just really sad it's okay desperate
I'll fix it
all fix it oh are they fighting
theat maybe they just freaked out by S
oh charisma skill here Embrace Embrace
Embrace we don't have to go immediately
to kissing oh yeah just going to take it
slow take it easy yeah but they're so
funny I still love
you I'm sorry I was acting kind
of bro this is
crazy oh he takes care of the baby okay
okay then I'll you do that I I'll eat
something yeah make some food as I
wanted to I'll even serve uh for
everybody so faux BLT what does that
even mean how do you make a fake
be vegetarian safe and lactose free I
don't know why why so there's no bread
why would I make that so it's just
lettuce and
tomato vban vban that's a salad yeah
right here Coran food K
jimim what's K Jim K Jim I'm not K
Jim I mean obviously C you know what
it's
soup is it a yeah rib St rib St make
girl dinner what's girl dinner why was
she's too sad to
cook what what she's very
sad no she can't go there what do you
mean you can't oh oh yeah sorry you're
going to have to sell the um oh yes
oopsie the micro
Wall E way I can't do anything there's
no counter
space makes sense
now there we go o
yeah that looks
good on top of eyes
yummy what yeah yeah eating while
looking at the Cockroaches M and the
rats and a Dust
Bunny I don't think children obliterate
do it do it do it do it do it do it what
does that mean I don't know how do we
obliterate fails oh my God kill it the
fire oh there's a hole
here okay wait so when she finishes
eating now I'll just put fill the hole
oh she puts a thing in there ah
oh oh the rat's right there yeah I has
to go back
inside I hope that did is it coming out
again cuz it kept on coming out pretty
quickly oh these diapers oh my god oh
jeez stop all this oh my God come
okay I think the I think it's dead oh
did you put poison in there no it's just
the the snappy thing oh nice okay dude
it's like okay let's just let's just
make up let's just make up it's
ridiculous we're meant to be together we
literally just had twins like that's a
sign how do we get back together SW kiss
I can't that's cuz he's still in the
red okay oh true okay ah wait that takes
a lot of
time okay no no no we can do yeah he
likes you really
easily
me I almost went for different two
different guys but thank you for ruining
my other
relationships you love
him he's a good guy oh he peed
himself in front of me that's okay I
love you even if you pee yourself in
front of me you should ask him if he's s
do you want to show with me oh my God
you're not you're not there yet no we
not sad let's hold
him stinky I think we need to rurn back
on their ability to do things by
themselves ah oh yeah for him that's oh
no but he is he is doing stuff but he's
like also not you know maybe it's yeah
okay cuz I can't we're not allowed to
control him wait disable autonomy for
selected s okay that's good yes oh but
wait we also have to turn it off no on
and then yeah yeah yeah so
L the babies what's
wrong what's wrong what's wrong what do
you
want so far only daddyy has Del
baby what we
treat the baby like you treat your cat
throw a rock at it oh
no I don't know I was literally didn't
know what that meant for
moment okay you're crazy that
worked ew e what about what about
eradicate oh one is obliterate and this
is eradicate funny mhm finally he's
taking a shower thank God he's stinking
the whole place up for real even the
babies are
upset stinky
winky
[Music]
stinky I love who's your favorite Telly
Toby I don't think I ever had a favorite
one I didn't care that
much it's crazy I can't I can't
say I like Po
PO is my
oi I wore a PO is a red one right yeah
he's cute he's
small
yeah
me baby care change dirty
diap where' she go oh I have show oh
please wait for me baby okay thank God
there's a
Daddy thank God he didn't leave after
you divor him you
oh he even woke up for them man this is
like real life H like a be we had twins
you and
me a there's a in the bed uh there must
be a hole in your room somewhere maybe
yeah whatever it's okay I I I accepted
just how I accepted Casper no F put a
trap in the hole wait wake
up we have to continue our relationship
problems here can we can we go to
therapy I want to go to therapy can you
actually request that I don't think it's
a
thing he's romantic orientation he's
exploring he's figing stuff out what
because
or why is he
uncomfortable well now he's also
flirting because of the Rat rude
awakening oh yeah okay
never wake up a la oh because I woke him
up it's okay because he's flirty so just
flirt with him declare love
publicly I don't know who else is here
but I'll say it publicly yeah I love
[Music]
you
AB that's okay baby has priority that's
okay that's
okay I think we're out of the red yeah
no we are out of the red you're starting
are you single yeah are you sing do you
consider yourself
single me we divorced but we didn't end
relationship we should probably sleep
yeah
I'll rats let's I want to the
first I hear fighting from the other
part
yeah who's fighting the neighbor Penny
pizaz I thought she lived alone I guess
she had someone over oh well now he's
still awake so h
ke ah okay okay I have time I can
go to sleep okay okay wake up wake up
wake up and what's this stinky spot here
I have no idea maybe it's like a bug
from the diaper like it's just over
there stop biting I'm trying to
[Music]
sleep you have to get out of this
apartment bro they're
crazy oh the R's back what's going
on doesn't work just doesn't why is it
cuz you're not together
[Music]
anymore you might as well sleep more I
don't want to wake him up so I'll just
turn on the TV which will wake him up
too I think pee like a
champion the you deserve it
sh I'm so tired again okay it we
have to wake him up we need get
married baby needs a DIY
change I'm getting help good morning
good
morning very very very good please let
me marry you
please
me a
why can you get married again if someone
you wear to yeah
totally he loves he loves to
[Music]
flirt I'm actually running out the
time this is not so easy I mean you got
him out of the
red I did but you can quickly change
that
this is not riged from the start guys
this is actually difficult as you can
see yeah you could have way earlier you
want to he could
[Music]
have now actually it's more difficult
with the babies yeah cuz we have to take
care of the babies too and
sleep how much do you want we're like so
much in the pink
you are not so much in the pain you're
not even
[Music]
halfway it's going up so fast we we boy
be a
boyfriend you're speed
running wake him W him okay he became
your boyfriend okay we can't sleep now
we have to we have to talk about
marriage was an option propose wake up
feels like it could be paranoia it could
be wait it feels like it has been
forever since salm has been romantic has
been romantic with his partner it could
be paranoia it could be anxiety or a gut
feeling but Sal can't help but wonder
what his partner is up to or who they
are seeing behind his back what I'm not
cheating on you but of course yeah I can
understand the
anxiety he said yes of course he said
yes what a toxic relationship all right
no l immediately
what the
I'm on the floor and no no no no wake
up wake up I need to L
immediately I'm still in my thing right
okay okay okay I just need one second
to yes why is he
crying who's happy Happ
[Music]
tears it was meant to
be no second we we have twins we do
everything twice you know we got two
babies we got two
[Music]
married well
congratulations you did it fair and
square happy we found out I'm not a very
good
devil I think it's just maybe it's more
to do also with your sim skills yeah you
got to work on the Sim skills it be
easier if we owned the house so we could
like do more stuff you know but but this
work this
work well okay it's
over
it's so over but
it's it's a good thing they're happy yes
they're happy our weird family we
haven't saved once they'll be deleted
once we exit the
game no let's save this family I can't
believe it twins I thought I honestly
thought Lissa would win killing her
seemed much easier I thought so too but
apparently getting married is like a one
day not even a whole day activity you
and yeah getting a
too I can't believe it I can't believe
that you just did that I
mean yeah Sims are just they're so easy
to romance yeah I mean I I I I I guess
it feel like in Las Vegas or something
maybe some like iral humans they also do
that sometimes you got married and
pregnant in one day but then getting the
baby out took a while only 4 days and
then you managed to divorce the moment I
had my baby no before my baby and then
you know that's because I wanted I
couldn't get the thing to crush
you the end though the time I had only
three Sim hours left so otherwise I
would have been back at the vending
machine trying forever to crush her
Crush buying drinks crush
crush
yeah well I mean okay whatever you guys
say about fairness I didn't know this is
what this was my first time it's okay I
didn't challenge nobody did it ever
before so I didn't know like what is the
perfect way now we know for next time
that the optimal way is to turn off that
and or just different goals different
yeah yeah I say maybe we we make someone
in advance we do cheat in some money
just to buy an actual house because it
makes it easier to manipulate than like
a small apartment you can even house for
the basic the first the starter money
it's just a shitty house yeah
yeah but no kiata wasn't cheating I was
messing around not cheating I was
cheating not I wasn't like Lally
cheating yeah yeah yeah yeah I mean I
was not following the rules I removed
the door you brought it back all is okay
yeah as long as it came
back but yeah but you were too ni I was
even cheering for you at the end yeah
and you were too nice to to him though
and I I help you he's a nice guy I
trying to help you yeah know she
literally helped yeah me failing to be
evil round too rather than us
manipulating This Woman's life we were
manipulating each other a little bit
there yeah yeah yeah but no not
manipulating but I guess helping and
that's kind of manipulating ourselves oh
my God is that why he felt like he was
getting cheated on because we were
cheating in the
game cuz I removed the door he's like
sometimes the door is gone there was a
fireplace and then I I W I went to the
bathroom and came back and it was gone
he's so
confused the real victim is St for real
this poor
guy well it that was fun yeah it took us
a while to I was scared that this would
be over in an hour and I mean we could
have probably ended in an hour if we
were really into it you could have but
yeah free hours
good tomorrow guys I'm going to do
probably uh one last solo stream CU I
feel you know that I I I I I should do
one last solo cuz there's been so many
collab streams yes before my break one
last solo it will just be a Super Chat
reading I think it'll be in the evening
my time yeah n this was our
last
forever but I love you
well that's you can't you can't do this
to
me you can't do this to me no we'll do
collabs in the future we still want to
do the Smash Bros collabs yeah we have
to again since we were foiled the first
time by the internet I want to play all
those characters
that I want to play all of the links you
you don't want to unlock them yourself
no it takes forever it does want to play
the fire Bloon character yeah you're so
cool well we'll do it
sometime and honestly uh I I really
wanted to get like Sims multiplayer um
mod permission yeah I kind of like asked
for it like millions of years to go but
I think I need to apply for it again
yeah and see if maybe this time I'll get
the PRS it's too hard cuz then we could
like even play with like five six seven
people and that would be really fun
that's so crazy it would be like an mm
we what if we force move out the
vampires from The Vampire house and then
we move in yeah that's what I always to
do you just want to live in that house
okay okay it's a pretty house and then
we can sleep in coffins oh or you can
temporarily marry Kaleb have him turn
you into a vampire and then kill him
okay yeah if you want to get rid of him
sure
yeah so okay guys thank you for watching
today today today today do I sound like
M no today no no
today I really love intimida intimidate
today not tomorrow I don't sound like
her at all either today yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah that's it yeah you need to
have a she always has a little bit of a
rest yummy she's so cute yeah yum we go
to sleep now I'm sure you're tired there
is some yes I'm going to cuddle with you
against your will not actually
we're going to cuddle with the keto it's
one cat for you one cat for me yes it's
perfect and now at the end can you give
me a a consensus of my cats I love them
right they're so cute I I I'm
convinced now that I need the same type
of cat yes which are a Cheeto and a
radioactive cat I I need a Cheeto and a
radio like I just I'm so in love with
them they're so cute they are so fluffy
but you already have cats yeah but like
they're not my cats they're my sister's
cats but now it's different to have your
own I need my own Cheeto you know and
and and radioactive cat they're so
lovely but I think I think honestly any
cat it doesn't have to be that same
species any cat will be lovely I mean
but I have I have two cats oh and
they're they're they're but I
love them but they're like other
siblings yeah little
man but are you serious like anytime
soon or like in the for the future
probably in the future cuz like getting
one now while you still have other cats
yeah in the same place yeah I know
little lady when we first got little man
she was really stressed she started
licking off all the hair on her stomach
that they had to get her a little soup
and they got a pink one and she looked
like a raw turkey because she's so fat
raw
turkey but she loved it she loved
wearing clothes so okay that's cute yeah
I wouldn't recommend getting cat now in
the same place with all those cats there
just one day if you ever move
out ever one day it'll happen for
example when you move to
Austria yeah
totally I keep on telling her to move to
Austria yeah she's desperate for me she
won't it h it's expensive it's no no no
no no but you love everything here so
much like the smoothies I do I can't
believe it they're so cheap and the
calories are so much lower than like
equivalent smoothies in the state and I
just think that's crazy she she bought
like four different uh smoothies cuz she
got so excited and then didn't you buy
even more no no you got to buy I wanted
to I really wanted to but I can't take
them with me when I eventually
go they don't have Culver here either
that's true no they're no cers no but we
have those movies and they the the
they're really young yeah even if if you
buy the offbrand ones they're
amazing oh wait one more thing I want to
say absolutely amazing guys remember
when when narissa said like she doesn't
like jeans and this and that today she
gen genuinely to me said um I think I
want to go buy jeans like yours we
didn't though we didn't well okay but
keep in mind it's because okay I want to
explain
myself I'm in you know Austria and I
noticed everyone in Europe is like in
general more well-dressed obviously
there's still some people who are like
wearing sports care but like in general
people have like really nice fitted
pants really yeah like I noticed so many
people have well fitted pants no they're
not just skinny jeans trust me I've seen
just skinny jeans well fitted to me
sounds like skin no but they're like
they're like trousers they're not jeans
they're like trousers and they look so
well dressed even like when I was like
at the airport like you think people
would just like we
said that yeah American airports
everybody dresses like BL yeah but
like everyone was so like well dressed
and I was like wearing like leggings and
I was like bro and um I wore leggings
throughout pretty much the whole trip
because I was like oh it's cold so I
don't want to wear the skirts I brought
um and we're walking and eating a lot so
it just makes sense because it'll be the
most it couldn't be NE and comfortable
but I was like it would be so nice to
have fitted
trousers yeah I'm I'm fascinated she she
came with me to buy shoes today though
and can I tell them about that machine
yeah oh my god there was a crazy
machine I stepped on it I'm sure
you have it in the merch I have never
seen that before and you stepped on it
and it like literally perfectly measured
your feet so the guy was like this is
exactly the measurements of all your
feet in like 2 seconds all your feet
yeah and then he was like let me go I
can find the perfect pair for you and
then just went and gra yeah that's
normal I don't think it is person is
German oh I see we do have it I've never
seen it before I've never ever seen any
SAR yeah sure I'm sure you guys do the
only feet measuring technology I've seen
is putting your foot on a little rug to
see if your shoe if if your foot fits in
it and then underneath it says the size
maybe it's like cuz like this store
wasn't a shoe store it was like a sports
store so like it's not only for normal
shoes but also for like measuring your
ski shoes and all that it's pretty
important so maybe maybe these more
specialized stores yeah like running
store shoe stores whatever those maybe
generally have those measuring machines
but now you know crazy now you know like
immediately he pointed out that there's
a specific brand of shoes that has the
perfect measurements by default for her
yeah for my foot width mm and yeah that
varies yeah and then so I said we have
the only fitting shoes in the whole wide
world here in Austria narissa so that's
another reason for you to move here she
just wants me to live with her she she
now that she just want to let me go guys
she's grown attached to me what are you
going to do for your own good
uhhuh I love you I love you
too but I'm sure that after this after
this uh your family will be like don't
you even consider moving to Austria you
can't do that no no be like you are not
allowed to go anywhere ever again
no but yes thank you for playing
Sims yeahum guys ask her for for ustra
tangents when she's back home you know
she has to talk about it we'll have lots
to talk
about I'm tired so tired let's go to bed
let's go sleep okay
okay and in German we say bye your
darling sorry well off Fe
in by darling wait say it again I'll no
the other one by
darling
remixing
remix okay I'll
the
[Applause]
[Music]
a