[Music]
bye
do
[Music]
me
everyone's okay john mutes go go
[Music]
wow
welcome everyone to the first ever full
whole live english collaboration
[Music]
wonderful i hear a lot of motivated met
crewmates only crewmates of course
oh let's not talk about it
we're going to talk about it especially
about you finally it doesn't matter if
you hide behind that little
block there
just a potted plant
i see a green root
vegetable
i just want to mention what happened
before the stream we had a little uh
testing session and uh we just wanted to
play the game seriously for once and
then
after a little while we had no reports
which was kind of just so fanna
did an emergency meeting um just to you
know because she was obviously scared
and which i was too
um she reported okay she did an
emergency meeting and then what what do
we see free deaths
she's not subs because she made the
meeting but turns out she was the
imposter how reckless is that
not to mention she weren't you also so
easily yeah she was my imposter and she
got voted out in the first round oh yeah
definitely immediately
sana's life as an imposter was so short
oh my god i'm surprised you even noticed
there's a color that's better suited to
you yes i was
wasn't sure i wasn't sure if i could
enter or not listen well welcome callie
you're not feeling good we forgot to
start the streams oh wait
wow
but
unfortunately apparently so
it never
um so i would like to get some
introductions from everyone and we
stream up yet
is everyone
are you ready
are we all ready yes
yeah okay i have a stream going okay
okay i can hear you guys all around
[Music]
self introduction can you all girls give
me a reason why you are not today
starting from amelia girl oh why i'm not
suss today um it's because i'm naked oh
okay um hello everybody i'm amelia
what's good hello live english miss
number one detective and um i'm not
wearing pants
that's why you're not stuck
yes
i can't if i don't have any pockets to
hide stuff yeah were you honestly if i
was wearing pants i'd be more what was
worried you know
[Music]
representing chaos everybody how you
doing can you stop vlogging because we
have to follow you in order to hear you
proximity baby
sorry okay i'm not sucked because um i
got a cute pet look at my pants oh yeah
it's a win purchased a little hamster
you bought it with real money
it looks like a bug
real human dollars
[Music]
wow that's kind of kind of weird
what interesting
all right um so yeah um death is real
sus but guess what everyone i'm not
death i'm the sheriff around these parts
and because i'm the sheriff the sheriff
is never suss the sheriff obviously
didn't do it um
some people may say i i shot the sheriff
but i did not shoot the deputy meaning
i don't know what that means it just has
something to do with the sheriff and i'm
not i'm not suspect so there you go how
can you be the real [\h__\h] whatever you
can't even spell sheriff right
no that was because now that was because
there wasn't enough room for for me to
spell it correctly
all right
listen i'm definitely
i'm the sheriff
that that is very necessary yeah
i don't know
because there's only one all right who's
next who's next we're gonna get kicked
who's next
no my name is fauna and i am simply a
potted plant therefore i cannot kill
enough people for today so your deed is
done
no no no plant has never killed anyone a
little chocolate forest doesn't really
ever
never i remember that musical
and good um
please and why you're nuts
hi my name is
here what's up everybody oh i'm not such
because um
[Music]
i'm gonna get kicked hurry up all right
please thanks
please oh hi
it's iris live english project hub video
slash
uh
i am very excited i
am a hundred percent say so i would
never lie which is why i would never
recess
that's not what happened to my voice
yesterday
[Music]
a very very um
good self-introduction while a lot of
people mostly just say hey my name is
is
[Music]
oh yes
hello my name is cronie oro from
the council
and
i am blue
yeah
um it seems like your senpai has stolen
your color
but i'm a more royal color royale
so
okay okay
where's the blue okay don't look at the
color objectively look at the color
that's inside all of us
she's right she's right
all right um uh wait did cronie say why
she's nuts us oh right i'm not sus
because look at this i'm wearing a mask
i'm doing my uh part
in this situation don't get close to me
[Laughter]
well i tried to social distance but i'm
not sized because i'm doing my part in
the society
and for you
i'm an upholder
i knew it
alright we'll hide this one
you guys
there's like other
oh yeah mine says that too
hi mike muted
i don't think so no i think you have to
start a new stream yeah there we go
because once it starts before we go
bye we're back my mic was muted
[Music]
stir time is always on time
everyone made it okay we'll continue
with
nasi lemay actually i am the guardian of
civilization and i am an apex predator
of the sky and i could kill you if i
wanted to
stop that's right
but i don't want to so i won't
okay
i believe that because you are so
peaceful
i think
[Music]
um
the
priestess of the ancient ones
i think yeah sometimes i forget but um
oh
i am not sauce because i'm already dead
look at the the halo above my hand
that makes a lot of sense all right then
thank you ina
next stop sana is not streaming but
she's here so please let us know who you
are
we're flying through sinai right now
um hi hi i'm sana sugama from honey life
english council
it's been a while hello guys
i have a big limiter on my head cream
if anybody thinks i'm sauce i'm going to
take it off and take all of you down
with the oh god oh my god oh that's a
threat that's us that's really
reassuring to back into the space where
you belong right or
part of it migraine you should be fine
you should be fine if you get kicked out
i have no i have no reason to
oh um well
i'm very happy to have you here sana
thank you for participating we're really
glad to have you as part of this even if
you're not streaming thank you
yeah yeah
and of course the future will be
back soon
[Music]
and uh i am the one organizing this
and i'm really happy that we could all
get together 11 people is a lot but
we're going to have a lot of fun today
so let's get right into it are you girls
ready to go
[Music]
[Applause]
hello hello
oh my goodness statistically speaking
wearing clothes oh yeah because i'm
civilized
hey
i'm sorry
i must do my tasks
they call to me
free there's free lemonade here
oh yes this is the thing from animal
crossing
oh
oh yeah oh i saw one of those the other
day
is that doc
oh there's two people dead
fana and and callie are dead look look
at the screen
ivana and callie are dead but we need to
call a meeting
wait they're already done yeah
where's the button
i don't know i think it's up i think
it's above above yes how do you know if
they're done look if you check this uh
it's a screen yeah there's vitals right
here
oh my goodness that was quick the
sheriff's already dead they must have
spawned with two other people who
spawned like in the same spot what's
this hmm
so you guys are safe then i bet because
it must have been two people who killed
them because there's a cool down on it
yeah so us three are pretty safe right
now
[Music]
oh my god hello
it looked like either iris or big it's
probably both of them
it's iris
and they put it in front of my face
or was it good enough right in front of
my face
wait hold
[Music]
we just got started should we do a new
lobby i don't know if it's gonna be any
better though
i'll try fixing it but maybe i don't
know maybe reinstall a mangas or
something because you had that before
where did you spawn
where i spawned yeah record or
in the middle thingy there oh records
okay uh
where did you spawn
i spawned in the in the i was by myself
it was the room with the folder on the
table oh records okay iris where did you
spawn
uh where did i spawn let me look at the
map real quick the engine room a
detective
i do not have never really played this
map um i think somewhere like in the
main hall
okay well me sana and cronie all spawned
in the cargo bay and we were all by
ourselves and we checked the vital
screen down there and cali and two
people were yeah they were already fauna
and cali were already dead so whoever
spawned with them there were two killers
with them and they both died at the same
time so it could have been iris and bay
i was alone i did not wait hold on
right we're talking about the beginning
right all right i'll trust good on this
this time
uh
i appreciate it lots of really all right
iris it's true
[Laughter]
virus
bye rice
i'm gonna say sauce
girl's a rat
wait
uh onion lettuce onion
onion
lettuce
what a disgusting burger
can anyone vent i thought only imposters
could vent
i'm a crewmate right
am i
i just have to clean the vent oh
guys i spawned alone for real this time
but it's kind of nice nobody's around i
can talk to chat
get the [\h__\h] out of
here can i jump
[Music]
wait a second out of the questions that
i asked them kiara and gouda said they
both spawned on the folder but gooda
said she spawned alone
and kiara didn't have any
he didn't have any uh
input like that
i think one of them is lying maybe it
was bae and kiara after all and not iris
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
get away
wait oh you're safe right corny
yeah yeah i forgot that we were here
together we're the safest oh
this yeah you can develop as a ghost you
can develop some photos
[Music]
i opened it
hi where's bae
i don't know she was just with us
i'm scared
this map is too big i'm going to the
lounge if i die i'm sorry uh cody said
okay bye
you have to just press tab then you see
where the tasks are tap tap tab oh
yeah now you can run around with the map
okay
okay out of all of us
hey
asus
like that is it the space bar
um it's a it's a card sway mission
i don't know how to do this
i'm even talking to myself are you even
are they all supposed to be on
yeah oh okay i think i did it
it's kiara
nobody can hear me hello
hello
hello hello good day
where are you
tada
click me oh it's pretty hey
so whoever kiara was with sana last so
it might be kiara
we should
we should go press the button and have a
meeting
why don't you just press it i don't know
where it is where is it oh there's a
report button on your body yeah but you
have to be on the body i didn't find the
body because i was looking at the vital
screen
oh okay
i
got in there yet how do we uh i don't
know i have not left this area yet i
need to go up
to
so you have to go
we gotta get down to get up okay i'm
gonna follow you
okay if i was an impostor i probably
would have killed you already unless i'm
on cooldown
[Music]
i have found this body but i have
absolutely lost because i was running
around a while here and i
met no one close by there was so i guess
someone said you were seen last with
sana what do you have to say about that
no no no no i was singing last week
so who's done with their tasks right now
because i'm done
i'm not done yet i'm not oh i'm actually
also done
yeah you're done with your tasks huh
i can say though well it says total has
completed but i think that's something
that an imposter can do like show that
show with the delay that it's i think
they can fake that i don't know i've
heard it yesterday anyway uh uh i think
crony can vouch for me that i'm not cess
right brony what do you think
well i i know that watson and sauna were
definitely safe because the killings
took place when uh all of us were still
around
and the only people who are considered
suspicious to me would be
bae or
honesty my guys then we'll just check um
yeah we'll just stroke yeah i'm gonna
check uh bay
first and see if the uh the taskbar goes
out when she doesn't
um i don't know what i think that's us i
don't know who to vote for
i don't i'm out the whole way like how
amelia is trying to control this whole
room
no no no watson's definitely in the
clear because i was with her
with sauna
well i can't undo my boat now
that's kind of suspicious what if i
don't vote because i got stuck in the
bathroom for the entirety of the last
round because i don't i didn't know how
to open the door i don't know who to
vote for it yeah
go with your guts
i feel like if it wasn't based
she'd defenders my gut's out of the
toilet i couldn't see anything i thought
it was bae but maybe it's kiara yeah
chiara is a
a little suss
for me
because i don't know
i can't even begin we're dead now we're
gonna die
oh you choose where you load in yeah
yeah of course we can hear each other in
this screen
all right we got to stick together
yes i'm gonna check
i'm gonna look for bae and see if she uh
if her taskbar goes up oh okay i don't
think i've done all my tasks so i
i probably should do that
okay i'll i'll just follow you around so
then okay wait the tasks are like those
exclamation points on the map right
yeah yeah
okay
so you just have to open the map and
just keep going there
okay
hey
following you guys are you
yeah good
good good
are you done with your tasks
okay well i got a task right here
um
like yesterday yeah it was fine hello
i'm not sass okay
okay
no no no no no no hey always walking
around alone
both are pretty so it's not gonna lie i
gotta go this way
oh you didn't hear that
this way
hello
i need to go to the viewing deck oh uh
this way
right here good uh
hello
hello oh god
how do you think okay i did it
somewhere that'll take us far far away
pretty sure it's kiara
well we'll see when they if we see bay's
body on our way back up
wait
i was with her for a little while but
she could have been on cooldown
i don't know
is there a cooldown like when you spawn
in
i don't know but uh but uh yeah much
though a different imagination
so i'm going to the showers if i die uh
let's look at the camera the bay's all
alone and the engine
hey guys hello what is this
we got split up
[Music]
gary's doing fake tasks
i will kill you i'll kill you
okay maybe it's not it must be baby
hey what are these thingies here
where are you guys on you there's like
doors here with uh thingies
i'm a business are you gonna uh you
gotta start with number one and then go
to two and then three
okay
who
are you
[Music]
[Laughter]
and i left her and i ran him around
because i'm done with my tasks and i
found goodness dad is awfully quiet
no yes
if you have been with me i couldn't find
anyone i was trying to find a bunny
where have you been where have you been
just now
yeah hold on let me look at the map
where was i um
let us make this quick though so that
ina can come back yeah immediately
uh voting began
i was checking um bae in the
surveillance camera and
she wasn't really doing her tasks she
was just walking around around the
maybe i mean were you doing tasks
yes
what were you doing what was the last
task you did
um it was in the
was the exact mission
uh it was
something emptying the trash in main
hall
uh-huh anyway
tara what's your favorite
tiara yeah
what was your last
the one with the the the code where you
have to enter like a diamond ruby
emerald diamond code for example was my
code and then i would have had to go to
the other side to input it what part of
the map
is at the
um
i think it's between
storage and like developing room the
question question question room well i i
know i know for a fact i had just seen
kiara like right next to me uh we were
together by the doors that opened and
closed and then suddenly she reported
somebody but
if she killed them and i was the one who
reported the body too right yeah this is
my second body i'm reporting yes
okay all right all right i voted for bay
[Laughter]
you won't regret it
no no no no no no
seriously
bye bye baby
[Music]
wow
you really threw iris under this
was it iris was it her
it looks like iris on my screen though
she as i don't know if it's
i don't know iris did kill me
[Music]
[Laughter]
i was
[Music]
hey
all
[Music]
um
leave
[Music]
yeah me too
i'm also the sheriff
um
you keep on sussing your senpai huh
why would you put the blame on me
what
i've been the previous round right i
think it's because you
are so uh
experienced to
say it first
and i always think whoever says it first
is suspicious
uh
i feel like imposters are usually very
quiet like they try not to talk because
they don't wanna unless they're very
experienced in that sense yeah
yeah yes
people are usually the worst bust into
the room be like all right so who did it
[Music]
hi hi
everyone's just like uh you
you
you did it
oh i think that's huge like oh no wait
okay
[Music]
all right which one of you suckers is
the imposter um it's probably you callie
it's probably you
oh so it's cali
it's cali
is kelly looking in the future already
yep i'm the imposter
[Music]
thank you i hope i'm not an impossible
okay
sorry about the box by the way yesterday
yeah yeah it's okay i mean apologize for
the fall waiting for it oh wait
you can't
i saw i saw the blueberry
[Music]
and you know it doesn't matter anymore
i'm gonna
because i'm getting in i'm
gonna reopen the lobby one more time
all right
okay um
[Music]
hello
ah
are there like specific rules on it
kiara
that's okay it happens
ah
are you guys oh that's why my opinion is
not that not that good
it's not that fast we gotta have discord
on a different uh audio channel nerving
me i'm just sitting here in silence
sorry
screen when typing code that's right
yes
is there a new code yeah i'm still all
right i'm calling
yeah
maybe maybe we can try i i don't really
think it's closer but let's try maybe an
asian server
we can we can try
do you want to try you know or should
maybe someone else you guys can try it
someone else can try making it okay i'll
make one i ate in asia everyone okay
sweet raw chocolate
okay i never been to asia before
oh wait should we not just play this on
stream
i'm not saying it okay
the coda's code okay
[Music]
did you get in first try
yeah that works um though if if i end up
block screen again just just go on
without me it's fine
i want to hold everyone up
okay mute the discord
it doesn't let me join is it because i
have to change my region
uh oh yeah yeah
[Music]
hello
cheers
[Music]
[Applause]
my god
[Music]
i'm all alone
ah
watson why are you so scared of me i'm
not doing anything
why
oh god there's a violence look check
this check this you can see where people
died here
no one's with me she can vouch i didn't
do that what the [\h__\h]
hey you guys
you trying to think callie are you
trying to think are you trying to think
hey callie can you hear yourself
thinking oh my god
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
this is where i can do a test
[Applause]
holy [\h__\h] the only thing i can say about
that the only thing i can say about that
is that i heard kelly's voice close by
for a moment but
that was like i didn't even see her
close by i only found the body like a
few moments later
there's a lot of tasks i
[Music]
i saw her coming up towards me and i was
in the armory which was on the bottom
left side
and that's very funny
together but kelly went off pretty oh
callie you're in the keeper
you weren't doing any tests now you said
you weren't doing the tasks
oh god i don't want to play the [\h__\h]
game
calm down
if you really don't know how to play the
game i will give you a tip now a serious
tip press tab to open the map so you can
run around while seeing the tasks and
that is very easy tap tap yes
did you
that's enough to throw me out
i'm just kidding what is that noise in
the background it's me
charlie says for now i don't know
um
i've never been to the brink finish this
test okay so oh hi
oh no
oconee i want to see you guys oh wow oh
hey wow
oh well you know she's gonna find out
she already knows now
all that she needs is to find the body
i don't know where i'm getting it can
you hear yourself thinking uh
[Music]
we know what you did you know
yeah
i wasn't to kill the time duo
we know the sins you've committed
[Music]
where do i go
i helped
[Music]
you're so haunted
very very peaceful game and i haven't
seen
what
just
what are you waiting for oh there it is
[Music]
the toilet door
i was about to go uh to the very very
bottom decided to kill me right after
going to the toilet we used a toilet
right after the toilet
um because when i found iris
[Music]
can
you
but i didn't go up i came from the other
side
someone's in the bathroom
um
here's a better proposition whoever's in
the bathroom pink posters let me spawn
back in while i see you come out no
[Music]
i mean i was running around with santa
at one point
lost
okay
okay i don't know well found us us for
now
what
why
not talking
i don't know maybe her mic
maybe her my sensitivities no cuz i had
no idea she was talking to me
hello
um
i am
main hall
i have some tasks to complete
ina
hello i am just
talking
[Music]
she just had to respond
maybe i can get i can bait one of them
into saying something
i'll ask them questions after i finish
my tasks
this
sweet
you know i can't hear me
yeah come on
i thought uh
imposters could hear us
i have a weird feeling do we do we look
at this thing oh my gosh i cannot play
with my task
i saw something
i see only the person who killed me can
you hear me right area
before the wreck
um when i was about to enter the
rankings area i saw kelly so i wanted to
say hi so i followed her you're [\h__\h]
kelly next moment she completely
disappeared i want i went into all other
like like uh
ways to look for her but she disappeared
and there was a vent right where she
disappeared so ben
walked out of the room
you can vouch for me i went down to the
bottom and tried to go through the event
and i couldn't
let me talk
let me speak
okay
what i mean is there was a vent down
there and i couldn't get through it
because i'm not the [\h__\h] imposter
that's what i mean
went down at the bottom i was trying to
go to the pride
i was
[Laughter]
why else would you call this a [\h__\h]
suspicious emergency meeting
imposter tactic you're sounding a little
desperate callie
i'm gonna skip for now i don't know
yeah
you don't have to vote i just want to
mention it i'm gonna fight
no we should read it
[Music]
be a good sheriff
how's the killing going huh you doing
you having fun be a good share
this map
callie can you hear yourself think what
if i
trust you
hey callie
where'd you get your hat callie
where'd you get that hat me i'm just
trying to look at where the tasks are
i'm peace stay here the whole time cali
i'll follow you
nice and clean
yeah is that a task you're doing that's
crazy
that's a really short task
oh i have been murdered
anna welcome to the club
oh by ina ina can hear you but callie
can't but kelly i killed her or she
killed me i mean so
oh
why did you hear that it's just like how
it's supposed to be kelly is it
chad did callie kill you yeah
okay yeah yeah i'm surprised people are
not voting her off
she's the sheriff i haven't seen her
kill this around the hang of it i'll get
the hang of it uh
what are you talking about
you have a good hang of it
the hang of it people are not
[Music]
[Laughter]
holy [\h__\h]
you're
shaped like
[Music]
yeah carol is with us too actually yeah
yeah they're fine they're all fine
[Music]
leaves them
[Laughter]
literally kill someone and then report
them immediately
all right well i don't like you pointing
the finger at me babe and i think that's
suspicious so i'm gonna point it right
back at you
on your boy i'm just trying to be a good
[\h__\h] sheriff
your boy
sheriff
callie in your next
[Music]
and it is
were alone but i did [\h__\h] nothing
anyone who would vouch for kelly is
there anyone listen um
[Music]
why are you pointing your finger at me
i don't think i can vote over can you
see me
no you have a reason why
why can't you vote
because i'm so unsure
oh they're right
[Laughter]
you know went and
backstabbed the sheriff
but at this point everyone had something
about someone vouching for them except
kelly it's really good
hey
for example i don't know how to sabotage
[\h__\h]
you just open your map
okay let's go do our tests
[Music]
i need to ask them later because that's
a big game changer
so you could or she couldn't hear me
i can hear you now oh sometimes you cut
in and out where am i did you
oh okay it has a filter
oh
[Music]
a little more go a little more crazy
nuts though
what's right
[Music]
yeah somebody threw away a whole pizza
in the event
one more task left
[Music]
one second
oh one more tesla good luck you know i
guess i have all my capacitors by the
way
this map is big
what's this
all right i guess we're done
yeah you guys like my sweet hat
my brain hurts
oh no
what the mermaid doing
okay
let's see
oh no again i'll be moomi's guardian
angel
yeah a big hat for a big brain
let's see what's this thingy
let's see these arrows again
somebody never played online oh i didn't
even see that
okay
i thought that was a okay um
i'm almost done almost
oh my god
she's gonna yell again
iris
[Music]
huh
now
is
kept saying that she was lost and i
thought that it was
suspicious
what was the last task that you did the
last one i did was the one where i had a
dress
[Music]
who has tasks it's
it must be bae
hello
hello nina is a very good imposter
yeah there aren't enough people maybe
someone has to go to the left side i
hope someone's going to the left i go to
the left side please someone please go
to the left side don't kill me don't
kill me don't kill me oh no oh no
i could have it was moment but it wasn't
callie
it wasn't callie
what i am following kiara
did you do your tasks
i did okay oh my god i want to go to the
meeting room this is scary where is xena
we have to go have a meeting
we have to go have a meeting we gotta go
get a
there why do i'm not here to leave
everyone
hello hello oh they're joining are you
joining
me
oh my god
[Music]
so i have a question so when you're
imposter and you're like going
pretending to do tasks etc can others
tell if there isn't really a task there
to do
uh no
you know what so
like if you're doing certain like if
you're asking to do tasks that should be
probably longer because there's really
long time that kind of can stand out
that you're
done so quickly
what's codes showing okay
[Music]
sorry
smooth entrance okay oh i can't not card
anymore
okay
let me see what i can do i don't know
this game
give us a statement of how you were able
to hide your imposter-ness for so long
um
i blended in with the crowd you know
even if i could make the kill
i i waited for my chance i was patient
because it was my first round too so
she didn't know
the moment
performance yeah so genuine you actually
went around my heart
oh yeah i was asking eena not to kill
two times hallie could you hear me well
you're always so sorry
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
i could tell
oh i wish i wasn't
let me
boy
hey connie did you get impostor like you
wanted
oh no no i didn't
how about you
well if i was one i'd kill you unless
i'm on cooldown in which case i'll
follow you until my cooldown's over
and you know
for me
saw
[Music]
god that can you explain what girl did
what did she do excuse me hello can i
have the floor please she was walking
out explain yourself electrical
after
taking off kiara's ahead
excuse me
yes self-report because you panicked uh
excuse me i have a question
was the shark near the washroom no
questions no okay i saw
[Music]
i was humming the berries in cream tune
and i was like i know where electrical
is
[Music]
did i stop by the washroom
and i spawned in the place with the
folder on the table and i went right
down to electrical i don't remember how
what's happening never stopped by the
washroom that's pretty good
i forgot how was that
i just walked every time every time you
were in the city you would do something
in the washer
oh
she wasn't in the washroom
[Music]
we just spawned in i don't know i'm
pretty
i'm pretty convinced okay and your story
is starting to stink good because you
didn't shower
can i
can i can i have a moment please please
i have no enemies
i don't know flopped her story she's
gone from meek and shy to very suddenly
very demanding of the room's attention i
do i don't know
obviously
you're sounding a little
defensive thank you
i have nothing to say about any of this
i wanted to have more room
okay
someone followed us
[Music]
i need to make a burger so i'm going to
go to the kitchen
you should know what's going here it's
good hello hello
do the tasks
right
um
what is this
oh
i see
wait [\h__\h] diamond square diamond
reminds me of like the monster
who is that like oh somebody's in the
showers be careful because i believe
so i believed you last time
okay i remember
i got a photographic memory
feels nice the warm water um
[Music]
uh
i see i've never done the test before
can other people hear that can other
players hear that
uh
make a burger
don't kill me cronie
uh i won't don't worry i'm just cleaning
the onions lettuce
onion lettuce
and make the perfect patty
there are no buns on this
what
meat tomato lettuce
meat
tomato lettuce
this is the worst
[Music]
um uh we should probably turn that
lettuce lettuce meat
i keep exiting out by accident
oh same onion meat onion
[Music]
i'm just making sure that you're not
oh thank you well we should probably go
do that those glory we should go to the
glowy thingies those are i think
everybody else is probably doing it
though
[Music]
i don't know how to i don't know i don't
know
[Music]
where is it i don't have anything there
um
[Music]
oh okay i got it
uh i got another task over here i have
something up here are you waiting for
your cool down huh
hey
all right sana is in the vault
keep track of that mentally
button
one six eight four six
yeah i kept telling her not to follow me
and she's just like cronie
[Music]
no i was trying to i was trying to keep
an eye on you just in case you know you
go for that kill
how is it okay that ina keeps watch of
you for protection but it's not okay if
i do that it's unlikely it should be a
blaster twice
when i reported when i reported ina
absolutely flipped her story and went
from the super meek i don't know where
i'm going to suddenly
super loud and embrace i don't know as
if she's trying to protect herself
to be honest i don't trust either of you
so
okay that's fair yeah
she went to go do a task and she ignored
me and i yelled and i thought she was
gonna kill me no but she didn't but she
might have been on cooldown waiting for
my cool down
i think two imposters still no
definitely it's the problem but the
reason why
i've been suspicious about gura was
because i kept bumping into her every
time uh it was just three of us in total
so if one person uh left
it would just be two of us
and i kept having that situation
because you were being left alone with
ina you know who i haven't heard from in
a while
moving
i don't know
put my vote on girl i don't really have
a reason so i don't know both inna and
cronie were like dora so makes me
mindful of inna
that's all i can do to be imposter too
you're really trying to put it on ina
it's awesome
if i had to guess between who left is in
pasta but not good
it's probably moon may because mummy's
been pretty
hello i'm innocent
i'm innocent too i would have killed you
right now that you were talking about
the whole cooldown thing but i trust you
yeah i'm on cooldown right now actually
and when we get up here
just kidding
okay i'm on cool down huh oh [\h__\h]
that's right hi
oh no we're good
we're cool we both showered together we
showered together right oh yeah that's
true yeah yeah wow i wish i was there
i mean
took a shower
uh yep that's scary i'm gonna i'm gonna
stay away stay away
from you stay with me i'm safe oh [\h__\h]
oh
lights
you know is running away from the
from the thingy okay we gotta do our
task
okay we can vouch for each other that
was good that turned into a wholesome
interaction hey watson why are you
following me
cuz i feel like it
hi
egg
a few more tasks left
sweet
one more task
this way
[Music]
i just want to say something quick that
gurus and the clear have been uh
following her around and
her alibi
you're her alibi now
oh yeah and i saw her doing the carding
and okay
yeah it seems like she's in the clear so
is it inaudible
so i'm pretty sure she's in the club too
sana is also in the clear we saw each
other and didn't kill each other so
as well
so girl you really could have killed me
that it's ina though
i mean i've ran into so many people i
haven't seen so many chances i didn't
kill anyone
is your name no it's not let me answer
the question thank you the microphone is
in my hand uh because at the very
beginning of the match i was singing the
berries and cream song and i went into
electrical everything
beheaded that person
the stories changed good uh okay you
changed your story
nice job detective you can't read your
own handwriting it didn't change i don't
know
i don't know what to do
i don't know
yeah
enough you saw me in crony showers i'm
just yeah yeah iris isn't in the clear
uh-huh if it turns out that it's not ina
i don't know i still
i mean
you guys see crony following gura
once a while but last time i saw crony
she wasn't with like nearby guru though
um so that was when the lights were
taken out
and i saw cali
all right well i don't know what to do
so i'm going to skip freaking out wait
who made you found the body movements
definitely it's still i have no reason
to make it you found the body
yeah
where did you find it
yeah where the mannequins are
oh
are you doing a task there
so easily
what do you mean
you're pointing a lot of fingers
when you first told the story you didn't
accuse her of killing you just said she
was more suspicious but now you're
saying that you saw her cut the head off
i like cutting out
yes it is
[Music]
i have one more task
i just need to finish my last task
yeah when when a good was first telling
the story about spawning in i want to
swipe the card again
please no you don't want to or you can't
huh but one two watson why are you being
so aggressive
how
what's this
oh we got a thingy up there
i'm gonna go in from the other side
god what a pain in the ass
mummy and sana
gosh every freaking time i'm about to do
a freaking task
i was watching the security cameras and
ina and iris iris leading ina behind
went into the room to the left of the
engine room and then only ina came out
and then cronie came in and i said hi
cronie and then nina came in and i said
oh crony i'm going to go see that body
that ena just left in there and lo and
behold there was the body of iris
oh well that's a very convincing
[Laughter]
wow girl i'm sorry i doubted you holy
[\h__\h]
i feel bad i mean i never i never voted
against you but i'm sorry i doubted you
i'll be honest i thought i was going to
um
not last the very first trial but i
turned it around and i think that was
good enough for this round so tell us
was it this long who's the other
imposter huh
and why is it amelia watson no it's not
i haven't killed anybody
[Music]
a chance
to kill me
yeah i had it also had a chance to kill
me so neither of them are safe
watch somebody stay with me next time
you'll see
oh god you're good
[Music]
[Laughter]
i know what you did
oh [\h__\h]
the imposter
i would kill you right now but you're
lucky i'm on cooldown
i'm gonna gonna look for her again and
then say hi cool
no
okay maybe it's santa unless we find a
body over here
she sounded suspicious
i feel like i'm being followed
am i done
good i'm safe no
no if i wasn't imposter i'd kill you
right now so easily goodbye
out of here but i didn't even though i
thought listen even though i thought it
was you i didn't vote for you because if
you were the impostor i'd want you to
get more kills
you said it changed my story when i did
it oh yeah cause you at this at the
start you never said that you actually
saw ina doing the killing but then this
time you said that you did see her take
off the head and that's why i thought it
was suspicious because it's kind of a
change in the detail because that's like
a pretty big detail in the story you
know yeah well on my side i did say that
detail so it must have been the
microphone yeah probably
okay look if i was the imposter i'd kill
you watch i'm gonna stand right on top
of you and you won't die no no no no no
it's fine
my cooldown's over look fine my
cooldown's done why don't you go fix
that okay
[Music]
we finished all our tasks i guess
who was it let's see we have good at
iris fake yara
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
unless we would have done all the tasks
so good job quietly just keep quiet
i was really suffering with good adele
because
why did the whole thing unfold from the
first moment
you feel bad
i never voted against you
all right i'm sorry i voted against
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
right yeah we can't even if he knows the
crew i'm just like maybe we should just
vote
it's not my problem
okay good job
next round
[Music]
does everyone have imposters here dead
uh checked because it didn't work last
round i think it's only the person who
killed you
yeah because
i'm i'm more curious about the private
talking vents is that working because
i've never like oh i think that's
unchecked
yeah that's the same i think so
yeah but i'd be cool
like the imposters
play some classic musicals are here
[Music]
is that what you just said
oh
[Music]
yet
[Applause]
[Music]
no
[Applause]
and never
they actually
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
definitely me all right cool cool
some tasks i'm ready to do my task oh
there's no food
you can choose where you spawn
yeah you can
uh
[Music]
hey guys i'm doing a task over here
i'm doing a task right now there's a
cost
somewhere here but i don't can't find it
what are you two doing
i'm on cool down right now so you guys
should run while you can
test
yes i never talk to people like that hey
oh hi please don't kill me what's up i'm
downloading stuff from the cockpit
nice
what kind of stuff
um they look like pretty important
documents
yeah yeah
i only didn't kill you because there's
other people here by the way
right
right why are you following me i have a
task here bozo
[Music]
last time yeah likely story
i'm literally just trying i'm doing the
task here
i'm doing the test well i'm doing it
faster
probably
[Music]
hi guys
hi you're gonna push us out she's gonna
wait
[Music]
likely story
well why would i be standing here
wasting time instead of just killing you
i can't do that
these cams kind of suck
just saying hey what's up hi
i don't know i can
uh
is this the right way
nope
i think it's where it gets going
no wait you're the imposter no
i'm not the imposter i'm doing a task
okay
all right gooda seems safe bae seems
safe
trash
lights
nope
dude
i was hoping kelly could hear me
i wanted to scare her
i hate this part of the map
i'm learning it though
oh hey
if you guys aren't an imposter open the
door then
thank you
i got tasks to do
i'm busy
oh no my chat crashed oh you can't open
this door
is it because you're an imposter
i love how kiara says that and as soon
as you say that there's a report three
holy
because she's been doing tasks alone and
i keep on running into her and i can
watch for uh
as a detective a beacon of the law i
clear cali and gouda uh from being uh
imposters as i was with them the whole
time and bae
or actually i don't clear cali
i didn't see watson at the end i was
trying to open the door i couldn't open
it because you're an imposter huh the
stupid card no the card keys
because she's talking to you huh because
you're an imposter you openly no i was
still in ghost mode
[Music]
she's talking to you right now huh cause
she's a ghost and you killed her oh
i see you on this extra talk oh no
no
oh yeah
because i've i've cracked the case
i'm just gonna stay
but why would watson uh out her own
teammates yeah i think i'm gonna skip
the omnibus
i know kiara
i
she's cracking
cracking like an egg
it's gonna be crosstalk
good luck it's hot oh okay where are we
never mind
and then my chat crashed
trying to fix it
oh this is what i was gonna click
anyways
i'm pretty sure imposters could open the
door right like
with a map
oh perfect this is exactly where i need
to be
this one
[Music]
a wet rat eela
smell it it's a girl we were alone and
she could have killed me but she just
went off and did her test
kindly howdy and i went on my way i saw
kiara and we were on the left side of
the map so this kill couldn't have been
kiara but i think it was the other
imposter who might be moving or even
iris
where did you see me
i was trying to get to the whatever it
was sabotage i forgot what it was crash
course or whatever
i was in records but i didn't see
anything records
it might have been the room next to it i
was trying to go towards the other side
does it have the
table with the folder on it that's the
wrecking room
yeah like i walked in from what's what
wait i'm not so sure anymore why are you
trying to blame me chiara
i know you were talking just really good
[Music]
it might not be records if you didn't
see me but i'm pretty i thought it was
records it's like
describe it
i don't remember anymore it was but i'm
pretty sure it was records uh are you
sure it wasn't the showers iris
no it's not that i take my vote back i
don't even know where
is pretty close to the showers it's
pretty close
and who are you voting for
with the
huh i don't even know where the showers
are wait i don't know
you haven't heard a lot from mumei or
ina yeah i know isn't it oh i was all
the way okay i spawned in kitchen with
mummy and then i went to do my task in
the uh the bottom left thing
it's called uh so our our suspects are
iris and kiara got it
i don't know usually usually would be
like deducting and like
stuff but
gouda can vote vouch for me right
i mean you didn't kill me
yeah and we were up there at the top
room where it's really easy to kill
people blood didn't and the shamers got
the same family and lie though i'm sorry
we have 10 seconds left oh what not
oh my god oh god we're gonna lose
um
let's see we got some tasks up here
[Music]
what were you about to do chiara huh
yeah
don't follow me
okay
oh god
see i'm all alone with you you're
waiting here getting away from me
emergency button just in case i wouldn't
help help
i'm keeping watch on irish i will follow
you wherever you're going
is following me she's we're gonna die
you know it's both of them
i have to escape bye callie
watson you're not going to kill me right
i don't know
watson's just [\h__\h] with me
oh boy
uh oh thank you eno okay why are you
thinking enough why were you thanking
ina nothing nothing no no no no um
okay you know all right we got we know
who it is
now we know who it is
right interesting let's uh i guess we'll
vote for iris first thing uh yeah
that sounds about right
what no hold on hold on
okay
wait kiara's dead yeah i guess it wasn't
her
i need to you need to hear me out right
now okay so i was doing my favorite task
the potty task right elbow deep in the
toilet
um
and
uh kiara came in
and ena came in
tiara is now dead i was the one that
found the eyes
[Music]
okay guys bye bye
you know what i stumbled onto i was i
was just bi i wasn't aware i was dead i
was with um i was with ina and iris and
kiara and i left and i saw callie and
then now kiara's dead so that will tell
you
um
yeah i think that's pretty telling you
know
i think it's either who are we both of
them
yeah let's go for eno
um i don't know i'm trying to think
it was me kiara and ena and literally
seconds afterwards unless somebody came
in i cleaned them
why haven't you voted iris i think it's
iris too i haven't oh i haven't voted
wait uh
uh i just voted for ina though guys so
if you want to i think you want to make
sure that we yeah yeah definitely both
of them but we gotta be strategic about
who we vote off
oh there's one for each of us and then
we could call a report and then vote
yeah yeah no i think we have to get to
the button in the meeting room
oh boy
hi ena
skip it
[Music]
three times in a row that's crazy
emergency meeting okay
[Music]
this looks like that among us gifts was
working
[Music]
we gotta do a scratch watson okay wait
how can we call a meeting
either
[Music]
hi where's the uh oh god
oh god
[Music]
okay iris is on cooldown right now
because i think she probably just oh
yeah you're still alive
[Applause]
um
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
that was pretty funny though
oh
[Laughter]
i'll be there
hope is being shot into space not in the
galaxy
[Laughter]
well you know what um
regardless of where you fly after this i
hope you learned your lesson
to not to not kill people that's my job
if
um
[Laughter]
see my theories have been really
accurate
and
the washroom and grass
[Music]
hello
discord audio oh all right sorry guys
there we go
[Music]
good fun
my dream came
it kind of gets questionable when you
get it three times people don't even
trust you off the bat
it's harder as the games go along yeah
with me three times yeah
three times in a row
what are the possibilities yeah yeah
yeah
i feel like i feel like a mama does that
it keeps giving impostor to like the
same people yeah yeah i was really
surprised that like you would assume
that you would assume that the reaper
would be like the number one killer of
everyone but i'm actually just the task
master like this yeah
i do like the task
when i when i saw you cali you are so
scared of death
i don't like yeah exactly we'll see
that's the thing is death can't die so
when the prospect of death dying becomes
a thing it's quite frightening oh
super scary
i think we got a lot of really golden
moments out of this stream i'm looking
forward to all the clips to see the
other point of views
oh yes
i'm really excited about everyone's
point of views yeah
it's really fun to hear ghosts oh yeah
the problem is great
iris you almost blew our cover the last
one she did she did blow your cover yeah
i thought we couldn't hear me now yeah i
was like i was like okay if we get a
double kill like like this is good but i
couldn't say anything so i was just
trailing you around
yeah
just like they did yeah if you were on
cooldown or not so no no
that's why i like i i thought we were
going to do a double kill too that's how
i was like around and then i killed
someone and i see you went somewhere
else that's like oh no no the double
kill and then i think yeah because
someone tells me
that right so yeah uh
i'm sorry yeah
i thought you were like my mouth we
would have wonderful
but you know at the same time like you
know the senpai's i i can't i can't go
and kill my senpai's right away
[Music]
save us for less you can savor the kill
huh
i like that i like that way of life good
good one
okay girls i'm gonna go through everyone
from top to bottom again to give a good
bye one by one and maybe tell me your
favorite moment from today or your
favorite kill or whatever so let's start
with amelia watson oh uh wait what are
we doing
oh goodbye and your favorite moments
like your favorite kill from today okay
uh thank you guys for watching and thank
you kiara for setting it up again and
organizing everything and my favorite
moment
uh i really liked messing with cali that
was fun yeah every time i saw callie
i gotta admit that was pretty good
yeah you mean uh saying that she's the
imposter what happened oh she would just
outright say things like like i'd be
like are you going to kill me she'd be
like yeah you're lucky my cool down is
off and like run away
that's another one for the archives for
me okay well thank you amelia next up
bails
um
thanks for coming guys i hope everyone
had fun thank you kiara for organizing
again so powerful
[Music]
okay
yeah it was like bathroom music right
it's pretty fancy
right yeah i mean you can
oh and yeah right here in front of
everybody really guys come on
get a room
[Laughter]
now let's dial it back just a little bit
give me your google
[Music]
me oh let's see my favorite moment has
to be um when i was trying to hold up
the the cell phone to get the cell
service on the deck where anyone could
have killed me and i saw sana come up
behind me oh and i was like holy [\h__\h]
this is where i die
and she just walked away and she's like
no i have to do my task here and i was
like okay so we just switched spaces and
we like watched out for each other it
was kind of cool as a bonding moment
yeah
it was really fun
thank you next up fauna
hello thank you everyone for watching
and thank you kiara for organizing
everything it was a lot of work
and i really appreciate it
uh my favorite moment was not being the
imposter
oh
yeah i don't know i think i preferred
um being impostor is just so much
pressure yeah it is
and especially with the what's image you
can't really say anything because
because
yeah
i wanted to get into that situation
unfortunately it didn't happen today so
yeah well thank you fun i'm glad you
enjoyed it next up
how salty are you
i'm fine
i'm saying i was talking to my channel
about like how i don't usually i don't
know have conversations i don't talk
like this usually like accusatory
whether it's in a game or not it's like
it feels very draining uh mentally i
guess
yeah i feel like always minded on me
my favorite moments were
uh and i'm asking clippers please uh the
various perfectly cut screams with the
proximity chat
specifically
where everybody was terrified of me and
every time somebody would walk by me it
would just be blood-curdling
i'd like to see a perfectly cut screams
uh compilation of some sort if there are
me too yeah
you had a good one too for putting this
together thank you
[Music]
oh okay wow thank you so much for
organizing this wonderful collab camera
i love among us to bits
i'm so glad i was able to do this and i
i i would go for among us like off
stream anytime if we had enough people
how much i like it yeah but
yeah it was a lot of fun and being
impostor was great pressure but great
and my favorite moments have to be yeah
killing a lot of people that was fun um
and also like
well personally for a moment that really
didn't have much to do with me um i
really liked how cali you know when she
found fauna's body was like it was me
boys
you're just kind of out of yourself that
yeah that was i i found that hilariously
oh god i need to be careful with how i
say words
yeah that was my personal favorite place
genuine very fun game thank you so much
yes
all the time
good kills when you're uh
when you're imposter though because i
was playing safe i was like okay if i
get all the aggros and maybe the other
imposter can go on a killing spring oh
yeah yeah what am i doing when i was in
posture too i was like oh you knows
probably i'm probably going to have to
be aggressive so that's right i'm
killing and killing you
aggression is the way to go but i was
trying to clear my name and that was how
i got out trying too hard to clear my
name but i'm just saying because i was
yelling in her ear the whole time
yeah
just laughing a ghost in my
ears okay crony next doll
oh
sorry um
what was i was i gonna say oh yeah thank
you
no no no thank you so much for arranging
this
thank you so much to kiara uh for
arranging this i really love this game
and
it's been fun i think my favorite moment
was
uh
well every moment was pretty funny but
whatever the
the proximity chat exploded whenever a
meeting happened
the first time when the meeting happened
everybody was screaming and i didn't
even know what was going on but that was
funny so thank you for that
yeah that was more fun thank you cronie
next time
hello
thank you kiara for organizing
everything everyone says that
well you we're doing it
[Music]
i'm blushing thank you please continue
uh i think one of my favorite parts that
i experienced was i spawned where ena
were with ina
and i turned her and i said wouldn't it
be something if you're the imposter
three times in a row
yeah that really would be she just
walked away
[Laughter]
i was exploding i was like yeah it would
be really funny wouldn't it
walk through
it's absolutely drenched in sweat
well then you know your goodbye and your
your favorite moments who who was your
favorite kill maybe
oh
best putting a knife through their
stomach
well um it's gonna be half
there's there's been a lot of good kills
but i think it's gonna have to go with
the
uh cronie in the
wasn't the first game or something where
she was like please don't kill me i was
like okay okay
poor cronie incredible
he just said sure but only
i think cody would miss a good imposter
if you if you missed her
[Laughter]
i want to see
evil
yeah this would be very scary and
intimidating though
every time when i was cessing callie
like she was like so intimidating to me
i was so scared when she was yelling at
me oh
it's you huh
no it's you know you erase
okay give us your your goodbye and your
favorite moment please
okay thank you very much for organizing
the collab cura um i'm really happy to
play a game with you guys again it's
been a while me too
i missed your vlog
my favorite moment is like
yeah
we're so happy you are here today sana
yeah yeah
waiting for you to come back about my
favorite moment as uh
pretty much every time i heard kelly
scream but now my favorite moment is
spending time with all of you guys
[Music]
[Laughter]
you should next time next time you
should uh leave me leave me alive
because i
believe everything you guys say
all right well um uh for me my favorite
moments one i had so many but i guess
the one that stayed in my head now is um
i think it was in this in the
round before the last round where uh
everyone was saying
gouda and she was just trying to speak
but then like i was really
mad and then amen was like well i'm
gonna follow you to see if you're really
innocent and i was like chilling with
inna as ghosts and we were just playing
the better curling and just we're
standing there together as ghosts and
then ahmed and guna ran into the room
having a huge fight like disgusting
[Laughter]
watching the kindergarten fight
in the garden flying girl that was good
they were running in circles yelling at
me
[Music]
i'm really glad this all worked out fine
in the end uh you know i had some
troubles in the beginning but i'm so
relieved yeah i'm sorry about that
okay
it worked out i didn't even just
worked out for sure
as the organizer i'm just happy as to
dad everyone had fun and and no holding
and scuff was that present today
yeah not as president
[Music]
thank you for appreciating i'm sure
there's some some among us who are a
little bit tired of this among us game
but uh i think with proximity voice chat
mod it made it a whole lot more
interesting and kind of refreshing so
[Music]
oh yeah it was their project winter
baby for christmas yeah
yeah winter's coming up
only up to eight really
ah and some of them
one more thing i kind of want to do is
like because i organized the en id mario
kart tournament now that we are on 11
years we completely
and my account yeah yeah
11 people like not 12 by 11. is it just
one of the one of the people are gonna
be bought is that what it is yeah one of
them
a butt i think or you can just leave
that one out i think we can just oh okay
okay
is it time for another training arc from
well it is uh past five a.m for me so i
hope we can oh yeah very nice oh yeah
you have an announcement
um i have an announcement for next
weekend that we will be having another
collab
yeah another one
[Music]
yeah you guys can put it on your
schedule and mark it on the calendar
yeah
details are secret for now but uh yeah
now you guys mark it down
girls and friends
yes anything
yeah this one is
[Music]
i'm just really saying it's genuinely
going to be amazing perhaps amazing
this one is amazing too
yeah this is oh yeah this one's great i
love that it was really fun
and no no we're not only myth
english
in english i mean outside oats council
to home and oats england what's the end
english
publicly
okay
[Music]
right
me
[Music]
do
hey
[Music]
blue
you