the
[Music]
[Applause]
hi hello
world what wh where am I what is this
Cube why is everyone saying h hris i
what's hris that sounds like such a
interesting
word I don't
understand why am I alone in this in
this
room um
oh what is this Cube what am I supposed
to do here
[Music]
um
what what what do I
do there's there's I I don't even know
why I'm here I just know that my name is
Iris and that I'm SLE extremely sleep
deprived for some reason I feel so tired
but hyper at the same time is this
because I don't have any memory of what
the hell's going on um
[Music]
I just I could just feel the tiredness
in my body but I don't know why I'm even
tired I want
to I want to do something I just don't
know what I want to
do I don't even know what kind of
personality I was supposed to
have
uh do I wander around in this Abyss for
eternity is
that is is that my my duty of just
staying here being trapped alone
absolutely
alone
why why am I here why am I
[Music]
here
oh what is this this oh oh I can't move
my okay echo of Forgotten memories yeah
I I don't know what's going on I have
press the sneak key what sneak key
uh who I am the world I live oh no I
accidentally skipped and more than
anything I AC skipped a
bunch and and more than
anything why am I sneaking
the people I hold most dear I didn't
mean to
skip I have people I hold dear I'm not a
loner I'm so glad I'm not a loner I'm so
glad this this these words just confirm
that I'm not a
loner what is this world oh faced with
Oblivion I
feel empty
I feel empty but at least there's a
there's a pretty World in front of
me I wonder if there's anyone else in
this
world relieved yeah I'm relieved that
I'm not stuck in a cube anymore yes I
feel very relieved
mhm oh wait a sec wait a sec sure
[Music]
I hear random text on the
screen I I see random text in the bottom
on the bottom left of my screen but I'm
just going to ignore that for now
perhaps distraught yes I'm very
distraught I'm so distraught that that I
seem to be
alone while there's a party going on
without me but maybe you know it's cuz I
lost my memory maybe maybe that's why
maybe that's why I'm
alone I do not know yeah I seriously
don't know I seriously don't
know
lowly so
lonely people asking deep questions in
in in the
text uh so much I don't know and yet
and
yet and yet I feel like there's so much
to
my to to me there's so there must be so
much going on with my life for me to be
stuck here I must have been living an an
a I don't an either amazing life or a
very shitake life oh what is shitaki
wait why did I even say that why did I
say mushroom that made no no sense why
did I just say the name of a mushroom in
my sentence it made no sense
huh that bright light it calls to
[Music]
me it does call to
me am I a weird
person I go toward the light
oh Le liestal castle where is is
this oh my God they're so cute who are
these are they
soldiers you there what are you doing
here I don't know what I'm doing here I
just suddenly transported here am I
isekai what does isai even
mean oh wait oh there we go you have the
look of Outsiders about you do I I don't
look as cubical as you probably yes
huh huh wait could it be could it be
what is there something weird about me
please don't don't treat me like an
outsider I want to be
[Music]
friends ignore ignore ignore whatever's
going
[Music]
on I am pressing a lot of the sneak key
and I have no idea what I'm I can't move
yet right away right away what did I
accid skip something again
oh oh my God is that the king the Royal
audience chamber that chair is way too
big for you welcome Heroes this is the
kingdom of liestal and I am its
king you know I don't have any memories
but I could tell I could tell I could
probably overthrow this King in a
day so why am I meeting the king is it
cuz I was um iside I don't even know
what that word means but I'm saying it
anyways the guards who brought you here
have informed me that you remember not
but your own names yes I just know that
my name is Iris and there's like a lot
of voices in my head right now saying
stuff about opinions and and just a lot
of text in my brain right now with I I
have no idea what's going on
[Music]
h a side effect of travel between worlds
no
doubt I was in a different
world what's a
world this must all come as a surprise
to you but hearken what does hearken
mean to was I who summoned you
here you summoned
me so I was SI I mean
summoned it means to listen well oh
thank you whoever you are thank you for
telling me what hearken
means how am I able to communicate with
so many people at once you see an
unprecedented Calamity now threatens our
world are you telling me I have some
sort of secret power
[Music]
it has sewn the Earth with corruption
and driven us from our
[Music]
homes this blighted land now gives rise
to creatures of Shadow known as
stains stains we're not talking about
clothing stains are
we not that I know what that's supposed
to be
[Music]
either this Kingdom of liust and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to
leeston can I yes do I have the power of
a
detergent can I Splash detergent all
over the world is that what I can
do but should the Calamity be left
unchecked it is only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire world n
oh you're so short faced with this
Prospect you're like a cute pet I
scoured the ancient texts for a way to
combat the Calamity oh I wasn't able to
read that that
fast the ritual of hero summoning I'm a
hero
you who hail from another world has been
summoned here by me to become the
saviors of the
Vistal what this could be a light novel
wait what's a light
novel only you have the power to save
our world only me am I the only one in
this world really I'll take your word
for it I'll I'll take your word for it
okay if I see anyone else I'm just going
to think that they're random people not
chosen people
[Music]
and so I ask Will
You
Huh veridus y your
majesty who's this he got a really he's
taller than the
king what is it
a great host of stains has broken
through our defensive line oh no is it
time for the The Chosen hero the one and
only chosen
hero
no
no we are rushing to mount a defense but
the S situation is dire Your Majesty we
must get you somewhere
safe yeah I don't think he could have a
[Music]
fly I love these exclam exclamation
marks showing up who are these strangers
what do you mean these I'm the only one
here I'm the one and only hero that was
summoned what are you talking about why
are you saying saying it like there's
multiple people around like there's
supposed to be multiple people around I
think there's something wrong with you
what what you what say you Heroes will
you accept this Destiny wait I thought I
was the one and only hero why is it
suddenly plural
now there is great power within you will
he use it to save us to save this
world I mean I have nothing better
nothing else better to do
honestly what else am I supposed to do
here chill become a become a neat what
does a neat me what what does that even
mean huh I regret that you must face
such danger so soon after your arrival
as his majesty no doubt explained to you
our Kingdom's fa faces an unprecedented
crisis oh my God they're so cute wa uh
the Calamity befalls the land leaving it
bereft of life and invested with the
monsters known as St
[Music]
not even the mighty liestal Castle can
be said to be safe
anymore oh I can move now Perhaps it is
too late to save the world from
destruction nevertheless this dude's
talkative it is our duty to defend our
King and our countrymen to the very end
Brave Heroes From Another World let us
go forth with Valor and fight
together together you mean
alone wait oh defeat the stains oh that
that's okay wait how do I how do I m I
mean how do I fight again okay okay
okay oh that's
huge power
detergent
ow huh what's going onuh
I'm not doing any
damage I am the chosen
one oh please don't please please don't
go shoot shoot shoot am I really the
chosen one I'm doing
nothing why am I speaking a different
language um what huh huh wait what
happen why why why
why oh wait I have food I need to use
that wait I have a wooden sword why
didn't the King give me something better
give me an Excalibur I don't know what
that means oh
wait how do I eat
again how do I eat wait I I lost all my
memory I don't even know how to eat wait
um how do I eat
[Music]
right click oh there we
go okay
okay what am I supposed to do how how am
I supposed to kill this thing
I have been using this weapon it's not
working huh huh what
happened hold your weapon and left click
shout
Revelation what I have a weapon you mean
are you talking about my
bread
Revelation oh wait what is
this what are these Stars
they look like the things that are in my
head
re
[Music]
Revelation did I want hit him the stain
host has been routed oh my God it's that
easy why did you give me that in the
first place
you fought bravely kind Heroes I I have
a cheat I have a cheat spell guys I pray
you are not
injured no I I I died three times what
are you talking about I I died three
times that Mighty armored one must be
their leader the stain King fast
fasinating Most
Fascinating well I see why they call you
Heroes we'd be in a right right pickle
without without without your
help wait I don't even know who's
speaking who who's I know the green one
is vidus but I don't know who everyone
else
is we sustained minimal damage thanks to
your Valor our kingdom is in your depth
thank you
one of them talks funny I must hasten to
inform His Majesty of our Victory will
you accompany me sure but I kind of want
to talk to the one that talks
funny
whiffin I heard the news though we
called upon you suddenly you Rose to the
occasion you have my deest
gratitude you're welcome I don't know
what the hell I don't know what the hell
happened but you're welcome what
interests me most however is the strange
power you manifested during the battle
with which you were able to defeat the
stains
uh-huh that power May well be the key to
saving our world from anal an
Annihilation oh my God I remember how to
spell pronounce
that according to the heroes the power
came to them like a forgotten memory
when they spoke the world Revelation
word
revelation
really it was it was all about the word
revelation so I should just scream
Revelation left and right and I'd be
Invincible right but once they used it
to Route the stain host it seems that
power vanished Without a Trace
[Music]
well that's bloody brilliant ain't it oh
oh it is a it is an
accent the whiff it the the the whiff it
was what threw me
off revelation we must uncover the
secrets of this phenomenon if we are
able to if we if we are to Prevail
against the calamity
many questions remain but one thing is
certain the kingdom of the best still
stands today thanks to you you guys
really couldn't beat that one
monster you guys look fullon geared up
you know like you're level 100 150 or
something here here so here is I ask of
you once more will you lend us your
strength to save the bestl from ruin
[Music]
oh I I'm totally not nodding my body is
just automatically doing that marvelous
on be behalf of all the best I thank you
my for some reason I was being
controlled to suddenly nod I didn't mean
to we are blessed to have your Aid kind
Heroes
Celesta that's a cute
[Music]
name allow me to introduce the four
Great guilds which are responsible for
ensuring the Kingdom's peace and
prosperity The Haven for the Curious
where knowledge and creativity are
valued above all the Scarlet wand oh oh
we're going to introduce each one of you
guys okay
okay the home for Glory Seekers with
ambition and vision where closest alleys
become fiercest Rivals the Amber coin
the greedy ones
right the sanctum of healing where the
spirit of empathy and de devotion
thrives the seruan cup uh-huh okay so
the the kind ones uh-huh the beacon of
the righteous and loyal where great
threats are faced with even greater
courage the Jade sword the Jade sword
okay the law
gotcha and then the red are the Curious
ones
okay one of these guilds will become
your home during your time
here what Guild could I possibly belong
to
Beyond this door lies the room of Truth
therein the will of the ancestor shall
decide your
guild the
ancestor I have an
ancestor my bloodline goes that
far uh I can't move do I just do I sneak
more am I just supposed to sneak
[Music]
more fear not introspection is a vital
step on the road to Enlightenment uh
excels here as I always say even
higher sorry I did not understand a
single word you just said just
now time to roll the dice eh be seeing
some of you lot down at the Amber corn
Guild Hall I'm kind of liking Amber
corn let us save this world together
okay that's simple
let us save this world together yeah
totally let's save the world together
the room of Truth awaits go forth with
Valor with
Valor with Valor go forth to the room of
Truth there are no lies in this room I
belong to wherever they take
me step on the platform and receive the
will of the ancestor where is the
ancestor I mean they are an ancestor
they must be dead right I'm assuming or
a ghost a
ghost can I can I Revelation in this
here oh I can Revelation in here
Revelation ooh it
explodes I can Revelation in
here
rev oh oh I have a long loading time
okay I have a long okay
gotcha the light it glows amidst the
endless flow of time seek the power that
Amber
grants seruan cup you know for a second
I thought it was going to be an
Amber Dawn the
cloak oh oh Dawn how do I Dawn the cloak
wait wait wait wait I can Dawn the how
do I Dawn the cloak again
it looks just like a no nothing nothing
I don't remember what it could possibly
look like wait
um oh what is this
cloak it looks it looks really
nice I dawned it I dawned
it armed with an unwavering will seek to
defend the soul of Jade can I fly in
this enigmatic
recollection what awaits me
oh oh my God I'm part of the good
guys I know obviously everyone's good
guys we're all here Heroes right oh my
God I have so much stuff I have a steed
summoning egg what I can I can summon a
steed u a radio a waste bin I have
magical Tob and a map and I have no idea
how what I'm supposed to do with these
huh and I'm broke I'm absolutely broke
uh
uh um hello the ancestors blessings upon
you hero welcome to the Guild Hall of
the Cilan cup I'm Celesta The Guild
Master hello that you would come to the
best's aid in her time of need even so
soon after your summoning speaks volumes
about your
selflessness selflessness selflessness I
do have mhm
mhm as a member of this Guild you'll be
join the effort to cleanse this land of
stains and bring Salvation to the
world but one must walk before a one can
run first you should learn about this
town we strive to protect as well as how
to accept and perform
[Music]
quests
okay within this town There's a location
known as the quest board there you will
find the quest master who will impart
his knowledge you may also use this time
to familiarize your with the
town speak to your Guild Master next go
to the quest board and speak to the
quest Master Quest Master where's
where's this
board I'm sure this is what the map is
for oh found okay
okay oh my God there's so many
Lees oh my God they're all so happy they
look like seals that are walking on two
legs what are seals I have no idea what
I'm talking about the quest master so
far can I not run
faster okay okay
there's so many of them wait there's
there's somebody I see people I see
people and the people running over wait
I see people who are
you is my mic
on what is a
mic hello
is my mic not working hi
hello who you know how to open the TR
who are
you with I open it I think they're busy
this way here oh wait maybe oh a new
face is here hello can you guys hear me
hello oh thank God hello there's so many
people I have no idea who are you why
are there so many cute girls all around
me all of a
sudden are you in me lady oh I I don't
know what I'm do untable I'm not going
to lie all right sound like someone I
want to get my nails done with
oh I haven't gotten my nails done in
ages my name is Iris and I don't know
anything else besides that name oh Iris
he sounds so helpless and
weak yeah honestly it makes do you know
what cup you're in my dear
a cup what do you mean Cup oh I got a
new Quest what what quest what do you
mean cup what group are you in my dear I
I seem to be in The Blue
Team oh that is the Cerulean cup that's
what I was asking oh goodness all right
another one I is is there a problem with
that is there a problem I'm in the blue
team is it cuz you're red ours matters a
number three I haven't said it do we
have what have I done to these people I
don't understand
you know you have an interesting
accent hey did you not get a quest
that's build something ask questions
what have you
done I don't think I've done I I don't
want to know what I've done we all
heroes but oh goodness I hope
we only who is interested in conru you
Time Around Town selling item ventes
here
come to post jobs and
requests
yeah Rich oh I'm rich what I'm so rich
have the rich I mean the B the
three um no I got the same Quest though
um okay I'm the and you'll
find yeah there are many I don't know if
we're close tired of my P now so much I
can't concentrate
we get started we can actually switch
the
pages what do I do go to the okay I
already okay let's get all of them this
here looks like the perfect job for you
okay
okay complete the side quest and then
speak to the quest
master I see okay is there over there
Iris yeah oh you know my name the blue
people yes you do you want to like join
the blue people I you can join us too oh
yeah I don't know who the blue people
are and I I honestly trust you guys more
then who blue people come I haven't even
seen them our our party leader shall
invite you to our group for now yeah too
babysit you babysit me please y y we on
your first Quest yeah I am I am we can
help you with that thank you how do I I
how do I accept this invite I already
did um um you click key and then you
click on accept with your cursor oh
there
go nice nice oh my God excuse me excuse
me uh you you you seem to have a blue
aura around you I do no we we have to
the babysit because found her I found
her help teammates teammates to the
quest they're they're trying to k out
who are these people they're trying to
take away no she's ours now she's ours
they're trying to take away she's ours
Mommy okay don't fire we can take turns
oh my God there's a
fire with my life
she fight you were not there when she
needed you quick come with
me join our you hands off
I think it's to late now
so
okay what what what you're abandoning me
no no honestly if you want to be with us
you can be with
us we'll help
you come here come here come here come
here let's go Iris super come
hereis let's go leave that
behind no come to the dark side well
take dark side I don't know why I'm I
know you have two Hales one dark and and
a lighter one you must I do listen to
the darker
one she's suddenly hitting me she's
suddenly hitting me who are
[Applause]
you hey re Revelation re
reation reation
Revelation
[Music]
Revelation oh nice fist oh my God
everyone has such cool
moves they look like from a retro game
Revelation rro game yeah yes I know not
of what you speak who are you you
beautiful beautiful violin lady oh at
least you know I am to be the next Queen
of the kingdom of
lesto really I did not know of your
intention oh so that's how you say it
this is not an intention this is meant
to be your destiny it was meant to be it
was meant to be are you related to them
are you you must be blood blood related
are you blood related to that tiny King
what no we have blocked eyes and we knew
that we were destined Mar you married
the king that's how you became you cover
with the
King it's complicated she married the
king he was to propose to
me well you don't have you didn't have
to accept wait I wanted
to talking
to all right all right this is the
future Queen of the pants yes
yes I'm glad you know fellow peasants
peasants
PE I'm sorry for speaking to
you we will not protect you if you don't
respect us that's why you're in a
different Guild I'm talking to IR you
need to you need the support of all the
guilds in order to be sucessful that
was whoever you are brown brown cute
cute
Cen how D Vinci the great the
third are you on our team now what's
going on I have no idea return I have no
idea cute brown owl what is what is your
name I my name is Iris and I'm curet I'm
currently yeah nice to meet you what is
your name my name is Jonathan g spell
the G
I'm I'm going to hang up now okay okay
I'll CL okay GG for short Jonathan J G
oh jonath Jonathan G Jonathan with a G
Jonathan with a G so much bread now yes
Jonathan I'll I'll call you Jonathan
Jonathan Jonathan oh okay yes I would
like that so okay um Queen Jonathan um
who are you hello I have a name not a
queen well you don't like it you can
call to
be for
sure so sounds very cute and then who is
this rock that was trying to kidnap me
i'mi
beu yes oh wow my name is your name is
beu I see I don't know why that sounds
familiar but slightly different from
what I remember different I don't know I
don't know but I've always been be why
am I being surrounded by so many people
we are one of us team you are one of us
us you are of us cop but but I but I
joined another team wait you can leave
no no you did not join another team you
are one of us you you've always been one
of us we Des for each other really what
what makes us what what what what why
why am I one of you guys I I see it in
your eyes because you have empathy you
have I feel your emotion
it's sa I do have empy
and you guys don't you I don't know
especially you you don't seem like you
have empathy in excuse
me I am made of empathy you are I am I
am liquid empathy I've seen it in her
eyes in Tam's eyes the way she spoke to
that child she is full of
empathy I see I will I would have to
discuss with my current uh my current
team members on will you return to us it
is Jonna Watson she wants to kill the
kid Jah Watson Watson Watson who joh
wats why so many joh
NOS oh it's reason oh no she thought she
thought Revelation was Revolution and
she was planning to the kingom
king I mean I can understand that that
misunderstanding but what era is the set
in I have no idea what era what what is
even an era I have no idea what an era
is oh you're right
where did my team
go Jonathan would never kill the king
go I don't I know
the te
wat excuse
me stay away from my guild member I
should probably do my
quest everyone's
probably complete the side quest and
excuse me excuse me excuse
me what's the side quest how do I check
my side quest oh wait I see the I see
the child how do I check the side
quest um this way do I like sneak or
something no
no the map doesn't tell me anything how
do I check let me ask my teammates hello
hello teammates oh oh hello hello sweet
little lady hello my name is Iris Iris
hello there hello hello Iris hello what
may I call you
to my name is the bay the B
I'm I am Cleopatra Eisenhower D Vinci
the great thei oh W that's a very very
in short you can call her three
three Cleo you can't you you can't do
that but what am I to do about it
you're right I'll I'll just call you
three and there's nothing you can do
about it you could call me mum or
something oh that cameand where did that
come from I think it means no name so
I'd rather you just call me that you
have no name I thought you had a name I
thought you had a really long name do
but you guys are acting like I don't oh
not a
hold okay I'll call you I'll call you
moons just to shorten it you know we
need even shorter than that
just to shorten it moms all right oh my
gosh wait what are those I feel like
I've gotten to know UN in as three so
I'm going to call you three from now
what is that fine what are you have the
Naruto thingies they're not Naruto
thingies what are Naruto I narut no no
they're not sh I mean I don't even know
what you're talking about I don't know
what shurikens are no they're they're
Stars they're they're the power of the
of my angel devil uh they're my halo
it's my it's a part of my halo
what Halo did did you understand that I
didn't understand a single word that
came out of her mouth I think she might
be the town Looney or something I have
no clue what she
say see I thought she was like the cute
sweet little weak girl you were going to
do on but
no why are they why am I suddenly being
judged so much wait am I just supposed
to admit that these are shriet or
something is that what I'm supposed to
do I me Halo you think you're no Hal
honestly you just got to tell the truth
we value honesty in this group well do
you think shurikens do
this
what honestly yeah yeah totally could do
that what what else would they do you
could totally see that happening in
Naruto what what else did they do Naruto
what is Naruto what do
you sounds like what I don't know what
it sounds like you the first thing that
comes to your head y my Revelation my
Revelation isn't
farting no no I will never is a I would
never not on stream she from that one
movie do you know from that one movie
where they sing and make pretty girl hey
Jonathan yes I thought you were about to
say do you know John Cena I'm sorry I'm
John Cena John Cena can you see him is
he around here I can't see him I can't
what is who is Jonathan John Cena
Jonathan Jonathan is to kill the
king Jonathan Jonathan is this an
inside is a it is it
is you know
right your we have to get you to
safety are you going to make him gathan
we we
have no it's no it's j Amber amberin if
you kill him he'll be gone but your
highness I I put my my name on the line
us ambercoin nothing to do with Jonathan
with the Amber you on the Amber team are
you of Amber she's of Amber are
you what's wrong with there has been a
misunderstanding you're not even in
Amber what are you talking about I'm in
your team I'm in your party what no you
are
on you're on no you shut huh h huh wait
I mean you you shut your humble mouth
what did you just almost say to me huh I
did not say anything I I thought you
supposed to be a part of the empathy
team huh yes you
too do not
defective I I don't even they they
they're the ones who reached out a
helping hand and I you're supposed to
refuse it man you're in Cilan Cup oh
well I mean I didn't know you guys were
in Cilan
sorry now you
know our we should we should we should
our from this should I I Jo should I
join
part want to go
crazy before they ask more questions
want to does anyone not want does anyone
want me to stay in their party or or
just yes nobody wants you except us
nobody oh nobody wants you accept us the
seruan
come wow we are so compassion
empathetic we are taking
out your magical tomb do you see this
the magical book open your magical book
and locate page four locate page four
magical
book and dissolve your
part wait click to disband click to kick
click to leave try leaving try to leave
yeah should I maybe say something before
I leave no no no just leave just out
yeah they did just you you belong with
us they dit you they did they they did
they ditch me did they really ditch me
they did it's not a Mis us now it's not
a misunderstanding yeah you were just a
decoy uhhuh okay okay you were meant to
be with us you one of ours let me let me
just say let me just say in chat I was
ditched so I will
leave we accept you for who you are
traitor or not you can make a new with
us we we we have been tied by the
strings of I'm sorry I will
switch yes
yes is this really the right
answer this is the right answer nobody
loves you except us okay yes nobody only
toxic this feels very toxic but okay no
don't we we are we are we are the
empathy group we are the group that is
full of empathy why can't I open the
book I'm trying to I'm trying to leave
wait wait wait okay okay I can't open
the book all of a sudden wait
wait oh there we go that's recycling bin
on page four of your magical tomb do you
really want to leave your party yes yes
yes yes yes yes okay okay I have I have
I have alone now I've left now now we
will join our team join us join our
party you are one of
us oh okay okay you guys are actually
full of empathy right yes we are full of
kindness and love take our love
[Music]
okay
compl and now open your magic radio yes
my magic radio I have a magic this is
Magic this is mag radio what do I do
with the magic radio and join our call
us ring ring our radio is it a party
call it's a group it's a group chat
there
[Applause]
go I feel like I belong yes you belong
here now
yay us
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm not getting anything done let's go
go we supposed to be the Cal one we we
are calm we are calm we are very calm
we're full of empathy we Cal we so
empathetic yes we're so nice kind we
know love we know
peace does our ancestors actually know
us I don't think they know
us yes maybe they were like us and they
rewrote history they were like we are
the calm ones think about by the way my
what is your quest sorry my beautiful te
yes my beautiful teammates uh uh how do
I check what side quest I'm on oh you
done your magic book it one more time
and you you flip to page two oh Che your
oh okay okay yes it says I do not have
any active side quest
what you talk to you talk to the board
okay the
board hey the quest board okay okay are
you guys are you guys you know fully
already much farther ahead words I'm on
Quest I don't just ahead of me we are
three quests ahead if I were to guess I
see
mayhaps yes I I came I came a little bit
you know a little bit after you guys
probably because I'm just that important
you know uh-huh you are we are just so
full of empathy we understand we know
why the board the dude empath okay okay
oh there's so many
quests except all of them all of them
anyone because we are helpful every
Quest I think there's only one yeah I
think there is only one
okay there is only one it looks like a
lot okay and then I go to the do you
want the fast pass through some of the
quest oh there's a fast pass is this is
this gizy what is gizy land I have no
idea what I'm talking about it's called
the uh special
oh the enoa special please give it to me
meet me at the Smithy where's the
[Music]
Smithy the Smithy the Smithy is this way
I would like a horse where do I where do
you get a where do I get a horse your
egg you
crack oh my God horses are are born from
eggs yeah egg and the best that they are
yes oh H well that's new knowledge is it
over here and how do I get off of it oh
there we go
do I just abandon the horse or just oh
goes back you shift the button yes
Sak yeah
gotcha oh sorry wait no there you are
hold on
okay hello hello fast pass fast pass
here is your pass you are drenched you
are soaked I am drenched yes I just saw
in the water I can't wait I can't I
can't give items I think you have to
trade you have to you have to trade you
have to trade you get a cold okay um no
I'm way too high you cannot you cannot
Fastpass she must Dawn the actions on
her own you're drowning
help
drowning no I'm not drowning I just like
the red block I just I am theer thank
you fast pass
I am a silly little
clown materals needed at the
and
drowning what's going on you're
drowning oh my God what hell going
on was was
tortur are you guys torturing somebody
is no no we are having a nice bath that
did not man this is such a peaceful team
I'm so glad I felt hands put under the
water though was it you no someone was
holding me down who was
that I couldn't get I couldn't get to
the surf must have done it the Amber
coin used their telepathy on you is is
the ambercoin our like our our main
enemy yes they are they are are oh they
are so they're they're the ones that we
should go out to kill kind of enemies
yes in the name of empathy we must kill
them yes in
the we
must violence to show how empathy Works
yes I see I didn't know empathy was so
violent but it makes sense one of them
plans what do you mean it makes sense so
sometimes violence is the only answer to
to have empathy show up we have to
restore balance yes restore balance I'm
starting to understand a lot of things
thank you yes this is what empathy means
okay empathy is to kill empathy is to
kill go bad the bad in this world
empathy means to kill for unfortunately
my my loyal companions I have a a pull
somewhere from the unknown and I must
are you being summoned by the forces
beyond your knowledge the the the
darkness is C in and I must can drown
Force um but I believe in you guys you
guys will you come back to us I I will
come back to you back I will I will come
back to you come back to this world as
soon as possible please don't forget
about me okay don't forget I would I do
not to be forgotten we will never forget
we will never forget you we will never
forget I am Ki beu and I will return to
you my companion we will no matter we
won't forget you never forget forget you
please wait for me I will I will see you
again again I will see you again goodbye
goodbye
goodbye uh uh uh
[Music]
uh she is gone the for she has
disappeared K the greatly forces have
claimed the sword oh no but she'll be
will that happen to all of us eventually
perhaps eventually all of us will will
be die will why do you have to be so
dark like that because empathy is
sometimes dark I see that makes so much
sense light there is Darkness M wise
words Queen wise words
wise Slay Slay the queen no no no slay
the stains like Slay Slay like slay yeah
I try can I I will try I will
try good good
good now can someone tell me where the
leeston child is once
again he is in the garden after you've
spoken to him oneon-one
uh yeah about the owl oh Ena how do I
open this box that you traded me with
like items oh you just right click after
you have it in your hand why right
clicking oh okay right click try placing
on the ground oh yeah place it on the
around with your right hand yes with
your right with your right maybe try
interacting okay I got it I got it with
the Box the ground thank
you man my throat is dead I don't even
know why it's
dead it must be the multi-dimensional
transference that caused it ah that
makes so much
sense what what it wait wait side quest
side
quest where is the J sword Guild Master
does anyone mayhaps
know nope if you um perhaps find
something green green go to attempt the
arena maybe you will find
them perhaps inside the
arena I'm not sure Apprentice you know
the pit Dorman
huh yeah I need to talk to pit you saw
the quest I posted what this the pit
Dorman is he a Dorman or is he a
Pitman he's I think he's a d Pitman M no
idea oh there we go you mean like a
Pikmin what's a Pikman I have no idea
what do you
mean something something something I
remember it's like hey dandor I am to be
here I kind remembering the the art of I
I think I master I'm remembering
something about Pikmin and the only
thing I can remember is that you
throw at people but the art of dandi
tell me where your leader is is there
any other Quest I can do your leader is
no thank you jna Watson even though you
wish to kill the
king excuse me do you know where are you
guys I am faced with a Amber coin member
and I you need to kill the king oh you
need assistance an Amber coin member yes
I feel thre save
him where where are you guys second I
must hang up
my te I need
to let me follow
hello where where are we going I have no
idea I thought you knew the way I don't
know the way why would you think I would
know the way I'm a baby Baboo hey let's
go tease the ambercoin amberin ambercoin
am ambercoin you're right ambercoin
disgusting coin I agree
e hey hey don't like them hey why are
you doing that you don't need to be so
negative about that no it's only a we
you know I'm just I'm just so negative
about myself and the ambercoin I just
man I wish wish I wasn't part of Amber
they're poo poo
stinky wait what's wrong what's wrong
yeah yeah we can we can we can we are
full of empathy we will totally listen
to what's wrong yeah do you want to join
us do you want to join you you full but
I must go speak to the
children the children children I speak
to the children in the gardens you have
children in the gardens do you know
where they are yeah take us to the
children they're at the gardens this is
this
way do you know do you know how to find
your way of course I do I of the Amber
coin I am Amber coins money they're not
a yes I love money you got some money I
can't get enough of the gold I love it
so much Le beston child does not have
any
money oh this is not the G well as I am
part of Amber coin I would hate to give
them my
money what the heck is this placeway is
this your children is this your child
where is P that is
Henry what
Henry kind I adopted
Henry wow with that much money it's easy
to adopt so many
people pit Dorman thank you you are you
you met pit Dorman I'm so happy for
you okay wait am I still not done with
the Smithy Quest
[Music]
huh I thought I was
done oh wait I wasn't done I guess wait
where's this where's the Smithy again
I'm lost
[Music]
Smithy Smithy it's suddenly so quiet and
then I realized I think it's because the
group chat the the party call is
something quiet okay I'll
just how do I how oh there we
go you brought the logs thank you so
much see my master over there if you
bring the raw materials to him he can
make all sorts of tools and items for
you do I
still what should I make
make do I need another sword no no no
maybe I would an axe or
no oh I can't buy
it this confusing
[Music]
wait maybe I'm supposed to talk to him
more oh there we go craft a wooden
pickaxe at the Smithy then speak to the
okay
okay wooden pickaxe
hey am I supposed to
like need planks oh
okay okay okay it is Minecraft okay
okay what am I even saying what's
Minecraft okay and
then got
it oh okay 20 coins okay stick I need to
make
stick uh I realized I realized
stick
stick I haven't done Minecraft I mean
I've never never played Minecraft but I
don't remember ever playing Minecraft
before let's go okay I spent money
though I don't like the fact that I
spent
money what now what now
Quest
okay try bringing him some planks and
sticks I already did I made one
[Music]
from now on when you find new materials
stop by here and talk to my master the
more different materials you find the
more you things he'll be able to make
gotcha
yay collect craft a wooden pickaxe at
the Smithy then speak to the
back okay okay
okay this book is so
handy ah collect 10 Cobblestone and
speak to the blacksmith's Apprentice
abandoned okay okay how do I get
cobblestone let
me oh nobody's in the call
okay wonder if there's anyone I can
bother where is the Cobblestone where I
should probably look at the
map could go out on an
adventure you have it Ena gave it to you
already you're right but I kind of also
want to know how how to actually you
know get
it our magical radio connection has
dropped where have you
gone my Jonathan I mean is it is this
how you spell it my
Jonathan let us connect once more
[Music]
what
oh
why I seriously don't know why wait okay
okay let's leave let's
leave chill chill
[Music]
okay I have no idea what the hell went
on no wonder suly was so quiet it's cuz
I don't know why I left I don't know why
are we yelling I have no idea I at I am
at
is this the board this is the board
right I think the I think it's something
bugged oh oh hello I don't know I don't
know why I left please please let me in
under your wing again once more we shall
we shall
remake is
[Music]
sure let me I mean I mean what our Rock
is gone so we have
four that's true we do have
four
please are you in a party you're you're
in the party right we should we should
disband the party you can join the call
again by the way
how with using the green uh radio item
but I'm not in the party so I can't join
oh it says I'm not in a party yeah oh
maybe that's that's why yeah can can can
you please okay we shall we shall get
rid of this party it's not it's it's
weird I don't know why I like they
suddenly shoved me in a party with with
some ambercoin members
disgusting we must leave this
world
for a
second to
resolve this issue
okay it's all right you will leave this
world for a slight second and you can
return oh to the blue house I see
probably I I need to leave this world is
that what I need to do I think so okay
I'll also do that I'll be right back
okay I'll leave the world and be back
wait a sec wait a sec oh hello hello
hello I'm trying to figure things out I
think I think something um went a miss
you know I will leave the world and come
back okay okay I will
also
sure okay okay and then like
this okay okay okay here here is an
invite to the
party where did my M oh there there we
go oh there we go
and now we can join there we go the
wonderful
radio yeah
St the way you move ain't
fair where' you where where those words
come from I don't know I don't want to
get involved I don't know it's just a
hor mem I guess
hello new people beautiful pink lady wa
beautiful um oh gosh these two are
exhibiting an aura that I've never
who are you what is your
name I feel like I feel like your legs
are calling to me your thighs I feel
like she the master of sneaking your
thighs are calling to me I have ay I
want to sit on your thigh I don't know
why I want to sit on
your hey hey hey hey hey hey back I have
a and I'm not afraid to use
it you're your sighte is so sharp but
you know I also have some shurik like
things
Amin you're not Amin are you you I Jade
sword okay then you're okay Ain sucks
but if you're Jade fine oh no she's been
there so much
between I have no idea that's what my
guil told me to say it is focused on
well as long as I can join you for your
adventure I guess bronze no brain menen
my fair Maiden can you open your magic
tombs and go to page four weaps sure
what a and leave your party whatever
party you may be in we are better than
that so no worries I'm going to you to
you swine did you did yous do that say
my brain is Tiny I know this place like
the back of my hand I am very smart
welcome I've joined your party Welcome
to our party welcome how do you know
this place like the back I'm not
abandoning Elizabeth she seems to have
made
friends
what are not friends we are not friends
we are not friends to each other no
noed I was but about to hush a traitor
she is a
traitor is supposedly ambercoin Amber
she's Jade sword I don't really know
like
this oh my God
I just I just contacted someone she is a
harlot too what what
happened harlet what's a
harlot you do not need to know wet
what wet I don't know it sounded a
little wet don't you
think wait um well you know let's let's
let's let's forget about you know oh
recollection recollection Revelation I
forgot everything that happened get your
sword upgrade you must be flustered
where do I the fluster the fluster
Amber the beautiful pink beautiful pink
lady I'm going back to our Guild okay
what will you do there they're going to
make more money that's what they're
going to do oh I see oh yes I love money
for I am part of
amberon you liar you bloody liar you
bloody liar what did she Li
what what guilt she's a part of if you
guys aren't Amber coin and you're not
Jade sword are you ceran cup no we're
we're the we're the best team in the
world and you should join you should
join our our our call our call on the
magic radio what is all right we have
the magic col yeah you're not in the
magic R you don't you don't need to you
don't need to possibly join what is the
magic radio this this thing that's in
our hand right here and then you you
click on it you right click on it and
you ring ring with the diamond thingy or
I don't know if it's a diamond thingy
but the thing what is Diamond thingy oh
actually I don't know it looks like a
pile of dust to me where I'm trying to
I'm trying to recruit the pink the
beautiful pink thighs to join our call
oh I in it yay let
us the castle Gates everyone the castle
gates gates I understand everyone do the
quest up until top
follow me up until the uh the ruins the
ruins yes no I'm still at the Smithy
Quest wait wait let me let me finish
that real quick yeah okay is there
something we wanted to do after that I'm
assuming we speak to well like you got
to get to the quest first cuz our quests
are not synced so oh okay okay wait wait
wait wait sorry let me let me do this
real quick uh do
I uh could you bring us 10 Cobblestone
okay okay okay okay yeah yeah it's so
hard talking to these um these Leeson
that you have to like you have to like
Crouch like crazy to make them and the
sticky keys the force of the sticky keys
comes on and makes it very difficult why
is everyone
falling I think they turned off sticky
keys actually cly people maybe I'm the
only one that gets the sticky keys we
were advised
turn but if you press shift six times
though I have not been getting greater
Powers have advised to turn off those
sticky keys how do do to them wait true
I want to give it to them H I am being
swarmed at the castle Gates there are so
many I hey how do you get
cobblestone tell me Cobblestone follow
me follow me yes my Queen off what KY
Mor k your name they
hurt what what happened what is your
quest my quest is to exit the Town Gate
head to the plains and speak to hastas
of the Jade sword okay we're on the same
Quest okay great Iris wait is your name
Iris your name is Iris yes my name is
Iris what yes follow me here this is the
castle gate speci okay you're all very
special let us go we are full of empathy
mind
youy is our middle name oh my God this
world is so large what all of our middle
names is Cobblestone is this
way see over there
oh it's minecra I mean it's it's Stone
excuse me what is Minecraft yes
Minecraft I I have no idea what I just
said this is what how do you CFT the
mines
yes what are you yeah bully that puppy
bully that puppy it's making puppy
noises we are not bullying him we are
freeing him of his they're quite a
different why are you trying to kill the
rabbit yeah it's a dark one
what's wrong with the dark one I don't
know they're EV what the rabbits are
fine blue St no no it's not what about
the cows it's just a normal rabbit can
we can we can we make meat out of the
cows wait sorry instincts I want to get
off the horse oh there goodness wait let
me
Revelation Revelation Revelation ghost
stories Revelation the cow didn't die
from the Revelation wow this cow is
strong wait that is a strong cow that is
a strong cow die Revelation
Revelation oh my God I didn't mean to
kill those oh God why did I it drop
anything it didn't even drop any meat
these guys I will help you I can't even
kill
coins hey the monsters Dro
coins Rich to be rich
I no we are not to be full of greed that
is not us we are full of empathy okay
you I have no idea what empathy means
anymore what does empathy mean can
someone give me a definition of empathy
passion compassion yeah compassion peace
empathy how that's what it means are you
Cerulean cup yes we are all ceran C we
are all Cerulean cup yes nice to meet
you this what is what is Jade all about
huh what is Jade all about hey hey hey
hey don't don't be so aggressive oh
tense thing we are courageous fighters
who fight for what's right oh wow oh
okay you guys seem like the actual good
guys okay yeah what do you mean actual
good guys we are good too the actual oh
yeah oh yeah you're right you're right
we're full of empathy and we forced
empathy on people by killing them right
no no okay well everybody's their kind
is that taking things into their own
hands I guess control your horse is that
oh excuse me sorry my horse is a is
quite a um you know Rowdy fella you see
I I don't know how to control it oh what
a Ry horse I'm I'm talking to I'm
talking to a ambercoin member right now
and oh the Amber coin member this
ambercoin member is the same member that
adopted many children and um and is and
loves money what yes I wonder why I Love
Money Amber she must love money cuz
that's what she says like Liz who is Liz
I eat money for breakfast you eat money
for breakfast does it does it
taste you seem to dislike a that the
amen diet oh wow what kind of money do
you eat every single for breakfast lunch
and dinner is it different every single
time Iris Iris where are
you breakfast you're at the I for
breakfast we' like have you uh copper
flakes copper flakes oh yes I will
silver when do you eat
silver hey hey hey stop talking with
that fake Amber
coin hey get out of here you don't you
don't own this place you don't own this
place hey US cups are here stay I was
just asking what her n diet was she's
really not bad don't don't talk to don't
talk to her she's like a fake ambercoin
oh she's I mean that's not a good that's
not
yeah she's Jade sword apparently oh
she's not is she actually not
Amin not am I am oh I actually thought
she was amberin yeah yeah I thought she
was ambercoin too yeah wait you you lied
to me I thought you were I thought you
were ambercoin you kept saying you loved
money that was just like a full yes I've
been lying to you this whole time I am
part of the Scarlet wand how dare you
how did your teammates
go while you were saying Amber coin wait
where did your teammates
go I have to apologize I was also lying
on her behalf saying that she was a
member of Jade sword she is not no she
wants to keep her her ID even
Jord oh she's a compulsive liar oh my
God she lied don't know where she is
from oh she's
dangerous so is I she's in the red team
I mean it makes sense but hey hey you
don't talk to hey you don't talk to my
killed member
like stop stop it you shush your mouth
hey do not raise your voice at me I am
the next Queen in line you will have you
will respect me Queen alone leave me
Hiers alone she is you put your SW where
it belongs on the ground is PVP can show
you where there's PVP yes there is would
you like to follow me yes there is
that's our Guild the J I will take you
to the J I will take you to the Jade
sword Guild what there's at the Jade
sword Guild it's right this way follow
me so she is Jade is she Jade sword is
she wait who's I don't know what's going
on is she Jade sword or she not Jade
sword I should just remember this St
welcome to the Jade sword Arena guys are
we are we going to dungeon
let's go to the dungeon right go to the
you're right we should go to the dungeon
let's go to the dungeon to the d sword
Arena whenever it's waiting for you
yeah the only place I do have courage is
on the battlefield I need to do my quest
you guys can I need to do my quest wait
uh what was the next Quest I need to go
back to the quest Master Miss ninoa
where is hastus at the plains you can
check the map left shift oh
onwards I need to get off the check the
map and I should show you the NPC need
to go to next I know we've got a Dy but
I hope
you I not see him on my he's very far
south oh you here started yeah I'm on we
just speak to the shop I think it's just
strange where is the
shopkeeper the shopkeeper is right
across the the Smithy okay thank
you yeah I am here he has been expecting
me is it just straight AC what the oh no
what is this Jade sword I think I see
shopkeeper shopkeeper shopkeeper
shopkeeper far south huh am I just
supposed to talk to the shop
[Music]
maybe across the planes I see
oh hello we must kill all these ooh
gold dude do not be so easily distracted
hello sorry I'm sorry my my empathy I
must return to kill them all you have to
do is talk to me and I'll show you when
I've gotten stock then s what do you
want to buy isn't that easy my empathy I
must put the stains down do stop by if
you ever need anything
okay her you have a break and do
something okay you can try visiting the
Gill Halls of the four Great guills for
instance each of them has an activity
okay oh the great room do I have a lot
of quests I need to do I gu which one
are you at I'm at the shopkeeper Quest
well these are all side quests and
they're all you're you're
like you're almost there I think you
have to go talk to the the kid in the
park you got some time why not visit the
gardens the children are attending to
them I'm sure okay the children children
let's stock some children stain I oh wow
wait wait while we wait for friends I'm
going to go ahead and pin my my jade
sordel emblem where's the children
where's the children lead me to the CH
where's the
children in the
there's a child is it the place with the
Amber coin is it where um Liz was trying
to take us or is that a different place
no if you if you check your map you'll
see a red marker for the next NPC you
need to talk to do you want me to help
you wait let me see if I can figure this
out why does it say I don't have any
side quests huh I thought I
did did I
like where should I pin it I'm coming to
find you where are you I'm in front of
the shopkeeper and I'm just like wait I
thought wait do I so I talked to him he
was like go find the children but then
like now I don't have a quest and I'm
just like where's the children oh so
like just follow me mhm I I think yeah
it should be I think it should be around
here maybe it was this
way yeah I think are these the
children uh there there's a child like
in the middle of the garden there's a
Gard great sword yeah there's a garden
garden wait maybe this isn't it speak
to yeah it's the Leeson child and it's
must be one important child to be called
the Le best and child I know right he
the child of the country where where did
crony
go I thought I was following you and
then I W very cool thank you isn't that
a p where's the sharp part going into my
eyeball theal child oh found it I found
I think I see the Leal child wait oh
really I think it showed up on my map
now it wasn't there before I swear that
was cool okay good thank you CU I can't
find it I will now make Jade sword a
part of me Leal child let me talk to you
I just want to say hi Leal
child Leal child yes the it's the best
child ever is the Leal child spawn if we
end up perishing in battle in this ruin
oh
wait is that theal child it looks like
any other kid what makes this one so
special lock the ruins oh some have
reported hearing a strange voice but we
know not what to make of it okay let's
see Souls of stains open the
way okay looks like our team members
already figured out the the
riddle there's a riddle I mean yeah it
says oh slay 10 stains and then want to
do some building or gardening got it
leave it to me I'm
ready cannot proceed yet oh yeah you
we'll see about
that I've been slaying stains this whole
time dang it speak to the bestern
children okay speak to the pit Dorman
okay now I'm at the pit Dorman okay pit
Dorman okay you found the pit Dorman
where was the pit Dorman again was like
in it was in the yellow area right it
was in the green wait was it yellow what
the heck is this
I remember crony saying she wanted to
see the pit dormant 20 minutes ago so
yeah CR I can't I mean I mean the queen
I mean I mean Tam Tam Tam oh oh wait
what is your
name Tam Tam your name is Tam yes oh
where'd that come from oh I mean Tam
Jonathan Jonathan named me Tam stands
for the Azure Maiden Tam for short I see
now hold on makes so much sense what yes
yes yes I'm so soaking in all this
information maybe I didn't use it right
oh oh no not the map want to get
riching the who is Tam that's strange
that's
me you we have been in the same party
for tens of minutes and you do not know
her name your name isn't that a bit odd
huh I was told that the faker
are you talking about Liz yes and you
lied to us about her affiliations why
does she yell at me then why would she
lie then she just doesn't want we can
gamble here apparently she's in the
arena but I can't find
her The Guild Master wishes to speak
with you please meet him at the Jade SW
confused speak to the P speak to the
Jade swword Guild Master Okay Jade
swword Guild Master oh what are you
doing all by yourself after our
Quest None Shall
breach wait oh never mind you're not the
master you look like har hold on I got
to I got to drop out of this call for a
second excuse me
[Music]
excuse what the
hell I just hear Harlot and all of a
sudden I'm kicked
out I hear Harlot and then all of a
sudden the group chat just
disappears you heard the Harlot yeah I
just heard her say oh what a harlot and
then all of a sudden we're kicked out
and then she left or she like
discontinued the party call or something
I think she is fighting the
Harlot man there's so many harlots I
feel like I've heard her say Harlot 20
times already there's only one har
there's only one Harlot yes there's only
one Harlot it is Liz the harlet oh I see
that's the Harlot okay she's the Harlot
gotcha I mean she she was kissing
Harlot as well she did KISS never call
her
that okay Watson is pure of heart she
did kiss
me yes who kissed you Liz yes she she
she smooched me and see and now I can
sing a song about kissing a girl now oh
wait
congratulations will you sing now I
can't actually no I can't remember the
Melody I couldn't possibly remember the
melody I just remember that words I
kissed a girl and I liked it the taste
of her cherry chap I did not
like no no no I didn't like it it's just
the lyrics you know and I liked it the
lyrics The Taste of her cherry chapstick
I don't think she was wearing Cherry
chapstick you eny H it would taste like
Wax personally yeah I think it would
probably taste like many around you I
will
help the Calamity in the St okay okay am
I shaking go I pray will okay finding a
way for you to regain your powers of
[Music]
Revelation what see she's so mean to
me I will have a word with her do wish
we could all get along you're over 10
now oh there's no such thing as getting
along with everyone what are you talking
about oh true enough I have to drop this
call to give her a piece of my mind oh
there she is
go I like how when someone drops a call
the whole call just shuts down wait okay
I did
not I did not understand a single word
he was saying or more like I wasn't
really really paying attention
Okay the gate what did they say Town
Gate huh uh exit the Town Gate head to
the Plains and speak to hastus of the
GRE Jade
sword Town Gate where's the count game
again Co
cool
okay oh wait wrong
[Music]
way I'll just join just in case okay um
and
then where do I go I know Ena really
wants to dungeon
so wait oh wrong one I'm going to head
to the plane speak to hastus of the Jade
sword hastus where are you hastus hastus
is not shown on this map maybe I have to
go
further
hastus is it is it the red thing over
there is that
Hess you know I'm looking at the map
that I can't even you know you know
admire the view I'm just looking at the
map
oh I see people seems I cannot give you
my
melons what are we talking about the
Harlot is talking about melons
[Music]
now I
tried these melons are stuck to my
hand oh there am
ions I apologize for not giving you my
melons can I have your melons too
I would try but I cannot give it to the
why why how can you try and and fail at
giving
melons I I am using the uh muscle the
muscle the Q muscle is not working oh my
God okay wait I'm just going to pretend
I didn't hear that and just go oh is
this a Shar chest arrived we have been
expecting you do you have do you see my
stuff inial for
theu with no way to enter the ruins we I
guess everyone can use it some have a
strange
voice oh good you have to slay 10 stains
exit the Town Gate head to the plains
speak to Okay Okay slay 10 stains then
speak to it's okay okay I think I'm
almost at the the dungeon Quest probably
yeah you just need to kill 10 10 of them
I just got to kill 10 of them okay okay
there are more like out in the
plains is there no such thing is like
you know um koing them with the jump
attack let me just kill
more oh I should equip the sword you're
right stains come
hi hey hey hey no crits damn it there's
no point
in guess I can check the thing with you
you have shields Shields would be ni I I
made a trade
request
nice how many more how many more do I
need to
do did you go inside well I have no
doubt she could
clear okay okay okay is my skill aing
Revelation Revelation I can't tell how
far it goes oh my God it barely does
anything you
killed weak oh sorry I mean I Revelation
it what are you talking about I didn't
kill it I Revelation
it
reation I'm
dying okay where is uh I forgive
you what is your name red thing
Elizabeth I am Jonathan with a
G oh ow it's actually Jonathan G
gathan oh that that is a Jonathan gathan
no no no it's Jonathan I think there is
it's in the other
shop like ational regeneration yay I
killed 10 of
them yes there one closer to Extinction
to accept oh why are youel fashion
surprise
box I just be that
way that way now what do I do um maybe I
can trade my talk to the dude where the
dude through the power of my empathy I
forgive you I know it must have been
very rough to have fallen in hard
times ow oh did you guys make up I'm
I've made up with her okay that's good
oh yes I got the key I got the
underworld key thing I don't forgive you
yeah show I'm working through it get one
to see like go too but don't we need to
be in a party I can go to the dungeon
now
anyone all does everyone have the map I
mean not map does everyone have their
key yeah I think already entered though
didn't
she give me a second I'm shopping last
minute but I'll be right there okay
who's doing water alone is this is this
the dungeon where am I he has this key
where is the dungeon anyway oh I can
hear you guys now oh my gosh or you guys
can hear me sorry about that right there
it's at the end yeah I got the
key enter no I'm back at the town just
chopping a bit how do we know how many
we have SE I see it you have to use and
then you go all the way to the
end do you think wooden swords is enough
what if you guys you didn't get you
think that would be good should we buy
should we buy
upgrades well we don't really have iron
you know what let's Let Me Mine a bit I
see gold right here maybe they want to
stay with their
group oh that's mine no what are you
talking about what do you mean that's
yours actually I was almost I was almost
done no that's mine actually no get out
of my way get out of my way was almost
done I was almost done no that's what
you did to me you will never you will
never successfully dig that one out you
will never no no no no I I will not
allow
you
you're you know what it's probably
faster if I start it appears there are
people on a cut scene in front of us or
they're seeing visions in their head and
they are reacting to it well they must
be crazy then they must be crazy then
wait I oh I think they must have cleared
the uh cleared the dungeon okay do two
other people want to enter the dungeon
together maybe let's enter the dungeon
let's enter the dungeon if five of us go
then one person will probably be left
behind really only four can go only five
yeah we have
five yeah but I feel like we should also
what about Liz she's not in our party a
we can go into teams of three we can s
yeah we can split yeah yeah that would
be the best way everyone meet
inside are we really going to go are we
going to go in with um with wooden
swords I I think I should
stone sword can I can can you possibly
be kind so oh so kind to um throw me a
stone
sword gathan beloved gathan will I will
have to return to town to get you a
stone sword you know I'll come with let
me make haste let me come with I think
we have to SP party before going into
the
dungeon there's a area in there that we
must make ready checks I think we are
owed to oh split the party before we do
our ready checks okay if you say
so oh there they
go all are repeatable I think yeah oh
okay so look here Fair Maiden Iris oh
gathan my lovely handsome gathan yes yes
yesc Jan maybe after we clear it the
first
time it is pronounced joh I I
mispronounced many words no that's
comically large please accept this trade
this is how a normal sword looks
like yes I have a stone sword you may
have some raw beef thank you I will eat
it in front of you to show how
appreciative I am yes please eat the raw
eat it raw
exit the
call how did that taste it tasted so
good really I have to purchase a back
super happy to hear that she ate a raw
okay
um and then where's the oh okay I have
to right click oh
click this and then there we go o oh you
gave me the whole set thank you actually
no wait no sorry I misunderstood wait
where is it okay nice nice nice thank
thank you nice nice nice I'll
just pickax this yeah okay nice okay let
us return let us
[Music]
return I'm getting the hang of
this
fast gidy giddy
up I'm going the right way no knows how
to wining yeah towards the
bridge we are
here oh no she's still
[Music]
SL okay know do we we have to do this
quest to be able to do the next bit yes
did you guys kill 10 go into the kill 10
if you kill 10 then we we can go to the
next
thing
Elizabeth do you not have a normal sword
myal
I do it seems my my my my freakishly
large one is wonder what I can do with
the stone pickaxe freakishly weak yes
youly weak sword could I
possibly get up some
copper oh my God I can I
can oh my
God I feel the civilization
let's
go one of these
respawn oh yeah wait I should
probably we are trying to
get Liz her Quest completion so she can
enter I think she needs to kill a few
more stains outside by the way Liz it
won't tell you if you kill 10 you just
got to you just got to
know
wait there's one over here I'm going to
go dig for some more stuff
while I got to hoard all the all the
materials you
see that's what I'm here for I'll be
right back hoarding yes okay than
thing hey what are you doing what are
you doing here huh you hoarder pink pink
hoarder you hoarder yes you what do you
mean hoarder you hoarded my gold you're
a hoarder hoarded your gold who are you
speaking to I'm speaking to one lady
that is not in our group call for some
reason even though she is part of te why
do I keep getting
disconnected how could they do such a
thing man she she really likes hanging
up on us so you know I don't know what I
don't know what's her atically
know maybe it's the person who creates
the phone call hangs up and it hangs up
for everyone perhaps
oh perhaps I'm going to test
it what what my fellow friends finally
oh yeah I don't know it feels like if
someone leaves it just ends the whole
thing did it work yes it did kick it
does drop I see I see I see
oh oh I didn't mean to oh I can't swim
he how do I swim oh there we go oh
there's diamond in
here how do I
swim it did the gods did tell
me okay in the end wait wait wait no
worries I'm going to I'm going to make
some Diamond that's what I'm going to do
wa wait
first is there any other material that
I'm missing
no oh it's not like she was just testing
the water why do you keep hanging up my
connection I was entering a tunnel uh
the tunnel seems that the magical
connection between our brains causes it
to to drop the call mean this is all
talking is
telepathic yeah I'm talking directly
into your head oh
wow Sasa magical
world well how do I throw thing oh waist
bin okay yeah recycle lady recycle
copine you may be a queen but you should
recycle copine what what excuse me don't
think I've ever been called something so
foul
myen no maybe I have but that's
definitely very
[Music]
yucky the Smithy won't let me make more
stuff I have an autograph I don't know
what she what a pleasure to see
everyone oh hey we are
incoming with many people okay awaiting
you I
[Music]
seen yes yes friends are here really
what what really what
okay I trust you as as a member of the
Cerulean cup I trust
easily wait don't do
that I can't I can't there's a wall oh
okay there's a l i are you
sure are you sure think she needs to
join the party can she join the party I
can't jump it's not allowing me
to only how do I this
away to invite her what's under here
we'll split into into groups of three in
a minute we're going to split into two
yeah party is different than the coal oh
okay
okay please do not bother me is everyone
inside the
dungeon oh okay are we going in the
dungeon first and then we split so weird
yeah no we yeah go inside pass the
bridge and then we can split our party
yeah okay okay pass the bridge bridge so
around here this area where we're
waiting in front of the
dungeon farewell I passed by something
farewell maidens
yes
Tashi
kii I shall meet you
again past
the greater Tash goodbye Tanashi Kiara
your name's
Kar I don't know what they're talking
about they're making me really
uncomfortable maybe it was
K Kia sounds familiar can you please
leave me alone where is everyone I have
issues with people I am right in front
of this the Ed at the edge of the bridge
group chat okay Comm maybe we should get
out of theou hello hello group chat
group chat oh my God hey assemble
Assemble
assemble leave me alone I just want to
go in the dungeon with my
friends I don't know what you're talking
about please leave me
alone no I don't know what you're
talking about I just want to go I just
want to go into the dungeon with my
friends is someone stopping you from
entering the dungeon big up
SZ I should get out of here who was pre
hey what are you guys doing to my
honorary guild member on there's a CIA
person that's being very rude let me get
rid of
them uh me put them in timeout for 24
hours there we go that's right I'm in
the toilet so away what the hell should
we go in what the hell what no no no
just come inside just come come um
that's not the dungeon yet you it's the
it's the path going toward the dungeon
so you can go inside I get it thank you
appreciate that what is crony doing in a
to
hey like I said group chat assemble stop
hanging around in the toilet wherever
you are yes not in the
toilet how what what what what are you
letting out that you're taking so long
in the toilet just wait where are you
hurry we're we're we're in front of the
dungeon I'm in front of the dungeon what
do you mean you're you're not in front
of a
dungeon You're the only one that's not
here what AR we aren't we at the canyon
no click the thing to go in after you
get the key oh
okay
henceforth known to all we must enter
the dungeon okay we must split and enter
the dungeon yeah we got to split up I
don't know if Liz know does Liz
know okay okay let me go let me go see
if I can pick her up Liz I don't know if
she let let us go to the
dungeon towards the dungeon if we're in
a private call let us go in Dungeon no
she can hear us we are in a radio call
okay yes yes all right let us I am going
to go to page four of my magical Tob
okay we can make a new group in this B
this
party yes party
disbanded I'll make a new one then
um who would like claim your three two
claim your two my two huh your two who's
my my two claim who wants to join te
claim your two yeah yeah oh you guys
yeah yeah oh my gosh they're very
frightening but I'll invite them what do
you mean
right let me grab Miss
ninoa okay let me grab Liz who I have
forgiven I mean aren't you also aren't
you also perhaps like something that
might be connected to this dungeon we
have a cheap code yeah huh I mean I do
get a familiar
feeling competition now she party invite
Miss Liz we should probably drop out of
the radio then I suppose so a new radio
call then yeah oh okay okay is everyone
ready standing by enter the dungeon oh
there we stand by okay we're going to do
amazing I have no doubt be we're going
to finish faster than the other teams
yeah yeah we will enter the dungeon no
players standing by you got to stand we
got to ready we have to ready first yes
there you go okay
enter all right your party
enter we're ready yo we made it wasn't
there something we needed was there
something we needed to kind of like I
don't know play play play play when we
enter the I don't think so don't worry
okay okay the underworld domain
oppressive Darkness as feared as it is
unavoidable it holds a final resting
place for every creature that walks the
Earth yet even in this realm of the den
there are those accidentally skipped
everything it's a guy ready for you you
know it feels very familiar to me I
think you're supposed
to death oh that's such a that's such a
scary concept
death also yeah also the other let me
explain to the C people the other two
are are gone because uh they're in a
different instance we split they are
facing in a different dimension
split oh no no no please hang on this is
okay you are bad at this should we build
a
bridge excuse me I just had a little
slip a little slip oh there we go there
we go good good good nice nice okay
there seems to be a light over there so
let's go okay that light seems promising
scary
I'll go towards it too uh oh wow that's
a should we make a bridge uh can we make
a bridge let's try it be the safest
beted to make a
bridge uh no shall try jumping they say
I'm going yeah no yeah it won't let me
oh no placing blocks huh well then we'll
have to be
careful how
about go that no that's where we came
from let's go that
way okay lead the way let's go that way
and then we go this way and then she
want to know where she's going I totally
know where we're going oh yeah there's
another yellow thing over there
yeah oh is wait wait where are you where
where are you where are you over here
yeah it's like a some kind of like
Obelisk where's where's where's I mean
where's Tam oh there we go Tam her name
is me Tam Gander oron Gander who's oroni
okay if you say so I'm little confused
checkpoint checkpoint nice so perhaps if
we die if we have a perish we'll respond
here that sounds promising that's
comforting
promising oh I think we need to go over
there that's ominous looking Church o I
think that's a castle that's not a
church that's a castle it's like a sky
in the sky yeah Okay jump jump jump oh
so that's why so many people
ding oh yeah the mystery jump though we
can all jump we we will not die even
once we are we are better than that
exactly we are what do they call it
Gamers yes we are totally
Gamers person who plays games well yeah
games yeah try not to bring the team
down oh new Che you're a gamer me your
checkpoint checkpoint wow we're just
speeding through it huh yeah I know
right and then we go this way and then
we go this way and then we go this way
settle down bu wao she's really
quick you seem to know this place better
than me and I feel like this used to be
my home or
something yeah sett down buddy oh boy oh
she definitely doesn't know where she's
going no I just it was just a slip of a
slip of a hand I'll be right back I'll
be right right of a foot more alike yeah
that's true ni one wait
she'll be able to make it back I'm sure
no I'm right behind you I'm right behind
you right yeah a speedy teammate would
definitely be right back right behind
the next check maybe right behind you
whoa that looks really
familiar okay it's not this way it's a
not this
way did I get the
che well I don't know if
I don't need it because I'm very I am so
gaming I don't even know what G what
does gaming even mean that sounds like a
that sounds like a word that's only for
people who who game actually games yeah
yeah it's a term that only I know well
you guys don't play games just in your
free time
for doesn't know what gaming means no
but I'm just curious ow I thought
everybody has Hobbies I a lot of people
game you know what your hobbies are you
remember what your hobbies are C
apparently yeah they say jumping and
also I'm apparently a
reaping I think who told you you're a
Reaper you're you you must have be
you're more you're goddess people not
not a Reaper you're a goddess goddess
what why do you say a goddess a godd
makes me really embarrassed when you say
that but why do you think that she's a
goddess how could she be a Reaper no huh
I made it to the castle got us to you I
don't know I'm going to die everything
which is ironic it's okay I died twice
already no wor I never died cuz I'm the
queen well that doesn't matter that that
won't matter you'll die soon enough no
worries trying to take the
throne no no no no like the The King and
I oh man I can't believe I have to
explain the story every single time but
the King and I we locked no no they
locked lips thing is the
Kings what no we didn't go that far what
are you say all right I mean hey live
your
life no wait not like that it's supposed
to be like a political thing okay oh a a
marriage arrangement of convenience a
political marriage where I gain the
throne because I mean look at the king
it's easy oh I he's pretty old I guess
but I I I could definitely popet him
behind the scenes man man look at this
lady talk oh oh we're in the
dungeon oh we're in the dungeon okay oh
get in here oh cool it's dark it's time
to fight okay I'm ready whatever enemies
may come our way oh my God is a demon oh
yeah it was too fast Revelation the
demons everywhere get them yeah oh my
God reation is bad God wait wait wait I
need I need to put my sword
get him Revelation crits exist crits
nice nice job okay I think we got to I
think we got to keep I think they keep
spawning so you just got to push through
them maybe do we have levels in this in
this world well I'm level 15 but oh this
one had an
item maybe we retain our levels they
have like they have rice balls what are
these things oh my God they have shapes
they have shapes they have like a like a
star shape and oh my God they hurt
yeah they do hurt quite a bit it hurt
quite a lot oh my god
oh oh my God oh my God W this is really
oh my God it really
hurts ouch quite a maze isn't it it it
it's
amazing shut up
also recollection oh my God they don't
die they don't die from it's
recollection it's revelation reation
[Music]
waa that area is way too dark wow wait
where are you
guys oh wait I found something oh oh hey
I found a door a door yeah I'll watch
your back where's the door okay there's
a triangle
key how do I you know some of the
zombies are actually holding these
things oh y you must have picked one up
hey there you are you found us y unlock
the door y nice one yeah let's go I
totally did something I'm sure I did you
found the way can we ride the oh we
can't ride the horse here okay no horing
around I've definitely been here before
ooh so you must be a goddess yeah if
this is if this reminds you of your home
then you must live
in a castle W look at those chandeliers
oh I want to swing on
him whoa she wants to
swing from the chandelier chier Smiley
Cyrus
chandelier where' that song come from I
can't remember I don't know I'm sure we
heard it somewhere what do you think
this thing does is this a puzzle I think
this is a puzzle it looks like maybe
it's a movie screen maybe we just jump
into it no never mind do you usually
jump into movie screen I don't know oh
we're looking it is a puzzle oh okay
wait it's like it's like one of those
things where you like eventually make
everyone everything light up right by
just clicking on it like randomly um hey
I got this side
uh-oh but all the the other sides affect
each
other oh really maybe one maybe one
person should do it then aoop aoop oh I
don't know I feel like I'm not smart
enough for this kind
of aoop you're doing good you're doing
good a Boop yep y yep yep yep a boop
boop boop boop
boop Yep this is hard a
Boop are you why don't you do something
rather than just you know why don't you
Bo I usually for these for these puzzles
um only one person should do it cuz
otherwise you're
just you could do another side of you
don't could Boop another side you know
there's four sides to this right yeah
yeah yeah yeah why don't you go Boop
another side and do it faster than me if
you're you know if you I want to but you
keep messing it up buddy really is it
changing the other sides too oh it
is
yeah that's okay common mistake don't
even worry about it oh okay I thought it
was a one I thought each side had its
own puzzle I didn't a you're cute so
it's forgiving yeah it's it's
okay bashful oh no I'm embarrassed now
why did I say that thing to say
beautiful pink lady likes
me she doesn't like you what she doesn't
like you she she doesn't huh no not like
that not like that well hurry up and
hurry up and solve the puzzle then hey
man tried to take my time
here meanwhile oh man I will mingle with
Pink Ladies to hurry up me yes oh hi you
know you're pink too actually I didn't
know that I'm solving all this puzzle by
myself I'm hot
pink yeah I guess you are really
beautiful yeah yeah I'm hot pink oh oh
my God not just pink oh what's wrong
what's wrong I thought you were going to
solve this I I
am oh she's Violet I don't know it's
it's like a I think yeah it is like a
hot pink violetti is color it's very
beautiful it's a pomegranate thank you a
pomegranate what is that that sounds
delicious it's a really Juicy Fruit oh
wow you remember your fruits I'm so
proud of you oh yeah I mean I remember
basic things just not my history hey
guys you know like the bonding time is
great and all but do you really want us
to help you with this do you really no
like you know I mean you know cron are
you sure I think we're just going to
ruin it for you wait wait I think you're
close I think you're really close though
wait wait
[Music]
we're really close wait wait we need to
move them over you figured something out
probably I'm going to ruin it aren't I
no no you're not going to ruin
it you feel like you need to switch it
back hey all right now we're on to
something I got this whole part here
dark okay this this part is filled out
no
psych oh one part is filled out wait how
do do you I I can't see the pattern
honestly okay you can't ruin something
that isn't even close to solve sa that
says the Kia people that's true okay
that's good wait wait hold on hold on
hold on hold on hold on hold on it's
she's cooking it's getting
there I think that the way we need to
end it is yeah just one unlit one in the
in the corner
ajacent oh man
huh oh
[Music]
whoops I can't go much higher than that
strange
CU maybe work both sides to one side
just keep wrapping it around maybe if
you go from one side wrap all the way
around and solve it that way oh no the
one side that was full is no no no
longer
full I wonder if it was my fault for
touching the
cube forbidden Cube forbidden
Cube actually can I can I try it again
you guys can can you can you guys kill
time while I try to do this when are you
saying are you saying we weren't helpful
no no no no no no it's just that like
you know like I like I like no no no no
like I like solving puzzles no no I like
solving puzzles just you know like I
don't know if you guys like solving
puzzles so wa I think I'm starting to
figure it out wait oh really
okay never mind that was weird let me
know if you want help I feel like I
might ruin it though no you're not
ruining it
like she's she's seeing the way yeah I
know she is over watching over us
overwatching us oh
yeah okay what if we just stay on the
same side and work together on it why
does that sound like a game name no no
no that's
crazy oh
[Music]
wait yeah if you think it's wrong you
can always switch it back yeah
thankfully that part is good that's what
I'm
trying I think I'm started I think I'm
cooking guys oh yeah oh okay
okay
oh
sorry I'm hearing news that the other
team used to quote unquote bug It Out by
spamming lights oh my bued it out yeah I
think we should maybe avoid doing that
I'm getting I'm I'm cooking I'm
cooking she's
nice I'm cooking yeah just toggles a
plus shape is what it does yeah it's a
plus
shape yeah oh I'm cooking I'm cooking
I'm cooking I'm actually cook yeah she's
doing it she's doing it yeah
y Iris the genius I'm a genius genius
genius I was I was doubting I was
doubting whether I was a genius or not
but now I remember I am a genius
remember that you're so smart you must
have been really smart in your past life
I know yeah I must have been absolute
like like I must have won the Noble
Prize whatever that
is what's a Noble Prize I don't know but
it must be something special if I
remember the word you win it if you're
noble yeah cuz I mean know must get it
soon too I mean I think you need to be
you need to be smart and Noble and I
don't know if you have both well you
only have one of those at the moment
what you're saying I'm not
Noble oh wait no you are noble oh you're
wait the puzle
huh
the heyy this way this way this way see
the skull in there this Hot Topic in
there wait I don't know what Hot Topic
is oh wow wow that's so
cool Hello Father I can't eat maybe not
my dad but that guy I want to be friends
with him
oh hey wait why would you do that what's
what's wrong with your dad why would you
do that not my dad I don't know I just
got a weird Instinct
angry I just had a weird Instinct that's
all oh boy oh we're stuck here oh no
we're waiting I'm waiting for may have
died oh oh
hello hey uh huh this is the checkpoint
from before Oh
Oh wa what is this place it's a mushroom
we fell down do we eat it wait don't eat
every every strange mushroom that you
see oit Bone Heads can I eat it no I
can't pick up the bone can I cut it oh
he he
revives yeah that is one
very very persistent skirlington am I
supposed to feed the mushroom H him or
something no wonder huh hey hey back off
boneman oh no your place oh you're
supposed to kill him okay okay okay
wait kill him around kill him here yeah
bone meal will drop and make the tree
grow yeah it all makes sense yeah yeah
yeah the Tre this way this way you
fiend he is only
father yeah for our big
tree
yay is it done now I don't know it looks
done so tall are we supposed to climb it
all the way up
maybe I think we should let it grow a
little more yeah we probably need to
grow a little bit more you killed it in
a weird spot I'm sorry my
help come here come here from hither
[Music]
up here up here up here up here come
here come here there we go you think it
work I think that's it I think that's it
I think we can climb it now I'm almost
can you make that jump do you think no
we can climb the vines oh the vines ow
I'm bad at climbing vines how does one
do that do you hold space yeah you hold
space you jump and hold I'm going to die
I'm going to die hold on a sec let me
kill this guy
don't SP what what someone something
just hit me okay now heal yes go up the
vine first so much for a noble Warrior
all right up I
climb here we go
here
oh this is interesting I've never had to
do something like this
before yeah first time for
a less underworld inrig first time for
ah first time for ah under that was
never one for climbing trees I don't
think it's not very
familiar a not bad though
nice we can make it
work no wonder did we go here maybe and
then up here and
then this tree is hard to climb yeah I
don't really know where to go to next
I'm having a hard time yeah figuring out
oh maybe
here did you find the way oh yeah I
think I found the way too here here this
way there are two mushrooms we got to
kill the skeletons really we still got
to kill skeletons here wait wait here
here Callie Cy come here here I I think
oh I have to reclimb the tree don't wor
it's fun don't don't climb it all the
way to the top oh yeah there there are
two mushrooms here oh
oh just not much of a clim you see you
see where I am I'm so bad at jumping
this way uh let's see one moment let me
see where you
are hang on control maybe I should work
on the quests well this is why this is
why the Minecraft like those Minecraft
me you know I have no idea sorry I don't
know what I'm talking about I must be
crazy um I did it I did it um let's see
where crony
is I'm
attacking oh I see you oh yeah you did
it they're ahead of me before I Know It
wait yay wow you're so quick what a a
gamer thank you was that about you not
being a
gamer oh I am quite a bit of a gamer Oh
wrong oh it work I think royalty should
not be playing games true we should be
taking care of you your h no no there's
a royalty that plays games no you
shouldn't have time you should you
should be spending all your time making
the citizens lives easier that's what
your job is right as royalty well like
I'm not royalty yet but I will be well
so that means you're only playing games
while you're still not royalty and once
you become royalty you'll be you'll be
um a slave to all of the citizens you'll
be a slave to the citizens what yes
that's a very negative way to look at it
well there's some truth I don't think
you're ready for for becoming a slave to
the
citizens a slave excuse me I think we
can climb this now or do we have to
connect the trees like why else are
there too connect the trees yeah they're
still they're still spawning okay come
here come here come here they probably
continue to spawn regardless though even
if the tree isn't complete do don't you
think maybe but like why are there two
trees yeah I'm also curious about that
hey hey hey don't follow
me back away back up back up back up
back up
wait okay I think we can climb it now is
it
climbable I think we still need to do
one
more oh boy everybody's getting slamed
bying oh
dear can you can you can you kill that
thing this way this way can you kill can
you kill can you kill skon kill can I
kill oh I can kill K yes don't
spam okay one more hit one more hit one
more hit probably there we go there we
go nice good job nice nice nice oh
there's there's there's
Vines I'm going to climb the right
side cuz why not yeah uh-oh maybe I'll
climb these this seems right this goes
quite a ways
up oh maybe this isn't the
way oh hey
going it's got to be right probably this
way probably this way lot a plat go this
way maybe that's how I got so good at
jumping jump oh you like platforming too
I like platforming she might be a jump
King what what could that ever mean
that's what everyone was saying to me I
didn't get it but now I think I do oh my
God I almost
died being in the ah me too if being in
the Underworld with re Ires this much
jumping perhaps that is why oh I'm
looking up your you're looking up at
what C nothing at your cape it's very
beautiful thank you thank you you guys
looking up she's looking up her cap it
was she you know her life is looking up
that's what that's what's looking up oh
I see yeah oh God I'm so
embarrassed
wait okay okay okay
no fall oh what are you talking about
I'm here already oh you you know you
think I was going to fall while I'm here
first you checks I was an overachiever I
uh climbed way too high well you know I
mean you did say you were a gamer but
you become you're going to become
royalty so you don't need those gamer
skills anyways you're going to be a
slave to the citizens okay okay than
that's the word on the street what does
that mean to the Dennison of the
Underworld the light emanated by Souls
was vital
they needed it to survive in this ever
cold and dark environment yet among them
there was a heretic who called their
Customs into question do we really need
to take others lives to sustain our own
no there has to be another way and so
she stepped yeah I know right into the
plane
above oh what a dummy why would you
leave all these people down here to
suffer and die she was selfishly what a
heretic it's this way okay I'd never do
something go personally know I believe
ow
yeah oh we did it the power of
Revelation has grown stronger yay level
up maybe did we get the treasure of this
place and now we sneak again guys we
love
sneaking a portion of your memories you
recovered a portion of your
memories ooh nice a memory what kind of
memory am I going to remember how to
spell things now
oh hopefully hopefully click here to
watch video
oh oh
what click here to watch video is it a
oh is this I got it are you sure you
want to open the following
website this is where we
um can we watch it will it will it
automatically play or do we have to play
oh you have to open chat press ke
shall we take a
look wait is this is this okay to show
on Screen Pro probably right or should
we
just cuz I security warning wait wait
let me double check don't do it it
steals your security your social
security number there's a download
available so we can we can play it
ourselves you know oh I think it is okay
to play it we can yeah we can play it
but the only thing is I think
all right I think I'm just going to use
the one that the other one I will show
you guys a portion of my memories I will
show yes we will share the portion of
the memories that has
unlocked yes yeah all right let me let
me just uh should we should we mute yes
sure let's how Sil how do we mute again
uh press
V and then mute V mute okay
here we go chat I mean the voices in my
head Oh wrong one uh voices in my
[Music]
head a Reaper's job is to end people's
lives and take their souls oh wow that's
how it's always been isn't that
beautiful P the spirits of the
underworld need their sustenance what is
she doing
is she sacrificing Soul
B that's funny wait wait can can I
replay this
again wait a sec sorry sorry chat um I
just realized you guys could hear it but
I couldn't hear it so I had no idea what
was going on wait um
properties audio properties
okay like
[Music]
this a Reaper's job is to end people's
lives and take their
souls that's how it's always been the
spirits of the underworld need their
[Music]
sustenance but I keep
wondering she sounds like her
what the
hell is she evil she's throwing away all
these innocent lives this the right
thing to
do no it's
not she's feeding the
monster oh no she
died oh now she's at a
[Applause]
party that doesn't seem what's going on
[Music]
look at
that what is going on turn out we can
also use people's
emotions saw you don't need their souls
at all I was the one oh so she she no
longer everybody returned to the duty
they won't want to be friends Reapers
should help the
living not take away their future if the
others can't accept that I was the herir
L It's All Coming Back to Me Now that's
why I got Mo I got to go I got to run oh
okay so she turned good things my way
they all see the same memory is me I see
wait what if they saw their own memories
though I see okay okay okay we were in
the
Underworld I got to go I have I have
watched I have watched a TI a peek of
your memory um Kia Mori me are you sure
that was me though yeah you were doing
very evil things things but it's okay
you seemed to have learned that it was
evil and decided to do good now so All
Is Forgiven wait so you don't care that
I betrayed all my underw fellow
underworld Ians no you did it for the
for the good for the good cuz I mean
look at your dad dropped us all down
down a hole you know that that's not
good Parenthood oh you know sorry I'm
sorry
yeah yeah I'm not sorry I'm not sorry
then yeah do do you guys forgive me of
of course of course you were we we we
went through this dungeon together we
are a nakama whatever that word means
nak nakama nak are you sure Hakuna
Matata Matana Hakuna Matata Hakuna mat
what does that me how do we know that it
mean Matata Hakuna means was it was it
family Matata
that that is not an
explanation my oh well I guess it's okay
then everybody seems to be in good
spirits so we have done an amazing job
perhaps I'm in the clear well if that
was my past it is what it is it is what
it is it's I'm glad I end up being the
past don't matter all that matters is
the present and the future I feel like
the underworld Ians definitely don't
like me
though beautiful who are are you a
beautiful Raven lady oh you have such a
long
spear wow than you for noticing such a
beautiful spear oh I just realized guys
my My Little My star thingies are shiny
do you can you see the shine no are they
no I I see they're kind of sparkly
they're sparkling they're sparkling on
my screen too ooh Why pretty is it cuz
we went through a dungeon I think so
maybe
wait I don't I don't see any other
reason Cy yeah pull out pull out your
weapon my oh hey mine Sparling
too I can't see it cuz I haven't done
the dungeon yet you want to do the
dungeon yes I can uh we're going to me
me and beu and and those two mysterious
looking dogs are going to do it in about
30 minutes together have fun that sounds
like a fun time whatever you see in
there though you know take it with a
grain of salt yeah is all I'm saying oh
okay let's just say it's a lot of
jumping yeah there's a lot of jumping
and also it's apparently my home so I
hope that you guys enjoy your time there
I guess I'm sure we will it it was a
really nice scenery yeah I'll take care
of the dogs too they are also of the
Jade sword so I have a lot of respect
for them
yes I wonder if that means nice seeing
you l
Revelation Revelation wao can you do a
beam yeah I'm a beam Blaster I'm
stronger than Goku whoever Goku is
what's Goku I don't know Goku it's oh
I'm going to experiment on this chicken
Revelation oh did it really deserve I
saw Stu going on behind your head when
you did Revelation what was that I don't
know I think you your head just exploded
when you did a revelation what was that
oh dang okay I guess you're using brain
do you use brain cells every single time
you re you
revelate Revelation oh wow my mind is
K's Revelation looks kind of cool scy
wait why I Miss's Revelation looked kind
of cool not going to lie yeah it just
needs time to warm back up but yeah my
Scythe of death and destruction I will
use it as a sword for
peace I'm waiting for my Revelation to
wait
ooh hey why don't you revelate again
please revelate for
me what no I mean why why is it all in
caps ah what if she wants to hurt me you
guys are a lot Kinder I
think your memories it's okay so that
that one's really aggressive I feel
though the orange the GG One the good
game one she's really aggressive no no
no Jonathan is part of the Cerulean cup
and we are all very full of empathy yeah
that's why we're in the Cilan cup cuz
we're full of empathy and kindness and
we think about peace of the world wow
great job guys hey we saw your memories
yeah how interesting I do but did you
guys just clear or did you guys did
something else after it's a little
embarrassing no everybody seeing my we
CIT and we were just like waiting and we
just having you know just having fun in
that we take that long we were did we
take that long yeah you
oh yes we we oh yeah we we finished wait
3 hours ago
even what let's go turn the quest time
flies you know oh yeah we could turn in
the quest yeah did you guys notice that
your Revelations are sparkly now after
the after the dungeon they
sparkle oh we're too far they can't hear
guess it wasn't a bad memory they
sparkle now Sparkle yeah they do check
it out later on they're so shy
right
cool we're out now where do we get this
my horse is
amazing
hey my horse is better than your
horse's my reason for that my horse why
am I always trying my horse my horse my
horse my horse is better hey that's a
nice tune yeah I know right oh
yeah oh yeah should we rejoin the big
call now maybe oh yeah wait is there a
big
call wait how do we join the big call
the private call wait party
call I think Kelly hasn't realized that
it doesn't change because our party is
only three
people where's the big call
[Music]
wait it's suddenly so quiet oh yeah I
think it's because I I turned down the
bjam
wait there we
go let me just go talk to theud weaken
the power of Revelation AIT at only a
fraction of its potential
that your summoning and the discovery of
these ruins should con coincide so
closely there must be some connection
between the ruins in the power of
Revelation I see I see Brave hero seek
rubius The Guild Master at least I don't
have to read any of this anymore his
Guild has also been searching for
strange ruins in the lands of lesto
mayhaps they have discovered something
she is transcribing for him yes thank
you thank you my throat is dead today
from all that stuff
the the Scarlet wand Guild
Master where would he rubius that's his
name mayhaps they have discovered
something Jade sword Guild Master speak
to the Scarlet okay Scarlet
Letter my horse my horse my horse my
horse my lovely lady horse
um I don't know this horse might be male
I'm sorry
um rubius
rubius I'm coming for you rubius oh oh
my God his hat is so
long his hat their hats are so
long oh Ruby Ruby's kind of cute not
going to
lie going to make
good day returned from investigating
those RS are you I've gotten the gist
from virus no nothing less nothing more
I now sense within you a of the power
big hats I love those I love these hats
they remind me of a certain Moon Queen
from ohing this from from a certain elen
game yes yeah with with lots of rings I
I think yeah I know what you're talking
about lots of my preciouses oh
investiga it's the power of Revelation
fascinating Most Fascinating one might
hypothesize that those ruins are the key
to unlocking your powers we of the
scared wand have also been investigating
near the Plains and wanted to know it
just off the coast we speak to Corin a
spine a spine El speak to Corin wherever
coron is where is coron travel to the
coast and Aid
in we go we go
forth I love how I have to like
basically stare at the map and not
really see what's going on around
me what a waste of shaders I don't know
what shaders even
means maybe it it just means I have
sunglasses on right now and I just don't
know it I'm sure that's what shaders
mean
right well hope you have a nice
stay are we are we talking about pizza
have a very good day t
g Pizza we're talking about my name
hello we're talking about her name can I
introduce
you her name is t gender Tam Gander your
last name is Gander your first name is
Tam she kept she kept saying ton tan
tender Pon see even she thinks that
we're talking about pizza no I don't
talk about pizza all the time oh I love
the pizza oh pepperoni pizza I thought
you to about pizza cuz I love the pizza
doing
[Music]
that you guys remember this language why
do you guys remember this language what
is this language actually what is this I
don't remember
anything this is the language of love
the language of love yeah that's
beautiful language of love yeah I
thought it was French that's love why
what's French what's French what is
French the only French that I I've heard
of is is the is the smooching French is
what I've heard of what what what is it
I don't know I actually don't know
anything else past that so oh wait
tender it was very fun not tender Gander
what dander oh hello tender you're
saying on purpose there's no way oh
you're saying this
on Hell calling me T tenders it's cuz
her name your name is tender you just
thought it was she's harassing me
because her I'm not harassing you're
harassing oh wait these are side quests
yeah okay coron of the Scarlet wand
where is scarl where's coron again um
right cck
I
coron I am
ready to see and
unleash re ow Revel
[Music]
Revelation
really it got stronger but I still can't
defeat this
thing
well I guess I just need to grind
harder don't you dare call it fart
magic don't you dare call it fart magic
it is so much better than that did you
see the the did you see the M the
memories the memories that we lost the
trailer memories yeah the trailer
memories that did not look like a fart
yeah it's like a fart oh shut
up okay I need to find this dude where's
this
dude over there
okay I do need to go soon my throat is
actually kind of dead for reasons
unknown unknown reasons
[Music]
where is this place
wait through
empathy actually don't know where wait
wait how do I get back how do I get back
to
the through
empathy oh where am ien hello please let
me in your
empathy oh I am not the leader I think
oh it is die I see the fair maiden of
dark pink dark pink hot pink of the
super hot pink she
says super hot pink she I am hot pink I
am let me just let me just you know
emphasize the hot yes hot pink hot super
pink yes hot pink yes yes
mhm we await right here the hot pink
Maiden has is waiting for you please the
hot pink Maiden you must join our party
once more thank you I know hot pink maen
is very popular mhm yes a stain I'll
protect you thank you thank you my oh my
God yes yes yo ena's weapon actually
looks kind of cool that's very cool this
this just a book you're actually spells
you're like a magician I'm just doing
ninja stuff
wait oh wait where's cro I guess crony
crony is too busy doing her her crony I
mean her Tam
stuff yeah no I mean t mean the Queen
the Queen the Queen the queen Tam Tam
[Music]
Tam
Tim you are under attack I'll save
you back
off they cry like a dog to make us feel
guilty she's looking for the Scarlet
leader isn't it somewhere around here
that's why I'm Al also here a Scarlet
leader is is back in town this is the oh
really back in town
uhhuh wait it's actually sparkling right
my hand right it's sparkling and the
inventory too oh my God you you have
knuckles I need to see your Revelation
can you re revelate for me can you
revelate
Revelation
y yo she's a punching quite cool
punching girl that's actually kind cool
how about you show was how about you
revelate for us yeah are you talking are
you telling me yes okay yes hot pink one
okay wait wait wait a sec let me let me
just get the Revelation um thing wait
wait here wait uh go let me get my goex
I mean not my goex I mean um what what
exra what what no no no no sorry no
nothing nothing okay I'm ready now I'm
ready to revelate okay reate okay
Revelation that is C
where did that go where does that go I
can't tell where that beam goes it went
to the ground I think whatever you're
aiming or your uh Vision wherever I I
imagine yes her yes where her aim is
true where her eyes aim exactly I aim at
my targets yes oh then re revelate for
me hopefully into the end revelate for
me Ena Ena I mean Nina all right Nina
okay
Revelation
ooh oh my god oh it's like a gun I
mean I mean I don't know what a gun is
what I have no idea what a gun is but it
must be something like
that words if I knew what a gun was I
would say it would kind of similar to
yeah something like that like a
gun man I love holding on to these two
stars this is
assassinate some people I can those I
can someone called me
Naruto what's a Naruto I don't know I
have no idea what they talking who's a
Naruto it's a what's a Nar what is
Naruto
cron who's
crony join our party T Oh yay yes man
imagine imagine having a girl named Tam
in our party right now man
it stands for the almighty right Tam is
great Tam is is Jonathan actually named
me so yes thought said for the almighty
the Azure Maiden yeah and then Tam said
it was too long so I said Tam is okay
too
yeah it's a good name your last name is
Gander right yeah Gander yeah when you
become Queen is your is your last name
going to change I'm going to assume
you're going I kind of want to keep my
last name though I don't know but you're
going to get married to the King right
so best yeah well I don't want to be
called like you know
T you're going to become Mrs
Leander Leal how would you
hyate you know I I want to I want to
keep my
name keep it yeah I'm just going to keep
it I'm just going to tell the king like
no I see besides like stole my
kill your exp whatever that is is mine
is mine is mine yeah yeah I'm level 10
now you you do you do hold for him right
Revelation yeah yeah it takes forever
for course oh okay
okay I see it's because of your re
Revelation Revelation Revelation
Revelation your Revelation I can't
really tell what your Revelation is uh
Tam
yeah I'm going
fast her Revelation is kind of cool yeah
that Revelation is cool right that
Revelation is awesome man oh I'm sorry
I'm sorry it's fine we're on the same
team yeah
[Music]
empathy no I keep getting scared when
Kingdom yeah it's for the kingdom you I
just realized for the kingdom your
kingdom I just realized I wasn't in the
ched again yes Tam isn't in the voice
chat either yeah Tam is too
slow it does sound like you need
dangerous dangerous monster from another
life are we going out on an
adventure wow the water is so beautiful
it is swim take a
swim
oh how do you get up
we got it we got it this is just a
little it's a it's it's just a little
splash splash in the
water hello hello we are dipping we are
dipping the water's cool I feel like I
remember your horse's name but it slips
my mind oh do you maybe from another
your horse another time what letter does
it start with an a yeah I think so I
think I feel like like there was a
strong connection between you and the
horse s yeah I just can't remember the
name Adam
oh sad get away from the queen all the
St she's
remembering she is remember she St she
did see her
memories I should get more raw meat all
right are you guys ready to go to the
coast this is where the coast to go to
the coast yes yes we do I think so yeah
hold on how do I remove
someone the magical tomb magical tomb
Quest we must complete before we might
be a get rid I cannot get rid of our
offline our I mean our disconnected um I
mean our sleeping member let's see our
sleeping member you mean our our
banished member right yes our B
member she seems to have disappeared I
know not
where let me reform our is odd yes we
must reform I must reform okay okay
sounds good take shape to a new
form yes I will
accept I
hear I'm just
reading yeah you got to open your mouth
when you speak crony what are you
sorry sorry okay no need for the Sass
spicy no it's okay I get spicy when I
make friends oh okay spicy spicy yeah
the spice must flow yeah oh I left all
my stuff in a different Barrel well
maybe I'll put it in this corner Barrel
too if I'm
[Laughter]
allowed yeah I always take the corner
Barrel breathe underwater we believe
this is no me rumor as the Guild Master
was able to find breathe under water
what does it mean I don't know we're
going to be able to breathe under water
just came into my mind yeah I think
we're going to be able to breathe under
water I think oh next is
Atlantis what what what's Atlantis I
have properly what tantis T tantis
tantis does have something to do with
Tam it starts with
tetis how where you come from Tam oh
were you originally from were a mermaid
Tim maybe that's that's why she's
marrying the king it's like a marriage
of different rumor countries different
species you
mean
species different species and countries
lestans and mermaids they are joining
together she's a mermaid can they
reproduce I'm sure they all right let's
go back to town guys if you talk think
about that if you talk to the uh the
thing go back to town okay okay okay
Coral shards huh is what we need where
do we get the coral shards it says to
gather them and then speak to the Guild
Master where do we get we need 10 yeah
where do we get the coral perhaps there
there are some Corals in the water
nearby I don't know should we go look
wait why why' we try to go town are you
are you leading us to them are you may
have to Leading us to the coral the
coral is thatly areal okay I think that
you guys didn't see where it was I see
Coral Sea I see Coral rainbow you see
are we colleting it uh oh yeah I got
four oh oh yeah these are rainow oh I'm
returning I'm
returning yo I can't tell if I have how
many I
have I I need Coral in the water easy
yes so delicious
Y at least it's not dead coral it's not
like the true the coral is still alive
and fresh which means that the sea is
very clean and
healthy say to is the one that where
there's no more Coral I need more Coral
not them they're so you can always go
back oh speak to the Guild
Master I make haste back towards Kingdom
me too let's go let us ride together yes
I don't know if it's just me but Ruby is
reminded of another hurry up another
person has thank you Tam who is joess in
another world what's your name
Pink huh hot pink hot pink yeah no wait
what's your name though you could call
me hot is it you're not
high wait a minute excuse me which
direction oh no you're excus us
farewell wait wait only
rubious speak to the Scarlet one is he
not the Scarlet one he is a Scarlet one
Guild no no no we have to go see Rubi
and he's in the vill maybe Iris the way
okay okay let's go then will guide my
way Iris will guide your way yeah she'll
guide my way
huh she has descended and she is not not
alone yeah literally okay crazy guys no
so many similar
songs please let me go
back yo you guys follow you guys
following I'm going I'm going to in a in
a minute oh I see it it's right over
there you see
it um there's a path right there's a
path need me to lead you here where are
you here I'm no no no there's no go
right ahead it's a it's a a Sandy path
right okay let's see and then Rus is
right over there here's rubius yeah yeah
yeah got it don't worry about
it
I I have a map
right are you guys
digging tunneling
a they're digging a
grave could be I think they're digging a
grave
heck yeah yeah I
think grave diggers
grave
you is block you're digging me yeah
feels like maybe I I am hot pain per if
we give enough time will open on it own
the PA will open on its own
eventually
today men yes what Fair the well Maiden
The Well right yes there the well
goodbye goodbye indeed goodbye lovely
lovely gorgeous
ladies oh I guess that's I will do a
magic chicken disappear
oh oh I didn't disappear right away oh
shoot I was I was planning on disappear
exelia he really silly Exel
Exel okay where's the
silly we go all right where where's
maybe I shall do something that calls my
name what calls your name it calls to me
a small blue
box a small blue box small blue box
we're not talking about the manga right
oh wait no no no what's a
manga what what is a manga is that how
you pronounce it I don't think that's
true I do not no I've never seen one
before you're right we would have know
how toon it manga small BL I have no
room I guess I I can get oh what did he
do rainbow Coral cluster an object only
red how do I use this waste B oh I know
we become
mermaids just like
Tam yeah just
like just like Tam she didn't need this
item to begin with like can we
farm
farm we can Farm yeah I think that's
what the shovel is for right like
growing things yeah gr cuz we can build
at our Guild base oh yeah oh yeah can
build a small Guild House yeah and then
have some some do some farming some
wheat so we can not have to pay gold to
make bread right can we can we make
bread we should do that we should make
our own economy who is
Gigi g we can have like a guilt chest
some is calling me Gigi I am Jonathan G
she's gathan I thought you were good
game gathan what what is good game I
drop the telepathic call even if it's
going to drop
[Music]
it Jonathan dropped the call why did
gathan do
that oh well
shame it's been fun though it has been
fun I hope we are cross I want our paths
to cross our paths will cross as long as
the Stars alive yeah I think so too well
goodbye goodbye goodbye oh goodbye a
goodbye
goodbye where are you off to
Tam Tammy Tam Tam huh hello excuse me
Tammy Tam Tam what what sounds like
you're making fun of me no no I'm just I
just wanted to say your name so so very
often because it's just so appealing you
know oh okay okay mhm well we got to go
check out the Ocean Temple dungeon
wherever that is I don't think it's even
open is it
open oh is it not open I thought I
thought the dungeon's open like daily or
something oh okay I don't know I I
that's what I thought but maybe
not oh maybe we should just go to where
the ocean Temple is and I think I might
go sleep sleep yeah I need to also go
sleep sleep I my body is extremely tired
me too cuz I don't know why but I think
I was having some upper day you know
this thing called yeah I don't know this
place called the gym the gym what did
you just Tor is that you tortured
yourself today is that what you did yeah
I think so I I think that's what I did
well I don't know why I did that yeah
what what happened are you an M are you
on a Mist what's an M I have no idea
that word just came up at the top of my
head but I don't know what it means w
that's weird I I never came up with that
kind of thing well I mean you know you
were torturing yourself and you enjoyed
it right so well you know oh well I
didn't know that there was a term for
that I mean I've heard I've I've heard
um the back of my mind is screaming to
me that apparently a gym is not even
free you have to pay money to torture
yourself oh oh I mean when to put it
like that that sounds really weird
right why why would I do that I don't
know I think I think you should become a
better person now that you forgot you
lost all your memories you know and stop
doing that to yourself maybe you're
right again that's weird oh hello hello
hello ladies hello ladies we got horses
you don't we got horses you don't I I oh
I guess you're just horsing around then
huh yeah oh oh no you're making the same
joke I did an hour
ago nay I disagree n my horse is my
horse is is a very onx Onyx colored
Steed look at how Majestic my my Steed
looks mine's a normal horse but I like
we is it just me or is ena's horse like
like a pony sure yeah try moving Ena
what why are you Mak my horse what is it
done to you what short oh there oh never
mind never mind never mind it was only
pretending to be a pony yeah Pony want
to be don't listen to them don't listen
to them you're not short at all oh is
that the name of your horse G you're a
wonderful horse yeah that's G I will
find my gem it was nice to see you fair
maidens all right goodbye take
care
exio all right well we're going to go to
the coast the coast The Sea Calls to
us the ocean the ocean wait where did
where did
fair for you oh hello hello hello you
have returned to a precious Rock I am
suddenly talking to so many people at
the same time wao you know someone was
looking for you yeah yes I am I am
looking for them a raven they're out
they're in the town you should go look
for them okay I will I will go onward
farewell
[Music]
beautiful be
youwell that's your name yeah that's her
name k hello Fair n n are the stars have
aligned over to the coast again oh can
we do that dungeon I don't think so but
we can maybe get ready to do it yeah get
ready sure sounds good to me I'll go all
right let us let us ride let us Ride
Ride Like the Wind Busey
running over we are fast and
furious I could use some carbonated
drinks right now carbonated I would love
some carbonated drinks carbonated love
do you love your carbonated love I do
indeed oo I I don't know what that means
but it must be something amazing oh wait
oh and we can cook I mean I can cook
investigate speak to the I can stained
meat actually yummy where is this ocean
Temple I think the Ocean Temple is
somewhere far out in the ocean and you
know we have this rainbow Coral cluster
so I think we can breath where where's
my rainbow chloral cluster oh yeah we
can yo I can breathe yeah let's
swim that's awesome to did you find your
Rainbow Coral
cluster it should be in your
inventory it's not was my inventory
full if you cleared the quest like the
they the rudus gives you one yeah but I
maybe my inventory was full oh no this
is a rainbow Coral Shard which was used
to make the thing hello ceran members
what is
happening a coral rainbow Coral uh
cluster is missing oh check my check my
magical book
ah there it is where where was it in
your was it in a was it it was in the
magical tomb of greatness oh okay thank
God for that thank God thank you yeah oh
I can breathe underwater now PR Under
the Sea Under the Sea Under the Sea
Under the Sea Under the Sea SE Under the
Sea Under the
Sea something tells
me I have to watch out for something
called a dmca the that I don't know but
it tells me be careful that sounds scary
DMC sounds absolutely scary I think I'm
going the wrong way oh is this it I
don't know this looks suspicious where
are you guys where have you off to I'm
wandering I'm trying to wander off to
the to the uh to the thing on the
map what's that that looks like
number okay we go down like there's a
thing on the map that we're aiming for
it's the dungeon I think the Red Dot on
the map that's on the DI no not rubius
not rubius um it's like I got right side
I think not left side left side left
side inside the
ocean I on my way yeah I think we're all
kind of split so no
worries don't tell me I can't get these
no I can't yo it looks so
beautiful wow so deep can I dig can I
dig let's try
dig
[Music]
wow W oh she's finally
joined I will find what do you mean
finally joined welcome back Tam Tam
doesn't want to join the calls I spoken
with some Mario Jonathan keeps dropping
the call so I I have to speak with Mario
Mario said that she's Queen and that
you're a liar who's Mario wait I had to
do this she is pink and she looks like a
cat okay okay I get it why she's called
Mario okay okay yes that is what she
called herself not Luigi but Mario okay
okay yes her name is Mario this she was
the one making fun of my
name made fun of your name she was
called you may not be able to get into
the mysterious place she kept calling me
Tam tenders for no reason T
tenders
tenders T tenders T
tenders why would
she what an evil she said that she
wanted to kill everyone oh wow that is
evil yeah that is pretty evil I bet
she's part of
ambercoin yeah Amin I bet she's part of
Amber coin oh no we can't get to under
we can't get to the dungeon there's a
invisible wall oh I see I feel like time
will solve the problem wao look there's
something called time this is Diamond
did I just go the wrong way I have a
strong enough pickaxe for
this I'm going to be rich oh no I'm at
the edge of the map gold I'm going to be
oops hi sorry
I'm oh I knew you were going to say that
precious dungeon is still
dormant oh is that what it says when you
try to enter yes it is
dormant see that can enter just
yet Perhaps tomorrow maybe we need some
sleep yeah maybe yeah I think it's about
time I need to I need to get some sleep
yeah I need my sleep get some Shi let's
meet again let us meet again us R when
time opens up a new gate towards the
next when the gate opens let us meet
again I will be waiting the ceran The
seruan Guild Masters will make us
assemble right the seruan assemble right
I will say a carrier pigeon letting you
guys know with my pigeon you're a love
you you have a lovely carrier pigeon by
the way thank you thank that's really
cool yes I will send a pigeon to your
inboxes and they will leave a note to
you we have inboxes you mean you mean
our mailboxes right
yes yes your your mail box is I will our
carrier
pigeon yes yes
M I will send
note be frighten thank you well have a
great one everyone take care take care
everyone
farewell tomorrow Goode and now
tomorrow I love you I love you tomorrow
marrow how do we all know this song very
weird I don't know do we come from the
same world that's crazy I hope not maybe
oh why
not why do you hope not I I
don't problems has her problem
no yes her name is C I named
her hey don't put it like that
hey I don't like I don't like the sound
of that I named her
EXC allowed me to a suggestion
[Music]
farewell all righty then um to the
voices inside my head the um what should
I call you the huses you guys were
screaming hrus in the beginning of the
Stream So you're the huses too my huses
um I will I will need to go now because
um my my vocal cords are dying from uh
from the the dark uh
um I'm so bad at saying medieval sort of
words
um from the dark powers that enveloped
me and kept me from from uh resting my
throat yes I will need to go into my
deep
Slumber and drink some hot tea whatever
tea is I have no idea what tea is but it
must be something I can drink I will see
you guys again um um very soon as for um
the super whatever what what are these
super chats I have no idea what these
super chats are but I I do have to
pretty much go I am pretty much dying
here so than but thank you very much for
them super chats um what what's going on
oh yeah okay we're good we're good I
will see you guys again soon thank
[Music]
you it was a lot of fun and also I'm
going to recover my memories just for
like a split second like give me like 10
seconds I'm going to something I'm going
to scream Revelation and I'm going to
have my memories back for just 10
seconds okay Revelation okay thank you
very much for thank you very much for
coming thank you very much for um the
for for San Japan for those who came and
for the meet and greets I'm super glad I
was able to you know participate and
even though I was I participated a
little bit later than everyone you know
it seemed like it worked out in the end
so I'm happy thank
you thank you very much all righty then
see you guys again okay um um D
Revelation oh no what the hell was it
saying in the past 10 20 seconds I have
no idea my memory just went blank for 20
seconds well I think it is time for me
to go now goodbye goodbye goodbye
R what am I saying that sounds that
sounds weird but but I can't stop saying
a
[Music]
goodus
byus uhhuh
like I'm back
home
F slowly it all begins to
fade I got no power left
today I don't know I don't know if
things would ever change I think I'll
just be stuck here
anyway those nights when your energy is
nowhere to be nowhere to be found do you
see the light or do feel like a oh it's
bottomless bom I'm trying to figure out
how to stay in this world and all of it
gravity when every day The Bu is grabing
me and it Le to thinking nobody hears
what they're said to me maybe I'm
maybe I'm not
[Music]
alone
I oh God literally like I was recording
stuff last night um I had had to had
some deadlines to meet last night so I
recorded that and then after that I oh
by the way my memories are back right
now
um and then after that I had I I went
over because um me and baa did a karaoke
panel so we had to meet up we had to
meet up at at Bay's
place I went I went up to B I went to
Bay's place to do the karaoke because
you know obviously there' be there'd be
time lag to do the karaoke
panel and then we had rehearsals at like
at like 12 uh 1:30 we had we had
rehearsals at 1:30 a.m. and then after
that we had the actual thing and like
rehearsal was like two Tech rehearsal
was like two hours and then after that
was like we started at 5 a.m. for the
panel ended at 600 and then and then I
went all the way back I went all the way
back
home and then I had a meeting with my
and then I had yeah I had it was a
pretty long meeting cuz I haven't had a
meeting with the mon town for like 2
weeks um and then after that I had my
meet and greets so literally I just had
pretty much no Str eye no pretty much
barely an attempt to rest let's go but
it was fun it was a very very very
action packed so yeah um my throat
actually
hurts but it was fun thank you very much
for coming see you guys again soon virus
bye
virus that's why I'm that's why I'm mean
a c do