m
[Music]
n o
you
[Music]
w
hello hello y I'm so
excited
yay
hello welcome good morning we are
ptsb yay we're
traumatized let's dump our traumas on
everybody know
yay well can I just say I'm so excited
this the first time I wanted to play
this game for a while but the first time
I'm playing it they have freaking
October Fest
F no it's October Fest yeah it's October
Fest it's going to rock your
world they have
pretzel and sausages and Leos that we
can get as items apparently oh what's L
hosen a leather pants thing oh oh
leather pants yeah like the brown
leather pants usually Brown
you know it's like the the uh opposite
for the dle oh my God how are we
dancing first one the twerk is a winner
you're forcing us to
Dance come on baby is this stream music
I don't know oh I turned on stream mode
so I I don't get copyrighted music well
we'll see how are you doing this there's
a streamer
mode my legs won't stop moving yeah in
option
dwarf press Escape but you I guess you
don't need it cuz you're not streaming
right I
know but it's cool
yeah is is there a TW how can you can
you change do that Arena Dance oh it
happens on its own I think you have you
like enter and leave the where's the
twerk there's no T they took it out for
October Fest why would they do that
that's
sick oh yeah oh
yeah they're right
though uh oh chat is is audio okay is it
balanced enough audio check AUD your
check check check oh we can order
around oh we can order a
beer Bal
okay oh it looks so cute
wait I
asked oh it gives one for everyone hey
drinks on me guys oh Le lover
special isn't that more like um
Patrick's Day theme do we do we compie
together or something yeah wait one get
your drink who is this get your drink
bro go get your drink what get your
drink fat butt move your fat butt over
there whoa wo wo wo get your drink
already come on calling me fat before
I've even had a drink what
the leaf lovers yeah it's
vegan okay all right let's drink this
smovie how do we drink this
[Music]
actually
cheers ch ch oh wow wait does
everybody's colors match m is this Kiara
with red no excuse me what the hell was
that oh I don't know what color I am is
there ow you look Canadian how did you
throw that you're camo and you look
Irish oh my god well well thank you you
got a
buttchin well ow you look evil who's
that oh that's am is that hi hi
yeah your chin is amazing
wait did I fix the audio am I more
audible
now audible audible audio
AUD
[Applause]
yeah oh cute you're still quiet audio is
fine I'm just going to turn everybody
else
down
cute can I change my outfit
somewhere yeah like the color of
it this is some Club Penguin Music
where's where's the hey man I mean I'm
fine with
this so oh
gooy and am oh God you two have played
the game before and me and crony are
beginners so goby please you know help
us out oh my God that twerk is insane
holy C Shake it's so hard the Earth is
shaking that's way better than my fite
work oh my God go driller go driller go
drill you hear the clap of
your oh my God Clap the butt
cheeks okay are we going to go to a
mission I can set up a mission wait
there's a
wardrobe we going inside here let's do
this way this way oh okay oh is it
locked it shouldn't be is it
wait oh
God let 's a
lot okay so apparently there's October
Fest rocktober Fest missions so we could
do those
right um actually we have to do I think
all of us are still pretty early in the
game so we have to do like con unlocked
okay that's
cones we should do that we'll unlock it
is what this is sausage doing the wait
which one is it hold on it's been a
while since I played on a
fresh
Noob we're in a
noob croni got so lost during the
tutorial I had to lead her through she
got lost a million times in the tutorial
can you guys imagine hey hey that's not
because I'm not good at gays that's
because I'm directionally challenged
there a different I'm directionally
challenged too and I made it pro pretty
easily that means you're
better wait am I being
is my audio actually that uh messed up
on my side sorry guys you can add a
filter to your microphone that had
SK then but I haven't touched anything
your audio is fine okay yeah your audio
is fine um through Discord at least so
it might be
yeah and does it does it look an OBS
does it look like it's in the yellow or
yeah no it's it's maybe a touch quiet
but jum buds want to have your ears or
your voice like really deep inside their
brain want ears
too no I keep them shs even have ears
you got one guide I got one guide yeah I
think they have holes in their head they
feel vibration I think
oh
um I wonder if we unlock it for
on my and I if it will unlock for you
guys as well I don't think we hopefully
we'll just do this one then because I
think oh man I have to do this one
who whoa we do level one because we have
new
players yes please I've only done the
tutorial so far which was already so
much
fun I like this
game oh God wait uh
October which assignment do you guys
have if you go to the the Assignment
Board
um what is that objective conquer
haes is that your objective yeah seems
like it is it boes for it's selected I
guess selected and active and it looks
like that's the only one I can do
because the others are gray out so
okay okay so yeah we should be good then
I will be this going with that so we can
clear
it we'll start with a level one low risk
yeah a low reward but that's
fine y y collect 10
fossils get get in the get in the get
robot get in the robot slap the dice
slap the dice that's really not much
time what happens if we don't get in
though what happens you leave you behind
oh behind
this gives me lethal company Vibes but
like way
better lethal company's good though I
didn't realize how in-depth that game is
really yeah they have a lot of new
updates too they're like pumping out
updates like crazy yeah there's like a
game a truck game is yeah there's a game
yeah no no there a
truck
I sorry yeah there's a game it's amazing
smelly hold on
what is that what is
that someone's playing
pyro why ises it
hurt oh is are you playing
pyro yeah kind of I guess let's go oh
wait I call see that there's like
a wait why does it hurt so much do we
have to like shoot these mushrooms
it's the smoke that it's giving off yeah
don't go too deep into the
smoke it's show like audio master volume
I'll turn it down oh yeah guys is the
game audio okay or do you want it louder
do you just jump down he I guess zip
line yeah one of us may could create a
zip line I I guess I does my character
yeah I think my character know one more
time and then I'm not touching it for
the rest of the stream okay it's done
okay I haven't played this in a long
time I'm your scout I am
oh
umer don't want to make it too loud uh
did you jump down I'm going jump down
does it not hurt when you fall from the
sky like an angel you died you died yeah
but she resurrected me how do how do you
throw a zipline again what's the button
for it how do I use oh my God I haven't
played this in a
while wait where are we
drilling is it up there do I have to go
back up up what the
hell is it three I made a zip line we
can now use it yeah I think we got to go
to this middle level no oh why you going
that way how do you ping
again ping control and then excuse me
yeah yeah do you want a zip line
Amy oh no you that's is that Amy I'm
here okay good okay all right boys let's
dig dig
yay is there uh uh can you damage uh
your partners is there friendly fire no
okay too
bad oh what yum what are you putting
down there that is C4 what what the
heck occasion what are you using before
wait is is there friendly hold on is
this gr I think you guys there there is
there's friend of oh my God in order to
hack this game you have to play Flappy
Bird I'm killing myself
what you have to play Flappy Bird to
hack this
what really open the box
grony that's fun what is it I don't know
boots boots upgrade let's go so now oh
everyone can get it like a jump wait
hold on everyone can get
it w jetpack get it did we already have
that before was that the boots we love
Jetty
boot oh these are Health Stones what are
we doing salvaging you guys your boots
yeah boots crony the red stones if you
get them they give you
health oh I have found that out
now if you see a fossil grab it big
animal crossing fossil are they usually
out in the open or is it more
like uh why are you choosing to walk
through
it Oh I thought you had to I didn't know
no like we had jet packs don't hurt
yourself they're on the walls okay so
are they out in the open on the walls
they're like blue swirlies blue swirlies
okay loot Bo oh my
die yay loot whoa what is this how do
get down is that our spaceship
here wait I'll make another zip line
up
Yi oh I found oh there's a big spider oh
my God wait I want
to I if I can reach this wait that's not
very good what is that feeling what is
that feeling
ah I
died you died by
accident thank
you aesome sweet of
you
course ow
ow sorry did I hurt you guys you
probably friendly fire in this game
apparently not yes didn't you say no
before yes wait let's test
ow does that
hurt not really where's the other
battery beep beep
beep big boy going down those
crustations terrain scanner just got
updated with a new location
cool where'd everyone go um I'm looking
for another battery that's going
beep beep thought I saw a
fossil oh oh right my shoes I forgot
about the shoes I see a fossil beep get
it
what's this beeping box I got it it's a
it's a where are you I want to see an
animal crossing fossil where did I put
it oh I see it oh animal crossing fossil
what was that I died can someone revive
me please yeah a thank you is that Amit
hello thank
you I don't know where it is oh my God
I got
for
nice I feel like I need to be um taught
what all these deadly things are because
it keeps on killing me I mean if it's
attacking you then shoot
it is it
there who I'll kill
him why which one the screaming thing
it's gone there's so many
nice oh you can shoot while I'm flying
sick oh wait what what is this is it
pink on the map feel like I need a
better my fov is like super I'm dead
again I'm
so thank you this this supposed to be a
easy this is overwhelming there's a lot
of happening yeah it's uh it's very
cool need healing where's our
healer we have no healer what the heck
there's healers the best
no fossil get
hoay there's so many fossils
actually look my di
[Laughter]
again I I overestimate how long the
shoes keep me flying I'm sorry hold on
I'll come with you soon I'm so sorry I
got I got it I got it she got
it I'm a phoenix I got to die
sometimes I want that though
it's
it's Danger dice skin for the driller
there's a skin up
here skin Oh I F like real skin Oh I
left my skin up here for
you e is it for everybody again my skin
suit
my uh okay so yeah we want to collect
those fossils and then we want to
salvage mules which look like our mule
here Molly but they're tiny and green
oh okay is it like meals that other
people abandoned it's these things here
they're blinking and glowing and you got
say here what
exactly I think on your map they show up
as pink yeah if you hit if you hold tab
you get a map and there's pink things
all over the map
oh okay okay
okay
um no ammo oh my God this is what a
crummy level one this is why what do we
do with all these
legs got to put them together how do I
get ammo again how can I pick them up
this Nitra is what we use
to buy more ammo so if you see it mine
it the red stuff the red buy as in later
when we're back or now immed oh you you
buy it now if we need
it okay okay you guys have to dig up the
legs and then attach it to
the thing I'm so lost I should stay with
someone who is that that red is crony
what are you digging
up it's one of the little mules
okay good to know and then you build a
little mule and then you make
it yeah
die is
cool I like shooting things where's the
other mule there's one
here where is here I think oh I see it
is this a
thing no what is this I think she
already did this oh
okay
okay Bing Bing
being the the like when I even when I
don't look at the map I see something
that says mini mu that somebody like
Mark that or
okay oh I think I think that should be
the fixed one I missed there's no
way burn it with fire yeah do they
really spawn on level ones what the heck
yeah this feels quite the difficult one
compared to the
tutorial heck yeah to level
up I I I fixed the other
one nice let's
go okay done the is again we just need
more more of
the fossils okay I got
fossils just take
oh thank you so many zip
lines yeah shouldn't have made so many
the maybe not those no I think it's good
you get to like like but now I can't
make no
more oh can I pack him up and like take
them
back one more F who's got
it fle oh I saw one before but I
couldn't reach
it collect Nitro call supply drops Nitra
is that Nitra it's hard to reach if you
need more ammo we might have enough
Nitra you call in uh drop uh how would I
call them I believe
it's is it five
five whoopsie five five is it five how
do you call it yeah it is five five will
call in oh that's where I place it
okay
coming is on the way
H okay
resupply is on the way is crony dead I
am dead I'll heal you if I can
y y here Phoenix better for
you
yippe oh yeah right we can run I just
called myself a fat boy
why I don't see any fossils anywhere
okay you guys can get supplies too
there's like
several
okay hunt for the last fossil who's
going to find
it find now I'm motivated need to find
it where's the whoever finds it gets a
friiz from you or from the
game from the game m
M you're just giving someone else
the the honor yeah
no I'm looking for it to Mission
Control you guys for that stupid
bugs when there's something you want to
get and there's no way to like stand
next to it to mine it is there any way
to create platforms with a different
class or so
you use your might be able to maybe
depending on what build you have well
now I can't find anymore what I saw
before Engineers can yeah what Engineers
can work oh I have to deposit the fossil
that I found oh then we might have them
already oh sick what I thought it went
up like
automatically wait where did the drop
pod go is that the drop pod I forgot
what it looks like how do you Uplink I
[Music]
forget okay we're done
time y
Yi we have to up link to Mission Control
what does that mean this is green box I
don't remember how to do it it's been
Supply you have to push the button
yeah the drw
[Music]
Callin oh oh that's what that was oh
yeah yeah yeah the
button thanks for the r
o
okay on the follow the
mules yeah let's go mules that's so nice
of them to guide us ah now we do it get
come beat this box up connection between
the and the space Chad is the game guide
yeah I just need a quick refresher so I
can help
everybody this is too much for
me what's happening right now are we
just waiting for the spaceship to do it
thing triang ini not triang if you stay
in the circle ccle it'll go faster
there's a circle over here where are you
come to the up link we just got to kind
of like
ah I didn't see
that
okay DOD
everybody's my fire hurt you guys yes
not
sure I'm
fine
triang how do I install okay never mind
blink we're up blinking me up
blink let every be
die
easy bring us some bigger
mobs need no I get ammo again ammo is
like that
way it's over here oh God I
miss you missed than you
what are you missing
with ow who shot me something shot me
too it's this thing in our BAS are you
dead Okay revive the
shark oh wait did I
resupply ah it's so stinky here Goa when
I revived you why did it make the stink
you
Cloud what I'm
sorry it's a b I
swear well when you die I'm sure a lot
of things come out of your body right so
yes and what no
[Music]
shame oh there's an ammo pot here too
oh refuel the drop on oh yeah we we're
done with the oh wait sorry ref the drop
pod is this not what we do this part
incoming
do we how do we do
ah we smack connect it g drop pod we got
to connect
it connect the
thingy
ah there should be a green hole on the
right
here y this way yum
this way no double
yeah put it in the drop pod's belly
button drop we're connecting the
umbilical
cord yeah I'm stuck put it in where's
the belly button oh that's the belly
button One Way Tobe put it in the drop
pod how to refuel
how how do you get fuel oh you just put
the cable in there oh how did you do
that put the cable in the hole and then
you smack the
Box okay this is something I can
do
yay beautiful
Char work Makes the Dream Work stay CL I
like how Mission Control always tells us
what to do but nobody ever listens to
Mission controll I'm trying to but I
don't even understand what he's saying
cuz he's
British okay Green Man
all that's a lot of enemies
oo enemy
spam more oh
owie ooh
thanky protect
attack plus you can you can Trash Talk
Mission Control cuz's he's all talk
he'll never come down and actually
discipline so feel free you sound
experienced yeah
control maybe you shoting trash talk
people who can talk Sor I don't know
what it was mission control can talk
back he just doesn't actually uh commit
to the
discipline oh more coming from West
ow boom
[Music]
boom are we doing good
Chad wa what was that explosion game
music my thing that was me
Oh I thought that was mine no that was
my my uh detonated was
C4 oh I guess we did it at the same
time I set a trap for them just a little
bit of
C4 w't too bad we're almost
done oh my
God how we looking how we cooking the
good
out hold your ground okay wow they're
stalling so much
man thanks for nothing
MC do we have to stay around the the
green uh bubble thing I think so go
wherever you guys stay alive for a
minute who who who
powering Dr
ping the Dr
P who wo all those
proteins
love they're like
everywhere so easy to miss them when
they attack you from behind ow
what I'm out of ammo again I'm going to
get some
ammo got to refuel yes
yes 12 seconds 10 seconds stay
alive oop oh
sorry oh
okay you look so chunky makes me want to
shoot
you sorry good Target pretty chalky
aren't we
all is this the drop do we just get in
here
ow
[Music]
wait no ah this is a drop guys you can
come around to the front oh okay we can
get out of here mission complete oh
easy
y our first mission complet
[Applause]
Yahoo round that was so easy rock
forever Rock
Stone over so that's where it came from
rock and stone rock
stone is there like an option for the
fov I feel like it's so zoomed in I I
think there might
be who in your sh I mean if it's first
person they should oh what does this
mean is this good I had the most kills
ooh oh biggest gun
too wait maybe not that might have been
too many
stats you had the flamethrower so you
had the hottest gun for sure yeah so is
is pyro The Meta in this game at least
oh my
God what's the meta in this
game I'm traumatized using Pyro from TF2
I have drill fist okay I'm not just a
pyro to me you're just just a pyro
pyro he this slander no it's cool to be
pyro at least I thought so until I
played T is the
truth no yes right okay is everybody
safely back
yeah Mission uh is your assignment board
moving Kiara cron moving as an
assignment board
um it looks like it's still the same I
think yeah okay well uh what does this
mean did we not do
it we definitely free requisites or
conquer Hawk's for and then spec
ops uh you will have to do the more
drial
sabotage they have to do the mining
Mission yeah it's just cuz like our
our early in the gamess is staggered so
Amelia and I are also like not fully out
of the game a a beginning
game
[Music]
oh I was wondering if if I push and us
through the rest of the Hawkes thing
maybe then we can do the grade out
missions for you guys anything's fine
for for me I just have a hard time
understanding what's going
[Music]
on uh they're saying you and crony could
catch up to amam if we're on the same
Quest still I think we are we have to be
we only did the
tutorial yeah we have the same
assignment do their missions first it
won't skip you ahead oh God okay all
right's okay we'll start with this one
tell goba to Choose Your Mission choose
my miss doing it doing it
Yi all right it'll be so refreshing cuz
it's going to be easier than the other
thing right I would hope so I would hope
it should
be 200 more kites 12 gun
[Music]
seats oh my
God I hate time pressure customize in
this game that's
awesome how come I can't sit am I'm too
big more K our butts are too big yeah
your butt is too big yeah your your your
your face is too big your Beard's too
long M your on it o Pew there's no thing
such as but too big I wasn't the one who
was
stinking does my odor offend
you yeah it's offensive to the world you
should
apologize everyone one man's stinky
beard is another man's uh bouquet of
erotic roses exotic roses erotic anyway
anyway
anyway species would
know let's go all I light it
up oh this is
pretty yeah what are we doing
morite was the was that the the black
Stones oh
man Rock boots shiny green it was green
okay is oh wait I got this we got this
this
right figured out the cheese
platform Gunk Gunk seeds e yeah they're
hanging in the ceiling I made a I made a
platform I made the zip line to the
other direction if you okay that would
be a lot better
oh oh I see a lot of Gunk on the walls
is that dirt yeah that's dirt I will get
the gunk seeds at the top of the map oh
that's Gunk seeds they're gray and they
hangy down and they wible oh doll how
you going to get dos like with my gra oh
you shoot them yeah oh you just right
that's so simple I didn't think of
wait a
second what's this wait a
minute I guess do we want to go through
here
probably you laughing at oh taking all
your stuff taking all my
kills n took all your mining stuff my my
someone take this SE yeah toss it down
here well down
here give me your Gunk seed is this the
right direction give me your I'll drop
it
right here I I can't where are you I'm
down here oh throw it how do I throw it
me I opened up A New Path click click
girls can't find any more moride there
try the New Path I made oh
nice I'm sorry I wrong button wrong
button I'm sorry that
was together I'm sorry stop hating each
other I I wasn't hating I was just aot
potato with a grenade I'm
[Music]
sorry uh I'm in I'm I'm I'm like uh
in different part of the map now but I
it looks like we eventually have to go
here I have a feeling so oh did you dig
through the oh you D yeah I dig through
the dirt where you were digging like
something else I don't know what were
digging uh let's go that way then follow
K yeah come over it feels right there's
a tunnel
here does everyone get a zip
line no right here around in what you
got to ride zipin yeah oh there it is
okay zipin are so
fun ow hey hey oh hello what the hell my
shield oh welcome
welcome hi are we Health here don't
worry we're missing
crony's going to gun me down I got to
keep moving I'm not going to gun you
down I just
like touch you are
un rock and stone rock and stone when I
think of unbreakable I have to think of
unbreakable kimy
Schmid do you guys know that
[Music]
show who's kimid it's cute like a I say
spin-off series but not really no it's
not a spinoff is it anime is the anime
there no anime girl kimid would have
been good as an anime
maybe yeah yeah cuz it's so
dorky what is Kimmy Schmid
that's yeah I'm I thought you were
saying
Aid what I was like
a
aim my bad I don't know I thought it was
anime
but if it's Kimmy Schmid that's so
that's so American yeah like a sitcom
name yeah is pretty much
sitcom I love my American sitcoms Kimmy
Schmid lives in
Suburban just like
Rano
Rihanna e something sounds
gpy is it gor
gorie e e is our is our little pod still
following us you can hit C and it'll put
down a a
marker
marker is this oh there's more okay
yeah well I want to give my gun seed to
some to the Pod
right I think you can call it over oh
yeah I'm calling
it's coming her name is
Molly Molly it's called mu a it's a cute
name
Molly stom stom stom Molly the
M don't give it a name we don't have the
boots anymore one of us probably for the
best it's not like us yeah it
is like mly can
carry excuse me
ah
[Music]
sorry what is this doing
here what direction did we come from I
lost directional
sense oh oh oh it's an
explosive did you get
hurt ohwi I heard a little bit of a
Tinus we can go this way there's more
dirt this
way compacted dirt oh there's a be mug
what do I do with this beer mug right I
was thinking too like what is that doing
there we must have not been the first
dwarves to come
here stand back step aside hold that I'm
oh uh I'm overheated one second
o yeast
cone
yeasty what wow so pretty get the beer
mug how do we pick it up I guess we have
to dig it up okay I'm going back for the
beer mug you know that some people can
make bread out
of out
of there it is that of what
do I have to put it into the mule okay
said bees I thought you said speaking of
bees bees can make
bread I bet you make bread out of honey
over
here found one well you know um you can
you can make bread out of yeast
infection Performance Point heard about
that
Tech I mean
I'm coming I heard it tastes a bit like
sourdough I think my brain is refusing
to process what you just said Sor what
what food are we talking about wor
melons naturally have yeast inside them
did you know that oh really yeah you
could probably make yeast bread with
that inside of a melon oh how do you
guys feel about the fact that if you
wanted to take over the the world you
could essentially just have like a a
brain control yeast because every human
probably has some type of like fungal
fungus inside of them and once you get a
funga fungus inside of you you pretty
much can't get rid of it so you can
really just like yeah sounds like a
little Fung
guy fun guy it's like the last of us but
in reality it's kind of scary to think
about oh yeah yeah lighting up
ow so how am I going to reach this I
need an engineer to make a little
platform oh
okay you know where I am but now it's
stinky
here where are you the fungus is the
true
way um like this one like here oh yeah
yeah oh uh not there but around the
corner but maybe it's not worth it maybe
I better go to different area although
they're all all these morat thingies are
up pretty
[Music]
high
Zine I can try and help oh Market the
city RL okay I will I will once I'm off
the zip line oh damn good sorry I take
over your no no how do she just jumps up
there and holds on to
it mining
guac
guacamole
guac me too me come
down it's hard to get up
there where did the mule go it's um it's
where Gooby bar
is what is a gooby
bar that's my
name excuse her that's her name now okay
she officially legally changed her name
to gooy Bar Gooby bar what kind of name
is Gooby bar no offense
wow I named her that oh I'm sorry it's
like a better better name why is there
battle music playing they got to raid
everybody no ammo I really did somebody
like already plays but by any chance
like one of those reloading thingies no
yet no no how do we do it again
Chad tell
me uh how do we resupply okay I'm I'm
putting it I I put it down
okay play chicken play
chicken guys what's the button to mine
stuff again uh right click you have to
hold it right oh hold the right I've
just been using my fist oh what
no cuz I have drill fist oh okay is is
that the
equivalent so
help watch out behind you
you light them up
whoops oh we have enough gun seats and
enough moreai let's go yeah now did it
yeah
yeah now it's enemy rush time again and
we can either do this or we can just go
home I wouldn't mind going home then we
go home mid raid let's
go okay now we follow abort Mission I'm
taking some of the ammo abort Mission
well abort abort yeah aborting but
successfully
wait we missed the pink
thing so we follow mu follow the MU are
you riding
it I was but for once you're too tall Go
diva to get through to some through
something too tall to
ride
oh it is not over yet be careful my
companions have you guys seen the SK
version of the
the version of what
Su
SK
SK has anybody seen it here no no I
haven't seen it we don't consume such
empty minded things I doubt it I doubt
that oh
I mean we we all consume like something
brainless one way or
another well in any I I will say the
only thing in that format I watch is
YouTube
shorts and perhaps on whatever's on
Twitter
well the crime documentary YouTube
shorts
basically brings me the best from
what you get over
there where's my Instagram real
Chad
yeah no
[Music]
Instagram yeah I don't even look at
Instagram
reals I mean my friend sends me that but
that's yeah when they send one my only
friend on
Instagram wait I feel like I have been
abandoned Watson what uh oh no I haven't
been using it in a while you freed
yourself kind of are these signs of
where to
go what do you use me I
use uh YouTube shorts I guess sometimes
Instagram and
then Twitter I guess mostly Twitter what
you the same as me you send you say all
the things except Tik Tok wrong way oh
sh yeah I don't use Tik Tok it's the
same pretty much okay
I feel like I'm all alone uh out in the
dark just follow the signs yeah I went
the wrong way first Al so you're
definitely not being timed so don't
worry don't look at the I see your timer
on my screen but it's okay we got enough
time um I see
youson that's me
wait almost there yes I'm here you're
100 you're 100 me away what happen if
she just make it sh left behind I'll
make it I'll make
it I'm I'm almost there I see a
zipline and trying to light the way for
you all right yeah did you guys put that
there or does the mule put that there
those signs automatic yeah M so nice of
them
Molly okay sorry I keep on forgetting
that its name is Molly yeah it's not
Molly it's just a mule oh my God no the
name is
Molly don't give it a name you'll get
attached to it we have to respect
things' names I would say people's names
but that's not a
people I have
arrived oh you were you waiting outside
for me
oh you can slap
people those the
dice slap my lucky
dice so was that the first mission that
me and crony had to
do I think so
oh I do believe hooray hooray
success wow look at us we're so
cool and everybody I wish I could trim
that beard to make it look nice I know
you can customize it later Watson's got
the the quad
chin
yeah it looks like something hanging hey
I got that beer mug
oh you did the multier
Y yummy oh now we moved on go we the
mission thing something moved there
unlock
nice okay we'll do the next oneg I'm
going to stand in front of the elevator
but I'll be right back like one minute
[Music]
okay let's hunt those eggs launch
reports in the
launch putting foreign objects in the
tube I I don't
know sa hey those pretzels
no what sausage flavored be I saw you do
it I don't do that you're just trying to
clean
right yeah I have a bit of
a Obsession so this is the official
trash can now I
see wait come come oh wait wait for
Watson we put a weenie in it
I think I'm going to eat sausages
today oh
yeah beer October Fest oh actually I've
never been to an October Fest for real
for real
but my October Fest happens at
home oh yeah a I just you know eat
sausages
alone well I don't drink beer but what
you like what is the what is the
celebration for um well because it's
October and um I don't know I guess it's
maybe like an Autumn Festival kind
of
okay for the Harvest oh yeah Harvest
Festival yeah maybe it's our kind of
Thanksgiving what we we don't grow
sausages oh thought you like Harvest
them
no wait no you would Harvest The Barley
that would make the beer yeah and I
guess the bread also I don't the
bretzel the bradel it all makes sense
yeah yeah yeah yeah oh Watson I put a
weenie in your beer come drink it oh
we're drinking again just for me yeah
yeah I put my wien over cute we should
turn on music
buping
yaying
CR yay your be wait since when can you
drink it with the beer that's drink it
with the I don't know wait since when oh
I
can I
can
yippe Oh
Come Oh cute
Oh
Come Oh he lik it sorry I got too
excited oh
yeah
yeah that's how diggers celebrate let's
go I want to dig some
more dig up some Stones rocking Stones
you're
flossing no
way my dance move is still boring better
Min wow my God what are you looking at
never even see we've never seen MC's
legs and he's that mean what are you
looking at why wa I'm just looking at
your face it's making me nervous oh what
we s we chose a mission oh
God I'm bringing my be mon I'm bringing
my beer
monk weenie beer souvenir time who who
launched the mission what are we doing
eggs eggs yipp collecting the eggs it's
like it's
Easter that's Easter eggs yay oler
[Music]
AER
AER exactly you get it said
cheese round is is this just a standard
Mission or a rocktober Fest Mission
these are these are two Mission we got
to get
to can't
it two of them H three of them a I'll
dig
up I got it suck nice maybe get up with
the I got it I got it
nit p
chees C where the the fossils you say
cheese K cheese
C
oh you know there's sausages with cheese
they're called
kesak yeah quak for Carl oh that's like
here they have hot dogs that have chili
cheese in the middle
yummy chili cheese I've never had chili
before really oh it's good yeah chili in
a Sourdough bowl with the chicken
strips the cheese sprinkled up
top H stuff is
so into a
wall did I go the wrong way yeah seems
very much like it when I look at the map
oh my God where' everyone go oh we're
coming back going
down yeah it was the way but sometimes
the way they dig straight down wrong I
thought if there was like this rock
stuff around it that that's the way
we're supposed to go it is it is it is
oh if tab you'll see like where the the
next room is kind of
confusing oops dig straight down Metroid
Prime
okay down yeah yeah where are we going
now everybody I missed
you did you girls go up down down down
yeah if you open the map you can see I'm
going
down how did you get
there
oh
ah well not these things
not
proud rock
on you knock my rocks
off I love these
guys they're so happy with their job and
their lifestyle
fil you really rock my rock I want to be
like
them do you want to I'm I mean you're
going to risk your life every single
time you have to go
mining but somehow it seems
fun you like it's
really yeah it rocks my world you know
it really rocks my rocks I'm getting so
rocked you know rock and roll surely
they'll also have a phrase where they
say that right what is this sure
we're looking for alien eggs and fossils
alien EG fossil the alien eggs on your
map the tab they're orange and yeah they
got like purpley flesh all around them
what up I picked one up wa
CR your I didn't do that I feel like you
did that I did that it was me I stole
something oh no I don't mean the music I
mean the explosion there I mean yeah
that one I did but like you
know it's
shaking swarm repeat swarm I don't care
I'm I got to get the fossil oh dear oh
oh oh
oh can't get you can't oh no
no okay fight fine it's fine it's
fine oh oh oh oh
that's uh a lot let's maybe throw a bomb
let's
go maybe I should have throw
them hello
boys I know how to help ow at least I
haven't died in a while for o alien eggs
yay where where where
I want at the top at the
top what are
[Music]
you don't jinx it there's no such thing
as
jinxing there we
go
enem practically Eric you did a good
[Music]
job job
all right all right all right all right
my are those alien
eggs where are the
rest there's one watch out
oh they said practically eradicated they
lied
MC control yeah GL say
something can't let this just stand
he's lying to us
complain I'm telling
you I don't quite trust him anymore
who's going to call him a wet but I
don't really know what that means a wet
wet do mean part pooper yeah okay so he
has a wet
blanket interesting adding to my
vocabulary ah I see there's one egg
here is the fossil gone that I wanted to
get looks like
it why are they all so hard to access oh
my God it's shaking
again that did you take something again
is that an alien egg I don't know what
that is found some purple things
[Music]
what what Course St like a b
oh oh my God I'm going to die are there
any heal thingies
ah why are they so fast what is
this wait what the oh
de what it's a horror game
now oh we're shooting the core shoot the
core yeah I'm looking I'm looking for
help though aren't those Health Stones
wait okay what's the cor stone is that
the core Stone building back up though
need ammo oh but we already got one
third just I called in
a okay okay okay oh my God is that where
the Pod is going to
okay mine the stone ah this Stone oh
yeah
okay I don't I don't okay wait wait wait
wait cuz it like kind of re covered
itself into a cocoon all right all right
let's back out shoot it shoot it shoot
[Music]
ah oh I don't even know where I
am the music is cool yeah it's bossing
oh there's a thing
here stop
that thing can I dig it
already maybe I have to
finish okay mining time a thir time this
boss fight isn't too difficult I just
don't like how fast these things
are
ah I am I am have one HP and the dream
[Music]
I said back
up sorry did it
yipp
[Music]
nice oh my was that maybe the new season
thing nice you got
it wait
where
oh oh yeah after this let me longest
shower ever
can I not put do I carry this into the
spaceship or what somebody have a fossil
maybe they haven't deposited yet um no I
deposited also yeah I guess we do we
have to carry this special container
carry it carry it a special
container uh a special drop pod for it
okay where is
that I can't can't see look up right up
here or up here this one is this not it
oh
M where did this come
from we're going to get so much bonuses
right team will be instrumental in our
de do I hurt nice job no getting supp
yeah all right going
back okay I just quickly got some fre
supplies I'll follow you so I don't get
lost
it's
it's wait where'd you guys go it's uh
where did everyone go we're down here
we're waiting that way I'm waiting
for okay never
mind we can go this way
no
yeah I'm going to get far behind again
ow that way I can't get up I can't get
up no you can't get up I got you
ow here this
way wait I found
it oh hello big boy
that didn't
work okay I with the girls
again
[Music]
bong this
way this way the oh yeah this way ignore
my diip
line I can't
see where
H it's right here you were just right in
front of me how did I miss you
again
oops up there oh my God it's okay you
got time
yeah okay okay okay oh my God
surprise my my my
rock oo one last party nice send off
wow that's so
toxic what is the
flossing what what I do
[Music]
rockone we did it once
again
complete I haven't picked up a single
fossil
they always put them in like the high
Corners no yeah
yay I didn't find a a beer mug this
time oh we got the cor Stone oh yeah I
guess that was
optional
noise was it very noise is it corstone
on every map I think it spawns randomly
or maybe that was the egg because it had
this little bit of a egg
shape Maness we got all the other eging
Miss okay onsite
refining is next maybe on sweet or is
that on the mission I'm not
sure before we go anywhere we got to
drink another
beer and dance another round
Y kick around this old Wier I'm going to
order oily o
brew that
sounds yeah we had didn't have that one
yet I think oh it looks so basic oh it's
so classic it's like Tavern drink you
going to add something to that something
nice no nope no that's it all right
someone turn on the music
coming yeah I hope I Twerk this time oh
that
sucks a this
is oh
man but that's not easy to dance
Too K did you turn off the did you turn
on the stream mode nah oh oh my God no I
think I probably did the other time I
played it so unless the settings
reverted
then why what are you hearing right now
um something pretty pretty slow like
slow sound like
Hawaiian yeah yeah yeah
Hawaiian
Chillow yeah like country music kind of
yeah yeah they're literally playing gam
Style lyrics and
everything all right Kaa huz check these
hips
out you wish you could wiggle like your
scout cheers
ch's
mine should burp but I literally can't
[Music]
burp go
oh this is how we do okay let's roll
what next what's
next that's that's something like a
burp no that's
good let's get out of here
refreshing drop sequence
initiating let go bless you bless you
thank you that was a good sneeze
go thank you are we complete I can't see
I'm complete
okay
H but you need to be complete Titanic
Earth my I don't know man if I knew that
I wouldn't be
here again maybe you need a air Fred
twinky you're right an air fryer is
going to fix everything let's go just
my liquid morai oh goody oh more
fossils oh that means we have to do
pipes yeah who shot me
no
no no it wasn't
me okay this is
fine no this is
fine what is that's the big thing oh
golden Loop bug
[Music]
wow what's this volcano thing
doing so that's
that's we got to suck the morite out of
that out of the volcano thing yeah so
we're going to start
here at the big thing the big on-site
Refinery and we're going to uh there's
three tubes that are going to shoot out
of it and we got to drag those tubes to
the volcanoes oh she's so
knowledgeable it's coming back to me now
yes
I'm I just wanted this put my stuff into
the mule oh I see a fossil what is this
elimin finally a
fossil what is this where did the mule
go ow there's no
mule
what where do I put my stuff then I
guess I
can't put it anywhere oh that's
it I don't think Molly can hear me from
here it's a Sal Crystal yummy oh and
then this turns into skate skateboard
the game lights
suck looks like sorry guys my request
and is inbound oh that's what is that
going to make a pipe there the pump yeah
I guess so
yeah to plug the pipe in which one I'll
drag one over to you guys
Jing
okay she knows what she's
doing I do yeah yeah no I mean good B
but you too I
guess wait w how in the world is it two
far no I just got to figure out how I'm
going to we might need a Watson to like
or we can use a platform tool oh we
could
yeah wait wait wait oh my
God I'll fill the rest of the way with
your hole mhm mm what what wait what you
feel you f the rest of what did you say
I'll use the rest I'll go the rest wait
I'll will Traverse the rest of the way
with your hole that you have dug dad
makes sense yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay you have such a way with words
thank you I'm sorry I'm distracted I'm
glad that came whoopsie Finders Keepers
I was here
first so if we don't have a mule where
do I put my
fossil in the big mu the big mule
okay a our ship
or this thing
the onsite
[Music]
Refinery I fell down oh hey I found one
though y I got it I got
a
yay from thect what you get trying to
steal my my fossil
huh it's okay I I got a pipeline thanks
to you though thanks man Team
workor all right one is done estblished
okay oh so we we have one and we need we
need three R over here yeah and we got
three in specific
locations up there over there you open
tab it's ping on your map we got one how
do you ping stuff control control and
left
click and oh do you want it my God
light is up I say you get it oh you get
it
okay do you want to you're so
short what where are we
going I'm trying to figure out how we're
going to
get we need I think we need crony or
Watson to help I have a pipeline not a
pipeline I have a I have the thing if
you thing yeah the
the where do you want to go what
direction
oh no no no I meant like we got to get
this pipe down there oh this one mhm and
if we could if we could put the pipe on
but yeah know I don't know want to get
down there I would help you if I knew
where you guys were oh my
God wait how are they over there how'
you guys get over there we jump
walked walk maybe build how push me down
sorry um I'm no no no like we found the
pipeline because of that
so I'm make
overheating oh you can over
here yeah I know that my drill hands I'm
loot gramlin now loot Goblin I think I'm
going up to the platform I just I don't
know oh not sure wait how did you guys I
think this is the way they went you're
I'm trying we're trying to get back to
I'm not looking at the map so I think oh
you're going the opposite way you're
going the opposite way St
way
um wait I think I dug a really long
hole yeah you really dug a hole for
yourself
there I'm pretty much going the right
way almost I just need to turn
we got to get back up there I
think it sticks on them nice okay to go
down
therey Cory should I
not got to go up there that
way where we where go over there I'm
here yeah we got to go that way okay I
can just have a traversal tool
they go this
way
okay maybe
high
oh hello
heyo
bro time
ladies okay something wanted to kill me
okay anyway where were
we there's like a way that I
could get
[Music]
around
why I have no idea how they got
over um
it's fine don't worry about it we no
Nitra what is it called Nitra they went
the Army away maybe I shouldn't be
here it's okay we just got to re swarm
on the
way to
where swarm
swarm I'm going to go back up then with
my zipline you can come help me dig this
hole cuz I would to try and connect to
them are you still trying to go to the
same thing then I'll look around to find
you I'm I don't see you I'm supposed to
see you on the map right oh I think I I
know where you are maybe but there's a
lot of enemies
here oh
y are they just where do they just spawn
wherever we
are are you guys also getting
attacked okay
yeah yeah
ow ow
no
okay I see L I found Goa okay okay okay
I shall be your shield on your
back okay Let Me Wait Don't Shoot Me
Wait don't
shoot me see if I can put this my the
tunnel is of utmost importance
[Music]
ow wasn't me I'm trying to protect you
don't shoot in the hole I'm here but it
was on your
back oh my God there's a lot coming are
you still building the thing I think
first we have to kill the
monsters I'm good okay
okay there's a big one
coming him but he's too big he can't fit
through okay call good oh oh okay all
right hello boys yeah I think it's calm
again I still hear Boss music okay so I
think we got to go this way oh I see you
guys hi hello
Hello's down there down there okay
that's where the the thing is oh
yeah wait k drag that pipe over here oh
okay he please oh out of ammo I found
Aid I am out of Lights that's not good
it'll be a beauty once it's complete who
take
okay like
here we have to get that
here a yeah
watch
a here just drop down
here can it go down so
steeply oh yeah oh yeah can you can you
guys just drop down here or no we can we
got to bring the pipe with us
oh
better yum hey is am somewhere close by
she could build us like a tunnel that
goes down I'm out of fuel oh no
oh uh wait how do we place the fuel the
thing again with g no that was a b
careful
sorry well we could try to make a tunnel
with the bombs I don't know five five
how about how about
here mhm MH
MH and then
here can I
not is it because we built it before he
can but it's a pretty tight
Corner uh how about
here Nitro hold
on hold on I think we got to I only have
two more left oh
God how about
I want to go back to ship fuel yeah you
guys want to look for the red stuff yeah
I have a bunch of it but I need to
deposit it in the main ship which is
super far now cuz I'm down here in this
hole hold on I think I can still make a
zip line but where to go in the
hole I was h
dude this we're going to do this will so
help me I'll go get I'll bring the Nitro
no we don't have Molly right now can all
the way back to the big thing
mhm it's difficult valid valid oh we're
doing this um oh oh oh wait wait
wait oh yeah oh yeah
connected now I can skate all the way
back it's kind of in the way it's too
sharp it says okay like here yeah
yeah
yeah it's working yeah yeah yeah boom
boom it turns around for us okay okay
now we can grind it now we have to build
it oh wow yeah it's pretty
far I hope there wasn't like a really
blatant shortcut that I just didn't see
under it's
okay it is fun though the longer the the
way do you know those like not quite
roller coasters
um what do you call those like
Countryside
random roller coasters that are not
roller
coasters if you know Dark Ride like the
ones in the mountain yeah Alpine
coasters Alpine
ow those are fun those remind me of my
childhood never been on a try does yeah
well usually they get kind of hot and
then cuz they're usually out of this
like steel or whatever and then it's too
hot on your butt cuz there's some that
you ride on your butt I think and some
you ride on something else I don't know
where is the the I can't I'm too wait
it's literally here okay I'm I'm stupid
I'm
stupid I was looking for it guys I was
looking for it that's why I was jumping
around okay we have a Nitro now yay I'll
make one fossil I'll make a machine one
fossil we got to get this thing down are
coming it's too calm doesn't feel too
calm this way
rest wait that's not going to
work realking is now
possible please contact your closest
supplier of stalks and
ammo are we in need of one more pipe oh
where are you going with this one
aming you want to go down or Bel or
above oh I'm that works yeah this one we
won't be able to ride like the other way
wa did they extend that that's so
far seconds that's going to be fun to go
down I can already
gr that's amazing I like this Mission
it's way more complicated and longer
than the other ones
but how do we Mak the roller coaster
[Music]
maybe
maybe here I try
to finally
light let there be
light let there be light let there be
light let there be rocking stone rock
stone rocking
Stone why am I dealing with building the
pipelines huh eh what
probably it's a hard job but someone's
got to do it also build them that's
still
blocked okay all right
fin why do you me too
steep request accepted stand clear pump
jack inbound pump jack pump
jack
oh oh we're getting there there
oh did you get
squished no I'm good
okay
thanks there is Tik Tok music so good
it's not Tik Tok music no like it's it's
going Tik
Tok where I can't Tik Tok dance to this
what oh it has been
connected
[Music]
y fight fight fight
yeah rocket Stone rocking Stone like
they sensed that we were about to finish
they knew
it me where's where did you guys put the
drop thingy wait uh ah it's at the base
can you can now grind your way up there
and then you can drop it at the
base I mean resupply at the base it's
there
too
ow this is fun shooting while on the
pipeline that's fun it's Tony Hawk gate
three but more oh yeah I used to play
that on the
GameCube oh Tony h
than I think I think it was the game
yeah g had a lot of good games
mhm a great Cube the G Cube oh I'm out
of
ammo the game
go Sor all
good
okay sorry if you guys can't see where
are you
[Music]
W oh is the resupply already empty maybe
another
one another
resupply another
one and another one another one he but
we made already free tunnels what's
happening now a free free supplies H you
have
to build the pipes is that what you're
talking about but aren't they
built step one build the pipe step two
build the pipe oh
you step three protect the
pipe we're also looking for last fossil
I haven't seen one FL look for the
FL wait how do you you just how do you
build it on the like most it has to be
this here you you can do that one now oh
there you go you can do the rest okay
congratulations You' been promoted hey
are the others also not built yet all of
them uh that's the last one I think oh
okay
where yeah where where you guys are at
I'm
here I don't really know in place and
theid is waiting okay where you guys are
at well if there's a pipe you can grind
back to
base now
I am I'm going to do this
now so now we're sucking the more kite
through the big tubes we made yeah but
they're going to break
down so we're going to have to fix them
at the top right you'll see which one is
failed one two
[Music]
three and we still missing one fossil by
the way keep an eye out mission control
is not putting the company budget in the
right place
so we get poopy
pipes see that am oh man
no all the
pipes okay I will go to one of them I
don't know which one we have to go like
to the bottom of them
right you see
no I see yeah I see they're destroying
specific Parts save
him it seems like when we created these
pipelines we didn't do it with much care
no it's like that's not
true this is now Plumbing the
[Music]
game how's the reparation going I fixed
pipe free what are you are manager
you're just overseeing this no pointing
your finger no over there over there oh
pipe
two where's pipe
two SP Plumbing my favorite is number on
that oh that's one two oh they're
actually numbered
amazing get out there fix number two I
still haven't seen that
um I'm on my way to it
yeah oh oh oh get
off
no
no oops that's not what I meant to
put okay out of my thing fixing number
two and finish finished finished we did
we're almost
there up good work be done in no
time I misspoke not fish
finish yeah
fish
we please leave me alone no please don't
please this looks like more door can I
grind with this I don't think so I
can oh what are you holding no orb
oh sorry
sorryy CL the broken
again oh okay don't cry no
oh they're all
broken yeah again they're all
broken I got you I'm I'm by pipe one
somewhere on the bottom yeah I see you
lovely you the best Charming
Lady Of course bro did you fall yeah I
fell when I was like grinding down and I
wanted to stop for the repairs but I
fell too hard yeah it to be like that
sometimes but it's exciting thank
you all right I see p freeze
fixed is this fix you're fixing one okay
is fixed but you need to Cle
this reminds me of a a boss fight in was
it not it takes two the other one what's
the other one called
again
uh way out I no then I do mean it takes
to I guess that's a long game
yeah uh is it it takes two is the one
with from the where you where you turn
into a puppet right yeah little po to
save the marriage or something did we
all play that cuz I did finish
it did I yeah I finished it I finished
both a way out and it takes two did you
guys not finish a way out no we did you
did okay we we itex to is really fun too
F but God yeah I like the like way out
mhm that was really fun was fun it was
pretty it was pretty hilarious yeah yeah
yeah I want more games like that with
the split screen buil in yeah and the
Betrayal I love that oh sure love
betrayal that's what you're into I see
crony
betrayal that's what I'm used
to I'm going to fix pipe
one okay I'm going to
fix whatever that is
fake I'm going to fix what's broken you
can't stop I don't know how to fix
this smack
it oh I see okay now I get
it what difficulty is this this is big
still this is more than
satisfactory yeah I'm having a good time
PTSD let's go
yeah we love betray
[Music]
I don't think I don't think that's the
right put it on a shirt
[Laughter]
my incom swarm show them your dwares
swarm swarm you know in German we say
when we have a crush on someone we say
that's our
swarm isn't that weird yeah you're my
infection I'm infected by you you're my
parasite all right oh I wish you were my
parasite oh you control
me you're lodged in my brain I want you
to latch on to me you're my little
tapeworm yeah please I can't focus on
anything with with you in my body that
sounds
really romantic very romtic my calories
please I'm
hungry I would like to hear that from
someone make me want to lose weight
crowny no
no that's just a very
toxic very toxic for you don't oh my God
what's going on why is it taking off are
you in that you didn't okay no you're
all there we got enough fuel
okay and then they leave we have fossils
though we might see it on the way back
we get paid well though don't
we what did you say
yeah they pay us right
oh it's the
satisfaction oh yeah of living this
lifestyle rocking
Stones there the drop Rock
Stone
drop I thought this we're missing one
fossil
yeah follow this one follow number
two follow number two oh my God I don't
know potentially can we go back without
the last Foss fossil is that Foss a
secondary objective but yeah is that oh
[\h__\h] I'm out of ammo I can't I can't
protect myself anymore wait
um oh God I'm out of juice okay I
ordered the thir resupply in case
somebody wants them but we're extracted
in 2 and a half minutes oh you can take
these okay what which which pipeline was
it two you take number two okay I guess
I don't need my race anymore
but take number two and then take
crony's platforms here number
two one last
[Music]
grind damn [\h__\h] is such a great
Scout yeah I don't light the
way at
all typal Scout look at me I got to grab
me on me this way this way I'm going
YY
uh ah I see grappling
hook God damn bro how do I maybe maybe
you can make a over here here I made new
why I keep falling oh not you I'm sorry
I'm talking to myself sorry no no no I
didn't even hear what you said I just
you're freaking platforms I can't jump
them no I can't jump in either I'll go
to you and I'll show you the way ow oh
no wait who died I'm but I'm I'm here
with her I'll will revive her and I'll
show her the
way cuz
ah wait are you sure you got it yeah
yeah yeah yeah I think now ah there's
still enemies
spawning okay where are you okay
now where are you
guys uh we're we're almost good okay
follow me YY take this first zip line
and then from there I made a second zip
line okay back off creepy careful that
jump is really difficult I failed it
many times
why I F again 30 seconds 30
seconds far I think it's like right in
front just just I'm not good with time
pressure
TW come
on no I'm not going to make it what what
happen no will I fail it no no no no
what
sorry thank
[Laughter]
you so heroic oh I still get the
completed though oh good good maybe I
don't get any okay nice like
exp that's my that's my she's breathing
you're alone yeah breathing yay thanks
for coming back for me I guess cuz I
guess that's what that implies you're
welcome know we sent the b in to get you
maybe as long as you sent something oh
that's
true thanks Mission Control next time
next time there moral you always hating
on Mission
Control
sorry oh o perk
points all
right another mission
complete we playing more what are we
doing
yeah we in the hospital
G was wearing pink pantties I am oh
because I died kind of I want to look at
myself I got to dance to look at
myself that
reminds cute pink underwear but aren't
you supposed to be naked under that
no I want to take that off and then
work we got more
eggs wait no
don't
hey Lo what one more mission mission one
more mission is that what you guys said
or didn't you I don't I don't know oh
[\h__\h] am I hitting the
gritty what is is this that's a sick
move what is that what is this I've seen
that
[Music]
before wait we need to drink a
beer okay I want to drink the glyphid
glyphid but do you guys have rank seven
we haven't tried The glyphid Slammer
yet but needs rank
seven n I'm only four okay then I think
we want the sausage beer beer for me and
my friend
sausage is so cute that the handle is a
sausage
too so cute does sausage go well with
beer well I suppose probably I don't I
never tried it but I'm guessing that's
why there's so much beer there oh they
say yes I like this song St dancing and
get it's cute Che I'm doing the peace
dance
wienie cheers in German we say pro pro
yeah is it proost p r o s t FR
FR FR chug chug chug chug chug chug
chug hey oh hit the mission boys
let's go yeah if am is okay with it oh
yeah are you okay yeah last mission
maybe okay all right hope it's going to
be an interesting one
again it's going to be hard we're going
to die oh this counter is giving me
PTSD should I make it
harder no no it's okay I'm really
looking forward to me working with you
guys let's roll really looking forward
to working with you guys he says me too
my go I'm here oh she on the ship I'm on
the ship really she's the ship crying
cral who hurt
you yeah we got to oh low Hazard though
final
mission what if this one's too lame not
a good one to end it
on I don't think so okay leave no one
behind collect evil
nuts
bonut this looks pretty
friendly yeah is that a nut that's a not
right terrain scanner just got updated
with a new location cracked it open
you're still not wearing you're still
wearing your hospital again
what uh is there stats like uh oh am
I of enemies still
work well I'll just use you girls as my
armor you'll be my meat Shields
[Music]
sneaky I'm fine it's it's like when you
would like go to the hospital when you
were in elementary school and then you
would keep the bracelet on so people
would be like oh my god what
happened did you go to the doctor that's
kind of I always wish to break a bone
because I want people to be like oh what
happened you never broken one no never
and I really want to so then I can get
one of those cats can I sign so that
everyone can sign your c yeah I want
someone to sign my Cod on me I had that
I had a broken arm in school once a
that's so
fun so fun yeah oh there's an eye I'm so
jealous you broke a limb you shattered a
bone
how did you break your
arm uh I was swinging between between
two chairs like the couch chair and uh I
was trying to like swing and do cool
stuff and then I fell on my
arm and then nobody knew it was broken
for a few days and I was just holding it
weird and they were like uh it were you
not in
pain yeah but I was just being quiet I
was just like I don't know I didn't want
to get in
trouble they always told me not to play
on the couch like that
a e your pain tolerance must be
crazy I guess you
guess explosives sorry I put an
explosive down by accident don't mind oh
lighting up boom boom Oh it's taking a
while come
on shoot
explode barage
in Oham
G is it going to is it
um what in what in the
[Music]
ow died fast
L wow what's that you can pet him
[Laughter]
I am sorry no Molly Molly's
here Molly's there again we missed
her
Molly see Molly's better than whatever
potentially hostile
creatures yeah yeah oh yeah so you don't
have to pet those oh
oh my God there's a million tiny spiders
oh you already did
it where where are we that way this way
okay come collect your more more
gu too sure and not are these the nuts
that we're looking for yeah I think
so you missed some dude w that was rude
I left it for
you
oh I love keep missing oh well it stays
oh we're going pretty far yeah o
gold what happens if we get like other
resources that aren't important I think
it will add onto our loot yeah so I
think we should go for anything oh my
yeah I think might give us money slimy
give me money I can't pet it
money yeah press e
oh why is he flirting with it wa did
they change it no they
didn't look at his mouth I
don't he can hold stuff
okay call it a Pog plant
why doesn't isn't POG I can see why they
would call it that say POG juice how do
you put down our Molly
again
[Music]
see
okay I want to dispose or
some PA
ebo ebo
nut
okay which way are we going go I'll
follow you you seem to have act actually
surprisingly a good sense of
direction she uses the map
yeah uhhuh I'm not I use goba
ow I like how you scratch your head each
time you look at that the M yeah you
scratch your head cuz I wonder we're
supposed to go this way thinking so hard
thinking real hard starved for brain
cell wait did I go the wrong
way NOA wouldn't go the wrong
way that's right me the wrong way
[Music]
no what's
this it's a
n no everybody knows I have great
directional sense alien plants actually
I guess we were are we traveling to
different planets each time we go around
cuz that was a spaceship right and
then maybe so is this like alip I
thought it was just like a drilling I
guess it is but we went for space right
in the in the
cutscenes no it's all on the same Planet
okay but this is at least not earth
right no I don't think
soame where are
you uh I think I'm going toward guys
maybe not oh yeah I am really we
my all right oh got a jam cover
me jam oh sorry ah ah why am I shooting
my friends what's wrong with me the
planet is named
Hawes this is Ohio oh
honestly caves of
Ohio oh you can pet the loot dogs too
don't flirt with the Enemy
[Music]
oh nut oh
nut crack it open looks like a walnut
damn Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum but inside
looks like a wait do you say in English
do you also call it a
a
lei Lighty okay oh yeah the inside of
the nut looks like a Lighty
are you talking about the Slugs
uh slugs the the fruit right yeah the
fruit what is a slug called the li no no
no no no no thought mean you can shoot
no no I mean the I mean the nuts the
inside of the nuts looks like a ly yeah
yeah H where to
next oh
crony H I found some more kite what I
some more what a more kite that would
probably be easiest with your platforms
or Watson can dig her way up sorry I'm
dealing with something right now oh D
good oh oh yeah you
are there's a thing right there oh my
God my stomach not a big deal I have to
log off forever
thank you I'm going to
go uh you didn't hear that right no
didn't hear it okay no I didn't hear it
[Music]
okay it's all the beer that we've been
drinking with the
[Music]
sausages do you know there's actually
this time so I've actually this brought
I thought about this the other day and
with with the the the the the I guess
the change coming with with myth um I've
been thinking back on all of like cringy
stuff just I guess reminiscing over the
years and there was this time that uh I
was recording something you know in
Japan and when you go and you meet the
the like the mixing team and you're like
you know hello hello hello
um and it was just it was just me and
and staff and then the mix team and
whatever in in a studi so it's quiet in
the studios
and to and we're sitting no no we're
we're sitting there and they're
discussing things and I can't
participate in the conversation so I'm
sitting quietly and then it goes really
quiet cuz we're waiting for something
and then um my stomach starts just going
at it like
just really loud and
awful and I'm thinking that it's I'm
thinking oh my God everybody can hear
this right now everybody's listening to
this is so embarrassing but I actually
don't don't think anybody could hear me
or my stomach going crazy but I thought
they could so um after
like you're Bing too much after after
like 3 minutes of intense stomach
growling I just out of nowhere I stand
up and I go okay that's it and then I I
leave the
room and um I still don't I don't think
they had any idea what the heck I was uh
talking about I think they now I'm I
think they think I'm recording room it
was I was in the recording studio oh
yeah they could definitely hear it oh
good oh good I
great I'm out of ammo there's
no maybe they heard it but they were
being considerate and not saying
anything cuz they felt you might be
embarrassed about hungry yeah well I was
hoping that I hope they didn't just
think like wow girl is weird she just
like she just got up and like what with
some you did that be like what was your
problem dude I placed the
thing the resupply Pod so oh my God oh
my God I'm going to die cuz I can't
shoot a supply
me oops okay I have been supplied now I
can
shoot does this just heal you have a
shield I have a
shield did you girls know you had a
shield we had a shield maybe you just
have Oh you mean the blue stuff oh guess
press for I press for that's the sh is
that supposed to be a
shield oh you place it on the ground you
mean it's like a ah I thought you meant
a real
Shield so that was a shield oh I think
it's different for everyone mhm mhm cuz
I get a sentry gun if I press four oh
throw in your hammer
for a
pickaxe out
of boom boom baby
y I
need yeah but now I got nervous cuz I
thought that like some staff members
thought I just had like this really
weird explosive burst I got to get out
of here no it happens then everybody
quiet the quiet oh the quiet got the
girl she's lost her
mind I had to leave and skitter up the
walls but actually I just needed a rice
ball yum yum yum yum I love eating when
I'm in Japan yeah I love the the the
salmon row wait what was
it I like com com
oh my favorite is Maybe too basic it's
just tuna
Mayo I like Tao yeah spicy cardro yeah
yeah yeah the row yeah yeah did you try
the one there's like they had these
Deluxe ones in black bags they had s
really Deluxe salmon Row one was so good
yeah they probably still have it oh wait
I want to try that I I didn't even know
that was a thing it's so good
is
y tun where it's at tuna is a bit basic
but you know
what but it's plastic
yes it's good it's really yummy come
here I love tuna I love Tuna on pizza
too I thought you didn't like fish
really Tuna on I don't like raw uh raw
fish get supp yeah tuna and pizza is
very common here oh that's new M now I
want pizza damn yeah me too getting
hungry I only had a quo so far
[Music]
today oh wait we got all this thing we
just need
[Music]
these we're just looking for
nuts okay I hope we didn't miss any cuz
then we'll have to go all the way back
no surely there's more like extra ones
in case you miss some
right why Jem why
gem
you stomach please not now have you
eaten go B I did it just makes noise oh
sorry Make some noise Make some noise in
G uh
tummy Make some noise for
digestion
God can't hear you enough louder Make
Some Noise please please no I want to
hear goodas tummy what's going on in
there oh I get so self-conscious when I
hear my stomach Grumble and it gets
caught on stream and it's like oh my God
oh my God I doo have a digestive tract
no please
oh yeah ah we have enough nuts and
enough moride did we realize that
already Yi
that's drop on
inbound
am how do we go back
up wait somebody yeah this music is sick
just drill somebody hit the button we
can backrack the path that we
took I would do
that ah I find it maybe oh there it
goes got it you want to follow the guy
we can where's the mule he's down there
oh
oh oh he it
downwards yes a downward spiral as they
say yep I'm down
all right Yi RMA this time I will not be
left
behind I'll be
firsty where' everyone go you have to go
all the way down and you'll see the the
green sticks yeah follow the lights
follow the green light
greenen follow the lights yeah I see
them maybe I'll even be faster than the
mule I'll leave the enemies for you
girls okay I got to pad my stats I have
PTSD now I I don't want to be left
behind
anymore not ready Flare's
recharging mu mule do something
mu
hops
that you walked into my
bullets h
gry
oh oh shoot that looks dangerous later
nudes
OWI maybe I shouldn't have gone all
alone PT s PT
s let me catch up to
you yeah are you behind me yeah no
no
no too much
time no you're
cheating take me with
you no I have those two but they don't
work as easy as
yours mine aren't as
flexible oh
ah I bur I Bur
okay now we'll help you shoot from up
here
webbed oops we oh oh oh [\h__\h] stuck I'm
all of I'm just running I'm also out of
ammo let's just
run work for
me die creep retried
I want to eat a jar of frosting right
now Crocker where are you I have a
feeling I know why your tummy makes
funny sounds
[\h__\h] why you just eat frosting like that
I said I want
to oh my is everyone on board no I'm
fighting can we go in already okay oh my
God
all right are we now all on
board
yeah time to
go my step back why does it not close
step back step back do we need to kill
this thing please step all the way
inside oh all the way okay thank
you let's just take the new the pets
with
us rock rock and
[Music]
good that felt refreshing do my
God that's why it felt refreshing
because my ass was on in the
open makes sense you had a nice
breeze that's why I wanted to run first
so you all can see where that breeze is
going
towards while you're walking behind me
does crop us crop dce crop
dust lethal crop dusting
no oh
okay yay last
beer yeah beer let's get okay one for
the
road dance Monkeys dance what you call
me yeah that was pretty rude I will give
you that he's rude on you nice thanks on
me
[Music]
another sausage
one give me
that oh wait drink
drink oh sausage again it's the sausage
fest
yay one last round to
[Music]
ptsds m
bye and yeat the cups in who's face
you Bry yeah I this time goba oh goba
got two hits Amy got two
hits
y thank you for guiding us for the game
experience except kill stuff got it
that's
important yeah it was fun I like this
game yeah I like the drinking aspect
of oh mini
[Music]
game
oh oh oh
nice that was mess oh I
didn't this is not happening oh this is
gets faster what
like just spamming it somebody else try
try the Flappy Bird game oh Flappy
[Music]
Bird
oh hey can't play the Flappy Bird game
Flappy Bird where where jelly boot oh
all right my fans once made made a kfp
version of floppy
birds how does this work you press what
what's the I'm guessing it's not space
how do
you I think you left click left click
left click oh okay it's it's a boot I
had a it's Jetty boot that video game
will you lost no I wasn't sure about the
controls okay okay here we go g r your
brain I bet you Mission Control has a
permanent indent from his
headset digs into his brain did he like
hurt you yeah maybe she has
pts he's insulting us I'm sending it
back so he knows nothing M with us bird
is too
difficult I prefer the the the kiky K
game this is maybe an idea for another
Ian REO game oh W games yeah this KCK
different kfp into like sure I don't
know why it has to be
kfp why not am I playing portug yeah
you're playing you're playing you're
playing you're here to work yes not to
play video games huh we're literally
playing a video game right now uh-uh
we're working
yeah work is video game and die
coordination
practice level
two increase damn you got a CL
bird don't kick the
[Music]
machine last level last life come
on
no it's
hard come on want to try oh only
want let's see how good you are now
people on stream are watching people
watch people
play easy video game
sub oh oh oh she's getting a feeling for
oh wa wao professional Jetty
Booter oh boy level two let's go
lock in
cron she's locked in she's locked in
she's oh [\h__\h]
wa you are so locked in you're so
close is there there is that the last
mini game I think so oh yeah I think
so oh
sausage the forge H the forge the
sausage in
space bye it
byebye big
button oh
cute
leg what what is
that gravity oh gravity that didn't help
me
much one more
please oh it's still
going oh jet boots there's jet boots up
here oh o for free for free all way the
top all the
way wait can you die you can't die
right try it
out um okay okay oh top hanger maybe
it's here top no I don't think you can
[Music]
die well well happy rocktober Fest to
everybody October F October Fest hold on
wait I want to get jet
boot well who did he say that to maybe
he said that to you
crony yay okay I have jet boots okay y
you to know anything about it okay
no take fall damage did you does it take
fall damage I don't think so no no no
bar to be alone
and okay always she's forever going to
be in this Hospital down yeah I don't
know I guess until I change my clothes
why what it was a shot over
there launch yeah
well if I go into the Wardrobe it says I
am wearing my MK1 Gunner
suit oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I
don't know well I'm I'm fine with
this happy with this um it shows what
I've been
through oh now I'm back to normal
apparently
a
okay um so think we're going to let I'm
go to do her thing now y get ready did
you is it listy can we raid into it oh
no I haven't scheduled it yet sorry
thank you though I apprciate it well
everybody will know where to go later on
you guys know where to go I will post it
on
Twitter yeah I was going to retweet the
myth collab but then there was no stream
like on Twitter so I was like oh I'll
just like
retweet the schedule I guess yeah I
always post the thumbnail and stuff
really late sorry oh it's all good man
the way yeah hell
yeah wow oh yeah you were watching crony
huh yeah I saw when you guys planted the
wrong seeds in farm well did you see
when I died uh in your stupid
Tower well you fell for the stupid Tower
yeah well I saw water at the bottom I
thought that it was going to be fine it
was obviously a
prank it was just a prank
yeah I'm going to go in there and blow
it up last two hours I have access to
Minecraft server and then she can't be
punished
anymore yeah try that what try crony
will punish you in person she will go
visit you and punish you personally
blame me on a different
member no you never know me yeah NOP
well no I would I would delete the
evidence there won't be any actually if
you uh don't do it ah on stream come on
guys yeah that's true no but who would
do
that on the on the server oh like you
know on the en server no l and so
recently you know well yeah she
announced her crimes already so yeah
exactly oh I like still maybe maybe it's
a different M they get got the idea for
me and
they're and then they're going to blame
it on me because they know that you're
just going to blame me and they'll never
get blamed I'll put up some security
cameras thank you security that'd be
cool I'm surprised her bunker doesn't
already have security
cameras no it would be nice if we added
that
oh already has always has been secured
and obser my security camera a I didn't
see any end when I was there they were
slacking should be around somewhere I
guess so God damn they're
gone but yeah but okay that was a fun
collab thank you had a good time yeah
thank you guys want to play can thank
you for playing yeah thank thank you
yay so don't forget your Le hor and your
dle and your sausages and don't forget
to rock and tear no rock and rock and
roll walk and tear whatever Rock and St
Rock socks do my
socks so
often what's with your socks do they
count as later in uh
no no no
socks ro ro
rock rock
rock hope you guys had fun chat I did
and
you in chat no you too definitely here I
forgot they were
here I'm just
[Laughter]
kidding
okay and what do you guys
say
off yeah
oh thank you you girl say your
goodbyes
farewell bye oh so proper sorry
okay you do you free actually wait crony
has a bye-bye greeting CI right yeah but
it's a little too early for C I feel
like are you sure don't you just want to
go back to sleep right
now me you were so you sounded so tired
when you came into the
VC I know right cuz cute yeah but yeah
okay uh
then
bye home Watson that's more like a
that's not a goodbye but sure oh yes
time yeah see you
see you Lon see you see you
later see you
watsoni
byebye byee
[Music]
n
oh
[Music]