[Music]
ah
K didn't even notice it's a new stream
welcome guys it is a new stream yay
yay yay this is kiaha and quas
y
hi or
[Music]
say uh unfortunately all the lag all the
buffering kind of you know threw us out
of our nice conversation we had
before the yeah before this yeah we'll
never ever get it back no sure of course
we will
you wanted to know
more it's over no it's not over it's
only over if you if you want it to be
over no I mean yeah no I mean what do
you remember what we talked about we
were talking about
shows no no before that before that how
can you forget dude my memory is not
that good oh my God you okay so before
um I will not say any details don't
worry Quon but I was asking Quon what do
you do after this and and she said she's
going somewhere with her family right a
family member and then I asked uh oh not
you you were like oh yeah can't talk
with family member because different
room or something like that yeah right
right oh oh okay now I remember yes we
are doing Wellness stuff wow but you're
doing it in separate rooms right yeah so
you were like oh it's not much of a
family time cuz like we can't talk
during it right yeah yeah yeah yeah and
then I was like oh yeah okay now I get
what you're trying to say now okay yeah
that yeah yeah and then I I was like
well and I want to hear everybody's
opinion on this because I was kind of
confused when when crony got so confused
but I said like what do you mean like
can't can't you just you know do the the
family mind mind conversation thing like
Comm unicate for your minds like that's
a family thing right and she was like
what and I'm like what what what and
what what is the family mind thing
though like I'm just confused like
talking through your like don't you have
this connection what's it called again
in in English a telepathy telepathy
don't you have like a natural telepathy
um connection with your family that's
normal right like telepathy yeah like
you can't do it with anyone you can just
do it like with really really close
family like even though they're in
another room like it can be like hey mom
what's up yeah doing good you feel it
you feel
it I feel in in your brain waves and all
that like I I've done it really yeah
dude that's amazing yeah how do you do
it it's easy it's like uh just I don't
know you think about it and then that
you get the point
across sometimes it's kind of like vague
but mostly you got the point across yeah
foku yeah foku do it foku are a good
example I talked with them about it and
they were like yeah yeah totally like we
get it we do that all the time that's
the only reason why we can sync up so
much is because we have the family
therapy
uh family we have family therapy every
day so our relationship is really good I
mean surely can help having therapy but
they certainly do it yeah telepathy it's
really strong with twins but like you
can do it with your mom too yeah I mean
with like twins I think it's like strong
like I think there's definitely
connection going on by the way where are
you I'm I'm I'm I told you I'm in the in
the in the fancy beginning
area Okay I I just got out of my bunker
but anyway come out of your bunker come
here to the the the spawn
area sometimes indoors is so much better
but yeah like the whole like speaking
with your mind like how far does it work
like even when you're in a different
country does it
work it depends on your connection like
how strong it is I would say and like
how how much you've used it to that
point
to like you know if you're if you're if
you have a lot of experience with it you
may be better at it than if you barely
have used it until now so you like you
could probably try doing that if you're
in the same room and don't say anything
and you like you really concentrate
really hard and then it it could work
may need a few tries but if you're
suddenly in a different country and
you've never done this before cuz I
don't know how I I don't know I guess
because you live in the bunker
it's because you why you don't know
about
it no so of course you can't do it
naturally now out of nowhere that take
some
practice I mean like you know like when
I'm in the same room like with the
family member and like all I do is like
just stare at them they be like you
looking oh they may have heard it in
their brain yeah and that's why they
like think the same thing about you
maybe it's like you know they're just
uncomfortable they're like what like
what do you want yeah that that that
maybe it's a one-sided um telepathy that
they get your messages but you don't get
theirs like maybe you have some kind of
blockage in your head maybe go get that
checked
out how do I get it checked out like do
I go to a doctor like hello like my
telepathy is blocked can you like
unblock it yeah I mean you should go to
a psych what do you call them PS
psychiat yeah I mean sorry I don't want
to say like something's wrong with you
but like judging from our conversation
now it does seem like you're lacking
something really
basic I I have to go to psychiatrist for
this
are you like gaslighting me it's like
this serious
man like all I said was I don't I don't
have telepathy
and
PS I can't anymore I can't anymore this
was fun though because like especially
before we started talking about about
this publicly you were really just like
genuinely like yeah what do you mean
what what what what do you mean like you
seem so so innocent and like almost as
if you would believe
me oh you're B oh you're lying to me
what what of course I am how I
am okay oh my God I thought I was going
crazy dude this like the freaking line
test
dude like wait did you actually like low
key like think that something about what
I was saying could be
true I I was I mean no but like also at
the same time like but of course I'm
lying like what is she going on like
like is is it something different like
is she describing something differently
like what's yeah is because I'm I'm
Austrian and you know language barri I'm
just I just had issues communicating
what I'm trying to say um
yeah I mean like is there with twins
like for sure I agree it's not no no no
no it's not it's not it's not but
they're so sinked up like because that's
just because they spend every second
with each other like don't I feel like
you can do that like if you and me live
together for 5 years and we go we
everywhere together by the way huge head
just you too
your brain is so big wait how bad is my
fov oh it's not that bad I like my fov
that's brain is so amazing
gigantic
she
she okay Cy let's get to the to the gist
of it uh let's do it because we don't we
have limited time right because I don't
know if you know just another important
fact about life but we're all going to
die eventually you know that one
right dude why so suddenly
though you do know that one right I I
mean yeah we're all going to die
eventually like that's something I
always say but I didn't expect
to I you were lacking the telepathy
knowledge s far maybe you're also
lacking
that
just making sure dude like that that
made me question my life really hard I'm
glad I'm glad I'm happy to hear
that what what oh man it's so fun man I
should people more often oh
what's at all these cards oh
oh I'll take one move
slowly come on crony you can do it too
push push push push oh
man wouldn't it be cool though if you
could the fa fa therapy was a thing if
uh wait what's it called telepathy oh
those words are so
similar I mean yeah I mean that'd be
super cool would be really great yeah
basically you know I have a I have a a
perfect way of you doing that with your
mom that will actually work you want to
know
I don't believe you anymore but yeah
sure so when you're in those like
massage rooms
whatever when you lay down yes there's
there's an easy way you you take your
phone and you start a call a WhatsApp
call and then you can have a
conversation big brain did you ever
think of that huh CR
huh call her why would I ever do
that oh my God she's going to be so
angry at
me what what I mean you're going
together to do something nice why would
you be angry yeah because we're doing
something nice she doesn't want to be
interrupted a okay well that's kind of
sad that that's exactly why you can't do
uh telepathy and that's also the reason
why you should do
therapy I should go and see a
psychiatrist at the end
of that's moral of the story that's a
moral of the story I need to go see a
psychiatrist same same oh my God why is
he so angry he's like stomping and
moaning
moaning yo what the heck is this
thing you you're unaware of this too
like what how many basic things are you
missing in your brain
I I just I just have a lot missing in my
head I just have you not played
Minecraft in a
while um is this like part of a new
update or something yeah yeah I think it
did it come with the Sakura update I
think possibly it's so cute it's sniffy
sniffing you it's sniffing you out like
a duck Turtle thing
yeah have no chill today I don't know
like crony really um like easy to to um
you
know bro but like you've been doing this
since before the stream and like you
brought it up again so I was like wait
like this entrance isn't this
entrance amazing this I didn't make
this who made it narissa cuz she moved
in with me uh a while ago oh wow oh but
here it's just a normal
door even from the
outside I mean this is still
like I almost said abnormal door like
special door Abal this is you said this
is just a normal pretty you're you're
missing out on all the good updates the
new updates dude but all the soccer
trees are
taken taken what do you mean taken I
have I found a a Sakura Farm on the Ian
server like I made us so to say a farm
oh oh if you need if you're in need of
sakura trees or flowers I can show you
where the good stuff is at oh my
goodness M I would be actually delighted
to show you if you actually end up using
it then my dream will have come
true heck yeah yes PK are you interested
I am interested all right let's go but
but wait what happened with the beds
we're sleeping feet to feet now me and
Nissa touch and feet why feet to feet is
that her vein does she like sleeping
feet to feet with
people oh my God for free for free I
guess okay I know what's coming for me
when we go to the males me and
Nissa oh my God sleeping feet to feet
that's a new thing for me but I I will
not discriminate and
judge anyway crony today I hired you as
my maid basically cuz thank you you are
amazing and I want to say crony one
thing have you ever realized that I am
the only
one until recently because I I think I
was kind of forced or so but I'm the
only one who respects your boundaries in
all of H life have you noticed
yes yeah yes so you know that like
everybody went to the bunker Rooney and
I'm like the only one who continuously
like rejected to go
there because yeah you want your
privacy I've given up on my
privacy but still I wanted to respect
that cuz I respect you I respect the
out of you thanks man you're
welcome in return I'll show you you my
secret place after stream oh oh after y
there's a secret secret for real secret
place yeah there's a secret secret place
that I've been keeping it hidden ever
since my other place got found out oh my
God you're so serious about it oh my God
what so secret that that like people
that that that you couldn't show it on
stream that secret yes yes oh okay
okay okay but so basically I want you to
look at my boxes and I want you to cry
about how unorganized it is I mean it's
still
like some there there is some like you
know no oh my now the food is uh no I
don't have much food in the first
place you should get some food yeah oh
I'm okay I'm surviving I'm
surviving
nutrition you you'll be that you you'll
be the judge of that now for
me and this is just like a a precious
things box over here but yeah so ideally
I I would like you
to um organize my
damn please please I have a uh I
have a few more things I have my own
bunker here down
here just go go down yeah let me
your UND skirt nice
um there's a bit more stuff here that I
just gathered when um traveling the
lands of the
mines ooh pink petals oh yeah you can
have stuff like that if you want you
know I have plenty and I know where to
get more this will be your payment
today oh heck yeah
yay what is this place for oh it used to
be the this is quite interesting lore um
really really early on I think it was
still 2020 when we debuted you know and
the first few months I started playing
Minecraft and U my artist hook Papa
was uh on the server for like maybe one
day or so um because like you know we
were trying to to make that a thing uh
but yeah and then this is the bunker
that he built with some stor and I kept
it like exactly the same way just added
a few more
boxes yeah but he is he's only been on
the server pretty much like once and
never ever after since because uh this
is why we can't have nice things no just
[Laughter]
kidding yeah but that's why this place
exists and uh maybe so either I will
leave this absolutely to you but even we
extend this bunker and make a kiaha
bunker made by quason or I don't know if
you see more Vision upstairs to
like you know get some organization
going upstairs I don't know what you
want to what you think would be the best
way please make it your own I'll help
you thank
thank do you think you can help me in my
problems in organization I mean this
looks pretty organized already in a way
M wow that is that is a great compliment
coming from
you like Mis organization crony cuz or
Oro or or yeah I I'll I'll keep I'll go
with qu after that's better it's
better you like my nickname that I made
for you it's uh it's very fitting right
right fitting it is fitting fitting it
is it is
SP okay hey so like do you want me to
put all the gold here I want you to do
what you think makes the most sense oh
man oh man were there always two
chickens this is also nissa's doing
cute we can we can extend the uh
underground the bunker if you want if
you need more space the top
maybe no extension because that's going
to be difficult outside um I do have a
second house if you remember that's
right next door that I don't use I have
some more storage there actually a
little bit oh just a few more things on
if that's the case okay maybe I'll I'll
take
this okay then you know what let's have
completely different storage room but oh
okay do you want to see what I have in
here I I took a sh box so maybe we can
uh St Al on I think in this first floor
there's not really
anything where'd you go oh I'm in the
first floor where did you
go first
floor oh where she
hi hide here left left
no holy hell
what
my my
home
my it's okay we can fix it we can fix it
we can fix
it can you pick up my stuff though
should I wait how do you open your in
okay I don't know I don't know if I have
so much wait let me put out the
uh oh God that is incredible that is
perfect because we do have this like
remaking stream today like organizing so
yeah this it's also kind of like
up which just happened but yeah this is
really messed up it's great though like
this is this is this why why is there a
creeper yeah cuz there's there is light
why why the was a creeper there
that is a great question that is the
exact question that we should be asking
ourselves why can the sh not go into the
Sher I'll just put a couple of things in
there and you can um get oh that's yours
that is really I am
angry
right anger is consuming my body right
who was that anyway what's his name what
the what what is his audacity to
just like come here record a song no
that's not what oh that's what you
do releases a banger tape and
leaves he just comes here and destroys
part of my home CU he heard there's a
currently a recording of a remake going
on of Home Improvement or
what do you know Home
Improvement home dude you can't throw me
all these shows out there I don't know
I haven't even watch friends you know
the one with uh uh Tim Allen he goes
like when he question
something that's a good Kiara
I'm I'm
kidding oh man okay so I fixed the
stairs uh I there's the door I don't
know um I guess a lot of the wood was
actually destroyed huh
where are you anyway I hired you for for
doing something why are you not here I
know um I died you know why surprising
why would you die on the job like what
do we do about insurance do I have to
pay for that like what that's a problem
I mean that's a big problem you don't
die on the job yeah I mean I should
probably sue you honestly no I should no
I'm going to sue you that was not in the
contract you dying was not in the
contract I mean yeah I didn't really
expect it either but you know I didn't
really you know get the OA stuff going
on in your area sure thought my safety
would be
[Music]
guaranteed I see I see OA violation so
you know excuses excuses only
excuses excuses I
exuses we had had we had a thing we had
a we had a beautiful working
relationship and now it's just going to
be tainted yeah like man what are we
going to do about that eh we have barely
made progress and it's been like we
should have started 36 minutes ago we
started late and now this happens now
you're dead well you know part of that
is you know none of her faults cuz you
know YouTube decided to yeah hit the bed
yeah what the
hell yeah you I know what the hell right
they have it out for me I'm telling you
crony they hate me YouTube hates
me well you know I don't feel bad
YouTube hates
everyone so why why is it taking you so
long to get here uh because I died but
like where the hell are you I ended up I
ended up in the JP server and I had to
walk all the way back
that's why that's why you don't just
desert the I server you know you should
be living
here I honestly maybe I should I'm going
to okay did you see how did you see are
you watching the stream on the side did
you see what the hole looked like
because I fixed it
already you fixed it already yeah this
whole the the Lightwood is where I fixed
it and this light Stone and the you know
here some of your things in the white
Sher box
but in Shar she has a castle you have a
castle in the Japanese
server
I do where's the blue sheler box ah I
have it I have it I have it
here wait I have fresh kicks I think so
is this mine I think so oh wait where I
mind I have also normal diamond boots
that have no name I wasn't sure which
ones are yours oh that might be mine
then here you go oh okay I put the the
other things in the in the Sher box oh
bless okay this should be mine okay okay
Shar another I call it Japanese server
because it's just us moving into the
Japanese
server I have strong feelings about this
okay it's
uh it's you know it's different yeah
like cuz you know this is
like like our
simple
Abode not really I don't even know how
to like describe it like it's just very
like
cozy you mean here or there uh like you
know thean server overall is very cozy
exactly exactly we like to live in the
Stone Age
yes I mean we we're not living in the
Stone Age you
know it's different it's not that bad
just just exaggerating so what do you
want to do cron what's your plan
Quon okay I want to um I think in order
to make it more easily accessible for
you I might be good
to have this
like like have the chests
like well like I want it to be easily
accessible for you and like going you
know back here and then up seems kind of
tedious for you I mean compared to like
your thing this is nothing though cuz I
don't even have as many things as you do
no no no no no no no no no but like okay
uh let's see that's the W
corner I think we can like dedicate one
section of the room for just chests
maybe okay
uh let's
see we have an iron farm we have more
than just an iron farm we have a lot of
things here okay yeah we
do we have we have a um access to a a
Mesa biomi and a Sakura biomi even yeah
we have our own things yeah like we have
like unique things going on
man ah but man like a separate storage
room is nice to be very honest but it's
okay it's okay I can make I can make
this word why are you doing this to me
what why are you doing this to me what
what are you doing like why are you
sabotaging yourself again why are you
doing this I thought you came here to
work I this was not in my job
description it's breaking so
slowly hi
what you would just watch you would just
see this is an ocean
violation oh oi oi violation sound like
you're my OSI what do you who do you
think you are you don't even know what
an OSHA is this is serious oh my
God I have to go to court will we get
anything done crony tell me I I just got
to figure out whether or not we need a
storage room
oh man I think we should extend the
storage
room extend
yes okay uh which one do you think you
might not need like immediately like
some
something this one this
one this yeah both of these okay both of
these okay
SI and I'll just use my Shel box man so
far so far I feel like I'm on a
roll why are these candles on and these
are
[Music]
off oh sick I have food okay and then W
she placed it in the
air
yeah because your place is kind of you
know I have no
Choice what I think you built it on a
half block or something oh is this a
problem for you does this like trigger
something deep inside you um I mean it
does like trigger something but you know
that's okay I good Happy Feelings could
Trigger Happy Feelings yeah good good
Happy Feelings do you need
the the white cha box to transport even
more things at once
uh you know what that would be that
would be nice maybe have a lot of
shelter boxes
huh yeah yeah cuz I am I am you know
also every once in a while I go to the
nether oh so that's why there's nothing
in the nether huh no well what can I do
if you debuted second and I debuted
first okay well okay touche yeah you
know what that's true wait where did my
pickaxe go wait where' you put my
pickaxe oh I might have it which one is
it the one with eff efficiency 2 or
efficiency 5 efficiency five are you
sure yes or are you just ripping me off
very very sure very very 100%
sure
okay and I shall provide you with a Sher
box that I will throw it you know thank
you dude come to think of it this this
is a dangerous place to be working in
huh why like I almost got all my stuff
Tak I'm just kidding but like you know
it's dangerous here yeah I mean
partially I don't even know why like why
was there a creeper here that is the
real question cuz I thought wasn't there
an update where they made like enemies
uh spawn less like you don't have to
place as much
light but there's plenty of uh light
here and still came what the hell yeah
like I kind of don't understand why
that's not even my
fault it's not my fault I mean actually
actually that's not your fault than
normally I would say that is your fault
but this time it really isn't your fault
so not sure what happened well anyway
are you extending the let me check if
you yes I am oh no it seems like still
kind of crowded in here not going to
lie I mean I didn't know you want to
expand expand I thought you wanted like
more chests kind of thing oh I don't
know I feel like we should expand a
little bit maybe that way me this
way maybe you can like dig the path yes
hell yeah I'll dig around this
stuff hell yeah okay in the meantime I'm
going to go like
move stuff okay teamwork wow I thought I
I wouldn't have to lift a finger just
kidding that'll be boring anyway sounds
yeah I know that sounds
boring sorry crony I'm so sorry and you
don't want things to be boring now don't
you I I just thought that maybe this
kind of stuff would fulfill you I you
hat it things were boring I just wanted
to give you like a big opportunity to
like let out all these desires that you
have like you would you would need to go
to a kinesiologist with all that lack of
moving you know I definitely have to
yeah I probably
should yeah you
should okay I'll go after the stream
yeah okay and you go to the
psychiatrist that's great you go visit
the nutritionist and then the kinesi big
checklist so much stuff and I just need
to I I only have one professional to
visit in comparison so that's are you
sure what about family therapy to learn
about telepathy no that's
foko they're your therapists no they
they need family therapy you know what
I'm talking about you
[Music]
imagine yeah benefic they should
probably know about you know
how to keep a family
stable yeah they can show me yeah both
of us would know right I don't
[Music]
know I'm so
sorry did you want to Hung no no I'm I
I'm I'm I'm somewhat fulfilled and fine
I'm I'm I'm fine I'm fine I'm so I'm so
sorry it's it's okay whole life is is is
there for
me no I'm okay I'm okay I'm just kidding
okay I'm just joking my mom is watching
the
stream she's definitely watching she was
looking forward to
this oh really yeah does she like
Minecraft or something she oh she did a
lot on the server actually she helped me
create or like renovate uh phoenixon the
the town that I have
oh wait wait hold on put a torch here a
creeper might spawn here uh yeah okay I
guess I I can do that for
[Music]
you uh should I extend the ceiling cuz
there's a little part over here that's
higher uh yeah you I mean no like this
one's just for like uh so that you can
open the chest oh okay okay so maybe
around the
edges I do
that uh yeah yeah if you want to put the
chest like on the side or something yeah
I wanted crony Style
oh you want it okay okay
M if that's the case that's going to
be on on crony
style oh my
God only crony
style like you know any any other thing
I would have been like I I would have
went along with it but I I can't
no no oh no that's I was quite excited
about that one but
okay um I'll I'll put the
some
stuff did you pick that up I I don't
know where to put them for now I'm just
putting them like so that not they're
not in the middle of the room yeah yeah
yeah yeah okay uh
see nice
nice that was so good that was good
thank you oppa homeless style not
homeless style I'm not homeless I have a
hom not homeless wait do you have a kind
of worried about the L of torch can you
put more
torches sure sure of course I
can I I I'll I mean it's your home like
if it if there's a creeper and it blows
up your home I mean that's fine you know
I'm just a I'm just a contractor but
still
you
your I want to put it in the middle but
there's there's no
middle oh no there is ah there there
is oh there is okay
SI okay know your symmetry I'm so proud
of you yeah
yay should I move those other shulkers
over there too the blue one is yours
right ah you're like sorting things but
these are these are kind of sorted
already more or not really not
satisfyingly okay okay well Kiara I have
a task for you yes can you like space It
Out by one like the chest by one here oh
I can attempt
that uh the wooden chest you mean yes
the wooden chest but then that means I
have to first take out everything right
in order to move them sure or yes ma'am
wow that is like pretty lame but okay
I know but you know would Isn't it nice
having you know problem is my my
inventory is already so full let me like
put stuff away sounds like bunch of
excuses Kiara I no I think I still have
things from when you
died I I didn't I only had four things
when I died wait what did you empty this
chest already you incredible genius yes
I did like like one of the upper chests
yes wo
wo okay I know that that kind of like
threw me off that that overwhelmed me
there like damn I didn't expect that
girl like
sheesh an empty chest that's that's
that's crazy that's that's like crazy
insane sheesh girl God man thanks man
and now you're now you're going to make
me blush stop it I mean something like
that like wow I mean it's to it's
totally what I hired you for but like I
I don't I don't think there was actually
going to be any progress you know so oh
wow I mean I didn't know you were so
easy to
please you're calling me a genius like
damn maybe what's really happening here
is not that you're
cleaning or helping me organize maybe
you're actually just stealing my
things oh you caught me
there's a reason there's a reason why
I'm not like streaming my po ah see I
knew
it I knew it me
lady I knew it all along something was
iffy
like you can't fool
me I did though I guess no you'll be
paranoid if I'm actually taking your
stuff or not
h M I have to take
inventory very
slowly very SL
[Music]
take let's
see
dirt well you want me to move this one
space to the right yes please
okay ooh there's another shulker in
there the shulker I will place where the
shulkers
are nice potions oo organizing things y
see actually doing things look at that
wow okay and you were doubting
me I believe in your passion for this
stuff very
there are books books oh oh wait let me
put this but I'm going to put those
those back in but that doesn't mean that
they're organized right so you're going
to move them where they belong right oh
yeah obviously don't you worry okay okay
don't you worry your pretty little face
I got you going to be done call me
pretty pretty girl call me pretty
W what do I do guys what do I do I mean
you are pretty
pretty get
in wow that's not that impressive for
someone
who so amazing it's not really oh I'm so
good I'm so amazing man I love myself so
by the way c yeah yeah what are you like
you know like Christmas is getting
closer
yeah and like this T the season of
toly so like besides like crashing your
car against your own fans have you been
doing anything that's like like Jolly
joyful every day man amen bless like
what like what have you made Christmas
cookies yet because I have made
Christmas cookies and if you didn't any
then I don't know how you are living the
the Christmas spirit really I don't know
how that works that's
uh have you been
carolling
uh well actually about that I've been
kind of sucking off I haven't been out
carolling cuz I'm busy wa you actually
do Carol
no you're so gullible K I don't know you
didn't really seem like the type of
person who would go carolling to be
honest and I'm not I'm not so I was
like CR
[Music]
caroling yeah kind of weird it's
okay I see I see how it is it's okay I'm
still I'm still normal I I still have
some of my sanity left in
me are you saying people who care all
don't have sanity
hey hey hey hey hey I didn't oh I didn't
say that I I say such thing that is
messed up I would never messed
up man that is messed up I can't believe
you would say such a thing but people
actually Carol like in in North America
cuz like I I don't think I've ever heard
of anybody carolling in
Austria I don't think that's a thing at
all that's because you don't go caroling
no but like I've never been caroled I've
never opened a door to people singing at
me randomly some songs that I don't want
to hear at the time that I'm busy where
I really don't want to see car or not do
you want to be Carol or not no not at
all I don't care about that at all like
why would I want to be Carol you you you
almost sounded so disappointed though
like oh they won't Carol me CU it
sucks CU they hate me man no I
don't think it exists in
Austria or in Germany
even it's not terribly common but it
does happen in US
[Music]
CA I see
I it's it's rare for me to even have
like you know the the Girl Scout cookies
or Boy Scout cookies to like come by and
be like hey I got cookies we don't have
that either we don't have that either
man I mean we do we do have it but it's
kind of rare yeah
yeah you know you know how excited I was
when I was in America uh this this year
was it this year I think it was this
year yeah it feels pretty recent still
in summer I was in America to record
something at uh the the the pineapple
motion capture for pineapple at am's
place and then at that time it was the
first time ever that I experienced
something that I only ever watching like
American sitcoms and so
on a little girl with like her parents
there standing there too uh with a
little table selling self-made lemonade
oh
dude and I was so excited I was so
excited I said am please we have to I I
need to I need to buy the lemonade I
need to experience it so we did get some
lemonade and it was pretty
oh okay but that's fine it was about the
experience I thought I thought the story
was going to go in a different direction
like oh it was pretty good and then that
was it right it was all right okay was
quite all
right I mean but like you know the
effort is like pretty impressive right
yes it's cute it's so cute and it's
surreal it was kind of surreal seeing it
I yeah wait I don't think I heard it
like how much was she selling for ooh I
I don't I didn't say it cuz I don't
remember did I say guys back then did I
mention
it I put like dollars probably more than
a dollar maybe more like oh my God yeah
inflation
bro what happened to all the cheap stuff
M there is no more cheap stuff why is
this growing so much I thought it was
going to give me
light what light this oh you need to add
bone meal to
it bone I think I have some let me go
find
it lemonade and dis
economy highway robbery for real for
real bone block do
I oh let me get all these potions and
put them in the potion
chest and I guess let's take the Bon
don't be that mind
blown there is yet to come there is more
mind blown about why is it this one oh
okay I have so many splash potions of
Fire Res or potions of fire resistance
left over I think from either the Wither
fight or the other
fight the oh it doesn't fit
crony okay we put it in another place no
I don't want
to well there's no choice
Kiara why don't these stack
crony can we write a formal complaint to
Minecraft
um I don't
think I think they'll be pretty
busy do you think They Don't Care About
Us does does do the Minecraft developers
not care about their Community say that
I didn't say that I didn't say that I'm
saying that does MOJ not give a
about
me I mean like you know it's not about
you okay it's about me no it's not it's
not sometimes it's not but I speak about
for all of us I speak for all of us GR
[Music]
you guys know I'm joking right everybody
knows making sure CU sometimes it seems
like you have to make very sure people
understand a
sarcasm sarcasm is a dead humor
nowadays oh why is it not a mom's hum
[Music]
humor mom's humor yes cuzz you said
that's
[Music]
humor
[Laughter]
humor so
anyway um can you like bring me more
stuff if that's okay yeah yeah I I I you
know what I just did I went out of my
way cuz I had one empty potion bottle I
went out of my way and brought it over
to ena's potion place because I thought
she could use it although she's when's
the last time she played Minecraft yeah
I don't know I don't freaking know I'll
bring you
something I'll yeah bring you these
things even if they don't fit in my
inventory let's
see and we need we need more boxes
anyway right we need more chest what if
I make you some chests
too you can
yes I
will wait let me think I need where's
all the wood I don't want to make it out
of this you have wood down there don't
you wood yeah wood there's plenty of
wood I'm going to turn the coals into
coal blocks so that's going to take a
less play
enough you little
shits yeah well the thumbnail did have a
lot of
chest nice
chest wait what oh there we just are
nice
M
why I
agree I think they're so funny they're
so
funny but I I dug out this really old
old fan art I I typed in uh my fan art
hashtag and yours and there was sadly
barely
anything but a little there was a little
bit and that hella I used for the
stream hello you want uh all of them to
be like free rows right oopsie
um yeah since there were like uh three
rows to begin okay did I see where the
heck did the wooden block go yeah that's
fine I'll just put it right there oh oh
yeah I took one out oh it's okay it's
okay cuz yeah that's that's what the
things here all for right to use them
right I mean yeah but I thought you'd
like place them back to where they
belong no because I need I'm not done
you know oh my God done I took another
one oh you took another one out okay
that's fine that's whatever that is that
forgivable oh yeah that's completely
forgivable I'm messing up your your
whole system it's okay that's okay I can
live with that that's completely fine I
can we need more CR K collapse I agree I
agree so people were pretty surprised
when I said I on my schedule I am having
a collab with
cron what it so surprising people
thought it was like really like sudden
and random and it kind of is because
like we we didn't really collap much in
our time you know it's true is true it's
true but uh yeah we recently had a nice
conversation and uh I thought I want to
continue that you know yeah I do
too what is our what is our uh collab
name we don't need one not everything
needs a collab name I've recently come
to
understand takes a it's you know it's
too it's too hard it's too hard to come
up with these things all the time you
know well people do call us Su dial
Sundi yeah like oh that's
cool yo that's a that's a pretty radic
you never heard that before Sund dial
yeah I mean yeah I have but you know
yeah that's pretty cool it sounds cool
yeah it sounds pretty
dope I got to put all the gold and
everything in this spot okay I got
this this this and then a little bit of
this so with that I I I I ask
you artists
kindly to draw more
quason and waa art although this one
like it was
even it was separate artworks but from
the same artist in the same style so it
was perfect you know yeah exactly it's a
beautiful I think I think
kindly where the heck
okay I don't know what to do here
there's like an
awkward let me I know what to do I know
what to
do um
uh some brand new in here cuz that
belongs
[Music]
here oh my God it's organizing it's
being organized yes oh yes yes and I
have my own bunker now kind of cuz like
there's more and more chests that that
should hopefully hopefully be plenty oh
my God this is so exciting yeah really
does it excite you it is so exciting
yeah
organization
oh so
good I'm happy that I can give you this
Joy yes thank you very
much I'm very
happy I'll move this
around this
and so
colorful maybe I'll bring the things
from my second house over here
la
[Music]
she still didn't see my second floor did
she cuz she died at that moment well
yeah now I'm scared to go up there not
that much honestly that place is
actually relatively organized so I could
keep the things the way they
[Music]
are what if I
die H what if you die if I die
again then I will will honestly doubt
your motivation to be
here okay okay I see you I see
you no just kidding just kidding you
know what you know what you know what
what what what what do you want to say
kind of treatment with this kind of
level with this with this level of
treatment and no regard for your fellow
worker like I don't know what I'm going
to do yeah that's the thing is you're
misunderstanding something here
completely yeah misunderstanding what I
feel like I'm completely you said fellow
worker fellow worker oh I'm a slave now
okay no you're my mid you're my maid
understand that and then we will
understand each other you know what you
know what you do know that Maids can
quit too right that's right you won't
quit I fire you oh well you know what I
fire
myself can you please wait until the
stream is over what
well yeah sure okay okay thank you so
much thank you I appreciate that thank
you of course that's really nice of you
no I'm pretty
nice that that's why I like you so much
you know oh thank you but I'm still
getting fire I'm still firing myself no
I'm I'm quitting you no I quit no no I
quit I quit you no that's not how it
works H This
Woman This Woman This Woman woman what
are you what are you trying to say this
woman you're a woman woman I'm trying to
say you're a woman are you not huh you
have a problem with that yes yes I am I
mean oh my
God falling
apart what's falling apart everything
everything is falling apart everything
we worked so hard for I mean I didn't
work for this you work for
this
okay you're really you're really
confusing me here but
okay sorry I'm just Tak up the gold it's
kind
of like what do you mean this like all
the gold you have like what are you
talking
about no no no don't worry about it all
the gold the gold what what happened
with the
gold it's gone wait I made so many
chests down there there but
[Music]
like uh maybe I should put all the
valuables here that's right
okay this down cuz I'm actually out of
wood crony seems like it unless you put
some more wood somewhere else yeah I put
all the wood here I I oh that W the not
Uh planky
Wood yeah why is the I don't really like
that like why is that shouldn't that be
in the same box kind
of I
mean they're like unprocessed and these
are like a little more on the processed
side you know I don't know you don't
like it it's okay you can always
reorganize it that's okay yeah but like
then I have to lift a finger you know
and that's kind of like I mean you're
already lifting a finger so that's
okay no it's fine um I do think the wood
should be with the
wood but I will I got I got you give me
one second oh she is the the one and
only the truest of them all the
goat I am pretty she she gets it I I
always get it okay I have
completed this
section Al now I see
something that I feel
like yeah whatever it's fine it's fine
put all the valuables uh isn't this
nice so nice I I'll help you now but
like what what should I you have not
been helping me no I have I have I feel
like I have been totally helping just
need to figure out what to sort into
what what do I have a lot of oh this
stuff what else would you put in a chest
that has
Saddles Saddles um probably like put in
like bunch of Tools
Leather what do you mean leather tools
and
Saddles tools yeah tools like Saddles
and like horse armor and everything H
horse armor okay horse armor I can
understand I don't really have much of
that though why did I seem like you had
quite a bit though where did I put
it yes I made a
mistake the Box won open now it should
open yes okay there we go see we fixed
it we did it I did it yeah yeah yeah we
did it
mhm I mean you did it yeah you want to
be very particular yes you
did you did sometimes you have quite a
bit of mom energy I like
that all of a
sudden I was feeling that when I heard
your morning voice before the stream you
guys didn't even hear her morning voice
aw too
bad it was really nice her morning voice
was like kind of giving me mommy Vibes
like not like yes sorry Mommy no but
like
mom mom please it's not a face making
this weird you're making this
weirder it's like it's not a mommy boys
but but you know the more you try to
elaborate on it like you know it gets
more and more fishy you know no
no I have a lot of wood here in this oh
like dark oh yeah there a special dark
oak log do you know the dark oak the
really dark wood yeah should I make its
own chest for it where are you are you
changing the wood
organization yes I am where are you
leaving them in the corner here or are
you putting them elsewhere I'm going to
put them
in around this area give me one
second okay
done
[Music]
oh I have to remember my mom is watching
the stream she kind of always I always
have like I I I honestly I forget about
it and don't really worry about it most
of the
time but thanks for reminding me I
should have that in my head all the time
now you're paranoid yeah yeah and your
mom's going to judge you every single
time you swear or something nah not at
all she swears even worse than me
[Laughter]
probably that's where I got I got it
from my mommy I got it from from my
mommy hey where' you get that saring
from was that a was that a uh sigh song
I think so yeah circling back to the
Sigh
only only crony
style it's it's not going to
work it just worked it it really did not
work it really did it really work not it
really did not it's uh really lacking
I'm Sor can't deny it I think everybody
would agree I think I'm denying it but
it worked it kind of it really didn't
work okay you do you
qu okay see see it's it's getting so
organized yes now that the wood is with
the
wood yes the wood is with the wood now
it's now it's pretty nice right it's so
nice it's
beautiful surpris God don't want to like
organize this
no cuz you're organizing it yeah I'm
doing it I don't know is this the same
thing Birch
oh Bruce wait
what don't don't worry about it I'm what
are you doing organizing somewhat maybe
honestly wood might need two
chests I would two chests cuz there
eventually will be more I feel like and
that I have even more
actually maybe bamboo can maybe saplings
and bamboo can be its own
chest okay I'm going to put all the
armor stuff here for now this this this
okay
okay this can go
together weapon stuff two cool stuff
goes there does this make chat Happy by
the way does this feel good watching
finally finally an organized waa
Minecraft
space yeah what is
this what is this it's like a completely
different place it does yes I'm in
different H
okay do you have a place for sandstone
sandone
Sandstone you have it mixed with other
things don't you what is this crony what
who are you is this really you yes I'll
take it I'll give it its own
box you'll give it its own box yeah I
will watch
me watch me watch me watch me whip watch
me
na watch me whip whip watch me na
why watch me watch me watch me
watch mom obnoxious your mom is
watching the stream what would she think
it's probably also really confused
what's wrong with me
today what's
happening so very hper today M I'm just
so excited to be with you
crony Jes
to like
jeez are you not I mean yeah but like
it's sounds a little
scary I'm so excited to be
here
okay I thought you you like hearing that
I it is it is uh very energetic it's
nice thank you yes of course man
yeah
okay okay I'm going to put these oh
she's going to be so impressed with my
[Music]
actions where did I are you sure I think
you will love what I'm
doing where did the books go
there I I do not appreciate the saddle
being here so I'm taking that I didn't
work that yet okay a work in progress
okay do we say chankla or
shankla what do you know
sh
Chang
no
Chang Chang CH Chang like the sandal to
hit people with oh I have not heard of
that before what what's going on is this
another like telepathy
moment yeah it must be crazy crony has
been sheltered I
think I have been pretty sheltered
unironically
yes I mean it wasn't a bad life all I
watched was fairly odd parents and we
watch that
too yeah you know what I've heard this
the other day that there was a live
action of
bad what yeah there's a live action of
that but I I think I think I heard it's
really bad Fairly Odd Parents yeah the
live action of Fairly Odd Parents oh God
like with real actors
yeah hers really
bad oh yeah it sucks oh yeah Drake Bell
was Timmy
Turner oh that does not sound good at
all oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's a it's a thing
it's a
thing I'm I'm kind of disappointed not
going to
lie I I don't think it ever needed a
live action so can just continue living
your life with ignoring
it sorry I gave you the
knowledge dude when when was that
released
I'm not sure do you guys
know do you guys know wait this is I'm
so
confused I have so much of this see but
isn't it easier to organize now that I
put it like
this sure
2011 oh 201 so much more organized I
know thank you so
much
uh what about like random stuff like
fences and maybe I'll should
I I'll make one chest for fences and
rails and ladders that's pretty similar
like a terrific idea thank you thank you
and maybe even trap doors yeah see
you're like having your own ideas now
about what you want yes I think with my
own brain
wait where I'm going to put some this is
just I'm guessing this is your random
stuff box I I'll put some stuff here you
you figure random stuff box you figure
oh yeah that's a random stuff box yeah
it seems like it
enjoy thank you thank
you oh my goodness there is order there
is harmony are we going to put anything
like are we going to leave anything at
the top
floor um uh it depends on what you want
to
leave you want to leave maybe like AR
arm n important things I guess like arm
but
even whatever we run out of space for
downstairs I I don't think we'll run out
of space downstairs
really H like there are a lot of chests
here so I don't think we'll run out to
be very very honest maybe just like
really common things like a second chest
of wood and food and
armor okay
ooh oh yeah stone stone is also still
upstairs I guess we're keeping Stone
upstairs there also a couple more empty
Sher chests
here I'm I'm getting there I'm getting
there just just because like I already
filled up uh
the space
mostly down here with the suer chest so
yeah
maybe yeah I mean at the end of the day
like you know as long as I'm giv like
General instructions I'll be
flexible what you want
okay we can keep those remaining Sher
chests upstairs perhaps and put either
nothing in it and keep them for
traveling purpose like when I want to go
you just like put them in the chest or
something I I guess for just shulker
boxes but then I forget about them you
forget about them
no like you forgot about
me when when did I ever forget about you
see you even forgot about forgetting me
oh my
God more gaslighting let's go oh let's
go
okay imagine imagine my my feelings guys
I
can't it's unas lighting pretty sure
that'd be
[Music]
exciting
um damn this place is going to be like
so empty after this though I know that's
why I was like what do you want to keep
what do you not want to keep cuz you
know cuz that concern which is
very I guess we got to have at least one
chest of random things because I don't
know where else to put the extra
lles I guess into the
ocean no no why would you release them
into the ocean cuz I don't even I don't
know why I caught them I don't need them
oh
so they're so cute you can't
just yeah okay then I guess I'll keep
them in the bucket forever yeah that
sounds like a wonderful
idea wow
okay if that's how you treat your
axelos am
I I don't want to know I mean unless you
decide to have an aquarium for it or
something yeah H I did make a frog um
what do you call it
terrarium maybe it's about time I make
something for the two exra lles that I
have
Hello does it have to be
[Music]
that that there
nice nice nice nice uh conon how's are
you good with
time good with time still good still
good few more minutes
just I noticed the potential that I
didn't
use what potential the potential in the
time
joke don't don't you dare don't you dare
do you must so sick so sick and tired of
it stop I can
imagine which is exactly the reason why
I should say
more I will
cry is the qu W going to
cry emotional I'm I'm going to be so
emotional I'm going to break down in
fact a little baby yeah yes yes
yes oh my God I'm so sorry gry I don't
know what's wrong I'm I'm I'm just I'm
just having fun you know I'm just
enjoying our time together me
too
okay now I'm going to
cry stop crying you're you're so you're
all over the place today what's wrong
with you wake
up
I'm just um I guess I'm just trying
to I don't know make make you en enjoy
your time with me and oh I'm already
enjoying my time dude it's so this is so
great organizing oh okay I
love where's the
you I mean we we we love we love
organize
love you okay we I I love what yeah I
don't oh no that's too strong that's too
strong of a word I'm too shy you know
love is a strong word like I don't use
it you know like I don't even I only use
it with myself that's fine that's I I
totally agree with that yeah I love love
love love it's a strong word love
love love love we love love I can say
love ah love you don't have a problem
with that word yeah
love oh love
love all
love love love what are we doing I don't
know okay dude like I just get kind of
embarrassed whenever I say
you know yeah I don't even say it with
my family and you got some issues
girl I got to go see a
psychiatr good that good good good that
you're are aware of it that's I'm the
biggest step I feel so enlightened like
from the stream really yeah I just
realized that I really need maybe you
should pay
me
baby baby you know what just maybe
maybe I don't need any payment maybe
with this I'll realize that I'll have
to psychiatr exactly you're welcome
crony thanks now
I'm now I'm
dramatized you weren't you before I mean
yeah
probably you're everything you're so
right everything everything that you're
saying is right it's just me I'm the
problem I realize yeah you are yeah I'm
the problem it's always me mhm I wish I
wish I can do something about
it you can't I can't but that's
okay no crony I'm sorry it's over for me
no you're
fine it's over no it's I'm sorry about
what I said you're pretty fine over
you're pretty fine you didn't have to
add that last
part it's hard for me you know
like saying
things the language that you don't mean
yeah that is pretty difficult yeah I'm
not pretty fine I'm not fine that's just
what you're trying to say when you think
you're fine but you're not really cuz
like you you
know I'm trying to do the meme but I
don't know how what what she says
like I understand that you were trying
to what what is that when you when you
when they say you no when you say you're
fine but you're not really
fine you know it sounds like you're
trying to do the the kid meme
instead kid me like yeah BR when you
have the dream when you when you do the
when you do the dude what's that you
have a you have the dream they ask you
how you are and you just have to say
that you're fine when you're not really
fine but you just can't get into it
because they would never understand
that's the one thank you you cheated
dude no it was in my brain all along no
you cheated you're a
cheater could
you how could you
cheat how could you cheat like
that oh now you're going to
cry yeah yeah yeah what are you going to
do about
it going to I'm going to
cry well cry harder I can't
hear
no I'm okay C I'm fine C cry no I'm fine
but I'm not
C I'm fine by the way people you should
know that we are you know just messing
around this pleas yeah have to do
occasional disclaimers just in case
every once in a while every once in a
while every once in a while make it
really
clear yeah we are confused as well I
think but you know our brain is just
like roaming around yeah oh I have a
good idea I have the perfect tools for
doing what I want to to this
plan excuse me yeah that's what I
said why because I have the better
things oh damn what is this doing
here organize the
food heck yeah hello wooho for real are
you good with time though for real for
real I still got few more minutes okay
and why does this not connect I thought
you can connect a lantern to a
chain uh yeah you can why does it not go
here not enough space ooh the ceiling is
okay okay I'll make the ceiling higher
after all
Quon yeah you can do that just a one
block it's okay
okay I hope nothing will leak from
above and if it does then you know God
spe it will be fine it'll be
fine does oh does that still work then
oh that's a fence right guys
probably
fence that can
stay no the chest what what's the chest
is it f it's a probably okay okay then
we add one more EO it was even the right
color okay now we don't have to feel so
claustro claustrophobic Santa
claustrophobic is claustrophobic the
word for having a phobia of Santa
Claus excuse me
CLA is it not
it's I mean you're so right so right
thank you you're you're so right oh you
make me so
happy
just surely there's a word for that
right though right right surely being
scared of Santa yeah I feel like there
probably is I don't know just say you're
sonophobics
[Music]
is it
not I mean what you think it
is it's just a little
too well long it's not like not like
you're going to Bonk your head cuz we're
all the see size in here I might no
you'll be
finea by the way all the armor stuff is
here so if you like to move them
upstairs you can
oh oh you have the horse armor there
okay see you do have plenty of horse
armor look at that that's
crazy what are you laughing about this
time because I think I just took the
thing that you later on Realize oh that
I guess that goes there and then I put
it there while you were talking about
it how could
you I read your mind maybe we are
twins you think
so no then maybe we can use
telepathy that's what I was saying but I
wish it was
true but I I don't think we are related
at
all yeah it would be crazy if we were
related you know that would make things
kind of crazy kind of crazy actually
dude dude that'll be sick
D are you making fun of me are you
making fun of me no no no right now it's
just making fun of
dudes
dudes how could you that would be so
sick dude that would be so radical dude
radical is that what they say yeah
that's what they
say is there no one tile
picture one tile picture well oh yeah
there should be it's not letting me make
one what what if I what about a a six
tile picture do something that's
actually going
to oh like you'd have to like remove the
sign here in order for it to
work I like this
sign I know but sometimes you need
sacrifices what what the
what the
why is this still W what what sizes
do we have for pictures what's what's
the availability pretty sure there's a
one one by one like as long as you block
it off with the Torches like it should
work
theoretically no it just goes under the
Torches oh
what maybe maybe tried several different
times maybe no okay maybe maybe not a
torch maybe just like you know stone
blocks yeah
sure
[Music]
wait are you going to use the shulker
boxes as a way for storage rather than
having chests
or yeah I guess at least the ones are
down here
[Music]
here oh there it is there it is guys hey
that was so diff so much work yeah what
a pain in the ass
man at least it looks beautiful it does
it's so small I don't know what it is I
got to look at it from the back but the
lamps are blocking it it which is also
an artistic
Choice maybe you should change maybe
have revisions to your artistic choice
if it's getting in the way me thinks um
no no maybe
not I
see understandable you know that's
that's also a choice that you can make
oh there's another one what is this one
this one's actually higher so you can
actually see what it
is
soup soup maybe it's soup do you like
soup crony what's your favorite soup
chicken noodle soup chicken noodle soup
what a coincidence I am a chi no uh
Phoenix so you think you're a chicken
no so in the end you just think you're a
chicken you're not a phoenix or anything
you're just chicken no I said I'm a
phoenix you're a
chicken okay you said it okay Cy okay
Cy I'm ending our friendship after
this amen
amen hallelujah I didn't say amen I said
a hey man I said hey man not a man dude
that's my oh hey man what's why why is
there so much hay
here you know that's a thing that is
like a German
meme uhhuh like imagine walking into
this
room and you say whoa there's a lot of
hay
here cuz there's a lot of hay here and
it was so random and you're like why is
there so much hay that's a German meem
so it's like Dad jokes all around no no
no it's maybe a mom and dad
joke a mom and dad joke yeah what was
just a dad like not only dad can be
involved oh okay it's like everyone
every Mom and Dad yeah it's a very um
inclusive show a family matter okay
yes big Family
Matter y look at this this so beautiful
holy moolly
y
yay thanks to you
Quon of course man I'm so happy to help
we may have had like a rough
start today but um wow yeah but it
worked out and look at this it's so
beautiful now saying you're
done I kind of have to go but you know
it's not done it's not done that's fine
that's fine that's fine you did plenty
you did
plenty I will have to add some finishing
touches honestly okay and then and then
you come back in and you'll be like hey
I want this here I want I want it over
there then you can do exactly that it'll
be
likeing well let me check then uh this
looks Messy as but okay um okay you
know I just said I just
said holy
cron
[Music]
well well it's kind of nice watching you
do
[Music]
this what a blessing it is to have
you oh why do I have this gold wait you
have one chest here gold oh my God see
now you're organizing I'm so proud of
you I've been organizing all this
time here I'm adding more get charcoal
you want charcoal cuz you put coal in
here too heck
yeah look at you now you're organizing
your chests now and hopefully it'll
continue for a very long
time I'll consider
it you'll consider it I'll try but yeah
I think no it's at least good to have
like a like a base
uh like an organized base to go off of
cuz my problem was always
like when it's already so messy it's
kind of difficult
to get it organized I need I need
someone like you my mom I think tried
once to organize my place
but I
mean was L there was still room for
improvement AKA Home
Improvement and you're
damn you're so like specific no cuz I
recently I've been binge watching Home
Improvement for the past two months or 3
months my God maybe two months
yeah dude you should watch like Pimp My
Ride or something yo I used to watch
that
yo man when they pull like a wh
pool on the back of the car or like like
how are you ever going to use that I
would use it let's
go like oh heck yeah Whirlpool but what
am I going to use that for you know or
like a disco what what did they do do
what kind of stuff did they do beside
whirl pools disco balls like fridge and
then all that
stuff Bridge fridge a fridge the fridge
the fridge and then like they made their
trunk into like a big boom box or
something really loud loud gaming
setup TVs Xbox well that's not even that
impressive but
sure deep frying in the passenger seat I
I doubt that but yeah that was really a
cool show wait so you watched like MTV
back in the day like that I watched some
MTV yeah yeah do you know the show where
um there's like uh one one dude or girl
who is a fan of like one specific artist
singer or actor and they're like so
obsessive and they really wish they
could date that celebrity but of course
they can't so they get like threee
people in who also like that artist
singer
usually and um they dress up like them
and they prepare a set they sing a song
everybody gets like their own little
stage that is like themed after that
celebrity and then they all three of
them perform and the the obsessive
fanatic watches that and then chooses
their new partner According to which one
was the most like their celebrity
crush like they would have like a LaVine
lookalikes and stuff like that
and it was pretty cool I enjoyed
watching that that's kind of a cool
premise honestly yeah they had some good
ideas back
then what happened now it doesn't exist
anymore yeah it doesn't exist anymore
damn no I I watched this documentary
about how MTV basically kind of like
died and then revived itself and then
died again
cuz like they used to only play music
and then they realized like cuz like
they had like 5% of shows that were not
music and then they realized that those
were kind of the most popular after a
while after after I guess it was like
pretty common to to listen to music in
other ways too I guess and MTV wasn't
necessary anymore so they increased
those kind of weird show shows more and
more that were not even related to music
and
then the few times they would like bring
out the music related show it would flop
all the time so they eventually
completely
stopped yeah they lost the music but
then didn't they like they try it
again like what does MTV do now what
plays on MTV now I don't I don't have a
TV so I don't really know
anymore do you have a TV like where you
watch actual cable TV oh I just watch
YouTube nowadays Netflix yeah and all
these streaming platforms like aside
from that like no I
don't right uh probably still reality
shows yeah I guess
so I guess so well I guess so I don't
like reality TV shows I think like when
I was younger when I was a teenager I
still could kind of like enjoy it
partially cuz I watched stuff like Tina
tequila Tila Tila Tequila not tatina do
you know Tila Tequilas or flavor of Love
Tila Tequila dating show the the Flavor
of Love dating
show
yeah the Flavor of Love was like oh God
such a ride such a terrible
terrible
ride sounds like there's a lot of story
behind that yeah it's it's yeah like the
Flavor of Love was basically some really
old
rapper who was like small
looking but he was like 50 or 60 and
then he has this like apparently he's a
famous rapper I didn't know him but he
had this uh mansion and he got like 20
20 hot young chicks to fight for his
love but like pretty much everyone was
only there for the clout and for you
know being on TV and for money and fame
but they all like act as if they're so
into him Flavor Flav yeah and oh it was
so cringe all the time like these
ladies M acting and him being
like that that reminds me I did watch
like a reality like show where it's like
you know um featuring what was it
parison and it was her like choosing her
best friend and she I watch that too my
best friend yeah but did I want if
anybody of those best friends she still
is in contact with probably not I really
doubt that like everyone was there for a
cloud I really really doubt it
yeah that's so sad that's the sad
reality of reality
TV yeah but then you know she gifted one
of the people like a pink diamond or
something I was like
damn oh that's what gets you that's what
impresses you a pink diamond I mean yeah
that's pretty cool I see okay and now
write that down everybody write it down
write it down pink diamond oh no no no
no no not like that no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no you don't
want a pink diamond you want a blue
diamond there's a blue
diamond I mean probably can just put
like food food
dye or
Diet pink blue diamond is basically just
the you because you're you're a blue
diamond
Co oh oh stop
it cuz you're such a gem and you're
blue and you're like you're like topaz
oh where am I
yeah wow yeah yeah I'm so flattered like
you're just throwing the same totally
original uh I'm pretty original you're
right thank you you're too kind wow mhm
yeah okay well I have to go but you know
before that look at this look at look at
all the weapons I put oh yeah yeah I saw
I was watching you Armor's downstairs
yeah I
mean I would I would
probably see you know what you can do
exactly that as long as it gives you a
basic guideline of how you want to
organiz yeah and satisfaction and all
that
right damn yeah you gave me a good base
for real for real like and a good like
how to say k um a good reason or like
you know you gave me a reason to do this
in the first place because I or I gave
us a reason cuz I invited you but I
wanted us to do something together and
this was the one thing I could think of
crony and it's beautiful yes it's so
much more organized
now gorgeous gorgeous you have a talent
for this thank
you
damn I'll like finish up organizing
later on and then you'll be like w
crowny came by wow W maybe in the one
while you're you know doing the wellness
thing maybe give it a try the the
telepathy thing just just try yeah I'll
try my mom's going to judge me so hard
but but I'll try no she you just why
does she have to even know you just like
try to think really hard and get the the
the thought over to her head if it gets
across then it worked if it doesn't then
she doesn't even know that you tried
something yeah right
right okay oh I got to go my mom's like
Oh no no granny I'm going to miss you
don't go I've been having a good time
don't leave me I know what am I going to
do without you it's okay we'll like
stream real soon oh really yeah will we
when are we going to stream we'll stream
okay cool we'll stream stream together
you mean not sep right
obviously that would be a good way to
get out of like collabing with me you
know I mean dude that's really messed up
yeah let's coll collab together
separately stream together separately
yeah yeah yeah yeah you let me can you
stand next to me I want to take a
picture of
us next collab together
separately yeah on a different game oh
oh it's so it's so cute how you're still
like wearing your your your outfit from
the sports festival I know I'm pretty
quirky CKY like that aren't you just
quirky like that okay thank you I have
the picture um my dear made
crony you have made my my dreams come
true
somewhat a lot I'm going to put some can
I open this no I want to why why is
Minecraft like this huh then I'm going
to put wool blocks maybe and make a
carpet here I'm going to I'm going to
make the the floor
the same
flooring eventually oh nice oh I like
that right not so mixed like what the
hell what is these walls though like
disgusts me it just disgusts
me oh we'll work on it well there's
still stuff to do if you if you ever
feel like it you can try to improve it
if you're free if you have nothing to do
in Minecraft I will I honestly I haven't
been doing Minecraft cuz I feel like
I've done everything almost oh so wait
so
uh W you call a person who lays carpets
like I'm doing right now uh Carpenter
exactly exactly you heard it guys I've
been telling you all along nobody
believes me but this is a carpenter I am
the carpenter right now thank you crony
for finally confirming the things that
people don't understand allegations
beating the allegation ations
woohoo thank you okay this is all I
needed all right you gave me the tools
and I will be using them you gorgeous
gorgeous blue
diamond you you you giant
head you giant head no you giant head I
took a picture of your head what you
have a picture of my head yeah I took a
picture ear you're in the Stream oh okay
I found
IRL oh no no no no dude that's so that's
kind crazy that's that's messed up kind
of crazy I throw hands you go take care
of that huge head with your facial
massage you know maybe you can get rid
of that huge head thank you you too with
your ye big head
yeah my my
never heard that before outside of
GTA thank you
Quon have a nice time take treat
yourself treat yourself you treat
yourself no you treat yourself you you
go to
kinesiologist why I'm I'm not trying to
learn
Chinese what what what okay anyway bye
it's a joke in German we say not Chinese
but Kish with
K kind of more or less Kish yeah it's a
joke it's a German
joke that's the worst one of the
stream I'm I'm working on my comedian
skills okay not everyone can
land all
right but that was that was a e
efficient efficient productive that's
just you sou for Germans that's true
yeah some people in Germany they say
chines right don't they that's kind of
crazy k k I have to go yeah go go go I'm
just talking to myself byebye I guess
I'll go to or read super I'll read super
chats byebye okay okay
byebye
byebye bye-bye let's stream again real
soon yes yes next week no just kidding
too busy week yeah and everyone be sure
to check out kiora's new song sleep
talking oh my God thank you so much and
Callie and K's new fire and I we so came
out today thank you thank you wow the
plugs W yeah I know I got you can we
plug something of yours no okay bye bye
bye never really sing that song
that she gone she
gone I'm all alone
now that was nice of her to plug the
songs yeah today my song with uh uh uh
cie came out in case you guys didn't see
it's on her Channel but it's also on my
channel wow amazing how that works uh
yeah it's like I guess it's like also on
my Spotify probably is it on my Spotify
I don't have Spotify so I can't check
but I think that was like some uh way of
going around the weird weird
things fin death and life now hard
passion dou back
down yeah the the no not only the
instrumental I also saw the song like
without the MV is also like
automatically created on my channel and
on my
releases yeah yeah so uh but make sure
to watch the MV more than listening to
the thing on my channel because like she
she paid for the song So and she paid
for the MV so go go you know give her
back the money by giving her AdSense on
the
MV but also watch sleep talking yes I
think I heard Korean no there's Japanese
little bit of Japanese but mostly
English yeah
uh thought you ran out of money for M
what the all not but that not every and
not you say that but not every song
needs an MV I was just kind of crazy
with po wanting everything to have some
kind of presents on my channel but no
it's um organized by cie so the mvy is
on her channel uh yeah so please check
it out watch you can you can make
yourself a playlist where you can Loop
sleep talking and fire ice wow did you
think of that maybe also put in
retrospective and teach W and love Rush
while you're at it mhm
mhm anyway um sorry for being kind of
crazy
today I don't know it like it started so
crazy with me like joking messing around
messing with her like before the stream
with the like starting the the telepathy
like it started with that and then
I just couldn't stop like sorry I said
some dumb things
today but yeah it was kind of wild yeah
Special mood for a special lady unhinged
yeah she really was like she was like
really questioning what I was saying but
like not like in disbelief she was like
trying to understand in the beginning
and yeah then I was like we were getting
so deep into it and I was trying to
change the topic because the stream was
lagging and she was like don't change
the topic now now but then eventually
she completely forgot about that
discussion so I brought it back cuz I
thought you guys need to hear it yeah
she is easy to banter with she's like
yeah K is here here here
here yeah our collabs are pretty rare
yeah basically like the other day we had
this nice talk because like I was
reminding her like collecting the Advent
calendar videos and then uh I saw the
video that she did for the other day
with like the the the car and her
driving
and bonking her own uh fans so
uh I was like oh yeah right you got your
license right and then we started doing
like chitchat a little bit quite a bit
like we talked for hours of which is
like I think the longest conversation we
ever had in the time since she's been
here in her life and that made me feel
like you know oh I I I that made me feel
more comfortable with like maybe asking
her for a collab again yeah and and yeah
I don't know I've really had a great
time during that conversation and now I
had a great time now so yeah
know yeah crony nice nice lady I feel
like I've been recently
like
connecting
weirdly
suddenly with other members that I don't
know for whatever reason just didn't
connect much until now or like just uh
like really low key and and now suddenly
suddenly but better later than never I'm
happy about it some things take time you
know can't like but can you
really how to say let's say you're a
gardener and the flowers are the
friendships or the acquaintances you
have in your life if you have too many
it's kind of hard to keep up with like
keeping every single one healthy I
wanted to compare it actually the other
day I wanted to compare it with Sims
friendships and especially like with the
earlier Sims Sims 1 Sims 2 like I feel
like in the earlier Sims games it was
especially hard to keep
friendships on the friendship level like
if you don't call your one of your Sims
friends one day your friendship will
immediately go down you have to
communicate every day but that's
not realistic anyway that's not how it
is in real life at least thank
God yeah but like getting to a point
getting to
that like line over the line of like
first your acquaintances and then your
friends where you can say oh yeah we're
friends getting to that point
is difficult not only in Sims but also
in real life I would
say unless you have a really loose
understanding of friendship maybe or
like I don't know just more more
I don't know how to
say maybe it doesn't take as much to
certain people to consider someone a
[Music]
friend yeah but I feel like and recently
I've been able to connect a bit more
with people and that makes me really
happy not like not like you know um
anything was wrong before but it was
just like no not much uh opportunity
there there there's like always this
like issue also with me mostly being
active at times where others are sleepy
sleepy and that kind of like blocks some
opportunities but that's okay anyway
anyway why am I Tangen thing uh now we
have reached 2 hours maybe that's why I
have wanted to tangent let's go
here oh
small once I two years and each like
yeah yeah I I generally do that a lot
and I can't be friends with someone who
thinks that it's not friendship when you
don't talk every week like if that's if
that's a no no for you then we're we
can't be friends I
guess that is just the way it
[Music]
is but that's fine cuz I don't don't I
don't need much more friends I have
plenty I have my hands
full
so oh I think we're pretty caught up
mostly aren't we like like exactly
caught up I only have to read the ones
from this stream oh my God like I miss
you
guys what what do you mean the stream is
going to end so
soon I've been I've been missing you
guys you know
please please don't
go well tomorrow I have another exciting
collab with pomu we're going to do a VR
collab I'm going to oh wait a second has
has there been actually oh that just
made me
realize I wonder if the
things question
[Music]
time well well well yeah tomorrow not
frog wedding just a frog date me and
Pomo cuz she has her own frog Persona
and I've been wanting to do a frog date
with her
forever forever
literally
and just a a casual
reminder
of wait I think I
have casual reminder of this weekend
Sunday for me if you're in na if you're
in na it's also I think Sunday uh Sunday
PST 5: a.m. EST 800 a.m. uh Austria
Germany time 2:00 p.m. uh jst 1 p.m. on
Sunday it's finally time there have been
already quite a few announcements of
guests so far uh in case you're not much
on Twitter let me Enlighten you so far
we have had Aki say
byai yeah then we had M
standby this's POS by the way
may or may not be a
spoiler
you it might be but you guys are not
going to figure it out I
think if you figure it out then I love
you don't say it though don't say it out
loud if you know what it is don't say it
out loud but like if you know you know
and then I know that you're
cool and then today announced the the
Wayne this picture is also a a pose from
the dance the aisai one is not really
AOS from a dance but this one and the
mat one is
and I'm going to
say both the song and the dance are
quite
sensual quite
spicy so get ready
guys lots of kissing I think you said
that oh well
uh that that one tweet that was uh
actually
about my dance practices with M
St
yeah maybe you'll
understand
afterwards I I'll talk more about it too
afterwards yeah but um there's still
some guest announcements coming up and
yeah I've I've already watched uh the
cuz it's pre-recorded obviously I'm not
going to like claim it is not it's
ridiculous uh it's um yeah it's
pre-recorded so I already watched like
the the the the product I have been I
have been sent
it uh and I watched it and I got to say
uh I'm surprised because still not
exactly an hour so oops but the members
only part is actually a bit longer than
I expected a little bit L just a tiny
bit longer than I expected so um I guess
it balances it itself
out I definitely recommend you guys
becoming a member uh of this opportunity
if you're not already a member because
members are getting something really
nice I have to say like watching like it
now in the final form I I really really
felt actually emotional especially for
the members only part there's something
about it
that if feels definitely more
intimate and very
emotional and fun and intimate so look
forward to it yay memberships
yay oh nice nice
memberships yeah so maybe maybe the uh
main stream will be I don't know 50
minutes or so I'm surprised honestly
because like wow I I really thought it
would be tight I thought it might be
more than an hour but turns out um it's
pretty so to say short but then I
checked like the I am in senpai's live
the other day and that one was also like
50 minutes and she did have merchandise
to announce so I don't know what it is
recently with ena's I am is mine being
all kind of shorter but the thing is I
don't have merchandise to announce there
so that's also something that's missing
I
guess I just well I know it feels really
long though when I watched it chos was
like 45 oh really was
it what what is this new trend with like
things just turning out to be
shorter why it's not on purpose I'm
telling you
just kind of
happens like on the schedule it seemed
really tight to
me like like when I was making the
schedule like all like choosing the
songs and everything like uh I added I
actually added one song last minute into
the lineup um and I was like is this is
this really going to be okay and we were
like me and the director were like H
well yeah it's kind of tight but well we
can probably squeeze it
and and now it's still not feeling the
full hour that's interesting
honestly could have talked longer in my
MC um Parts but well well well well
before I now accidentally say anything
that I shouldn't be saying because I'm
tanting and when my brain starts tanting
it's the nothing can hold me back I
guess so as long as as it needs to be
yeah like like like I said like when I
watched the whole thing I felt like it
it felt like an
hour definitely felt really long
so I hope you'll enjoy it I'm so I'm so
excited I'm so ready I'm so ready so
look forward to more guest
announcements
and now I will rate the super chats from
this this stream only I
suppose
yo one of my guests no no no no
now hours are now 45 minutes
long wait dud ah that reminds me like do
you know that that Twitter account um
that's like the world the Earth Twitter
account and like that tweets like
patches like it's a game patch about
Earth things do you know that one I love
seeing that one I don't even follow it
but sometimes it pops up on my timeline
and I think it's really
funny
up yeah it was
funny teardo I haven't watched the tears
in video in a long time I don't know why
YouTube doesn't recommend it to me cuz I
was like really binge watching them a
while ago
do they have new videos
[Music]
TI oh yeah six days ago sabertooth
versus Raptor who would
win maybe the Sabertooth because the
Raptor has tiny tiny tiny
arms feel like you could push them over
really easily oh and then one month ago
was our Aunt ether op all right I know
what I'm watching for dinner actually I
have to cook dinner
[Music]
no dep pens on the
Raptor it says Utah raptor there's
Raptors in
Utah why is it called Utah raptor Utah
is a place in America
right she
no but the one on the picture has tiny
arms the one on the
thumbnail Utah Utah Raptors are kind of
big you're saying that as if they still
exist now they don't
right that's a
dinosaur oh the fossil side where they
were first discovered probably
all
interesting d damn youah rappers no
Raptors okay let me read super
chats oh wait there were super Chats on
the oh wait wait wait when I just
realized what I did to my channel
there's a there's a no stream like a
non-stream on my Channel right now right
like that is just waiting room right oh
God that feels really uncomfortable to
me right now oh that disgusts me
7 Minutes of loading
screen that is what the I will
delete that I will privatize that after
but we will read those super chats
that's disgusting absolutely
disgusting I was kind of stressed out
thank God that making a new stream
reservation worked out thank
God no the memories seven minutes of
pain that's all that is yeah
glad it worked out I'm happy I'm
relieved man
okay okay so I read 1080 snowboarding
[Music]
right I think
I sry of being fine right before we R it
I don't know about that that was
probably just your imagination or you
being like oh oh you want to change your
stream well now I'm going to trigger you
real hard by making it work
now now it's fine this
[Music]
way okay let's go um so this is both the
the first stream that will be deleted
and the current one
uh Jacob 47 SW fly thank you for two
pinkings it was a pleasure to finally
meet you in kfp kada my weekend at AF is
my highlight of the Year might never be
topped don't say that yet but surely
it's a great memory for now the C and
dead beats I was with really made it
special just hanging out talking about
takam Mori I wasn't alone they're my
family right I agree the meet and greet
was fun but the panel experience stole
the show
really you you're saying that the panel
was more fun than meeting me oneon-one
what just kidding it was kind of hyp and
I felt pretty hyped too the ending Koka
was my first idle Concert Experience ah
yeah that must be quite overwhelming
especially if you were you you were I
think in that corner in the front
shouting my heart out while waving my
pen lights it's Indescribable I hope to
see y'all at another con one day I love
k k thank you that's great I'm happy to
hear that yeah like I can I can see how
that would be like wow big wow moment
when you're just like mostly most of you
guys just support us like the the
majority of you guys support us just by
watching
streams um and then when you actually
make that move and go to a convention to
see us that's huge that's like like
stepping onto a next level of
fness
so I I wish that uh more people you guys
should more of you guys should make that
happen go see us at conventions if you
can if there's one in a reasonable
distance from you I feel like nobody
nobody who did that regretted what they
did nobody who went to a convention to
see us
regretted it at all the the the exact
opposite I think I'm shy though no need
to be shy there's many like I think many
would say they're shy many kfps or other
fans that came to the um conventions but
I feel like kfp generally like there's
so many openminded kfps that already go
to the conventions and they if you wear
orange you okay if you're shy and you
don't feel confident like you like can
talk to people just wear orange they
will talk to you and you don't have to
be scared about it because kfp people
are great they're great they're really
really sweet and I think you'll have a
great
[Music]
time if NYC was announced earlier ah
yeah I I sometimes I wish those
conventions would be announced earlier
yeah some some of them are announced
pretty late
yeah that's one of my
criticisms
critics I live too far and no money well
who knows maybe one day we will get
to some convention closer to you and if
you want that to happen one thing I can
recommend is you writing to your local
conventions and telling them yo I want
to see her Al as a guest go invite her
life please tell them about us some
conventions might not be so aware yet
but yeah I got really lucky with for
many people seem seemingly have gotten
really lucky that I finally got to Texas
it's not the first time we were in Texas
but I was in Texas for the first time so
that's
exciting yeah I do I hope we can make a
UK convention work this year I hope so
anyway Swan fer thank you m py d Cruz
Dan alar Dan fire nice fire nice down
she says the G for the red of chat fire
I is so freaking good boss especially a
time stamp to is that by any chance a
picture of my
[Music]
ass no right she
right you no way right no you
wouldn't you wouldn't
timestamp such a scene would you
now I know I know the MV was kind of ass
heavy which is great actually great is
exactly how it should
be all the UK accents that would be
amazing I would go crazy anyway thanks
for the awesome work thank you tel for
listening thank you for sending a Super
Chat to me but I I didn't do much I
didn't do much I just uh you know sang a
little bit
thank
you crony and then it cuts off but than
the arti thanks for the pinky Hi boss
your popup parade showed up the other
day oh yeah I saw I see a lot of them on
my kfp tag just wanted to you to know
yours is taller than Callie's however
unlike your 3D model uh and the the the
other two I've gotten so far they did
not as you once said nerve your C
Nerf my crotch what do you mean like
putting uh like the black
uh uh thing shorts
underneath I think I did see that as the
panties yeah is that what you mean uhuh
yeah interesting because I think if you
look at my default
outfit it's
kind of implied that if anything it
wouldn't be white it should be black
whether or not it's bats or
panties it should be
black but
okay maybe go in with a with a marker
with a permanent marker and uh make my
panties black no don't do it you'll mess
it up you'll like you'll make everything
so messy down there do not paint my
crotch do not paint my crotch and do not
take this out of
context thank
you for your understanding not even you
quest alsoo artist you may be an artist
but I don't trust your handling of my
crotch this is all not to be taken out
of context thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
yo honestly like um pranking crony like
that reminded me of me gaslighting uh
Bales which was with crony
right don't take it out of crotch text
[Music]
wow what am I listening to just got here
everything's everything's cool
everything's chill
who's bails I'm not even the only one I
noticed that the other day I think I was
watching narissa and she said sad bals
and everybody El was like who's Bales
I'm not even the only one who says
that so when are you guys going to get
used to it
h why why is that even a thing just
because like everybody calls her Bae
mostly we just
say her normal default name isn't
doesn't exist
[Music]
anymore k b says hakos BS B also says
hakos you mean she says the whole name
well that's crazy that
is kind of
insane imagine calling someone by their
phone name
imagine cop also says bals does
she does she well then why is it such a
meme there's plenty people who call her
Bales
[Music]
then it's logical she's her
kohai well no that no no she doesn't
call me Me by Taki
Kiara I think she just calls me kiar
Kiara I think
probably Bae herself has said who's
BS gaha that's how Callie says it gaha
GAA I think kie is the only one who says
it like that gaha
[Music]
and then there's some things who call me
Kara which really
hurts it's not
Kiera it's not
Kara
MH beu and Bs decided together to use
the full names oh really okay wow
they're like really exact
it
seems
you thank
you really is that a
thing she talk about that is that real I
am a chi be than chocolate insomnia D
Corona
[Music]
d d
d oh what the yeah that creeper was
insane that was actually I I almost
appreciated that creeper showing up like
I kind of did because the moment it
happened I was like yep
yep thank you that is comedy Nathan
cotton thank you for the red of chat
hello T I just got my k a popup parade
figure just in time for Christmas oh
it's Christmas right now what the hell I
thought oh what what I thought it was
the 24th not the
14th do you have any ideas for what I
should get for her for the upcoming
holiday Dej Vu
what wait but you should get
her well you should get the figure for
the upcoming
holiday hello parasocial
much what do you
mean let me read this again maybe I'm
misunderstanding just got M pop a parade
figure in just in time for Christmas do
you have any ideas for what I should get
her for the upcoming
holiday is it because you asked me what
I want for
Christmas is that why djab
Vu sorry Nathan I am
confused well if you want to get her
something get her Black
Panties
please she needs Black
Panties but don't paint
them no you the figure what the figure
yeah yeah get the figure Black
Panties
[Music]
maybe knit
them or so like yeah make it like you
know like for or go to a shop that sells
Barbie clothes that should be the same
size
roughly so your MV with you and Cali
thank you glad you like it it's really
cool the MV turned out pretty
badass I think like the m was done
before the song was
done which I've never experienced before
I
think
she so
[Music]
fast living in France for 4 years oh
yeah you're in you're in the UK now oh
that's awesome you've been all
around yay you're in my time
zone nice little
en asking the girls like Victoria Secret
to measure my K figur I've been to a
Victoria Secret shop once I think
they're not so common in Austria so I've
been to one at an airport somewhere in
Europe at a airport Victoria
Secret no kind of only to like kill some
time I didn't even buy anything it
wasn't wasn't as quite what I expected
not as nice I mean it's nice
but yeah who the hell is Victoria why at
an airport because I was trying to kill
time that's what you do at airports look
at the
shops I didn't get anything no I don't
think I did no it was actually
surprisingly more if it felt like it was
more non underwear than underwear like I
feel like there was more like jogging
pants and leggings and like workout
clothes then underwear I was a bit
confused but why not just just different
what I expected oh why are they at an
airport well why not there's like all
kinds of shops at airports
really like there's
[Music]
anything why would someone sell panties
in an airport in the first place
honestly I can
totally like there's can you not imagine
a situation where that's useful I can
totally imagine like what if you are in
the
plane and you're like changing at the
airport but you you have like two plane
rides but let's say you feel absolutely
disgusting after a 12-hour flight and
you didn't think of bringing uh you know
other underwear but you have another
four five 6 7 hour flight upcoming maybe
you want to buy a new set of underwear
for example oh that can totally happen
or I don't know I mean let's say you're
a lady and you got a surprise visit of
the monthly
Jack the Ripper I don't know and
you need a new pair of panties because
they're ruined for now so you go to the
Victoria Secret and you buy a new pair
of
panties can totally
happen can totally
happen plenty of things like that could
happen
no yeah what what if what if you
realize I mean I don't know why that
would be a problem cuz it would probably
be covered by another Garment of
clothing but one of you realize there's
a hole in your
panties thanks to the mths that got to
it and yeah you want to buy a new pair
that doesn't have a
hole you get it you get it now you
understand now that there's plenty of
reasons thank you then we can go back
don't question
it so thank you Nathan I'm still
confused but thank you che7 D the gamer
cre d d substitute
D yeah oh yeah good good reason to talk
to crony again thank
you for the red chat mama told please
get the sandal oh yeah I surprised she
didn't know did I say it so like
incoherent
does she never heard of or did she NE
never hear of
uh L shank what the hell I still don't
know if it's Lanka or Lanka but
surprised she didn't know about
it we have educated her it's more of a
Hispanic thing yeah but I'm not Hispanic
and I still understand it I mean I feel
like you guys probably taught me I
wouldn't have known without you guys but
it just kind of happens
just kind of happened CH in chaa okay CH
okay okay okay okay I think I'll
remember now
maybe as in chicken
uhhuh
interesting I also don't really know
many Hispanic
folks but well I guess it's just like we
have a a really really open way of
communicating me and you guys guys and I
I ask you guys about anything
so now she knows I share my knowledge
with her sharing is
caring
Corona job is a warful moomoo prison
what the
moomo prison I I'll have to play
I'll have to play Minecraft with crony
again I just need something to do
ideally when another update comes out
because you know how I feel about
Minecraft I really really want to play
it but I just can't find things to
do pudding Channel d i a beep D Mr Big D
whoops my bad d space waterfall D check
your channel Brandon
D endless thank you for the red New
Zealand let's go thanks for the stream
been working lots of overtime lately and
catching up with the SM RPG bot helps me
chilling out for a bit o I'm happy to
hear that looking forward to the fry
live with we know you worked hard on it
yeah I really did oh but it's going to
be at a good time for you oh my
God yeah it's actually a good time for
Australia New Zealand Japan and so on so
you're
welcome you're welcome Happy Birthday I
can't read your name but happy
birthday
yeah what happened to Megan King's land
oh my God I don't think I was ever
serious about
[Music]
that
sheesh but I wonder if there's a
Minecraft server surely there is a
Minecraft server that
recreated The Game of Thrones world we
should do more tours like that remember
when we did the Disneyland
tour I should I should find like
interesting worlds that we could visit
like
that there definitely is
yeah let's go remind me of it
eventually not now like December I'm
pretty much done January 2 maybe in
February we can look into
that yes adventure maps yeah yeah oh and
also like ages ago I got perms for that
Minecraft um
game R
RPG Minecraft I know there's too I got
perms for that ages ago but didn't
really find a good timing to play
those no there's plenty to do anyway
thank you endless I'm so excited to have
you watch the
results so please please stay tuned for
it and uh I wish you luck with work I
hope you have to work less overtime soon
but FAL you can do it
gum
what do you say comat in English uh do
your best I believe in
you thank you for still trying to catch
up with me though I appreciate
[Music]
that thank you Derek thank you it's
Sunday though I think isn't it
Sunday yeah Sunday don't mistake it's
Sunday
pyro and a refresh wait did I give
endless a kiss endless H just in
case oh there's
oh Korean Super Chat super long Super
Chat space wonderful dangun super bear
hero
dun uh thank you thank you Violet and
for the pinky I was waiting until you
had your short hair because it is my fav
design but I can't wait this is not
really my short hair
though unfortunately my birthday was for
3 days and AG go uh that means it's my
third birthday watching your streams W
love you as always and keep up being
amazing as you always
[Music]
are Violet ever
Garden yay
congratulations is this is this fine
even with this hairstyle I thought you
wanted the short one but
congratulations your first birthday
that's kind of crazy like wow these days
when you guys report to me like it's my
third third it's my fourth birthday or
it's like so and so many months with you
36 38 months seeing those numbers now is
kind of
insane it's kind of
crazy
like it really always comes with the
real I
ization that we are spending so much
time
together I'm happy about that
though yeah you guys still here
wow crazy thank you thank you all of
you
wow wow yeah look at
them
ah I mean the 10 months I feel like
you've been around longer than you're a
member for
[Music]
though I think this is my f coming up
shees yeah that's so crazy like
what that's such a long
time oh my God thank you guys well see
so much so many so many months that we
spent together it adds up it's crazy wow
W look at them look at
them look at them flexing
making use of their members messages
don't you want to use them like on on
Sunday stop stop stop
stop stop
H stop stop stop stop stop stop stop
stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop
stop
stop you don't read those anyway yeah
but like you can throw something out
there I'll be watching the chat closely
probably because I'll just be playing
the video
I hope the internet doesn't up
because apparently I'm the one playing
the video not uh the
studio so well usually usually my
streams are stable usually unless
YouTube says
you yeah it's kind of
scary scares me scares
me my imersion I don't care about your
Merion I think we have like
gotten this like in kfp we we just you
know I don't you so you know
you guys are I
think very very down to
earth maybe you don't need for ultra low
lat yeah the thing is like I've been
having problems with ultra low latency I
don't know if it really stems from ultra
low latency but then I switched cuz that
was in Japan recently and then I
switched to normal latency and then it
was fine again so recently I've been not
normal uh the low latency the middle
option I've been streaming with that and
then today was around so I said
okay I'm going to make a new stream and
we're going to switch to latency I don't
know if that really helped it that was
probably not the issue but now it seems
like ultra low latency is safe again to
use but ultra low latency does lower the
quality the possible quality so I'll
probably um end up um doing the middle
option shouldn't be an issue
mhm fingers crossed yeah for real for
real we ultra low it seems like it's at
least okay to go back to that
now oh your frankness is one of many
Charming points I love thank you I would
agree with that no no yeah yeah
yeah I like that we don't each
other most of the time and if we do then
it's you know as well our culture of
like messing around with each other but
like I mean in terms of we don't try to
uphold a fantasy
necessarily you know that is
not
[Music]
needed so this s yuk tatto Yuki Channel
than again and I hope you're feeling you
know welcome and and comfortable in
Europe enjoy Tony Cho sent a red super
chat with a lot of
Korean I could spend 20 minutes trying
to read this or I can put it into papao
I see however a Kik key at the very end
I recognize that let's
see
uh
oh I'm a Korean indie game developer who
often watches K's broadcast it's my
first Super Chat I'm a poor developer
but I pay for it the Super Chat I guess
oh no thank you for the broadcast that
soups my loneliness during my game
development e not too long ago a game I
developed for one person as one person I
suppose that probably is supposed to
imply was released on
stream let me look it up it's called The
Lost Prince and I'd appreciate it if
kada enjoyed it because it also supports
English and Japanese dubbing for real I
want to give you a key but I don't know
why to give it to you so I'll replace it
with Super Chat oh thank you for giving
me wait let me look it up is it like
something that I I would be interested
in opening
steam as we
talk the Lost
Prince
oh o that looks
legit
the faithful story of a boy chosen as a
sacrifice to save The Prince and adapted
story based oh on the Noel the little
prins a o oh the like character
animation thing is like the way they
stand there and move reminds me a bit of
like you know it's kind of Holo parade
style but the illustrations look really
good cute the business person is
cute ooh ooh
[Music]
car Takeo Rose Garden
Rosie oh
cute oh there's so many
characters recorded by various Korean
voice actors oh oh so there's there's
really dubbing
[Music]
damn what do you do story based package
game developed inspired is a it is a
visual novel based complex genre complex
genre is that a genre
in which the Story begins with the
assumption that the prince died from a
snake
bite it
has it has simulation RPG Adventure day
RPG and dating Sim really in its
tags
not oh it's currently 15% off guys so
check it
out
ever thought of appearing at Comic conon
that's not really something I would
decide that's you know usually the event
people ask us hey do you want to be at
this event and then we say yeah
[Music]
maybe interesting well thank you so much
for uh super chatting and I'm glad I
could you know be there for you during
the development I'm I'm honored yeah cuz
this is legit good job
good
job
[Music]
wow
congratulations on releasing your game
it looks really
nice
and good
work
for yay
or yo and
pop yes a big kiss for you good job Tony
keep on keep on doing the things that
you have a passion for make more games
I'm looking forward to the future of
your
endeavors t t
Brandon
d game
8910 no that's not true Matrix
D Dominic D requesting permission to
build a small KP theme park for in real
life what the
in ah wait it says it literally
says in a virtual way sure why not do
it okay do it do it
looking forward to
it only virtual first
first
okay sounds like you're
motivated going to go hoop with some
friends I'm going to go
too I I I I fire you you don't quit I
fire you cuz I'm leaving too mhm goodbye
guys tomorrow collaboration with pumu
rainpop I think it will be on both
channels maybe
probably two povs of two frogs having a
nice T wholesome day together hope you
enjoy today's
stream tomorrow in J say I'll be ding
quack quack
quack oh my God I'm turning into a frog
already
[Music]
bye-bye