[Music]
do
so
[Music]
foreign
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
okay
[Music]
welcome
welcome to another snack box review
but today
we're doing it with a camera as well
and bj i'm still too loud even though
i'm already low and really okay i'll
lower it a tiny bit more there we go
uh being the end
[Music]
ah oh sure
um disclaimer
or maybe i don't know are there are
there spanish-speaking people in a chat
who don't know english
in that case
disclaimer
[Music]
the snacks in the box
may not be
very um
[Music]
how do i pronounce today wait a second
exclusive
[Music]
[Laughter]
how bad was that
she speaks so fast that is that is very
authentic i can imagine um
spanish-speaking people always talk very
fast um
fake advertisement no
no no no no
if you if you want to complain about
that complaint to the company that made
the snack box not to me
they advertise it as guatemala but
uh
from the previous snack boxes that i had
from that company
um
they were they were definitely new
snacks from that country but
not necessarily snacks that don't exist
anywhere else or are originally
exclusively created in that country of
origin
you know what i mean
um
maybe it's just snacks that are popular
there but not necessarily really
come from that country but it's what
they eat maybe
um yeah last time we had uh we had so
far
so far we had an intern we started out
with an international world snack box on
my channel uh in a members only stream
to test out the format and then we did a
korean snack box stream
but
that one was from a different company
because i missed that one and i ordered
a different one from amazon but that one
was like really really old snacks
and here we are with a snack box from
surprisingly glad tomato i'm gonna be
honest um
i
i don't know i mean i had to look i had
to look glad tomorrow up i heard the
name before but i'm gonna be honest i
don't know much about the country
but
um
the actually the snack box comes with a
little bit of information on the country
so i want to look at that again
as well yeah uh
yes yes
my korean friends i missed you
and i know it's like down there in south
america
uh
yes next to mexico
uh i've been no wait wait
look at my chichi
what is it
yes next to mexico
oh
central central oh okay well that is
central america
i don't know uh
that side of the world uh the map i
don't know it that well
um
[Music]
neither kfp in guatemala it already
exists you have to think imagine it and
then it already exists
all right uh
uh
screen please
[Music]
hello
gloves but the color doesn't come off
okay
[Laughter]
so they
may maybe some stains on my gloves but
don't judge me okay
all right
all right we're gonna go for the snacks
eat them judge them and then uh rate
them and then and then and then
afterwards we're going to read super
chats
here it is
guatemala
yes
and i will first of all
don't look at that yet don't don't don't
look at that yet don't don't you look at
that
oh first of all
uh
look at what's inside the pamphlet
mm-hmm
so basically
you get a pamphlet and it shows you this
and it says
uh the biggest cities in let's learn
something about guatemala
the biggest cities are guatemala city
mexico which sounds like mexico
and villa nouveau
i thought villa is a house
new house villa nueva sounds like new
house
you have a city that's called new house
am i mistranslating that
huh
what do you mean floor reveal that's a
table that's not my floor
pamphlet best snack that's not a snack
no no
what are my answers
when my my comments come so slowly
villa's town oh
what utah oh i thought it means house
because you know buy a villa
interesting maybe maybe uh cause villas
are so big they are maybe it means it's
a house that's as big as a town
and then it says the uh capital is
guatemala city
[Music]
and the language is spanish the amount
of the people living in guatemala is 16
million is that a lot let's see how much
is in austria
austria
[Music]
uh oh you have you have a double
about
a little bit less than double we have
almost
almost nine million
in austria we are small but i suppose
guatemala is also relatively relatively
small
yes
uh-huh uh-huh
villains town or village why is why are
my comments so
coming in so late today that's weird
ah i mispronounced it of course i do
[Music]
and we have nine million we're pretty
[\h__\h] small and it says uh
at the bottom
that what's typical this is german by
the way what's typical for
guatemala
is the maya ruins i've heard of those
and
volcanoes and coffee
and bones bones
coffee beans
i don't have bones
very interesting
i should let me flip the page is this
one page okay
i feel like i can't touch the pages with
my with my gloves on
uh
fun facts oh let oh okay wait wait let
me there's a little bit of history i
think here it says uh in german
guatemala strength full of blood
oh there's a lot of uh secret uh not
spiritual secret but hidden hidden
treasures
oh really old
ruins
uh from the mayas that are really deep
in the rainforest
sickness
i don't know how to translate that
[Music]
us in or besides big
high volcanoes at volcano sand there are
big big big lakes
afternoon
uh surrounded by beautiful landscapes
and caribbean
uh beaches to fall in love with
wow wow
this sounds or it sounds beautiful
and there's a photo there that also
looks beautiful
let's see can you uh it's on the top the
top page this is
look at it
look
it looks beautiful you don't see much
fun facts besides the official language
spanish
oh there are incredible 21 other
languages being spoken in guatemala oh
yeah
really
do people actively use 21 other
languages there is it like
switzerland kind of
not even switzerland uses that many
[Music]
which languages are there
do you speak german and go out the
monologue
i'm impressive
uh-huh well
it's so late 21 yeah
ah
native languages
oh so no german
another fun fact is
yolanda fernandez de coffino
one of the first mcdonald's restaurant
restaurant
uh a lot of
potentials
of the of the of the country uh
uh created the manual
runout which is today known as a happy
meal
what
[Music]
guatemala made the happy meal
guatemala made the happy meal guys
did you know that
they came up with the happy meal
[Music]
um wow
i didn't know that
yeah
that's a nice fact it's a very fitting
fact for me
uh
in the northern part of guatemala
and you can find the tikka national park
which was also used in star wars episode
4.
oh
did you know that
damn yeah
i don't know what it looks like but
and then another random fun fact is
uh the word chocolate chocolate comes
from the maya word
translated it means
bitter water because back then it was
served as a cold drink
oh
so bitter chocolate water
and the the last fun fact is
in guatemala uh newborn babies
get a bracelet i'm translating this in
real time from german
get a bracelet on the right hand
uh this tradition is supposed to protect
the babies from evil humans
[Music]
on the bottom side it tells you where to
go if you go there i like i like these
pamphlets actually they they're doing
well with these pamphlets um
for example it tells you to go to
guatemala city
and to antigua guatemala which is the oh
the original um
wow it looks beautiful the original
capital
in the middle of
uh oh uh an ocean of volcano what does
that mean the it was originally a
volcano and now it's an ocean or is that
just say you saying there are so many
volcanoes that is like an ocean of
volcanoes i'm not
sure um
and then another stop that they want you
to go to is something called
kvets alton angot what the [\h__\h] is that
xela also known as xela
is what
it's uh
it's more
it's not very uh it's not a very
touristy city it's more like
landscape beautiful
pretty full beautiful landscape
and then the fourth stop that they want
you to go to is tikka
uh
because that is the city of the maya
yeah
that sounds really interesting i'm sure
my mom would love to see that
um
isn't there like a 3d program
that's called maya my mom used to use
that
i think
anyway
what's on the next page let me flip the
page i can't i can't flip the page all
right there we go oh okay and now we get
to the snacks and basically there are
some introduced here um
but we will ignore this and not read the
that but
um
at the end there's also a quiz by the
way
so we'll look at that afterwards after
eating the snacks so yeah pretty full is
a new word now also by the way i have
like a corner desk right now because i
added this desk so um whenever i look to
the left uh to the snacks my my face
probably won't be moving forgive me
about that oh no not a quiz oh yes a
quiz
all right um
uh we will start with a drink because
having a drink to start off with
is always good what the frick is that oh
this is a drink
that seems pretty legit
it's sangria
sangria
i've heard of sangria it's like berry
juice
it says sangria
[Music]
old people juice probably
yeah carbonated
[Music]
one second
how do you say cheers in
spanish wait
[Music]
i'm going to smell it
the smell is not so strong i'm not sure
about it
this is not alcohol i think um
i don't i don't think they would send me
alcohol
where would it say that there's alcohol
i think it's just a
um soft drink but i know that uh sangria
often is alcohol right
okay i'm gonna sip i'm gonna sip three
two one
hmm
[Music]
it's
it
[Music]
it tastes like there should be alcohol
in it but it was made non-alcoholic for
me
[Music]
uh-huh
uh-huh it's not bad i would um it's kind
of um not very cold right now i think it
would taste better if i would cool it
with ice cubes
um
interesting i've never had sangria
before
is this how it tastes like
is this
where my lama
guatemala people is this a drink that
you guys drink over there or maybe even
mexico because you guys are close so i
suppose that you share some snacks and
drinks
is this is this well-known
this one is this well-known
wine and fruit yeah it kind of gives me
wine vibes yeah fermented it does it
does taste fermented
not as fermented as wine but still
[Music]
it's it's all right yeah
um
it's not very sweet sweet
i expected it to be more sweet but it's
it tastes so
not not that sweet in mexico yes it's
mexican um
it's it's not from gladial i'm sorry
about that
it's their fault they're claiming it's
from guatemala
it might as well also be in their mexico
snack box so sorry about that
i told you my uh the disclaimer
i recorded
tonight
[Music]
shall we leave it here so people can see
what we have had so far
okay i will rate this now
um
[Music]
probably tastes better when cooled
but for someone like me who hates uh
alcohol even though this there is no
alcohol in this it reminds me of
alcoholic drinks
so
yeah
for me
i will give it up
i will give it um
[Music]
six out of ten
six seven ten we're starting we're
starting a little bit strict i don't
wanna be too easy on these snacks okay
you guys can take some criticism can't
you
pour in a glass
my glass is currently filled with water
so hmm i would have to pick up a new
glass whatever um
next up
[Music]
apparently this is what you guys eat
cheez-its
it's biscuits with cheese flavor i think
cheddar cheddar flavor knives
how what do you say about this one my
grandmother people
is this uh popular in guatemala
[Laughter]
do you know this snack it looks like
cheez-it is famous isn't it i think this
one is uh well-known and not only
that's american well
well it says here in
in spanish
[Music]
i do like cheddar
i'm generally not um someone who snacks
on cheesy snacks
um but i do like cheddar so this
shouldn't be too bad uh
how do i open this
let me get the scissors
[Music]
popular in the us right
well
it will have to do
so with the camera now i can show you
the inside of the snacks
you probably know what cheez-its look
like konna kanjina oh you just saw a cat
here flying by i think
uh yes
little little biscuits
um probably a little bit salty too looks
like there's some salt on it
let me try
i'm pretty small
oh [\h__\h] i got cat hairs all over it
again
how did i do that i touched it with like
really really
i barely touched it i need like i need
the cutleries and touch it with the
cutleries let me touch it i'll go i'll
touch it with the scissors
the scissor will now be in my um
[Music]
my
chopsticks here
[Music]
well
it's cheese crackers
what can i say
it's a
for someone who likes cheese and
crackers this is good
no no complaints here
and but as i said i'm generally not a
big fan of cheese stacks but this is
just fine it's not bad
[Music]
good stuff
okay
i will give this uh
six out of ten as well
[Laughter]
it doesn't blow me away
but it's good for what it is
[Music]
okay next step
snack
i wonder i wanna know what about this oh
it's uh potato chips
[Music]
papa's burritos
say something like it's mexican
um jalapeno is this uh
this
is gonna be um
this is gonna be spicy
that was a literally mexican yeah it
says so on the bottom why don't they
sell this as a mexican snack box i'm so
sorry guys
i don't know man you gotta complain to
them
[Music]
don't tell me chad i'll be faster than
you
ah yeah
striped
stripes
are they spicy
well yeah
it says jalapeno
cheesy and spicy
[Music]
accessories
i don't understand
low calories maybe
let me
let me smell
uh-huh
smell is okay smell doesn't smell spicy
um
it's just potato chips uh but i'll try
to show you the inside
uh
pretty empty why are potato chips bags
always is empty man what
like ruffles yeah yeah yeah i i like
ruffled riffle potato chips i like those
okay my scissor
pick me one and go
we're taking some scissors now
it looks like this
hi hi hi hi
i'm scared please don't tell me this is
spicy
spicy and cheese okay i will try i will
bite a small bite off of it
[Music]
it's not
spicy it's not
it's not really spicy um i think
a little bit if you eat more than just a
tiny tiny tiny
half potato chip
[Music]
look they taste weird
it tastes weird
i don't know what that taste is
[Music]
is that the hell is that jalapeno taste
karakola if
um
i will give it
i will give it a
three out of ten
[Music]
yeah i'm not so convinced about this one
yeah
i guess there are mild jalapenos
[Music]
i have someone coming over later to
change my layout of my room to help me
with that so i'll give all the snacks to
that person
next up oh i like this oh wait why does
it look like it's spicy
no way
next up we have this
uh squinkles
um it looks like
a sour gummy looks like spaghetti like
in the shape of spaghetti
what do you what do you say about this
one is this a guatemala snack
or did we fail once again
is this is this from guatemala
or do people in guatemala at least eat
this or
not never seen that one hmm
why do people keep on saying
what is that
that's mexican
that's mexican that's that's guatemalan
it was also mexican wow
well i mean as i said i mean for example
in austria when i would put together a
snack box i wouldn't necessarily only
put austrian things inside either to be
honest i would put in things that are
that we like to eat and those are mostly
originating also from other countries
like switzerland and
and uh germany and so on like you know
milka chocolate like a lot of the
chocolates that we eat are not from
austria because we just don't produce
that much um i think that's better than
giving someone stuff that's only
specifically from austria but then it's
not really what we eat you know what i
mean so i'm fine with that as long as
it's something that you guys actually
consume
toy clicks is a good tomato snack oh we
will see if it's in there i hope it for
you i really hope it because that seems
to be like the only snack that you guys
mentioned
okay okay well i will eat this now um it
looks yummy it says squinkles salsa
getting
deutsche enchilado and tira
[Music]
salsa
there's like a little bit of a flame on
the packaging underneath the squinkles
font that says salsa
are you telling me it's supposedly what
a watermelon flavor
but
it also has a flame there is it spicy
watermelon
[Laughter]
salsa ghetti is mexican i see well i can
put mexico in the title as well
afterwards i guess
uh
okay wait shut up about tatrix we're now
focusing on squinkles it's a cute name
though it's a really small packaging
[Laughter]
it's
so small what the [\h__\h] oh there's like a
sauce or something
as well like a little package underneath
what is this
what is this does this make it spicy
you look it doesn't smell good
it doesn't even smell the these these
noodles they don't smell good well it
doesn't smell like watermelon what ew
and i guess the sauce makes it even
spicier it says lucas cuisano
i will translate that before i eat that
lucas guzzano
lucas warm
deep l that doesn't i don't understand
that lucas warm
what do you mean you look as warm
well i'll try it first without um
it's hot sauce
why the [\h__\h] what what kind of snack is
that
ew okay i will try it because i am a
streamer and we like content
um i would first try it without
the
sauce
[Music]
i will try it
scishow sauce
isn't that supposed to taste like
watermelon
[Music]
it doesn't really taste good
[Laughter]
[Music]
doesn't really taste good okay but i i
guess
oh i guess you're supposed to pour it
all over
the spaghetti uh-huh
[Laughter]
[Music]
not gonna like that i
can imagine
it needs the sauce okay
let me let me get some cutlery
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay
i am
i am here
so i brought like small for the small
spaghetti
i brought small cutlery
and now
this will not be this will not be good
ah [\h__\h]
the sauce is all on my keyboard
[\h__\h] uh
one second
[Music]
time to get a new keyboard
time to get a new keyboard you
you
yeah it's it's finally done
because now it's in between
in between the keys
okay
well um at least
most of it is gone
accidents accidents happen i
uh
[Music]
all right all right all right i tried my
best
now
uh
cat hairs [\h__\h]
all right sauce time
[Music]
[Applause]
this will be so bad i already know it's
gonna be
[Music]
let bad smell
it still smells bad
okay now let's mix
or or so now maybe not let's not get too
much sauce on it here i'll do
this
[Music]
it doesn't work like that
okay i have a little bit of sauce on it
a little bit
um
[Music]
okay
knowing already i'm not gonna like it it
makes it even worse to uh bite into it
but okay
i'm gonna eat the whole thing okay
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's okay
it's okay there was not that much sauce
on it
[Music]
no it's okay it's not that bad
i mean
i will give it a
0.5 out of 10.
[Music]
gotta drink some water
who thought of this combination
watermelon that doesn't even taste like
watermelon
i don't know man okay
now
next snack please
what is this
oh
it's a juice
a weirdly packaged juice mango juice
what what
there's a straw on the side
what it says
you guys know this
you guys know this one
[Music]
how it's very popular in mexico
it's such an interesting packaging
triangle juice yeah
never seen triangle juice before
[Music]
what did someone say it freeze it
can i make it into ice cream
look triangle boiling juice
triangle boilings make me think of um
a certain lady with triangle boing
boings
[Music]
okay
well it's once again mexican but we
talked about this guys we talked about
it but okay i will welcome and never
drink because
the other one
that was okay it says
mango mango
mango
where do i put the straw ah the straw
goes
here
okay
i hope there will be no accidents yeah
lara croft i forgot the name thank you
that was who i was thinking of so lara
croft juice
okay
okay i like these juice boxes you know
from my childhood but i never saw one of
these or should i shake it let's shake
it oh nothing moves
it's like filled to the brim
okay we're going in
okay okay okay
what is so weird
okay okay
[Music]
of course that was gonna happen i have
some toilet paper here
[Music]
how are you supposed
[\h__\h]
how can i
i'm doing it so carefully
doing it so carefully okay
be careful
careful careful
okay
hmm
oh this is good this is good
this is good but i want to cool it and
then drink more
wait let me do one more sip
um
[Music]
good mango juice
very good very good boiling juice
of course very good a little bit uh
difficult to handle but also packaging
um very interesting very original
um i will give it um
a 9 out of ten for what it is it's a
good mango juice
and a funny packaging that i will never
forget
[Music]
nine out of ten
ten nine ten but i will put this in in
my fridge and then drink
more okay next up
next up
okay
we have
a presbyter
cookies chocolate chip cookies but
with uh with coconuts crumb coco ralado
what about this guys
what do you say about this one huh
is this common in guatemala
9 10. so far the the best one yeah
let me try to open this
cannot open as always uh kind of
difficult to open with
with uh
gloves
i'm gonna use my
then the problem is i don't really like
coconut but as long as if it's not too
strong then then i can eat it
if it's not too strong
okay so i opened the packaging and
there's like little ah little packages
[Music]
small
small cookies i suppose okay i'm not
gonna take out the rest but
okay
small package small cookie
[Music]
everywhere in latin america oh
chile from chile okay but you guys do
eat it
i wonder i i think like how many glad
mother people are even here probably not
even that much i saw some people on
twitter being excited um about this
stream saying they're from guatemala but
it's
i i would imagine that i don't have
that many people
actually watching from guatemala
um so i don't know how how many real
opinions we can get but
yeah why can't i literally not open any
package
there we go okay
[Music]
so there's two cookies in there
um
i don't i don't like the balance of
those white uh chips they should be more
balanced all over the cookie
maybe the other one looks better the
other one looks a little bit better yeah
all right i'll eat this oh you know what
is that coconut
are the chips coconuts cause then i'll
eat the other one with less
with less chips on it
[Music]
probably it's probably coconut
i'm from guatemala oh hello
oh
caribbean
argentina
[Music]
guatemala here kind of new industry
welcome
none of these snacks are well i'm sorry
okay i will i will dig into this
[Music]
a good cookie
yeah
[Music]
hmm it's good if you like uh coconut you
will like it more than me so i will not
rate it by that i will i will i will i
will rate it as if i liked coconut
and then i would give this
an 8 out of 10 i think
or 7 710 maybe
[Music]
it's pretty good
um the chocolate taste could be stronger
um
[Music]
i'll give it a seven out of ten
okay
next snack
guys i have a bad feeling um about the
snack that you guys are looking for i'm
having a bad feeling about it
um
i i see something that has a similar
name
uh
but it's not portraits
liz is the next snack tortilla
what is this oh onion there's an onion
on the image so onion tasting
tastes like onion
it's little it's a little crispy um
chips
filled with air
[Music]
um
what about this where is this from i
wonder
oh it says brazil
it says brazil i've been to brazil
it says brazil on the back
oh
[Laughter]
literally not a single snack from
guatemala so far that's okay
that's okay
it's like a big mix for all the people
here to be happy
there's a lot of uh portuguese and
spanish-speaking people in the chat
and so there's a little bit for everyone
today
okay let me try this
[Music]
opening the package onion flavor huh
let me smell
oh it smells good
let me show you
uh
it's like this
little puppy
puppy chips or something like that
yeah latino latino
[Music]
snack box is what this is
i i apologize
for everyone who's unhappy
okay i'm gonna eat this now eat the duck
[Music]
wait i need another one
very good
[Music]
could perhaps use a little bit more salt
but i like the crunch i like the texture
um the onion taste is not too strong
that's probably a good thing
i will give this
an
eight out of ten
[Music]
okay we're going really fast right now
holy [\h__\h] next snack
[Music]
interesting
interesting there's there's two snacks
in here that are very similar to another
one looks like it's kind of um trying to
imitate the other uh but the next snack
is from kellogg's so
[Music]
is our favorite cereal tiger
um giving us a cookie with some milky
milky flavor
in between
where is this from
it doesn't say in the back do you guys
know where it's from
where is this from
it probably tastes like the morning
cereal if it does taste like that that
would actually be interesting
[Music]
why do you guys know it on a different
name
uh
tony the tiger go
it's just frost flakes you made it to a
cookie
brazil again
let's go to brazil
portuguese
oh oh
i mean kellogg's i don't know where that
comes from that company but it's a
pretty big company um but maybe this is
a flavor that comes specifically from
brazil brazil never seen never seen in
mexico really
okay well the cookies are
uh like this in here
the smell i don't know the smell is kind
of neutral mostly
it's a little bit cracked
yeah okay i'm digging in
i'm digging in ah
[Music]
oh
my god there's cornflakes in the in the
cookies
it feels like cornflakes
tiny tiny tiny tiny crispy cornflakes
[Music]
it tastes kind of boring though
i mean the texture is interesting and
something i've never had before
[Music]
but it tastes boring
the milk the creamy the cream tastes
like almost like nothing
it's not very
powerful
they're supposed to be plain
oh yeah they are plain
[Laughter]
i guess you could maybe
eat them with yogurt or something i
don't know
[Music]
it does taste like cornflakes a little
bit yeah
not too much but they're better with
milk
i never
never never ever have i
dipped a cookie in milk before
but yeah maybe that's a good way to eat
them
also i'll put them here and i'll give
i will give them
a four out of ten
[Laughter]
okay
why is this why is this in here
so this
this is interesting
this could be brazilian too i don't know
man
uh
interesting
no it says mexico
okay sorry my guatemala people i'm so
sorry for the disappointment
so this is uh from the shape it's a
similar cookie i was saying that the
cookie we just ate kind of imitates this
one
shape wise but there we go
it's oreos but
a special flavor sabol
peppery delimon
galetta sandwich sabor chocolate
[Music]
i think um
lemon flavor uh oreos lemon flavor oreos
i think
we all know oreos but this flavor i've
never seen before
[Music]
i wonder
oreos yes oreos
lemon lemon lemon asino oreo de
gozaimasu
has anyone ever seen these before
lemon pie
oh lemon pie flavor
well that's interesting uh [\h__\h] i opened
the package really badly
scissor help me
it's a flavor that also exists in the
u.s hmm but maybe it's popular in
guatemala who knows
okay
uh
i i am incapable of opening packages
um
yeah
oreos oreos oreos
you know what an oreo looks like we all
know
oh
it smells good i love lemon uh
scent and flavor
okay i'm digging in i think i'm gonna
like hello cat i dare you to jump on my
table
[Music]
oh hell yeah
oh yes
[Music]
this is good mouth mmm
i think we have a winner
[Music]
oreo
hmm
um
there was once a time where i worked um
somewhere
and they had where i worked they had
some kind of
i don't know
not a collaboration but they were they
were like um
i think
i don't know why but we had like a [\h__\h]
ton of oreos at work to give away
to
customers i think
and therefore because we had so many
um the the employees were also eating a
[\h__\h] set of oreos all day
and
um because of that i kind of got sick of
oreos
but this is a fresh oreo flavor and i
enjoyed it this is good
we have one more snack it looks like
yeah
one more snack and i'm so sorry i don't
know why the [\h__\h] this is the last step
it is not what you were hoping for
i don't know why they didn't include the
one snake snake snake snack that
everyone thinks of when they think of
guatemala snacks i
i don't understand
but the last snack
nantes
okay
[Music]
barbie hurry
why
milkshake flavor
viva um
[Music]
originally is german okay but that's
okay this is a flavor that's special i
think not in not just never seen this
one here before
uh
barbie flavor
barbie
haribo
magical
magical horrible
[Music]
what
what is this and why do we need it
what are these shaped after
oh they smell they smell good
oh hearts some are shaped like hearts
they're sticking together
what is this oh i think that's supposed
to be a bee oh it's the barbie bee
it's the barbie beer
let me try that one
then um
hmm
this is good
there's also a yellow one
um
which is also shaped like the
barbie b
um
and the pink another pink one
what is that even supposed to be
what is that
[Music]
where did it go
i was looking at the screen
did it fall over there on the floor
[Music]
am i blind
i think i dropped it
oh yeah it's on the floor it's on the
floor
[Music]
it looks really weird
what the hell is this
hmm
i guess it was just supposed to be a
bean or it didn't look like a beef
oh well oh wow oh well this was it
i'm sorry guys nothing in the guatemala
box it says
here nothing in it was from guatemala
i don't know what to do should i change
the thumbnail
[Music]
five minute rule now it will probably
take longer than five minutes for me to
pick it up
[Laughter]
but but guys we have a we have a good
amount of quiz in the back okay
all right let me let me let me read the
quiz to you and also not only the quiz
but there is
in these snack boxes at the end of their
pamphlet they do write a
like a recipe from the country and guess
what the recipe here guatemala recipe is
choco bananas
chocolate bananas really why
but frozen ones
there is always money in the banana
stand
yeah
there is a recipe for i mean i don't
need a recipe for chocolate bananas no
wait there's another they didn't even
put a recipe there
okay anyway
let's do the quiz
there's six questions
uh let's see
maybe
uh maybe i'm gonna do
let's do a poll
one
two
three but you guys are gonna use google
probably don't use google okay don't
look it up don't use wikipedia or google
or whatever
um the question is number one welcome
and welcome to the quiz
the
guatemalan author who got a nobel prize
in 1967 for literature
is
who
[Music]
i heard that name before
answer time ten seconds ten
nine
eight
seven
six
five
four
three
two
one the answer is
a
migrate
uh seems like
um
majority thought it was pablo
okay
[Music]
now
okay in the end in the end one
one but still
at the moment where i gave you the
answer it was still number two so you
lost
okay number question number two
which country is not
oh
geography it's not a neighbor country of
guatemala
a
honduras
b
mexico
c
chile
um
is it
a wait
oh wait no that might be
that is
near guatemala i don't know if it's
neighboring to it uh ten nine
uh eight uh seven six
five four four two one
oh you guys know your geography well huh
pretty clear answer here it is
nice i didn't know i did not know
question question number three on which
day
uh
how do i
on which day did guatemala uh or does
guatemala celebrate its independency
from spain on the fifth oh wait i didn't
do mine
don't look it up guys
don't look it up
one
two
three okay and on the 15th september on
the 4th of july or on the 9th of october
go go go go go go go go go 10 second
delay there is quite the delay
seven
six
five
four
three
two
one
you guys don't seem very sure about this
one the correct answer is a
uh
15th 15th september oh no no now we get
some correct answers oh
15 september apparently which is close
to my uh debut anniversary um
noise
okay
uh we have three more questions
turn on your brain juices
[Music]
okay
what is the longest river in guatemala
a amazonas river
b
usumatinta river or sea
the mayan river
of noaa
i have no idea
maybe the amazonas river but does it
actually go for guatemala
i don't know
you tell me
sorry about the delay
sorry about the delay i don't know why
we have such a big delay
[Music]
hmm
one minute okay i'll wait a bit longer
ten
nine
eight
uh seven
six
five
four
it's in brazil okay three
two
one
the right answer is
b
the uh
river
[Music]
yay
i'm sorry i don't know where these
places the rivers are
i don't know do you guys know what the
biggest river in austria is no you don't
do you even know where the biggest
mountain nostra is
no you don't so don't judge me
all right next question
one
two
three okay
what is
it
why is this this isn't just like an
individual answer question but okay what
is one of the most popular
uh dishes of guatemala a
tamales
or tomatoes
b
black beans and rice
or c
nachos
[Music]
what is tomatoes
let me look that up
[Music]
a traditional
mesoamerican dish made of masa a dough
made from
mixtamalized corn what are these words
which is themed in a corn husk or banana
leaf the wrapping can even be discarded
for our feeding or used as a place
what is this
looks interesting
that looks interesting wait what's
inside what corn
what is that
what is the answer
let's see you guys say number one the
answer is
yes thomas
tamales good job chad good job
okay last one
one
two
three okay last one is what does oh what
does the name guatemala mean
lakes
or b country of the trees or c country
of the mayas well wouldn't it be
[Music]
is it not
my guess
maybe not maybe that's a maybe that's a
trick question
here uh oopsie uh [\h__\h]
[Music]
we had a little bit of a chitchat that
uh it stands for good amelia
guatemala good amelia
but let's see what what country
is it what kind of country is it
country of the trees country of the seas
the first one is country of the
uh lakes second one is country of the
trees and third one is country of the
mayas
because yeah they have the maya empire
and all that yeah yeah yeah wouldn't
that make sense
but no the answer is b
country of the trees
apparently
well uh people from guatemala would
probably know
but everyone else probably voted for uh
a anc
uh oh it's because of all the
rainforests probably
let me see is that really true
wikipedia says
[Music]
nothing wikipedia says nothing
but apparently it's country of the trees
because of the rainforest yeah
okay
that was the quiz
well you guys knew more than me i think
are there any statements about the
snacks why did i put them in there
no
oh
[Music]
nope
oh there was a chance that they would
have put like um
cheez-it the the first snack
instead of cheddar they would have put
in parmesan apparently but it depends
so that was
guatemala
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
for these snacks um
i don't know guys should i change the
thumbnail on the title or should we keep
it i'm not sure the thing is
here is an announcement listen up
everybody the next snack box i have
already here with me
and it will be
spain
spanish snack box so we might again see
some similar things uh and it kind of
connects to
this snack box i would say yeah the next
one is spain snack box
keep it
[Music]
maybe i'll keep it yeah
uh
but maybe i just changed the title not
the thumbnail
yes
[Music]
i know
yeah more snacks more snacks i won't do
it right away i will do it um
probably in in the beginning of the next
month
we're staying in the spanish family
exactly
[Laughter]
yes spain is in europe i know i know i
am aware of it i've been to spain before
but i didn't buy any snacks there i went
to restaurants but i didn't get any
snacks or so
so i'm looking forward to that and
hopefully you guys will be there as well
to check out the snacks the supposedly
snacks of spain
you know when my subscription of this
runs out
that is when this series will not be a
regular thing anymore if anything i will
try to get some people to send me
original uh
put together
on their own snack boxes
so that we can be sure that we get
what's really um
popular in that country
i was thinking i want to do a uk
snapbox
um i did see some on amazon
but maybe i can get someone
who lives in the uk
to get me one
and then we can always do an australian
one and perhaps um we can do maybe a
maybe a canada snack box
um
what else seems to be
manageable
french i think i could do a french snack
box i have a friend in france
i think i can do an italy snack box too
i have friends in italy
[Music]
yeah oh i can do a polish snack box i
have friends in poland
um
yeah but it has to be somewhere where i
have friends and i'm not gonna ask fans
you know because i need to give them my
address yeah has to be somewhere where i
know someone
oh yeah indonesian snack books yes yes
yes yes sisters we can ask garena
yeah yeah definitely
i'll ask elena to make me an indonesian
snack box
but for a while longer we're gonna be
using the snack boxes from this company
and hope for some good snack boxes
hungarian snack boxes yes that works too
and and and
what else
what do i want i want
i want to try
[Music]
i don't know
so far everything i've mentioned i'm
interested in
[Music]
cursed snack box
no no no only good snacks only good
snacks
worldwide friends yes isn't it nice to
have friends all over the world
beautiful
and dutch
oh yes i have a friend over there i want
to get a dutch snack box oh i think that
one would be really good
[Music]
a lot of the other countries that you
guys are
mentioning i don't have any friends in
unfortunately
um
at least i don't know of them
i don't have a friend in malaysia
i think
i also don't recall having a friend in
mexico
do i have a friend in mexico
i don't think so
i have a friend in brazil though
so if i
if this if this company is not doing a
brazil snack box within my subscription
then we can do an original one sent put
together and sent to me by a friend hmm
hot timeless
you mean australian or just snacks put
together by hachema because then we
might have a lot of
uh tarantulas and
weird [\h__\h]
that is something she should be selling
a hot summer snack box with the weirdest
snacks you can think of
all right you guys we're gonna read
super chats now so thank you for um
being here um
in my snack box stream if you wanna see
more i have uh the korean snack book
stream on my channel publicly and a
worldwide international snack box stream
on my members only
so yeah check them out if you want to i
think they were pretty interesting as
well
[Music]
uh
[Laughter]
oh you know what that would be the only
thing probably that i would be eating in
hanjoma's snack box the gyoza oh and udo
udon noodles she likes to use udon
noodles i think
okay we'll read super chats now because
i need to read the ones from yesterday
and from today
and and then i'll go today's a fairly
short stream yes yes
uh tomorrow by the way is the vr chat
dance collab also again on my channel
because i am the teacher so uh i'm
looking forward to having you guys there
it will be with all of the myth members
so that's exciting
yeah
let me change the bgm
there we go
ah oh before you guys go
um
[Music]
is
hey
[Music]
yes
oh do you guys you guys know this show
um
rmt recommended it to me and i started
watching it and i think it's uh
it's originally spanish but i'm not sure
from which country um but it's called
hotel
it's like a dramatic
um
spanish
what's it called again
downtown abbey
this it's a spanish
more dramatic downtown abbey
you guys know it
rnt is really addicted to that show i
started watching it too
never heard of it
spans perfect oh thank you
gracias gracias
grace crazy yes
[Music]
novella
season
currently
glow
glow hotel not gura hotel
gone
grand de grande grande
big hotel
[Music]
it's like a spanish downton abbey that's
what it feels like
um
maybe you guys can watch it how do you
guys not know it what
what i guess you don't watch telenovelas
i don't really watch telenovelas either
but uh rmt recommended it
[Music]
they say they say okay uh
is there a similar word
to this in spanish there's a this
italian word called alora that you say
when it's like okay let's do this now
it's like all right or odd is there a
word like this in spanish
um
something like
alora i wonder
it just says bien when i look it up on
d-bell
i will read super chats now
where do i start we need to read from
yakuza when let me go to my
other office
oh [\h__\h] what happened
what happened where's my table
the [\h__\h]
never mind
i need to clean up here
let's let's stay here
let's stay here then i don't know what
happened there
ah
it's so
similar
oh nice nice nice i can remember that
maybe
vamos vamos
vamos
let me put up the screen or i don't know
we can put something there what should
we put there
how about
how about some uh oh how about my
schedule
it's the beginning of the week skill
still we can put my schedule there
everything is uh going according to
keikaku
please read the schedule correctly
it goes from left side to the bottom and
then right side to the bottom and then
sunday on the very bottom
please pay close attention to it okay
uh tuesday with snack box review
tomorrow is kfb vr dance school with
holo myth
oh no h um
uh-huh please write the schedule card
shut up what do you mean right correctly
there's no mistake on this schedule you
guys are just reading what the hell did
we write it correctly you're reading
correctly
damn
these chickens always demanding things
always demanding things but they don't
have any
idea and let me see what about the super
chat those is this correct
there oh there are supposedly
some that i've already read in the same
stream but before my vacation because
wait [\h__\h]
i have a problem i have a problem
i have a problem
no because i i used the
original elven ring uh
reservation slot stream reservation
and then change it into yakuza but i
read the ones that came in from
ellen ring
i think
i did
i think i did did i did it i'm so
confused
i re yeah i'm really confused now
i reused it
[Music]
and then i mean i remember the last
super chat
there
or almost the last one
was it
this is really confusing
this is more confusing than i thought it
would be
is this really where it starts
um
sheesh
i need there are yakuza
yes but
did i read this um maybe these people
are here
they're all saying welcome back i read
these ones before
but they have the yakuza thumbnail
which means
they came in for alden ring and then i
privated it
so when where is the last one
it should be like
it should be
this one somewhere here okay i found the
ultra new bread super chat
[Music]
okay so let me put up the thumbnail
it is
here is this one
just gonna put it
behind me
on the tv
and then we'll get started
you're the cutest boss the most
beautiful phoenix very talented and
smart girl superb dancer amazing singer
your angelic voice and your 11 out of 10
looks make my heart go doki doki you're
very sweet and loving not a tyrant i
realized that in the ur
where does it continue
i
don't see
the rest of the super chat i think my
super chats are all mixed up again
i think they're all mixed up again
oh right now that's the end of the
sentence i thought it was
oh wait
so it's like i realized that in the ur
period
okay there was no period there
i will imagine the period
doesn't change your sentence you will be
staying in the usual room for a while so
keep on uh reflecting on your words and
your actions okay
yes
[Music]
doc joseph thank you for the rest of the
chat i bring you collected tribute boss
from a simp in sagawa's territory
i threatened him with one of your dance
battles if he didn't pay up he promises
to kiss the morning star and swear
loyalty
oh
okay wait who is it is it you
who is that person
show me his face
show me his face then i need to know but
okay i'll take your offering thank you
for swearing your loyalty to me
i kiss back
you kiss my morning star i kiss you on
your cheek thank you for your support
thank you
thank you thank you thank you
and we have a korean name here
does deep l not have korean
anyway let's put it into papago
[Music]
no text with it why why why
the gamer created
um
for the red super chat this is the week
everyone has been waiting for i wish
everyone's staying healthy and safe good
afternoon good evening and good night
thank you yes it's it's a very very
special week
that we've waited for for a long time
indeed yes um are you guys excited i'm
excited i'm excited
yay thank you thank you i hope you're
gonna enjoy the concert
yeah thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you very much for your generosity
tai chi i don't know what that me is um
related to anymore
unfortunately
you need to be more more
explicit and detailed in your texts in
the super chats
your voice stephen adams thank you this
week gonna be legendary hell yeah
i'm excited but with qualifications what
does that mean
i don't know
i don't get it
so excited oh my god hi bought my
spontaneous last night nice yes uh i
recommend you guys to get the spawn
ticket early
earlier because i think there's been
times where
um people have issues buying it with the
card or people
or like i think in previous
concerts there may have been times where
the site wasn't working so well
uh because of all the traffic so
make sure to get the
um
ticket as soon as possible
[Music]
um
you had these shoes you had issues
i'm glad you have it uh you have the
ticket now
yeah yeah got mine the day it was
announced that you're in it
first time i bought from spawn i had to
call the bank to authorize overseas
purchases oh oh yeah that is that sounds
uh complicated that's why i'm telling
you guys to get it early in time
listen to me listen to your headphones
listen to your boss
um
[Music]
night
thank you thank you thank you
nice to see you again felix how you
doing
hope you're doing well thank you for the
generous support thank you
next time next time you're gonna tell me
a story again all right
[Music]
i became a fan after watching an
interesting video about destroying a
colleague's trash can
it's my first time watching live so i'm
looking forward to it we'll kill oh
thank you
i mean that was for the yakuza stream
but still thank you maybe you're here
right now as well
[Music]
probably not
where are you
where are you where are you
i mean it is it is a little bit past
midnight but you could still be awake
spawn doesn't work from germany yeah it
should work
it should work
maybe try a different browser or
something
that trash can was not meant to be a
chair it's not my fault that it broke
down
i don't see him in the chat
he's slacking
he's not on his shift
no wait are you is that you
no that's not you
it's not here
it's unbelievable
unbelievable
i'll see i'm gonna see him
and mr kyle brown duncan
heat action tip the icon will appear if
you grab an enemy grab a weapon in front
of an enemy or if an enemy is on the
ground
don't press any direction buttons
okay
i'll try to keep that in mind
2 45 that's not an excuse
cold thank you for the pinky
it looks more beautiful today your
morning star my morning star looks more
beautiful
thank you colt come sign it up for the
pink super chat wow where did all my
korean bros come from again
seems like recently i haven't seen many
of them but in the stream from yesterday
and stream from today
there is um more than usual again
nice to see you guys
[Music]
unknown thank you for the pinky my
kotoni plushie finally arrived and i
love it so much now the only official
kiara merch that i don't have is the
first myth t-shirt that you designed i
really regret not buying it when it was
available now
oh
yeah if you have everything besides that
man that is a little bit regretful
[Music]
that is now a rare item isn't it
i do have the plushie should i show you
guys do you want to see it
[Music]
it is
so thick
okay so
let me show you
[Music]
economy
here it
is cute
cute
it has no feet though
has no feet
it's kind of flat on the bottom so that
i can so that it can stand up
cute
it is pretty big it's like uh the
perfect size to give it a nice hug
[Music]
you can play basketball with it it's
orange just like a basketball
just kidding don't play basketball with
kotori just kidding it's a joke it's
joke
don't play basketball with kotori
please
[Music]
my boyfriend wants to formally propose
to me but i think it's too much trouble
just go straight to the marriage
registration what do you think is a
marriage proposal really necessary i
already said yes
i mean
i've never been proposed to
but i wouldn't i
i think every
okay maybe not ever because you say it's
not necessary but i think almost
everybody dreams of uh uh a cute proper
romantic proposal
that means something that you can look
back on and remember like even if it's
planned then i i saw in like netflix
shows and whatever in cute romantic
movies or whatever that some women
are unhappy with the way that their
partner is proposing to them so they
make them they kind of start controlling
it and make them pre repropose
by
telling them i want this and this and
this and that
and then yeah
and then
you get the perfect proposal right
exactly like you always dreamed about
hmm
yeah well for me i would i would uh
wouldn't need to be i don't think i
would be that controlling
but
i would at least
like it to be somewhat meaningful
have some build up to it as well but who
knows if that will ever happen
oh i should turn off the camera again
hold on
i can show you something else i have
some more merchandise you want to see
more merchandise
oyster
[Music]
i can't spend too much time messing
around but
i feel
i don't know what the hell this was man
okay okay one sec one set
[Music]
oh
yay
let me let me ask something uh
manager song
gen ma you're watching this
genma you're watching this
are you watching
[Music]
me the merch i got
while
oh go with the
um
i'm asking if it's okay to show because
like i see some merchandise some whole
life merchandise but i don't know
where it's from like from what event or
whatever so i don't even know this is
already uh
already published or
actually um i actually don't know where
is this from
the omo cat one is okay
[Music]
look i though this one too
look
it's the catalog i like the catalog
cause like there's
things
oh my god interviews and stuff really
interesting
[Music]
oh
this is the this is a parker
i want to say i didn't open i opened uh
some of the t-shirts but i didn't open
this stuff yet
let me see
[Music]
i took the tracks here to call
you guys can still get it there's a
restock coming
and some of these are available anyway
right now in some sizes on omoket
omo c-18
looks nice
yeah the print is very big on the back
and in the front we have like a
polo
[Music]
writing
looks cool
looks very sporty
[Music]
now we have
another t-shirt
another group t-shirt
oh it's pretty small yeah i got an s
size
look
nice print
this little logo
that they came up with i really like
that one
it has all of our weapons and elements
in it
these ones are still
um on omocat shop some of them are out
of stock but please just wait and then
there might be
more stock coming
[Music]
oh
there's some more stuff i got so much
merch yo
look at these buttons
from all of us
yeah
then we have all the caps
i got all of them
i i felt a little bit bad asking for um
every single piece of clothing from
everyone else so um
mostly when it came to the clothing i
got my solo stuff and
uh the the general one but for the caps
i got all of them and for the keychains
and stuff as well
although i probably won't even be
wearing the caps but i thought at least
these ones i can line up nicely but it's
hard for us to wear our own merch you
know
um
[Music]
i like the color of this one
pastel yellow i want to unpack this one
i'm trying to grab something in summer
in summer you should get this one
because it feels
like a great material to wear
in
color yeah the fabric is
a little bit see-through a little bit
so very good for uh summer because it
won't be so
thick
[Music]
yeah that's the merchandise that i got
i got some like whole live merchandise
some recent whole live merchandise but
i'm not sure um where exactly that is
from so i guess it's probably better for
me to not show it
anyway i guess we can have this up here
for
advertisement purposes
oh camera
camera
there we go
yeah yeah
yeah
i got i think i got two
two part uh two hoodies two of those one
of that
and
two pixel t-shirts of mine and so on
yum yum
it's really good quality anything on the
back oh on the back no i don't think so
nope nothing on the back
yes
wet t-shirt contest um
it would work really well maybe someone
will wear this on the famous
american spring break
we don't have that here but uh maybe
we'll see some cute girls wearing this
on top of their cute swimsuits
please take some photos from me
yolo shikku
yeah cute t-shirts right i like them i
like them very much
i really like the the art of this um
little food truck here
i thought the art was so adorable when i
first saw it
like having uh um
having a how to call it a mobile a
movable version of my store like in the
form of a truck
i think is really
cute and me and the chicken suit i don't
know why i'm in the chicken suit but
they look
really cute maybe one there we can have
a food truck like that
there's some birds some kotori sitting
on top of the flag and the food truck
some really
yummy looking roasted chicken there
noise
when the first kfp store movable one two
i guess the arts that i used yes looked
like a movie yeah yeah yeah true true
true true you have a good memory yeah
when we first came up with the menu
i think
the art that i showed was something like
a food truck yes
or like um maybe not a food truck but
something like a smaller not really a
restaurant
a small version of uh kfp
hey
yes
anyway i should read super chat sorry i
kind of got uh distracted and
off topic
[Music]
gold
where was that where was it
so go get yourself that fancy proposal
that you can think back on years later
and be like ah wasn't that nice
thank you for the pinky
thank you thank you since you eating
wanna hear a story about my cat
one time she ate some of my hair and it
came with her poop the whole poop can't
come out and just hang in there and she
ran straight to me
and yelled at me and asked me to take it
out out of here
i see
why i am i'm very very tolerant of
weird super chats and stories about cats
but why was it necessary to tell me that
i wonder
[Music]
we probably will never understand
uh
but but at least she came to you to ask
for help rather than
i don't know i guess throwing it around
in the in the living room or whatever on
a carpet or so i guess that's that's my
comment i don't know what else to say
thank you for the support
dr joseph
oh yes taiyaki would be nice right now
um seems like you like i like the same
things that i do oreo and vanilla a good
order
[Music]
i made a list with the names of all the
chickens who told you to break your leg
they're probably wishing you the luck
but they may have jinxed you uh-huh
now we know whose fault it is i
recommend preemptively frying them just
to be safe
i mean probably a lot of them are
already fried
yeah
uh some of you guys
are very very very
hard to say
brave even though you've been here for a
long long long time but probably that's
the reason why you're
living so dangerously
um
um but i'm glad you like the dance
collab cause
tomorrow is another one yeah
in the middle of the night in japan but
maybe you can watch the vault um
i'm gonna be teaching them another dance
and i let them choose i gave them a few
um suggestions of what i could teach
them and what i could play on stream so
and i chose everyone chose the same song
everyone seems to like that specific uh
song and dance so yeah
everyone will be happy
and the focus this time will be mostly
on inna and kelly and gouda and ahmed
will be
taught as well but they will have more
freedom i will focus more on inna's and
kelly's moves
um
since they are my new students
and you will see callie's little poli
outfit for the first time because the
model was uh didn't exist before and the
and preacher was working on it faster
for the sake of this stream and it's
ready and we are gonna use it for the
first time in that collaboration
although yeah it will be six a.m for
callie so
i hope she's gonna be okay
there will be all five of us supposedly
i hope kelly will be able to wake up um
i'm a bit worried about that but but but
but it should be dijoba
ina's model was already public i really
liked her model
the the school uniform loopholey model
that she has but probably a lot of you
guys haven't seen it yet so um
you know had one already yes if you look
it up you probably are going to find it
[Music]
although i think it was a work in
progress and not a full body
either
so thank you moto sun
chef star dancing your boy stephen adams
dance and dances on dancing and boohoo
you for the pinky yeah i don't i know
you don't need any advice on being an
idol but if you ever find yourself a
little lost remember these very
important things in being an idol number
one i love you number two you love me
number three step and go
ah
[Music]
wonderful
thank you
for the pinky
is
yeah that sounds like 24 hours
cinderella to me
i love you it's a mother mo
you love me no papa
m19281 thompson smg dancing
one jane
for the pinky
down
first time being in your stream tango i
really love your songs and spirit to
cheer everybody up with your voice i
only watched your clips and
and
[Applause]
something in korean
[Music]
uh clips i don't know how that spells in
english but i will try to watch your
streams often
please do thank you thank you i would be
glad to have you in my streams or even
the vaults you can just watch the
archives afterwards because it's
probably at a bad time for you but
yeah i would be pleased to have you
around
thank you for being
[Music]
i saw this one i thought it was funny
[\h__\h] i just tapped out of the
super chattels [\h__\h]
it's
[Music]
um it is and looking for the top thank
you soon
panopticon thank you for the pinky hello
kaiser and the cooking i loved your
dance stream it was a true blessing oh
it will go down in hollow legends oh i
also love your elvenar streams i enjoy
your funny tangents rants and other
things that make you you keep up the
great work my aussie i'm your aussie
thank you
i'm happy to hear that thank you for
letting me be your aussie and yeah i i
enjoyed the dance stream i wish i had
more stamina i used to have more stamina
if i had more now then i would probably
be able to enjoy it even more but it was
fun and and i will um hopefully be
glitching out less tomorrow but yeah
dancing is fun and i i want to show off
some of the choreographies i remember
i'm actually surprised i still remember
them after all all these years from when
i first picked them up
but it's it's finally one of those
things that one of my skills one of my
specifically
kiwawa skills that the others don't
necessarily share
um that i can finally show off yeah
i
i wasn't wasn't able to show them off
until we really got into vr and i was
able to use my full body thankfully so
yeah even even though in vr it's not as
great as dancing without vr because it's
heavy
and annoying and makes me feel really
hot and blah exhausted
but
it's better than nothing
yeah
muscle memory yep yeah yeah it is a
thing it's like i don't know driving
riding a bicycle i guess
[Music]
i mean i do sometimes forget some uh
moves but if i look at the choreography
reference again then i remind remember
it very quickly
um i'm like oh yeah this is this is how
the
that move was supposed to go nagoho
yeah i'm glad i can show it off yeah
now i'm even stronger yes yes yes and i
do plan on using the low poly models um
even afterwards because um after the
after the
concert because i wanna
i don't wanna use the models uh before
doing a proper 3dw as i said before and
also i think the low poly models
they fit well into the
into the world that we had created for
the wealthy models i think they fit in
nicely i almost think that our
proper models may be a little bit too
too detailed and too realistic
i mean it would still be great and all
that and we'll
use them eventually but
i think i think
i think um
yeah we need to get more use out of the
low poly models and they work great i
think they're good in between
for like the wealthy models are cute and
and comedic and
um
small
but you don't see much body movement and
then the proper 3d models are big and
proper
and
cool and all that
and you can see the body movement the
best in those however they're not so
comedic and all that so if i want to do
a stream where i want to combine the
body movement with comedy elements i
feel like that's when i need to use the
low poly ones you know what i mean yeah
yeah
and ahmed agrees with me
oh we tested something out um
i mean i'm always like yo can someone
help me test something out and and me
and glitter were like yo yes let's do it
and then we
tested out
um i hope it's okay to say this
i'm such a [\h__\h] genius because um
this will be helpful to sync up the
audio a bit more properly during the
collaboration but also it will be
helpful for other things we now are able
to do like karaoke
in vr
there's like
um she had something programmed that
like you can put a youtube video in
there and then you press play and then
it plays it and then and then
and then uh you can look at the screen
together and you can also sync up even
more but just by playing it there it's
pretty much all
already
mostly synced up but you can still
adjust it in case it's not synced up
perfectly and then and then she um made
the microphone props so that if you pick
them up you don't hear your surroundings
so it's not confusing if um
if the if the other person is not in
sync
um but it will come out synced to
the third person who is listening to it
so i guess we would need someone to
capture the
third person
point of view audio if you know what i
mean anyway it was really cool so me and
me and kuda were like singing and almond
was recording it
you will never hear that because it's um
we were just testing it out and we were
both singing really really awkwardly
with no effort
um but
you know what that means
we can basically use that
as a karaoke collab method
without being together in person because
this was so easy to use
i know there was this this software that
i wanted to use uh try out eventually
with gooda to do um a karaoke
collaboration um stream but i never got
into it and now we have this in vr chat
and it makes it so much easier you don't
even have to use the vr models if you
want you can just have it running in the
background i guess and use it basically
as a tool to do kind of okay so i wrote
too good like yo
we can just use this now and she was
like yeah let's do it
yes yes
yes
yeah
the promised
should be happening
soon then
maybe maybe within this month
yes yes yes
yes
is
she is a freaking genius i mean okay she
didn't um we gotta give props to
um the person who wrote that basically
though coded it i guess i guess you
would code it
program it
um i think it was uh the name was no
no ref
oh
wait something like that i will probably
properly give credits during the stream
um
for sure uh the person has been helping
out with
a lot of the things in vr chat for us um
coding a lot of the things and working
really fast and really hard
amen is the brain and that person uh
carries it out i suppose
no not the ref pro that's it
yes sasuka
no no ami didn't code it or name i
didn't program it but i think it was
like we were looking for a solution for
the sinking
up thing and i think that's where it
came from
genius
i'm excited i'm excited we can do
you know i believe i live so far away
from everyone and of course collabs are
just not that easy um can't be done that
quickly but now i can do i can do listen
i can do a karaoke with nana t
she doesn't even need a vr chat model we
can just do it without we can do it with
our normal life 2d we just need to have
vr10 in the background i'll just give
her i don't know some frog model or
something
or oh an orange model i don't know but
we can do
i can do karaoke oh my god that's
exciting i didn't think that far yet i
didn't think that far but now there's so
many possibilities to do
[Music]
i will tell i will tell her about it
because we haven't done the karaoke in a
while when i was still in japan me and
ninety did of collab karaoke
two times
two times actually quite often
actually pretty often um we both like to
sing and we both like to show off our
dance moves oh wait i guess she could uh
because roboco i mean did that too when
she collab with double close senpai
um when i'mma collab with roboconsent in
vr chat you guys maybe saw it
but robocall simply used her own model
within vr chat
you know what you know what we'll keep
this
um karaoke option for another time
until i had my 3dw and i'm open to use
my own model in vr chat someday and then
we'll do
my real 3d model with nana's real 3d
model within
cut open
and we can even dance a little bit
oh that means i have to tell manatee to
get uh vr equipment
i'll let her know i will let her know
so exciting
wait we could even do
horatorii
[Music]
um
just the correction there are male
nipples
nipples and yakuza seven and you're yeah
i already read this one
you're particularly happy whenever they
showed up most notably in shirtless
fight scenes yeah i think i played
yakuza 7 not so long after playing raiza
and in rhiza i was so disappointed that
they didn't have um nipples on the big
open male chests it just looked weird
so
um it's not like i it's not like you
know i'm not
particularly into
nipples but i just feel like when
there's an
anime game character and they don't have
nipples i don't know it looks so weird
to me
yeah
looks weird to me
um
but yeah yeah thankfully yakuza has
nipples
thank you and jacob 47
thank you we're done with bianca's super
jets
um let me check something
[Music]
and
yeah it looks weird
looks so weird like they're a barbie
doll or something
[Music]
and yeah the placeholder is i rarely use
that one these days
um hmm nostalgic
thank you for the pinky i just wanted to
say that i really appreciate what you're
doing eating all those snacks so you can
maintain your thickness of your ties to
keep the work immoral high is a very
smart move
you're a true businesswoman and you have
my deepest respect yeah that is exactly
what i'm doing
now
phoenix kiwawa has the same
the same weight and the same body shape
always it doesn't change because i'm a
vetoma
i don't even need to try
it is a no effort thing
yep it is a magical thing
not applicable duncan dr joseph thank
you for the right super chat snack time
let's go holy [\h__\h] that's um a nice
snack though
yes nice variety and the boxiness and uh
just remember that i still need to take
a shower before i stream a very cold
shower
shout out to uh yeah
um
yes i had this piece of art in um i have
a folder with fan art and i always save
fan art that i like uh with the name of
the artist uh so that i will
know who drew it when i use it one day
and i have finally used this one i had
this one lying around a while
it's it's uh i think a lot of you guys
don't even remember
that he drew me before but yes yes
it's a nice piece of art isn't it
back in july
holy [\h__\h] yeah that's so long ago
it's it's really interesting to see um
other whole life mamas and papas
draw me in their style i mean there
haven't been many
um
uh
uh foreign
drew me also before and it looked really
cool
uh
who else
there have not been many
who
was there
apocalypse
yeah
was there anyone else
my brain
is empty
was there any other mama papa that
removed before
[Music]
need more need more need more need more
no
[Music]
i don't think mel's mama drew me before
portugal also now
don't no i don't think so i would
remember that
nobby mama not yet but i'm sure we can
get her to draw me if i do a collab with
her
which i want to do anyway
because i love navi sensei navi mama
if vada aduko drew you i would pass away
me too
i really like my article
son's style and she's into hello project
just like me
[Laughter]
[Music]
so i feel some kind of connection you
know
mello's mama drew you before
it showed me show me on twitter
if she did then i must have seen it but
i must have forgotten it
no way
please refresh my memory and show me
oh i'm on twitter right now
[Music]
did she
she drew me and callie
together in one picture
huh
that must have been ages ago
oh i see it
i'm retweeting it now
i may
have missed that completely i don't
think
it i don't think it came up on my
on my heart
even
[Music]
no she used arts of ashes as well but
sometimes
um especially if there's too much skin
color or too much orange and all that it
doesn't show up in the arts of ash's
hashtag because twitter sees it as
something too sensitive and kind of
shadow bands it
it happens before
it happened before a lot of times
actually
[Music]
it looks so good
i need to save that now
thank you for telling me i'll use it for
uh if i ever do a collab with cali again
i'll use it as a thumbnail
um yeah she streamed the process
apparently anyway anyway anyway anyway i
didn't hurry super tired i need to read
super chats i need to read some pajamas
i need to read super chat
we're done soon though so
you actually also sent a pinky soon
after that hey boss if you haven't
kissed me for my red super chat yet oh i
have could i give christina that kiss
that's okay i'll give christina one to
two months ago christina did that
adorable panel if you're giving a glow
stick to a chimpkin and it's third fast
week a long two months but we're here
yes that was so so so so so great so
christina
here's the kiss for you my extra kiss
extra kiss for you
hmm
that panel is coming true
can you share your favorite photo with
us
why no you guys are also good at
collecting fan art probably better than
me
two months two months since that art
apparently yeah
pepsi don geshen patsy duncan
for a pinky hey boss i like to combine
my pinky with ducks to make it red ah
give manzanita a big smooch okay i
already did mission accomplished all
according to kekaku the chicken with the
glow sticks will finally be happening
and i can't wait to cheer you on yay
the third face will definitely be one to
remember
i i am excited but i also i also want
to
um already plan
like a solo concert or i don't know what
would be nice is a holo myth concert one
day
yeah
more more screen time for us
i want that
i'm getting greedy now
[Music]
isn't that slowpoke
in germany
[Music]
thank you very much for the rest of the
chat here's a purple for you
thank you for coming today and watching
even even though it's late at night
thank you so much
hope you enjoyed the stream
alert vega thank you come sanitation
science
so many japanese uh japanese korean
people here in the super chats again
did they think i was doing another
korean snack box reveal
or was it just a good time it was past
midnight
[Music]
um
ppp
spanish today i have pronounced it
spanishly
but i'm not sure because you
donated in canadian dollars
maybe it's not joje maybe it's george
you know where i learned the
pronunciation of jorge
jorge from there there was like a german
germany's next top model and they one of
the juries one of the
yeah people there uh was like a catwalk
trainer called
very very fashionable
very very
muchos
spanish energy
and there i learned that his name is not
pronounced george but
okay or something like that
oh very interesting character that was
done
thank you for the pinky
uh was this uh spanish to kumasita
what's kumasita
is it how are you is that even spanish
i can't find it
i can't find anything
i just heard it before
[Music]
you guys will help me out with that
i don't know why
um
how are you i doesn't mean how are you
mamacita
mama
come on
did i just make up or where does
kumasita not exist
did i mix up mamacita and como estas
mixed i mix it up i think optimus prime
thank you the gamer
thank you for the pinky
buenos diaz
especially
is
it just cut off there and help it you
should be happy sit down
okay saying good morning
hope you enjoyed the glad madam sweets
by the way your spanish is really
improving thank you
and you even speak better than several
people and oh thank you
i'm not sure about some certain uh
letters pronunciations but um
i can't imagine some of them um
[Music]
oh yeah apparently they can help me with
a keyboard
mr casper
uh hey
[Music]
thank you
i was planning for isa to order just
plastic eggs um to paint them and then
hang them up as decoration
plastic empty small eggs crunchy spirit
of pakka danger and cornish spirit
alpaca thank you thank you
sorry that there was nothing uh there
from your country sorry
[Music]
foreign
i think the company you're using is
putting these boxes together based on
sales in the country and not whether the
snacks are actually made there
yeah that would mean that they are
popular there which is as i said i think
one way to do it one way that i would
probably also do it just putting the
popular things
there together but they
one thing that i noticed is that i feel
like they don't really know what's
popular there um
they probably don't have someone
in each of those countries who really
knows
what the people eat there like they just
maybe they have one person who sends
stuff over there but maybe it's like an
80 year old
grandpa
who doesn't know what's popular nowadays
um
[Music]
avenged me
brendan that one land evo
[Music]
hawking cheeses okay
zero schneider duncan thank you
i haven't been in streams because i
cause when i can it's always spoiler
games so i'm extremely happy i was able
to join today's stream
well if there's spoilers then you should
just watch it from the beginning or play
the game while i'm playing it at the
same time
hope to be able to join more streams in
the future love you always thank you
love you too
i hope you'll be able to join more as
well well yakuza will be going on for a
while an elden ring are you missing out
on elder ring as well you should watch
elden ring at least because uh there's
not many spoilers there even though the
title says so i haven't
um gotten pretty i haven't gotten that
far
so
um you should watch it
you should watch it
yeah play ahead of me or just say [\h__\h]
it i'm gonna watch her
and then play the game myself maybe one
year later because at that point point
you will have forgotten
what the story was like anyway
i hope you can be there more often thank
you for coming though tomorrow is also
something you can watch because there's
no spoilers for tomorrow
thank you
henry salvador
have you had an austrian snack review no
i haven't but if you guys are interested
i can do that at some point as well
but i would most likely not only put
austrian originated snacks in there i
would just put stuff there that we eat
here because we like it
skye danke sonora
colonel kotori
sweetie dancing colonel kota isn't true
i guess yeah the original also doesn't
have feet
true
eugene comes
in
now that you mention it you know the
original kondoni icon
[Music]
is guatemala uh currency never seen that
before in my super chance i think
thank you
thank you thank you thank you hope you
enjoyed it i'm sorry about um
false advertisements getting your hopes
up and stuff
uh
thank you for the pink super chat comes
on
[Music]
it says
it's not even real korean it's just
english and japanese mixed up
in korean writing
[Music]
yo
i don't even know these songs you can't
make me ask them if i don't even know
the songs
saludosa miss amigos the k and b
n
k knp
no i will not ask because i don't even
know the songs how can i sing them if i
don't know that maybe i've heard them
before but i don't know them
no no no no no i refuse
you are local you loco logo
supernaf thank you soon thank you
happy belated birthday
jardmo
i wore your whole myth t-shirt as a good
luck charm to court last year
we win a taco dashi walks free
what the [\h__\h] was happening there
they say we are at wa
with each other
but they don't know we are on the same
side against the world our lawyer is a
teammate what
i mean we have a lawyer too but that's
so funny a teammate um representing a
takodachi in court you're wearing a
whole move t-shirt
oh wait maybe wait were you the
takodashi or were you just supporting in
the back
i remember that what you remember that
it's a story you guys know
well you'll be a good taco daddy in the
future hopefully
you may be not not guilty this time but
be careful next time don't get in
trouble don't get yourself in trouble
okay
what
[Music]
i'm a witness you were a witness what
the [\h__\h] what happened witness to what
you guys gotta tell me about this story
on twitter
maybe it was all maybe
maybe everyone in the court even the
judge yeah was the whole live fan and it
was all kind of an inside job
everyone was
biased parsley thank you for the pinky
hi guys what was my birthday yesterday
so here's a pinky i may not be as active
and chat or your twitter as i was before
but i'm still always watching every
stream live oh thank you good to know so
excited to see you on foodfest much love
much love back to you happy birthday
congratulations
i don't know why you're not so active
anymore but you're always welcome to say
hello to to remind me that you're still
there okay
hope you had a wonderful birthday and
celebrated
and and and and i hope you have a
wonderful year ahead of you all right
thank you very much and you seem to
share a birthday with cronie then
is it true europeans think our chocolate
in america tastes like vomit
um
are hershey's from america
i didn't like hershey's in general
i think yeah i think
from what i've heard is that american
chocolate tastes
uh
definitely
but personally
um i think i wouldn't say like i think
japanese chocolate for example tastes
more artificial
um and then from the snack box that i
ate
there were some american snacks i think
but it was mostly international so i
can't judge perfectly well just yet
but i think your guys's chocolate
probably tastes uh also artificial but
differently than japanese artificial see
kind of different
[Music]
hershey's are american
popular ingredient i think they would
work as an ingredient yeah maybe for
like chocolate chip cookies or something
like that
but just eating them like that no
no
[Music]
yeah
good for s'mores yeah i don't know using
it for something else but not eating it
like just the way it is um
can sing that for you probably my girl
in the lyrics
i've never tried singing it though
wait is there a spanish
[Music]
how can you fit so many words in one
sentence
[Music]
is
say that again
so
[Music]
i can kind of do the dance
i'm trying to dance here
ah
how was that
you don't really pronounce the y in the
song
[Music]
hey
do the dance tomorrow okay i'll get the
girls to do it unless i forget
[Music]
perfect oh
almost done
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you thank you oh thank you oh
thank you thank you chad
i can't roll my arms like that but i
can't roll it like they do in in
japanese language like uh
uh
you know there's a difference between
like this
and the r that they do like yakuza do
for example you know what i mean
um
like for example if i roll like this
then for example it would be fuzza
but that's not that's not how they say
it i can't roll it like they do
because it's a little bit of an l in
there
they don't say like that they don't say
uh
[Music]
oh
the same i don't think so not quite
spanish spanglish version of the ketchup
song
ketchup song
i i know that i just feel bad what it
sounds like ketchup
ketchup song
last catch up oh that's that song you
should have said ketchup song
lfct uh
wait
oh
[Music]
i can't play the music
oh god
oh god i can try
[Music]
never listen to the lyrics before
this is friday time feeling ready and
looking fun
boom be handle wait i need the the
lyrics come too late i need it uh
already on screen
uh
ketchup
ah
song
what was it spanglish
i remember this
[\h__\h] boomer song
wait that's not the spanglish lyrics
[\h__\h]
friday night is party time feeling ready
looking fine vanderbilt
with the magic in his eyes checking
every girl inside griffin like he does
the mumble and it's the man on the end
this is who's playing harder he's the
king
[Music]
oh my god
[\h__\h] when i when i grew up i thought the
lyrics of this song
are
follow the following keep in mind kiwa
are very small at this time
i i was i thought this was not spanish i
thought they were singing english
um
i say hey
and ha
and then some blah blah blah
having like and the boogie and the
boogie on the beach like dancing boogie
on the beach is what i thought
they were singing
[Laughter]
[Music]
it goes three times like that okay i
want to sing it again
one more try one more try
from the beginning
wait the video stopped
why did it stop
hey
hey hey friday night is party time
feeling ready looking fine vienna diego
grombe
with the magic in his eyes checking
every girl inside griffin like he does
the mambo and he's the man alien disco
flames
he's a king
[Music]
oh
the
[Music]
it's fading out let's go i'm sorry this
is awkward please just add the
instrumental to my voice later on
[Laughter]
[Music]
yay this really reminds me of when i was
younger and my mom
took me to italy
um
on on
a vacation
and i know this is spanish but this song
was on the radio all the time and i
think people
uh were dancing this like in in some
like i don't know
i don't know people were like listening
to this and vibing to this and all i
heard was boogie on the beach man
[Laughter]
it's so nostalgic i haven't heard this
one in such a long time
oh
[Music]
never knew this was uh actually proper
or not really proper but spanish
it has choreography yeah
i mean we can try this one too
and one of the girls know it too
i said hey
[Music]
more dances let's go
okay i needed to finish reading super
chats
i was like literally about to finish
and then this happened
what was the other one that you said if
i know this one then what is el baia de
gorilla let me look that one up maybe i
know this one too
melody
159 million views
ah
um
do i notice is this really this young
girl singing
no i don't know this
oh wait
the chorus
i might have heard the chorus before
oh my god
damn
this girl is this like
you know there was a face around you
know we talked about rebecca black the
other day but there was this face around
when rebecca black had friday released
um
where a lot of
wealthy
young
american kids
were bringing out all these weird
songs cringy songs right do you guys
remember that
and it was a whole thing like their
parents would pay
for them to get like one song produced
and to make them happy because their
kids wanted to become famous
be a superstar
uh
is this what happened to this girl as
well
but like in spanish
or
was this not one of these
cringe
fest
[Music]
there was like a lot of songs from these
young people
young
boys and girls
yes is it is this like that
is this like that
interesting
that stopped i mean i don't know
um i haven't seen
anything
uh like that in a long time
yeah but but out of that honestly
rebecca black's friday
was
one of the better ones i have no problem
with friday but there were like some
really really really bad ones
from these young kids
like
like really cringy ones
ah
they were so so cringy ones out there
have you heard of cassolina of course
i know gasolina
they only release a song or two and
dissipate exactly exactly
it's just like the parents trying to
make their kids happy
and then paying for producing one song
with some record label
that just
takes some money and does whatever
and then they produce a song that years
later the kids are gonna 100 regret that
they did
[Laughter]
um
oh it might have been the same studio
yeah
um
yeah yeah yeah and compared to those
friday was great
it's friday friday i'm getting up a
friday getting down getting down on
friday right let's get down let's get
down
double
[Music]
i'm dancing i'm dancing
anyway where was i
uh
where was i
i think i was here cruz thank you for
the pinky
oh let's get loud not down oh [\h__\h]
so i wanted you to roll your arse so you
can so can you read the spanish tongue
twister
and
wait i'm better at reading
[Music]
tongue twisters in spanish than i am in
german i only made one mistake and it's
the first time i ever read that before
ever
that was flawless
that was absolutely flawless
holy macaroni
[Laughter]
let's go
what do you say about that um
respect
respect your heifer
thank you
thank you here's my thumb up
yay
can i read it better than i could have
maybe it's because i don't know the
language
maybe that makes it easier
maybe
[Music]
come back to me
oh
loud
okay and guys yes to you too chris total
respect have a thank you
thank you thank you very good thank you
you're just reading what it says you're
good at reading all things though
thank you i'm used to it by reading your
comments
you don't know the words of
pronunciation so it just flows out yeah
yeah
maybe
but i wouldn't necessarily say that's
the only reason because there's some
japanese tongue twisters that are like i
just try to read them without thinking
what they mean
uh and it's still really tough
uh wrestle free thank you you missed the
entire stream yeah tooth trailed
i hope it doesn't hurt anymore but um
you can watch the archive in
thanks to you thank you
thank you for calling it ketchup song
that's how i know it octavia rose duncan
dr joseph danish and levity duncan young
fan of junction
the chorus of that song is rapist
delight but mispronounced what
[Music]
what is your reason
we laughed a lot when the song first
came out
what
it's not spanish
that part is not even real spanish sour
salmon
okay i'm done with the super chats
thank you everybody for watching i need
to go because i need to receive a
visitor to
change the layout of my room
i need some help because some of the
furniture is pretty heavy
uh
i will prepare my room for tomorrow
and also practice the choreography so
that i can teach it properly again and
also i'll record another
uh kiana version oh do you wanna
do you wanna hear a clear clean version
of the
party about it psychopath that i
recorded i i know some of you guys
wanted to listen to it
i can play it for you guys in the ending
i think yeah it should be fun yeah yeah
yeah okay okay okay uh
okay
it's not mixed though so you know it
could be better it's not an official
song cover otherwise it would be mixed i
wish i had the skills to do it myself
that would help me a lot with times like
these
uh but okay thank you guys for watching
today thanks for the super chat thanks
for your support
it's 16 months youtube lying to me what
do you mean
what do you mean demo hollis thank you
thank you in 16 months you've been a
member yeah yeah
oh okay you thought it's 14 months
youtube says 16 months longer than you
thought it was
thank you for still being here
um
and in german we say alfina saying miss
vistancia
your channel so we can loop them no no
that's embarrassing no i don't wanna i
don't wanna but i might use them uh for
a
chiata only dance stream one day
cut out a video who knows if he's up for
it
you're welcome to use it
if you're listening to this you're
welcome to use my maka arena
bye bye guys see you tomorrow
bye bye thanks for watching today thank
you
thank you thank you
and um
[Music]
kfp
one
two three
four
five
[Music]
happy
oh
[Music]
um
what
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
guys
yeah
you may have noticed but
there are some scuffed harmonies in the
background because i don't really
i'm not able to come up with harmonies
myself much
uh some people have a natural talent for
that
oh and i didn't find any guides for it
so i just kind of tried something some
of them are scuffed up
oh
but yeah just kind of tried to back up
myself so that it doesn't sound too
boring um
yeah it's a bit embarrassing
i even tried something like i don't know
did you hear it it was really quiet but
i went like
for some some of the verses and then
like
did you hear that
that worked better than the then the
um
harmonies that's not even in the
original but i tried to make it sound
better
anyway bye bye
love you guys love you