[Music]
so
hey
[Music]
um
hmm
uh
[Music]
hey
oh
hello
oh oh thank you
hey cute stickers right yeah thank you
hello everybody
um
[Music]
hello
ah sorry for the wait i was trying to
set up this thing here um
did not completely succeed only
succeeded partially
uh today we are going to draw
kobol kanairu
and
also answer some questions while i have
the time
and
today we're
gonna
did i not save
i saved
did i not save it did i not save it
an image of course i saved it i knew i
did
this this girl this girl you know anyone
has has anyone seen this girl anyone who
knows this girl kono
[Laughter]
have you have you heard of this girl has
someone seen her
uh she is the new member one of the new
members of waterfront
of uh whole life indonesia third
generation
indonesia
lost child does it does look a little
bit like a lost child
uh sometimes
but
she's
hopefully not lost i mean maybe maybe
she is lost
uh
oh she's playing raft still right now ah
no no no
maybe when she's done maybe she'll say
hello
uh
no just kidding don't eat you said don't
eat i did the opposite
um
i uh don't um draw much anymore for many
years even though it used to be
my passion and my biggest hobby
so my skills and all that have greatly
deteriorated
deterio
you know what i mean
um
and yeah
i also still don't know
how to deal with the drawing program
that i've been using club studios still
don't know how to deal with it
uh the terry
oh i
did
terry oh
my favorite website for looking up
english by the way is dick dot cc
um
uh deterio
deteriorate
um
deteriorated
i mean that was close enough
huh
deteriorated deteriorated
what a weird [\h__\h] word
what a weird word it's like it sounds
like a stretch it sounds like you tried
to make a word and
you kind of just felt like okay i mean
close enough
what a weird word what a deteriorated
word
and detroit yes no no
um
so yeah i as always i like to say i suck
at art these days i i feel like i used
to be better
um
and when there's always
when there's always months or even half
a year or even a year between
the times i do draw
uh
you can definitely see
that
there's not even an ounce of practice
there
and
[Music]
i
when i have so much time to look at my
art after that
i i just start hating it it i uh
so hopefully today i will create
something that looks not so terrible um
i've started uh
already uh it's gonna be something
simple it's gonna be a close-up because
because
it will take less time and
less less
less chance to fail greatly
now i want you to look at this
look what i set up
yeah
actually i had this for a while
i had this for a while
uh
at my disposal
but i didn't use it because i forgot
about it and i also didn't
draw so
what's what would i use it for oh i
could use it for garlic phone as well on
the weekend
okay come on
yeah so i'm using it look look it's
called um
spud tablet if you're interested but
eden exile drew me
made me my own tablet in my own hands so
you can if you just download the spot
tablet thingy it'll it comes with it's
like generic hands but
i i have my own hands if you can see it
you can kind of see
um
i mean this is unrealistic but you can
see my cufflink there yeah yeah yeah
it's great it's great it's cool and then
there's actually also the close-up butt
now this is where i kind of started um
struggling with oh is this this is my
left hand yeah what is it wait what's
your cliffhanger yes yes um
the close-up one um now
the problem for me was
um
the window size is not the same as
what i put
uh
of the window from clip studio pro that
i put in there
um
so it doesn't line up like when even
when i make it line up at one point once
i go down then it's like not lining up
there anymore
so
i have to figure it out i think if i if
i would have both on my
in full screen
without cutting any edges then it would
probably be fine
um but in theory it's so cool right
yeah the bracelet is cute it says i love
kfp
yes cute and now now here is what i have
so far uh a little sketch
here we go
um
kobo
with
uh umbrella
umbrella and little thingy i forgot what
that was called
um
i
i i i wanted to
draw the eyes less creepy i feel like my
eyes um
tend to turn out creepy so i made them a
bit smaller than usual yeah attenuated
yeah ted rotated booze because it's like
you know she's all about the rain and
all that um
but
the thing it's kind of actually ironic
it actually doesn't make quite sense
because you put out potato terry bozo if
you don't want it to rain um
so it doesn't make quite sense that's
hanging on her umbrella that was my
fault that's like an accessory hanging
on her umbrella but um
now i started drawing her clothes but
when i was looking at the reference i
was like
already like [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
her outfit is so
complicated there's like layers and
layers and like transparent parts and
you don't know where what ends and what
starts like with the transparent parts
if it's it's a bit confusing um and then
there's so many like what the [\h__\h] like
what what when you try to draw it you
really realize i mean the first time i
saw it i already thought that looks a
bit complicated
um so i'm thinking maybe i should just
draw her
in casual clothes
no the raincoat is the is the difficult
thing it's difficult and if i draw that
then i realize that the hands wouldn't
be visible because uh her sleeves are so
long
yeah i might just give her an original
outfit
[Music]
so
so also i don't know this is kind of
this is cool i want to show off this
hand but
um
[Music]
it doesn't match
completely wait you can actually see
the
the circle
under the hand that's where my finger
actually is but the higher i go it lines
up right and then i go up and it goes up
there so the size the window size is not
it's not accurate
[Music]
and also i guess it looks a bit weird
that it just cuts off there because of
my setup being like this
i saw eofy and
did inna use it no but eofy used it and
um i think she had this in full screen
so that's why it didn't look weird and i
think it also didn't um it lined up
nicely yes i'm left-handed yes
[Music]
maybe at least um
like if it's if if i cut it here it
would look okay
but yeah i i can't i can't i don't know
about the size man um
hmm it's so cool to see yeah wait what
about
no no it's not it's not accurate it's
not accurate
[Music]
guys because i cut the clip studio
window as well i think hi felix welcome
maybe
if if let's say let's say in theory i
want to test this out
in theory
if i
if i i thought it would be cleaner you
know if i cut it but oopsie
if if i don't cut this
and
don't
cut this if i don't cut any of this
but then the window size is so weird
but it's very in theory
in theory
if this window
and this window
are the same size
like this then it should it should let's
say i'm in the corner yes i'm in
let's say this corner
yeah
here
that pretty much lines up if if both
windows are the same size of course but
now let's say
let's say
say
because i also wanted to fit on that big
screen but i guess it doesn't really
matter
i guess we could just
um say goodbye to the big screen
and then
make
oh dear what the [\h__\h]
oh damn it damn it
no this and this huh
why can't i only move one at a time
shut them up
no i don't want it to be full screen
wait wait wait whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa
let's say
it is bigger
okay we'll just do it like this
and then
yeah i just i'll just keep the sides i
guess you can see
it i guess
so now
now the window sizes are roughly the
same
corner uh almost down huh
corner
corner yeah yeah yeah i'm not that
actually works
i guess that works
helpful for beginners you can't learn
anything from me
because like i i don't even know like
how i don't know these brushes i i
i have not really had much opportunity
to experiment with them so that's that
also i want to
make myself
like here
uh on
it
yeah
when i look here
i've been looking to the side a lot
hello i will be looking to the side a
lot mm-hmm
now that it's lined up i could just cut
it now
i could just cut it now
at least at least on this side because
when i look to the side and my head
won't be so hidden and now
well now it still overlaps
oh it was that easy just line it up in
the beginning and then cut it okay
okay
your resolution kicked in noise you mean
youtube hd
oh speaking of youtube hd
that drawing stream i think that was the
most pre most recent previous drawing
stream
i think so where i drew myself right
that one
is 360p right um finally
i got a reply from youtube so finally uh
it seems like uh at the latest by monday
it should be fixed i don't know if it's
already fixed it should be the latest by
monday fixed not that anyone cares
anymore at this point
[Laughter]
maybe one person cares um but yes i
finally
have received the reply that they
have fixed it i think and it's like
processing or so i don't know i don't
know
um
i wonder what happened i don't know some
some kind of corruption
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah the 360p is really i mean i i
probably wouldn't care so much if it was
480p
but 360p is um
[Music]
yeah
i i can't
ignore that 360p is
next level bad so
unacceptable right mm-hmm
oh there's a translator thank you
[Music]
thank you
so
[Music]
excuse me what the hell what what you
mean you watched my streams on a
tamagotchi or what
did you watch my streams on
f144 gang excuse me
144 are you guys watching me on the
tamagotchi
stop watching me on the tamagotchi
that's like worst quality what the [\h__\h]
uh with nothing
wouldn't that be cute uh i can't speak
tamagotchi where you raise an egg into
two
into a chicken
wait wouldn't that be so cute
how do you make that
i want i wanted i want a tamakoti
because it's tama already tama is egg
oh that would be so cute
as birthday merch i think it would be
very difficult because it's like
it's a device
but who knows i mean ah
i mean i've seen other pretty cool
things being done as merchandise in
whole life but a tamil godzi sounds
kind of impossible
it would be so cute though that would be
so cute
i i
i will i really research
it might not be too late to ask
um
wait before i forget that
i'm going to now
um
but wait one one would have to program
that
somebody i would need someone who
programs it and all that right
yeah i don't think so
[Music]
yeah
no like how would that work
[Music]
corvo just
can cool make anything more than
websites
can she make more than websites
even if i feel like i could if i were to
ask a programmer i feel like i would ask
someone more competent
i mean she's
she has some skills but why not ask
someone
actually
professional
um
yeah
i don't think she can program a game
it wasn't cover a tech call
that is a good argument
we we are a tech company
um all right uh by the way what kind of
clothes do we want to give her now that
we have oops now that we have decided to
not draw her in her own clothes because
it's too much work
what kind of clothes don't laugh
uniform i don't think she i don't think
she would look good in it
a called oh
cute
like a yellow raincoat it doesn't even
have to be a yellow froggy raincoat ah
[Music]
um
i guess so i guess it's simple and and
works or yeah i was thinking also a
sundress could be cute but
isn't is that too girly too girly
a wrinkle a blue wrinkle
when i think of raincoats i only think
of yellow raincoats can i make a
blue raincoat look like an actual
raincoat
blue ring maybe with a cute pattern like
a cloud cloud pattern
that would be cute
yeah
so raincoat very simple okay
maybe
maybe a blue raincoat with a cloud
pattern
yeah are you hearing the
um
music by the way um
it's quiet for me
thank you for the membership welcome uh
wow it's my hand this is so cool
um
so okay let's do that also her hair is
fun to draw i have to say uh which pen
was i using
okay i forgot
was it this no it was not that
was it
i don't know
[\h__\h]
ah
[\h__\h] it i'm just using this
it's just a sketch because i'm very low
okay
i don't mind i don't mind raising it
[Music]
yeah i need to look at kobo reference
uh where did i put cool
[Music]
how many times was it 12 times
then you have to call for her it doesn't
work man
it doesn't [\h__\h] work i was not the
only one who tried that
someone else tried it too i saw a clip
of it
it doesn't work
it's false advertising
where is she where is she
this should have priority even if she's
streaming
when someone calls her i mean this is
her main job whole life is just her
second job
yeah is she on her way she's on the seat
okay why not take so much [\h__\h] time
wasn't she supposed to like immediately
show up what the hell is that
she's on a boat that's not an excuse
she's like she's like you know like a
rain
shaman so and she she said herself call
me 12 times if you need me so i'm just
i'm just doing as it's advertised i'm
just following the instructions
okay now let's uh
continue drawing this fun messy hair she
should try putting some gravy into her
hair maybe maybe that could help with
the frizziness
of it
[Music]
yeah my hair used to look like this
and then i started using gravy
yeah yeah
yeah yeah that's how it is oh that
actually ended up being
shorter
[Music]
is this cool or what
is the hand cool
i think it's cool
i think it's pretty freaking dope
she was working where i lived yesterday
are you sure it was her maybe it was a
colleague
where's the glove what
what love
oh you mean
because
when i use my webcam i usually have a
club
oh
smart question smart question
today management said it's okay to not
wear my glove
um because
because
it's uh it's
too sweaty um
i don't have to use it today
actually i'm already so far with the
sketch and it's quite simple we just
have to draw the clothes um
[Music]
i feel like i'm i'm running away from
drawing your original cloves but they
are look at them
and then the sleeve would take up like
the whole it would look like this
it will it will take up everything
um
yes i'm left-handed
should i
should i write a big
text saying i yes i am left-handed
because a lot of people gonna ask it is
you should just
answer the question yourself here as
your left hand and i'm drawing with it
uh
roll up roll up the sleeves
no
i i love her jacket but it's hard to
draw [\h__\h] it we're not drawing it
but the blue if we draw her a blue or
wrinkled maybe it will clash too much
with her hair
maybe it should be yellow it would be a
cute um
a cute contrast bgm volume what too loud
or too quiet now
i think the yellow would be a
a cute uh contrast
it's fine
[Music]
okay well what does that what does the
raincoat look like just um
it's really simple
um
[Music]
maybe
add some cute frills to it
this will be dark
down
so
yesterday
you know what i did yesterday
don't
please don't ask me if i did my homework
please don't ask me i tried i started
okay but the thing is i
i i came across a netflix show
that
holy [\h__\h]
it was
so addicting
um
so i watched it for
10 10 hours
no not nine hours maybe nine hours
um
um the thing is i didn't i didn't even
find it um in the beginning of the day
but rather late so i watched i think
from like i don't know seven or six pm
to like
three or four a.m
um
it was probably 4am
[Music]
but it was so good what there's there's
nothing bad about that i was enjoying
myself on my day off okay so you can't
key on
you can't i was just i was just having a
good day off
and honestly it was a great show i'm not
quite finished i'm missing one and a
half episodes because
to be honest the show is great but then
the last
two episodes
or like the the second to last episode
uh was actually starting to disappoint
me and suddenly suddenly the
it was just stupid and i was like
what the [\h__\h]
what's happening why is this suddenly so
bad
uh now the show is
i wonder if someone you saw it inventing
anna on netflix
it's uh yeah it is a netflix original
um it's about a real person
uh anna
sorokin
uh
um
who was uh uh
of uh of uh what do you call it someone
who frau frauded banks and [\h__\h] um who
went to who came to america answered as
if they had money um made a lot of
people think she had money a con artist
yeah a fraudster but she was super young
she was in her twenties actually uh wow
she really got a [\h__\h] ton of people to
to like give her so much money
and and yeah that show is about that now
um obviously what she did was wrong and
i don't idolize what she did or her as a
person but i feel like the netflix show
was really well made until
that second to last episode where
you know there's there's this reporter
in that show that they like to focus on
a lot
uh because she's pregnant um
but then holy [\h__\h] they focus so much on
her pregnancy
what the [\h__\h]
it's like so unnecessary like this is
not what i'm watching the show for i'm
not watching it for your pregnancy and
it's very dramatic about it sometimes
um yeah can still enjoy it no honestly
it was a good show
um
i think pretty good uh quality wise like
it was better written than that other
show i watched the other day upload
upload was
has an interesting theme but is
uh
not written as well as this show but
then it disappointed me at the end as
well that that's why i was able to stop
watching i could not smell i was so
binge watching i'm so into it and then
the second to last episode got really
bad so i was like okay it's four it's
how fast 4am
the show is starting to suck losing my
interest so how about we ended here
and it already kind of had its
conclusion at that point anyway so
it's like why why why would i continue
watching this so anyway
but i do recommend it it's fairly new i
think it came out this year
so
by the way netflix netflix bought her
story for
320 000
um
but then then the assets were
i looked up a little bit the assets were
frozen
uh because
uh she can't earn money from something
that like was a crime basically
right um
that's like some kind of law in america
thank god for that law there's a lot of
useless laws out there
but that was actually a good law so they
froze the assets but then um
they used it for to pay off
the things that she was owing people
and banks and hotels and all that so
at least at least that was paid off
i guess
although although
i mean that's good but
she should have
that's not even her money
in the end she did not use any of her
money after all cause like
she paid off the bills by using netflix
money by selling her story
it's not even her money [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] oh that pisses me off
it's not even her money so she will one
day get out of jail i think she's still
in jail she one day will leave jail and
will be free of
of
uh
debts because it was already paid
and and and
as
the way the way i know this world is
she's gonna get out of prison she's
gonna continue doing what she did kind
of but this time she will not need to uh
fake it because people will give her
money just for
for
exposure and for being her because the
netflix show idolized her so
she will probably
yeah get enough money anyway
so this is this is why i had mixed
feelings about watching the show because
it will give her a platform
um
yeah to have an even easier time
yeah and and i heard she's right now out
of prison selling art
making money
by selling art and people i don't know
how much she's gain earning from that
but i have a feeling that some stupid
people out there are paying a [\h__\h] out
of money for her art just because it
came from
some famous person
it's a questionable
[\h__\h] questionable
but
but okay um
yeah
um
i don't know should it be like side
because i don't always can barely see it
it's not like this
let's have the buttons be
clouds
oh that's so cute
clown buttons
yes i'm left-handed
yeah any publicity is good publicity it
it really
is true
it really is [\h__\h] true
[Music]
i know
see how i drew a straight line that's
pretty straight
that umbrella looks pretty straight i
think
good job me good job me yes i'm left
handed yes i'm left-handed yes i'm
left-handed yes i'm left-handed yes i'm
left-handed
[Laughter]
i did barely see her close
don't know what to do
yeah it's okay
it will work somehow
[Music]
yeah
surprise surprise surprise
i am left-handed you know what i like
about um
one detail i like about her design about
cooper's design it's like she's just
like this small
little cute girl right um
one thing that stands out to me is that
she has these like piercings on several
piercings on her ear
which make her
give her like a little bit of an edge
um
what like
she has this
this secret edginess if you look on her
ear
she has these side piercings on the side
of her ear
yeah yeah
you didn't notice that i noticed that
very quickly
i love her design but i'm not drawing it
because pain in the ass
okay um our hands are probably
[Music]
not that good
i'm gonna finish watching the show after
the stream today
but
i feel like i've seen enough at this
point
i've overdosed
on that show
it's like damn
it could have ended on such a high note
one two three four
yeah
could have ended on such a high note and
by the way on the background i want like
on on the it's a safer umbrella and i
don't know if you see it but i want
there to be like these these water drops
like it's like it's it's stopped raining
it's not not raining anymore but there's
like water drops on her
on her umbrella sticking to it um
question though does this umbrella even
make sense
the way i drew it
[Music]
when you when will you be collabing with
cobble for the first time i don't know
when we didn't set a date yet but
um
she was very excited about the idea of
collabing with me
and
i am too
so
we will
collab as soon
as the band is lifted and we find a good
date
a good time
perspective
angles
teach her english
i'm not an english teacher and she's
already at a at a
decent level
so i wouldn't know what to teach her
like teaching someone who can't speak
english at all is easier than teaching
someone who can speak english decently
because
like i don't know what what she doesn't
know i would need to be an actual
teacher and have like a
have a
have a whole
plan
but i was thinking of showing her maybe
the holo
hollow ian minecraft server
or i don't know there's not
i always think about good collab games
but
it's difficult it's difficult because
like the bomb game i've done several
times then there's this that
not the jack box one but the one on the
switch with all the games i like that
one as a collab game but it has kind of
been overused before and so i feel
i feel worried about playing it again
because when when the last time i used
it i remember people being like it that
game again
now it's been a long time since the last
time i
used that game but still
uh yeah clubhouse 51 yeah it takes two
now i already played the full game with
someone and that's more like of a like a
long time commitment i i've won
something that i can play for one stream
and then be done with it like something
like super bunny man or so but super
bunny man i've played with someone
before and i don't want to reuse the
same games over and over again because
then people are going to be like it's
the same game again
you know
don't umbrellas have something like this
like this
i don't know it doesn't have to be so
realistic huh you can just
say it's it's
beyond that point where that starts even
if it has it
assuming it has it
uh
overcooked i don't
ah
we've we've played overcooked like in
the beginning of holo myth
uh
right with um with the myth girls here
and there uh cali
was like doing [\h__\h] and kitchen right
and from my experience it was a bad
collab game
because
you have to really
[Music]
uh
focus on the game because it's so fast
um
but then like i i remember
it was i felt so awkward because we had
almost no conversation it was just oh
yeah
i gotta do this i gotta do that oh oh
dear ah do you have some of this and do
you have some of that and that's pretty
much 90 of the conversation we had
so
i personally did not
feel like it was a good collab game
that's why i didn't play that anymore
now actually someone from whole life
japan invited me
to play that with some people and
i'm i may say yes because i don't want
to turn it down
but i don't think it's a good collab
game
yes you can give me all those ideas but
those are not good games for playing it
with two people
playing uno or monopoly with two people
just makes no sense to me no no no no
mario party neighbor no no
something you can play with two people
maybe mario kart or
[Music]
i don't know
smash bros i've heard has like problems
with the pink
if you come from different countries
um
[Music]
so
yeah i haven't tried it yet i wanted to
but yeah
it seems difficult
yeah minecraft minecraft works
no matter how many people
it just works
hair is so messy
okay you could stop throwing game names
at me now
you can stop a lot of the games you say
are either in my opinion not suitable or
boring or we don't have permissions for
them or blah blah blah blue or have been
done several million times before
but thank you for trying
speaking of games though i i have
already let my members
know but um
after yakuza because we're getting done
with yakuza this week
uh
i have decided what game we're gonna
play as a series next
[Music]
the legend of zelda the wind wake up
wake up
i wanted to play wind waker for some
time
mm-hmm
[Music]
this game i
i kind of played before but i never
finished it and i never really got far
when i played it alone because it was
mostly a game that i just um
enjoyed watching someone else play like
my brother or like let's player
um
[Music]
yeah
so
we are gonna challenge it on our own i
don't know what the hell is going on
here this hair is still messy
and i don't i don't know what i'm
looking at anymore
it should be fine
yeah
can't wait
yes windbreak is super good you'll like
you like it i know i will like it i
played it before but just i never got
until the end and
i got help from my brother and so on so
yeah
i'm looking forward to it it's uh the
the second
no the third the third zelda game that
we're gonna play on my channel
previously we played skyward sword
and
and um
and link's awakening
but for the sake oh wait i forgot the
fountain you can barely see it though
because the picture cuts off there
uh
for the sake of
[Music]
doing this let's play
i
am getting
a wii u
i wanna i want the gamecube just because
i used to play it on the gamecube but
people told me several times that the
the remaster on the wii u is just much
much better so i'm like okay i guess i'm
gonna wii u
even though the wii u will barely have
any other use besides that
yeah
um
i i think i'll eventually get myself a
gamecube anyway
[Music]
um just because i want it
it reminds me of my childhood
hair makes her look weird now
i feel like she looks weird now
nice okay
still have my old game cube nice is it
purple
i know there's some non-purple ones but
the purple one is the classic one
mine was purple
i know there's some way hugens
i know but maybe twilight princess would
be
the only other one that i would play
that would make sense
yeah
and maybe uh super mario
oh what's it called what's it called it
was a super mario game on the wii u um
what was it called
um
no
oh
i think this i'm talking about mario
maker and super mario 3d world
yeah so super mario for irelia yeah but
i guess you can play it on the switch
too
ah and you super mario you yes yes i
don't know i think i think i meant all
of them
yeah super mario
you or something like that mm-hmm
that
could be fun because i want i said i
wanted to play
more mario games
um
on my channel
dip a little bit more into it like
rather than the 3d ones i want to try
the the 2d ones the the
3d looking 2d ones you know what i mean
so not no not the super old ones i'm
sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry
we start from new to old on my channel
uh-huh
that one is on the switch already
yeah they brought all of them to switch
see exactly that's what i'm saying with
the wii u would be so useless to me
um
just doing it for wind waker basically
i am just doing it for wind waker
you guys
um i feel like we could already do the
outlines
if you look
i think i will do
the whole
um
umbrella thing in the background
very much later after i'm done with
everything in the foreground because i
need to look at the big picture i'm just
going to draw a big umbrella and then
put it in there
um okay if we bring some cute thank you
so laughter
chronicles x
xl blade
what
[Music]
probably not a game i would stream
though
[Laughter]
i wanted to stream uh which xenoblade
was it uh
chronicles definitive edition
that one because i own it i wanted to
stream that one um
one day one day one day but it's not my
priority
that was not my birthday
mmm
is a lot of fun it's not exactly part of
the trilogy uh-huh
okay
i was looking at games for wii u
uh
and other games for the switch and so on
that you know i could i could do
i could play like because i was trying
to compare it with wind waker like which
one would be better now
um
but my decision ended up with wind waker
because
i am excited to play it yes it's gonna
be so cute i just love wind waker for
for the cute story and the music and the
characters and and the little side
things you know like the auction for
example i don't know there's like i i
remember i remember it very very fondly
and like i was
zooming across the ocean
suddenly finding like one tiny island
but just just just the feeling of
zooming across the ocean alone makes it
worth it so
i
i really really really really really
really want to play it and i feel like
now's the time now's the time it won't
be too long either as far as i know it's
like 30 30 hours
gameplay
so
it shouldn't take too too long compared
to yakuza
hope you guys are looking forward to it
yeah
[Music]
yeah this is just one layer
um because it's just a sketch i'm gonna
do the outlines now i guess yeah
i hate
outlines but if i'm fast i
i
i could i could if i if i were fast
which is not gonna happen i could finish
it in one day
but that's probably not gonna happen
uh let's rename this ring
[Music]
not a green how do i
uh i don't know how to use this
ah here
o l
and then
i'm gonna make another layer
oh l
extra
[Music]
and then we're going to tune this down
and we're transparent okay there we go
[Music]
i don't know what pen to use
it's a g pen
um
[Music]
these pens at all but i guess i'm just
gonna go with this basic one
all right it should be fine
[Music]
hydrate hydrate
also i was supposed to read some
marshmallows so let me uh
i i didn't i didn't sort through them i
didn't have time so i'm just going to go
from top and choose randomly if i see
something interesting um
[Music]
huh
i wonder if you got any specific song
collab plans now that you have done one
with each member of myth or it will be
more uh free-for-all without any
specific plans but more open to do one
with any of the whole members or even
people outside a lot uh yeah well you
guys kind of know i'm planning on
i mean there's a there's a song collab
with uh ninety coming out
soon
uh there was something that needed to be
fixed with the music video so it's still
taking a little bit of time um
but
uh yeah
uh
and then i want one with with reina
yeah
um
but besides that i'm not i'm not gonna
go by like any kind of
system anymore that i had before i would
i will just like pick randomly now who i
want to collab with
um
one that i've had on my mind as well is
moomay
i want to do a one-on-one song collab
with mummy
i don't want to do all of council more
so i just want to do mermaid for now
um at least from
my
um
i have to say
like if if i'm the one inviting someone
i would do a man if anybody from council
wants to do a
sound cover with me
i would say yes of course to anybody
but i can't i'm not gonna i'm not gonna
organize
a song cover on my own with every single
person in the whole life know
but i thought because mummy
we are weird two
english who have english
birds
so that is that connection and she's
really good at singing and i don't know
i just feel like it would be cute
recently i've been getting
closer with mumei and she's also coming
to visit me
um over here in europe so
you know we've been we've been having
more opportunities to get closer and
burp are better we vlog together indeed
we do
yeah
gonna make pretty thick outlines i guess
at least for some parts
and then we can still color them into a
different um color
if we want to also i want more
stabilization please thank you
um
hold up strong
i didn't even need to lure her with
berries she was gonna come anyway the
berries are just
a neat extra speaking of berries i made
i made banana
blueberry pancakes today and yesterday
for breakfast
and ate it of course with nutella
because i can't eat pancakes
without nutella or french toast or
anything i always add nutella
although actually today i use the
substitute for nutella because i ran out
of nutella and i ordered new one and i
was like you know what i actually always
hear bad things about nutella so how
about we order something more healthy
no
i ordered something that's like nutella
but more healthy
this i will still call it nutella though
um but yeah the pancakes are
uh great uh and quick very quick
i
i um
i have a new way
of making them faster and more
efficiently so now i can
now i feel more motivated to make them
because they don't take me so much time
basically
now what i do now is i throw the
ingredients into my smoothie mixer the
banana and egg and all that i throw all
of that in the smoothie mixer
and let that do the work for me
um so
now i'm motivated can make something
yummy so fast and then and then i add
some
uh
forgot the words the the mayo and then
and then
and then and then once i put them in the
in the in the frying pan
once they're already starting to be
fried that's when i add on top of it a
few
oh yeah flour a few blueberries
i don't mix them with the banana and all
that like a smoothie
um i do it
i just add them as a whole
on top
that way when you bite into them you
still get that that fresh blueberry
explosion
oh
yeah
[Music]
it's not a smoothie it's a pancake i
just made it in the smoothie mixer
because of the banana
because i had to uh
smash it
yeah
[Music]
and so i had some
good breakfast these past two days
the only the only annoying thing about
it is cleaning up though cleaning the
mixer
but if you soak it immediately then
everything's cool
and then everything's alright
and yesterday for dinner i made
carbonara
with a
bacon because i had some leftover bacon
yeah so i cooked for breakfast and for
dinner okay
i may have bridge watched for 10 hours
but i also have cooked for breakfast and
dinner which i usually i if if anything
i only cook one meal per day
but yesterday um in in terms of cooking
i was uh productive
no
that makes up for it a little bit
[Music]
yeah i know i always eat breakfast i
just don't eat lunch usually
or like i wouldn't consider it lunch i
would just snack something
maybe
in between but
[Music]
incredible accomplishment now you're
making fun of me for me it's a for me it
is an accomplishment
cause like i really lack the motivation
um for cooking also partially because i
just don't
um
i'm just not very good at it either
so
baby steps you know
baby steps
what's the progress yeah
i actually uh use the recipe
for quick quick breakfast
that you can do in 15 minutes
it's really easy it's actually not even
that sweet i could have added sugar and
all that but
i was like oh well you know what it's
healthier this way
[Music]
you're in an adult phoenix now
congratulations thank you
the food you post on twitter looks yummy
well i hope you didn't get fooled by
that don't tonkatsu a lot of a lot of
japanese people actually got fooled even
though i wrote it in twitter
so many people wrote to me oh wow
your tonkatsu looks so good but that was
just a random jif gif off of the
off of
tenor or what it is called
it's not my i even wrote it on the tweet
i said this is not my own tonkatsu
because mine didn't look so good but it
tasted good
people were like oh damn chihuahua
okay well let's just say okay it's mine
i made it
i mean it wasn't that far off
[Music]
people don't read that is apparently
unfortunately very true
isn't that i kind of too small
to the other one
only a little bit
just made it bigger a tiny bit
[Music]
okay
uh next
[Music]
um
was wondering what your thoughts are on
all these new game genres that you have
finally given a shot thanks to hello
live i know you love jrpgs a lot and
stunned by them as the best genre yes
but now that you've stepped out of your
comfort zone how do you like what you
have played if so what are notable ones
that really surprised you like something
that you know past year would be like
never ever did you get uh don't judge a
book by its cover kind of feeling
no no no because i think um
i judged
fps and horror games by its cover but i
did it correctly um accurately
um
i still
don't like them very much
um
[Music]
but maybe one one good example would be
ori
um
wait what genre is that not platformers
but uh metroidvania or so
not that i was like i would never ever
ever play this genre ever in my whole
life
but it's more like i didn't quite think
um
i don't know it was just not really on
on my radar i guess until then um
while
when i played it even though we
struggled a lot and i almost gave up on
it man in the beginning um
it did work out pretty well after a
while had some had some successful
moments and felt pretty accomplished at
the end
uh pretty strong i feel like i came out
more skilled and stronger
[\h__\h] i'm on the wrong layer
i'm on the
[Music]
i think i
improved and yes
i i went through with it and it was it
was worth it i would say
um
yeah
yeah um besides that
[Music]
as a genre
i feel like i had one more in mind
uh
you feel weird to me too
looks fine to me
although
[Music]
huh
it's fine
uh what fire emblem i know that is still
very close to
my
my my go-to genre
it's just the fact that it was like
strategic
was i guess
kind of
challenging um but not nothing too crazy
that i would have said i will never ever
play this with me no no no no
no no don't worry
don't worry about it
i was just joking
um
no no later locator is also not
something where i thought oh i wouldn't
like this no no no no not at all
ellen ring
i guess maybe applies a little bit but
also not quite it's still an rpg it's
just challenging
challenging rpg but games like um
[Music]
uh games like
um actually like all kinds of
platformers though
um i i like them
in kind of
i think i like them more now than i used
to before
like
i would
probably not necessarily have
um
picked up 2d platformers
outside of streaming
yeah
but
yeah uh both mario and ori and
yeah whatever
oh no
i did play autumn sphere but that also
had the big big bonus of having cute
character
um but something like mario
games you know those are like um
i mean i mean something like super mario
64 or sunshine is a different story
because that actually has like a story
and all that
now that i put in a different uh
category again but like those 2d mario
games um
i mean i mean the story i guess there's
a story of rescuing princess peach but
there's not much more to it right so
um
and then and then the whole platforming
aspect of it to me is just kind of
difficult so i just didn't think it was
that interesting until then
mm-hmm
uh-huh
adam's fear
oh this is fair i love audience fear it
was fun
i played it before hello
no so with horror games
i'm still big no
with fps games
it's like
i i i what the [\h__\h] is that i tolerate
them
but
i
i don't
genuinely enjoy them so much that i want
to
that there's a feeling inside of me
that's like i want to play an fps game
like
streaming is my job so
i will play
one for stream okay and i might have fun
with it as well
but that doesn't change the fact that i
don't really want to play it
it can still be fun especially if it's a
collab but
it's it doesn't
inspire me
to play more of it
on its own
yeah so
[Music]
should that be straight maybe it should
be straight
somewhat straight
yes doesn't get my new rinse going
okay next one
[Music]
how much importance do you place on
being able to complete a game when you
pick one up um
[Music]
for me
like for example for ellen ring i didn't
plan on finishing it to begin with so
for me
it's like
a different story but in general if i
pick up an rpg game
um on stream then for me like finishing
it is a given
so i don't put any importance on it
because it's just normal for me
in the beginning i remember i remember
in the first few months
my reputation among my fans was that i
don't finish games because
um i was starting like fire emblem which
took me months to finish it's not that i
wasn't finishing games i just everything
that i had going on was just too long to
finish but i ended up finishing
everything that i started like near
automata atomia sophie
uh
no not sophia wait which one did we play
uh ryza
um and so on uh yeah tails off
uh i finished it to the point on stream
where i was allowed to finish it
otherwise i would have finished it until
the very end on stream
um and yeah fire emblem and so on um
yakuza yakuza even though that first
stream was sponsored
i continued to play it on my own until
the very end because i enjoyed it
surprisingly
and now it's more like my reputation is
i play long games and i finish them
so that kind of changed my reputation
changed i heard i heard some other whole
life members have the reputation of not
finishing games now so
i mean even then that's fine like if you
don't feel like finishing it then you're
doing you
um
but for completion sake and also just
because i'm interested in
myself hearing this the full story of
whatever game it is i
i need to finish it
that's like a cliffhanger i don't want
to end it on the cliffhanger
sakuna was unfortunate i wanted to
finish it but
um it was not really good as a streaming
game at some point like one episode okay
two episodes okay
but anything more than that i i noticed
um
i wasn't the only one struggling with
that
um
dammit what am i doing
confusing
and yeah now we have like so many
games that we've started and finished
and have like a whole list
um
[Music]
i didn't no i didn't
but that's that's just because i don't
play games
upstream
because it just we discussed this before
i just
as a streamer when when this is your job
it's just many people who have disaster
job don't feel like
playing games
um
on their rough time that's just
perfectly normal
so i don't blame myself for that
but
in a different timeline where i would
where i was not in all alive
if i would have picked up monster hunter
rise privately i feel like i would have
played it more
even though i was struggling with it
like
that one time when i did play it i feel
like i had some issues with grasping
the game mechanics
definitely
um i heard there's a dlc coming out
right
maybe ina will play it
if you want to see monster hunter rise
i'm sorry i guess you got to go to
someone else's channel
it's like i don't know that that monster
hunter rise in theory looks like
something i would play on my channel
because cute cause cute anime style
girls and all that
but
yeah it wasn't quite my thing
was not quite my thing seems like i
is it just me because i have the feeling
that i don't
i tend to
stray away from games that are popular
why i just i just don't
i just can't find an
a liking and
in all those super popular games what
the hell
it's not that i'm trying to be hipster
it's just
those those are always the ones that i
don't really
like
for free your taste thank you
pick up a different game together
rune factor three five i saw
uh
i checked iris stream a little bit
um
it looks cute
but i'm
i'm doubting it to be a good streaming
game
yeah i'm gonna play it off stream and
there was some like discussion on our
discord like
surprising i was actually surprised
there were so many en girls that were
like oh room factory five let's play it
together even though there's no co-op i
think they just mean
let's play it in general
um
and
a lot of the girls were getting hyped up
about it
and i was like
you this is a jrpg right
i usually i'm the only one interested in
a jrpg
what's going on what's happening why
does everybody want to play rune factory
five
is it
yeah i've noticed that ian girls
they a lot of them are into these kind
of like farming games because they were
really excited about harvest moon or
whatever
i don't i don't remember all these names
of those games but yeah
they really like um harvest moon i think
and rune factory is similar right or
stardew valley they were asking for
stardew valley as well
i guess it's just they like farming
simulators
that's the only time they will pick up
and a jrpg when it's uh when it's a
farming simulator
oh sad
i guess i will stay
the one and only true jrpg streamer
in all of english
um oh my playlist stopped
ah right here
all right next question
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
plans for concert convention sca no
plans uh a wish yes but it doesn't quite
depend on me
depends on the conventions
[Music]
any chance we'll still get a phoenix
warrior themed outfit
seal unlocked maybe
um
[Music]
chances are low because
because i know we got a lot of outfits
last year
but
from now on like this year and the years
to come
we won't be getting that many outfits
so
i have to
make use of the
rare opportunities that we get now
to make something that will that i
really want otherwise you know i won't
be able to
do the ones that i won't
i mean
part of me
wants to do some
kind of like edgy cool
design as well
um but probably not really how you
imagine it but there's like so much that
i want to do and only so little outfits
that i can get
um
that i can
request
and um
yeah and then then the thing is also
that usually
uh we have a theme
and
we all have to follow that theme like we
decide on the theme but
you know then we have to follow the
theme and it has to be a theme that
everyone's okay with
and can imagine something with
so
um
if i were to do that everybody would
have to have some fitting theme to also
be i don't know warrior or something i
don't know and i don't think i could
convince them to do something like that
either
um
yeah
epic mythology theme
yeah i don't i don't i
realistically speaking i feel like we
would always prioritize
different a different theme
um
at the moment
yeah
yeah just being honest with you guys
don't want to get your hopes up you know
but
in exchange you can go on twitter
you can type into the search bar hashtag
arts of ashes
and already find a lot of really cool
badass kiana fan art some of it really
being like a
warrior version of myself sometimes like
me in different outfits and me in
different situations where it looks like
i'm fighting or something so you know
you know you know
maybe that makes up for it a little bit
yes
[Music]
yeah the elven ring found out was really
cool
a super cool fan out of you as my phone
wallpaper
thank you
thank you thank you for looking at me so
much
every time i look at your phone you're
looking at me
oh
who else has me as their phone wallpaper
kiana will call
[Music]
thank you ipad wallpaper oh that stuff
not me but you're always on my mind
no no no i guess that's fine
i have the art by mamaloni of you and
coco
oh wallpaper and lock screen thank you
guys
thank you
ah you guys are sweet
arigato
i feel loved
you
bouncy fluffy hair
[Music]
have your desk mad as mousepad
oh
that's that's that sounds beautiful too
that makes me happy too
earp peeking out here
[Music]
your ear peak
all of my both with phone and pc thank
you
the papa tapestry looks so gorgeous in
my window
oh you have it covering up your window
but that is a great tapestry i know i
know
it's so good
[Music]
i'm so slow
why am i so slow
need more water by the way
also i once again have a donut with me
an emergency donut if i need food
i wish i could have gotten all the merch
from your birthday what was the problem
financial or did the time run out did
you join too late
maybe one day we can do a rerun maybe
maybe one day
i don't know i don't know how
how popular the demand is
i think most of kfp who wants to merge
has the merch already
maybe
maybe in a year or so maybe we will have
enough new people to
um
sell something again we're a reselling
thingy would make sense
but in theory it's it's possible it's
not impossible it's possible
uh-huh
welcome egg
everyone off the myth uh you mean the
very first shirt you're that one that's
a shirt that not many people have
i think that one yeah indeed a lot of
people missed out and that was so early
that maybe a lot of people were still
like not as fanatic about us yet that
they would buy merchandise or whatever
um
how many ear thingies does she have
[Music]
wait what am i
um
[Music]
shirts in free excel sizes well that's
you tell that to cover not to me
i already tried telling them before
uh we need more sizes and all that but
you know i can't i can't change
everything and
uh and improve everything and cover no
no sometimes
sometimes people just don't listen to me
people just don't listen to me when i
say something so
i don't have the power
unfortunately i don't have i don't have
any power any power
i need more power
you're gonna regret not giving me the
power once illuminati takes over
well that's when they'll regret it
they'll be like [\h__\h] we should have
listened to kiara
[\h__\h]
should have known
how many does she have let me check
[Music]
and wait wait is it is that stars it
looks like stars
she has stars on there
it's not rings it's stars
two stars i think
right
interesting
[Music]
this is going around the ear i wonder
in any case this is okay just be small
four eyebrows
in my art or ah
i mean the
the line of the eyelids no no
i get what you mean because they're
really up high but no that's just the
line of the eyelids
she has actually pretty thick um
eyebrows i like it
pretty thick
long eye brush
blue eyebrows that's just you know the
confusing thing with anime style art
done in usually in most art styles
uh the eyebrows shimmer through the the
bangs
i do that
do i do i do that with my own art i
think i do it a little bit at least i
don't know
sometimes
i'm doing it now
i think
but the eyelids i don't
uh
draw them like that
[Music]
i wonder how i'm gonna color the hair
because because of the
gray it's like so especially
um
separated like the blue from the white
it kind of messes with how i would
usually color hair but we're going to
try our best
so far so good
so far so good next question
oh
oh my [\h__\h] god
i know exactly who wrote that
that's such a giveaway
um i will say that i am considering
playing spiral this year
not hellblade so
now
[Music]
spiral yes
exactly who wrote that
um
there's some weird questions some troll
questions some weird questions here
what's happening
oh thank you
um you don't know who i'm saying thank
you to
but
thank you
uh
huh
in your last marshmallow you were asked
the traditional shower question you
featured it on stream but then you
dodged it so i'm gonna ask again it
again which part of your body do you
wash most intensely
no that was not the question you
originally asked which part i washed
first no
i don't remember the question being
which i washed the most intensively well
that would be my hair probably
because you use shampoo and all that and
then uh conditioner and all that
obviously all of it is
gravy
so i think you miss your chance by
asking the question wrong you're not
gonna get any
sensitive answers out of that it's
obviously my hair
obviously
[Music]
oh
someone said someone wrote a sweet
messages message saying i shouldn't show
it but
i'm glad
um
i'm glad you think so i'm glad you feel
that way
maybe you know that i'm talking about
you
there's a japanese question
[Music]
[Applause]
the question in japanese was um
what kind of place
uh makes me
feel relaxed or healed
for them it would be a library no not a
library a
book book selling place
a book shop bookstore and i said well of
course obviously it would be home for me
or at least when when i have cats at
home then it would be home so anywhere
where my cats are a bookstore
um and the other place would probably be
a spa
um
because i know it's
been the luxurious maybe but yeah a spa
with
massage getting a massage there but even
just like chilling in the spa like
recently i've been getting into the
sauna
um i didn't like going into the sauna
before because i was embarrassed about
like other people being naked and me
being naked and all that but but i've
managed recently to go into the sauna on
my vacation quite often because i always
went during a time where no one else was
in there
uh or i went with my bff for example and
that already took a lot of courage but
um it it was okay
it was okay
i told her don't look at me don't look
at me please don't look at me
yeah
and then the other thing i said was
because i grew up in a and still live in
a country that has no ocean
um for me
just being somewhere where there is an
ocean so at a beach or or just i don't
know even on the bridge looking at a
an ocean
um
is for me very very beautiful and
inspiring and healing and yeah
i like that
so
for me it's maybe more special than for
someone who grew up in a country with an
ocean i would say
maybe yeah
yeah but we have nice um lakes and
mountains
so that on the other side is not that
special to me
but but it's nice too it's nice too
yeah going to a beach for me is every
time a big event big special event i
can't do it that often it's usually
always during a vacation
i want to go to greece again
[Music]
uh
someone asked if i want to make a slower
song
um
as an original song i suppose because in
my karaoke streams they enjoy those kind
of songs from me um i think i may have
mentioned this before maybe
as a song
part of an album
but not as a single
um
when comparing yourself to the rest of
halloween do you think you work hard
enough i think this this question is
trying to bait something from me but i
will say yes definitely
actually i was thinking about that today
because i was doing an
interview secret
um
but
uh
i think yes i work very [\h__\h] hard i
do work very [\h__\h] hard yes
[Music]
someone in japanese asked me during holo
talk if i um write
the things down to translate them and
yes i do i i constantly
i pretty much try to write everything
down one on one
um the way the guest says it rather than
just little keywords i know professional
people would probably just write a lot
of small keywords but for me
i'm not professional so i need to be
very exact with it otherwise i'll forget
things and i don't know like i've seen
them like a video before on how
professional life translators work
and they have like
little signs and all that that that they
know what it means and they can connect
it in their brain properly and it makes
sense for them
signs and small words keywords and all
that for them it makes sense but for me
i just write down everything with the
keyboard not with my hand
i wouldn't be fast enough with my hand i
just i just tap tap tap tap and i think
i actually
[Music]
i
i think
do i write it down in english already i
feel like i've writed
like they talk in japanese but what i'm
writing down is i think part japanese
part english so at that moment i'm
already translating partially
um
yeah
so yeah that's that
the talk
haven't had home talking about by the
way um the reason why
i'm not doing it right now is because
the only member i have left in third gen
is pecora senpai and
i'm nervous about it
and and then there's two other members
that are from before verge and that are
a little bit hard to get so i've been
struggling with that too
so
the members i have
at my disposal right now
are all kind of difficult in some way or
never
and and then then then i figured out um
the other day that
um
i can sit now and we in theory could all
sit
in 3d
um
so i wanted to use that for whole talk
but then i realized that is actually
we can't do it in collabs yet
don't don't ask why
technical things
so
i can't make use of it and i was like oh
maybe i should wait until they implement
it so we can use it in collabs but
that will probably take months months
and months and months so i probably
should not wait for it um
yeah
so yeah that's what i've been kind of
like uh
the reason why i've been holding
uh
on to the next hubble talk episode is
because
uh
um
the guest the choice of guests i have
is difficult
and i don't want to skip to 4th gen that
would be too fast too too sudden
hmm just please be a bit patient um see
it as some kind of spring break or
something
yeah i was thinking maybe i should start
with holo ian now
maybe do um the en girls for a while
um but for that i think
i wanna experiment a bit more so it
takes more preparation i wanna try
something new if i interview the en
members
you know some
i
i'm a little bit stuck right now
i know
[Music]
um
no
oh next question
[Music]
uh
um
[Music]
yeah have you cancelled your bus card
yet no
um
[Music]
ah
how many girls in her life i've met in
real life
uh only some of the ones in japan
so far
i've met cali i've met mine in senpai
i've met suicide senpai solar senpai
matsuri senpai
uh
brain brain empty
uh i've met
i've met uh super senpai obviously in
energy obviously both on senpai fixed uh
or like put to put apart my my pc
uh before i left canada i've met yeah
mm-hmm
no i did not meet peculiar senpai
where this is like for like a moment of
a quick moment
aytan i've met but that's not a talent
uh yeah i think i've mentioned
everyone i did not meet coco samba i
know
no
but
who says i will never maybe in the
future i will ha
[Music]
i think i mentioned everyone well yes
i've seen jago
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
open the express menu
i think that's it
no i didn't mention connor doesn't but
did you not listen
i did mention her
i was also just kind of a quick
a quick moment
um
yeah
i think
i think i've seen
one
[Music]
whole 102
whole stars
memories but i don't know who it
[Laughter]
was it was just briefly for like a
moment but i don't know who it was
i don't remember it was just too too
quick
yeah they
um i mean
i i should know obviously because of
course they we all look exactly the way
we look in real life we look like we're
looking on the screen obviously so i
don't know why i wouldn't know but um
it makes no sense obviously but
you know
it was just that it was darkened
and and cloudy and
uh i don't know there was some
some dirt on my eyes
i was distracted
i just didn't get a good look yet
that's why i don't i don't recall
sorry man
[Music]
but the most special member of the mall
that i've met is genma
[Music]
oh yeah
i think i'll get to meet genma again for
dokomi i'm so excited
i'm so excited
honey kanji no yomikata
[Music]
yo
your lunch
your lunch you're ah i'm gonna be your
lunch
uh wait i need to show you this
i'm gonna show you this
someone um
wrote me this text in japanese which is
just random
kanjis aligned
that all put together if you read them
one by one
have an english
meaning if you like you know because it
says
i am takanawa from
but
the kanjis mean something completely
different it's just a reading that
turns into
something english
so they were testing me if i can read it
but
it's it's a funny way to write this
troll
japanese troll
yum
where was i now
where was i
roll scroll here go
um
ah
are you interested in vr game streams if
permission can be obtained virtual
reality is gonna be good game for you
thank you for the question um wait
so japanese i want to
um yeah amma has been inspiring me
inspiring me for that too
um because
like for example the cooking the the
pasta
stream that she did was really cute and
funny
um
i want to i i'm not sure i haven't
really looked much into what's possible
in terms of
3d
in virtual vr streams because like
you know we need permissions and all
that
um
i don't know i haven't much looked into
that genre and that market yet oops that
was the oh that was the right layer
yeah yeah okay
um if you guys have ideas you're welcome
to tell me
on twitter also
hmm
beat saber oh i think that's not
interesting as a stream
but the one that ahmed did the cooking
one i wouldn't mind doing
myself but not right now i don't want to
do it too soon after she did it but
um
yeah maybe there's a similar one that's
more focused on fast food maybe
that we could do
um
[Music]
job simulator yeah i don't know there's
there's i'm sure there's a lot but i'm
just not really aware of many of them oh
yeah minecraft vr
gudet was struggling so much with that
it seems pretty tough man
yeah
my squash soul
difficult to control everything
good has a hard time with vr in general
yeah but me too though
i wouldn't even know how to show my vr
body on obs like that
i wouldn't even know that
vacation simulator huh vacation
simulator
interesting
oh
ah
well it's probably not that difficult
yeah
probably not that difficult to because i
mean good i got it to work so
as long as i have ame as my tech guy
i
think gonna be all right
i'm so slow i'm so slow i'm just slowing
[Music]
um
oh
my vr thingy i have a vive it's so heavy
and so
uh bulky and
it never fits right i mean it does
sometimes but then
you move a little bit and it's [\h__\h] up
again
i don't know if it's just because of the
vive or because it's just how
these
things feel
but the vibe itself is already pretty
expensive so i don't feel like buying a
whole new set
that is
basically
almost the same quality
because vive is the vibe itself is not
bad
it's just like it probably feels a bit
different it's just you know a bit a bit
different but quality wise it's fine
but
it doesn't fit well on my head i should
have like tested it out somewhere in the
store
yeah from what i've like noticed so far
because all the other myth members are
using a valve
um is that their they have
um i don't i can't imagine how they're
they do that with their hands they seem
to like i need to push buttons to change
my hands
but they don't seem to have to push
buttons
uh
so yeah
i don't know how that works for them but
that seems nice
it tracks your fingers
well that's cool
but aren't you holding something in your
hand
the index knuckles has finger track
index like i don't even know what they
use wait what will valve
valve
hand
[Music]
track
what what are what is like what's
included
ah
that's what it looks like
oh
i mean it's also like not the the best
thing obviously
to track hands but it seems to somewhat
work like i i notice when when they try
to make a specific movement they really
have to focus
to get it right
um
but
but at least it works roughly and that's
cool so you always have to you still
always have to grasp it though no
no you can
is it just
and when you when you hold it like this
though is it just hanging on your hand
like generally you have to hold it
though right
you don't have to grip
you don't
oh it's strapped around oh
[Music]
that's pretty different from what i have
with my vive
oh there's a there's a marshmallow that
i just want to say [\h__\h] you too
i just want to say [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] you very very much
you are stupid just get alive just don't
write to me anymore
[\h__\h] you
thank you very very much
just accept it the way it is and get out
of here
please don't stay in touch
um
did a collab with cali reviewing remixes
of her song it was one of my favorite
takamuni streams is there a chance we
get something similar with your producer
and a guest of your choice
no because like people don't really make
remixes for me and if i think even if i
did like uh
like a contest now
um i think the participation would be
pretty low
i feel like for cali back then
she just kind of um was able to
ride a certain
hype thingy
really well
and you know got the
got everyone's attention
the right people's attention and the
song you know
was cool so people were really into it
but in my case it would be like kind of
different like j-poppy cute songs and
all that so
i feel like the turnout wouldn't be so
great unfortunately
as much as i would love to hear a lot of
um
remixes
[Music]
yeah and it would have to be like um
together with a release probably to make
sense or
i don't know
um
yeah
i was thinking about doing something
like that before but
i
i don't think it would work so well i'm
just being realistic here trying to plan
out things so they don't fail
oh
i wonder if these fingers look okay
[Music]
this one looks weird
i don't know how to draw hands
who knows how to draw hands nobody does
it's a big mystery
[Music]
i think it's roughly
okay
like if you look from afar
[Music]
does it look okay
no
it doesn't look okay
the smaller one needs to be smaller
probably
you know what would be cute actually
i'm having trouble with like folding
them inside like that
but the small one would be actually cute
if she would uh extend it
wouldn't that be cute
i think that would be cute
[Music]
you she has a
she has a umbrella with her
i guess she would use an umbrella i was
about to say would she even use one like
i feel like she wouldn't mind having
rain on her
on her body
raining down on her
she's not made out of sugar after all
thanks for asking answering my question
oh
which one was it i wondered ah that one
it did come in
double um
what questions should we answer next
though
i don't even know how many there are
and i'm sorry if i
am not reading a lot of them
[Music]
you have mods i'm sorry i can't answer
your question because
i know people get very triggered by that
topic so
i've been talking about it too much
i've been mentioning it too much even
though it's just a reality but
oh
i would never want to be the president
or
king of any country
i mean jokes and all are fun about being
the empress of whatever wherever the
hell
but
that question i cannot answer seriously
should i answer it jokingly
uh
i wouldn't want to be i wouldn't want to
be a president or king i would want to
be a princess
of anywhere it doesn't matter
[Music]
ah
which one would you rather want as a
gift bunny girl kiara custom figure
or korean traditional handbook
[Music]
are you gonna
how are you gonna are you planning on
giving me something generally you can
only give me gifts and document not not
you can't send it to cover if you're
choosing hanbok what is your free size i
need to get it to humble
my
friend well first of all
i would choose the handbook because i
don't really um
i don't really
uh um
um what's the word i don't collect uh
fake ears i don't know how serious this
is are you tricking me
it sounds kind of serious though
um so i don't care about the figure
although it's cool if it's a custom one
it's pretty cool
um
now i i can't really tell you my free
size
what is keanu's free size
well there's an official kiana body size
handbook handbook doesn't really need
free size i know what a hamburg looks
like
i know what a hanbok looks like if
anything you maybe need like the the
bust only
isn't the rest of it like really big and
flowy it doesn't it doesn't um
it's like a big big loose
skirt so
it's not it's not
around around the waist and around the
hips it's not even
it's not even um you know
uh fitting so
but if you're serious about it you could
just get um
i think
is there no sml
maybe just um
in korea
asian size maybe something between s and
m
considering it's uh
asian size
problem
probably s works
anyway
i do want a handbook
this probably was just the system just
trying to
get the free size out of me but but but
i i legitimately want a humble car
but isn't that expensive though cause
like um
i know kimonos are really expensive
japanese traditional clothing and for
for austria our traditional clothing uh
dandel
you can get a pretty cheap one
in theory um
but
i wonder about hamburg
if it's expensive
[Music]
i have a custom one not really expensive
really
what do you what do you mean if not
really expensive
also for kimono there's like a summer
version right that's yukata and that one
is cheap
kimonos are expensive yukata is cheap
now i wonder is there a summer version
of a hanbok
that's also cheap
i wouldn't know about that
i mean even
actually i guess yeah even if i had a
hanbok here in austria like i i wouldn't
wear it
i would only wear it in korea if
anything
usually rent
[Music]
yeah yeah
even if i had it here
it would be kind of weird to wear that
outside in austria
so you know what just uh let's let's say
i'll take the bunny bunny suit custom
figure
you better not be a jerk
now i'm looking forward to it are you
coming to dokomi to give it to me
now you got me all excited
a custom figure
oh i'm excited
[Music]
my
deaf joke no don't be so negative it
could be real
[Music]
why do people in europe smoke a lot what
a weird question
i don't think europeans smoke more than
any other
continent
do we is there such a study
i don't smoke
i don't know the people europeans smoke
much i don't think so
i don't think so
not much more than any other country
probably
but i don't smoke
[Music]
um
hackle bell for employee meal
on your own cost yes but i'm not paying
for that you're gonna the only food you
get for employee email is kfp food
[Music]
why are you asking can a youtuber claim
streaming equipment as business expense
and tax reduction
streaming equipment yes
but
uh
games and so on even though i use it for
my stream
as far as i know
no at least my tax person says no
i'm sure other people try it and can
make it work but my tax person is kind
of strict
games are really not cheap that is true
and we play so many like those [\h__\h]
nintendo games are 60 [\h__\h] dollars 60
70 dollars per copy
anyway
[Music]
foreign
someone asked what kind of collabs i
want to do
if um i get to do an off collab again
and i've i said that currently
i am planning enough collab because some
girls are visiting me
so
actually i have been thinking about it
and
i want to do
um
maybe
you know watch a movie together because
it's more cozy when you do it
um
like in real life together
and
try
okay and also try games that um
you can only play with couch co-op
there are some games out there
like uh warioware but besides that i
can't actually think of so many right
now but there are definitely some more
couch co-op games that i want to use the
opportunity to play them um so i might
ask you guys
about some more suggestions of games
that
are not playable online oh yeah we
should play smash
yeah and then you're here we should play
smash oh [\h__\h] yes remind me of that
we're gonna smash hell yeah
um
we're gonna smash
super smash girls
wonderful
let's go
[Music]
need more controllers though i have a
pro controller and the two the two side
controllers
maybe one of the girls can take
um
can bring their own switch
as well
but only the controllers
undertale
uh
maybe sometime in the future i'll play
it maybe
maybe
i know a lot of people love it
but the next game we're gonna place link
uh uh netlink's awakening uh um
uh uh wind waker
yay
yeah we're talking i know we were
talking about online games oh i forgot
this part here
like multiplayer games
[Music]
i think that was just unrelated
oh
what did i just dream that or is it true
that
um
breath of the wild too was at least
delayed to 2023
was it that they originally had it
planned in 2022 yeah that seemed um that
already seemed
difficult
yeah it was delayed it was delayed oh no
20 23
ah will i even still be alive in 2010
yes i will i'm eternal i'm a phoenix
oh man but the [\h__\h] that's so far away
if it's gonna be winter 2023 i'm gonna
cry winter is unacceptable i will riot
if it's winter
can't do that to us
i want my favorite nintendo youtuber to
play it and then watch it rather than
playing it myself i just want to watch
my favorite nintendo youtuber play the
game
that's the one thing i'm looking forward
to
it's not about myself
see
no one can ever say i'm selfish
i'm i'm i just want that youtuber to
play the game i'm i'm so unselfish
while
wow
[Music]
how inspiring
where am i what the [\h__\h]
so confusing
[Music]
when i was younger and i didn't really
know english that well i was so confused
by the word selfish
selfish because
i was like
ew it's a fish
[Music]
i don't like fish so i don't like the
word selfish
[Music]
what a weird word isn't it
i'm so slow drawing this
thank god we didn't draw her actual
clothes i would be sitting here tomorrow
still
and day after tomorrow
have you done an fish video yet i've
done m shark yes
she sells seashells on the seashore
selfishly that's a new one i haven't
heard it like that before
yes i do need my rest
i'm just gonna copy and paste those
buttons
[Music]
it's a pussycat doll song
old one
really old one
remember
[Music]
mmm
i'm gonna pick up another question in a
second [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
[Music]
dreaming days
okay
[\h__\h]
line is too thin
are we doing yakuza last episode
tomorrow yes we are
just remembered i just oh my god we're
finishing yakuza tomorrow
let's get a question
can we post banners to you and document
yes of course
uh you can also
bring anything any other gifts besides
letters which you can usually not
uh send to the
present address in japan this is one of
the
only opportunities you get
if you wanna
give me something physical
but
no food and
preferably also no plushies
because we kind of have to test them
and i mean you can do plushies but
if they are
if it's hard to test them for any
anything inside then it might get
ditched
uh
yeah besides that i can't think of
anything right now uh that's ng
no iris won't be there in person so no
i don't think you can do that send her
gifts like you uh at dokomi
um
[Music]
kfb look at this question
do you have an answer this to this kfp
can't look at this question
look at this
look at this just look at this
wow
[Laughter]
i've done it at least once i've done uh
i think even twice
i've done it um
i've done a whole live original songs
jazz karaoke and i think also a normal
one
yeah
you're lacking critical information very
critical information
[Laughter]
wow
sorry i had to just point that one out
um
[Music]
a few other hollomans have created
twitch channels and some have streamed
on them lately do you have any plans to
do the same
i don't know i don't want to be left out
you know so maybe because of
um what's it called fomo
feeling fear of no
fear of missing out yeah fomo
maybe but
currently i don't want to
um i i feel like it would will be um
kind of a pain in the ass to keep on um
leading people to a different platform
we're comfortable here so
don't necessarily want to do it
um
but we do have to think about the fact
that it could
help kfp grow a little bit
um
you know i know it's cozy in all but but
and there's and there's a market there
there's a lot of people who only watch
twitch streams and don't watch youtube
streams and i don't know
maybe maybe some
new ones for us
um
but at the moment it's not planned
uh
yeah
um
does this make sense the way i drew it
it doesn't
not exactly
i only want you to never go to twitch
before whole life i didn't watch youtube
streams
at all
um so but i also didn't really watch
twitch i just didn't watch streams at
all
so but if i were to watch somewhere it
would have been twitch i i watched
one streamer on twitch i think
kid boga
but
only only in during a time where i was
like
um where i caught up on all of the ones
that were on youtube edited down i was
like i need more of this so i went to
twitch to to watch the whole
the whole show
uh but yeah besides that
no
where where is the arm where where
should the arm be what am i doing
that makes no sense i should
just
continue here that's okay
that is okay
i don't want to draw the stick because i
don't know is that perfectly straight
can i draw i can there's a little tool
for a line right
[Music]
there we go
oh
ah
straight line brush size
somewhere here
oops
okay so
yeah it's okay
and then
upset
then
here
now
over here okay
is that
the same thickness
i think it is it looks a little bit off
to me but okay so we have to fix some
things here
we have to fix some things
i should have just drawn it on a
different layer but oh well way
another question
[Music]
how do you feel about meeting your fans
again in dokomi this time i think more
people are coming from overseas and
different continents as well really
looking forward to concentrate meet
greet and meet
reading great and overall conventions
and this is the first time for me to
visit
are you coming from korea
so maybe this is the same person who
asked about the figure in the handbook
who is this because they ended the they
ended the
marshmallow with with some korean text
so it sounds like they're coming from
korea
what
who are you
which one is coming from korea and
bringing me a handbook
who is that
i know i have more than one korean fan
but i feel like i only have one korean
fan that that could be that that that
that would go that far to go to germany
to see me on one day
listen
who is it
who
who is it i want to know crisis why is
why the [\h__\h] is marshmallow anonymous
shouldn't have made it anonymous who is
then i want to know who it is
but yeah i'm i'm very excited about this
year because um this year at least like
uh
there will be more cave people
last year i'm surprised
that we actually even had any kind of
people to begin with
because my appearance was announced
after tickets were sold
out um
so i i i was surprised how they were
even any any cave people to begin with
but this year
this year there's so many more
to come to see me
so last year i was actually
really nervous you know i have some
traumatic experiences when it comes to
empty
audience and um
i was really nervous about it now it was
not full anyway because of the sea thing
they could not let
a lot of people inside
um but but
so i was trying to i was trying to tell
myself that but
but but this year i think the
restrictions are not as strong as last
year um also because they're selling
more tickets
that is proof of it
so
i think we can fill up the hall maybe i
feel like the the having one seat in
between open
might not even be necessary i mean that
will be something that we won't know
until
um until dokomi happens but
um we might see we might see a lot of
people also i want as many people as
possible to get into that hall
because um
there's way more okay if people trying
to get in now so
if i heard that last year a lot of
people were
stuck outside because they closed the
the doors and couldn't get inside
anymore because of the cc restrictions
safing restrictions you know
i'm excited but i also feel
kind of
nervous and
pressured because i know that there's so
many people coming from outside of
germany this year spending a lot of
money on flight tickets and all that so
now
now i'm actually worried i can't make it
worthwhile for you
um
oh nervous
[Music]
dawn 2k oh my god
not going just for you
huh
what do you mean not just going for me
that doesn't make it any better
but maybe it does make it better but
when you say it so directly to me
and then you make my heart code sunset
okay
we'll do whatever whatever you want not
that i care i don't care
i thought i was special i'm going mostly
for you
drop that mostly immediately
drop it drop it
drop it like it's hot
[Music]
so there will be
a stream again
of the concert so you will be able to
see that and the panel will also be
streamed like last year i think the only
thing you can't see uh online is the
meet and greet
meeting great is for people who are
there only
yeah so that's that and now uh
everything here is messed up because it
didn't align properly great
[Music]
i hope
kobo will be happy about this i hope
is she still rafting
[Music]
definitely if you go to germany from
outside of germany
for for dokomi you should uh enjoy
enjoy everything
that dusseldorf has to offer while you
are there they're so rafting wow
damn
isn't it like pretty it's super late
over there in indonesia
[Music]
they started 15 minutes before my stream
all right they started really late for
them
speaking of which how is it a halloween
wrapped book
um
i don't know no one's no one's talking
about it it was like hololen is so weird
man they they're like let's play this
game and everyone's like yes yes yes yes
yes and then no one takes the initiative
to do it
unless me unless it's me
it feels like i have to plan it fine
i'll do it myself
yeah these weirdos these weirdos
i want to play too
i want to know what all the the craze is
about like why is everyone playing raft
it's just like basically
minecraft on on one block minecraft on
the ocean right
that's basically what it is i think
with somewhat
better graphics i guess
hmm
okay
boat simulator no rat simulator
so interested in physically visiting
conventions outside of europe of course
i am what kind of question is that
do you watch many whole life clips in
your free time oh they show up in my
suggestions a lot so i do watch some of
them
yeah every now and then
um
i wouldn't say i
oopsie watch it
like
every day but
and mostly
this this may be maybe a little bit
narcissistic but mostly i watch um
clips where i am in
just because
uh
i want to see how
they like put it together and and
how it came across and all that you know
it's kind of like checking that that you
guys are not doing anything bad
like certain people have certain editing
styles that are really funny to me that
i think really make make those moments
even more funny than they already are
so i appreciate that
um
funny hair
you know kobo has that kind of hair that
i feel like if she wasn't like
junior or elementary school
i feel like the other kids would
probably like have bullied her for her
hair they would have probably put like
gum in her hair and coco would cry and
be like mommy they're boy
oh i can totally see it
oh
poor baby
you probably were bullying her because
of her hair
like pull her hair or
make fun of her because of her hair
oh man must be so rough man cool boy
it's okay come on
i'm just making up
sad stories that didn't happen but but
can you imagine
throwing bath bomb
no don't pull flash bath bombs into
kobo's hair
it doesn't her hair doesn't even work
like that probably
i'm getting sad about things that don't
even that aren't even reality
[Music]
yeah
typical
ah
there's so much hair
how did she do it
i is there so much hair oh my god
okay
yeah
a little bit
[Music]
yeah
i thought you said you wouldn't be doing
answers anymore when did i say i
wouldn't do it ever again anymore
what changed your mind um i think
nothing changed my mind just felt like
doing something for kobo
and i felt like i needed a little bit of
variety in my schedule so it was like
what did i not do for a while um drawing
stream that's all that's all there is to
it
[Music]
i'm skipping some questions that i
already answered several times recently
[Music]
oh my god
uh
[Music]
there's a lot of small questions would
you prefer to be seen as cute beautiful
or sexy
uh cute
favorite time of the day
[Music]
one question
6 pm
um will you try to make a tailless video
just wondering i did one
before
in one of my first streams with ina as a
collab
the very moment that you made you think
i want to be an idol when i saw betty's
kobo
hens or roosters
for what purpose
for what just which is general what i
prefer like what does it doesn't matter
love both
can you give us a list of idle groups
individuals you followed
you mean i don't sell a like and veggies
kobo everything of hell project um
at least back in the day nowadays i
don't know
them so well anymore there's some new
groups that i don't follow
and um besides handling project there
was
not
much
in terms of
japanese idols
um
the hell project is morning muslim and
venice kobo and cute and smiley and
um
bono
and so on those are really mostly the
ones that i had interested in
uh
i'm gonna skip the rest
is there a talent you have
discovered after joining whole life
discovered for the first time
have i
maybe maybe i'm
shooting arrows in
minecraft in video games not in all of
them but
some of them shooting arrows
archery
uh
live translating
i guess so
um
yeah
graphing design no not really i don't
see that as a talent of mine nor as a
skill
unfortunately
i wish i could call it a calendar skill
i'm not that good
i need to fix so many things i should
have drawn the stick first
it's my passion it's my passion
totally graphic design
is
is my passion although you know i was
really flattered i said this the other
day but i was really flattered when
gouda was like
can you make pumpkins for me your
thumbnails are so cute and and colorful
and poppy
i was like
my thumbnails
are nothing special
yeah it made me pretty happy
it was pretty flattered
i will tell you that
but it is
[Music]
okay okay okay one will be faster
breathe faster
look at that mess
i'm gonna clean it up
[Music]
your thumbnail designs are great thank
you
thank you
there's definitely some improvement
there compared to my old ones
although i'm not so happy with the one
from today from this stream i was like
i was in the middle of binge watching
somewhere or something so i just wanted
to get it over with
um
yeah it's okay um the thumbnail for
today is okay it's okay
hmm
i think i need to eat my doughnut
doughnuts
[Music]
let me cut that part
right
oh my stomach is growling
[Music]
this part can be messy even in the liner
it's not so important
[Music]
zoned out there donut
i have once again a sugar glazed
doughnut with me
and it is all mine
guys
it happened again i feel like i'm being
i feel like there is a hit man trying to
kill me because there's again a hole
in my donut
i think i think they're trying to
tell me something maybe it's like
if you
if you don't
if you don't stop eating
donuts we're gonna put a hole in you or
something like that some some message
i'm i'm receiving some messages
but i'm not quite sure what it is
why can i not continue eating donuts why
is there a hole in my donut
anyway i'm gonna eat it anyway
oh um
okay i can i can
i can multitask
[Music]
um
yeah making a yellow mm-hmm
is there anywhere else where i needed to
fix something because of the stick
um
we're getting
oh we're getting close to an end here
hmm
oh yeah
[Music]
um
what line on her face
[Music]
where her hair needs to stick at the top
are you telling me to fix this or
as i noticed i started with such a thick
brush
here on on these sides
and now it's not so that's now it's not
so thick anymore ah maybe wait do you
mean this one
do you mean this hair
what's up
i used to wrong
oh what did i just fix
maybe you mean this one though i guess
we're gonna fix this one
oops what the hell
make it more dynamic
i finished my donut already by the way
why is a donut such a short and fast
experience
[Music]
no i don't have more donuts that's my
only donut i only got one donut
yeah because they took the hole
if they didn't take the hole i would
have more donut
unbelievable
[Music]
uh what am i what do i want to fix
i think i will not fix
this
[Music]
we can start coloring
soon
[Music]
oh wait her arm oh wait i s oh that
looks weird oh i just saw something that
really really looks weird
her whole arm should be like way more
over here i think
and that was the wrong layer
that's okay
i think
should be
i mean right now she has like really
droopy
shoulders
the arm
i think
should be here
oh
i will flip it again soon
and then
we get rid of this
and this
and then we check it again
if that looks okay
[Music]
okay
mama mama so let's take a look oh
does she have bubba
she has a little bit bubba
okay
in that case
i completely ignored her bubba until now
i drew her really flat
[Music]
that's hair
that would be
um
sorry kobo john i took all your blah
now you have a
that's still maybe that's still too
small
let me give you a little bit more
kobochan
let's let's pretend
let's pretend you drank
uh
all the milk when you were small and you
ate all the veggies
although
it
doesn't probably it doesn't even depend
on that
there's no science for
booby growth i think
and
if i do that though
that's great and all but i kind of have
to fix this
and then i have to move the buttons
oh no
let me move them ahead of time
because that would be
[Music]
bye
the other day it was the birthday of my
booby booby dokal
of my
favorite idol who is not an idol anymore
yeah i tweeted about it
not that i can really like
do anything for her on her birthday
cause she's not an idol anymore and she
doesn't she doesn't even know i exist
um probably
[Music]
i don't think she knows about me
kanyon
aka model
knows me and follows me she was one of
my or she's
but my number one commie aussie
she doesn't know i
exist so
that's that hurts doesn't it no it's
okay she's not an idol anymore so i
shouldn't even
i should i should respect that uh and
stop stop hoping for things that are
never gonna happen
[Music]
foreign
one of us
okay
in this case i don't wanna be one of you
i want my idol to know me
i want her to know me
[Music]
no what no
no
if that comes from here
[Music]
you want to add it after all
look
[Music]
here's some extra lines i'm missing
just because
[Music]
and we're gonna add some
foams here
[Music]
um
that looks like that would be the finger
here
but it's not it's just supposed to be in
it will be colored in
and then it will make sense hopefully
although in order to make it look a
little bit more
separate on
this yeah okay
uh
i never watched indiana jones
[Laughter]
i actually never watched where's the
thumb the thumb and when you hold me
like this
there's a chance you don't see the pump
depending on how exactly you hold it
i know you're shocked and all calm down
calm down hold on you're gonna get a
heart attack i don't want you to get a
heart attack okay
i'm watching them aren't there more than
one movie which one would we even watch
isn't there more than one
i have not seen
indiana jones four
four and we would watch the first one i
have been on an indiana jones ride in
disneyland
and it was fun
it was really fun
there are only three
oh why did a lot of people say four
the fourth one is terror oh okay you're
ignoring the existence of the fourth one
as one of those those situations and i
don't
i want to
make this outline here thicker
look at my messy lines here oh my god
oh dear
[Music]
how long have we been doing this three
hours okay i still need to read super
chats uh later today so
i'm not sure how long we're gonna do
this i don't i can't do it for too long
i need to need to read super chats i
need to catch up
[Music]
i think i'll like fill in the colors and
start shading
um
but then finish the rest of stream
another time but i'll try to get as far
as possible
on stream
um
okay let's look at this whole thing
horizontally flipped one second make it
bigger
okay
um
looks fine
play ready thank you for the donuts
ah wait i see something oh
what am i doing
ew
what did i do
her head her hair shape looks like [\h__\h]
ah
um
[Music]
that side is so different
the size is so different
the whole this part here too
it's way more volume on this side
i know
thank you
actually i i toned it down i think at
least i tried to tone it down
uh
but i'm glad you think so
that's probably just weird too you know
what we're gonna
just gonna
stitch this
what does that look like
[Music]
what is that brush anyway
i'm glad i noticed that
also
the balance here is
um
off too
[Music]
but that's i think
this side is actually fun this is the
one that bothers me
it should be higher kobachan kobo is
here finally are you done rafting
i was i was
chanting kobo 12 times and you didn't
come it took you so long
what took you so long
just finished what what just finished
sailing now i'm going to sleep in peace
while watching oh okay okay
i i wait let me give you i'm going to
give you a tour
um this is the outlines
i'm glad you like it
uh
this was the sketch
oh i forgot the tattletail booze i know
teddy teddy balls it probably makes no
sense for you
because we want it to rain in your world
but we're gonna add it anyway because
it's a cute thing you know what
territories is
it's cute
that's cute and i'm giving you an
umbrella
i'm sorry i didn't draw you in your own
clothes because
i think you are aware
that they are
a little bit
tough to draw
isn't kobo's job to get rid of the ring
no she's supposed to make it rain she's
a rain shaman
straight line
straight line oh that looks pretty good
[Music]
yeah your outfit is so detailed i really
like it but the moment i started drawing
i was like nope nope nope nope nope
nope nope
no no no no no no no that will just give
me a headache
maybe she can get rid of it too
but i think her general purpose is
making it rain
in indonesia arrangements are
cool
what is your job making it rain or not
making it rain or both
enlighten us
probably just both
no
now i'm confused too
did she fall asleep already that was so
fast
she said she was gonna fall asleep while
watching my stream she's that was
[\h__\h] fast took her one minute man
that rafting must have been exhausting
no we can't do voice chat because um
collab band is not lifted
i need a massage cool boy
massage your mommy please
help
ah okay i'll look at it oh you can do
both i can see if we can
[Music]
i think i would generally prefer no rain
now let's look at this without the
sketch
are we happy now when we look if
something looks weird
does anything look weird
[Music]
yeah
the ear should be higher
i'm excited for coloring it
rain for my plants no no no they don't
need it no i'm already over watering
them already the way it is
as as is
i'm already
uh
over watering them we don't need extra
rain
good
i think
[Music]
now i feel like
now we fix this shoulder
i feel like
the other shoulder
or like the whole arm
should be more
around around
here
um
also
it's kind of a perspective thing and
also because i cut it off here
but that arm looks really short but it's
supposed to go my gun until like here
like it's supposed to be like this you
get what i mean
but maybe
maybe
okay
because the folds would imply that
that's where the arm is falling but it's
not really there
wouldn't find
i'm trying to fix it
yeah i think it's the perspective but
but but i'll try to manipulate
perspective and i'll also
do this
i'll do this
huh
let's see
if it's help oh [\h__\h]
she [\h__\h]
i should ask her uh answer
[Music]
someone asked in japanese in whole life
super expo 2022 the mascot characters
which one was my favorite and i i have
to say small amount
because
it was just so cute and and she was
doing so many cute things
yeah
like she seemed to be struggling with a
lot of things
like holding things or getting up on the
chair i think i saw a video where she
was trying to get up on the chair
and i was like
[Music]
that oh the wrong
glare
[Music]
right yeah and
the way
the staff helped her was cute too
yeah
so small ammo was great but small amount
kind of had a little bit of an advantage
to the other mascots except for miku
tanya because like miku dania and small
emma were actually like
like not masc not quite masculine like
the others were
like sweaters duck and ankimo and udding
are like you know
animal mascots
and then mikko daniel and smallam are
more like human
small versions of
their actual
self so
so
they have a little bit of an advantage
there
i would say
are are her arms and her shoulders too
wide now what do you think was
actually
[Music]
huh back shoulder
behind the hair
[Music]
i don't know how
i would do that
[Music]
no keep it that way yeah
someone's off with the arm
i feel mostly it's okay now
you know
i would i would what was i going to say
[\h__\h] i forgot what i was going to say
damn it
is her neck too close to her right
shoulder
and now you guys are overthinking it
now you guys are just overthinking it
no swearing and that's cool does kobo
swear
she will be fine i'm sure she'll
eventually
swear
in her streams if she doesn't yet
i thought she was a pure sacral
little shaman girl but
i was instantly proofed wrong anyway
so
i thought i thought she's not a kusuki
but then she turned out to be a kusukaki
so at this point at this point
i
i don't i don't trust her
about being cecil anymore
yeah there's some gremlin energy
all right what are we what are we
looking at
[Music]
[Applause]
stupid pen
keep on choosing the wrong pen
let's change this a little bit
now i'm turning into a perfectionist i
should just
i don't know if i'm making it worse so
i'm making it better
let me like read a question
um
what's your story how you got into art
haha good question
um i'm sure i told this before so sorry
for the people who've heard it before
um but it has to do with tails off i
once received a copy of tales of
symphonia from my mom
or me and my brother we received it and
we played it together
and
then one time i tried to play it alone
but i
i was kind of lost um so i looked up
some
like guide on the internet
and when i looked at the guide i found
i found a whole
tales of community
like a an online forum where where they
and the website where they were like you
know it was just a fan community fan
made website and all that and so i
looked at it one second i'll have to
adjust the microphone
uh uh uh okay
i want no actually that's
too low there we go
oh sure
um
so i looked at the website and i looked
um for some help and then and then i
realized yo you know what it would
actually actually be nice to be kind of
part of the community so i signed up for
the for that
forum and and i made some friends there
and
that way i also found out that there's
more tales of games than just tales of
symphonia
and not only that but that there's just
generally this whole world of jrpgs that
um
all have this kind of like cute anime
style
and the rpg elements to it so
um that's how i discovered the whole
jrpg world and
at that time i didn't quite understand
like where this kind of style came from
you know that that
japanese anime style
and
and i
um
i then figured out aha okay
this is like japanese anime style
somehow
and then i was like i want to draw like
that and i want to make
characters
that look like that i want to recreate
that
so because of that i started drawing a
long time ago and i was like really
actively drawing
and i wanted it to be my
my main job i wanted to become a
character designer for jrpg games
which never happened but
i i was pretty active i was i think my
art was better than it is now so
as i said i i
am
i lack practice nowadays i used to draw
every day now i draw once per year
once or twice per year
yeah
um but yeah that's what motivated me and
got me into art at least like japanese
style art that was really really hooked
on it i was like i like i really like
this and before that i was already kind
of creative
and
enjoyed like drawing but it wasn't quite
like anime style or anything like that
yet
[Music]
honestly i feel like for cooper
um
no one of those see-through raincoats
would actually be a great merch idea
kobo are you listening
remember this you may have thought of it
yourself already but i feel like a
raincoat would be a great merch idea
like
something like
oh
yeah yeah yeah
nice
[Music]
something like this oh okay maybe more
manly maybe more neutral
but that's cute
ah it would be cute
looking at raincoats
or i guess this would work this is more
small small but uh
this looks this looks very
um
neutral
have some cobol logo on there somewhere
and have it with cobble colors
she responded
here i know i hope i can make my jacket
as much the jacket oh the jacket looks
tough but a raincoat is definitely
um in reach i would say
oh
[Music]
okay
um
sure yeah if you make this jacket
you know i would buy it but i don't know
if you're if your male audience would
wear it
maybe you can make
a more a more wearable version of it i
could see that
a little bit more like a toned down
version of that jacket yeah i could see
that
i have so many ideas for merchandise
this might this year will be my second
time releasing birthday merchandise and
have so many ideas yeah
when i have a question here when is
jonker's movie's birthday see i actually
don't really know the exact date when
they were born
um i know it like roughly
but like i feel like
it's not the real date like um i think
that the the original like owner um
just didn't document it incorrectly
because it was something like the first
of february or january or something like
that or december
and the first just sounds
too
perfect
yeah i don't think it was the first
i mean i wasn't there but it just
doesn't sound right to me
no
um so i don't celebrate that verb i know
it's surprising that this
cat
lady takanashi kiara who is so crazy
about her cats
doesn't surpr doesn't um um throw a
birthday party for her cats
but no i do not for a birthday party
when i get
i should i should but they don't
understand birthdays okay they don't
understand the concept of birthdays and
i am fully aware of that so i'm not
going that far to celebrate their
birthday no
um
have you considered playing omori for
the mk punishment
money is horror
i thought it was just just like kind of
kind of like emotional rpg
but i didn't think it was
horror
um
for the punishment i keep on forgetting
it it's not like i'm trying to
get rid of it but
um but i just keep on forgetting it you
have to believe me
um
i don't i don't know what like i don't
know many horror games so i also don't
know what i should play i don't want to
play something too scary
thanks for the membership welcome
um i was i was um considering that game
where you're a barista
and um
i don't know
i mean there's low-key also a chance
that we could do
ring fit even though i don't like
the thought of it but the reason is i
have this fan art of myself
and i want to use it for the thumbnail
sometimes there's just art that
i feel like i need to make a stream only
in order to use it for thumbnail
i want to use this in my rainbow
adventure
youtube
[Music]
so this is perfect
i want to use this
this is this piece of art is
single-handedly motivating me to play
room for the adventure on stream
[Music]
there's a chance there's a chance there
i can't promise the artist was um
nexit nexit gun n-a-x-i-t-g
that should be it i always save them
with
the
um twitter handle
i think we can start
uh
putting the color in by the way
we need to try a bunch of file for this
fantasy 14 art
you know
i wouldn't mind doing one stream on it
but it just feels like you know like a
little bit of a waste because
an mmrpg is supposed to be played over a
longer amount of time and with people
and i would have never people i know
there's a few people streaming who
stream final fantasy 14 in whole life
but it's not like they're suddenly gonna
commit to uh i don't know twi playing it
twice weekly or so just for me
um and i can't commit to that either and
you know how many times i bought final
fantasy 14 and i would have to buy it
one more time and i've already spent
probably about 200 bucks on final
founders fantasy 14 just buying the game
several times therefore i do not want to
buy it ever again
[Music]
ah tantra during one of your alice
madden's return students you were
talking about airlines and mentioned a
bomb story but you didn't give any
details is there a chance you could tell
us this bomb story
yes i was keeping that story for
when i'm really desperate for a story
one day
should i tell it i'm not that desperate
right now
i'll give you a tlr now but one day i'll
tell it properly
i was
on a plane to japan
there was a
a hint that there could be a bomb in it
so after taking off pretty fast after
that we went back to the original
airport
all of our hand luggage and the inside
luggage everything was checked for bombs
hours and hours and hours and hours and
actually many eight hours uh
24 hours later
i got into a new flight
and found out that
somewhere in that time when i was
waiting found out that
there was
there was a bomb in the plane
wait why am i laughing
it's crazy isn't it but don't worry
apparently it was a bomb that couldn't
have gone off
ah maybe it was a troll um
[Music]
i know it's insane
it's insane i know
um which made me
commit to
never never flying with that airline
ever again because the whole
the whole chevy bang around
it like
you know customer service and all that
was so [\h__\h]
that
i i was like i'm never giving this
company money ever again not because of
the bomb but like like the way they
treated me and the other passengers
it's kiara she's
um
so
one day i'll tell you the story more
details
i just dropped a bomb on you didn't i
[Music]
it apparently happened
quite often back then for that airline
for for that airport for all the flights
going off of that airport
um i found out it was like actually like
it happened often but it was always a
bomb that wouldn't have gone off what
the [\h__\h] happened here
no that's okay
like i don't know what
they're i think they're just trying to
um
that damaged the
i don't know
like
they're probably just trying to troll
it's so weird like
they're trying to
they i guess i suppose they were trying
to
just
damage the business
i guess but i don't know who knows who
knows what they were trying to sabotage
the airline or something
who knows who knows
this is such a weird
surreal topic
i'll tell you the full story someday
but if you if you if you
dig deep then you might might find it uh
anyway
stop someone from taking off
yeah
i was really mad because
um it was when i was going for a short
trip
that would have been
just seven days
um
and then
losing twin over 24
hours hurt
a lot because
that's one one day less from seven days
or six days or so
so
yeah
uh from for like i had i had no time
already to begin with so
it was pretty
[\h__\h]
bothersome troublesome
um
[Music]
okay
let's read another question
and i will i think i'll i have to stop
outlining now i have to start doing
colors
um
i think
i think we're good to go
i'll put this in here
ah
pick the colors
all right
let's take this color and
this color
we have reached the next stage
um
refer to editing like yeah okay
and next question is
do you prefer boneless or bone
chicken wings uh boneless always
you know any koreans are not idol songs
probably not no
what's your favorite tulato character
yeah
i really liked kuroko back in the day
but now i would probably
pick someone else but i'm not sure
who um
[Music]
sorry my english somewhat weird it's
because english is not my mother tone i
always fascinated when you're telling us
about your lore and i really love these
phoenix incarnation and kfb settings so
here's my question really try to make
any content based on all these canons
but i have
been doing that already maybe you're new
like for example hinotori is obviously
based on me being a phoenix
and um
um i mean i may have not mentioned kfp
in the song before it was kind of uh it
was unfitting so far
unfitting um but like also my background
is kfp themed i do some streams that are
kfp themed like
um
the menu stream for example very
recently
and i always i always joke about kfp i
have the usual room
and
i want to do something like a job
interview stream sometime
stand-alone lore i don't understand like
what only
like about phoenix i don't think so
not anytime soon that sounds like a lot
of
a lot of effort
[Music]
but no they did mean like songs because
afterwards they say maybe some original
folk balad songs or make it bigger like
in the musical
like uh cronies original song is close
to my imagination so yeah um hirotori
hinatori was that and um
yeah
uh a full-on lore stream i know at some
point i said i wanna do that but
it's
probably
probably not really gonna happen
um
a full on lower stream
cause i would have to like
make up all these things no not makeup
of course not of course not just kidding
it would already be there so where's the
problem
you know what i mean
and then and then you guys would always
quote me on that and i would have no way
of returning anymore
i could never backpaddle anymore because
we would be like but you said on that
stream on that day
that it is like this and that
kiwa
you said it yourself
and i'll be like oh
i forgot
yeah kibaba was lore but it was future
lore i hope you enjoyed that
[Music]
we're doing colors now
there's too many lines here that
obstruct
what i'm trying to do
[Music]
ah cool
sleeping oh good night
and i probably won't finish today but
i'll finish one day and i'll send you
the completed piece
oopsy
[Music]
[\h__\h]
no that's okay
i'll fix it i'll fix this too
we'll fix all of this
i like the selection tool from paint
tool side because
it shows everything you selected in like
a blue color
um and that's like way easier to see
what you selected than what i just did i
think you guys were also
not able to see well what i selected
you know what i mean
uh huh
no i mean i i like it's not like i don't
care
um but
yeah i mean
i don't know i'm not i'm not some kind
of book offer so
but i think i'm still one of the people
in her life english or in her life
overall
that plays
more
uh with
my lord than others do
like
kfp is part of my lore
and the whole reviving i did all those
re-debuts that was basically lure
that was making use of my lure i do make
use of it
i would say
actually pretty often hmm
yes
[Music]
and like for example even things like
that minecraft um
a sports festival
i made lore
a a i made a
choice because of my lord to be the the
one that's flying
the the darts game
the birdman darts
[Music]
that was because i i am phoenix so i am
bird
[Music]
i think i got everything
ahmed does emma use her laura a lot
these days
i couldn't say i mean i watch her but
like um i guess
maybe she does
oh sure
time travel
yeah okay okay true
she does
jork around with that a lot
[Music]
i fill those eyes so they don't look so
creepy anymore
uh where was the locking this one was
the logging
okay for now we'll just keep it like
this
oh yeah you know
yeah you know he doesn't use her lore at
all
cali does too though like she
i mean at least i feel like she used to
use it more and also she implements it
into her songs a lot
um the whole reaper theme
is used a lot in her songs
um
it's very edgy so it makes sense like
using the whole reaping thing i think is
way more cool and edgy and makes sense
in a song than using like the kfp theme
like i'm a fast food worker
i make burgers for you
do you want pickles on it or not
i personally don't like them
but when i wake up
i don't wanna go to work
so you work for me
even if it hurts
yeah yeah you work at kfb for me
you work at kfb
always every day
[Music]
that's that's the song that's the song
see it doesn't work quite so well
yeah being a reaper is just cooler
what a banger shabby bang
[Music]
thank you thank you
since you encouraged backseating and
some games you played was backseated by
chat have you considered doing a stream
where the chat only plays it you mean
where the chat controls what i do
i mean i don't i don't think i could
like do it like like properly like you
know i saw that one stream before where
in a twitch
um
stream they just they play pokemon or so
and you don't get anywhere
it sounds fun but i wouldn't know how to
technically set that up
um maybe in like a simplified version
it sounds like it could be fun yeah
yellow
raincoat
we are living in the yellow submarine
yellow submarine yellow submarine
you're living in the yellow submarine
hey yeah what's up maureen hey yo what's
up marine hey
i forgot the strand of hair there
[Music]
okay let's see
right that needs a lot of coding the one
that that um that emma did
for her
uh outfit reveal before i always
wondered
like in there were some times when i was
like did she actually really like is
this is this like
being
actually controlled by the chat
she
she i feel like
it probably wasn't but she had me fooled
every now and then
i was like
what how like because sometimes it
didn't make sense for me
if she was controlling it then why would
she
like
make the chat waste so much time on
certain things she genuinely seemed
pissed off in some moments
like some moments she really seemed to
feel like she wanted to move on but the
chat wouldn't let her but i guess she
maybe just like even though she was
controlling it maybe she was just acting
along you know with what the chat said
because that's what the chat was doing
even though she had control over it
maybe maybe it was just that
she was just trying to stay accurate
to
the chat's
decisions
i don't know but she probably
ah
yeah
something like that would be really cute
and fun but then again like
see when i see stuff like that i also
don't want to flat out uh copy it
because like
that's like her
her thing so i want to come up with my
own ideas
you know
always better to come up with your own
ideas
i mean it's not always possible because
pretty much everything has been done
before
you can't always reinvent yourself
a million times over
unfortunately it's not that easy anymore
um i mean yeah i guess that wasn't so
original to begin with anyway because
other people did it before yes yes but
still like in within home alive it was
the first
i think but then whole life it was still
original
and and that's at least something
i also want to do things
with our original women whole life
that's that's that's a certain
level that we can
try to reach
[Music]
okay i think we've got it
you know when i think of yellow
raincoats i always think of
bakamunogatari as kampalu
always
actually gonna fill up the background
here with hair as well i think
that
like this
it's really
cool to be able to use this you really
see my
hand movements over the tablet way more
clearly
think of inna i told eno that like you
know when she put out that song uh that
music video that that i
have to think of [\h__\h] monogatari
i told her
it's like it totally gets me
i can't think of anything else when i
see a yellow raincoat
which color do we want to have that be i
mean or uh
yellow is
this bright yellow is a bit tough to
work with maybe just white is okay yeah
pink white is okay
i'll leave this white but
i have to add another layer
again
right and these clouds are of course
gonna be white too
um these uh
straps things should we keep them white
as well
white works well i think so too
make them could make them blow um
i wanted to match with the rest of the
raincoat though so if i made that one i
feel like
um
it could be white too
red like the original
oh
she does have oh yeah yeah yeah we can
do that we can do that red is i guess
it's okay yeah
okay
i can't see your job
what
oh i'm um eraser
i'm gonna make this red yeah that works
i think
oops
wrong brush this
is
[Music]
so good to see kiara drawing really
thank you
i think ina is not streaming today is
she so i'm like for all the taku-dachis
who want to see someone draw maybe
maybe i'm like i can make up for it with
my shitty art yay
yeah she's uh
she's not feeling well is she
i hope she feels better soon
wasn't she sick didn't she get sick
it happens i want to start coloring let
me start coloring i will color the skin
she has a very um pinkish skin tone
pinkish
shading as well
[Music]
ah but i don't know these brushes
i'll just brush i just use this one
i'll just use what i can get
rough roughly
uh
shading first
and then a bit more detailed
meanwhile i'll look for
i'll look for another question um
which council member would you face off
with an arm wrestling match no no no one
but maybe the weakest one because i i i
have absolutely no muscles
so who's weak in counsel mummy seems
like
she could be weak but then also
surprisingly strong
[Music]
who's weak
bane no no no babe would would kill me
drama maybe yeah fona
could be
a match but i would probably steal those
i would probably steal those
um what are we gonna do here
i don't want to emphasize the nose
that much
for only 60 years old you can take a
crony for sure
no
i don't believe it until i see her
um
yeah
fauna lifts fauna works ah
phone works out
crony is too cool for the gym
yeah why would she have to improve her
body when she's perfect right
right why why try improving your body
when there's nothing to improve to begin
with
that's probably the logic
that she goes
by fair point
what is there to improve
fauna would be like hey granny wanna go
to the gym cronie would be like huh
what what is there to improve with my
body are you saying there's something
wrong with my body that's impossible
that is impossible
blasphemy
[Music]
no i don't like that
i want to emphasize it
but i think in general like besides
maybe
i don't know someone who really really
actively works out maybe bae i think
besides that most of us are just weak as
[\h__\h] because all we do is stay at home
and stream all day
let's be realistic here
so probably no need to be so scared
for me
[Music]
hmm
i'm getting tired [\h__\h]
four hours
bay can solo all in
you get the ring fit regularly
are you
what's wrong with you why are you
why are you saying such nonsense
are you where are you drunk are you
aware of what you're saying
are you okay are you drunk or you know
who's streaming you're watching
i think you lost lost child you are
[Music]
is
question
do you like olives no
you have a plan from kelly or i'ma go to
your place if you have consumers no i'm
not sharing and yes i have a plan
i'm looking into doing a daniel kiana
cosplay soon what are the kiada concept
designs you would like to see being
cosplayed
oh
i
i remember that wear probably the most
of this casual outfit that i'm wearing
right now out of all my outfits and
i understand it's probably the easiest
to recreate
[Music]
actually like i don't really expect
people
to do the kimono or even the empress i
mean that person is manageable i think
but the kimono is like really really
tough i think so don't worry about it
but what would be cool is yes sparks
cosplay i don't think i've seen those
sparks cosplay before but that's because
it was just you know
it's nothing too official it's not a
real outfit it's just a music video
outfit but it would be pretty cool to
see that
and sparks i think is also
not too difficult to recreate the outfit
[Music]
yeah
but i'm always very happy to see
you know
see cosplays
of my
uh
myself yeah
very very happy to see that
because you're basically
a walking advertisement for me as well
i hope you go to a convention
um with you know a cosplay of me
it's like you're not putting a kfp
advertisement on a truck
but trucks can speak you know having
a human advertisement is even better
because you can you can tell people when
they ask like oh what are you cosplaying
you can actually answer them
and then get them into
into kfp get them hooked
[Music]
i want to do the eyes actually i'm not
done with the skin but i want to do the
eyes because they look so creepy and
lifeless to me
so she has kind of like a pink highlight
at the bottom
and she has really um
psycho eyes if you look at them
they look a little bit psycho
um
that's that's just the
the art style so i'm not gonna
100 recreate that
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
i don't know the rest of the story
uh-huh
[Music]
a love their art for eyes especially
looks best in your cali yard what
what
their cali art
who's cali art
my cali aren't
like
or this artists kellyard when did this
artist uh kobo's mama drought drew kelly
am i coming they they probably meant my
idea why you're saying date
as if as if you're not i
sounded like you're talking about
someone else
it's probably about me you can't stop
thinking about me anyway can you of
course about me
yeah i love you too
although i would love i would love to
see uh kobo's
mama
draw some other whole life mentors
it would surely look interesting i
genuinely want to see more whole life
mamas draw other
whole life members but they're probably
all very busy
so
yeah understand the bullet they don't
really have the time
[Music]
see i i don't need to
mimic the original art style because i'm
good at making the eyes looking psycho
on my own without even trying
[Music]
how are we gonna
how are we gonna draw this i don't know
how do i want these eyes to look like
[Music]
can i
can i change this i am to
multiply
oh
hmm
thank you for the membership welcome
papa already drew inna during garlic
fungus you mean papa
uh i don't remember him drawing enough
but maybe he did yeah but he definitely
participated in the garden phone call up
yup yup yup
oh maybe i should
invite all kinds of mamas
to garlic
because i did an artist edition but
maybe i should do like a mama edition
know what i mean
she looks weird
hmm
i would be too nervous now
don't don't even don't even get your
hopes up i'm not doing it i would be too
nervous
uh what color is that like a coral
coral color
almost like a skin color
[Music]
cute oh cute
and right now she looks like a dragon
ball character to me
i don't know why
but
isn't there a dragon ball character that
looks similar
yeah buma bummer yes yes yes
but it's probably just just the blue
hair
and that's it
that's all there is to that
and i don't even watch dragon ball by
the way don't don't don't don't
misunderstand
i really
have absolutely zero interest
in dragon ball
zero maybe below zero
to make it very clear
[Music]
no
no [\h__\h] way that i'm doing a watch
along
it's it has a million episodes too like
how do you do a watch along of that
ah you guys
i spoil you too much
i just spoil you too much
[Music]
oh dear
first and favorite whole life member
thank you first and favorite
you didn't stray
away and find other girls that you like
more thank you
that's good to hear
means i've got everything under control
[Music]
okay now she's immediately gonna look
way more alive because i am going to add
highlights in the eyes
like i'm like a makeup artist right now
what i just said sounded like
things that makeup artists say
[Music]
and now i'm gonna choose this color from
my naked palette
i absolutely love this color so much
because it really makes my eyes pop and
brings out
that
purple color in it so much
[Music]
yeah that's absolutely divine
yes
look how cute she suddenly looks
incredible that is just the power of
this palette
yeah i really don't like the palette
they brought out before that but this
one is just chef's kiss
wait what
so fetch
talking about makeup palettes you know
absolutely nothing oh my god it's so
basic
oh basic
ew like get away from me
okay beautiful
that's beautiful hello girl
that's just another thing
you stop making
do you stop stopping
you stop you should stop to try to stop
you should stop to try to making stop
you should stop trying to stop
fetch from
happening
do we have an understanding
[Music]
i don't like this brush
shading is like
it's like therapeutic to me
it's my favorite part
[Music]
how could he not be happy
my
my drawing tablet is on a on one of
those arms those floaty arms
and it's shaking like it's not because
it's not shaking because it's unstable
but it's just
bouncy
so bouncy man i don't know if i if i
dislike it if it's bothering me
i guess it's okay
let's answer a question
[Music]
uh
not sure if i can answer that
[Music]
hey boss do you think you can mock us
italians imitating our accent incredible
i can't believe you can sleep knowing
that there are some employees
suffering from your jokes
the usual room is one thing but this is
too monstrous perfect keep doing this
hope you're doing banana and most
importantly i'll be dancing
are you good
are you okay
i'm sorry for hurting your
um your spaghetti feelings okay
[Music]
i get a uk fan here
remember for just over six months when i
realized you were my one and only ocean
i've been watching your content since
debut
all right since debut book member for
just over six months ah
ah so you were here from the beginning
but six months ago you decided
i am your one and only oh [\h__\h] that took
you some time to decide man
why did it take you so long what
happened
what's with all the time before that
huh
here's a simple uk food question for you
have you ever had or would you like to
try a full english breakfast and or a
proper sunday roast dinner
full english breakfast you mean like
with beans and stuff
wait what's what's full what what else
is in the
full
english breakfast
oh dear
no
i don't think i've had all of that at
once before
[Music]
that is toast
uh fried egg beans sausage champignons
bacon and ketchup
maybe
maybe some some of them have potatoes
um thingies
why does every i will never be able to
eat a full english breakfast if every
single one of them comes with mushrooms
i mean all the other stuff
i think i would be fine with although i
don't know what black pudding is what
what the [\h__\h] is black pudding
wait that's blood pudding
it says black pudding here
what is that
blood sausage
oh i think i've
i think i've had it before
yeah the only real problem would be the
the mushrooms
because i hate mushrooms with my
full passion
what's a sunday roast dinner sunday
roast dinner
oh
that looks yummy it looks normal like a
normal food that people can eat
oh that looks good
it looks like
um one of those things that
are served in like like cartoons like
family guy you know how they always they
always eat
the same [\h__\h] it's always some kind of
roast with mashed potatoes and gravy and
so on
it's like the the one thing they can
draw for dinner is
that have you noticed
[Music]
you haven't they always eat that always
always the same
it's food a
unrealistic
but it's not as um it doesn't piss me
off as at all and what pisses me off is
that for example in in big bang theory
and other similar shows
there are so many scenes where they're
where they are supposedly eating
something they're often talking while
they're eating in a group
but they never actually eat like they
they they poke their food so much with
the fork and it triggers me so hard they
like pick up some uh some food with
their fork like only a tiny bit while
someone else is talking and then and
then they're supposed to talk so they
put it down on the table again
they were about to take a bite but
they're they never take a bite they
never take a bite
and i keep on looking at their food and
it triggers me i cannot pay attention to
anything but the phone like why are you
not eating that yummy looking delicious
food huh i mean of course you got to do
retakes and all of that and that's you
would then you would be eating too much
you know what the solution we have for
that
become a better actor
stop doing retakes just act perfectly
and then you can actually eat the food
once and not get fat
roasted no just kidding
[Laughter]
if there were no retakes to do then you
would be able to eat and it wouldn't go
you could eat it in one go
imagine just just imagine
[Music]
yeah but i guess
i guess it's too much to ask
it's just too much to ask
it triggers me so hard
oh the eyes are looking good i like it
[Music]
look
i gave it some softness
with adding some blue in the middle and
some skin tone on the sides
this bothered me too but i never
realized it because it was because of
retakes well i think it's partially that
and the food gets cold and if they
actually eat then
for retakes the food will get less and
less and they don't have endless amounts
of food
um
yeah
and it probably is cold
all the time when they when they're
shooting it's probably cold
yeah but like take at least just like um
take a bite please and then when and in
the very one out of hundred times when
they do take a bite it's such a tiny
itty-bitty tiny weezy bite
no one not even i
take it
tiny weensy pizza bites like that
yeah
i i i
it looks
looks like you know when this when this
um
[Music]
is it let's say this huh
this is the fork
perfect fork
and then what they actually put in their
mouth
is this
such a tiny piece who eats like that who
eats like that
maybe they're
of course they're hungry it's like
scenes where they are literally coming
like to their break from university into
the break room in the cafeteria
and they have this whole meal
that they're planning to eat and they
don't eat a single bite and sometimes oh
what what's even worse
is like in some scenes not only big bang
favorite but only another shows and also
other shows too when when when when in
some scenes they start eating
and then i have some fight or something
else to do or something or not even a
fight but just like the lady feels
insulted or whatever whatever and then
after
after eating for two minutes
they leave or when one one of them
leaves
but there's so much food and you just
sat down and then
often it's because the other person
started this this difficult talk that
they knew
might result in a fight
now why don't you keep that talk for
the end of the dinner why do you have to
bring it out at the very beginning of
the dinner
[Music]
risking that you will fight immediately
and then all the food goes to waste
why would you why would you start that
talk in the beginning
stupid
it's always like that
stupid tv shows absolutely stupid
television
[Music]
foreign my immersion is broken if you go
to lunch break and you don't actually
eat your food this has something to do
with immersion too right yeah
anyway back to the art
[Music]
i feel like
refreshed
letting out that frustration
beautiful
movie good but they didn't eat so it was
[\h__\h]
exactly
[Music]
she has pretty
pink lips did you notice she has like
cute pinkish lips
don't look too much though
i
prohibit you from looking too much
she needs a blush blush blush blush
mini blush
and then we
soften it out
[Music]
did you catch a fever
you look so red
now just when i look at you
i feel flustered because you're so
beautiful mommy
oh kobuton
you're charming a little
umbrella fountain
see it's so charming
stop being so charming will ya
what do you mean what do you mean it's
not a fanfiction it's reality
she said it to me today
somewhere
behind the scenes
[Music]
gosh next question
uh
i don't know why people ask me this kind
of questions i know i talk a lot about
this and that but it's not like i can
give any actual real answer to this um
since your position is in hollow life in
whole life is quite unique only one from
europe do you think will ever get merch
ship from europe
this is what i think i can't i don't
know probably not
[Music]
but maybe from america i don't know if
anything if anything it would be america
[Music]
oh when you look into
2023 what do you see for her life
i don't know it's so difficult to
try to
see where it's headed because
v tubing is just still so
so new
um
so fresh
and there's not many like examples that
you can go by
right
uh we need to ask him
[Music]
she didn't say anything about 2023
specifically but
i wonder
[Music]
i mean
i think about that too you know like
how how her life will hold up in the
next
couple years
[Music]
i'll think about it too but i don't have
the answer tell me when you know
[Music]
organizing collab seems like a lot of
work what challenges arise that people
might not consider when collabs happen
uh that other members
um
don't answer
and so you call yourself
oh my oh no
you call yourself a hell of a project
fan huh surely you aren't a fake fan
aren't you answer these trivia questions
name a hello project member who is
left-handed what elder club member is
known as aya
what elder club member
what's an elder club member
[Music]
uh some hp members used to be called egg
why is that oh
egg
what egg egg is just uh there were hello
project eggs that's where um
that's where
brady's kobu and kyoto came from
uh
oh you mean like og members
oh
it's even part of
like the chanting of one of your songs
and so yeah egg is like a
like a train trainee group
what date did risako sagaya graduate
i don't know i don't remember the date
who is the shortest member of betty's
cover
ah
wait momochi or sakety but
[Music]
i think yeah very tallest should be sudo
masa
and then then it should be probably not
so yucky me but miyabi and then should
be probably recycle surya
and then probably sakety and then
probably momochi
i wonder if i'm correct should be it
should be somewhere around that
i do know some of this i don't know an
hp member who's left-handed right now
but i answered all the other questions
except the
graduation date
why would i why would i want to keep
that in my
in my memory huh
[Music]
wow
actually now i'm curious is momochi or
shorter very scoop i think it's momoji
ah that might be close a close call ah
no socketing is a little bit smaller
i think
it depends on the shoes what shoes are
they wearing
no sake is smaller than momoty but
momochi is the second smallest yeah
i i knew it i had like a doubt in my
mind when i said
although it depends it depends on when
there were certain times because they
started when they were like nine years
older so there were certain times where
momochi was smaller probably something
to do with growth spurts
like in the picture for for um genghis
khan momochi looks smaller
yeah then other times
may have been someone else's small
in the picture for um
another song they almost they
pretty much look the same height except
maybe that two centimeters are so
different
i don't
i don't talk
who is left-handed i wonder now
elder club sounds like grandma club or
something call them oh geez that hurts
elder club
call them oh geez or or senpai club or s
maybe senior club but el elder cl no
senior club is bad too
elder club
yeah imagine coco senpai being part of
the elder club
[Music]
did i pass the quiz at least partially i
think i did you can't tell me anyway
if that i'm a fake fan or so i've been
to several
concerts of hello project
i've spent a lot of time and money on
them
i love them they're my babies okay and i
know a lot of their dances
and and and surprisingly i know a lot of
the names of the hello project members
not only the group that i like but
others as well
mm-hmm
i followed them for a long time and i
even watched the dvds of them going like
on a vacation trip to
hawaii or wherever
[Music]
i even watched the making offs of the
photo books from them like
you know they have some idol photo books
and i watched
i even watched them making off
because
because they're so cute
especially especially
[Music]
and i'm using clipping studio it's
written at the top of the window
clip studio playing pro
why don't you do more appearance action
on streams and their collabs that don't
have a game involved with them
because
why do there's one of them when i can do
both at the same time i do that while i
while i play games
[Music]
uh huh
um
[Laughter]
hey kiara i went to austria recently and
i was disappointed to learn that your
popular catchphrase and in german we say
auf wiedersehen is not authentic at all
everyone always says farewell with ciao
my question now that the truth is out
there will you reimburse the viewers the
authentic german farewell i estimate
there should be 500 and the germans say
we say ciao
keep up the good work
sayonara
[Laughter]
what a punchline who wrote this
who wrote this
you don't even use ciao yourself at the
end you just say sayonara
who the [\h__\h] wrote this
i have a feeling i i i i know some some
people who could write this like it
feels like
a familiar style
well
no
we definitely say avidas in
um in german
but uh ciao we used to but not quite the
the we wouldn't even write it the the
way that italians do it
like c-i-a-o
but we would write it t
s-c-h-a-u
so it's like a german version of it that
became like germanized you know
so yeah
yeah i want to do the hair now i'm still
not 100 happy with the skin but it's
okay i'm gonna start the hair but we're
not gonna finish it probably i need to
i need to
read super chat it's already been almost
five hours
yeah and we say choose
or juicy
or
[Music]
no don't say
and in german we say
um
no
that was not what i was trying to say
just just leave me alone let me know
leave me alone i'm pressuring me
i feel pressured
ah this is a nut this this could be nice
oh yeah i like that that's okay
i can work with that
go back to drawing your daughter yes
okay
raja
so
auf wiedersehen is kind of polite yeah
um
yeah
yeah yeah yeah and the thing is like
even when you come to austria as a as a
tourist
um unless you're in like a
proper restaurant like a like a more
um
not so homely but more elegant
restaurant
or if you're in a hotel or so then
they're probably gonna say auf
wiedersehen or something similar
but if you're um
[Music]
just like talking to like
like normal austrians asking for
directions or something like that
they're probably just gonna say
um ciao or or say in english bye bye
because you're a tourist
so you may have not gotten the accurate
experience
hmm
what would i say
i actually i would probably also say
ciao a lot
i probably say juice and ciao
the most are so many ways to say goodbye
probably in every language
yeah
i'm just gonna roughly
roughly shade now because she has so
much
hair holy [\h__\h] this part is going to be
white later so i don't really have to
shade that now
roughly but that's
[Music]
ends don't shout peace as goodbye
yeah whoever just complained to me about
you know
austrians not using advertising you can
go to cali's stream and complain to her
about people not actually saying peace
aggressively when saying goodbye to
someone
okay
pick a fight with her
no they don't
adding some green tones for whatever
reason
oh my god what am i gonna eat for dinner
today
i have nothing i think
i've got nothing
wait do i have something i have nothing
i mean that's a lie i can warm up
something and i still have cut pull up
but i don't want to cook after such a
long stream you know what i mean it will
be like probably now it's 9 00 p.m
i'll end the stream probably and
i'll do some speed reading so maybe
maybe in two hours or two and a half
hours
i want something warm something good
something that tastes
that tastes like my mom cooked it
why is there no restaurant that cooks
like my mom cooks hmm
that's homely
homely taste
or simply a pizza
i really like like like properly
like pizza that is properly
made like italian pizza but this looks
so
when you order food here there's so much
[\h__\h] pizza like the ratio is
too unbalanced
like out of 10 pizzas
eight of them
eight of them are gonna be
just
so basic
and two of them might be good
somewhat italian resembling pizza
no
yeah i think probably america has the
same problem if not if not voice
um but you guys have something
uh
awesome that we'd like to call here
american pizza
the thick
the thick pizza a pizza with the really
fat
uh
base
maybe that's is that chicago style pizza
deep dish you call that deep dish i
don't know we just call it american
pizza here
i don't know what's deep dish deep dish
is from chicago is that the same thing
deep dish pizza
ah no that's not what i'm uh met but
that's also [\h__\h] awesome i never had
that before
it looks like a pie it looks like a cake
like a pie
pie
and now when i think of american pizza
when i say that um
i mean
just a thicker
a thicker thingy yeah
oh my god
that reminds me of japanese pizza and
japanese pizza is crazy and expensive
crazy expensive
[Music]
one japanese pizza so expensive man
i would
legit never order pizza in japan
because it was so freaking crazy which
is ironic because if you go to a
restaurant in japan
um
that serves pizza
like saizalia or whatever
you can get it really cheap
or not only centeria but also a normal
italian restaurant in japan they sell
normal normal price pizza but but um
[Music]
the the only the companies
that deliver pizzas sell it insanely
expensive
and then it's still like really small
size too
like for me it's enough but
what you get
for
for one small size pizza and when i say
small it's not even this small that you
get in in america
but really small
is like i don't know
25 to 35
bucks for one small tiny pizza
how do they
what is their excuse how do they justify
that
huh
um
[Music]
that's pizza for one person but even you
guys would probably not even be full
from that one person pizza
the only good thing about it is that
they have really creative pizzas like
interesting pizzas that you wouldn't see
overseas like
they love cheesy pizzas
they love to add all kinds of crazy
things though
also they love mayonnaise
[Music]
oh
it's gonna take a million years
[Music]
i'm hungry i'm so hungry
i'm so hungry okay i think i'm stopping
here now
and we'll do the rest eventually either
in a stream or privately
um because i i need to raise your chest
and then eat
hungry
[Music]
oh um
um i might
i might um make a
sad i have bread i have bread i might
make a sandwich
and i need to go to the idol meeting
yeah so um that's my little coco chan
doesn't look like cobra at all [\h__\h]
after after i add those white parts in
her hair then then it would look more
like her hopefully also
i'm gonna probably fix some things
off-screen like her eyes her eye shape
kind of bothers me uh right now because
one looks different than the
other but yeah for now for now for now
this is okay
thank you everybody for um
watching this and i wonder how many
questions i didn't answer
um
maybe i'll look into them tomorrow
during the yakuza stream as well if we
need something to talk about
okay
thank you everybody for sending in
questions in marshmallow and for
watching the stream watching me draw
thank you very much and it was really
cool to test this out thank you eden
excel for making this so cool so cool
you got the necklace
don't leave though if you want to stay
you're welcome to stay because we're
going to read super chats and chill
okay
so in german we say
see you later alligator uh
just kind of go into an intermission
uh might take a few minutes because i'm
gonna make a sandwich too
okay
thank you see you in a little bit
no no no no no yes yes yes yes
[Music]
do
um
yeah
bgm name crispy fry fry party
with k crispy
it's um
from
an instrumental
only
myth
ep
or so
that we put out a long time ago
[Music]
clear now it's like a soundtrack
i knew this would happen
so weird
i'm back and i'm eating
my sandwich thingy
i mean i wouldn't quite call it a
sandwich it's just bread with some
um
yeah
sliced thin
sausage thing underneath in between and
some tomatoes
but i just need something
to put
into my mouth to make my my hunger go
away
oh
that's a sandwich
in german
we call
um things only a sandwich really when it
has like
[Music]
like
more things in it
next salad
um
and onions or whatever i don't know
may still not
no i'm not a fan of ramstein
do i look like a fan of ramstein to you
do i come across as a fan of ramstein
singing all those j-pop songs and doing
cute pop songs in my karaoke
[Music]
hmm
i'm not judging a book by its cover i've
heard that einstein's music before
i don't like the whole genre to begin
with the whole genre is nothing for me
i may know kiara may not like samsung
but i love canada thank you yeah no
problem with people who like
einstein
but yeah not my thing
but music is something that where tastes
really um
grow in different ways
[Music]
what's the most intense music you do
like hmm
intense
edm
can sometimes be intense
oh
no euro beats yeah euro beat is probably
the most intense
because that gets um
that gets kind of yeah that's intense
that's
probably something but i mean i don't
i don't randomly listen to eurobeat uh
sometime in the middle of my day
i would i would listen to it sometimes
maybe as a joke
um
maybe when i'm in control of the music
it on a car ride
i wouldn't mind turning on some eurobeat
then
oh yeah when i go pick up an oreo shake
from burger king
[Music]
one of the tomatoes fell out of my
sandwich
i hate that
um
super chats
i think
from
karaoke
um
[Music]
yeah that was a great kind of okay
doubt i can see the rebroadcast why
did you watch the original
there's the rebroadcast is going to be
in a time zone
that's sea friendly
the previous one was for
europe and north america and so on
that was something personal that i had
to get done
[Music]
oh
hmm
sorry i looked at something and
misunderstood it
okay yeah
yeah
don't call me polo
no
you could only read after yakuza
um
should i order food for later
i love you singing thank you
i'm glad you like it
should i i mean
um
[Music]
i have some
some things
like
frozen in my freezer
a few a few left overs
but i that's either that's either bone
is or
curry
if
i if i even have curry left over and i'm
not really feeling like bolognese i'm
not so sure
noggy money non-kids no kids
nuggets
noggies
thank you for the nuggets
i'm not gonna get nuggets probably
though because um
those only like um yeah
that was only a little it tastes like
[Music]
i can't talk
should i get an air fryer i still i
still haven't pushed order yet on amazon
but it's in my cart
shouldn't i buy
dana it yes
reyna did say yes
where
where was where did i order that
good pizza
a while ago
where did i order that
good
guten pizza
do you have any
any emails
from
pizza
i can't find it
that was a good guten pizza
first write down free recipe oh i'm sure
i would be able to get more than just
free recipes that i would use for air
fryer
uh
potato fries
roasted chicken
fried chicken
schnitzel
um
i'm sure there's more that i just can't
think of right now
i mean there's much there's so much you
can do
hamburger
many things that you can do with that
but there's also so many things that you
maybe wouldn't think of first but that
are totally possible as well
am i crazy or did i even see people bake
bread in
air fryers
basically you can bake everything that
you can bake in an oven right and also
uh fry everything that you would fry in
a lot of
oil or pizza roast
[Music]
no no i just said i didn't get it yet um
i won two but
i already have
so many other things in my kitchen like
um
i have
two different toasters
i have a water cooker i have a rice
cooker i have a slow cooker i have a
smoothie mixer
um i have a cook what do you call it the
kitchen machine
um
and probably one or two more things
so why two toasters because one is like
a you know the toast where you put the
toast
in the two slits on the top and the
other one is the the one where you can
make the toast sandwich thingy you need
both
you need both can a waffle machine no i
can make waffles with my with one of my
toasters because i have the waffle
thingies as well although i don't really
use it
um but in theory i could use that for
that but i i
those two toasters i hundred percent do
need because i need
both
ways of toasts toasted
sometimes yeah it's like a like a panini
pretty i guess like a sandwich man can
you yeah basically
both is 100 necessary
yeah like a press exactly
and i i got some extra
shapes thingies for like donuts and
waffles
and
uh
pancakes i think too which i don't use
any of them but that's okay
now sorry for the wait let me just um go
through
uh something quickly i wanna i think i
wanna order food
cause like it's gonna get late
and i better order it now
oh that's where the good pizza was
the pizza was so good last time where i
ordered it but they didn't forget
the one topping that i added the one
tapping
how could you forget but it was on the
bill
so i was gonna be angry but i'm gonna
give them one more chance
um
[Music]
then i am okay if it's just margarita or
something simple but
yeah
usually i love me some tuna some tuna
and some some corn the corn is always
the best maybe i make some corn pizza
do you have corn pizza
and where is the pizza no
here's the pizza
what the [\h__\h] does that mean
i need to google what is written in here
the [\h__\h] is that
is it olives no
okay
[Music]
i take this
i think pizza
and we've uh with the corn with the corn
and do we want uh
normally i'm already full after uh five
pieces of the pizza or four pieces of
the pizza
but i feel a little bit bad when i order
food and only order one thing
so sometimes just because i feel bad i
order the more food
[Music]
wait i don't think they have anything i
want
oh my god maybe i order a drink okay
but the drinks is so expensive mama mia
mamma mia how about a salad
oh [\h__\h] this i only ordered the pizza
but i'm paying extra when i do these
just to get to the minimum
come on mia
i'm not gonna pay extra and get nothing
uh mama miami
but last time i ordered i did not like
it i only liked the pizza
oh mama mia what do i do
my mama mia
no mama
mia it's a dilemma i will order a drink
let's go
okay much better now i'm getting
something for my money
am i of legal drinking age
i ordered ice tea
but yes i am i'm a phoenix
huh
why are you asking me this mamma mia
i guess it's a compliment
did i order long island no i don't think
so
how how late can they or descended oh
let's go with very late
[Music]
uh
today's friday
[Music]
yes
okay
[Music]
i think that should be okay
old show kendra are you calling me old
joe
how old are you
gian mod
[Music]
probably younger
i'm waiting for your answer
i'm not here i'm unusual
oh you're right yeah but you can still
answer apparently you're chatting how
can you not answer the question then
how come you can't answer my question
but you can't write in the chat normally
it's not an excuse
it's
you don't need to reveal your age
don't feel pressured
we're gonna read super chats now
let's get it
started let's get super chat's red in
here and once again superchat's red and
huh
one call can't afford you anymore
because i don't want to go back to the
usual room it smells bad
that's your own stink
that's your own revolt
oh yes yes the super chats oh my god i
smell like
a good like shampoo smell right now
um
my my bathroom is weird like sometimes
the the bathtub will make like
sounds
nothing comes out of it but it
definitely smells but the thing is it
smells it doesn't smell bad but i know
it's not my own bathroom smell it's from
someone else's bathroom
and sometimes it's pretty [\h__\h] loud
and goes on for like
two to five minutes
yeah it freaks me out
mm-hmm
yeah the pipes the pipes
plumping issue i think because like i
shouldn't be i don't think i should be
hearing that so loud and
so long
and then my whole
apartment smells like that shampoo
whatever that person is using
it's like a bath ghost yeah
pipes are clogged in the apartment was
like you should mention to the owner
you mean
clogged because of not because of me but
someone else or like generally just the
pipes
is there something that's my fault
how do you unclog them
yeah at least it's a good smell i was i
was thinking so too like that's the only
reason why it's tolerable
sandwich line may be backing up
i think i'm not the only one with this
problem though in them
in this building
this is the buffalo i don't know just
oh no
i can't tell
volleyball is an apartment so it could
be just about anyone it could even be a
problem with the municipal online
i feel like they are kind of like a
little bit um
um
careless with some things here in
general
anyway
i'm scrolling by the way
[Music]
this still scrolling
i'm still scrolling um i think i'm
almost there maybe i'm there i'm there i
have arrived
okay
yeah i don't care that much it's okay
for me
mr casper stankish in the game of cretan
cushion not applicable
[Music]
she just said it again what did i say
what
but this one was written differently
[\h__\h] you
doing
the spanish ones keep on fooling me
[Applause]
[\h__\h] you
you are the night of spain golden
[Music]
uh doug joseph thank you for the red
super chat oh wait it's a rainbow
oh
you are the dancing empress young and
fetch only to wish less
dancing in praise feel the beard from
your bro
crowbar oh yeah
you can dance you can drive having the
time of your life oh
see that girl watch that cake digging
the dancing impress it doesn't fit so
well doug joseph
your tears are you turn them on
leave a burning and then you're gone
looking out for the 3d debut not just
any venue you're in the mood for dance
and when you get the chance
it goes on like that like before
thank you
oh really thank you samurai welcome wow
i feel flattered thank you
um and your dad joseph for the beautiful
rainbow that's one of my favorite
mamma mia songs
and maybe one of my favorite
old songs overall
mommy and abba songs
in general as
well thank you very much
thank you very much
rainbow kisses for you
did she mention me
i'm flattered
wrote pick two one three five donkey
shoe and i am a t
at least you stopped trying to fool me
but you could never fool me
i always saw right through you
the game okay
soon
[Music]
kiara alka time i want to do it more
often yeah i've been
not doing karaoke that often so want to
do it more often
thank you for renewing your membership
thank
you uh so i hope you guys join me
whenever i do karaoke again
and let's have more fun
together thank you tai chi
kicked out of applebee's
dominican kitchen mrs
[Music]
everyone's referencing
mamma mia
i love it i love it it's beautiful
thank you
for the pinky unity
you're like a fresh of rough air
wait what
how could i read it wrong it was
literally written correctly
why didn't i why did i read it wrong
[Music]
it took me a moment to realize even
what
it sounded so right doesn't it
nothing sounds wrong about that
[Laughter]
netting
[Music]
um there's some flash jets i think
why wha was i singing something that
was asking for flushing what happened
there
mata thank
[Music]
ah i did an idol meeting so early on wow
that's unlike me
i am
i'm
i'm new i i know
i know
[Music]
thanks for the pinky pinky for those
high notes show them how it's done
tenchu
what was i singing
but i enjoy
i enjoy singing high notes
so
yeah i'm not very good with like um what
do you call it like
um
we call it
ah
[Music]
what's the word
um
[Music]
no
no i don't mean any of that describing
uh what ariana grande does the whole
time
like um adding some random hoo-hoo
and stuff like that
um yeah i wish i was uh
good at that
because that can make a your ad-libs
that can make a song
a singer
sounds so so good
[Music]
sometimes sometimes i try and sometimes
it even works somewhat well but uh
those are still really really really
weak though like the the kind of ad-libs
that ariana grande does are like
[\h__\h] insane she goes like
wow
[Music]
like she goes up and down and up and
down the blue
[Music]
are you thinking what happened you
didn't send any message blue what's up
what's up blue
thank you though
thank you very much
ah
i wasn't yodeling
dave and duncan
i'm a criterial girl yes i am
looking for the top down cause she
wobble gobble gobble so cute thank you
someone made a video of me m turkey
a self-made m turkey video
and at that moment i was not even trying
to sound like a turkey i know it sounded
a little bit like a turkey but if i
tried to look at sound like a turkey i
could probably sound even more like a
turkey than i did at that moment
just want to say that i just want to say
that okay
just want to mention it
[Music]
prove it
no i will keep it for an m turkey video
um
looking for the top donkey soon
all right ghana thank you for the pinky
gokiana thank you for the support
i see you i see you cheering with those
light sticks ragana
don't forget to charge them until the
next concert okay
thank you very much
jazm thank you
come sanita
brandon thank you for the pinky yeah
singing has cured my depression
really
[Music]
you're so sweet
you're so sweet you deserve all the
happiness
for giving me so much happiness too
thank you
tiny delta dan kitchen for also on pinky
so many pinkies please excuse me i need
to get my jaw up from the floor
what was i singing
what was i singing i think i was singing
dance with somebody because the super
chats after that uh
or the song right before that hmm
thank you very much whatever it was
i apparently did it well uh holding up a
hero oh that was fun that was so
dramatic
[Music]
i don't i don't remember
i learned so many songs for
florida
okay it's really it takes a while to
learn songs um so well that you can
sing them
with no backup vocals properly in the
karaoke
um convincingly
not just
[Music]
just like looking but like properly
so
so these karaokes do take up some
preparation work
and time a lot of time
well it takes some time
thank you senior mcm
seat yes thank you thank you
thanks stream
by the way i think i'm planning
next week
korean
duolingo or what's the week after
i think it was next
week
no the week after that
like sometime between the 18th
and the
22nd
yeah korean duolingo i'm gonna give it
another chance but
just because there's nothing else that i
can use on stream um there's another app
that i requested uh
permission for
but
somehow
my
my requests usually don't get answers so
i'm not i don't have any high hopes for
it
[Music]
sorry i just
i just saw something on the discord
what was i talking about
oh well yeah for like a teaching collab
show sure we can do that but like i mean
like i also want to do a
stream where i
calmly study on my own with duolingo or
some other application there was this
like
i i found um
an app that i think someone recommended
to me on twitter
that
um
kind of combined
duolingo with
a kind of like shitty phone
rpg game
um
which would be shitty on its own of
course as a game but combined with um
combined with language study it's pretty
fun
because like you would be in a fight
with some monster and in order to do
damage you would have to solve like
questions like what does this mean
how do you say this how do you what do
you
what's milk in korean and then you say
uyu and then it does damage
endured shadow lingo
yeah it's not only for korean but other
for some
but also for some other languages and um
i wanted to do that one but i don't
think i'll get permission for anytime
soon so i'm just gonna go with duolingo
again and and
one day one day
buddy
buddy i see you
how how are you how are you doing are
you translating me what is that long
korean message are you translating me
are you translating me
buddy when are you going to make clips
again
40.
korean people are forgetting about my
existence
what is this
[Music]
ah he is translating me
i just looked it up
korean people gonna forget me
boring korean people gonna fall for
forget me
shouldn't die something
[Music]
we remember
but we had a momentum you know we had a
momentum
[Music]
we need more korean clippers
when are you making cups again though
are you ever gonna make clips again
[Music]
yeah
you're just saying that
i'm just saying that
still busy
[Music]
he's getting milk
i'll give you
[Music]
fro foreign
with somebody who loves me that's right
that's right let's go
or somebody who loves me i want to dance
with somebody who loves me
i want to dance with somebody who loves
me
count and dance with
that team
i want to feel the heat with the energy
[Music]
with somebody who loves me
i think i think nina team loves me
i love hair we have something special
with some nana who loves you
works well too oran's too strong it's so
sweet too because not only kfp really
likes the idea of orange but um
i i quite often seen energies fans
also being very um
excited and and eager about seeing more
of orange like sometimes when i eagle
search even when there's like no
particular reason sometimes i see like
ninja fans out of nowhere saying oh
i wish i wish there was more audience
uh stuff
and they so they like it too
they like the idea
of orange too
mm-hmm that's nice
not lou here's a kiss for you
nathan cotton thank you for the pinky we
love you tanja will you dance with us
i think i think we talked about this
before and i would love to dance with
you guys but you guys need to um you
know make a totem pole
stand on top of each other to be tall
enough to dance with me someone did a
fan art of me like that before
after my request
so if you can't manage that if you can
find some people to stack
on top of yourself or under yourself
then we could dance
i'm not a good dancer though when it
comes to like classic dance
um
yeah
how do people in the movies always do it
like they they don't always just do like
left right left right but they sometimes
they do like really these link
these spot fought through moves
like kind of like choreographies how do
they know
so unrealistic no way that people
actually
people who who don't dance regularly
with one another suddenly bust out these
these great
no i'm not talking about you know them
having body
doubles i just mean
you know suddenly
i don't know doing complex synchronized
dance
moves it's just it's not realistic i
think
sanji sean danke
andrew wright thank you for the pinky
you're two awesome full words kiara
andrew
don't be so charming
you're prince charming someone's gonna
take me away take you away from me well
i need you to stay in kfp but if you're
too sweet to charming then someone's
gonna take you away
andrew
thank you
doug joseph thank you rodrigo
dominican
superhuman blue dancer
if you use all the city to apply pitch
shifts with high quality stretching
it sounds way better
what
why would i do that for my color okay
why would i use all audacity
for my color okay
one thing i did notice when listening
back on the color okay um when i
was singing that uh black of peace song
uh which one was it
um
the one where i supposedly used like a
um an auto tune
in my headphones it sounded so strong
but then on stream it was like barely
noticeable
very interesting
[Music]
they mean for the instrument ah
for the instrumentals
not a hodo well but you know um wouldn't
that
need me to download the audio and then
put it into other city and then
save it and all that but the thing is
like it's within the
within the
the
the program
so
there's no download button for
the audio in the program i would have to
separately uh
recorded and i don't know that's just
too much trouble and i
uh
if the program already has a function
i'll go with it if it's just like one or
two
keys then it doesn't sound too bad but i
had like four keys higher for never
gonna give you up
and that did sound
tough
hamsa nida thank you
hokan dissonance duncan
you're making my mob dance and sing a
lot really
i love that what you i made your mom
dance and sing
i did sing a lot of oldies but goldens
yeah flaming pants dandruff and ginger
ranger the fourteen danish and rick's
nalandi dancing the waffle supreme
dancing unity
always fun to say your name thank you
for the red super chat
like a prayer a good christian song
thank you we're back to kiana being tap
left
that's okay right i love you so much
boss top left
should nip you tap right but
but like a prayer
which
it just it just has such a positive
sound to it like
i think maybe maybe because english is
not my uh mother tongue i normally when
i listen to songs
i even though i understand the meaning
and all that i don't
i don't think
deeply about what the meaning of the
song is even when i sing it myself
sometimes
so i often don't
get really obvious
themes and meanings
even when they're very obvious
i think with german that would happen
less
oh
no
it's just like
maybe i registered subconsciously but i
don't quite notice it
[Music]
thank you curvedit
love you thank you very much i mean i
didn't know what it was when i was a kid
a kid
you were a kitten you were a little
kitty cat oh
cute
i'm gonna adopt you
now you're
in not a kitten anymore but an oldie an
oldie cat grand grandpa cat i'm going to
adopt you anyway
savage
[Music]
oh that was a rainbow that was a
backflip rainbow
thank you savage i will always remember
kiara and kfb streaming was good today
too especially my heart will go on song
touches my heart i wish you all the best
the salt dispenser was returned safely
thank you for everything dear boss yeah
welcome back i don't know if i can ask
you one two one to last ask can you give
me a nickname for good luck to future
racer
even if i leave i want to keep the one
name kiana gave me
wait you just came back and you're
leaving again
what
[Music]
what does it mean are you becoming uh
are you taking up racing
with cars as your career
what
oh it's like this with savage always
comes and goes
you're all busy
i don't understand purpose of your name
though
a nickname for good luck
[Music]
or future racer
for your car or
for for for your car
a nickname for your
car
i don't get it
he gone confirmed on twitter what
no i just saw him in the chat
[Music]
he seems to like racing in cars a lot
what be careful though
[Music]
how about
phoenix
fire
for the car name
if it's a nickname for your car
that sounds cool
my car's name is phoenix fire
that sounds really cool
what a lame name get out of here
get out of here that's not lame
you're lame
firefox no phoenix fire
it was a mistake asking
vanva
you're so savage you know what savage
should give away his name and give it to
you you should change your name to
savage because you're so savage you're
such a socky one of
such a solgaki
you're you're always challenging me
always challenging me
you little [\h__\h]
oh
man oh man
i can't handle you man
i can't handle you
[Music]
just because of phoenix fire but what
can i do about it i'm a phoenix and i
i make fire
there's nothing to nebu about it it's
the truth
anyway savage here's a kiss i guess a
goodbye kiss
i'm not gonna cry anymore i've wasted
too many tears on you
bye-bye
see you later
yuri of laundry duncan not a little evil
pinky
thank you
thank you no text why
gotta make it sound more flashy but then
it's not a nickname if it's too long
blazing phoenix oh that sounds cool too
blazing phoenix
arigato
thanks for the pinky
i'm so i need to yawn
wherever i want to cozy up in my bed
so wrong quentin
wait i forgot anthony webb thank you for
the pinkie we love you pee wobble i love
you too
all of you all of you all live
all of you you're my olives
i don't like all this but i i love all
of you
thank you
talisman g1
naivety imagine you don't
[Music]
simon
pratt thank you for the pink key almost
a red one really great set list and
performance kiara please remember to be
as kind to yourself as you are to
everyone else
wow thank you that's sweet
i can be a [\h__\h] too though i'm not
always kind
oh no no i mean
usually usually even if i'm a little bit
of a [\h__\h] i mostly keep it to myself i
don't really let it out
even though i want to there's many
moments where
someone's a [\h__\h] to me
but i'm in a position where i can't be a
[\h__\h] back openly well i could be
i'm not even talking about haters i'm
talking about
people i know personally
who maybe feel like they need to turn
against me now
um
and i could totally
fight back in theory
but i haven't put in a position where i
need to be the bigger person
so i'm not gonna i'm not gonna
participate in that kind of
fight
but
sometimes i wish sometimes i wish i
could just be like
[\h__\h] you
you're not any better you did this and
this and this and you you call me out on
that you know what that's just [\h__\h]
hypocritical
so many times
hold me back yeah kfb you need to hold
me back like you know how you hold
people back when they start to fight on
the street
you hold me back on my arms
i need several people to hold me back of
course because i'm that strong
i'm just that strong
i need about
a hundred chicken to hold me back
because otherwise i will just break free
hold me back hold me back hold me back
calm down boss this isn't you you're
right you're right this isn't me thank
you thanks dude
hold the line hold the line
i want my young
[Music]
i'm just gonna ignore all the comments
implying that i only need one chicken to
hold me back or even just a feather i'm
just gonna ignore that
i am watching bee thank you
and crispy thank you spanking and thank
you for the red super chat
i may have been around when most of
these came out thanks so much for giving
us this gift i always love listening to
you sing and this is extra special big
caddo slapped through it so he must be a
fake fan
no that's okay my cats sleep through my
streams as well mostly
so
yeah it's just cats being cats in
reality they're
appreciating it and yeah even when they
sleep there
appreciating it better better than them
jumping around in front of the tv or
screen or whatever
and meowing loudly obnoxiously like that
would be disrespectful yeah right but
they don't do that because they're good
kitties and they respect kiwawa
takanashi kiwawa
the queen of cats
oh for the question that was asking me
who i would like
what country i would like to be
the
president or king to i would like to be
the the queen of cats
like daenerys is the queen of dragons i
would like to be the queen of cats
[Music]
real nostalgia from start to finish
amazing set list i knew my empress
i promised you tonight
i always deliver what i promise there is
no empty promises in my streams
because i like to
not give big promises to begin with
i just promise not so much i i only
promise in little tiny bites that i can
actually manage
[Music]
okay thank you very much tenjo you did
great hope you can have another one like
this in the future
love you i suggest checking the movie
grace i've seen it before i think i even
saw it in school together with the rest
of the class
i think they showed us a as part of like
one class
and um
thank you i'm sure we can have another
one like that in the future because
there's still so many oldies but goldies
that i want to sing
yeah there's so many that didn't make it
this time
yeah
let's do it again
yeah i don't feel like teaching so
here's the movie exactly but like no
one's gonna complain about that
no one's gonna complain
so we totally don't soon
[Music]
i had so much fun i died of laughter
towards the middle but then it got
better thank you
in the middle
i thought my humps was funny and all
that but that was not in the middle i
wonder what was so funny in the middle
ah rickroll maybe the rickroll
that was the first time i think i
properly
sang it from beginning to end
properly in the karaoke i think that was
the first time
yeah because i always complain about how
not having a proper
instrumental but thanks to that um
program i can i can
uh
make the key higher by myself yeah
the game mccree don kitchen fro fro
duncan maybelline two five zero one
donkey should thank you
flame there thank you for the red super
chat
man nostalgia hasn't hit me this hard in
a while loving nakada okay you're
killing it thank you
nostalgia always is a great feeling to
have
nostalgia is one of the best feelings
besides love
yeah
it just feels warm and good and i mean
it can be sad too but
mostly i think it's good yeah
thank you soon for enjoying my karaoke
naked chicken
joseph thank you
thank you for the red super chat
there's so many names that i just
i've read a million times until now
thank you guys so much for
always being here
glory to kfp and kiara i'm looking
forward to more great things from our
newly beautiful bad bird boss
what you mean new newly beautiful bad
bird boss is that not what i've always
been
of course all of her life is great but i
have only one let's see the concert was
great attention i'm proud to be a part
of kfb here is my bonus from my other
job
thank you
thank you thank you thank you for
reassuring me that i'm still your one
and only true or she
that always helps me thank you
love you
[Music]
thank you good employee indeed
glory to kvp
[Music]
big cat woke up he must be a black eyed
peas fan thanks again
ah
black guy piece made him wake up
you got good taste
that's when you need to start to party
for real like if you haven't parted
until then then black eyed peas
is your last chance to party
spanking on thank you here's a kiss for
your cat
but
don't you dare take it for yourself it's
for your cat okay okay
alex donkey shin kuru no danke shin the
game okay
santa amara spanx was
is amazing thank you
not as amazing as you
angel thank you for the red super chat
champions got me spending ooh
spending all your super chats on me
spending time on me
uh though the latter part is
improvised by me
but yeah um it was funny when i was
singing a song a lot of people sent
super chat saying she got me you
spending ooh
or not not my fault that i've got just
those sexy humps my lovely lady lumps in
the back and in the front
what can i do about it man don't blame
me
don't blame me
thanks angel
alex tankishan dragon sanchez and mr big
duncan slick order duncan hollow knight
duncan in differential vacation james
mcphee thank you also for the rain super
jet i see you're also spending on those
lovely lady lumps
respectfully of course
thank you james
for you thank you
doug joseph thank you there's a boss
thank you but i haven't donal jones
thank you soon right ghana thank you for
the pinky thanks for the phone call okay
it was great thank you two for listening
what would i be without you guys
listening in huh
it would be nothing
thank you
thank you for the rest of the chat
applauding thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you
i need a applause sound effect
to play whenever i feel like i deserve
it i would constantly use it after after
after every sentence
thank you cotton
sadly human donkey shin jim tracy thank
you
for the red super chat thanks for
singing dan joe always love your singing
i can get some beautiful dream tonight
oh
did you did you did you dream of me
ah
if you did if you did no need to hide it
no need to hide it
it's understandable
many kfp chickens
go through that you know
same
experience
[Music]
i also saw you still in the chat you're
also still awake
are you guys okay
you guys okay staying up so late be
careful okay
i mean i
what time is it there four a.m i mean i
also usually am up until 4am so
you know what you do you
i think 4am is totally manageable if if
you don't have to work the next morning
then what what the hell what the hell
4 30 5 30.
yeah that's what i thought i mean 5 30
if it's 5 30 then you should be sleeping
but we're almost done guys we're almost
done
at least you know the good thing about
me streaming so long is that
every time zone has a chance to say
hello you may not be able to watch the
full stream
but at least you can say hello every
once in a while
yeah and if you're crazy enough you're
gonna stay from beginning to end
if you're crazy enough or if you live in
europe
if you live in europe then
no need to be crazy
time for everybody to move to europe how
about that
single-handedly
[Music]
creating millions of millions of euros
in the european economy by making people
move here so it's more convenient to
watch my streams
sasuke
oh my god we're done with these on
aircraft almost yoshiki thank you for
the renzo chad
thank you mama you sing so many songs
for us i'm so happy that to enjoy whole
party and i'm glad you have so much fun
in this karaoke stream seeing you happy
make me happy too thank you so much i
love you love you too yoshiki thank you
thank you for watching the color again
i'm glad i have so many people who want
to party with me
thank you for listening in and spending
your time with me
and partying
um
oh you changed your name nice
thank you and
now somebody said
i don't need to read the yakuza ones you
think they're not that many wait no
let's read you meant
they are kind of a lot combine combined
with the ones from today
oh sheesh
i'll read more
i cannot give up here
ghost of sakurasic
for the pinky oh no what happened
hey tenshu i love the new menu oh
i was just wondering where to find the
ingredients for the app burger i don't
see any fish around here other than me
of course oh oh god
did i mention how much i love you quinoa
because i really do love you
i would never
never hurt you i love your new profile
picture
this is funny i love your new profile
well don't worry you're not the right
fish for the ah burger don't worry about
it
you're not in danger
it would not hurt you
so i don't need to hide anymore under
that ghost costume come back to life
tales of our eyes progress update
okay everybody yeah dude i said by the
end of april right okay again
joseph thank
managed to get my ticket to dokomi nice
oh my god well you're coming from norway
that's so cool
bring bring me bring me a soup in here
[Laughter]
for you souvenir from norway
no food though please unfortunately
anton m thank you looking for the top
no way i'll see what i can do all right
all right
thank joseph with a red super chat says
wonderful tanjo can i dedicate one of
your healing kisses to pat see oh thank
god i didn't give it away yet it sounds
like pepsi has an exhausting couple of
work days hang in there all your
hard-working chickens you are so sweet
dog joseph
you always try to give away your kisses
patsy
[Music]
it's like it's like you're you're a
charity person duck joseph
no you're like you're like robin hood
you take
and then you give it away
yes yes
beautiful
robin joseph doug hood
the game agreed on koreans are tasty
thank you for the red super chat hey
today is the first birthday i spent with
kfb as i started watching your last may
i want to thank you for all the fun
streams since then
last may
wow
i'm looking forward to the future
practice and endeavors of my aussie
question do you know the game valkyrie
chronicles
yes
first of all happy birthday
congratulations
i want to play valkyria chronicles it
looks like something i would like
not only that one but one with a similar
name that i
uh that square enix is putting out
um sooner or later
like there's a lot which is like similar
names right
um
square phoenix
square thinks
profile was i talking about profile i'm
not sure what's that let me look at that
profile
oh yeah i think i was thinking about oh
no no not not that one no no no no no a
new one a new one i'm talking about a
new one on it what am i talking about
i don't know these are all mixing in my
head right now um but
uh yeah uh you asked me if i know it i
know it but i never played it i want to
play
happy birthday dolls
[Music]
are tasty
songs oh there's a new one too oh maybe
maybe i was talking about the new one
[Music]
thank you for the red
thank you
[Music]
it's been a while hell yeah thank you
busy work schedules have kept me away
but i dropped back in catch in to catch
a live stream for my birthday
keep up the great energy
you share a birthday with crains or
tasty did you know that
congratulations
[Music]
eh
bloody birthday to you
bloody birthday dear mood bloody
birthday to you
thank you for coming back you better
come back more often not only on your
birthday what about my birthday huh
and and every day is a birthday
every day is a birthday if you think
about it every day i get older
you better come more often muda i miss
you
oh i know
i want to play triangle strategy but
like all all these square enix games um
i've been waiting for so long that i
turned into a square phoenix
maybe maybe in maybe in 2023
[Applause]
maybe in 2023
oh you changed your name to
um non-korean so i can read it but the
message you send is still fully korean
let me translate thank you come sign it
up for the pink super chat by the way
so
this is again
wait what what the [\h__\h]
is
okay i think you're saying i should ask
fauna for help
because i killed my plant yeah
houseplant
[Music]
i don't know i don't know if father is
really as knowledgeable about plants as
she claims to be
i think she knows more about cats than
she knows about plants
i might test her behind the scenes
you know it's like um
it's like
wait what was a good sound example
it was a good it's like piccolo senpai
and not wanting to eat carrots
or
uh
wait i had other things in mind before
she spawn on the floor and flora is part
of it
she's nature
her name is fauna but she's a council of
nature
[Music]
sounds like you did a lot in one hour
hell yeah so here's a pinky and a new
platform oh thank you also today marks
the day 15 of tweeting to agf i will
never stop until they respond
oh dear well i i don't want you to like
um
you know pressure yourself too much if
you feel like stopping one day don't
worry about it um but yeah
thank you for the support
they might have already seen it but
maybe it's just like you know i don't
know when the convention is but maybe
maybe it's already too late for this
year that could be a thing i don't know
but thank you for trying and trying to
get my name out there and all that thank
you very much i do appreciate it
um
this racing game reminds me what
happened to the mario kart but
game of horror video um
now it's still happening
it's still happening i
i just i just keep on forgetting about
it it will happen it will happen i also
don't know which game i don't know i
still need to decide
[Music]
we have all the time in the world
to do the batsu game don't worry don't
worry
i'm not stressed you guys just need to
chill relax for a moment take a chill
pill
give me your dankest and high health
thank you for the red super chat akasha
[Music]
[Laughter]
anime
[Music]
foreign
you for the rest of the chat
here attention a small air fryer support
that's not a small air fryer support
that's basically
pretty much the full price of the one
i'm trying to buy
thank you play johnny
but well after after the cuts
that much that much left over yeah but i
will i will i will i'm pretty
pretty certain about getting that air
fryer
um
pretty certain
i'm also thinking about getting some
accessories they were selling some
accessories
like um
special
like
shape thingies that you can put into the
airfryer to make something specific
no
i need i need it now
mostly really because i don't have to
use
any oil like except for like one
one one tiny spritzer
thank you blaine johnny
i will report back once i have it
dominique duncan story corner dancing
patsy duncan pepsi
thank you
thank you thank you yeah i will i will
use it towards the
um
birthday concert
thank you
anton m dankesh in boohoo 723
yeah that's so [\h__\h] up you loved oda
and were creeped out by touchy banana
but touchy banana ended up being nice
and all that ended up being the creep
yeah i mean
yeah
and then both died so
sad and
[Music]
you have a
oh so many long messages in the coming
super chats telling me they're coming to
document them
oh well then your friend has to meet you
okay of people than friends too
well it's not gonna be fine you're going
to get along germany
trs or tires thank you thank you
employee number
uh
nine one
[Music]
scott you coming to talk to me
damn
skye is going to talk on me
what
i can't believe you guys are coming from
so far away yeah
i'm so excited so many of you i mean of
course he comes to document he's a
helicopter
but yeah the whole sky the sky
yeah i hope you bring good weather
miss miss dancing
i'm gonna carry down kitchen now i'm
really hoping to get as many people as
possible in the meet and greet yeah
um
oh i hope i can i'll get all of you
oh maybe i need to do free three hours
meet and greet not two hours
over only it's just one hour but i
already added like another session yeah
yeah
so maybe we need to add a third session
ah
i hope so
[Music]
thank you thank you
oh
well well let's see how many people sign
up first yeah
[Music]
and sean louis
have you ever thought of how amazing it
would be if you returned to r64 with all
the gaming skills you've accumulated
since debut and showed that stupid
plumber what the gamer oven is capable
of well yeah i thought about it
i think about it a lot these days
[Music]
too bad about the missed cutie but
here's a little something anyway
[Music]
might as well point out that more heat
that generally gives more boys
and yeah someone told me that good luck
and have fun oh and get the quick change
clothes fire kill you from the shrine
what
guess the quick change clothes fire kill
you from the shrine
what what is it
close or an attack or what
what is that
quick change clothes fire kill you what
the [\h__\h] is that
what do you mean
what day will it be at dokomi uh
saturday saturday
it's my day and sunday is iris day
i mean i'll
i'll be around but um
yes
who knows maybe i'll be sitting in the
audience for iris's concert
maybe i'll be sitting right there
you know what i'll tell genma to put an
acrylic stand of me on one of the seats
you can take a photo you can take a
selfie with me
move in the krill stand
so i don't know what you mean laser boss
but i guess i'll check out the shrine
gts
pockets
thank you for the pinky oh my god this
is perfect
what was perfect
what was perfect this was already at the
super chat reading
ah it was the lo-fi thingy that was
doing oh
yeah yeah yeah
you're welcome
i can still remember on my first time in
germany i mistook kevin as
referring to female toilet because
a toilet only had heroin or diamond on
the outside no stickman ah
okay guys remember
diamond
is for the ladies
herren
is for the guys
most of the time
there's some kind of sign on it but i
guess sometimes there is only the
writing
that is unfortunate
now we don't mean
seven jade
another pink sticker thank you
so many stickers thank you so much
and jim tracy thank you looking for the
top ten kitchen pudding channel thank
you brandon duncan may believe that
richard likes spice likes spines duncan
[Music]
glad you're going for one of my favorite
games oh
it's always nice to hear that people
um like the games that i play and play
them themselves
never tried jollibee no we don't have
jollibee here
batman boot man bob duncan jackie's
monkey danteshen el canada and boohoo
seven two three times
[Music]
i love you i love you too what a
coincidence oh my god
yeah this is oh yeah this is yakuza
super chat sorry i forgot the thumbnail
oh dear
wait what does this mean
what does this mean
[Music]
coming motion i think i know do i know i
know a lot of you are coming
it's so crazy i did not think you guys
would come
yeah i didn't expect it so many of you
are coming that's crazy i'm so far away
what
thank you
no i said i've been doubting you it's
just like
um
what
it's like the concert and the panel
they're both being streamed like you
could totally just stay at home and
watch it from home
you guys are going so far from me thank
you
we weren't so sad last year since we
couldn't buy tickets i was so sad too
i was i said this year
that
they cannot announce me
um
before
you know the ticket sales starts or
before at least but not before it ends
but how would you know you can't
anticipate that so you should announce
me before it starts to begin with
no they didn't quite do it like that but
at least
now there is more tickets so
yeah uh it all went well in the end so
hallelujah
robert kearney thank you so much for
fancy thank
[Music]
and now
we're done with these i'm gonna read the
ones from today tomorrow probably okay
but i powered through i powered through
those
super chat doors
really love to hear tantra's voice early
in the morning oh thank you
good morning sunshine
okay
i will now receive my
um pizza soon
and then
make a thumbnail for tomorrow the finale
for yakuzans tomorrow
there's less than five hours left oh wow
story five hours of story
hmm
well yeah okay i might do a little a
little bit of
um
side stuff if if i pass by it if it's
like on the way
um
oh yeah and then afterwards probably
afterwards bowling
reminds me to do it
well i'm really [\h__\h] at bowling in
reality though
i hope i won't be so [\h__\h] in
[Music]
um
it will be probably very very
exciting tomorrow
uh it's the last episode so the the
story will get really really intense i
think
last time was already intense but people
were telling me that next time this is
gonna be
even more intense yeah
bring some tissues oh yeah i should put
tissues
where i sit not that so that i don't
have to get up and pick them up
yeah yeah i should have them ready
really you think i'm gonna cry you guys
think i'm gonna cry
you guys think i'm gonna cry
i did
yes
[Music]
oh
dear oh there i have a bad feeling huh
okay
okay okay i don't want to get spoiled so
i'm not gonna look at the chat anymore
although i think everybody who's here
now
would not be such a [\h__\h] piece of
[\h__\h] to spoil me right now
everyone who's at the end of a super
chat rating
is a decent person i think
ah piccolo's reaction after i end good
idea yeah piccolo played it too yeah
yeah
ah
interesting
am i decent too
probably
okay guys uh i'm gonna go now
i'm a bit
mentally exhausted now
um but thank you for being here
i'll see you tomorrow after i recharge
my energy
[Music]
ears
gonna cuddle my cuttos
[Music]
i love you a lot you know that
[Applause]
why are you saying that so out of
nowhere so suddenly
[Music]
oh man
don't forget to eat the pizza yes i mean
it's not here yet but
i will eat it
oh yes me
can't help ourselves
i love you guys
i love you
thank you
the pizza gonna get it the pizza is not
gonna know what's happening when i bite
into it and you know much much much and
then i
eat it
it's gonna go into my belly
and i'll mix it with the apparently long
island iced tea
just kidding no it should be a normal
iced tea pretty sure it wasn't
normalized
violent yet i'm eating so violent
he takes so violent
i know i know
spiked tea i said iced tea
and you will always be my favorite of
all members brilliant
thank you love you
i'm gonna go now and watch the last
disappointing one and a half episodes of
inventing anna
do you know what they say in german
you know
they say a veda scene
can you believe it
oh my god
they say avida sin like what the [\h__\h]
yeah
imagine changing or she's could never do
such a thing i i'm loyal to my oshie
forever and ever even after she
graduated i mean there's some other or
she's that i have but she's my number
one aussie forever
forever
[Music]
what's up
i have no energy left so goodbye
goodbye
tired
i need my dab
hmm
[Music]
do
you