[Music]
hello
what the [\h__\h]
that took you two blank million years
you missed my sneeze
i sneezed
i didn't get my gaze
thank you
[Music]
um
you guys hear a different music i think
i'm hearing i'm hearing the fairy um
the fairy thingy
[Music]
let's go
a shorter
shorter intro because youtube delayed
things that's so weird when you start a
stream youtube
will uh see if you feel the connection
between obs and youtube and then offer
you to start the stream with a blue
button and i pressed that several times
and it said like it looked like it was
like starting but then apparently it
wasn't
hello
[Music]
okay
oh yeah right you don't hear that
[Music]
oh man i'm having a
a brain
slow
moment and
uh
i well you guys don't hear that why do i
hear it
and and
low energy but it will come back
it will come back uh
uh no i didn't just wake up
uh i was working on some things i had
like a
a sudden
idea
but that probably took up my
my brain juice and now i'm like
hello why is it not i guess
i guess this works that should work
you hear it now don't ya
i'm still tired
um okay
but it's probably too loud
somewhere around here
if data has been created good to know
we're starting the windwaker weekends
where's my
that's not it
what is this
oh my god
oh my god now i hear it
[Music]
i love it
i love it i love it i love it i love it
i love it i love it so much i love it so
much
[Music]
[Laughter]
it looks like um i'm licking
the
wind waker
[Music]
i'm eating a coin club like this
put some butter on it
[Music]
sorry okay
we'll always get stuck on these kind of
screens where the music was just too
good oh [\h__\h] my bird is cut off
why is the music so good
god damn it
[Music]
check profile oh okay
gosh you keep me [\h__\h]
shook
where's the whole button here
it's not mine it's not my profile it's
one of those weirdos
back no
why why am i on that profile
yeah close that [\h__\h]
i'm pretty sure i saved
let me go to my profile
switch user
[Laughter]
why the [\h__\h] do you want my password for
the nintendo network idea for [\h__\h]
time i don't even know what it was
ah
i hope it was this
we need to we need to delete the other
um users man
get rid of them incorrect password
what about this
[Music]
how about this how about this
come on
incorrect password
what
i can't remember what was my password
the nintendo network id password
but i forgot
to retire
which was email addresses i registered
sorry guys
i didn't realize it would do that ah
there
just check your email ah man which one
which one i have a million [\h__\h] email
accounts
is it this one
yes okay
okay
gosh i'm feeling dizzy
my
my breakfast was that cake
which had a lot of chocolate on it
a lot it was basically like
a chocolate cake with bananas
[Music]
okay okay
oh sh
we are in
we're in
now please tell me that
we could now
start the [\h__\h] game now go
oopsie
i love this shiny effect it's like when
you hold one of those shiny cards and
then
they have the same effect it looks the
same
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
okay first what we're doing today first
of all
is
go get
that uh
i said those monsters in this room well
that would mean
there's no attempt to lose we must
depart at one of the pearls where the
next person leaves when you sail to the
south no we're not going where he says
we're going
let me get on the boat please how do i
can i get on the boat
hello can you get on the boat
all right
we can't depart until the wind
ah you want me to do the
music i've heard legends that tell of a
wind god i'm gonna do the voices later
uh resided on this island it is said
that the winds obeyed his every whim
have you heard nothing of him
what on this island
you want me to get the music but i
actually i want to
uh
get the the sale from the auction
i mean we have 500 uh rubies rupees
uh so we might as well use them where is
that win cod
one second there's money every single
one
coin counts is it
a lot of
music pitch other side of the island
okay
can i walk around
[Music]
gosh i probably forgot how to play this
game because it's been uh two weeks
this way this way i remember that i
remember there being a god there yeah
yeah
hello yeah it's a shrine
jinjaya
tummy summer
oh up left right okay
you don't need to tell me anything else
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
and there goes the wind
hello frog
i can speak your language
um
but let's speak in english
oh
got some more cheek noise breeze
i don't know if that's the right voice
for him
the name's zephos
i'm the god of winds get up
so you're the new winter white car you
can't i don't think it fits
great great for brigitte you've got a
nice win sense about you kill i like you
kids get off
[Music]
that tune you just picked up well it
gives you control over the direction the
wind blows cannot
depending on how it's used which can be
a good thing you know or a very bad
thing you want an example of it being a
bad thing then you should see my brother
get up
oh yeah something was there
it saddens me to say that my brother
cyclist is moved about his monument here
being broken
and now he spends his time creating
cyclones to torment people with kettle
so if you encounter any cyclones that
see chester's my brother for me will you
get up
okay or that is my request for you kiddo
[Music]
i forgot that this uh god was a frog
i got that
okay we have wind but we're not gonna go
that way
you can
with this melody we can set it to any
direction right they make us choose as
far as i remember
so
wait are you happy now
or should i still like win
[Music]
we're making music
and we don't even have a sale right
uh self self stop stop stop
wow
oh my god
well
[Music]
what about this oh okay what voice did
we do
something
like
oh life
sorry
somewhere here
was it like this was was it like this
was it like this was or was the other
way around
[Laughter]
can we go
deeper um
hey was it really like this
was it like this
no
i don't
it was kind of different i think
[Music]
it's kind of different
oh well
the wind is blowing to the south is it
like this
quickly swim beside me and press a to
climb the board we must depart at once
for the place where the next pearl lies
sleeping
[Laughter]
clap go uh but will he be mad if i don't
go there can i go somewhere else oh we
don't have a sale i want the quick sale
the fast one where is
oh [\h__\h] don't go so fast i mean i want
to go somewhere else
where was where was the
where's the map first of all
[Music]
i was on my [\h__\h]
ipad weeper
okay well
bye bye pumu i guess i'm playing without
you
today i am such a sassy bucket
i was pressing buttons to find the
the
the map but now i realize it's in front
of me
what is this place outside island
forsaken fortress and
windfall we're going to windfall island
which is this way but that is
west wind
so
[Music]
no
yes west wind right we want to go west
so the wind has to go west i think
yes
okay
oh i thought he was gonna get mad with
me for going somewhere else okay okay
you have no problem with that oh i hold
it right there
who is you ah that fish i remember that
fish
eh um
[Music]
i
i don't know why you got your mitch on
that c chart you got there
but it looks to me like it's pretty much
got nothing but c-strong on it it's
pathetic in fact it's almost an insult
to call that being a c-chart if you ask
me
what's the matter smoke right i'm just
trying to be nice here i'm telling you
that you've got a problem and you do
don't give me that super fat look it
makes you look like you're out of being
diapers
just listen okay
i'm here to teach you what i know about
this island so open up your safety and
make it snappy
[Music]
and beach
okay
there's a real peculiar cave toward the
backside of this dragon roost island
you're real peculiar but i doubt you'll
ever get there to see it smoke fry
unless you mash your sprock wings and
fly that is
this voice is not
more like this oh no no
no
because you won't be getting otherwise
that's all i can teach you small fry
but i will do this for you since i'm
feeling so generous i'll send word to
all my brethren living near the islands
of the great sea good bunta fish
if you see a fish sleeping on of out of
the water when you sail near an island
sail up to it and spread bait out on the
water surface trust me this is a good
device fry
see the painting process allows you to
get a charge of the island along with
any info that might be of use to you i
highly recommend you make a habit of
doing so see you're definitely going to
need a reliable c chart to help you
search for things out of the sea i can't
emphasize that enough fry you need you
need a well-drawn shirt
if you don't get a charge for every
island you come across it'll just be a
bigger hassle for you later on now don't
say i never did anything for you fry
[Music]
for you there you kingly red lion guy
that's it i've repaid my death i'm done
you take care of the rest
what dabbed
what the
what that
okay that's what we need to bait for
but anyway we need something else first
so
[Music]
oh something's showing on my map that's
like ah is that the goal where we need
to go um
something with like
like there's no i don't see i don't see
like a shape of the island or so i just
see some some markings
can we go faster
no
so how do i jump
i know
no no
no no how do i jump
there you go
here you go
uh
i don't have to charge yet what charge
set arch jump yeah figure that out
[Music]
i want to get there before night time
it needs to be night time for what
sorry i'm not really following you guys
nah mommy where'd you go
what is that dude doing
wait what
no no no
no well this is island we were not here
before but i don't care i need to go
somewhere else
is my wind still going west
yes it is
but it feels weaker
[Music]
only goes to sail dead oh well that's
good i mean it's just going to be
nighttime soon i suppose i mean look the
sun is
setting
[Music]
up
i miss the fish oh whatever
nice job
the auctions happen at night see i don't
really remember those oh there's there's
sparkly thing but i don't care i need to
i need to go there in time
the time passes by also when i'm on the
island or just uh when i'm on the sea
just asking
just asking let me know
what is that
there's a hidden chest can i can i open
it
okay
can i get on that anyway
i don't know
time only passes that's it
i don't think i can get on there
okay let's go
it's night time
the hook shot not a hotel
don't forget to talk to the disco guy i
already talked to him before don't need
to talk to him again
can i go up here oh thank god okay okay
see i'm not very used to ships so you
know
it's a bit of a struggle where is the
auction in one of these houses i think
maybe this one
oh come on
how do you successfully participate in
the auction
[Music]
oh dear i don't remember any of the
voices uh do you guys remember was the
low or high voice
saved before
you got the cash we'll have 500 i can't
even have more right now
uh italian okay
okay wait a second oh yes yes i rent out
the first floor of this mansion in order
to run a nightly auction not very
illegal but don't tell anyone because
you're gonna get some good stuff out of
it too and actually tonight's auction is
about to begin ah dear me is it ever
now this is indeed an auction but i like
to describe it in more simple terms it
is a competition of the very highest
order oh yes it is a competition to see
who can get the item that is being
auctioned can you upbeat everyone else
and do you have the courage to [\h__\h] ah
now i remember i had like a thing with
the r
and the fundage oh the drama
oh but what's this ah well dear let me
do i detect a hint of curiosity i
believe i do fortunately we welcome
peters of all ages both kids and adults
oh yeah so tell me would you like to
participate in the auction
nap not to no no wait but i mean i do
but but i'll come back in a second
and shut down a minute how to save in
this game i forgot
save here yeah there it is would you
like to save yes
the game has been saved continue
[Music]
and now here again
so tell me would you like to participate
in dark souls and absolutely
really dear me really
now you are completely fine with me not
explaining the octone to you am i
correctly assuming this no please
explain what the [\h__\h]
i'm completely not defined
then my dear allow me to explain
once the action begins you must surely
tap a repeatedly so you can earn the
right to beat or the tap in the
excitement
mamma mia
yes yes when you want to beat the tapa a
as you do your gorgeous gauge will do
any build up once your gauge is full
the chance to beat has finally come oh
dear me yes a mamma
my gosh will gradually build up okay
once you're going for a chance to bring
this finally okay just just tap tap like
an insane person okay
now when you beat your name naming the
price of you're willing to pay for the
item let us just call you a chance to
show off your wealth flaunt it my dear
cash money of course if your fellow
beaters try to buy that they might form
under you by raising the beat you can
always raise it in return indeed this
produces so much excitement
[Music]
this dramatic back and forth goes on
until time runs out at which point the
person who had the highest speed gets
the sublime honor of purchasing the item
the octone only lasts one minute not
counting the time people spend talking
but do not worry i will show you how
much time remains when you make your
beat
now do you understand them
let us begin immediately it's not time
to doddle what does that mean
is a foot on your toes
okay
let's try to not spend too much money
um
but i also want to sail so mm-hmm
oh yes yes yes the ccc first let me
thank all of you berry and loving people
yeah for joining us this evening jeremy
want to turn out
he has cute twin tails
oh my god how cute when he takes off his
hood he has
cute twin tails
hello cute
the action is about to begin to see and
what do you suppose will pop up as a
right the middle of the evening oh dear
me i'm so excited i can't stop sniffling
the calm before the auction storm always
makes my nose run oh dear
let's get to it this evening oh glorious
octona item is this oh i swear to say
exactly
[Music]
at last the suspense is over
but all drama i said you should know it
is extremely rare to even get a chance
of to owe the fabulous item like this
it is precious the quality are very
valuable you see cccc isn't well for i
do not lie
my hips don't lie either let the auction
begin let's open the bidding and 100. oh
[\h__\h] okay how high do these people go
i mean they can't have deeper pockets
than i do right
like i mean technically
can they even bid more than 500 because
that's not fair because i can only bid
500.
oh [\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] kidding me okay but they don't
like go much higher step by step it
seems
[Music]
how can this old lady bid faster than me
but okay i'm almost it's my turn
[Music]
keep eating over 20 to send them okay
wait it's not over 20 it's just 20. was
that wrong
oh dearest me incredible the drama
everyone's struck i worked speechless
beat nice to mamma mia
what's with this kid and just how much
of an allowance does he get i wonder
oh let's go oh oh oh i didn't go i
didn't know i didn't know i didn't know
but what i i'm just gonna bid over
myself
[Music]
do i get it then
should i do 20 again
[Music]
keep it low
okay
i'm supposed to wait
i don't know i wasn't sure what to do
[Music]
hmm
but they will eventually stop right
they're going to eventually be like i
can't spend no more
i stunned them with bigfoot when the
auctioneer's completion
okay okay
so that i'm the last one bidding okay
okay
[Music]
so do i just wait until
now
yeah maybe for now
and just kind of
how much where's the timer where's the
timer
[Music]
oh
okay
oh [\h__\h] your bit
a bit
should i
i don't know should i go
[Music]
should i go or should i still wait
i don't see the timer
it will tell me
okay ah okay
[Music]
ah
there's 30 seconds left but it doesn't
stun them for that long
does it [\h__\h]
ah
what are you guys waiting for
um
it's done again
all right i mean it's not that expensive
we'll stand on once and we'll stun them
twice
[Music]
i just do one
i don't know how how fast time goes by
he was nervous
i'm just gonna do one
okay
[Music]
they can't stun me can they can they
okay
okay 10 seconds
does my stand work for 10 seconds
[Laughter]
okay
200 come on please
oh mamma mia
[Music]
and we're done bidding yes they are done
bidding i'm just gonna go anyway maybe
i'll beat one more one more
five seconds to remain are you done guys
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
do i have to do another 20.
i don't see all
do i have to stun them again for
2.1
seconds
to be safe
i mean
i feel like if i just do one then
someone's gonna follow me up immediately
[Music]
[Laughter]
i did save yeah
i did i did
okay
stunning whatever whatever
[Music]
oh
well i didn't have to stun them that
often
but you know it was my first time okay
first try first try
and tonight's fabulous sweep the same
goals though queue marvel for the price
of 250 at the rupees ah dear me let me
just say
[Music]
as far as i know
wait
was that was that a good deal
is that a good deal
i'm idea how incredible that such a
youngster walked away with surprise i
have i've never seen such a fat wallet
that kid was a beating machine right up
to the end
but now then on to busyness for you
lucky ones out there and yes also for
you not some lucky ones let me say thank
you for your participation
i must bring tonight's option to an end
are there like other items after this
that are important
[Music]
mele grazia
is there anything worth like bidding on
later
okay
a heart container oh
nice
i do want that yeah
so what was it about
the dude up here do i need to visit him
at night oh there's a fish
how long does he stay there
hello
oh the voice oh
that magical dance that changed the day
to 1990 today if i could only call the
river oh the ripple then i could dance
it perfectly
oh the ribbon
oh i don't have that one yet
changing day to night or night today
[Music]
oh
oh he's gonna teach me
oh my god
are you a god
[Music]
that's the rhythm i've been trying to
recall oh i can feel it i can feel it
guy
i don't know how what i did with his
voice i just knew he was excited
oh can you do that again
left right down
okay
left right
uh left right
or you mean right left right left
who
okay
[Music]
i learned the song of past single yeah
yeah
[Music]
right left down
that's it that's it it's perfect i'm
perfect now let the sunshine on
you're perfect you could uh
maybe go well with crooney
and what's the matter nothing happened
nothing at all why
i don't know why good question
what
right left
because i can only do it on the on the
ocean
maybe
oh no oh there it is
wow
i am god
was it that power
is literally the power of a god
i am god
is the fish still there i wonder
nice jump
um
[Music]
i don't see the fish anymore
oh
oh yeah cause i need i need bait anyway
right i don't know if i have bait do i
have bait
[Music]
yeah i do have bait
okay
and we are going south i think
matt
i think i need to go there
[Music]
um
was this right
now
[Music]
wow amazing
okay it goes up faster
yeah
uh
that way that way toward the edge that
way
[Music]
speed
the water looks so real are you making
fun of it
it's obviously not real but i really
like it
did you guys watch the
super smash brothers club what is it i'm
talking
i am trying to venture in our next
[Music]
he destination me to go
muscle dragon rules and then east oh
where the [\h__\h] is dragon roost oh okay
much
[Music]
so first uh
this way
that's where dragon roost island is
here
right
passing this one
i know yeah yeah
until we are at dragon roost island and
then we go down
yeah so did he watch it i i was like oh
my god
it can't be like that one time when
um
when the windwaker world was selected
for one of our battles
i was like immediately
that water looks like the wind wake of
water but the big ship kind of confused
me so i was like
is that really
is that really the windbreaker world why
is it not the small ship but then i
realized i was the big pirate ship
oh wait wait wait
i want to try to get that
why are you still moving
can i there we go
[Music]
i'm too fast i i can't control this ship
this boat and
here
savage
what do we get what do we get what did
we get what did we get use that art
articles
what money i can use some money now
[Music]
ruby
how did you know guys how did you know
there's another one over there i want to
go there
[Music]
is this here
smashing tournament
uh
i mean
if it's just one versus one battles i
guess that could somehow work but there
will always be lag and people that are
salty about the lag probably but you'll
just have to see it as
as like you know
a part of the tournament slash a part of
the game
yeah
i i definitely felt the lag when i was
fighting versus ninety i don't think
like i asked her and she said she didn't
really
feel it so
that's a bit unfair if only one party
experiences the lag and the other one
doesn't
you guys were watching her her point of
view so
you you would probably know
hello fish hello wait i'll give you some
bait do you want the bait
like she didn't have a leg right she
said so herself but maybe she just
doesn't know what the leg was
it looked fine and for me it definitely
even looked laggy it didn't really feel
like it looked laggy
um i don't need bait goddammit
don't think they make a premium brand of
this stuff oh well such is the life of a
fish so you want to hear the info about
this here island again
no
[Music]
okay oh [\h__\h]
i heard that before damned i think
i wasted my bae
um
okay wait wait wait wait now we're going
now we're going
south
okay
[Music]
um
down here
the fish baited me yeah i was trying to
bait the fish but the bait was fishing
me no what
the fish was big
i mean
somehow
somehow i do feel like i was pissed so
i'll [\h__\h] the other way
no no no no no
[Music]
no
go go go go
i don't need to change the window to
suppose what
oh that's what you guys think
what it will go the same amount of speed
anywhere i go or the wind is changing
with me as i go
[Music]
what that's so powerful that's totally
worth 500 rupees
[Music]
if not more
a little bit uh
off course there we go
thanks for the membership yeah well
if you spam it doesn't it go faster
no
i don't know i don't think ah is it
going a little bit faster
mean like this
[Music]
maybe
is it i don't know is it it feels a bit
faster
[Music]
maybe just because the pattern of the
water is different now
[Music]
so i can use it as my tooth pick after
all if i don't need it anymore
do you like the
thumbnail
i was um
like i had that idea two weeks ago
after making the last thumbnail i'm glad
i was worried i would forget about it
i'm glad i didn't forget about it
and now i was able to finally make it
this way i think that island over there
oh what is that that looks like the
maldives
we'll check out all the items eventually
but first we'll go where the game wants
us to go
one of my best bump meals
recently i'm doing a lot of those kind
of thumbnails
um the portable ones were
assets from like
other people that they created and let
other people use for free
but
this one
i was just i put the wind waker in my
mouth and then changed my
changed my um
[Music]
my face by myself
so yeah graphic design is my passion
oh
it seems we are correct
um
was it like this was it was it like this
i think so
yes do you not see what rises up from
the horizon
that is where you must go kiwawa the
forest haven oh no
ah i don't know but i remember this this
one being
kind of i don't know difficult
[Music]
it may appear as though this is but a
great tree rising far above the ocean's
surface
but it is a sacred place
wait is this the
big ass
deku tree
just
wait you know surrounded by water
because everything is surrounded by
water and wind waker is this the big ass
tree
is this a deco tree
oh my god
who the [\h__\h] over watered the deku tree
like that it's gonna die
that's overwatering
i think
maybe it's good maybe the tree doesn't
care
it is a deco tree
oh
he's telling me
it's a sacred place it is inside this
grotto that you will find the spirit of
the earth the great deku dream
but inside
i thought the thing that we see right
now is deku tree
you must speak with deku tree and
receive from him the sacred gem known as
faroese pearl
[Music]
i fear that ganon's vile hand may have
already already reached its most sacred
of sanctuaries
go forth with caution
[Music]
okay yeah i'll be very cautious don't
don't worry about that don't go
he's leaving as i arrived
oh sure all right
uh we're already going into the next
dungeon it seems
[Applause]
i'll remember how to fight
uh
[Music]
and there we go
i
i really don't know
can i eat it at least
oh for [\h__\h] sake
um
hi bird
uh i'll put something else there but i
don't even have anything useful to put
there now except
the bottle the empty bottle because i'm
so stupid
i used that one up too
call yourself a warrior hey
i took the bait in the fur right on the
ground
what
is it
i don't know how to fight this thing
how do i find it and i only know
i don't really know the fighting moves
anymore
ah lock on lock on with the
that's it
left
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
it just bounces off oh there we go it
worked our stick
but i don't need the stick
hey okay that that already is an
improvement okay
we remembered how to lock on oh what is
this fancy thing
goku baba seed
kobu
do you guys ever want to see a baba
version of kobu because now she's baby
she's kobold baby one day kobo baba
baba
this is the source of the evil plant's
magic perhaps if you can find someone to
cook it up its magic can be unleashed oh
make a potion into it or whatever
[Music]
okay uh we need to use the hook shot
i totally remember how to use this
there we go
yeah let's go okay okay oh [\h__\h] what is
oh i did it by accident i killed it by
accident nice
i don't know how i did that
okay
look i'm watching
[Applause]
oh here we go again that one reminds me
of
um that really looks like the one from
sunshine
super mario sunshine do i have to
i
how do i can't there
ah here
uh go
up up let go all right
we're in guys we're in
i like the whole atmosphere in here but
it does feel like
it could get very difficult
because that's kind of how i remember it
but i love these
10 million fireflies you would not
believe your eyes straighten it up the
skies that fell asleep
probably every time fireflies are some
what somewhere
on the screen on any youtubers stream
they will start singing this song
one brain cell
wow nice move sling
nice move
give me one example
where
in the stream
in a game or something five lives
are brought up and the youtuber does not
start singing or mentioning the song
one example
you won't find it
can i kill that
no okay
so where do we go in here
oh oh yo yo
what is that face
you have a funny face
ah the jelly monsters
oh [\h__\h]
are they hurting you do we need to pop
them like pimples how huddly
i do i ah the hook shot maybe we
pulled them away oh god they moved so
fast
this is really it
i don't think so never mind
it could it would have been a good idea
i think but
just oh wait what
nanda yo
what are you doing
i don't know i'm trying my own way you
don't like it roll at him eh
quickly you must jolt those strange
creatures off of the dick or tree's face
do you not know how to knock them down
excuse me i had a better idea i think
no idea
i like my idea more because it's more of
a challenge
[Music]
come here give me that jelly you mean
that's jelly give me that jelly
[Music]
wait give me the jelly stuff before they
visit me
oh where did they go
this boy
but wait there's more
one
three more
because i disappeared in the water
before i killed them maybe
[Music]
okay
come at me
there we go
now let me pick up the
let me pick up the
boxers
nada who don't um
hey
[Music]
and suddenly i felt a longing for an age
gone by
that longing caused the ancient tongue
to pass my lips
i am the guarded spirit of this forest
haven
the deku tree
i owe my thanks for your aid in
riddle gritting me of those foul
creatures
tell me was it not the king of red lions
the boat who speaks
who led you to this place
so it is true
then you have come here because you have
the beat of the pearl of the goddess
i see
i knew there was a reason the monsters
had begun to compromise in the regions
around my wound
now i understand it
he has returned
in that case we must make haste
little children of the woods this
traveler is not your enemy let your
hearts be at ease and show yourselves
we're doing a little dance
wait who's asking what do you call
yourself
wait up are they talking
no he's talking
well then
these are the koroks the spirits of the
forest
once upon a time long ago the kordoks
took on human forms but when they came
to live on the sea they took these
shapes
now they fear people but to me they will
ever be my cherished little children
as it happens you have come just in time
for a ceremony that the products hold
but
once every year it is about to begin
i shall grant the pearl to you once
their ceremony is complete
i must apologize for the brief delay but
if the ceremony is not completed soon an
ill-fate could befall us
so let it begin are you ready my
children
[Music]
what
okay
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
heard all this
the forbidden woods are right beside the
hallowed island of our forest haven
those woods the whole region is a
fireplace that is home to evil beasts
and now it seems to have taken a child
of the forest named mata
your presence here is no mistake i deem
the king of red lions likely expects
great deeds of you it is why he brought
you here i'm sorry to ask this with you
but can
oh yes
thank you
you are right
to enter it
woods from the sea is it
in chihuahua i would guess from your
size that you were heavier than my coat
of children
yet i think we may still be able to
solve this dilemma
you must use the item i shall bristol
walk on you and fly through the sky
yeah
gladly give it to me
oh no he's gonna sneeze
[Music]
he didn't really sneeze there it is
really why could the kodak's not get it
because they can already fly can they
not just
give it to me
come on
that's not the great oh my god
yo
[Music]
i would guess that our homes should
still exist somewhere deeper than the
woods
if you have trouble anywhere in the
forest just look for the sun-shaped
houses
is
is that how i'm gonna reach the
uh
[Music]
oh the music
well i mean look i see
okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
the flappy thing for that because how
else will i get
over there
does this not work right now
it's not for now to reach it
no wait it works it works it works i
just
i can't
i can't change direction that fast
it's acting up a little bit
this will take a few tries i think
i wonder if there's an easier way to do
this
maybe i just stay
once
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
i was supposed to go there but i was
supposed to go kind of straight
i thought i needed to go to the next one
but that one was up too high yeah yeah
yeah okay
but i think i
i'm able to control it now
sometimes it's like
he's not sure if i want to go or not
even though i'm pushing the joystick
forward
like now like i was pushing it
forward to the maximum
but he didn't reach
now he reached
yeah but this will ah it how did that
reach i'm actually surprised surprised
oh okay and now front let's just go
straight
there we go
okay
oh
there's a lock on
i have this part about playing with
winger it's a bit difficult yeah
yeah okay yeah i mean i get that
uh
here's the next
one can i
ow the hook shot
with the hook shot we fall into it but
if we fail we have to start all the way
did was was that thrift i'm not doing
anything
is that what you call drift
[Music]
i'm not sure
but okay what was i saying yeah we have
to start all the way from the bottom
oh god oh god no
baby i knew it i knew it
i [\h__\h] knew it
i mean i wasn't hundred percent
like into that either i'll admit that i
was kind of unsure of what was gonna
happen
okay a fighter
fighter i'll get better at it
stay stay
go
okay
stay
we're gonna go safe
and go
okay
aiming has zero controls i don't know
what that means
oh
okay
now
so
let's go
stay
i do not care for falling down and
oh my god oh my god
stay stay stay stay stay
cute
that could have worked but we're gonna
stay anyway always stay once and then go
okay oh it has motion controls oh
stay
stay stay don't [\h__\h] it up now
okay
and go
get that second try
[Music]
not fat not bad i got the decollete
plant your feet on the ground and use it
to blow blasts of air at objects and
enemies ah
it's not like i can fly with it i make
other things fly
yeah i would say second try is nothing
to be ashamed of in this case
let me can i quickly look at my discord
dms because i have nine line dm's
don't understand
oh
okay
no problem
[Music]
wow
okay
yeah actually the reason i have so many
dms is because
i am planning something special
[Music]
you guys want to know okay
i'll roughly tell you
wait i'll tell you in a moment after i
pour myself some iced tea
ice cream lemon
fuse tea by the way i used to um like
different iced tea
but then like a couple of years ago two
three four five i don't know not not so
long ago
um they brought fused tea into austria
and ever since then i actually like it
very much they have some really nice
tastes i'm not sponsored though
i just really like iced tea
if if i was in japan because they don't
have feels i would be drinking lipton
all the time because they have so many
different
um
uh tastes in japan
actually
yeah but here we only have the basic
lipton's like um i think it's literally
just peach and
and lemon which are the most basic ones
hmm
[Music]
yeah in japan they have um
peach lemon no wait i don't even i don't
even see peach that often but lemon and
apple
um yeah apple is one of the main ones
which we don't really have here
apple ice tea from other brands ever but
in japan it's like a main
main main taste and then they have like
time limited ones that i really love yam
they have so much variety
[Music]
i'm always like whenever i would go to
the convenience store i would always
like look if they have new flavors
of um
of iced teas of lipton lipton
specifically
yeah and whenever they have a new one
i'm like oh my god i have to try it
i'm trying to have to try that buying
this i'm buying this hundred percent yup
yup yup yup yup yup
in germany they have lime melon and
green mint what
what the [\h__\h]
what
what give
give me uh
germany not fair
you're supposed to share with us
austrians yo
we share so many things
why not share iced tea huh
we share a language we share the same
amazon mostly
and all that kind of stuff but i think
we share the same youtube
give
okay let's continue you can also jump
into the air and use your magic power to
drift on the currents of wind i'll kill
you so floating but not flying right
swordsman who's asking
who's
[Music]
asking me
no problem
um i think i hope
i don't want to go all the way up there
again um
let's replace this one r
okay so
yeah whoa
uh
how do i
do i hold it no
if i do it in the other direction
like how jump off first jump in an r i'm
scared
okay
okay okay okay
ah
fall damage
how do i
okay okay i did it look at that arrow
so obvious
yay
[Music]
ah i yay that those bottles to fill up
the the wind energy
oh okay okay
[Music]
you've already messed up
are they making fun of me oh my god
excuse me
[Music]
if you want me to do that you should be
nicer to me
okay
be nicer to me
yeah they are made out of wood
wait are you saying that's that means
that they're
but i'm not
gladys was right excuse me
gladys called me fat too yeah i think so
they don't know how much i weigh
i don't even know how much i weigh
oh hello
[Music]
uh this direction you say is um
southwest
south southwest yeah southwest
uh
[Music]
there's a storm coming up right at me
but we'll be fine
i had good timing when i jumped off
okay
hello i made it yay
so far i think i'm not doing too bad
with this mm-hmm
it looks like you've already mastered
using your decorative you're
thing you should quick is cut the grass
around here to replenish your magic
power
is at a much higher level than the
entrance to our forest having
in order to go up to such a high place
you'll have to catch a swirl in your
[Music]
once you're floating on the ground just
let the wind take you to the answering
to the roots
it's right there but i need to i need
the wind i need to change the wind too i
suppose
right yeah um here we have
uh west what
west north what northwest
uh
where is
[Music]
uh
okay now i just have to wait for that
thing
there it is
hi oh hi osenkai
waiting for you there's monsters there
too though that's kind of scary
three
two
one and go
are you
[Music]
um
what's going to happen
do i go back i don't shoot
look what happens if i fall down here
[Music]
okay we land here
[\h__\h]
i jumped early enough
this game is wreath
i like these bottles they're so cute
could put put some face cream or
something in those
and sell them as um fan merch
okay i'll jump a little bit earlier okay
i didn't anticipate it to take me so
long to get into the world okay
please please
please
yes
okay
[Music]
we've done it kfp we've done it once
again incredible
incredible
second try is first try
[Music]
for braden woods i'm not supposed to be
here it's forbidden
chihuahua always follows rules always
always
i don't i'm not supposed to be here
[Music]
yeah
okay so
let me tell you guys
um
reyna
wrote to me today
i'm saying that since her vacation is
coming up we should do one collab before
that
to like you know get prepared for me
and i was like yeah i kind of wanted to
do that too
and then elena probably because she
recently got herself a vr model said how
about we do a vr vr collab
i'm like oh my god i have an idea
for the vr collab
so i was like lena leave it to me
i have a genius idea
so i mean i immediately hit up the usual
people
i'll not tell you what we're doing yet
but it's i mean it's there's not much
time so it's not going to be like super
incredible wow wow
um but i thought of like a game
or something like that
and uh yeah
we'll do that
will before our vacation
we'll do it next week
yeah a vr collab
on my channel
yay
this time this time i'm i'm thinking of
these things yeah
i hope it goes well there's not much
time but these people are used to not
having much time
i didn't want to be one of those people
but okay this was urgent are they
endlessly spawning
me why they couldn't skittle
i'm doing the thing
can't wait but you have to wait what is
this thing oh i can pick it up oh
it's a nut
i has not for you
do i have to
throw it at something
also
[Music]
[Laughter]
that was fast i literally just entered
that is a a nice dungeon
is it falling apart
wait these nuts fall apart don't they
after a while
ah okay i think it's yeah falling apart
yeah the texture is changing
one can i use it again
yeah
don't go
and one more
does it keep on regrowing
it keeps on growing no
too close too far what which one
[Music]
ah
i think i was too close
but what about ah is that a teleporter
that was a teleporter i think let's go
okay
okay i smell
failures
many of them
do i have to go over there and then over
there and over there
i think so
no wait
i'm not ready
we could also just go straight down
apparently oh yeah
there's one here i could have fallen
into that and would have felt no pain
but no pain no gain
ah and i was
somehow able to make that jump but
i i
i
i failed
can i have more heart one more
one more one more please
[Music]
more jellies
okay what is that thing i need to throw
something at it again
[Music]
oh yeah if we get too close it closes
well what could we
throw
oh
a stick of these monsters
[Music]
oh blow the leaves oh so i suppose this
is not working
[Music]
our um oh
i thought some
useful item was gonna come out of it
okay i'm gonna try to stick anyway
maybe it works
oh [\h__\h] no
bro
my aim though
oh okay i don't think this is it
what about here
now don't you dare accidentally use that
chihuahua
in every every zelda game i panic the
moment i see a fairy flying around
because i'm so scared of accidentally
using it
okay
should i put something else there until
maybe until
like a boss fight
i won't need it until then
what is that stick doing on the wall
also i probably
need some item that's somewhere at the
top and then bring it down
is this
would this be too simple
yeah
is this one auto here will this one get
activated automatically
you guys are so smart and i'm just so
stupid
i'm just
so stupid look at me
tell me your stick
eh
did i have any other sticks
oh wait i think there's one here
or did it
okay
uh take stick
take fire
[Music]
set everything on fire
yeah
okay i got that one from chat thank you
[Music]
uh nice crest okay
okay i forgot what that was for
okay so now we go up because there's
nothing left
up up we go
where those
not here
here okay wait wait wait
now
i need to fly over there maybe
yes
okay okay okay okay i need to think with
the leaves not the portals but with the
leaves now we can probably go over there
ah extend our range you know
okay
no
where do we go from here
[Music]
ah probably over there
roger
i'm on my way
okay
and
um that's probably where we came from
so
yeah
ah too early
okay mistakes sometimes happen
no problem we'll do it again
i would have been able to go straight
over there
maybe
okay
do they fill up these flowers they fill
up my
my flying gorge thingy oh [\h__\h]
[Applause]
too early
okay
sorry guys still getting used to it
and drop
[Music]
yeah sometimes i use the
the leaf too early
this should be okay
of course
okay
easy
easy llama squeezy no no no no wait
wait i need something here though
[Music]
it's
okay so far
i
i don't think this dungeon is as bad as
i remembered it
so
i'm feeling
like it's it's manageable
i know when i was young [\h__\h] when i was
younger i had it
a bit more
scary and difficult in in my memory but
yeah that's probably because it's ages
ago
good
nice
i know there was probably a hint popping
up there but i knew what to do
i don't need your help
i hated this place as a kid
why why do we hate this place as a kid i
wonder what makes us hate it
it's not that difficult so far
okay
i see
that over there but i'm not on the right
height so i need to reach that first oh
hello
can i jump over there
yes
and now
i make some air
is that the right way yes i go back
and ride that thing
[Music]
and then the question is can i make the
air from here
i should be able to do it yep there it
goes more
more
no no no no no no wrong direction
[Music]
okay that is a little bit of a trigger
um
spot i would say
yeah
oh no [\h__\h]
oh wait i can oh can i just do this
no
[Applause]
no i can
oh well all right i thought i had to
i had to aim for
those wind generators but no no no no no
only if i wanted to come to me i suppose
yo
how do i fight you guys oh maybe with
the wind
you know oh oh don't yes yes
yeah you stun them and then attack
[Music]
oh yeah
aiming for this guy
yeah stun him
[Music]
that could have been a cool hit but i
messed it up because i wasn't focused
on the enemy
[Music]
it's very simple
did you guys see elena's uh youtube
music weekend so she has a vr thingy now
that
one can use
and
ow it's in the same style
that we have with our oh [\h__\h] you
[Music]
with our dance school um advertise yeah
she was a dj
cool
layna dj
what i was like what
excuse me
i remember a while ago she was like hey
how do you guys go about doing the whole
vr stuff
i want to make a vr model for like some
special occasion blue blah blue which
was probably the youtube music weekend i
suppose
oh you see i see
and yeah i told her
she should probably get it from free too
so we have the same style you know
and
now we bring this to the other side but
it's gonna
it's gonna break if i take too much time
take it take it [\h__\h] pick it up why
are you not picking it up
idiot
okay but i need to put it down don't
throw it how did i just put it down
okay okay okay and now
oh god
[Music]
you can't really see my mad face right
now
but i'm pretty mad at that
that's not fair
skull hey
the game breaks
oh should i just throw it from there
instead of jumping yeah but probably
distance wise it would probably work why
are you going there
good try thank you
[Applause]
okay
i take
i grab i jump
i i'm carefully put down
and then
wait win win let it be wind
okay chill and pick pick it up and oh
dear
hey really yeah
ah okay
wait don't get so yeah
okay
nice
i thought i had to throw it from the
elevator for a moment but no no no just
throw it over to the other side
otherwise it wouldn't reach all hello
hold up
reminds me of character varies
i didn't want to run into that
i see okay okay i see i see with the
wind we should uh
move it
there it goes
big brinky wow
[Music]
i should
pick it up
okay i like i like this dungeon so far
when is it gonna make me hate it
uh-huh hook shot
a heart would be nice
no no
no
okay fine don't need it i don't need it
[Music]
and then we go
those are moving too
wait for them and jump and wait for them
get the ball and where are we bringing
the ball though
over there okay
um wait we need to first
i guess i can uh jump
over here and then from there to the
door
should be possible
[Music]
yeah hey
speed one spring
but there's some stuff here too
let me get the money
we're almost at maximum money again
[Music]
okay anything else and we can uh what
are you doing
we can go higher eventually but
maybe the game wants me to go into this
door first
frodies
not gonna say it
not gonna say it no i'm gonna give you
that satisfaction
one of these funny sounds
oh ah those shitty things do you make
this sounds red i don't like these
little things spiky balls
oh i don't like them at all how do you
fight them again you just
go like a a swirl attack
to get them off of you i think
what can you kill them
okay come at me
but i really
suck at doing the swirl attack
ah okay we can just load it like that
i remember okay
your turn now and then some more come on
let me get you
and
you
now they should all be dead and we get a
dungeon item or something
and we already have the dungeon item i
get a rupee okay
uh no something like the compass or do
we not have a compass in these dungeons
i forgot did we have one last time in
the last dungeon
no right does when i cannot have the
compass because i have the
map anyway
wrong wrong wrong wrong
other side
there's always compasses oh okay
do these make me move slower i think so
it's kind of cute though how they stick
to me
it's like those bells oh
those fishies
that stick to other big fish
mommy can i can i have an owl ah
the greed
ah it's gonna kill me the green is gonna
kill me
i need hearts
it's because link always goes a few
steps further than i wanted to go
[\h__\h] i really need some hearts now
where are we going where are we going
what does this room even look like not a
hodor
okay let's ah let's go there first
uh
left okay
there's a bomb
i guess bump
uh i suppose we blow up that
door
is that close enough yes
it's another treasure chest
[Music]
i was wondering about you
what what do you mean akaihato is here
oh because of the hearts oh
okay
let me look at the map then
not a hodor
okay
i wonder if we still need the bomb yeah
over there can i like throw it all the
way there
without getting
don't go too far
ah
[Music]
[Laughter]
is there a shortcut no not really about
here no
[Music]
this distance
they ate it
it doesn't
i can't throw it that far
to have it land on that platform i think
[Music]
oh it goes through them really
okay it does
but that one did not hit oh it did it
did okay
i kind of know the way now
no not here not here
by the way because of all that italian
accent that i've been doing today as
well i will
be doing italian snack box review next
week
yeah dance
i already looked inside and it looked
really delicious
i'm actually looking forward to it
italy is like right next door
to austria but
it's still not that easy for me to get
to get italian snacks but italy isn't
italy the the country where all those
amazing chocolate companies are like
ferrero
fed by roll
for example
wasn't that italy
smoky yay
i think so yeah
so it's like
guaranteed guaranteed to get
some good snacks especially chocolate
italian
[Music]
two of those
thingies what why
i'll go to the lower one first
okay
what am i supposed to do with these
what am i
what am i supposed to do
are they just there to be
in the way for me to have a harder time
to land on the platforms
but it's no problem though
nothing is left go to the next room
i take yellow coin
uh moving
i mean i guess it doesn't go any higher
than that maybe it's just like uh the
one up there has like uh
what's what's the next stop the yellow
rupee probably it just has more money in
it okay then we can leave i suppose
but wait where is the next room
hey there's no next room here
this was there's no other door in this
room according to my map so
i just have to go back
ah you again
um
yeah
enjoy pendant oh those butterfly
pendants i don't really care about them
yeah i think at least not now maybe i'll
regret it one day uh i came from there
i think
and then i went in there
and to go
higher
ah wait we have the key for this door
what's that thing for ah we brought that
over there okay we have the key
he added you'll be wanting a few joy
penis later yeah
oh
[\h__\h] uh
panic
now come here
i can't even fight you there you are you
gonna die
down there
no
okay and then that's kind of
[Music]
[Applause]
annoying that enough
[Music]
to the other side we got
always get rid of the grass i'm such a
great gardener i want
to have a garden
but i say that but it will probably be a
lot of
work
oh [\h__\h] you want me to stab you i i know
i know but i forgot how to do that
[Music]
oh there we go there we go
what are you
okay these really are no problem though
poke eyes
stupid little
spiky ball
okay well
we uh first got rid of these fans
yeah
one stick for you oh this one is nothing
just a
bouncy plant okay
[Music]
oh oh oh oh okay second level hello
you guys gave me no time
[Music]
okay
what are those
we've seen them before those hanky
hangy things
what are those
ah do i need like to cut them off and
then uh we can use them as like one of
those balls
okay okay
are you going down
that was close
okay i killed one of them
good job me
can i not just take these
can i
how do i cut them off
without uh putting them up
yeah
i need the boomerang oh okay well then
let's go here first
maybe i'll get the boomerang there i
would hope so
oh
boss fight minibus
hello
the sparkling
like a mix of a moth with fireflies
oh it's [\h__\h] scary
[Music]
oh wait maybe i do that was not that was
not help but sometimes it's an attack
button maybe
[Music]
oh no i said
oh
wow let's go hello
[Music]
i am a warrior after all who doubted me
who doubted me hey
where's that thing here
give me all the shiny things oh phoenix
feather
and some money
oh they gave me those win-win wind
thingies but i didn't even need the wind
i was i wonder if we could have kind of
fallen with the wind
blower as well
what's easier than i thought it would be
i was me i doubted you why would you
doubt me after all the all this time huh
i got the boomerang
until the red targeting curse it changes
to um
yep okay
target up to five objects at once wow
oh oh i see i see what's up
i see what's up
uh okay
now we have three actually useful items
so we would do this oh wait but how
ah
i just go from one to that one and then
anywhere else
no
okay so just those two need to be
activated in a short amount of time
now i can leave woohoo
and now we can cut off those balls
oh yeah oh yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
can i go into this one thank you
[Music]
if you really want
the ones that are on this level
for anything
i don't think so but the fact that they
are on this level too kind of
confuses me
[Music]
don't forget the boomerangs also happen
ah yeah
oh
okay we need two of them
can i wait
actually oh
i was thinking there's two so how do i
bring them both like hold on i don't
even need them
oh dear
[Music]
go
they don't they grow back really fast so
i have to get rid of them all
fast no
maybe not
i kind of feel like there was something
like that
ah
okay so there's actually some kind of
realistic
um
physics there it will bonk the tree
and there's one left there's one left
over there
there we go
nice okay so they're all gone now
oh they all fell down there oh i don't
want to go there
[Music]
can i make that jump with my flying
thingy
i'm scared i don't want to fall down
[Music]
nice
next room patch patch next room
[Music]
oh we're up pretty high oh you want me
to uh-huh
i understand
leave it to me
oh [\h__\h]
i see now i can jump on that to pass by
what is that platform for
there's only like a some leaves there
that can blow away so maybe some money
and that's it
no way that's it
okay what if i jump down here now would
it catch me
or should i walk back
shortcut
shortcut jar oh that's over there under
the leaves
okay
let's see if i can reach come on i
believe in you link
smart
isn't that at the very beginning the
other one and then that's where the
thing is then
i can't i don't have words where are the
words oh it's in the ground okay i was
like how do you hide that
under those leaves okay they have placed
it there
okay
um
let me look at my map
how do i see which ones i which
chests i opened and which one i haven't
it doesn't look like there's a
difference i'll just see which rooms i
didn't go into
um
where do i see the teleporting thing
i don't see it
is it not marked
well we'll go in here
[Music]
[\h__\h] annoying
i can't fight here
i don't care about you guys
where are we going
[Music]
counter you knew
ah it's not here where's that thing
i have to go
up again
sneeze
sneeze sneeze jaw feel free to call me
sneeze jump
ah
stretch
stretch nice okay
echo uh
are we going i'm going there
i lost track of where i need to go
we're pretty
close to getting through the dungeon i
think though
thank you mina thank you the in-game
pollen
yeah
man look at all these pollen
they look nice though
do i really
i don't know where to go
i have to go the same way again
[Music]
my nose
a triple
triple sneeze
where we going this way
or is there any other way
ah that one
i'll go there
[Music]
i'm actually one of those lucky people
who don't really have any allergies at
least not to my knowledge
so thankfully i also don't really have
problems with poland
[Music]
oh my nose
lucky me
and well who knows it can still like um
[Music]
i can still develop allergies so i
shouldn't
i should not
celebrate just yet
you never know and i hope like if if i
ever get cat allergy i'm gonna cry but i
will do anything i'll take medicine and
whatever it needs me to
take
to survive
the cats
because cats like after
after living with cats my whole life
there is no way that i can live without
them now
um
[Music]
could not live without my cats me
neither
me neither man
okay
did i make a mistake by going all the
way back to the beginning
did i not have done that
yes i did
it offered itself to me
and i felt like that's what i needed to
do
[Applause]
on this level is where the the boss room
is but it's currently not visible to us
it's like somewhere else but on this
level
now we're on the one one higher
yeah
[Music]
they're just going back yeah i dropped a
big flower i want to see where the [\h__\h]
that flower is
here
oh
this is where those stupid
horns are
over here
here it should be here now
yeah can i not just go there
first i can
tell
i just go down here
no wait this is the level where the
bathroom is there's a door here
ah
or or the bus key i'm not sure but we'll
go there cause we can
we don't go into the hole yet
can i uh
well protect me
all right
[Music]
it feels like boss time yeah but i don't
have a boss key what it says on my map
if i continue walking
down this path
there's a there's a box i think
yes that boss davos or a boss is this
the boss key
no the boss case is a special box too
right um special treasure chest
[Music]
shut up
oh
ah
but we don't have the key
so
is being here a mistake
what are all these
things
[Music]
ah just to get some items
and hearts if i need to okay
okay
uh i guess we need to jump down and then
come here
yeah there was another teleport point i
don't have to activate them right or do
it
do i have to activate them
oh i thought i didn't have to
okay okay
let's do that
uh-huh
scoozy
oh all right there's something on top ah
wait i can get the stick and then burn
it oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
matsura
[Music]
yeah
well that water is fine because it's
kind of shallow
about a bubble
[Music]
where is this
okay but i think i want to go back
though
[Music]
yeah i was gonna go to the oh
bottom
now i guess that's fun
[Music]
okay and now we just fall down here
okay
we have reached the lowest point
of the dungeon supposedly yes b1
there's a big ass
flower is it bouncy
i can't jump that's right i guess i'll
just go yeah
whoa whoa
okay is this where the boss key is well
there's free treasure chests here
okay
that's fun
i guess but
uh
[Music]
oh god
it doesn't hit them oh ah he can't fly
anymore if i do that on him
[Music]
he grew back his wings for [\h__\h] sake
don't you annoy me like that
can i make that jump with those no i
can't no no no no no
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] do you all want from me
neat key wow squeaks his game sound
effects
um
i think there's like people who make
these um youtubers sound effect websites
i remember seeing one of myself
a while ago how do i not make them go
too far i want them to be somewhere
where i can fight them
i'm here
you're in the wake up here
wait the water is actually fine i
thought it was really toxic and the
moment that would be in it it would kill
me
[Music]
okay okay okay you're coming here now
no
seems like it goes back when it comes
too close to this place
[Music]
oh wait it actually looks like that too
hold on
i'm going this way
arms
do they also grow back endlessly because
i feel like they do stop it
just let me go let me go there is no exp
in this game so [\h__\h] fighting enemies
i'm too used to
games where you get like exp from
fighting enemies so it makes it kind of
worthwhile but
in zelda games you really don't need to
spend that much time grinding
[Music]
i see
make that drop so i can uh bring the
bomb over to the other side
fast brain is fast oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
scared me there for a moment what is it
oh
okay i'll just do it with the sheep
okay come here
shoot at me
yo
okay
oh i wonder after we're done with the
bump
we can make the
the big flower move like a boat over
there
yeah
okay first we do this
[Applause]
this is my mom and me two of the most
durable twin sister dogs ooh
cute
no problem
we have been working on this dungeon and
before that we just got the the swift
sail that's basically
all we did
[Music]
wait i'm not good with this
i'm not good with this
[Music]
the selection like when i uh okay i'm
not sure
sometimes how to make it select things
but
um
all right
oh phoenix
[Applause]
um i suppose i can fight you as well
with the boomerang
wow
strong
very strong
it's really not
wait i hear the sound crackling let me
fix that phone capture
boom head john
what's what's the problem with what is
he doing
i think that's drifting again
[Laughter]
i'm sorry i was writing some dm's
[Music]
my windows
closed
chat okay there you go
he's nervous okay he's shaking
his knees are shaking
and
[Applause]
i wasn't sure if i already took care of
that one
seems like oh
how did i go down again
no
ah no
[\h__\h]
how do i go on my knees again
is that our bad sword
said i okay
oh
[Music]
can the boomerang go through the
this this uh space
because now it's closing up
no i can't open it
[Music]
is it a puzzle
i want all of you
never mind never mind
[Music]
okay well let me try i mean i kind of
don't think it works but
maybe it will
from above
[Laughter]
okay we'll just uh
we have to think around oh yeah we gotta
think outside of the tree not outside of
the box outside of the tree
oh
can i even get up from here
i feel like i can't
ah
that is
one f
how the [\h__\h] do i get to one f from here
i think i'm gonna wait and i didn't say
that
i didn't
[Music]
okay
okay okay okay wait wait i don't know
where to go
[Music]
here
yeah
okay
so now
ah there's a bomb okay we go to the
other side we get the bomb we drop it
in
and there shouldn't be too difficult but
maybe i have an idea
first of all let's get the platform over
here
is shaking again okay okay
now we got a boom yep
and maybe some hearts huh huh
anyone yeah
no okay
egg bump oh can i just drop it here
drop it like it's hot yes
that satisfying sound effect
in there too
that was not much of a trick that was
too easy guys you can't even call it a
trick
i mean trick
no treasure george
oh for on the sea oh yeah right that was
treasure
maps ah
where is the bus okay there's one more
treasure chest in this
let's see
in this uh on this floor one more
so now i i think we have to use the
flower as a
boat to get to the last treasure chest
[Music]
it disappeared i have to get it again
everything was reset
first take care of you
this time i'm not making such a fool of
myself again
blind aim
there you go
all right
this is not um the ideal type of boat
but i think it works
okay
oh [\h__\h]
yeah
okay
sometimes you have to use unconventional
methods
reflects show shoot shoot me
mm-hmm
yeah
yes yes my reflexes are getting better
move your shitty flower
okay
i have arrived
[Music]
um
there it is the special chest
oh yeah
you think this is a challenge for me
does it always go in the order uh that i
activate them in that i uh choose them
in oh oh i see it
there's something there i have to go to
the top oh there's another one
okay there's five perfect i have to just
hit them from here
it does okay
one two
three
four
five
oh okay
stupid three
one
three is this gonna be a problem four
five four four
four
five
we
start here this has to work two three
four five yeah
really that easy that's how they give me
the boss key chest the other one was
more difficult to transfer treasure key
chest
that was so easy
okay but
what comes with this boss key
is perhaps not so easy
all right oh
oh hello i see that's where the
challenge is
you bring me the enemies afterwards
[Music]
did i do it
not quite
[Music]
okay i'll be using the boomerang a lot i
think
in the future
[Music]
you're still alive
okay
button smashing ooh
yeah you blame me for that um
add this one wait i don't need the money
give me some other stuff
oh i thought that was a what is this
hole a secret hole where i have to
uh
sneak into
did that fool you guys too for a second
or no all right
i'll have to go up
oh okay okay okay
[Music]
oh
ah
[Music]
oh the way back oh yeah probably because
the flower would have reset if we went
back the original way
so they make a different room to go back
okay well i mean
that works too at least i don't have to
jump on these platforms with those
annoying bastards
all right
uh
it's time for
the bus
second floor
two floors higher uh
[Music]
how did we quickly get there
both time
and i don't know where to go tomorrow
just to get on here comfortably what is
that one for
yeah what
oh he said how long does that go i see i
see i see jump jump jump into it
okay okay i get it i get it i get it
where do we go where do we go
[Music]
wait there's nowhere to go it ended
early
and ran out
[\h__\h] i have no energy
it will load up
inside oh but i need to
uh
okay but i still don't know where to go
[Music]
ah nothing lets me go higher okay okay i
was wondering like what am i missing
uh
this way
is this boss difficult guys
she's already here yeah i think i'm like
i haven't been
uh
like particularly stuck
anywhere and uh
you know been going pretty pretty fast
last dungeon as well last time we played
the game
today
i needed some time to get back into the
controls because i mean hey it's been
two
two weeks yo
really why is the grass not dropping
anything
just boomerang and swoosh your story all
right sounds easy enough is this a joke
is this a joke
on
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah the next room has some stuff
i know i know
maybe that that was on purpose was that
programmed like that
surprise surprise
um i would like some
wind
i wanted to use that counter but i'm
never fast enough to react to it
you hit it oh
there you go
okay i'm ready to go
[Music]
we have a fairy
maybe we don't even need to use it but
okay let's see
i'm kind of used to putting the
the boomerang there do i need the
the wind or the the the hook shot
because i might
oh but it's automatic did you guys say
it's automatic
in this game i don't have to activate it
was it automatic
okay okay good thank god okay
uh but let me save
save shield
bus fight
okay
okay okay
i'm curious i don't remember the bonus
i just like um
oh
friend
no no
i don't remember what it was i'll
probably remember once i see it
[Music]
what does he taste like
all right okay oh it's getting poisonous
oh
okay okay
i need to drop it down
make it drop down and then
attack the tentacles probably yeah yeah
okay
i can't select them
i'll wait i don't have to okay
because i was focused on the enemy go
[\h__\h] i think that didn't hit anything go
okay
[Music]
can it accidentally hit some that are in
the way i think though
okay we got him and now
[Music]
guys it's a boss fight
pay attention
[Music]
i don't know what's happening around me
why is everybody so calm
it's
time for panic
[Music]
well
i hope they get a bit more challenging
just just
gamerobin
presented to you by whole live english
[Music]
and still he just stands there and
waits
[Music]
we have five hearts okay that looks much
better
three and four hearts was really
live and um limit
living very dangerously but uh five
hearts is decent i can work with that
mm-hmm
oh he's coming with me
are you too heavy
you can kill it even faster using forest
water kills it instantly excuse me
you mean if i would have captured
if i would have captured that icky
looking water with my bottle and poured
it on that
monster what
okay but the game doesn't really give
you
a hint for that
at least i didn't see it so
i'm not that water at the water in this
room ah okay
yeah um i think you only really know
that if it's your second time playing it
so yeah
it's an easter egg yeah yeah okay
okay
uh
oh my car
you have returned safely you snack now i
can munch on you
that's the actual reason this ceremony
is taking place anyway i just want to
eat you little snacks
[Music]
[Applause]
just be more careful from now on you
have done well
one i must thank you for your brave
deeds
here is that which i have promised you
please accept it
oh my god
we're getting the second thingy
uh for roars
something tear not teal ball
dragon ball pearl okay rose pearl the
earth spirit the deku tree has seen fit
to give you this jewel a treasure of the
goddess ferrari and honestly i don't
know why
i was worried about this dungeon it was
so easy
it's really like these childhood
memories
they really uh
make you
remember things completely differently
um
childhood trauma yeah
weird so almost like if you were a child
i don't know it's probably like anything
that was dark
like the the fortress in the beginning
anything that was dark was just scary to
me
i was probably just like
as soon as i walked into something like
that i probably immediately
gave my controller to my brother
i just wanted to sail on the water
um
the floor monsters still scare me i
don't know what that is
i'm afraid of the dark yeah
i'm not really now but
i mean when it's dark in horror games
that's that's not so not so nice
[Music]
it is my hope that this pearl shall lead
you to a fair destiny
all is well makari do not cry
please play your songs for me as you
always do
[Music]
that's so cute that's such a cute violin
oh
[Music]
i love that or maybe it's not a violin
is it a bass not a bass what's that big
cello jello is that a cello i think it's
a cello
[Music]
i will
oh
[Music]
that's it
fools
um
[Music]
oh
is playing always now
[Music]
oh so cute
it was too short what the [\h__\h]
i was just getting ready this instrument
is the one that created three games
[Music]
he said it was an instrumental people
played long long ago
wait wasn't there a zelda game
that was about instruments like you had
to um
collect instruments all right we played
that one
but that was the yeah the dream the
dream one
is that what he's talking about
[Laughter]
but that was just a
spoiler
dream
so
was there another game where they played
instruments
[Laughter]
[Music]
was there cello
is there a cello it was just ocarina
yeah you're just playing ocarina
um
and maybe i'm thinking about the season
schemes
forests in yeah world
but both hello who studies the making of
persians and i are always on this island
please come to see us here again we'll
be waiting for you
potions
mommy where is that potion guy and what
do i need to uh
make him make some potions hello
hollow liver
look only on them so it's a
[Music]
where are you
is there a shortcut to get to him
there better be
hello hello
what is it outside is he outside
william what's this
[Music]
round for just a sign outside this cave
ah
[Music]
okay
uh is that the accent
and that must be the exit
what does it say
[Music]
hello
i love these sounds man come walk here
can you walk here
i want you to watch me no okay okay
[Music]
that would happen
but the ones i have here only seem to
work on my final class
i know
if you can somehow gain magic power
swordsmen oh
[Music]
ingredients that have become a magic
power here in the forest
oh for hot seats from the flower in my
face in the forbidden woods then maybe i
could make a portion for you
do you know
[Music]
wait i don't have any do i
forbidden woods but that's where we
would just wear right
did i collect them
let me look
i have um
what is this
[Music]
what are those
you have to show it to him
aren't these the ones
oh
sorry
thank you so much for bringing up
um
[Music]
if you don't have
ah too bad that i'm such a pro gamer
that i didn't use up by very in this
fight
hmm
i don't know is this potion worth it
when he says magic power does he mean
the the green bar
because i don't know that doesn't really
feel necessary
to have a bottle of dad carrying around
with me
at the moment at least
maybe
later
i messed up both health and magic oh i
don't need it right now
okay okay but i understand um another
time then
and i'll put back here okay
bye-bye good to know
good to know i didn't even remember this
one i don't think my brother ever used
the these potions at least i don't
remember them also how do i exit
this step
i want to leave where is the accent let
me look at the room oh but the map
doesn't show
um this room properly do i need to go
up follow the water out oh
ah
oh yeah right i came through the water
and you don't really need them do you
didn't know about them as a kid either
i suppose as a kid your attention span
is really short and you don't really
listen
so
you just you hear about the potion shop
but you don't really
you know
acknowledge it
and just move on without ever using it
i can see that yeah
okay
[Music]
okay kiwawa [\h__\h] chill that was so
easy
chill
that was too loud
what's up good evening
one better oh my god i'm getting hungry
okay and i have snags you've got mail
dear kiwama
if you're reading this
you have peeked into one of our many
post boxes i did i did
so what arrest me
i'm adapted to you i'm very sorry that
i let you leave without thinking
let me open my snap
uh please accept my heart but who's
talking to me
we cannot do much
to help we'll help you but we can at
least do this if we get any letters or
parcels for you oh okay okay okay
is it the big bird the the post bird
[Music]
i'm eating these salami sticks
so there are pieces too
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
someone said check behind
got it
how
i can't
you mean
what if i die
oh oh wait let me go back let me go with
the [\h__\h] oh maybe here
no i'm gonna go with the [\h__\h]
i swing into it okay
not now
don't worry okay
mm-hmm
for the next four times okay
yeah next pearl
northwest
okay i'm on the way
i wish i'll be okay
does he want me to go a specific
direction first again
or can i just go straight there
[Music]
hmm
i'm unleashed it took me off the leash
how nice of them
[Music]
we find something interesting
in between then we will stop
ahoy
let me just eat my salami
i don't have to change it
i forgot again
[Music]
hmm
but we have maximum money anywhere ah
nevermind no mind
is there ever anything else besides
money
we should buy something
we should go to the auction
let's go
let's get the heart container
the treasure chest i'm not sure how to
read the treasure map that we got
um
there's a storm
i know
scary okay storms are kind of scary
especially when you're
in the middle
of a huge ocean
with the danger of shipwreck on you
um we're going to rainfall island
[Music]
okay
okay i ate my
my salami for a little while longer i'll
be fine how long have we streamed uh
already three hours holy [\h__\h]
time passes by fast
[Music]
i don't think i can go too long today
though
because i actually have a lot to do and
i also have some appointments tomorrow
so i don't wanna
i don't wanna stay up too long
um
i don't
think i don't think we can squeeze in
a whole another
dungeon
but maybe a little bit of exploring i
don't know
okay do it do it
let me know
that's just whatever
three hours is not the short str it is
george yeah for me it's a short stream
um no no it's turning
day again but okay we'll change it to
night time and then we'll participate in
the auction again
free dungeon explorer yeah yeah
a little bit super chat reading yeah it
depends on how early we stop yes there
will be i have to catch up a little bit
anyway
did i talk to him here before
i should buy some fake
i guess
um
[Music]
but first we see what they have to offer
at the auction
mazu
i want to waste
money by collecting it but then not
actually collecting it
this is a nearby ferry fountain
oh yeah we should do that
very fountain
[Music]
oh wait i should save
if we really if we really [\h__\h] up badly
otherwise i won't i want safe scum but
just i in case oopsie no did i did i
save i don't think i did
[Music]
maybe i did
auction time
the salami had some
some weird stuff in it
yes i'm spending money again
yeah you don't need to explain anything
take my money take my money off of me
please
give me something good a heart container
would be nice
action really easy to choose yeah so now
i'm gonna wait now i know a little bit
more about this so i'll wait a bit more
what do we have
[Music]
a piece a piece
okay that's good that's good these
people these other people don't even
need this
they don't even have hearts
i i'm the only one i'm the protagonist i
have hearts okay
you guys don't need it
[Music]
i'll just chill for now
until he warns me
that's when i start bidding and studying
them
[Music]
86 okay no no no
no no i won't let it stop don't worry 90
rupees okay
[Music]
look about the day from having a heart
attack nah don't worry about them
they're healthy
[Music]
they're npcs they never die
and they never change
okay
do i hear another big
the other day um
when
when i was at that anime convention
um
and we had a dinner
oh [\h__\h] oh it's filling up on its own as
well
we had dinner with some people partially
people that i didn't even know
and um it was like we were so many
people
i think we were like it felt like we
were at least 10 people probably like 12
13 14 or something like that
and half of the people i didn't know
because i was invited and they invited
other people that i didn't know
look at link's face
and um you know when there's so many
people they always like chit chat
obviously i mean okay i can't blame them
but you know what really triggers me
maybe also because i was uh like doing
some waitress uh job before as well
but you know they take an order okay
then they leave and then they because
there are so many orders they come one
by one slowly uh bringing in the dishes
that are finished already and i just
hate it so much they come in and they
say okay who uh apple apple juice
and they say it again and again and
again and the person who ordered [\h__\h]
apple juice just does not [\h__\h] listen
and it triggered me so hard after a few
times because it happened like so often
it it triggered me so hard
that after a few times i started like um
like yelling out really loud i was like
who the [\h__\h] ordered apple juice apple
juice some acid subscribers in britain
and then they would finally
um react
so that at some point ended up being my
job i think the waiters appreciated that
because we were wasting their [\h__\h]
time i didn't want to waste their time
you know nobody's [\h__\h] listening
and then and then they're like if i
wouldn't do it their stupid reaction
like the the waiter would be like all
right who has this unagi don unagi don
[Music]
10 million times the dude would finally
realize uh oh what oh that's i guess
that's me
but because also the problem is
often they don't even like remember the
name of what they ordered because um
they don't realize it because they're
yelling it out kind of in japanese
yeah and then they're like oh oh sorry
[Music]
i guess that's me
come on
yeah
oh oh it triggered me so hard oh
just pay attention when the waiter is in
the room
stop wasting their time
ah that's why you write table numbers it
was basically only one table we had like
a like a special room
um
with tables connected but it was one
room
yeah listen to them
and remember what you [\h__\h] ordered oh
my god
i don't know like even if you're in the
middle of a conversation like still
wouldn't you notice
come on
pay attention
oh 30 30 seconds okay my other stool
like
not bad for a kid
well okay yeah i guess
i only added two but in total it's
pretty pretty not bad
okay
every time's running out no no no no no
no
no baby
shut up guys
my turn now
will he warn me one more time
is there a second warning
no i was like partially in a
conversation but i still always noticed
whenever they would come in and when
they had my stuff i immediately said
hello that's me me me me
raise his hand it's me that's my food
but don't waste your time
he wants you when there's five seconds
left okay
[Music]
it's coming
i think i think it's time to stun them
[Music]
go
wait how many [\h__\h]
i'm so impatient i should just wait
just do one
[Music]
come on
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
yes
oh my god so stunning
wow wow amazing so much money and sold
tonight's fabulous piece of art goes to
kiwama for the price of 201 rupees mamma
mia let me just say congratulations
[Music]
wow
sorry that took me some time to sit up
[Music]
thank you
you can stop now uh
could i immediately walk into another
auction or do i have to leave the island
once
guys i mean now i don't have that much
money anymore
but maybe we can try a new one
saving though
leave them come back not till next time
okay okay
continue
[Music]
uh i wonder what's next
maybe money
wait waiting for money that doesn't make
sense
[Music]
let's go
day it'd be
so remember men's file yeah yeah yeah
she did that as an impression for her
talk oh yeah um whole talk by the way
well because of the wind waker weekends
now i can't really do hall of talk for a
while
once we're done with the wind wake
awakens maybe then i'll return with holo
talk
i didn't think about that when i decided
about the wind wake awakens but
i've kind of been in a difficult spot
with holotalk anyway right now
there's like basically free people
um unless i skip all of them and just go
with someone else but i shouldn't
there's three people that i should go
with right now
i am in senpai coronado
and all of them are kind of difficult
for me to talk to in some way
um for some reason
um but yeah i'll get them eventually
no it's like
oh yeah i don't know i've been trying to
avoid
this
but
here we are what's with you by the way
do you need help
nobody understands how i feel do me a
favor beat it well okay
i don't know my nose well i guess he
isn't the right guy
what do you want can i help you
you pesky little brat nobody understands
how i feel don't you hear me nobody not
you oh he's so edgy
wait are you trying to tell me that you
do understand how i feel yeah it's like
it's not a phase i have i i feel you
i can totally relate
now for piccolo
it's like i'm kind of nervous about it
for corona senpai
it's mostly that like our schedules
haven't really
aligned so far
and for my example i i don't know
um
i
i kind of felt like she probably
wouldn't even accept i haven't even
tried yet
but
might be fine i think like she does a
lot of collabs like if anything she does
more collabs than solo streams
uh
but yeah she's also not no you know not
not she doesn't seem
so active so i'm not sure if she has
time
but i i'll have to
i'll have to try again i'll have to ask
quite a bit ahead of time which is good
now that i'm doing the wind waker
weekend but i'm not sure when they're
ending
worst case i'll just skip one day like
one saturday
[Music]
need need about three meetings to get
familiar with anyone
did you hear that in a clip
nobody says chicken shut up you're a
chicken
and
completely
oh really and i'll write a little text
and see if you really don't oh [\h__\h]
i want you oh a pictograph of the first
perfectly round pale thing you can think
of and show me
a round pale thing one of those pigs
okay
[Music]
bring me a pizza okay okay we'll do that
we'll do that because we won't do
another dungeon we'll just do some other
stuff
how about
i mean i also kind of was thinking of a
chicken
um because they're pretty round too but
i think he means
there's these piggies is there like a
completely
pale one
[Music]
far
off oh
do you like my thought process
the moon
oh it's not even full moon wait does
that change
because now is i needed to be full moon
are you kidding me
how many times are we gonna do this
[Music]
come on
down
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is the thing with wind waker in
ocarina of time and all these games
where you have to make melodies
keep on making mistakes
i boy boy
couldn't have just by coincidence
been the full moon on the first try huh
[Music]
nope
i can't say it
i can't see
almost
[Music]
the famous one
i only know this one
[Music]
okay
how about now come on
where is it
the [\h__\h] is the moon
if that's not
perfectly pale
how close do i have to get i wonder oh
my god the
doritos here how about this all
beautiful
[\h__\h]
no
[\h__\h] drift
no not
oh my god oh it's motion oh it's motion
controls
i think it has to be like perfectly
round so
here
i wonder if that
like wind thingy would
be a problem
probably fine
but i better take a couple ones
yeah
perfect i mean
that's a perfect picture of a moon
okay
that took so much
time any color
could i have
set it to color though
no
[Music]
[\h__\h]
why
i can upgrade it no [\h__\h] way i'll
have to go all the way around to full
moon again
okay
[Music]
it's pale i mean
it's pale
there's nothing paler than that
[Music]
when do i get the upgrade
oh man that triggers me hard because i
waited so long for it to be full
[Applause]
[Music]
the camera guy where is the camera guys
oh this one
oh that's so [\h__\h]
that's so [\h__\h]
what a waste of time
now i have to go all the way around
again
once you dead
i want to upgrade it
[Music]
can i have an upgrade on it
what do you want
[Music]
wow
nice pictures
[Music]
alrighty
finely snapped pictographs you must
admit it
would come now you needn't be so
surprised my young sir
it is a hobby of mine to sneak up behind
people
when they least expect that it's so
creepy
it's quite an amusing diversion think
nothing of it
by the way the pictographs you see
decorating these fine walls have all
been taken by none other than myself
they are my pride and joy
[Music]
you'll see my younger days i was
tireless sailing far and wide across the
great sea snapping pictographs wherever
i went
have a look at them youngster
[Music]
oh god choo choos
is he gonna test me on this later
that's a nice hut oh
a tiny rock island
resting far out in the zoo southeast
nice hint
south east
i'll find it eventually
a dignified butler standing before the
door and i snapped this
i'm certain this is someone's private
cabana
rising up out of the seas seeming to
claw at the sky it may spawn even
stranger silhouette what if such a thing
still remains out there on the high seas
lonely on the waves only i had the
chance i would love to see these things
once again
should i show him
[Music]
outside island
it is the most delightful of fishing
though this innocent racer of nature's
bounty
wait does he want me to go all of these
places and then he'll give me a new
camera
oh for [\h__\h] sake
need to show free photos to get the
upgrade free photos of these places like
uh like choose three places
take picture you have to take the same
picture
there's a chest
two chests
go downstairs okay oh he'll do your
tasks okay uh specific photos okay okay
we'll come down back here buddy
you have to look away
how did i get him to come back
[Music]
oh there he is boy
flash you've captained art yes yes what
sorry um can you give me those quests so
i can get that stupid ass camera
there we go
[Music]
and i'm thinking of creating a box with
incredibly
incredible picography capabilities is at
long last nearing frustration for
t-shirt
but now i've grown old and have no real
desire to leave this island young sir i
have a day to ask what could you yeah
i'll be your assistant okay goodbye
oh no
ha really really and truly thank you
thank you
my heart leaves at your enthusiasm but i
feel i must tell you the path and
assistant must follow isn't a simple one
i demand that whosoever takes on the
role of my assistant be an individual
who can take whatever command i may
issue and promptly complete it without
hesitation
it will be quite a challenge i assure
you are you still sure you want to do
this yes
parisian here we go
you must share my love of the pictograph
what is your name youngster kiwawa is it
yes
for your commands okay
now then for my first command
a love letter do you know what that is
youngster it is a collection of words of
love long unspoken and put into written
form
somewhere in this town there is one who
despite constant rejection never learns
the code lesson of unrequited passion
and continues to write letters of doomed
love
i'm certain the option of this sadly
one-sided affection is in quite a
quandary
over the matter i'm of the mind that i
must have a word of the unwanted suit
however i must have a physical evidence
and thus your first task is to snap a
picture wrap of this individual in the
act of sending unwanted letters
okay
on this island sounds easy
who's that dude
now i made her before
i don't see anyone actively writing any
right now
how about you
you look too happy
but maybe you have something else
[Music]
how many people in the town know that
that it kind of sneaks around behind the
building i think i'm the only one buddy
a little path besides the bombshell did
i know about this
which one is the bump jump
is he writing letters
no
[Music]
is this place again
oh he would be putting it into the
i was here for into the mailbox
okay
you're sending those super chatters
or those membership messages
how long do i have to wait though
just if i stand here
if i just stand here
would you stand with me and witness the
weirdo
oh is it him is he coming to the post
box
and i just take a picture of
him when he probably when he mails the
the letter
what's up
[Music]
is barely moving on
not him
i need to hide
can't be near the middle uh-huh okay
yeah have a hider i can hide
right here maybe does that work no
are you behind the tree
but then this dude will keep on talking
to me
move
shut up
that's not really hiding
okay i'm waiting
[Music]
is this a good position
act casual
hello
it's time to mail me your letter
[Music]
it takes a while
okay
i have time
some
some amount of time not too much though
who could it be i don't remember at all
[Music]
where is it gonna come from
must be him i forgot how to take a
picture i forgot how to take a picture
hey
focus
[\h__\h] it's not focused
[Music]
was that okay
is this okay
i didn't get him with the letter in his
hand
[Applause]
it wasn't even focused now it focuses of
course
don't think i have the right picture
damn it
wait
hello uh
boy do you happen to see the post box
down near the docks
well just so you know if you want to
censor it
thanks for telling me
okay
how nice of him
first time for me too really
shut up
[Music]
oh wind waker is so chill i love it
that's the music man
it's always plugged i'm i'm always
playing with it plugged
this clowns is constantly plugged
i need to show you maybe or
uh
[Music]
no not this one this one maybe has a
chance
[Music]
yes
i think this one works
[Music]
first test pass
okay thank god okay next test
next test
next command i'm going to search for
this town's most timid cowardly resident
i intend to vlog his spirit so let's
lend him some backbone
timid and coward i mean i can only think
of that old dude who keeps on asking me
to save his daughter but
no not coin
function gems and even the slightest of
surprises i need you to capture the
incident of pure fear on this
individual's face in a pictograph
that sounds difficult that's not the
dude that's not the old dude that's a
different one then
someone who was scared
i have i have not um
i've not seen everything on this island
it seems but you guys say the cafe
it's me
probably me
as long as i'm on this island i'm the
most oh [\h__\h] there's the wrong place i'm
the most scary the cat
chimpkin
the man
kimono where is that cafe
was it up here
no that's not the cafe
oh my god
get down there
get down in an instant
[Music]
there it is
so how do we capture
him being scared
like what if i bonk against the wall and
something falls down but then how do i
immediately grab the camera and then
take the picture at the right moment
you guys saying roll into the wall
though hmm
wait i'm scared though how do i take the
picture in
[Music]
okay it has to be closer
oh [\h__\h]
okay what
are you staying scared for a bit okay
okay he looks pretty scared
i'll take another one oh [\h__\h] okay i'll
take one more
okay that's good too
table is kind of in the way but one of
them should work
perfect really i'm such a photographer
photography is my passion too actually
i take like really good selfies
sometimes my friends ask me to take the
selfie instead of them because i just
have the better angles
totally they don't understand what a
good angle is
such amateurs
you need to understand your own angle
okay i did it oh wait i need to show you
yes yes yes
here which one is better
this one maybe
[Music]
oh yes
oh he likes it
[Music]
[Applause]
next test
next one please
what's the last one
open your heart and mind and listen to
what i say somewhere in the town is a
couple a man and a woman whose hearts
are secretly filled with thoughts of the
other and yet for reasons unknown the
two have never spoken
even when they haven't by chance to pass
each other in the road they need to
still breathe for
furtive glance oh am i supposed to
capture that
i can't let the strategy go on any
longer for the sake of the town and my
own desire to help these two persons i
shall become cupid arch of love these
two are timid burglars in the house of
love
and you must capture a pictograph of
them thinking their furtive faults
[Music]
okay if anyone help me on hope
you managed to complete this first task
then shall you be my number one pupil
okay
yeah that's very exciting thank you
and
okay
is it
what picture will they pass by one
another
stop following me
so
what about these two i know
that's that's not them
[Music]
put him in the usual room please
i think it's her but which guy
stop stop don't follow me
you have to take the picture from like
the top
oh those two
wait how do i how do i capture that
do i only need one of their faces on it
there must be those two
the kids
give up my location oh don't worry i
have i have it under control but
huh
we need both in the frame
oh the guy will come to see her okay am
i in the way
is he not supposed to see me
where am i where should i take a picture
from
[Music]
oh yeah that's a good angle
now we
wait and now we wait she looks like an
animal crossing character
[Music]
oh my position does not impact the event
oh okay
nice stalker angle thank you
i'll take that as a compliment
oh no that's children
[Music]
oh
yeah i mean that works no
does that work
what are the income
nice reflexes once again
angle not clean
we'll test it i mean i see both of them
but
maybe a bit more from the side
ah okay he doesn't like it
no no
first fail
i i wasn't sure you know
how
how we're gonna look at it but okay
if me being seen is not the problem
then i'll just take it from here
is that okay
try again
[Music]
oh
is it is it ng
is it non-forgivable of the kids are in
the photo
walk faster
[Music]
this is probably a problem
hello
it's about time
it's
[Music]
distract distract them kids come here
come here
[Music]
will they just stay with me now
[Laughter]
okay this works well though
[Music]
hi
hi they're circling me
how intimidating healthy can't be save
me
i smug faces
it's like i adopted them
are they mine now
but i only adopt chickens
human satellites oh yeah
when the [\h__\h] is he coming
am i doing something wrong
[Music]
so where the [\h__\h] is the focus there it
is
oh come on
[Music]
oh
oh there it is there it is there it is
look look
okay
this better be it
why do i always talk to you
[Music]
no words just pictures
pictures speak a thousand words right
like actions
oh
it works yeah
[Applause]
i shall probably take this pictograph
from you and use it most efficiently
now then my youngster you have completed
all of the tasks i set you to
my doctor but you have all been cleared
up i shall hereby be proud to call you
my sister kiwawa let's go
[Music]
let's go now we can do the other quest
which i already forgot what we're doing
i am taking a picture of the stupid-ass
moon
okay
go out there it's not pictograph snap
them in color for me for all the years i
spent unable to do so fulfill my life's
ambition
okay but there's no particular quest
anymore from you
maybe later
[Music]
time to take selfies
no
no no no
no i will take pictures
of this stupid-ass moon
and for that i will once again
have to change the time
well at least we're doing some side
quests yeah yeah
so
of course it's uh
yeah we just passed it this is gonna
take a while
[Music]
pour some more
liquid
i stink
[Music]
iced tea
hmm
old lady in front of the moon someone's
a picture she'll give you a c chart and
gives a piece of heart
what
what what a picture of what we'll figure
it out
once it's date to um again
[Music]
me versus mr williamson it was probably
to take selfies with the bosses in this
game and upload them for everyone's
parade
[Music]
is it her do they want the picture she
sounds sassy isn't she i can't believe
she's a skull patcher
rumor hasn't she has mountains of tacky
print pendants and earrings it says that
she loves nothing in the world more than
jewelry
now just what are you doing where you
listening to us your scalp
you listen young man haven't seen you
around so i guess you're new to windfall
but don't you know it's that eavesdrop
on conversations meant only for adult
ears
don't you bet no it's bad to gossip
though
oh [\h__\h] her face
we're discussing very very important
topics that kids just wouldn't
understand you're far too young to be
listening to us young men
do i have to look older to talk to them
[Music]
if you live in like
a village that's this small
and you mess it up with even one of the
neighbors like if you're new if you're
one of the newer ones and you mess it up
with one of the older ones and they
don't like you don't even have to mess
it up you just have to exist sometimes i
suppose
then
[Music]
i can imagine sometimes it's really hard
to make them like you again
or there is no chance for making them
like you again and you'll just
be the
the person everybody hates on in the
village yeah for small
small villages with small populations
[Music]
which can be really tough if it's a
small place like this
holding a grudge yeah
well so what do i want you want a
picture of yourself
i don't know he always shows up his
pictures of me just as soon as he's
taking them
[Music]
how do i look today you know yeah yeah
okay okay here
how is this even the game tells me it's
a good picture
wow is this how i look today i had no
idea that the gloss on my skin was so
perfect
just look at me
i'm so stunning is this cronie in 30
years
oh i feel so wonderful now i have to
reward you for making me feel so good
about myself
treasure
oh arigato
my son picked it up somewhere
okay
so now okay back to finding the moon
[Music]
back to the moon
luchi is like this already yeah yeah but
i mean you know
uh
because she's kind of old this lady
courtney ain't that old yet
i suppose it's probably not even
worth looking at the moon at this point
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
left right
down
oh yeah cronie probably doesn't even age
so nice
moon
i don't think it's full moon yet but
okay
yeah
[Music]
if the moon is like that how many times
is gonna take me can someone do the math
how many times until it's full moon
somebody
calculate it challenge for you
don't just sit around like that three
times really
six seven eight four
remember
what you said guys
[Music]
okay let me check after this one
down
[Music]
hi
almost next time next one
next one should be the one
[Music]
oh there was a quest for getting a full
moon in
our kills our students
did i do that one i don't remember
i don't think so
the game the moon phases on the game
were random
wow
that sucks
okay
fun
finally it's in color
it's round
yeah
okay
i think
it should be fine
took me way too long way too long
a second one ah it's too late
it has to work otherwise i'm gonna throw
this camera on the ground
hello dude oh wait let me show you
hey let me show you hi
hi oh it's beautiful though it's pretty
beautiful there's like nothing
else besides the moon it's perfectly
centered
amazing
oh that's right that certainly is the
pictograph i'm looking for the correct
answer is exactly what you've shown me
the full boy
unrequited love may have twisted me up
inside but i can still find the peace
when i gaze at the timeless moon
and of all her faces i particularly love
gazing at the full moon
i know i caused you a lot of truth
how do you know
[Laughter]
yeah it only took me about 40-50 minutes
or so let's get your stupid-ass picture
just because you wanted it colored
[Laughter]
i really mean it i want you to have this
for all your efforts oh that's it you
don't want any more pictures okay oh
another chat chart okay okay okay
[Music]
okay you know what we have free treasure
charts let's go get them
[Music]
okay
let's go get them and then i don't know
what we'll do after maybe that will be
it i'm not sure
hey boats nice [\h__\h]
okay so how do we do this um
uh
how do i add the iron
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] wait
how do i do it hold on
let's open it up but how do i this map
isn't open this map is is this my
partner
uh-huh
eh oh i don't understand it doesn't show
it on the big map it just
do i have to kind of guess where it is
can i find it myself
eh
like i only say like a part
like how do i know where that part is
oh coordinates
it doesn't say coordinates
[Music]
it helps to have most of the map charts
i have to figure it out once you're
closer you appear on it
uh but at this point where i have barely
anything
there's only one that i feel like maybe
maybe that could be it
is there is there one on dragon or maybe
that one
[Music]
i think there might be one on on dragon
roost island
me
maybe that's one of
them um
i'm not sure i guess let's just explore
oh but where do we go
i'll just go straight ahead
[Music]
set sail
for adventure and exploration
the whirlwinds are
i i should not go into them right i
think they bring me into a random place
on the map somewhere randomly
thank you for the membership welcome
[Music]
how do i not go there eh i can't move
at once i have bombs i can do something
uh
well where do we land i actually don't
care because i wanted to explore anyway
where do we go
[Music]
my map says i'm still in the same
okay oh we didn't move that much
i'll go i'll go this way
go go go go go go go power
[Music]
oh i do i have something to talk about
uh
there was something i said yesterday
that i wanted to talk about today
i don't know what it was
[Music]
look for the fish on every square of the
world map
ah but i have no bait i forgot to buy
bait
oh yeah therapy oh yeah yeah yeah
so hmm
oh hello i finished my um
once again another physical therapy
oh let's go what is that what is that
let me go there
it looks like
oh
tiny island
[Music]
um ah it's one of the photos that the
dude took
yeah so
you know i was kind of skeptical about
it because i've i've taken i've been to
several physical therapies oh i should
have read that
you can't
um
so i was like hmm
i know it will kind of be a waste of
time and and with the other physical
therapies that i had so far it was
usually like
one session in two weeks or three weeks
so there was like a lot of time in
between
um but this time it was two weeks four
days
uh
um in a row
from monday to first day
and
yeah
that's that's why i was also like pretty
busy the past two weeks partially
because that takes up
some time of my day
i tried to combine it with other things
like when i would go outside i
uh to the physical therapy i tried to
go
do some some other appointments combine
it kind of or buy some things that i
needed to buy anyway
what is this one traveler who seeks the
guidepost of the goddesses place the
pearl you hold here
oh
honey
what's gonna happen
what is this what is this thing
uh okay
oh i was supposed to do this like in the
future for
for the story's sake
a bit early
what are these dudes
are they dangerous
can i are these pirates are they going
to attack me
i want to go to them
yep
speedrun
it's the gallon
talk
your bump you must be searching for
treasure on the sea floor too aren't you
you won't get any from us but not like
please let me ask you something real
quick who won this around the fish
little sea
gouda i'll tell you who about only
pirates monsters and treasure hunters
like ourselves and maybe some other
things that i've never heard of
you know if all the weak island dwellers
who never leave their shores i'm amazed
to see such tiny little guy out there
like your style but i feel like i've
known you my whole life oh
[Music]
but you haven't i like your helmet
though give it to me
so hey bob tell you what as one treasure
hunter turned up i'll give you this
you'll be definitely needing it if you
want to hold up treasure
take it i won't take no for the answer i
also won't attack nay nope or not just
grab it
[Music]
i can barely read them though
unfortunately
um
plus suppose you can take your sweet
time pouring over the charts ah okay
um grappling hook oil in your boat to
haul up the treasure okay yeah
little treasure buddy good luck to all
of us happy hunting
weirdos i don't remember them don't
think i've ever met them before okay
there's a fish
here
is he always here can i like mark him or
can i can i just talk to him without
putting out the bait
no
uh
what happened don't have any paint
oh i wasted it
he wants to talk to me
and what if he jumps up can i like get
him in that moment
terry oh yeah okay i guess i'll buy some
at terry's
hello
get off the boat
okay so back to the uh topic
physical therapy
um it was kind of supposed to be in
preparation for a different therapy but
you know as i told you that one turned
out to not be covered by my insurance
and it's too expensive
i don't want to pay for them
um
stupid insurance can't believe they
don't cover it um but yeah um
at that point i was like okay
if i don't do any of the fair beans
my doctor will be like why didn't you do
anything
so even though i just came out of the
physical therapy which was by the way
one-on-one
this one was a group one
[Music]
um i would have preferred another
group one but okay
another solo one i mean
thank you
because i feel like you can
focus more on the person then and to be
honest
it was really true like i felt like um
during
these physical therapy sessions
uh
there were some things that
were not really
like related to my problems like like
lower back problems for example yahoo
he's happy so
um but okay like
it was just a general
therapy for for back problems like there
were mixed people
with mixed problems
in the group so yeah it was kind of
generic
and the last therapy that i had was
really focused on me and i just kind of
prefer that
but okay
um
and the other thing was that
like
um
ah i got some
the other thing was
uh what was i gonna say
what was i gonna say
a speech
thank you i will think
multitasking not my strong suit
turn turn turn i'd wait
here we go
are you are you gonna come here okay
yeah i have a lot of bait
take it
um
oh yeah give me give me a cheat sheet i
thank you
oh you're gonna paint on mine
oh he's just
okay he just uh
[Music]
draws the little islands on each map
okay yeah we need to find those
good very good desonaire
nothing handy for carrying fairies
around with you
i have one if you want one go south from
here until you see a miserable looking
submarine floating on the sea
look there
south from here okay thank you
[Music]
bye-bye
like how far let's just go south nada
hodo koko
susumu
uh why was i i really forgot what i was
gonna say
okay
i was saying
oh yeah the other thing i was gonna say
is um
[Music]
i kind of
anticipated this
i thought this would happen
i was pretty sure about it
uh is that the submarine
i mean let me go there because this
looks like i need bumps
and
the exercises were pretty much either
very similar or partially even the same
um from like previous physical therapies
so
i didn't really learn
anything completely new
you know
so it really felt a little bit
a little bit like a waste of
my time
but it's okay that's okay at least it
kind of forced me
to do some kind of
um
not
it wasn't really exercise that much but
some kind of
it's so very loud isn't it i didn't
lower it
[Music]
it forced me to do some of these
physical therapy exercises
four days in a row for two weeks so
that's at least something
[Music]
let's go second battle you
them up and then throw him on the ground
[Music]
well yeah yeah
finally it's over so now i have a bit
more time
and
and now i'm just waiting for that stupid
blood test that i did ages ago how did i
get there
i think i
need a different
tool to be able to uh maybe i can just
fly there
float there let me try
um
what was i saying damn it
damn it
what was i saying oh yeah oh yeah my the
stupid blood test that i did ages ago
wrong button xxx
let me change that before i accidentally
use it
ah nah that's not enough
okay hmm
the blood test was because like when i
started this whole thing at the general
doctor uh like last year
um he was like okay let's start from the
beginning
uh how about we do a blood test first
yeah
and
i want to find the fish here
let's see
that's the blood test first and then i
went to get the blood test and also
some kind of um
x-ray
of my neck
uh not so much the shoulders even though
i said i have shoulder pain
i mostly took it from
the neck
uh
i don't think that's it
[Music]
how do i move just a little bit oh there
we go
[Music]
no no
i hate it
[Music]
here
yeah
um
where was i
keep on losing track of what i was
talking about
oh yeah yeah we did the x-ray and a
blood test the blood test was just a
very general blood test
so then we
when i came back with the results she
said okay something here looks like
it could either it tires that fish it
could be
is that even still on this map
it could be some kind of rheumatic
disease
illness
i was like okay
what do we do
he sent me to
um a place that specializes on that i
guess
oops
[Music]
to get another blood test to see to take
a closer look at it because you have to
um there's so many rheumatic
diseases uh you have to figure out which
one it is
uh and that could perhaps
depending on which one it is be the
reason for my pain but it might also not
be the reason it might just be another
different thing
uh so i went there but you know when i
did the blood test next appointment was
like three or four months later
to just to get the results
as if they
you can you can get the results like
in like two days or so but i don't know
it's so stupid and they said in the
meantime
let's get started on therapy
because it might not be the rheumatic
disease okay
so you go to this place and do physical
therapy and this other therapy that i
couldn't end up i ended up not being
able to do
so i went there i did the stupid therapy
i'm not doing the other one so now i'm
just waiting for the other appointment
which is sometime in june for me
um so it's a running from one doctor to
another doctor once i have the results
of that test
i can go back to the first doctor to the
general doctor
probably
unless if it is really like something
serious some kind of serious dramatic
disease then probably they will start
treating me there or so i don't know
i don't know
yeah i'm already very busy in june and
uh
but these things have to be
have to get done
[Music]
it looks funny
is that one the one right behind me
you have to come sail these seats on
nights when the right half of the moon
is missing
how do i remember that
are we doing okay thank you
no i'm not gonna do another physical
therapy that was like my fourth or fifth
one i think my fifth one in my whole
life and they all do the same [\h__\h]
that's just some like extras like you
know in the previous therapy i had an
extra of like 15 minutes of
um like massage or electric therapy
or um
ultrasound therapy or something like
that
and
yeah and and then if you go to a
different place and they might have
something else but
uh basically it's always the same stuff
so
[Music]
once you know the moves there is no real
reason to go back there anymore
yeah
and i know the moves by heart now
um
it really helped when i had a friday or
maybe the first time but
if you go there five times
they're gonna teach you the same [\h__\h]
unless you have a different problem like
right now it's back problems if i ever
have leg problems okay then i could i
can go to a physical therapy that's
focused on on leg problems and learn
something new but otherwise if it's just
the same problem
it will always kind of be the same
physical therapy
i know the moves that got those moves
yeah
okay
the right half missing
should we wait here
yeah yeah
miki
well i mean what the hell
[Music]
otherwise i might forget it
what's gonna happen though
oh my god
where is the
oh i can click on the fish oh
really
ah when the right half of the moon is
missing now
but i want to get it done now i don't
see the moon though
this always happens
don't come i don't want to talk to you
it's not coming good
um i
so cloudy i don't see it you can't do it
now anyways oh really
oh okay i'll be scared oh is it like a
ghost ship
like we had in length so well not like
this awakening and um skyward sword
uh
what
[Music]
is
fish
[Music]
hello
nice to see you again fancy seeing you
again
hi
gohan dozer
[Music]
[Laughter]
yep
open up
um
what does it look like
another hodo
i need a big island
none of these look like the ones i have
on my
on my treasure charts
you know about nintendo gallery is this
again a thing that is not being in use
anymore
the only way in there is to hit a switch
that's way up high in the forest haven
is that useless
now
like the other thing that we had before
good night
a miiverse thingy
is an area within the game ah
i can do it
the only way to do that would be to
bribe one of the girls by putting a
little bait on your head
will they fly me up there i think i
remember something like that
okay bye-bye thank you
i'll keep on sailing
keep on sailing because i'm a sailor
appear on my head
ah
yes you can remember that
like something like that yeah yeah and
then the bird
does
something have i been here before oh
yeah that's the that's that one
oh oh it's not a treasure
oh which one is it is it gonna tell me i
see it i see it i see it it's here
[Music]
she says look at me i'm your treasure
you have my treasure
yeah
what you want to tell me to tell me yeah
i'll give you the tummy squid squatch
no don't run away oh she wants me to
chase your mouth
the moment i get up she runs away
such a cheeky cheeky brat
what if i close the door
i'll just go in there
go in there then you step
up
i caught a pokemon it's called chunky
wonky donkey monkey
hi baby
i miss you fluffy monster
hi
hi how are you
um
[Music]
let's lower the microphone for you you
want to say something chunky wonky
hmm
[Music]
oh
hmm
[Music]
are you annoyed by mommy yet
you want to go
do you regret coming into this room
very well
i shall let you go but don't get stuck
in my cables
oh no don't go change my mind don't go i
love you don't go
who's a baby where's the big baby you're
a big baby
hmm
[Applause]
okay now you can go maybe maybe maybe
just maybe
maybe okay you can go
okay i'll let you go fluffy baby
bye bye
bye bye i love you
i love you i love you
this movie by the way has also entered
the room
nice movie hi
hi
john grace has left the chat
smoothie scratches tree
smoothie say hi movie
schmovie
movie
hi
sorry i love my cats
can you blame me
it's been 4 hours 20 minutes
since i started to stream
it's time to leave what time is it 8 p.m
okay
uh
we'll get one more map and then we read
super chats
wait wait wait i didn't talk to the fish
in this one yet
but i guess it doesn't matter
oh well let's go to a neighboring one
now
let's try to get this one
i did okay
ah
[Music]
what
oh yeah we are
scary monsters many many many scary
monsters
there's no island here
it's just that floaty boat
uh oh dear
there's a chest hey well let's leave
though
let's get a different one
thank you for the membership welcome not
them and they look dangerous i need some
weapons that i can use on the sea before
i take on them
or take them on
me
take on me take me
[Music]
was that the lyrics
what's this
[Music]
purple ruby
okay i skipped a few words so let's see
oopsie doodles where am i i'm the i'm at
the corner of the map
let's go this way
[Music]
okay thank you thank you
give me title
[Music]
what's up
these are
your friends chips kids chickens
if you would diet a little bit you might
be able to fly just like them
yeah get rid of that
yummy chicken meat but nah what that
would be such a waste we need you guys
to make yummy burgers
um
you can yeah yeah and look at yourself
and then look at these verbs try to find
the difference it's it's the amount of
meat
[Music]
that's all it is
i do wonder uh what the real reason this
is
is it really the weight
or
why why is it that chickens can't fly so
well shut up i'm trying to okay i'm
trying
i keep on reaching the edge so
often
i'm not trying to let's go this way
they just built differently not
aerodynamic then you have to get a
little bit thinner
right
wait and breathe there you go i'm i
wasn't so far off
oh [\h__\h] it's a shark
please leave me alone um i i will leave
your territory okay and you leave me two
of them
you'll be three of them
if it's muddy white
oh my god
i still have nothing to fight them with
i think they left okay
[Music]
they have left and given up on eating my
yummy phoenix meat
oh what's this
oh
[Music]
fish
stop
[Music]
yep
there it is
last fish
these lovely phoenix moms check it out
i drive these birthdays crazy i do it on
the daily they treat me really nicely
nicely they buy me all i see dolce and
gabon finney and don
what is this
only wearing black well i i i ask you to
say that i love my acid seven genes
through religion i say no but they keep
giving i'll keep on taking i know i am
thinking keep on demonstrating and give
a little name i love my love
[Music]
in the back
wait sorry i didn't listen to you
i'm loving that too
oh spending all your money on me and
spending time on me you've got me
who is standing
what was that can i enter
is it dangerous
oh no bums
live live live live as long as i don't
have bombs
i'm not safe there
[Music]
cat hair in my mouth
i know i said i would stop but i
want to find
treasures
[Music]
of
fabulous degree pressures
that are meant for me
equals
[Music]
i think this place is new
let's check it out
[Music]
looks fancy oh my god it's burning
is it burning it's on fire
this beach is on fire
i should be able to
and a thing for the boomerang what is
this secret dungeon
okay
wind doesn't work
uh
what if i step on
on this button
what is this
what did that do there's a crack over
there yeah or i say croc but uh what was
the english name again kudos yeah
is that a dead tree friend of yours
i'll help you
up
[Music]
all the foreign
sprinkle the water from the body
[Music]
ah i feel like i want to do that before
i forget it
uh southern fairy island
oh [\h__\h]
that way
which way that way
ah
[Music]
i want that south and fairy island but i
also want the water okay can you guys
remind me next time tomorrow
to uh get the water to the tree
and now i want to find that southern
fairy island
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] dodge dog don't
touch
[\h__\h] i kind of lost track though
what does it look like
somewhere
here it that thing over there
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] i don't know where it is
is it that thing
what a tree yeah what a treat tomorrow
fairy island now it looks like a like a
mushy uh
um
shell
and a water ocean shell wait fish first
fish first fish fish
okay fish are you here are you with me
a seashell
seashell
so close
that was so close
what do you have
draw it
[Music]
like a butt
on outer island buried beneath the black
soil there's some serious treasure no no
okay outside island
i say try using an animal i remember
there was like something like that oh
okay okay
uh-huh uh-huh that's something i can do
now though i think
okay
uh the ferry will
make my pockets bigger right
that's something we wanted to do anyway
so good that we found it by accident
do i need bombs
so
oh blue electric one oh no i need bumps
ah i can't get this one
for fire arrows or anything
can i like mark it on my map
i don't think so
can you guys remember remind me whenever
i have fire arrows
to go here
this is like kind of the sad thing like
you feel motivated to
look around the whole ocean but then you
keep on bumping into things you can't
like see
or check out yet
that's a bit unfortunate
bomb also works
and maybe i need to wait a little bit
with all this side stuff
do the main quest first until
i have a certain amount of tools
[Music]
i'm getting better at this
yoga
[Music]
okay making money
making that money is that a fish don't
you see a fish
did you guys see your fish
maybe not
maybe it was just that that line that
wind line
hallucinations
i know i said i would leave now but
oh yeah that was again a fish didn't
talk to that fish yet i didn't let me go
get that beach
i feel you
oh helicopter fish
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh yeah
uh
the bait the bait weighs a bit
where's the where's the fish where's the
fish where's the fish
where's the fish
let's make it daytime then they won't
show up right
yeah i'm kind of addicted to fishing now
[Applause]
it's really dangerous
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh i
can't see you
yeah but do you just take your time and
draw on my map
i appreciate it buddy
ah
looks like the whole live logo
on the cover logo
a famous pictographer lives far to the
north
off here in wonderful island yeah i met
him
he's apparently really intelligent in
the ways of peterborough and then
he trashes above all other things
he keeps them hidden away and the
secret's safe
by the way small fry what exactly is a
pictograph do you want me to take one of
you
okay bye-bye i'm out of here
thank you
[Laughter]
run run run
and
i shall
save
the game
it's time to end it we continue tomorrow
anyway
oh wait no sorry i mean save
and um title screen
[Applause]
[Music]
that was fun
at least for me i don't know about you
guys
[Music]
sorry i need to read super chat chunky
monkey you guys wanna uh read the super
chat in the cozy room
that i showed you guys yesterday in the
members only stream so that the
non-members can see it too
[Music]
are you getting impatient
you guys have no food
are you out of kibbles
oh can we okay i'll turn it off because
i want to actually hear the soundtrack
so we open the soundtrack separately
[Music]
wind waker
down
[Music]
how about that
10 hours let's go
[Music]
no that's not good
i love it but not for super chat writing
[Music]
intro
mama
are you having a uh i want cuddles face
chunky monkey
she's cuddling with my tripod right now
you're good
[Music]
okay bye-bye she's so cute oh my god she
looks like this
ball of fluff i can't take it here
[Music]
don't run away
he's playing dead
playing i am stone
yes i got her i captured her again
so cute
ah
i'm chunky wonky
my fluffy bang bang
baby
[Music]
she's not close to the microphone so you
can't hear it but she's powering
very much purring off awesome
makes me so happy
recently i've been
um
short stream excuse me
recently i've been sleeping
in some weird position
because chunky wonky of course continues
to always sleep in the cardboard box
next to my pillow
always
but smoothie has
recently um moved a little bit away from
me
she's still on the bed but she's like at
the at the very corner
uh of of the foot side of the bed it's
so far away and i want my my smoothie
cuddles too you know so
recently i've been
adjusting to her so i sleep like
sideways at the at the foot side of the
bed
to cuddle with her until i fall asleep
and sometime in the middle of the night
i wake up and i'm like
why am i why am i here
why am i
at the foot side of the bed sideways
i'm so confused and then i move back to
chunky wonky
and yeah
that has been repeated
several times in the past couple days
and weeks
now chalky wonky gets her cuddles too
yeah yeah yeah don't worry they both get
it i tried to balance it out you know
oh
no you wanna leave chunky monkey
are you sure about that
uh the maldives i'm gonna miss my kitty
cats y'all
um i miss them but
maybe there's some kind of animals i can
pet there too besides fish
i wonder
[Music]
if they have an island cat i'm gonna
give them 10 out of 10 rating
[Music]
yes okay
let's do this
uh loop loop oh i don't even need to
loop this this is 10 hours
but let's go to
my sofa
my new sofa
[Music]
my show
[Laughter]
[Music]
there you are here's chad i'll put you
here
sofa cuddly sofa time
[Music]
to show
yesterday i showed this place for the
first time
yeah yeah let's do 250 maybe yeah
perfect
chill it's not chill it's so cozy
and you guys are there listening to me
and my super chats
yeah i need to i need to make use of my
backgrounds that i have
more often and we don't do watch alongs
that often especially actually they're
pretty much only members only
um
so
you know i need to show it to the public
too somehow so i think this one fits for
super chat readings quite well
yeah
i call being the one holding the popcorn
i'm holding the popcorn
oh you mean those over those ones over
there the one in the middle
i'm the one holding it
this one looks so cute i'm glad you like
it it was kind of rushed according to
eden exile
uh because i was doing the uh the
members only movie watch along yesterday
so maybe there will still be some
adjustments
not sure
the chat is kind of cut off that's fine
how there's one two three four five six
seven chickens here and there's about
several hundreds in the chat who are
saying that's me
how is that possible is it different
dimensions
how i don't understand
no that's me no that's me that's me too
what a coincidence
yeah they do blink
maybe you you move so fast that i just
can't see it but why are you moving you
should just sit there and chill
[Music]
that's
now that you think of it that's you
uh-huh uh-huh
you're the light in the projector
how
are you stuck in the projector how did
you get in there liquid chimkin if i
fits i sits
[Music]
well anyway thank you guys for watching
uh windworker today hope you enjoyed it
tomorrow we'll hopefully do another
dungeon and maybe some side stuff if the
game lets us
[Music]
what are you doing no talking no no
don't get don't go up there no no no no
no no no no no no no no
[Applause]
um
[Music]
it's my favorite nickname for her now
chunky wonky tried to get up my shelf
and knock over
some
[Music]
acrylic stands we don't do that
you're turning into bunkers
[Music]
doing cat things you know
what time is the documentary oh yeah uh
i think there is like a one hour
break between
the wind waker stream so it should be at
like 2 p.m i think
[Music]
maximum one hour hopefully i didn't hear
how long it's gonna be but
i don't think it's gonna be longer than
an hour
um yeah has the meet and greet thing
been put out there or or not yet have
you guys seen something
[Music]
what is that cute
they said we'll know tomorrow yeah okay
i've already seen it so
um
yes yes
it will be
a raffle
so
wait for tomorrow to apply
for the meet and greet if you're
planning on going there
[Music]
i will be reading the super tattoos
where do
[Music]
only that
portal 2 what about kobo with portal
kobo with porto portland what are you
doing
both of you
are you zooming
they're both in my room doing stuff
climbing up my chair my other chair
okay
[Music]
i can't be mad at them so
here it is
we probably won't continue until
after the mall lives so please be
patient
it goes
[Music]
it's made free somewhere by now when
this is read i'll have
done yet and have a complete orbit
around the sun you mean
what is your birthday
[Laughter]
the second while watching kiara if i
could make a selfish request because you
say a little [\h__\h] about bgm a few times
with different emotions
[Music]
what
happy birthday
don't be damn you say okay
you little [\h__\h]
oh you little [\h__\h]
your little [\h__\h]
yo little [\h__\h]
okay
that's enough happy birthday
a few days late but
happy birthday hope you like your
presents
enjoy enjoy it
okay our field voice i don't really know
how cr-field voice was
yeah
it was like
your little [\h__\h] i don't know
i don't know
okay busy i'm back
[Music]
hope you had a lovely birthday
thank you for being here for so long
and spending your time here with us
[Music]
felix sound thank you for two red super
chats hey it's been a while i feel like
angela i can't express how grateful i am
when i see you doing more and more
collabs yeah this week was a lot of
collabs and at the point of
the corporal collab you guys didn't even
know about the energy club hmm
i started watching richard was when i
first became an egg of yours and then
you showed me the rabbit hole
which i voluntarily jumped in just
please don't be mad at me for being a dd
no don't do that jump no
now
you can't hear her
oh she's zooming oh [\h__\h] she's zooming
[Music]
once again
you're too easy to capture chunky wonky
also
[Music]
she has to do me as young
running around oh smoothie has zoomies
too at the same time it's like they're
in sync
oh
uh
what are you saying also i can't stop
laughing when i picture it it's your
hand on cobble's face and kog's on yours
yeah i can't get it out of my head now
what do you mean that's what it was
supposed to be
that's what it is my hand in front of
her eye and and her hand in front of my
eye
it's not an optical illusion that's
supposed to what that's what it was
supposed to be
yeah yeah yeah getting more original
i don't know what to do with the next
one
if we do part two i'm not sure hm
[Music]
i'll figure something out i'll i'll
think of something
[Music]
hey the arms were difficult okay because
like i felt like they were kind of too
big
but if i made them smaller then they
won't fit the eyes
they have more of those assets well i
mean there's there's a lot of them
out there just have to find the right
ones
useful ones
no they're not my hands
one of them the one that's in front of
my eye is kobo's hand and the other way
around
[Music]
the family of cura eating cover off the
platform
but with portal i've been kind of like
having this pattern of close-ups
in the middle of the screen
and doing something with hands and mouth
[Music]
yeah yeah
i think you can notice by this by the
skin tone as well
i made mine a bit more yellow
[Music]
very cute fountain thank you
give kobo the gloves
no no no no no no no no no no
anyway feelings thank you um i'm not mad
but i hope
i hope you don't um
go to other people's streams when i'm
streaming you know when when someone
else is streaming and i'm not streaming
and you have time then okay
but kiwawa must always be your priority
felix
okay
and if you have some archives to watch
then that's also the priority
always watch the archives first before
watching someone else's streams
very important
don't fall behind
hashtag
thank you
thank you felix
i hope you're doing well thanks for
stopping by
schuberth
[Music]
papa
there's a korean text but i suppose that
the english one is has the same meaning
it's a pity that keanu's broadcast
always start before i go to bed
[Music]
oh when i wake up in the morning i'm
going to watch a rerun ah
yes please please do
sorry the timing is so bad especially in
the past two weeks i
i couldn't really start my streams
earlier most of the time
you know because i was going to therapy
um next week i don't know i'll try to
mix it up a bit more
and
yeah i try
i hope watching the archives is not
um
to
i don't know how to say i mean i know we
all prefer to watch it live
i hope it's okay for you
thank you for supporting me thank you
i'm sandi da danke
[Music]
thanks for the pinky have fun thinking
we'll pour those tanjo the titan will
keep us warm in the usual room
thank you
it was it was actually really fun
doing it with someone else i was a bit
very actually very worried about it
beforehand
uh but the kobo did a great job was a
good partner in crime
so all what all was good and we had fun
both of us i think
that is not too bad
thank you good thank you
[Music]
but to be honest like towards me
i've seen some memes too that like
towards me she's like really sweet and
mommy but then took her
whole life indonesia
peeps she's more of a kusakaki
good very good
she must respect the phoenix
the fast food mogul
otherwise i have to give her the butt
slaps
my both of my cats are still in my room
it feels like they're
expecting me to end the stream
i think they want food let me check if
they have kibbles okay
[Music]
i'll be right back
i feel i feel um monitored
one cables
[Music]
it might really have been that
they had pretty much an empty bowl
usually i always keep it full like 24 7
i keep it full
it's it rarely happens that it's empty
but i forgot to fill it up today this
morning
oh
okay
well thank you teasant thank you
riley the charm thank you for the pinky
we have the test results here you and
kobo are adorable together it's amazing
we weren't even testing for that but
that's what it says adorable
[Music]
there were like so many clips of the
stream too like immediately after as
well
and also a lot of fan art too so i guess
you guys really enjoyed it thank you
thank y'all
we'll do it again soon
thanks for
enjoying the stream
[Music]
and my heart will destroy by their cute
things no don't die
yeah but i understand
there's a word in japanese
that's called uh
dying or
[Music]
and i think a lot of people might have
had that happen to them
in the kobo collab
kobo lab
more deaf yes
it happened to me oh sorry
well now you know to be better prepared
next time have some kind of
shield against it or something that will
have the opposite effect on you
an official name for the pairing
[Music]
this one could also be quota
if you think about it but we had that
before
[Music]
sounds decent
has a good sound to it a good ring to it
[Music]
rain bird blue bird
blue bird owie tony owie
[Music]
that implies there is no kobold because
nashi means no not non-existent
[Music]
yeah i didn't i i didn't put the minus
in between i forgot
i didn't realize it also means chicken
coop
thank you
please come again okay i'll see you
again
in my stream hopefully
thanks for the pinky for horseback
riding with kobe
yeah i mean renting a horse for one day
uh shouldn't be too difficult so
that seems realistic but um i actually a
while ago
i think i told you guys when i did that
but i talked to some friend
of a friend who has a horse
like when you have a horse
usually most of the time i guess it
depends on the country and like how
common it is and all that but at least
here
what you do is you own a horse but you
rent like
um
you rent a place
to keep your horse
in some kind of
um
barn or so where there is actually a
staff person taking care of them too
[Music]
yeah you rent a stable
um or
you can also
just
not buy a horse
just rent it for the day or so
make some old horses happy by giving
them
some exercise
but i think you know the whole thing
with giving cool presents i mean
it was originally just a joke but then i
felt i thought it was pretty obvious and
it was a joke and then people kind of i
don't know i wasn't sure when they were
like sounding like they expected me to
really do it if that was a jerk too
but that i felt the pressure
[Laughter]
but it's okay i will i will take her out
for horseback riding if i ever meet her
one day in real life um
that's
doable that's manageable
[Music]
for what was it violin or guitar
uh i think she said violin
um the thing is like there's really
cheap violence but those are more for
practice i actually looked into it okay
i looked into it and the the cheap
violins are just meant to be for
practice and i wasn't sure like if you
buy someone a violin you should buy them
a proper violin and that's just a shitty
violin for practice
but
but then then it gets really expensive
if you want to buy someone a proper
violin those are really expensive and i
was thinking honestly
once kobo gets those super chats i don't
think she'll have any problems getting
herself a violin or a horse for that
matter if she really wants one
so
i don't think it needs to be me
no i i'm not trying to be a sugar mommy
but then i felt all those expectations
people were maybe taking me seriously
though
mom didn't promise
i just said
i'm buying but it was a joke
no no no no she'll be able to buy
anything she wants
by herself sooner or later
yeah pretty sure pretty sure
[Music]
especially if she uses stream labs and
not super chats
[Music]
thank you
at the beach are you trying to make me
jealous i want to go to the beach
that's all the first thank you soon so
we toured
you thanks for the pinkie thank you
merry pip and thank you sure i'm glad
you enjoyed it thank you
[Music]
as the designer of some of these outfits
it made me really happy to see people
draw fan art of the outfits even though
it's not fan art of myself
just fan of something i designed but it
was really cool to see it
[Music]
some of the outfits that i've designed
have been very popular especially the
crony one and the imo fauna yeah
emo golf fauna very popular choice
[Music]
it seems that my designs have left
an impression
i've caused resurgence in imo fauna fan
art
i've seen yeah
i've seen it
that's good i wanted to
i wanted to draw some
some unique designs that
i could totally see being made into live
2d you know
something
something that stands out
i mean
if i were fauna if i were given a casual
outfit i probably wouldn't want to
make that one casual outfit the first
extra outfit
uh into another second into
um
an emo outfit
i would probably use a chance to make
something more
normal casual
just because they don't have many
outfits yet and you kind of want
something that you can use for
many many purposes
um but maybe in the future you know
if they ever have some kind of theme
where she could go for emo
then let's [\h__\h] go
yeah like maybe like the theme could be
alternative
personalities
or so
[Music]
um
would be cool if we get that too
yeah bale said that the one i drew of
her
uh
yeah here here it is i have the png
that she has every piece pretty much
of these clothes in her in her
wardrobe which
[Music]
i was happy to hear because that just
means i captured her style
perfectly without even having ever met
her before before and um
not knowing her that well either
[Music]
you know
when i was drawing her
she was actually one of the
easiest ones for me out of all the ones
that i drew i felt i felt like um bales
was just
very obvious
what
i should go with for her
yeah
it was pretty easy
i like this one i'm proud of it
i like it it has a good balance it's
stylish it's realistic i feel like girls
like bales or me even
might run around like that outside on
the street for real
yeah yeah i can see girls running around
like that
something like that
[Music]
hey
how both of y'all need to get with bae
and jagger i don't think that's so
interesting or special but
um
yeah the the one that ena threw that's
also something that could have been an
option for me
but i was like
jeans jeans jacket
[Music]
jeans jacket it is
in this case a ripped one
yeah
yeah yeah but combining it
combining the jeans jacket which is a
little bit more boyish
as well as the the parker is also kind
of boyish but combining it with some
girly
elements like the mini skirt you know
um and and the fact that the
the parker is cropped i think makes it
kind of girly girlish too so combining
boyish and girlish and energetic um
elements with one another was my goal
[Music]
yes inside into a designer's brain
if i had
more time
then some of these would have probably
ended up differently and all that but
yeah i kind of want to try again
sometime it was a lot of fun designing
these outfits
[Music]
punk style a little bit yeah
the skirt it's not red stripes
but yeah it's um
what's the english word um
[Music]
what's the word i forgot the english
word for that pattern
ch not check it played late yeah check
it is
something else again guys
ah
you don't know fashion
plaid
yeah
oh cocoon dance
[Music]
wheatgrass juice what the [\h__\h] is that
you
[Music]
should drop the uchino when it's a juice
blend and make a new product line but
uchino
just means something small
in italian it doesn't mean coffee don't
even get me started
don't ever get me excited okay mike
he says starbucks is being confusing
with their naming should drop the uchino
when it's a juice blend and make a new
product line
don't don't don't even
[Laughter]
knows doesn't doesn't mean
there's coffee in there but okay
whatever
i was just joking though during the
during the pre-chat
i was in a good mood and uh i mean it
triggered me a little bit that you guys
had no [\h__\h] idea that would
frappuccinos work
that i had to teach you about it
yeah that triggered me maybe a little
bit but generally it was a joke
triggered
there's a timing out you know me it was
just i was just playing with you guys
you guys enjoyed it you guys were
challenging me at that point anyway
you guys were 100 percent asking for me
to bonk you
7 000 calories yeah they definitely have
a [\h__\h] ton of calories yeah yeah
that makes it even better
genie dankelsen spicy mayo chicken
i'm gonna read the english part okay
have a good show korean fans and others
enjoy the show i'm going to work in the
morning peace
i think i think it's probably the same
meaning
yeah yeah looks like the same amount you
know that
thank you i hope you enjoyed watching
the archive by now
it was a short one anyway
at least these collabs are a bit shorter
than my normal stream so you guys um
have some streams that are easy to catch
up on you're welcome
and i like keeping
these kind of streams
shorter so that they're more compact and
not dragged out endlessly i talked about
this before
but i like having
like first of all an estimate i always
ask
when it comes to these collabs
i always ask the the other person
beforehand like how long do you have
time
is there any
any length of stream that would be too
long for you
and then
i tell them what i think the estimate is
and what what i aim
the length of the stream to be
because i don't want them to be too long
and i i want
there to be
um a system and and like not a system
but what's the word
i want it to be fought through well
and um
planned out well structure and structure
i wanted to have structure
yeah yeah
so
for that i think it's important to
decide roughly
um
what the length will be and then you
have to figure out like how long are
these
things that i want to do actually gonna
take
originally i kind of wanted to do even
more outfits i wanted to do like two
outfits per um council hope member but
it turned out to be pretty perfect i
wasn't sure how long it was gonna take
originally but
it turned out to be perfectly one hour
like introducing the outfits and then
having them being judged and all that so
it was as if i have calculated it yeah
and honestly if it would have been
double the amount then i would have sat
there drawing outfits for six hours
[Music]
yeah
exactly it took me three hours for six
outfits if we would have done 12 it
would have taken me six hours like thank
god i didn't do that
[Music]
i kind of underestimated how much time
it would take me to draw them beforehand
[Music]
on this
she would
probably like it very much too
[Music]
let's go yes we have gone
you know that song
i love that song yeah
i like it
you don't it's very old
old black eyed peace song right
it was black at peace
not very well known i think because it
was just an album song
an old one
it's called gone going
da da da da da da da da
[Music]
from the monkey business album
you guys should listen to it because
that one is actually really chill
compared to the other
songs they made in that album this one
is really
relaxing and
yeah
kind of gives me vacation vibes too with
the instruments i think i haven't
listened to it for a long time though
i'm a true fan
i mean i was
i don't know i've never went to the
concerts because i was too young back
then anyway not like they would come to
a shitty shitty small city somewhere in
austria for concert anyway
they were going to the big places
they did make bangers yes
i already checked all the black and
peace songs that i can sing in
in that karaoke
software that we have to use
um
they don't have that one
in it they really don't have that many
yeah i did almost say australia how do
you know
yeah they don't have this song and they
actually don't have that many songs from
black eyed peas surprisingly
and uh
yeah
kind of have to use that software
or
instrumentals where we have the written
permission
personally
aimed at us
telling us that we can use it it's kind
of
you know
difficult that's why i still can't do it
i want a [\h__\h] duck k-pop come on
[Music]
i tried i i looked up some k-pop karaoke
instrumental channels and some of them
even say feel free to use our
instrumentals but that's not enough
i sent them in but never heard anything
back
now
sometimes i feel like if i just write a
youtube comment in the comment section
asking can i use this they would
immediately reply and say yes
probably
but it doesn't work like that um
[Music]
alberto
thank you i'm glad you like the outfits
nathan cotton duncan
[Music]
sending that daggers and zen boy is down
because everybody loves the emo fauna
not applicable doggerson
ernest thank you sticky
sticky sticky sticky sticky sticky suit
[Music]
the red superchatto
yesterday was the day i got fried oh
bucket time
so after a year of amazing content wait
isn't there a saying
that says kicking the bucket or is that
only in german
kicking the bucket when you die isn't
that so perfect when it comes to kfp
because you get turned into a bucket
when you die
yeah that's what it yeah yes yeah that's
what i mean
you kicked the bucket yeah
i mean you're just
dead as a fried chicken for a while
you'll get revived eventually don't
worry about it but meantime
you're kicking the bucket
[Music]
it's perfect
kick the bucket
this health plan sucks
hey
you knew it from the start
if you look at the membership icons and
you know everything
you know your future ahead of time so
don't complain to me
[Music]
oh yeah reviving
was not even a thing in the beginning
so if anything
the conditions have improved
by a lot
since then
since the beginning
in the beginning you weren't even
supposed to revive so
i'm not taking any complaints only
praises
and thank you
nostalgic the pictures they're not even
that old besides the halloween one
that's the only one that's
somewhat old
[Music]
what will happen when year 3 and 4 are
possible i don't know will they ever be
but maybe i don't know what will happen
we will have to wait for that
uh but once i wanted to stop lurking and
say thank you for all the work and
creativity you put into everything you
do streams like today are the reason kfp
always have things to look forward to
has a girl casted look thank you good to
hear
i try to keep my content somewhat
interesting within the means
of
what i can do
uh next week you will have a vr
stream produced by me
so i hope that will turn out well you
guys will enjoy it it will be a little
bit special
yeah
besides that uh oh yeah there will be
one more special stream
um also we'll play kiwi with mummy again
um
yeah for the rest i'll have to
i'll have to um plan some things i'm not
sure yet but i think it will be at least
one two three collapse at least three
collabs
[Music]
original song no original song will be
more like at the end of the
month
if not
i don't know probably at the end of the
month or like the
second
last week
or something like that
um thank you the conduit please continue
supporting me and watching my content
lurking is okay i guess but i would be
happy to hear you say hello sometimes
yeah in the chat as well
but thank you for being here
i appreciate it thank you
thank you thank you
been amazing here i would love to see
more stuff like this in the future don't
you want to get vengeance on inna with a
rematch
nah there's nothing like that
i feel like we both did
find
this great designs and it was a lot of
fun i don't feel like i need revenge or
something but
i want to do more stuff like this but i
want more ideas like it takes me some
while to think of these ideas hmm
you're good to live idea or japan or so
many possibilities yeah see i also don't
want to
repeat the same idea too many times you
know
if you have ideas feel free to throw
them at me
thank you dotanaka maybe if enough time
passes we can repeat this in some way
but for now
for now for now
there will have to be some other
streams
yeah i remember the rap contest and the
queen's song
love confession yeah but all of these
are like
things that i have to get some vr stuff
done for and
the quiz show you mean you mean the
it's not the question you mean the no
laughing allowed thingy that one is just
a huge
idea that
i don't know it's so big then i don't
even know where to start
um
it's more likely that i'll go with
something else but give me time give me
time please we have to spread it out
anyway
yeah
yeah now i'm now currently i'm preparing
for other things like my birthday life i
actually have to
design the stage
you know how the stages are
kind of different depending on
um
who's doing the birthday stream
kind of different not completely
but i can't
i can't think of so many things i'm
struggling a little bit because i don't
want it to be in like burgers everywhere
i wanted to be more like cool
or pretty
um
but it's kind of difficult to put a
phoenix into
like themed objects besides fire which
is gonna mess up the frame rate and i
don't even know if that's possible to
put fire there
and well okay
i don't know
ashes okay
maybe some feathers i can't think of
anything else
i wanted to be cool
[Music]
olympic torches torches that's more fire
the thing is like i kind of regret
putting so much fire
on on this one
on this one this one
you know what i mean because um
the frame rate was so [\h__\h] with that
once you have fire on stage like that
holy [\h__\h]
it's so pixely
so there shouldn't be too much
[Music]
the flowers is just so basic i want
something more personal
like i've seen some others
so think about what i could put on there
i've seen some others like
uh fudeon stage
in the mighty standby stage and all that
and they have really cool ones that are
very really really personalized
[Music]
ah
who gets flower field in that one art
yeah that that's true that one was cool
but
it's not like
even on that picture there's not much
that i can really work with
[Music]
i don't know
if you have some ideas please please
please throw them at me
afterwards in a tweet maybe
but keep in mind it can only be like
some
you know some additional objects we
can't change like everything
but i would appreciate some ideas
[Music]
austrian elements
mountains
but okay that's that's i guess more
personal that's not very phoenixy huh
but i guess yeah it depends on what i
want to go for
i wanted to look cool
but but
my mountain maybe
volcano mountain oh
i see
[Music]
i like that idea
i wonder how
if it's just like the volcano and some
lava flowing down if that kills the
frame rate as well
or if that's
fine
[Music]
burn the frame rate burn it down
okay let me put that
let me put that into my
my current sketch one set
png
of a volcano
volcano.png
[Music]
why does it save it as a [\h__\h] webpage
i hate it
dot png
[Music]
i can't put it into my photoshop
okay i'll do it later
i hate that
[Music]
fading in an outglow effect yeah that's
cool
[Music]
testing is not really an option they
make it
and then
i can't just test it out in a member
stream
they make it and i have to use it
but they can probably tell me ahead of
time what's like possible and what's not
um
[Music]
i'll take your entire stock of golf
supermodel fauna what a deal
it's not on sale
oh what you mean it's not on sale
which one did she even end up choosing
didn't she go for the non-golf one
herself anyway
[Music]
sorry dude man it's not happening
it was just too special i think
it was it was ahead of everyone's time
i think they were not ready for that
yeah
[Music]
they were not ready for it
we need to give them some time
they probably everybody also in the
youtube poll everybody that voted for
non golf probably regretting it by now
nothing against inna's dress i really
love hers
but
let's be real golf
golf fauna did some things to you that
you just don't want to admit
[Music]
you don't want to admit it
it intimidated these people
[Music]
thank
you
i hope for you you seem to be a sapling
i hope for you that one day you'll get
more of your golf fauna
so it wasn't really golf but
let's let's just say it is what you want
it to be
the dominion is just titty i'm dancing
in the satisfied dankeshen it's me thank
you
afternoon's prime time cushion
swimsuit fashion context now hold on
[Music]
that's not much to draw though but i
guess some
beach fashion could be the theme
combining swimsuits of like
hats and sunglasses and
some
um
kind of see-through
knitted
dress thingies that you wear on the
beach
yeah
could do something like that yeah yeah
mr big dankeshin another fermented
thanks for the stream idea extreme great
idea thank you for watching glad you
enjoyed it you're welcome
[Music]
i'm happy with it too christopher p
chicken shine they came a creepy
tangashin every now they're called
duncan andrew ghost duncashin thanks for
the pinky
and moondog
and oliona
nama
thank you for the pink super chat
thank you for the fun stream i really
love your edgy fauna design oh
thank you as well glad you liked it
it seems to have been
a lot of people's favorite one
yeah
glad to hear that
i think if ina tried to draw uh
an emo fauna though she would have
absolutely nailed it too
if that was the actual theme
oh [\h__\h] enough would blow us away i'm
sure
her real powers would be unleashed
oh yeah i saw that the combined one that
looks really cool too
very very nice
[Music]
does he not have the inner emo to
express herself
i don't know
i'm not sure
if she doesn't need it she's just
already too based
she knows how to make things look good
so she doesn't need to have emo
experience
[Music]
okay we're done with those super chats
no not really
not really
[Music]
why is it so addicting
okay i think i can go through the ones
from today as well
it's not too much
[Music]
salute
amazing thumbnail
wow
wow wow
i want to snuggle i want to snuggle too
snow animal village
[Music]
animal village
yeah you like those eyebrows
there was one whole life member who
um only one though who has eyebrows i
think it was hard
with their angry face
her eyebrows go like that
they don't go like you know mine like
downwards
well hers go like the one in the
thumbnail kind of like
questioning it's more of a questioning
look
than
uh an angry look it's it really stands
out
i think i saw this on reddit the other
day there was a post with all
of the angry faces of all of the whole
life members
and the one from hatsuma really stood
out to me because she's the only one
with like weird-ass eyebrows
and they go more like that what the [\h__\h]
yeah like that like that
did you see it
it was on reddit damn
all right yes you did but it's okay
thank you for coming
[Music]
i
rarely
recently a bit more than usual that post
was by me what
really
what kind of coincidence is that that
you're here now really was that really
you i want proof i want to see the proof
i'll have to look at that later
it was a couple days ago i think it's
not up anymore not at least not in the
top
it's the same name really how do you
remember
oh my god
wow
well then you're welcome
[Music]
ah
silly slowpoke
i think i think slowpoke this one
it's kind of
kind of
a paradox
because you're reminding me just in time
shouldn't you be reminding me one year
later or like i don't know a couple
months later
um
he says i will send you a reminder in
one year to sing that funny farm songs
oh wait never mind wait i misunderstood
it
just a slowpoke planning on sending me a
reminder still okay okay okay okay then
it's okay okay so then one year later
i'll finally receive the reminder okay
okay excuse me shut up
shut up i'm gonna time you out because i
know you're slowpoke
you're you're making fun of me i'm gonna
time you out you can call me a tyrant i
don't give a [\h__\h] get out of here
i need to silence him
[Music]
[Laughter]
who the hell is that in your profile
picture
ah i think i've seen the gray before but
i don't remember the name
ah
violet evergreen
you are straying afar
very far your new oshie excuse me
excuse
me
[Music]
a little [\h__\h]
you have like 20 or she's at this point
[Music]
said it was okay i didn't mean it
i don't i just don't wanna
[Music]
sound
like i'm controlling you guys too much
but of course i didn't mean it you
should be loyal
collecting once you like it's pokemon
yeah that's just wrong
i think i think it's not only me at this
point who feels like what you're doing
is wrong
you shouldn't have so many oshies it's
just
not how
god intended it to be
[Music]
in the game of
on thank you for the red super chat meow
to you too sir
wow
[Music]
thank you
you probably sent that because you
thought i was chilling with my cats and
that's when i was late that's not true
really youtube was really acting up
today
[Music]
kind of weird
it loses its sweetening if you have too
many there you go lexington the lion
says it the way it is
[Music]
thank
you what
[Music]
in
six [\h__\h] months
what i do what do i do when i need some
music
[Music]
but in those six months you'll be able
to use it more than 20 minutes a day
your phone
are you here now demo
[Music]
probably not
we need to bad military service so that
you guys don't leave me for six months
in a row
it's just not acceptable
[Music]
i can't tap you guys leave me like that
by the time you're back you already
forgot about me
is there anyone who came back from their
service and like actually came back
was there someone who said hey i'm back
from my six-month military service
i still love you
just as the day i lost you
me really i i do huh
[Music]
there was i don't remember anyone
someone
a tank guy is still tanking
he's still tanking
and i hope they come back
maybe we still need to wait for them to
come back because it feels like a bunch
of them left like a while ago
and six months haven't passed yet
thank you
thank you for still liking me
and
but good luck demo
don't forget about me
okay
[Music]
what gd duncan there was a number that i
already gave to someone
last lady the number 999 given to james
jackson was already taken it may have
suggested number between 993 and 998.
[Music]
uh what for james jackson
or does james jackson have the 999
[Music]
what do you mean ford james is it his
originally or did i try to give it to
him yesterday
[Music]
which one is it
james jackson need a new number
okay
nine
eight
point
nine
[Music]
that's your number you can also write it
just as 998
but remember the correct number in your
heart is 998.9
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's a special one but officially it's
998 okay
officially it's 998 for your for your
google sheet
you know just so we don't crash the
system exactly we don't want to do that
we want to keep a
structure
yeah i used rounding it's super
effective now i rounded down though with
not 0.9 you should round up
but like rounding down
[Music]
yeah i know your systems can't handle
that so it's 998 officially
in the system
but you can
have in your in your mind and in your
heart the fact that it's 998.9
okay
i think we've reached um
a middle ground
yeah i'm not part of your sister i'm
gonna fly
[Music]
i'm not feeling all too well right now
but watching your stream and being
bundled up to my kiwawa hoodie makes
everything better
oh thank you you're wearing the omo
catkin lava hoodie
[Music]
nice i heard it's really comfy
i wish you all the best hope you get
better soon
drink some hot tea or hot chocolate or
hot milk anything that's hot
okay
eat some something yummy something sweet
some cookies
it is it is
thank you very much super huang blue
dankeshen
kitchen randy rj
[Music]
ah
looking for the top a tasting no cotton
oh my goodness you like me too much
jacob 47
[Music]
french
um
a kiss of
probably some cat hairs some certain
amount of cutters
spicy mayo chicken
thank you
oh you have an appointment okay okay are
you watching the archive now hello
thanks for catching up
[Music]
brandon
ah you also played with your brother's
file
nice i have a connection
[Music]
oh
and a korean message with the red super
chattel
[Music]
style
no problem
thank you for staying as long as you
could
thank you
i appreciate it thank you thank you for
your love and support
[Music]
thank you see you again tomorrow
hopefully um
i need the boomerang
can um tell me remind me of that
tomorrow a great fairy at the two-eyed
reed
who doubles your magic that you only
need the boomerang to get just look at
look for a flock of seagulls ah
those seagulls have a meaning right i
forgot
i forgot
write it down write it down
[Music]
and looking for the top
there's not gonna be a next zelda
weekend
where we can play minish cap or so
because
it's wind waker weekends not zelda
weekends and it's wind waker weekends
because it just fits so well it's www
now
[Music]
i'm almost done chunky monkey
yeah it's when do i go in kit
i don't even know if i could stream
a gba game i know that ds games i can't
stream i can't because they don't have
the input i think or output
yeah yeah we're not allowed to stream
those
because we technically can't hi chunky
monkey
junkie monkey
walking through my my cables
oh it's on the virtual console okay no
but before we start another zelda game i
think we'll be starting something else
we need a a break you know i'm enjoying
wind waker now but
uh we'll do something else afterwards i
don't know what to get but
we'll do something
[Music]
that would actually
maybe be a good idea
[Music]
like uh
let's see we have let's say we have an
off guy
but it's like kind of difficult as a
youtuber
um
if we wear real tubers i would like to
do
like something where we buy clothes for
each other and then we have to wear them
[Music]
it's not it's not quite the same
as a youtuber you know
realtors yeah
i am real i am very real i'm a real girl
there you go you see my nose growing
bigger and bigger
[Music]
i'm a real now
flesh tubers no i mean real tubas
who said fleshtube is her decided on
that term
ew that sounds so weird
sounds gross there
and real quick potatoes
yes
call them fleshies excuse me
what are you guys talking about as if it
was a normal thing
you guys confused me
[Applause]
[Music]
yes
eight
five
one
is your number wrestle free
i hope i don't make up the same numbers
it would be weird because there's so
many numbers
[Music]
thank you
i'm glad you're enjoying my streams and
that it helps you somehow thank you good
to know
glad to have you cd dancer and donkey
wonky in this movie some movie should be
this movie it's movie to be
smoothie baby
okay i'm done
yummy
okay
i have to make dinner now and then
finish my design for my stage and then
uh
prepare some things uh
yep
i have some appointments several
appointments tomorrow before wind waker
so i'm gonna be kind of busy
hopefully
hopefully i don't have to delay i don't
think so i mean we have the
the twitch stream before so i'll be at
home for sure
um
good meal thank you i don't even know
what i'm gonna eat
ah i think i wanted to
um i have one hello fresh recipe that
was with shrimps but i don't like shrimp
so i'm gonna substitute them with
sausages
and the rest was just potato wedges and
a salad so i think i can just get rid of
the shrimps and eat it with sausages
instead i think
i have sausage sausages in the fridge i
just don't know if they're still good
merci beaucoup thank you for joining
[Music]
yeah tomorrow there will be um
a little stream on twitch with me and
iris uh because of that uh events the
german convention that we're gonna be on
and so if you're curious if you're going
to doko me especially then you might
want to watch it to catch some details
and do some chitchat
i'll be posting it the link on twitter
it's gonna be two hours
before the windwaker stream
i'll definitely retweet it or tweet
about it so keep an eye open
is it in german or english well since
iris is there i think it will be in
english if it was just me we might just
talk in german but since iris is there i
think
it will be english
so you'll hear some
very german english again from that uh
fisky
german english
[Music]
now iris is not german just as much as i
am not australian
yeah the catboy remember him
[Music]
that little cat boy
who's organizing the event
maybe i'll put on my cat ears and insert
dominance
[Music]
i have the bigger cat
yeah yeah that's english that's what
[Music]
is
there he goes my translator he's like oh
he has this raider he's just watching
watching the stream kind of
chilling and then and then he hears
kilauea speaking germany he's like my
time has come
by the side is the common
[Music]
a
i will be on um twitch tomorrow
and then we'll be um
playing some more wind waker so
hope to see you guys tomorrow again
see you guys tomorrow
yes yes yes yes
dokomi tv yes that's the channel
[Music]
thank you everybody in germany i'll be
there
[Music]
and i really need to go to that idol
meeting
bye bye
love you guys thank you
thank you i need to
will be so happy
[Music]
foreign