[Music]
[Applause]
he
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
h
k
[Music]
k uh
uh no start TW what but a tweeted uh
next stream tweet which was uh an
starting tweet at the same time because
I forgot to do a next stream
tweet that's that's the real problem
double audio
what
what there's no dble stop one guying
me huh I am a cheat you little
[\h__\h] I just come back and you're one
guying me what
for
why yeah I should stop reading your
comments because you're the one guy who
one gu me I close your other tab yeah
maybe it's just your other
tab maybe is that what you is that your
problem H it's been so long since since
I streamed so you're feeling like ah I
got to have double WWA today to make up
for the days where I didn't have the WWA
I'm just going to get double WWA this
works right this is how it works I can
get a double WWA doses or even a triple
or
quadruple
maybe maybe test it out go test it out
seven Wawa tabs how many can you do guys
until until you go
insane I'm back
guys
T I had such
a such a
stressful stressful
weekend um but a fun
weekend maybe before we
start I'm going to open up paint
uh because I'm going to talk about this
like airport
situation and it might be good to
visualize it Mama Mia that was a that
was a real Mama Mia moment not going to
lie oh by the way I'm not participating
in the arc uh stuff I just don't I don't
know I don't
really I don't know maybe if I would go
get into it maybe I would enjoy it
but I I don't know I just didn't really
feel interested um but I might
participate in other projects in the
future so we show just not Arc also I
don't have the time anyway I I want to
do like like I don't want to this one
week when I'm back I don't want to fill
it all with the same kind of game you
know what I mean cuz I don't know how
long I don't think it's going to take
longer than one or two weeks right uh
the arc project and I don't want to fil
this time where I can stream
normally uh with the same
game yeah okay
so first
up I need to hello
sh my okay let me unmute windows so you
can hear this oh is it working now
okay Mama
Mia Mama
Mia
air air
hello
airport it just loses track of my pen
sometimes and it does just like
uh the whole time like I don't know why
it's like something with the cable being
probably loose through the cable
management
airport batter there's no
batteries but anyway so we're talking
about the Mama Mia airport I'm not going
to give it or may maybe I'll end up
giving it a real name the real name that
it
has um but for now let's call it Mama M
airport because it was a real Mama Mia
situation so okay here's the thing this
is going to be a little bit of a story
time before we get
started hello hello I want to paint my
pen is here thank you here yeah
story
time okay so a real bastao situation
yeah God damn
it okay so this is interesting now that
I'm gonna uh vent about airport you may
think that it has something to do with
this crap crowd link Cloud crowd link
situation so actually I flew with my
friends to Italy uh on Thursday morning
a crowd strike yeah that's IT Crowd
strike crawling out
yeah and uh on Thursday uh morning and I
mean we did have some interesting
situation there but it had nothing to do
with that um this is also not not the
Mia airport
story okay let really quickly a tangent
in the tangent on our way to Italy
basically we were waiting for the
boarding and then um some some flights
uh I think maybe like the smaller
flights are often affected by this when
they can't pay money to get like a a
good connection from for like a tube
into the airplane sometimes you have to
go with a bus right uh so anyway we were
boarding and then we were first all put
into a bus so we like standing or
sitting in in the bus and everybody was
like yapping yapping yapping loudly in
the bus
and um like a weird amount of time
passes and passes and passes the bus
just wouldn't go but you would think the
moment they put you into the bus like
like the airplane is ready to go already
soonish so you should go the bus should
go but no the bus just wouldn't go and I
swear like we were in there forever and
I was actually starting to lose my
mind I was really starting to lose my
mind because the longer I was in there
the more the loud voices of everybody
like you know when something is loud and
so you're trying to talk louder to over
tone that and then the others are also
starting to talk louder so it was a
situation like that where it's it's
getting louder and louder and louder
gradually there's so much yapping
because there's so much time passing too
and I was going insane so I put on my
thank God I had my noise cancelling
headphones yeah I was I I I was like
losing my mind I put on my headphones
and even after that even with the
headphones the thing is like they cancel
noise but voices they kind of keep in
right have you guys had like the the
same experience with noise cancelling
headphones They Don't Really they don't
really do a good job at canceling out
voices which I think is maybe on purpose
so that you can hear when somebody talks
to you or
so yeah if you put on music then you're
probably going to be
fine I was basically having a
conversation with my friend with the
noise cancelling phone headphones on it
is on purpose right
yeah but it helped a little bit but it
still was making me feel insane like if
you're not going to let us go onto the
[\h__\h] airplane then let me out I was
thinking that and then it happened like
after I don't know 40 minutes or so it
felt like a lot of time in the bus
suddenly they open the bus doors we
haven't moved yet at this point and they
tell us to go back
inside uh because there's a technical
issue with the airplane they don't give
any details and
um yeah so we're like well I'm glad I'm
getting out of this uh bus but one of my
friends is a worse Doom poster than
me like legit it's so funny my pizza
friend is such a doom poster it's insane
uh like I was still pretty chill like we
just wanted to get uh to Italy during
this day and it was still uh before noon
right and my pizza friend the Doom
poster he was like the moment we step
out of the bus he's like oh no no what
what are we going to do if we don't get
to Italy Today anymore oh no mama M oh
my God we're so [\h__\h] we're so [\h__\h]
we're not going to get to Italy anymore
and today and the thing is like okay
even if we didn't make it today we could
still go tomorrow uh probably but like I
think there's a way we can get there
today anyway but like he was he was Doom
posting like crazy and I'm like calm
down calm down it's it's going to be
fine like it's going to be fine like
even if we wait like 30 minutes or so uh
or like you know you know it's fine
there's still plenty of flights to Italy
we could take a train
whatever it's the end yeah for real and
then like we were still you know you
know so there's um there's the these
thingies with the scanny anything that
you pass through and then maybe usually
you go maybe around the corner you go
that
way after you scan your ticket you go
for like a little tube or so and then
you go into the plane in our case it was
stairs that led down to the bus but we
were like there was like uh so many
people here like on the way back to the
seats sh for [\h__\h]
sake back to the seats to wait until the
plane was exchanged or
whatever um and and then like you know
on this on this path on the stairs and
in this tube is when my friend was Doom
posting and I was like calm down like we
were still just we came out of the bus
it was like 1 minute and he was Doom
posting and literally while we were
still in here is when they told us after
all to turn around again because
everything is and we can go get back
into the
bus the wheels on the bus go round and
round round and round round and around
and I had to laugh so hard because it
was like see see nothing to Doom post
about it's all okay Mama
[Laughter]
[Music]
Mia yeah interesting bus what it's an
airport
bus but no no no no they said that
something's wrong with the with the
airplane and then apparently one minute
later it was resolved so it's I think
it's like so hello hello
hello Okay so let's say
um this is a clock I don't know what
time that is
but we're in the bus
and they they realize okay they they're
Pro they were probably waiting for
something to be fixed and thought it
would only take two or 3 minutes so they
already put us in the bus but then they
realized it's taking longer but they're
like let's keep them in in the bus
because Sur it's going to be fixed soon
and then 20 minutes are passing by and
they're like surely it's going to be
finished soon so let's wait a little bit
more and then 30 minutes pass by and
then 40 minutes pass by and then 40
minutes maybe they're like finally like
okay like this seems to be a bigger
problem let's get them out of here so
everybody walks out and then one minute
later it's fixed you know like you could
have stayed 1 minute later in the bus
and it would have been fine but I think
it was probably something I dad like oh
oh oh wait never mind we actually just
fixed it okay turn around turn
around and everybody was relieved um
that finally we would go I was scared to
go back into into the bus because it was
a traumatizing anxiety
inducing bus situation but then we go
whoosh the wheels on the bus go around
and round round and around run around
and we go into the airplane everything
was good yeah yeah yeah yeah but it it
was a it was an exhausting Journey
because we went with the airplane we
didn't go to our final destination we
went to the mamaia airport and from
there we took
a
train we took a
train uh and then we took another train
and then we took another train so we
took like three trains in total um
glasses no
uh until we reach our destination it was
like it was really really
hot so that's a bit man and I was tired
because I didn't sleep much because it
was early and I streamed the day before
and I still had to pack and all that it
was a bit rough but we were we made it
and everything was cool and I think we
even went to the beach right away more
or less right away yeah so this Mama Mia
Airport was really no problem to arrive
[Music]
in I did not know that it would be a big
problem to leave from the same
airport but my whole friend group and me
we went through uh the Mama Mia airport
on our way to Italy but on the way back
for some reason they all abandoned me
for cheaper
flights via Ryan Air that would also be
like so that they don't have to take a
train and all that back to that mamamia
airport like they had a closer
connection that was cheaper so they were
like yeah adios
[Laughter]
Amigo um while I because like they took
so long to book flights and I was like
okay this is a situation where I have to
do the first step so that my friends
follow the lead so I booked flights
before everybody else did and then they
waited still after that they waited a
long time to book flights and then they
found like this connection um with the
Ryan Air one on the way back and I was
like Well I booked mine already so have
fun I
guess so I was going to be alone on the
mam Mia airport on my way back uh but
yeah crowd strike actually started
apparently the day after we traveled uh
to Italy and I only heard about it a
little bit over the weekend but it also
resolved itself over the weekend
seemingly so we were kind of lucky that
we were not affected by it but but uh uh
I was told that the airlines that were
affected by it were not uh the one that
we ended up using so even if it was on
the day uh we would not have been
affected actually
lucky so we were double lucky wrong day
and wrong Airline but they were
apparently a lot of airlines affected
yeah so they use
Linux it was like a Windows
thing question
mark That's funny do they use lenux no
way no
way like every airport airline that uses
Windows got
[\h__\h] a cloud some people write Cloud
strike some people Crow mostly crowd
strike it's like an anti I'm not 100%
informed about it I only heard like
rough
notes Windows update
broke the
antivirus that the Airlines use why does
everybody use the same airline is that
like a
trusted uh antivirus is that a trusted
antivirus from the
airlines weird weird
stuff but I wasn't affected so that's
okay okay now the mamia
airport as I said was fine to arrive in
but not fine to leave from and
it's it was not nice let me tell you
that so on my way back that was uh
yesterday on my way back I did find um
cuz like there were other people like
everybody my friend Circle and all the
other people that we knew they all went
through the other airport with the other
Airline I I me and maybe a few more
other people but like only one or two
more people that I knew were going for
the Mami airport and I found one uh like
acquaintance who went for the mam
airport as well why am I doing it like
this can is there any other other way to
do it
yeah and basically we somewhat traveled
decided to just travel together so uh we
took a
bus to the mamamia
airport at least that's good because
otherwise we would have taken several
trains again but there was a direct bus
so that's nice we took the direct bus
but I was tired as [\h__\h] again and uh we
had traffic
jam but without traffic J we would have
uh arrived 2 hours before the pl plane
leaves and it's a 1 hour flight only
short distance so 2 hours before is no
problem at all in Europe it's like
that's how early I go when I have a
longdistance flight
actually so no problem with a little bit
of delay with a traffic jam uh we did
have half an hour traffic jam apparently
but at the same time while we were in
the bus our flight was also delayed half
an hour so that was fine it evened it
out right that's that's nice so we're
back back to 2 hours then we arrive at
the airport we immediately go to the
like um checkin for our bag but we
noticed this airport is
like kind of weird like I've been to
many
airports in my lifetime and like in
Europe and in everywhere it's small
airports big airports but this is the Le
least organized looking and and least
intuitive airport I've ever seen like
all the checkin counters are hard to
find and like they they are very SE in
separate sections and it's just really
weird really really rly aligned but we
finally found it and uh with a lot of
time to
spare uh we checked in our
bags uh
yeah airport on hard mode yes it was so
disorganized already at this point but I
did not know what was Yet to Come
however my friend who took the other
airplane uh recommended me to try a
pizza place at the airport that was
really good apparently when they took it
last year and I was kind of hungry and
we had still a lot of time to
spare uh until the boarding even started
so we decided to take a b pizza so we
had neapolitan pizza which was really
good
and
considering what was about to happen I
wish we would have not taking it that
easy but if they had everything under
more control then this would that we
could would have been fine but they
certainly do not have anything under
control uh um after we were done eating
the pizza uh we finally got up to find
the
security gate thing where you check your
stuff and your belongings and uh first
of all finding that was very confusing
as well
um you know
what I think I'm going to put up a
[\h__\h] map
if is this can I even do I even
understand what this
is no
[Music]
no may
maybe I think maybe nah I'm not sure no
I'll do it without I'll do just like by
feeling of my memory so we finally find
some stairs that lead up to the security
thingy it's on the floor above but then
there's a lady standing there who's
saying no no go the other way all the
way all the way over she's just pointing
somewhere to the other side um because
those stairs they were like there was a
tape over them so you couldn't pass
somehow they didn't want people to use
that so we kept on looking for the other
uh
entrance into that or to at least go to
the second floor um and then we finally
find it it's like really far away and we
go up and then we see basically we come
up from some
wait we come up from some
escalator and I think you could say
let's see uh he
here here
are
some
security gates not many but maybe
approximately this many where you go
through by scanning your ticket and then
you know the the usual like uh you put
your
bags uh and you go through a human
scanner and all that so that's
there and we didn't even look closely
over there because we we were a little
bit far from that um but what we saw
was you know the usual a
line a line that was very very full and
we were looking for where to go to like
join this line and there was like a
little bit of a cut off here and there
was a guy standing here who uh people
were constantly going to with tickets
and asking him to let them into this
line because there were a lot of
people here standing like it's just a
cut off here so that people could pass
through to go somewhere else or to join
the line if they
are well important enough in terms of
their boarding
times um so we like still kind of
clueless to how long this line is um but
we go there we check with him he's like
he's like pointing to that direction we
go there and then there's another person
here and then we realize okay this is
not it uh the line then
goes over
there and then uh
uh there was I think another
[Music]
turn that was I think maybe I don't know
exactly anymore but there was another
turn and then there was the doors to
outside of the
airport
so
here people were also standing I think
there was another person maybe standing
here and then and it was like this back
into the airport kind
of so this was not normal especially
because I swear to you go
Gods there was another
crazy really not understandable amount
of
lines here as well
this was packed with I swear over a
thousand people probably more they were
especially this area was dense as [\h__\h]
and then all these lines were dense as
[\h__\h] and it was so long like it took us
a long time to find the end of the line
in the first place and then we realized
that we were [\h__\h] because uh normally
at a small air airport you know like you
we were going to be there when the
boarding would start but now with this
kind of security
[Music]
chaos we we knew we were so I knew I was
[\h__\h] but my acquaintance that I found
that I picked up to like give me some
company was pretty calm about it I was
starting to panic
I was a little bit starting to panic
because when we started to stand in line
uh I think our boarding was about to
start like maybe in 10 minutes or so but
then it would be like 30 minutes of
boarding but at least while we stood in
line our flight was in total of like all
of this it was during this time it was
uh delayed two more times in total like
minutes so that I I at some point I was
like praying for there to be more delays
because more and more it seemed that we
were not going to make it and it was
late and I don't think we could have
gotten out of Italy so we start standing
in line and I'm stressing and my my
acquaintance is like it's going to be
fun it's going to be fun I'm like I'm
[\h__\h] stressed out I can't I can't and
there's like you know these people here
standing there right so I noticed that
our boarding has begun so I think I
checked with one of them here before
boarding began and they were like yeah
this line just go into the line but then
at this point at this checkpoint we were
boarding uh boarding has begun so while
I'm in the line I asked this person
while they were being bed by a lot of
other people from the outside too who
could not believe this line either and
they were like let me in please and
they're like no you got to go over there
this is not the beginning of the line so
I asked this guy here this airport staff
uh volunteer helper I'm like hey our
boarding just started can
you uh like do something is this okay
can we make it because I noticed
actually when we were standing around
here there was one lady going around
yelling out names from destination that
were literally like they had like one
more minute to board uh so she would
that's when she was like going around to
call out the names uh of the
destinations to see if anybody uh wanted
to go there and was stuck over here um
uh and our destination was not part of
it so I was like yeah okay we're already
boarding and they're
not calling it out okay but then and
here I asked him because it was really H
here we weren't boarding yet but here we
were boarding so I was like hey can we
is there like I don't know can we like
get through uh faster and he checks his
phone they're like communicating over
WhatsApp it seems and on WhatsApp
there's like a there's a they have like
messages of the
destinations that can get priority at
this moment because uh the boarding is
cutting it close and he checks his list
and he checks for our destination and
says no not yet not priority yet and
that's when I like understand what's
going
on these this airport is absolutely
[\h__\h] um so I'm like okay we're already
boarding but this is not considered
priority yet how long do I have to wait
until we're being considered priority
but I figured that once we were being
considered priority the lady who's
calling out the names of the
destinations will say our destination
and then we'll just say yep us us us
please um anyway we were getting through
it was getting really close when we
finally got into this
zigzag um it was I think maybe 15
minutes left until
boarding but this amount of lines looked
like it would take I don't know 30
minutes especially cuz like when we were
going through here I thought we would be
fine because I didn't really quite see
how bad this part was but once I saw it
I was like uh-uh we're not going to make
it we're actually not going to make it
we're not going to make it [\h__\h] I was
getting really nervous and actually like
like for for 40 minutes or so standing
in line I was like losing my mind and
then
um over here I guess there was a
uh wait yeah there were like some gates
here too where you scan your ticket to
even get through uh to the next lines
and we scanned it here and actually
there was a sign here that said uh that
you're not allowed to enter this zone
until 120 minutes before you fly so you
can't even be purposefully ear
cuz I guess they're trying to not
overcrowd the
airport but then I
uh what was it did I ask another person
here I don't think I was able to but I
noticed there was a lady going around
here calling out the destinations again
and I was trying to hear if she was
saying our destination but it didn't
seem so and so we just had to go further
further
further um but it was really really
close and if you're like somewhere over
here in the line you can't even reach
one of these volunteers to ask anything
you're like stuck there and you can't
talk to anybody so I was just hoping
that we would soon reach another
volunteer and could check if something
can be done because time was taking and
then finally we got into this part uh
and I'm about to go into this part and I
hear the lady more clearly because it
wasn't really audible over here and I
hear her and she says something that
sounds like our destination but not
exactly I think maybe she was saying it
in Italian couldn't really hear it like
if she was saying it in English I would
have understood but the Italian
pronunciation of our destination may
have been
different so um but I'm still freaking
out so I still want to ask her so once I
got to this point I'm like scy scy scy
senora and I tell her um I'll boarding
ends in 3
minutes and then she like looks our
destination up and she's like oh you're
so late and I'm like well
yeah we were already boarding here and
you guys didn't like think it was
important for us to get through so you
know and then she says yeah okay enter
this PR prority line because for all of
this there's like this one priority line
kind of where people keep on being sent
to if it's urgent and they they put us
in here but the priority line is not
perfect either uh it's still pretty long
and yeah it's pretty bad and like at
some point we finally make it for
here and this is where I'm really like
about to cry because literally uh I I
think okay here maybe it was still like
7 minutes left but like here it was
legit 3 minutes left until boarding ends
um and boarding ends 10 minutes before
the flight so uh I I put I I throw my uh
bag into one of the
trays uh immediately and I me I I I try
my best to be as fast as possible and
I'm like shaking and I'm really about to
cry like I'm trying to hold it in I get
through but then there's like these
other people who are really slow and
like putting their bags before mine
and and I'm losing my mind and then I
finally get my back at the moment
because like this is like one of those
moments where you you want to be fast
but you can't be any faster than you
already are because you have to wait for
other people or you just in a situation
where you can't move any faster than you
want but the moment I got my bag we like
booked it we absolutely we booked it and
we ran to find the gate because even
that was like kind of hard to find and
there were were barely any signs but I
followed my women's intuition and I
booked it another word I learned
recently and I book
it and I find the gate and there's
they're they're currently uh calling out
no names they're just saying uh this
flight to this destination is boarding
now not like last call or whatever but
it should be I'm feeling like it should
be like there's one minute left to board
maybe I don't know um and there's no one
else standing there anymore there's just
one lady and we uh get to her and I'm
like uh is it still booring and she's
like yeah you're you're so late why are
you so late and I'm like um um you work
at this I'm just thinking to myself you
work at this airport you know this
situation right you know what this
airport is like right what do you mean
I'm late I tried everything to be faster
but I was not considered priority uh in
terms of like next flights that should
be you know put further to the
front
um but that that's when I like kind of
was like
crying uh but yeah we kept on running
and we ran and then we had to go into a
bus and uh yeah me and my acquaintance
were they they had to call a bus just
for us we were the only ones in the bus
we were the last to board and we
were so close like legit if we would
have been there 2 minutes after I am
pretty sure they would have closed it
completely and it would have been gone
forever now somewhere in this line I was
getting curious if this is a normal like
situation for this airport and I looked
it up and it was two months before
several months before there were people
complaining about this situation saying
the same thing as I said arriving at
this airport is fine leaving at this
airport is terrible the lines go out of
the airport and back in again and out
again I don't [\h__\h] know this is an
insane airport like apparently this is
normal for this Airport
and I'm never going to use this airport
again out of the airport yeah our line
was also like this whole part is out of
the
airport where is this airport what's
this airport it's called mam Mia
airport no
it's it's the bologna airport look it up
on Google reviews and see scroll a
little bit and see what some people are
saying who had the worst days like
me absolutely this is this was the most
stressful situation at an airport or
maybe one of the top three that I've
ever had because there's nothing I could
do nothing I could do we we were at the
airport well in advance and yeah we ate
a pizza but apparently while we were
eating the pizza this line was not so
bad yet because uh some other people
that we met in the airport in the
airplane they I asked them like when
they went in and if they experienced the
same and they said no so like this kind
of all of this kind of formed in a
matter of like half an
hour I don't know why but it seems like
there's some certain Rush times when it
gets like really [\h__\h] bad
yeah it's it's just insane I I was so
terrified and anxious and like my heart
was racing I was shaking I heard my
heart
going all review pictures are of the
lines yeah please look at it I'm not
kidding I am not kidding yeah you're not
priority also airport you're lit yeah
what the [\h__\h] are you saying to me you
work here and I I I do not envy these
volunteers it looked really stressful
for them it's not their fault you know
the airport is the airport's fault for
not hiring more people and have a more
organized like system but
like like you if you work here I'm just
saying you know the situation you can't
blame these millions of uh
Travelers for how [\h__\h] I've never seen
something like this I've never seen such
a line ever before except maybe for
Comic
Market uh in
Japan and it wasn't like you you
wouldn't guess it would be like that
when you just arrive at the airport when
you go back it it's like this
Insanity Windows
please oh yeah in the dod Stadium okay
there's several places where you could
expect a line like this yeah
but so I'm never going to use that
airport again I've learned my lesson
because apparently this is a very common
situation at this
airport sorry I'm drinking my I tea in a
weird
way yeah kind of
crazy 10 out of 10 artwork f thank you I
think I recreated it pretty
nicely uh what's my closi doing wait
what does that mean
again what does that mean again closest
oi cloned
oi clean
oi clever
oi clown oi am I a clown to you
closet
o what what does it actually
mean number two o that's not what that
means crazy no it's
CL but yeah I have a few more tangents
maybe but this was just an opening
tangent to get this painting uh done
we're actually going to play Fallout
today I put out a uh schedule so check
it out it's on Twitter if you want to
see what we're doing this week uh now
let's have some fun with Fallout I don't
know if I remember how to play this game
though uh we will see we'll
see we'll see I don't know where we
stopped last time
yeah this is a Fallout
stream oh well am I going to do full
screen did I do full screen previously
or did I say oh it's such a like old
game I don't why is it showing this
Discord
thing wa
sure should I do full screen
did I do full
screen no should I cuz I want to show my
merchandise
thing not sure if I did full screen I
don't think I actually I think I didn't
do full
screen in the past but we
can today where would I put
myself in that case Al I guess I guess
we're hiding this for now buy my
merchandise though buy it buy my buy my
birthday merchandise
please yeah I didn't do full screen but
let's
see it's been a
while it's been a hot
minute continue from your last save game
yeah where where were we
literally Alice MF laugh to all know of
the Crimson has additional jobs
available okay I don't know if I want to
do them what what are we up
to this is the Crimson
caran I don't know what I was [\h__\h] this
is a problem when you play things like
more like with breaks in between okay I
know how to get into this
this is the
quest talk talk to the Brotherhood of
Steel Elder at we wanted to do this
right or did we like for sure we wanted
to do much of this do v v help the
boomas around
Nellis okay we can do that please do V
it's Peak go back to the Boomer place
thank you for the pinky yay W is back
[Music]
yay Amnesia role
play okay yeah I know I helped someone
with his love
interest uh this is like the taking
pictures
thingy tell me if I'm close to one of
these
inform the Yes Man ah the Yes Man the
Yes
[Music]
Man yes ma'am okay so if I do the V
thing where where are we then uh asked
to
go it's giving me several spots can I go
to any of them
Nellis hangers Nellis Air Force and
what's the what's the other one
huh oh no that's the that's not the
those markers should I just go to all of
them the hanger
okay okay I'm being thrown into this
cold water I don't really
know what I'm doing but we'll figure it
out
e for exit I always want to press Escape
that will not change and it's probably
worse now than it was
before uh the map let's go to the local
map okay there's one really
close if I go straight maybe no if I go
in
here money
hello who are those you can't keep that
thing under control control I will what
thing my
dog Janet Janet isn't
she Janet and Jack are those the people
I put together
no no where who am I supposed to talk
to oh one of them Jack I've never been
so happy in my entire life
what do you do me I work with loyal
mostly Electronics work in robotics
keeping the old Technologies alive right
wait is this even what I need to
do loy's a great man but he's getting on
in years so a younger's got to learn
everything he knows this this the guy
that'd be me the man knows how to fix
and build just about everything that was
ever made it's not easy keeping up with
them if oh wait what recover a lady is
this is this not another difference side
quest did I say that sometimes I just
say stupid things sorry about that Pearl
will tell you when the time comes if I
mean I should really be
going
huh
what sorry I don't I don't really
understand these markers anymore is this
all for the main
quest help the Boomers around NS oh just
oh I just need to help all of
them with everything you can't keep that
thing under control I will mf's been
riding asses again better lay low I
don't know how you survived the
bombardment that's incredible so it's
just like did that Quest is just telling
me to do all of the
quests I
guess uh
okay so including
them wait where did they go
did you give me a quest now I don't
think you did so happy why why would you
give me any other Quest you I already
helped you okay he seems to be
agreeing is there anyone else in
here this there's
there's the Jack guy but also I guess
him
lo I hope knows what she's doing letting
you wander around Nellis as you
please I'm looking for ways to make my
Stu useful if that's so how about you
look into repairing the solar arrays on
the roof of the generator building wow
that already sounds complicated about it
but it's a long way to walk my old bones
and there's been that ant problem over
near there ant problem you can't miss
the array it's on top of the generator
building smack dab in the middle of
Nellis between the two runways it's
definitely complicated where should I
look for the spare parts huh if we had
spare parts do you think I'd be asking
you to fix the damn things that's rich
now maybe you're just lacking spares a
while back and Jack and I have been
doing our best to patch the arrays up as
best we can sadly we're at our Wit's End
there have to be spare parts somewhere
around the Wasteland but I just don't
know where to direct you you may have
noticed we don't get out much
H okay be sure to stop on back and let
me know what wait so what kind of spare
parts anything specific or just like
electronic spare
parts because I even saw some in
here does it say what kind of
Parts find the spare array Parts maybe
it's like specific ones not not
something like this these scrap
Electronics
they always Pro their problems on me
yeah they just love me too much they see
I am the hero to save their everything
sister but who's going to help me who's
going to be my hero huh
huh I want to get up here oh you can get
up here
yay that's
cute okay where the [\h__\h] where the [\h__\h]
are those parts are you going to show me
on the
map uh
uh are those all the
parts is oh oh oh here as
well I can be your hero
[Music]
baby no
that's song from
Shrek it really well okay ah yeah right
that that's the song that I know from
World of Warcraft uh clips
from two million years ago I can be a
hero baby like really dramatic sad World
of Warcraft roleplay
Clips ah
ah you can take my breath
away that's the right
direction this is going to be dangerous
I think I see one of those
ants and a bee how do I shoot where's my
how how where are the
guns where are the guns
how do you how do I change the
gun 1 2 3 4 5 6 is not working
anymore it to me it looks more like
spiders but nah the closer I got the
more yeah it looks like
a o nice one
Ro what the [\h__\h] oh my what the what did
my dog
do what was
that
dog Rex get up come
on what the [\h__\h] did he do oh he's
getting back up wait is that like your
your attack is like exploding yourself
to explode others but then you die in
the process what are you doing
what are you
doing okay I'm kind of far away from it
it's like this
way is it in
there it's kind of
far the ants
explode no you guys are saying yes so
the the dog explodes
wait are you saying I need to go here
the main gate is at the front where is
the
front that's the main gate is at the
front you should be saying the front is
at so and
so where is the
gate maybe the front is over there or
all the way over there but I would think
it's over there
this is a place for a photo oh maybe
like this
part how do I do that
again take a picture of the helius one
sign how do I do that again how do I
take a picture
again f11
nah no
way
uh really
no the camera
weapon I have a camera
weapon uh codak this one
yeah this looks like what ladin
has how do I this how do I do how am I
out of film how do I take a
picture oh oh it seems like I have taken
like several pictures it just didn't
really sound like I did all right
y I think I need to reassign all my
weapons it seems like it lost all the
assignments but I'm okay for
now oh
that
[Applause]
flag was from who
again are these my enemies or my friends
NCR oh NCR they're my
friends so can I get in this is a
restricted area State your business and
I want to steal your
parts
uh h
uh oh should I offer them my
help
maybe you're being here as a start
Soldier we aren't exactly overflowing
with Troopers here but if you really
want to help us talk to the idiot with
sunglasses in the back of the plant
building okay at least tr get this place
R for months and hasn't made any forward
progress talk to the idiot wearing
sunglasses
uh okay later
but so am I allowed to steal the parts
or am I just actually going to take them
in alleged
way if I were allowed to steal them that
would be taking them in a legit way but
am I supposed to steal them or just I'm
allowed okay where are they but first
sunglasses
guy uh
somewhere outside how do I get outside
this
way what is this
place
what medical
clipboard
beer is
this what's this what's this what's this
this building is a maze yeah I can feel
it
already which door do we take maybe this
this
door hello when I got this assignment I
was hoping there'd be more
gambling M then you got to go to New
Vegas
baby you're in the wrong place
fishing battery police
Bon I
[Music]
need I need uh Parts we're supposed to
be relieved any day that's what they
keep telling us I don't think anyone's
coming I can open this really can I have
stim pack let's
go thank
you stim packs are always very
appreciated
[Music]
oh my mic is peeking a little a that's
because this is Peak
Wawa
Peak I don't know if I want to try to
unlock these doors I don't want to get
in
trouble I'm why am I why am I I'm in the
[\h__\h] maze
get me out of
here
oh maybe for
fixing do I need to fix how do I fix
again
ah what just happened give
me
R
oh h
I guess I can't fix
it am I in the wrong I thought I only
have one I thought I had another
one
a okay where the [\h__\h] am
I we're supposed to be relieved any day
that's what they keep telling us I don't
think anyone's coming but but I
came I'm here
is this not am I not who you wanted to
come over I'm sorry for disappointing
you another
sack fancy lady
snacks snack cakes only oh wait did it
say Lads or lady cuz I somehow read lad
lady did it say Lads damn it well I am
also a fancy lady excuse me
Eastern reflector control terminal
password
n Eastern reflector control
what is this for this can I tell
him on Tuesday February 16th at 2m. D
will be running a test of argument and
its connectivity with our plan security
system under no circumstances should any
employee be out doors under the plant
grounds until the alarm claxon has
ceased and
claen that's a new song a new capop
song all clear is given we have deaf and
dismemberment waivers from all employees
on file and are not responsible for any
accidents that should occur during this
procedure
okay the initial testing of Archimedes
Arch Arch archimed was a success though
not an unqualified one several minor
systems were overloaded despite all
precautions taken and a 2 and 1 half
minutes of downtime following the test
is something we can work on improving
more importantly we have received
reports from nearby facilities that they
experienced system frying power
fluctations at the time of the test
notably the Black Mountain
Communications aray and the military
bunkers at the Hidden Valley we're going
to make it Priority next time to prevent
such collateral damage uh-huh
Ares Bren Scott low of the US Army will
be visiting the facility starting next
Monday and staying on site indefinitely
when
AR
KES uh goes live he will be the only
person here allowed to author authorize
its use for anything other than a test
civilian employees are not required to
salute but it is expected of everyone
that you obs observe Furrow grooming and
hygiene regiments and dress neatly while
the general is with us the general
expects the best from all of his men and
Poseidon men should be no different in
the presence of such a fine and
decorated soldier Poseidon men oh
posidon net the people here are called
poso men
what oh oopsie wait same thing can I
tell him a proide on energy publication
for new employees as a member of the
posidon family it will be natural for
you to become enthusiastic about the
incredible Endeavors you'll be
undertaking with us and to want to tell
others but just a second there my good
man let's take a minute to consider what
could happen if com company information
fell into the wrong hands and whose
hands those might be can I tell my wife
well let's say you do you tell her not
to tell anyone your bond is s sacred but
a woman's idle tongue is the devil's
play thing no sooner do you leave for
work the next day than she on the phone
telling her best friend candy then candy
tells Gertie Gertie tells Maxon Maxon
tells Lulu while Lulu is telling Doris a
Chinese agent posing as an American
operator listens in and the next thing
she's on the line with the Forbidden
City singing like a treasonous canery
the following day you and your wife are
bound in shackles and China is sitting
at the controls of our entire
Arsenal can I tell my children what
father wouldn't want his kids to look up
to him don't be that father one day it's
School Ivan bikov will get more than
lunch money out of your kids he'll have
National secrets and while they're par
parad parading him through Red Square as
a national hero your children will be
working in forc labor camps right next
to you and your beautiful young wife
who's now wrinkled and homely since the
Communists have banned makeup because it
expresses
individuality can I tell my drinking
buddies surely if there's somewhere safe
a man can place his trust it is with his
other male friends but how much do you
really know about them are they friends
or comrades don't be too sure even the
most transparent window can hide Secrets
when it's lined with iron curtains
always remember you are a member of two
families now and you have obligations to
both but your obligation to the Poseidon
family is greater because while your
children may misbehave and your friends
may change and your wife may nag and
cheat on you posidon energy will always
be paying for and protect in your way of
life don't tell anybody about anything
about the projects of President energy
when pressed tell them that your job is
repetitive and not worth discussing but
the company is nurturing and gives good
benefits and is always looking for new
Talent can I tell
wa oh well that was fun a fun read a fun
little read
at the end with a little bit
of uh advertisement to get people to
work
there basically they're under an NDA
relatable can I tell can I tell my kids
about whole Al what I do no you cannot
because they're being listened in by so
and
so no I'm suffering I can't tell anybody
I'm about to [\h__\h] explode I'm also
about to explode and blow up this whole
place because it's a [\h__\h] Maze and I
don't know where to go but where did I
just come from did I just come from up
here
no this is this is yeah that was a
really relatable little
thing happens to me all the time I
always ask jenma can I tell this person
can I tell this person and Jenai is like
um no do you want to like [\h__\h] and
everything oh just kidding that's not
really what we discussed at all I don't
ask those questions
um what about this door oh this is
interesting this is looking
interesting eyelasses oh
oh wait are you the guy your name is
fantastic who the hell are you fantastic
baby bring you in to replace me they're
replacing me aren't
they I don't think so unless you told
your wife about your job then uh you're
going to be replaced
immediately
uh why are you worried about being
replaced worried do I look worried to
you I've got this under control baby no
one else can do what I do here what do
you do what else I'm in charge this
whole operation depends on me no
fantastic what is your job my job is
being in charge sucking my teth what do
you do being in charge I'm being in
charge that's my
job it's like it's like it's like when
your job is Beach what's your what's
your job Beach what do you do at the
beach I uh Beach I do Beach so he also
what he does is just being in charge
yeah I get it I get it it's uh
understandable I
I don't know what you do but I just know
that you're in
charge what exactly do you
do [\h__\h] man everything I push buttons I
turn dials I read numbers sometimes I
make up little stories in my head about
what the numbers mean oh what one time I
imagined they were a code to get into a
vault full of naked women wow man how
cool would that be well that would be so
sick dude well that's amazing world dude
that's I love it man how'd you get this
job it was easy man they were going door
too asking if anyone knew any scientists
I said Look No Further oh they asked me
if I knew anything about power plants I
said as much as anyone I had ever met
they asked me how well I understood
theoretical physics I said I had a
theoretical degree in physics
they said welcome
aboard I have a theoretical degree in
women hot
women no man but no mine is more
practical I just don't know what effect
it's going to have over there controls
power in this building that station has
readouts on the computer network that
big map there makes a crazy noise uh
Sparks come out of that slot if you put
stuff in it and I'm learning more every
day sick
tight what are you trying to accomplish
well see we're getting power because the
guy running this place is
fantastic but the mirrors outside aren't
aimed right so we're running at 1%
efficiency and I guess that just isn't
good enough for some [\h__\h] but why
don't you trouble is most of the
controls for this place aren't here
they're in the tower and that place has
some crazy pre-war security system that
the dumb [\h__\h] NCR set off when they took
over killed two guys now they won't go
near it they want me to make an omelet
but I can't break any of their eggs know
what I'm
saying don't say something so
traumatizing to my
people how would someone retarget the
mirrors there's these two terminals
outside they control the mirrors I tried
fooling with them but didn't get very
far you'd have to get them to talk to
the main frame up in the tower then do
the rest from up there I'm guessing but
it sounds good right hey you're not
thinking about going up there are you
well of course I'm going up there well
hey if you find yourself up at the main
frame do yourself a favor and make sure
you send the power to the right place it
needs to go to the strip and McCaron
uh-huh uh why because I get paid that's
why per kilowatt hour whatever the hell
that is that's where the NCR wants the
power so that that's where I want it but
you know you do that maybe I put in a
good word for you with them Fantastic's
Little Helper there's a reputation you
can hang your hat on a if I'm
Fantastic's Little
Helper then I want to
be divine can my name be
divine fantastic and divine here you
want this it's the password to one of
the terminals outside found it written
on one of the Stalls in the
bathroom
okay okay wow important man doing
important things hey don't push me
around but your office looks kind of
nice I'm not going to lie many buttons
that go be beep up must be
fun he even sleeps here it
seems next to the
buttons what's in
here o ooh only alcohol hey
man I am a strat Edge player so I cannot
use that oh you got a little other
helper I thought it was your only helper
I thought it was special who is ignasio
UN to see a new face here are you a
soldier or a
scientist both now
both my interest in this place is
scientific oh wow that sounds so smart
then we have that in common home do you
typically work with oh oh I have a
speech answer this is your Turf for all
I know you could have me killed for my
allegiance who are you
with well but I am with the NCR so I
think that's a good thing
anyway
oh but I want to use it it will unlock a
secret plot line okay let's go very well
yes I'm part of the Followers of the
Apocalypse apocalypse familiar we seek
peace and the spread of knowledge
knowledge that must never be lost to the
world now your turn sounds
important I want what you want that's
reassuring although many who've made
that claim to the Followers of the
Apocalypse over the years have had less
than pure intentions but if it's really
as you say then take my advice this
installation carries with the dangers
that no one here has realized take care
of what you do here and who you listen
to some things are best left buried with
the old world oh like what what more is
there to this place than a power plant I
don't entirely know our records on the
company that built this place suggest
that their dealings were not only in
energy but also in weapons where are
they and I've seen equipment here marked
with symbols used by the pre-war
military targeting computers shock
sensors a C- word comes up repeatedly in
the papers I've looked through here yeah
Archimedes yeah I saw that I saw that in
the PCS m
you think Archimedes is a weapon they
built here yes and the technology they
have in this facility is like nothing
I've seen some of it reminds me of
Enclave equipment but more advanced a
weapon based upon it would be
catastrophic no matter who claimed it
it's no wonder the Brotherhood wouldn't
give it
up the Brotherhood of Steel knew about
the Archimedes they weren't here for me
to ask but I doubt they were here for
electricity when the NCR first came came
here it was under Brotherhood control
they usually star clear of one another
but something here changed their minds
the brotherhood's interest in pre-work
technology has always been in weapons
it's likely they were trying to reclaim
Archimedes when the NCR arrived H
okay
uh the NCR does not know about the
weapon not yet by some miracle they've
hired an imbecile to try and decipher
the systems here he spent months working
at One console trying to get the solar
reflectors to track the Sun what he
doesn't know is that the only thing the
console controls is the plant's intercom
system huh I tried to tell him but he
insisted that the largest console had to
be the most important still it's only a
matter of time huh he means fantastic
right that's the imbecile uh NCR asked
me to help increase the plant's power
output then I would say do it as long as
the power of this plant is committed to
the regional grid and not to a weapon we
are safe if you're the one to restore
output then you can route the power
where you choose and they'll never be
the wiser I can't get you past the
security in the tower but I can be of
some help I've discovered a password for
one of the mirror control terminals
outside you need
it a different
one where should I route the power oh
the NCR has their own designs for it no
doubt but resist the urge to send it
only to the thriving communities H the
need for power is great everywhere
Distributing it evenly is the most
rational and is he telling me to send it
somewhere else from where he wants me to
send it h the Fantastic guy why would
you trust me with this I'm a man of
letters I'd be Torn to Pieces by the
security system they have in that Tower
I'd never reach the main frame but
eventually the NCR will or if not them
Caesar's Legion they will use this place
for war because the possibility exists
you might do anything else you're the
only choice I
have well well you said you have a
password and you're not giving it to
me goodbye is it going to be like in the
quest marker thing what he didn't give
it to
me he gave it to me I didn't what what
is
it how do I have it I don't
know it's in my notes oh okay I didn't
say it out loud
well this is kind of like the the
yapping is kind of complicated I don't
really understand everything they're
saying but sure I'll press some buttons
and I'll go beep up beep up and then
I'll save the world
right I'll I'll make the elect
electricity go to a nice place and and
that will do the
trick I don't know why they can't do it
TBH but
okay we are outside
what about the other Quest I need to get
those
parts what about the other
Quest so it's like I guess across these
around these
thingies there just some scrap ones
lying
around let's
see yeah fantastic is dumb
no I get it okay there's a guard there
but I can go in right is it in there
we're supposed to be relieved any
day may maybe I don't
think ow my [\h__\h]
[Applause]
leg
ah ah
ah
I could do this
forever okay where is the scrap
Point what the [\h__\h]
my arm my
arm
why
why why
isn't this one of the things I need it's
kind of huge I don't understand wait let
me heal
myself well can I sleep there oh yeah
how can be
oh I just noticed chunky wonky it came
over to to um see if I'm okay that's so
cute that is so so
cute can I sleep on here okay I'm not
allowed to take the bed but I'm allowed
to take
this so cute chunky wonky she was
worried about me making those Peter
Griffin
noises
oh do I need
this
maybe electron charge pack sure
no okay what I still don't
understand
what what's the scrap is this not
ah reflector panels on this array are
damaged you could salvage some of the
array's parts would you'd like the
Solage array repair 20 or higher
required do I have 20 or
higher thank you for the right Super
Chat I didn't realize you have to kind
of stand on top of
it uh try anyway
okay array
salvaged okay so I took it with
me and that's one
of I need all of
them okay no problem uh there's one if I
go that way I think
uh around there okay okay okay okay okay
will they all take
20 okay then there should be no
issue okay so far today's quests have
been
interesting I liked it so far what I've
been getting
into okay these are kind of far
yeah I see the compass but it's like I
want to see how far it is and I can't
see that on the compass cuz I mean I see
a million Quest markers but it's like
reled it could be really far it could be
really close I want to see what I'm
looking
for
okay shut up shut up about the compass
you little [\h__\h] I know I'm about the
compass but it's
confusing it
sucks can't [\h__\h] control
yourself this
[Music]
do I need
this I feel like I don't
what who you want to fight it's outside
of the fence is it not chill doggo
chill oh oh wait that's the last one
behind
me guys I had so much so much
gelato in Italy and I had some good
cabonara pasta and I had uh a like a
kind of like
a uh what was it padina or so like a a
pizza that's like folded kind
of oh it's
completed and what else did I
have another a
pizza a Bata Pizza my beloved
Bata did I have anything that was not
pizza or pasta
trying to remember but I don't think I
did I love verata
yeah any good
meats can't remember but we also had
good breakfast in our uh in our hotel
like it was a pretty cheap hotel but
they had breakfast until
12 Mama me yeah I've never had a hotel
have breakfast until this
late and it was so help it was so useful
we went to breakfast like at 11:30 every
[\h__\h] day yeah so good and then they
had a pool which was open 24/7 like
throughout the whole night and it was
heated and it turns out I think uh I
don't know if it was like just if they
always have breakfast until 1200 and all
that but I think maybe they may have
considered the the like season like you
know the E events in the city and all
that maybe but yeah there were also a
lot of other hotels who had uh breakfast
that late and also um pools open until
the whole night basically
24/7 so that was really nice so
sometimes we would be like in the water
at like 3:00 a.m.
[Music]
yeah so
nice non wobbly water yeah the ocean
water was not very wobbly
either what where the other Quest that I
want to do so I did the array
Parts wait what I need more didn't it
just say completed repair the broken I
already repaired them did I not when I
stood on them I repaired
them let's do this
yeah smooth water
yeah but not very sefr water but that's
okay we need to go to NAS okay you bring
them to the Boomers okay uh but that's
why I'm still here we got to do
this we got to do this
aha ahuh okay so it's like these two
towers
huh
huh is it this it looks too
close to be what I'm looking for w
parkour parkour
par and now I'm in the middle okay
sorry distance is hard
to uh
imagine I thought I was looking for a
tower
P which one which one which wa one of
these thingies maybe but no well at
least I already set up some bombs and
stuff hey I can't set up set off that
much more can I is it that yeah it's
Dad what exactly am I here for do I go
to the PC probably right I see nothing
that could hurt me
anymore okay activate terminal one
okay I don't have to type it in myself
good
oh arimed testing on Tuesday February is
this the same that I read before oh yeah
I think
so yeah but not with that one funny
email damn
it okay I'm resetting it is that what
I'm supposed to do
yeah okay bye
and then we go to the other be careful
ah I'm telling you be
careful Mama
Mia Mama
[Music]
Mia so eh am I going the right
way over there ah now I see it it's
pretty
hidden can I jump over this
oh they are trying to hit something why
is this one such a maze looking thing oh
is
that is
that do I shoot
you oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh sh
no am
I going to be attacked by
everybody
um no sorry the music scared me but it
seems okay but why what why why why he
was he want to attack my dog is that
just a dog thing is that just what dogs
do it's a dog eats dog world
literally okay no other traps is he was
he was the defense
mechanism
okay he wasn't enemy right why
though I'm with the NCR but I guess
guess like he was acting as the bomb
basically so
H so when do I get to decide who I'm
sending ah oh yeah
okay the main frame
power Arm argumented Security system to
wipe out all
nearby all nearby NCR if I was working
against NCR that's probably what I would
want to do
Are My People able to get out of there
they're just going to teleport
right wait my my my Japanese my Japanese
keyboard is activating let me turn it
off okay now this big
one is there something in here still oh
might want to save why am I sneaking I
don't know am I sneaking ah okay thanks
for telling me should I save let's
save
uh new
okay do we enter for
here I love how they just like put me in
charge even though I just walked in here
they don't really know if they can trust
me
[\h__\h]
what
oh is a
robot what
the what the
[\h__\h] Robo
brain go go no
no what what am
I what am I supposed to
do
no do I have like something that can go
kaboom
on the
robots I have laser rifles I have
hunting rifle maybe hunting
rifle now grenade would be nice
maybe does that even
reach did I even hit
him is it seems to be strong how do I
use Vats again with
v oh
a oh should I shoot that too the 2 22%
is like really
low
[Music]
yeah oh I can't shoot the robot
H try didn't
work
uhoh what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] uh let's eat something
bad angle try to go into the rim across
from
you
okay ah get in get
in
okay like the moment I looked at it I
was like
H probably should take a step back from
[Laughter]
that I was like what is this and then it
hits me and then it hits
[Laughter]
me oh
man oh
man too funny
okay is there anything else dangerous in
here I'm
girl I'm scared to
move what I was wearing this
still what
I'm wearing my naughty nightwear this
whole
time uh I think I can wear
this
okay okay now I'm way more mentally
prepared for this maybe we can even keep
the dog alive
no the dog ah [\h__\h] I
forgot I
[Music]
forgot dog also forgot it
seems so how do you unarm this stuff
again Wonder go how do can you how do
you how do you
I can shoot it hit e on it ah
okay okay
okay there we
go any
more no I think we
good oops it no
okay turret
system can we turn it off
please wow it's such a programmer how do
I know all of
this where did I learn this Tippy toppy
Tippy
toppy oh yeah we're
password Hing to the gate
eight and it's uh okay uh wait do we
know how many letters I haven't done
this in a while I don't think we know
how many
letters uh aain status stages alarms are
all are these all the same amount
anyway let's see how
about how
about uh
Craven one letter
correct
uh alarm alarms two
correct so probably the a in the
middle and something
else okay
[Music]
green a could be this no uh reset
reset
oh ah thatt removed okay I need a reset
though do removed
uh where is
it where is
it reset H uh this this is one
right
okay um alarms had
two a grease had one only
interesting so but this was like if it
says one is correct did it like mean
that it's also not just the letter but
also like it's at the right position
right but that makes me think it was not
the a I'm
confused no I no it was the a probably
but agre didn't have the a at that
position so
M I don't
know I can't
think yeah it's probably the S at the
end how about starts four out of
six ah so definitely the a definitely
the s what's similar Stones no stages is
very similar four out of
six uh stance is also very and status is
very
similar stance
St star S
A basically the letters that were
different was was the RT and the g e so
status it could be status or
STS it was
status
y yeah I know how to do this don't worry
I know
I'm a
hacker hacker
WWA
um what reconfigure targeting parameters
deactivate we we're probably going to
deactivate the turret system
right Alo what's system
information that's
it that's
it okay
deactivate
reconfigure uh
oh oh what but it didn't let me
choose activate the turrets
again e but they'll shoot me ah warning
no targeting
data please exercise caution
yeah let me do it please exercise
caution
H they'll shoot anything
now it's already on leave the PC for a
second
oh
oh oh doggo what
happened are they
gone Danger danger danger danger danger
do where did you
go what what's
happening is that a turret
too what are you doing Dogo what are you
angry
at the wall what did the wall do to
you now deactivate them
again how are you so confused why why
would I not be confused
oh I was sneaking
still they killed the robot for me ah
okay I wish they would also kill each
other so deactivating
again uh powering down DOT do dot okay
what they were still shooting
test
test test test oh it's
off and you're off too
right off to a great
start are you're not even carrying like
anything
[Music]
special maybe efficient
battery I
[Music]
guess oh no take it back take it back
take it back
wait why are they shooting
again why are they shooting
again oh
no what could I give
you the lud tickets they don't weigh
anything egg
I don't need the eggs
right
[Music]
wait please let me do something stop
shooting me thank
you can
combine can combine
oh I think that's it but we're down a
little
bit why why why why why why why why why
why why why why why
why isn't it
off it says activate so it's off
oh there's still like a robot down there
ooh can I get them to kill the robot
when I turn them on
again no where where is it a
where where where where
where should I I'll I'll try again to I
let's see if it works if
I I think this will work will they shoot
it maybe not
oh maybe not okay I'll take care of the
robot
it's hiding because it knows it knows
really nah no
[Music]
way
uh
drinkies oh there we go what
what
what what
what yeah I knew there was something
right in front of me I was like can I
really shoot it I mean it gives me 55%
so no no no
no no no yes yes yes okay now we got 63%
that's even
better okay Critical Strike is it dead
not
[Music]
yet tactical
Retreat shoot no
no yes
[Music]
52 not
no
no no no no
no the turr is on no I turned it
off maybe cuz I uh closed the program
before it was completely
off no it's
off it's just a bot
what what the
[\h__\h] it came out 95% okay I
[Music]
mean oh it tells me to
reload why is someone always trying to
run between us
whoa don't
[Applause]
die I have to save her help it my dog
also don't die
guys come on oh
no I swear to God why why are you guys
so
careless ah okay we did it oh wait I was
using a what what's the gun I'm
using Rex everybody's always running
between
us is there any more of these robots
there's oh God I thought those were
mines but I I should should be more
mindful of Mines shouldn't I
anyway missiles okay but those are heavy
aren't
[Music]
they
B I'm looking out for the
mines and oh computer does not seem to
be
working just
exploring save to
enter yes Save to enter save to
enter save to enter
ah I hate
this sure I'll take all of it thank
you that safe was safe to enter for sure
oh there's more of
these
mhm
mhm fancy lady stand
I'll take the pre- war money thank
you
n what what what what what what what is
it what are you sniffing sniffer
sniffer what are you
sensing what am I supposed to do was
there not something here that H this
thing maybe no SC
uhoh
scanning who was that
[Music]
uh-oh
no quick
safe I guess that was just a little side
room
why did I hear that voice so clearly and
closely oh there's a PC here no not
working step into the open and identify
yourself Simpsons have nothing to
fear it's talking to me area clear
proceeding with search protocol oh it's
searching for
me I cannot wait to find you so I can
kill was a personal favor to Uncle Sam
do you hear that guys it's really
quiet a personal favor to Uncle
Sam they must be over
there oh
oh it's already broken it looks already
broken this one's
broken search
this one's not the talking one I
think I can sleep
here a but right now I'm not even
crippled oh but I oh maybe
I I used the doctor's bag by accident
why is it on
[Music]
E now I want to go back to to my safe
point I I don't have so many I only have
[Music]
three let's go let's go let's go let's
go let's
go I didn't check this
thing okay nothing oh you are in a
different position than before aren't
you
oh I can't sleep cuz there's enemies
nearby
a uh-oh ah okay around this corner for
sure do you think you can hide from
me I'm scared what about the other side
maybe I like the other side more that's
a small room of some
treasure I have to check it out first
[Music]
ah
sorry oh I heard a shot and it was not
mine shots shots shots shots shot shots
shots sh sh sh sh shot sh shot shot shot
did you shoot my dog piece of
[\h__\h]
where where are you
[Music]
chess let's go all my homies love
chess where's my dog
that's
nice
people ah my dog is down
there oh are you
stuck stupid
dog stupid this is why I have cats
he is so stuck he does not want to admit
it he does not ask for
help well there's nothing interesting
down
here look at him being
V
Bako wait Bako that's identify
yourself have nothing to Bak know is
literally what
Louise from zeron Nota says oh she's
running she's booking it what are you
booking let me go with you wait I'm
stuck too
now put down your weapon and submit to
Authority I hear it loud and clear wait
wait wait wait wait wait oh oh oh oh
there's many over there please step into
the open and identify yourself
why did they take so long to find
me why did I take so long to find
them are they where are
they don't just stand
there are they they're not up right
there's a room there that I didn't see
got my eyes peeled huh she's alive
that's a good thing h
thank
you thank
you still
looking still looking me
too this area clear how blind with
search protocol am I wait
warning that worse
what
oh girl please step into the open what
how did I
not Laing CI area
secure they're right
there of deadly force is in progress
areound the area until order has been
restored okay okay okay
okay don't shoot
the Hostile okay
okay plasma rifle should I use the
plasma rifle
okay I thought it wasn't so good
failure what is this teleportation
thingy wa I want to fight some to you
already killed
them a
mommy you're are such a fast
boy what is this can I clone myself can
I be your
closy no you just tell me tell me which
weapon to use and then I'll use whatever
you tell me to use and then we're all
happy oh those are charging stations for
the robots makes
sense that makes a whole lot of
sense H I feel like I'm still not
finding anything
significant move
what what do you mean check your energy
they told me to use a plasma
rifle so don't are you saying don't use
a plasma or laser was it plasma or
laser I got one guide that's all my
fault what can I do
what's the difference between DPS and
damage
o thank you thank you hunting rifle but
I don't want to shoot with rifles all
the
time like what about the revolver is the
revolver okay
where where's the main
frame I don't
see wait this way
maybe oh yeah this way
H oh hello
sir posidon energy employee ID card can
I read that
[Music]
ooh can I read it
huh no there's nothing on
there oh nice
passwords hey I want to read it there's
nothing to read on it I want the lore
what happened to this
guy these cigarettes are not even worth
it I don't know why I'm picking them up
you guys told me before to pick up
cigarettes you just want to you want me
to start smoking don't you you're not
going to get me to start smoking I'm
telling you that oh another employee ID
card what am I going to do with those
are they going to be useful can I tell
people hey this dude
died H because they're lightweight okay
oh see I almost missed this [\h__\h] door
again
unbelievable y
chess milk
bottle coffee and milk H the robots like
like coffee and milk ah wait
what
huh elevator to helus one observation
level I just wanted to see what that
said
what oh I found the main
frame this main frame is currently
unresponsive the amount of power
reaching a terminal seem to be
insufficient restore power to from via
the auxiliary
generator uh now where would that
be probably
upstairs but let me check around a
little
bit the auxiliary
generator what down there
what what this thing oh it's
uh it's smoking
hot the generator looks to be fine but
some kind of large verman has chewed
into the power cable with the proper Kno
how and some scrap metal I should have
picked up
more okay repair or 45
repair of 35 or higher and one piece of
scrap metal oh just one
okay that was
[Music]
easy are these the same email
still I think
so okay so we haven't talked about what
we want to do I think we should not do
what fascinating or whatever his name
was wants to
do I don't think that's what we
want oh there's a full region option too
oh fantastic close
enough full region is what ignasia wants
M I like that but what would this this
is the weapon like giving the energy to
the weapon I guess I don't know
full region emergency output level so
this is like full region but stronger
maybe I don't know AR Med this for the
content not that
[Music]
one I get the
weapon but then what happens to the
people a tiny prank I just a small okay
well let's let's uh inde
D might want to maybe uh do I need a
proper safe I don't
know it upsets
everyone okay will I see them be
upset major
consequences
h h
they get over it if you're nice enough
to them they have no idea you'll see
something all right oh
okay I want to see
something find out let's [\h__\h] around and
find
out
oh well was that now initiate reflect
the retargeting from the console on the
Tower observation
deck arm a Aimes plant defense
system ah do I put on oh so they're dead
now cool AR laser is now armed move to
minimum safe dist before initiating test
can I watch that I want to see when it
[Music]
happens I want see him
die wa shiny wa what the
[\h__\h] is this what ate
the the
cable python this robot has been fitted
with a variety of tools specialized for
industrial maintenance however there's
nothing left in the room for it to
repair oh could you have repaired the
cable
too oh
wonderful that's a good view I would
think but actually I don't see anybody
from up here how do I get down
there go go go go go go go go go do a FL
flip no [\h__\h] way am I doing a
flip oh oh is this an
elevator why are they not that yet down
there no
way I don't I don't know this is not
really what I'm going to be doing right
am I thanks for the rain
we're going to turn back time
right so I don't really have to think
about this too much but
[Music]
um I don't know I don't
know complet are they going to die
I can't [\h__\h]
see
what what on Earth was
that oh oh
oh oh oh
oh oh
beautiful they are still alive though
oh okay yeah they turned red as well so
they certainly don't like me anymore and
kapow yeah stand right there stand right
there and oh fun where is this coming
from what from the
Sun
W what what the
[\h__\h] the sun did
that for observing the energy safety
protocol have a nice day thank you for
for observing the safety protocol okay
cool you're welcome well that was
fun I like how they all like gathered
there to kind of like try to fight
something like how the [\h__\h] are you
going to fight that like good luck
good luck with
that uh so this one I
think we of course don't want to do
that why would I want to do that that's
still full region I guess that's fine
right that's a good
choice
uh should
it do I have to arm the defense system
anyway though don't arm okay okay
okay the choice for the common
man yes everybody deserves
energy you get energy and you get energy
and you get
energy okay but it did say I have to
like finalize it or
whatever you got energy too yeah but not
energy drink
I have so many friends who are like
addicted to energy drinks I was telling
them stop stop drinking so
many I literally only need two sips and
I'm
good but even then I try to avoid it
because that feels like a wasting the
whole
drink
[Music]
activate talk to ignasio Oh Mr Fantastic
will not be happy about this
wait how do I get to him fast oh I want
to see it want to see it again want to
see me do it
again
wo
beautiful maybe is it beautiful I don't
know are you guys happy about this you
should be how do I get
down do they have to go up to go down
can I teleport
maybe go back in
okay praise the sun praise the
wa oh hello why is this thing here I
don't get
it but how do I get to ignas
faster don't tell me I have to walked
same way I got
here
no not really right not
really no
way no
see I'm already
lost this way and then right and
[Music]
then
up and
up and here and up up is okay up is easy
to understand
you're just
chilling and up here
up
yipp and around this nice little robot
but you're taking up the whole [\h__\h]
path
fat ass
robot okay I made it that wasn't too
bad
whoa
so you once you turn this [\h__\h] on you
can
actually
see is this realistic that you can see
the
Reflections going up like
this I've never seen this before
so yeah no no sometimes if it's dusty oh
really speaking of Dusty and because we
had the word apocalypse mentioned
yesterday on Monday you know our flight
was late
and so we had some
time where we could kill some sometimes
so I was like I want to go to the beach
so me and some of my friends we went to
the beach and it was still nice weather
where are you going he's booking it it
was still nice weather so we went to the
beach we paid um this is with a discount
and I find it kind of expensive
but we paid like 10 per person to get a
loue chair at the beach with a sun
umbrella this is with the discount
otherwise and it's uh at the front of
the beach and it would be more expensive
if we didn't have the hotel discount you
think it's je M maybe it is maybe it
is I guess it's
okay yeah and so we were you know taking
our time to go into the water just
chilling we shouldn't have taken so much
time but then we go into the water and
the water was really nice it was like
pretty cool the other days it was pretty
warm and the waves weren't too strong it
was like very calm actually no wobbly
Waters and I was like chilling in the
water with my friends and then we we
look to the to the other end of the
ocean and not not the other end of the
ocean but the other side of the beach
and we
see huge dark clouds Dark Cloud remake
went
when and I'm like ah we'll be fine for
sure they can't possibly come here so
fast right um but they they came over
really
fast and then we saw from far away like
it got like really dusty like the sand
was all in the air like everything
looked really white from the sand and we
saw I feel like we saw something like
the rain
further ahead and we saw it storming
like all the sun umbrellas in like right
in front of us they were still calm but
over there they were
like yeah they were too late to like uh
put them down but then the people in our
area they saw what was happening over
there the storm was brewing so they like
hurried as fast as they could to close
all the umbrella in our
section yeah and we were like hm how
long can we stay in the water with this
storm can we stay through it how long is
it going to take so we just stayed in
the water because it was kind of warmer
in the water than when you get out and I
didn't want to get out and we were like
well even if it rains we're already in
the water we can just hide from the rain
in the
water it's going to bother us less if
we're in the water right m
so we were waiting and waiting and then
there was like close to us there was
another group of fre people in the water
but besides us there really wasn't
anybody left then it it got more and
more stormy and the waves got more and
more violent and it got really dark and
the storm reached our section but we
were like ah apocalypse how fun yay yay
we were just like we were so indecisive
too like do we go out do we stay in what
we do but we saw like everything just
breaking out in the
apocalypse and we were having fun being
dramatic and the other three people they
left and then we were like ah
cowards you're already leaving we're
staying oh thanks for the XP
well but then eventually we kind of got
kicked out there was like uh a
dude Safeguard I guess a
can going with his whistle like ah come
out come out come out I'm like it's not
that bad but yeah it got pretty bad and
then I like we were making our way out
slowly walking through the water because
it's hard to walk in the water and then
I saw from really far away to from my
left side I saw a big ass floaty a
unicorn floaty a big one
like zooming in the highest speed ever
booking
it floating over the water really fast
with the wind to my direction from
really far away and I thought the
Lifeguard further away was trying to
like signal to me to maybe catch it but
it seemed like they were not really
signaling that but I thought I should
catch it because otherwise it's just
going to pollute the
ocean so stood there and I spread my
arms wide open and I was like this is my
mission I'm going to be the hero I'm
going to catch this unicorn floaty and
if I find the person who it belongs to
then they'll be so happy that I saved it
from imminent doom and I I caught it and
I felt so so amazing I felt like a hero
and then the lifeguards again were like
get out get out and I'm like oh I was
just catching the the thing
and then and then the lifeu was like he
just come out get your get your stuff
get get away from the beach you can wait
in the cabin until the uh the storm is
over but we just ended up leaving
completely um and the floaty I didn't
find the owner the owner didn't seem to
be looking for it so yeah it was a real
ichy bun
moment yeah I paid back the karma yeah
yeah exactly I didn't want something to
get lost in the ocean like in the malds
that was that was so embarrassing
because it happened twice with lus lus
floaty getting
lost like
twice right and my own when when that my
own got lost we kind of were able to get
the like some neighbors to catch it I
think that's what was
happening but yeah so we gained a floaty
but I just gave it to my friends because
I didn't want it and um what now it's
complete isn't it not wait
uh talk to ignatio where is
he how do I get back
inside uh
here ignasio this you what can I help
you with uh the question is
what did I help you you with I diverted
power to the grid I saw that on the
monitors here and you sent it to
everyone very admirable I know now that
the NCR is more or less what they want
hopefully their curiosity about the plan
is satisfied and they'll dig no deeper
the followers will be Greatful here take
these as a parying gift I hope you'll
find them useful
what big book of science ah is it for
like extra skill points thank you oh
bags cool thank you Followers of the
Apocalypse Fame
gained keeping watch Mostly trying to
make sure the dangers of this plant are
minimized okay goodbye
good hooks have come to accept you for
your helpful nature yay
yippee
yippe I think the choices I made in that
uh previous safe were quite fine what
was it again besides this did I play it
in science n
medicine so I'm going to do the
same so do you have any comment on what
just happened yo yo what's up what's up
no adios Amigo
okay he has no comments he probably
didn't even realize what just happened
that I didn't go according to his idea
ideology sorry sorry bro suima sorry to
disappoint
you he has no clue and he will forever
be
Clueless yeah that's what happens when
you only have a theoretical degree h
what so [\h__\h] bright
man uh this dog doesn't know that I
killed the other dog right you can't
sense that from the blood on my hands I
hope speaking of blood on my hands I
watched I've been watching I'm up to
date on the house of the Dragon
episodes and um I'm not going to spoiler
anything but last night I was so tired
but I felt like I had to watch the new
episode and
yes nice I didn't even get spoilered
before watching it but I saw some people
saying uh that I have I have to watch it
because I will like
it and somehow that was enough of a hint
for me to anticipate what was going to
happen even though I feel like otherwise
I would have never anticipated it but
you know the thing that happened at the
end let's not say it but but just
because somebody said I would like it is
why I anticipated that outcome
funny it was kind of out of nowhere
right I don't think I was
thinking about that where is the
exit uh last episode I don't think I was
considering that as an an option is that
what happens in the books too though I
want to know
tell me while I'm looking for the
exit are you team green or black though
you mean well in the books it's team of
black right but uh in the show it's hold
R I found it it's red or black red or
green in the show not
explicitly there're short
stories um
oh oh yeah right because I I yeah yeah
Al shift told me
personally that yeah I guess the book
that this is based on is basically just
like a collection of like history
notes so you it's not really clear I
guess if something like this happened
but maybe there was um well I'll chip I
still have to watch his like recap on
this episode so he will probably tell me
if this happened the books or not and to
what extent he always talks about that
stuff
yeah yeah let's go that was a nice
episode nice
episode H but I got to say so I really
still like alisand a lot I've liked her
since the beginning I've liked her in
the middle and I still like her now I
know it's an unpopular opinion but
because of her
I I'm kind of rooting for her but I the
more I watch it the more I'm like [\h__\h] I
hate obviously I hate her her children
so and Kristen I liked him before but
now I don't like him anymore like he's
gotten too upy and
cocky so yeah I there she she's had more
going for in season one I
think uh now everybody around her is
unlikable and she's the only likable one
in for to me in her side on her side so
it's really hard to still root for
her but yeah maybe utto is coming back
and that is going to be interesting utto
is not my favorite character but
together they
could maybe get some something going
again yeah we're talking about House of
the Dragon
yeah ah cuz I really liked alisand in
the first season for a lot of reasons um
her decisions and her some of her
um ethical
thoughts I don't know her ethics her
ethics I kind of liked her
ethics
so yeah her moral choices CU of um Renea
Renea
basically you know all the [\h__\h]
around that she
did with you know making all those
bastards and you
know uh selling them off as uh her kids
with the other guy like I don't like
that fakeness like come on yeah I mean
you know he was gay I guess so that's
your solution to that okay but like
Allison was at least honest and stuff
and like committed to her duties and all
that you know
yeah so I respect
that no don't fight me fight
me hey shut up
she's
pretty shut
up I like her
okay You' win you think so I'm a phoenix
I can break your little chicken legs
with my tiniest finger yeah I can just
blow on your chicken legs and they're
broken what you going to do about it huh
what you're so round if I blow on you
you're going to fall over and you're
going to be stuck on your butt rolling
around and you're never going to be able
to get up again what you going to do
what you going to do about it eh
kfp you're just going to roll around
then what are you going to do roll me
over you little tumble weed
yeah beg for uppies
cute um what was I doing
uh we got to we got to go to whever that
is do I go here
now What's
um
probably um
I don't know how you survived the
bombardment you're loyal that's
incredible you look so much brighter
outside you want to hear something
crazy
um one of my dinners in Italy when I was
uh in Italy
Balia uh I organized a
dinner um we were like I don't know 12
people
maybe and I I booked a restaurant I
reserved a
restaurant um that was
like you know uh not like fancy or
anything um we had a table inside even
though most people were seated outside
we were seated
inside so wait I still have to pick up
these things here too
huh and yeah we sat down after a while
of waiting even though I reserved a
table they didn't have it ready um we
had to wait like 10 15 minutes in the
hot
heat and then we sit down and like we
start looking at the menus and
everything and
suddenly this was crazy suddenly I I was
like sitting against against the wall
with my back and when I looked straight
I could basically see the whole inside
of the restaurant right
and I on my right side there's there was
the entrance to the kitchen and
everything and on the left side it was
like all the other tables and the
outside of the tables and and so on so
the waiters kept on passing uh from left
to right left to right um so suddenly I
see two waiters two
guys um one the front one holding a lot
of plates and a big like tablet was also
filled with plates like he was carrying
a lot of stuff
right and right behind him like kind of
so close to him like they're almost
hugging each other is another waiter
who's kind of pushing and pulling him
and the other guy is like trying to get
away from him like walking relatively
fast but something is crazy is unfolding
at this very moment like he's pushing
and pulling him and suddenly like he
pushes him over I still see this and
when the guy falls down it was a purpose
push a purposeful Push by the way when
he falls down all the things he's
carrying a falling down but it was like
kind of like a not just an on the spot
falling down but like a continuous
stumbling falling down so that like you
heard Things fall and C crash and
shatter for like several seconds and I
now at some point they were like falling
into the kitchen so I couldn't see it
anymore but I certainly heard it and it
seemed like you know when he pushed him
the guy was like also trying to like
they were starting a fight they were
starting to like punch each other and
they were already in the kitchen and
more things were being shattered and
broken oh thanks for that
um really really dramatic and the other
waiters when they start hearing when
they started hearing things stratter
they were all screaming and and and the
people in the kitchen were screaming
because it was apparently very [\h__\h]
crazy and chaotic and they were like
having a full on fight and then other
waiters came running over trying to pull
him apart and they were able to pull him
apart for a little bit but then a few
minutes later they went back in for
round two ding ding ding ding ding but
in between they were uh like trying to
clean up everything and you saw some of
the waiters like uh being really [\h__\h]
stressed out and the one guy one one of
the waiters I saw him like bandaging his
fingers and bloods all over his hands
and everything Waffle House a dinner and
a
show it was a real
brawl and like it went on for a while
and they went into round two and the
whole atmosphere was kind of crazy all
the waiters were like what the [\h__\h] man
and we were sitting right next to like
the kitchen basically and right next to
the cashier and where they were
bandaging the hand of the guy so like we
heard and saw everything I I saw
everything cuz I was sitting with my
back to the
wall yeah it was kind of concerning and
that's also why it took such a long time
for us to be even asked what we want to
drink cuz they were so busy to clean up
everything yeah oh was quite something
and I was just
wondering is this like a Italian
restaurant kind of
thing cuz so we had in our group we had
one Italian with us the rest were all
foreigners and so I asked the Italian
Friend Like is this normal is this
like what
is this Italian
passion but no apparently not it's not
normal I don't think Italian people are
very passionate you know but of course a
fight like this can happen
anywhere um but it's kind of [\h__\h]
crazy and a little bit scary but also
sorry but it was a little bit
entertaining
uh oh thanks I discovered it now
I fix
these repair
65 or use so ah okay I use the ones that
I brought that I brought from The Other
Place
ah if I had high repair I could skip
that part I
guess using your knowledge of
photovoltaic sells you for clean POS
also clean okay
cool
ah you could like shortcut this I see
see they know how to end also to
yes imagine Waffle House but in
Italy that would be maybe even crazy oh
would it be would it be though would it
be not sure not
necessarily any more broken ones over
here oh this
one the PVP Arena
a that was so
crazy I feel bad for the other waiters
and one of them actually was sent home
then like the I think the one probably
the one who was like the the
aggravator is that the right
word the one who pushed and pulled that
guy and like seemed to initiate the
fight mostly who knows what happened
really who knows knows what happened I
have no
idea oh
get completed tell loyal the array has
been repaired okie dokie he will be so
happy about it and so thankful the
aggressor yeah the inator yes no no
police was called it seems like they
like cleared it up upon uh uh uh within
between each other yeah I mean between
the workplace
but yeah
Damn Damn
son how close were they to you like six
5 6 M away from me this whole thing
happened maybe 5 m like literally just a
few steps
away it was right in front of me it was
really
loud was
crazy is the guy outside still
you're not the guy hello is he inside
now hard to say oh wait I think he's
over there
were they swearing in
Italian I didn't I don't know I just
hear scream heard screams mostly and
like I don't know it's hard to hear
their
conversations but surely that was some
saring under control I will
100% hello Outsider
[Music]
need a code for the VR pods I don't
remember what is that anyway I repair to
solar raise and increase their
efficiency an impressive piece of work
yay I'll keep that in mind if jobs come
up in the future M thank you yay 300 XP
Sunshine Boogie and I got the fame now
can I get a code I don't know what I
need it for but no those aren't for
Outsiders to use leave them alone you're
so mean but I'm genuinely interested in
your people's history what are the parts
for well if you genuinely care so much
they're flight simulators if you don't
know our history yet you should see Pete
and get the tour uh you mean the small
guy one day Rule the Sky the little dude
I already had the tour like five times I
think I got 50 XP for that okay
bye-bye oh I'm
idolized oh
wow I am an idol so that makes
sense uh what now return to per oh I
helped them plenty it
seems return to
Pearl yay I did it I did it
all is is she in there I'm following the
marker yeah I think she's in here Pearl
is this you yes you have done well to
earn the trust of my people child yay I
yippe
well I think I've done everything I can
to help out I believe the time has come
for you to show your value in full the
people have come to accept having you
around find loyal and ask him about our
he'll tell dream he will tell you what
to do next okay I just came from there
but
okay speak to little about the Boomer's
plan to raise the bomber from the bottom
of Lake meat uh the bomber
do I want to hear about that
plan I'm not
sure I'm the idol of the
Boomers well I'd rather be the idol of
the Boomers than of the Zoomers like IRL
and in this game cuz I don't know I feel
weird having people younger than me
happy you came along surrounding you the
answer to our Dream Pearl sent words
saying it's all right to tell you about
the Lady in the Water The Lady in the
Water
unine from Tes of Symphonia I don't know
what's that that sounds really creepy no
tell me a long time ago long before the
war that killed just about everything
that ever lived a bomber crashed not far
from here a bomber was a flying
contraption that could drop explosives
down on anything it flew over but anyway
moving on mhm this bomber crashed down
in Lake me pretty damn near intact oh
when we got to Nellis SE I found this
article in a magazine all about it oh
there was another b29 around here part
of a museum couldn't fly but had a lot
of spare parts see get where I'm going
no since I was a young man I've dreamed
of raising that lady from the lake and
bringing her back to life why you call
her a lady what do you
say how do you expect to raise a bomber
from the bottom of a lake simple attach
Deployable ballast to the plane and
float it on up here is a remote
Detonator once the ballast is attached
to the plane just hit the Detonator from
the shore and let buoyancy handle the
rest buoyancy boy yeah
boy if it's Al if it's so simple why
haven't you done it maybe you don't
understand hasn't been one of us not a
one to set a foot outside Nellis in over
50 years you la with your of the outside
and it seems the time's come to raise
the lady after all lazy or coward which
one is it probably coward probably
both all right I'll do it good here's
the Deployable ballast go find the plane
attach the ballast and hit the
button okay P the button let me know I
[Music]
coincidentally this song you wouldn't
know if you were at Zumer
so might try holding your breath if that
doesn't sound good enough talk to Jack
he was working on a rebreather
once oh rebreather
somebody in the chat is also mentioning
the
reever
reever reever that sounds funny reever
reever reever it's like a golden
retriever
or I don't know sounds
funny talk to Jack about getting a rebr
to swim into the okay we should get that
for sure cuz apparently that's what you
want apparently that's what we want Jack
Jack Jack Hit the Road
Jack is isn't he still in that uh bunker
thing he plays The
Hanger
probably
the don't you back no more
hit the road ja and don't you come back
no
how I've never been so happy in my
entire
life loyal said you can help me breathe
on the water can I become a mermaid with
your help I just need some parts from a
pressure cooker to create a hermetic
seal for the
rebreather a press cooker specifically
corn silk rubber hose and removable
adhesive would make a good hermic seal I
have science 45 let's go it's a
brilliant idea I can put that together
right now ah we
ski skipping the other part with the
pressure cooker nice
so scrap my how much can you
spare I don't know take two
thanks thanks cool why thanks for
dropping it off no uh
what L hello
what what was I just
doing
SK now I can head straight to the
lake I so wait did I already get the
reever
now I guess so attach the Ballance from
loyal to the b29 at the bottom of Lake
meat where is Lake
meat wait there's two locations
why is there two
locations is this whole thing Lake meets
here this
thing equip it
oh ah
[Music]
cool oh I marked that [\h__\h] myself
what H this one
okay ah it's so far I have no nothing
really close by
maybe the grub and gulp rest
stop oh I got to go
out seems like we're going to go on a
little road trip with no car though just
walking
if only I had a truck right about
now a Euro Truck
perhaps would be
nice H
the and don't to come back
no a castle door what is
that you could have you could get a car
oh did I attack
me oh is this the
castors there's so
many but their aggro doesn't seem to be
very
uh reach no no big reach oh that's no
okay big horns
okay am I going the right way cuz I'm
following the marker okay
ah so I'm actually going to swim through
here
oh that would be really cool what is
this
[Music]
place what was this
place look at
that W oh
hello
scy we won't go quietly the lead it's
been a long Tour all I can think about
now is going back I thought he would
have something more interesting to say
what is this flag can I capture the
flag
no
lame I've been watching so many jet lag
episodes really recommended they're so
fun when I got this assignment I was I
was hoping there'd be more gambling oh
you're not the only one who's hoping
that it
seems wait my chat broke or actually it
didn't didn't break it just
uh it scrolled up so it stopped at one
in one
point yeah jet lag it's a YouTube
channel and they like with really high
budget and really good editing and
everything they make like travel Vlogs
where they make the world into their
playground they make like a board game
out of it and it's really well organized
and it's really
fun they have like free main people and
then sometimes they get in some guests
to help them and then they fight against
each
other oh I'm going to get the constant
drink thingy no
okay I'm not going to drink
this
water can I stay in here forever
now oo
nice wow this is way better than Super
Mario 64 on thewat
experience way
better I don't think I can jump on the
water
huh okay that was one part of the lake I
suppose but not the part where I had to
go
no aha wait that was barely the
leg that was
nothing
oh can I get radiation from just being
in the
water as a
puddle okay I'm going into the real
water but is there anything I could
activate here no Camp golf was activated
that's that's
fine okay
wo I wonder there must be Treasures
somewhere down here
right
wow it's like I have steel boots on
because how else am I able to stay on
the very [\h__\h] ground of this instead
of
swim oh no what the what the [\h__\h] can I
shoot that under water
no I don't think I can is it just
because I don't have a weapon
on oh
no no I have a weapon
on
uh is okay did it stop following me that
thing shoot shoot shoot
shoot Wait
Wait Don't Let It Go Don't let the
go nice
one what I can I have to like go out to
in order to shoot
them ooh that
sucks where are my friends by the way
are they like well we didn't get a baver
so we're going to stay at home
they can't attack either oh wait then
why are they going for
me oh oh a there's my there's
Ronica punch him in the water I'm sure
you can punch him in the
[Music]
water I understand not being able to
shoot but apparently I am able to shoot
or did that not work just now ah
what game crashed
um
okay I am closing the
game yeah cuz the shots were under water
huh okay okay okay I will redo
that I I hope my safe point
isn't too
far sorry I wrote Moone a message he
it's about it's about a new song that's
in the works
[Music]
oh aren't you curious aren't you curious
little
chicken I know I
know so
game where can I continue where the [\h__\h]
am I oh
no oh I have to walk the
whole I have to walk all of that
again okay it wasn't too
bad reever is
on let's go
here wait this a different place is it
not or did I just never turn around
H I don't think I realized where it
was I just booked
it please tell us more what kind of song
is
it
honestly I don't really I can't even
really say yet it's not um that far yet
in terms
of you know the creation
process um and I won't tell you because
I need to keep it you know interesting I
can't tell you all my
secrets but I think it definitely has a
a different vibe from Kima
Lake Las
Vegas what's this place over there did I
know that
place oh what what is this place anyway
now that we know that there's nothing
down there in this
puddle oh misfit's
tent I can check out what's going going
on
here oh to see
you tell me a little about yourself well
I was born on a farm out in California
weren't much me ma and P my two sisters
and about 40 acres of corn and bronze
didn't have no problems really except
for some lean
years then I joined up and got shipped
out here to New
Vegas okay
what's Camp go oh it's a fine place the
lake is real pretty and we don't get
bothered much by them Legion
Fellers you're
boring you are boring
me the only interesting thing about that
was the
corn but what is this
building looks crazy
what are you guys doing mve almost makes
you wish for a nuclear
[Music]
winner do I want to look inside of
this he said the thing that was a thing
I make sense that this was a golf resort
because we saw the golf
carts
oh House
Resort
hello M
oh hello nice to meet you
what are you guys doing is there nothing
cool here I'm sure there
is
no no
oh okay I don't I don't have time for
this anyway I'm going to go book
it man I'm learning so many terms that
to me it feels like they're new and
people haven't been using them before
like how come I haven't heard these
before all these terms
how
come no one says him anymore well now
they are saying
it quick
[Music]
save ah
no
ah oh
nice blood for the blood
God
yeah
[Music]
nice oh is that a trap no
no the one time I'm looking out for it
it's not what I think it
is
PE where is this big ass thing that I'm
looking for
H and no
treasure
oh no treasure no
nothing so far at
least let me see ah
what
what don't scare me what is that oh oh
oh I can go
up I thought I had to walk on everything
it's just because I had my camera like
always like my face just kind of tilted
downwards what the I F
A I thought I F I got I thought they
couldn't attack me but I guess they're
out of the water I don't
know
bro they're booking
it
[Music]
super [\h__\h] off
are you still following me
no guys next week I'll be in Japan
starting from next week uh for 1 and 1/2
months
approximately a little bit l maybe I'll
be in
Japan yay Yahoo I have lots of stuff to
do that's why I'll be there for
long but we'll be having fun and of
course we'll
be gaming like usual more or less I
think so don't worry about it but I'll
be in Japan and I think we already have
an off collab plan for next week
[Music]
I've been asked finally I've been asked
I'm not the one asking I've been
requested
woohoo uh wait what do I do with
this I can teleport
here where exactly do I attach it like
at the edges of it
[Music]
what is there a point maybe maybe here
at the
wings
no under the
wings under the
wings oh my God oh my dog is oh no ah I
thought this was a lurker and I thought
my dog was trying to get the lurker be
careful
guys between the
engin no no no what do you mean I didn't
talk to Loyal it says attach it not talk
to
Loyal a I found ah here I found
it mhm and then on the other side I
suppose ah now I see this like invisible
thing
okay return to the shore a shark is all
you ever be near the tow winch and use
the loyal detonators to float the b29 to
the surface return to the Sea a shark is
all you'll ever
[Music]
I love this
song look at the so-called Gem of the
sea old and scrawny see what I mean
return to
watching it shows
[Music]
what's beeping what now let me read the
guide
again uh is this a to towel
winch no is
it what how do I use
this do I have a thing in my do I have a
a thing
ah there it
is
who I did that in a [\h__\h] cave with a
bunch of
scraps
damn I feel like we're pretty um what's
the word productive in this Fallout
episode with wava even though we tangent
it for for like an
hour but two all of my tangents combined
so far surely are an hour the beginning
now it's no more like 40 minutes
okay but I'm I'm still doing
stuff
okay I'm
going you know I just wanted to share
things with you I'm sure you guys wanted
to
be talked and yapped too I'm sure that
was what you were Desiring all
along is loyal even here I feel like
no see this is what happens oh but he's
actually
here I'm never sure about following just
the marker you know he could be behind
oh
let's go
[Music]
yippee
yippe I think it must have saved after
the quest uh moved on
[Music]
in the yellow stop
Maring oh when I entered the hanger
[Music]
okay then we're going to be all
right continue
loyal these hoes ain't loyal let me tell
you all about that it's going to be a
dream come true once you've raised that
I did it that's tremendous I'll transmit
instructions to the robots to start
packing up the plane to bring it back to
Nellis how exactly you plan to get the
plane back here I just told you the
robots are going to handle it they'll
break the plane down into pieces and
move it up from cville Bay and one shot
sorry you have to say everything twice
to me I have six
intelligence I just had one
[Music]
more why am I so
dumb um well I'm glad to have helped hey
i' better get rolling Jack and I have a
lot of work ahead of us yeah that surely
is going to get the attention of the
attention of NCR you're going to see
it was the the boomers are not friendly
with the NCR are they I don't know
anymore I don't think they are so why am
I helping them
anyway or are
they they're not enemies kind of neutral
okay or I'm working on them becoming
friendly they're very independent why am
I helping them to get them on my
side well okay I'm going to let Pearl
know that I did it once again Oops I did
it again oh did you guys see my tweet
where I changed the
lyrics yes for sure you did I felt so
inspired I was like in
a in a uh uh back room with staff some
staff some
managers
um and I the inspiration hit me it just
hit me and then I played the song
several times out loud so that I could
like get the lyrics to fit the
melody sorry no time to talk out oh yeah
you got time to talk to me for sure how
can mother Pearl be around today
important stuff is going on what you
have done for us is a miracle child you
have fulfilled the only dreams we ever
had outside our walls you are a trusted
friend of us all ha if there is ever a
way for us to help you child tell me and
I will make it
so yahooo 400 XP
there may be a battle in the near future
at the Hoover Dam can you offer any
assistance wink wonk H maybe you could
also join rira in House of the Dragon
she's currently looking for some armies
to help her out Wing
Wong of course my child okay after all
that you have done for us we would love
to help you in the upcoming battle REO
will be the training in virtual reality
the young ones would relish opportunity
skills to battle we'll be there when you
need
us
[Music]
bye virtual
reality oh I have to tell several people
that the boomers are supporting
me uh
what where's the other
one ah here ah the Ambassador Crocker
wants to know that the Boomers will help
me okay I don't remember who you are but
I'll tell you can I go here or
there what what are these dots [\h__\h] what
are
those depends who I side with
don't no no need to tell yesman if you
follow andere yeah I think that's what
I'll be
doing a the dots are the doors
okay North
Gate
North
okay uh I'm I'm allowed to go through it
right
[Music]
yeah making me
nervous you guys are not wearing much oh
wait never mind you are I thought you
were naked on on your
chesticles it's hard to sleep in this
place I tell you last night some girl
was ping on
my what is she yapping
about I didn't register
anything he's a
comedian I did not laugh at
all
[Music]
so I he Meow in the
distance help
you do I still have a lot of super chats
left to read guys how do you know how
bad it
is what am I talking
to quite a bit okay then I shouldn't
play it too long I think it's good if we
do it in smaller chunks like Amy did
it's good to have a friend of the NCR
here what can I do for you the toilet is
that why you here did you pee did you
have a good pee
Oh belly
[Music]
rub a good good old belly rub
I picked her up so far I don't feel any
wetness now you have to
pee my tea just got better you're
[Music]
welcome She's So Soft
guys She's So
[Music]
Soft they really missed me and I really
missed them and I'm going to miss them
even more cuz my next STP is the longest
one okay bye-bye she's booking
it but I
think I can ask you know for nice videos
of my cats and
stuff um yeah about the Boomers I hope
you've returned with good
news the Boomers
oh what does this mean they will help us
well yeah yeah yeah cuz they're helping
me mostly excellent work I can't tell
you how useful that would be in any
event I have another assignment ready
and waiting for you but we can speak of
it later isn't that kind of [\h__\h] up
and when you're ready speak to me again
I didn't really tell them that they're
helping the NCR I just I asked them to
help
me will they
be kind of pissed off when they realize
that they're helping this whole group
called
NCR they they don't really that's not
really like I would be kind of
pissed like I think I'm helping this one
person who did a lot for us and then I'm
being tricked into like siding with one
of the biggest parties of a
war unless they kind of know but I I I
don't think I was ever clear about
that h
huh well good luck with that future Wawa
that is a problem of future Wawa and
future NCR and future Boomers not my
problem maybe we can do one more small
thing what could we
do uh
um what should we do should we do the
Brotherhood
thing doesn't seem small but we could
still do
it where is it that one the Hidden
Valley okay if I want to go there I
could go by uh the good
Springs or yeah yeah that might be best
or like not even just this one but I'm
shunned
here oh I could go to the good spring
Source might be better for next stream
[Music]
H now I'll check it out
Shand is not that bad
really nice
surprise why do I have no weapon with
me does this make you
happier I felt it like I felt the
disturbance in the forest the moment I
put that on that
gun I was like
ah I hear some grumbling chicken sounds
I better change my weapon to the hunting
rifle before they get all
up Jean skydiving
ooh skydiving
desar
t let me take the main
road maybe it's
safer 10 mm pistols in a dream but which
one is better 10 or nine because I would
think 10 because the Bulls are thicker I
don't know the logic Behind these things
oh are they
enemies or FR enemies this one's a enemy
but this one is not
why is this going to escalate in a
moment can is better why is
he
aha like
that well who are
they shot next to them
twice ah it's the Powder
Rangers why was one of them aggro and
one of them
wasn't oh they took over this Crimson
Caravan oh
physic a
little
magazine that makes me
smor oh you want
some woo
what oh well now they hate me that's
fine hey don't have the do the whole you
guys may hate me but if you hurt my dog
the whole internet will hate
you you don't just hurt dog but what was
that
explosion what the [\h__\h] just
happened don't kick the dog don't stab
the dog Just Pets the dog it's not that
hard bloody mes perk 5% that was a 5%
chance that I had
wow
beautiful
oh I see
enemies are they inside of that thing
[Music]
go
wo
Yoo amazing I've had
worse
beautiful
[Music]
expion what is this train
wonder if there's something
inside door
doco no okay
no that sh blew my mind wait are you the
guy that I just shot because it
certainly blew his mind
thanks for setting me up on that
joke where am I going oh I'm right
there it's right there
[Music]
what this nice
jalapenos don't think I've ever seen
jalapenos
before why is this one running away from
me no brainer wait wait you're also
joking aren't you because that guy has
no brain left
anymore you guys helping me out with my
jokes thank you we're like we're like a
comedy
duo you and
me dog is struggling dog does not have
the platforming
skill I don't really think this is the
ideal path
either is there a better path oh this
looks like a
path but it ends
there wait what about that it looks like
a
bunker that's the
place in there
k no [\h__\h] I was going to jump over that
it didn't
work oh I going to get out of
here whoa that's a
sandstorm uh oh is that
open
yes I think so maybe oh yeah oh
yeah oh my God
darud
Sandstorm Nice
Shot
whoa is that that's the hidden
part and I lost track of where it is
there it is oh my
God friend they're still friend
friendly found
it let's
go let's talk to the big steel
guys mushy
moshy I run this
car I'd like a large Atomic shake and a
double brahen bger and easy on the Agave
sauce this time we gave you a password
Veronica it's for your safety Oh I
thought that was the password know you
live Ramos open up I thought that was it
sake opening up welcome back Veronica oh
that was a um a Sweet Sound to
that welcome back
Veronica welcome to the
Brotherhood listen up I'm in charge of
security around here and I can't say I'm
too happy about having an outsider
Waltzing around but since you came in
with Veronica I'm inclined to cut you a
little slack just behave yourself and we
won't have any problems okay oh and the
Elder's going to want to talk to you
he's on the second level just take a
right once you get down there my office
is right here in case you need anything
just ask for
Ramos um I
was those this whole time he was talking
I was
thinking of what kind of joke I could
make because he said I'm walting around
I was going to say something about me
being Austrian I'm just kind of like
bound to be walting everywhere and I was
going to try to get you guys to
visualize me just instead of walking I'm
just doing the Walt dance in order to
get around
places looking sharp Ramos yeah hey
yourself
kiddo oh hey there I'm waling
here I can't help but to Walt what do I
[Music]
do actually that really sounds funny
though that's right nothing gets in or
out of here without me knowing
it what exactly are the rules regarding
entering and leaving under the lockdown
only essential Personnel are permitted
to enter or leave w w that includes
Supply Runners and high security patrols
all other Personnel are forbidden to
leave and any Personnel that were out
there when the lockdown was enacted are
forbidden from
returning you guys are taking the corona
[\h__\h] really seriously huh fine by
me oh bye seems like I had no other
questions okay what time is
it
um [\h__\h] off so it's like
uh 30 45 40
48 uh is it
10:48
y
hello what 94 948 ah I yeah right
because like okay I know I know I know I
know because like that one it has to
fill up all the minutes until till 6 and
then by that time that will be on the 12
and that will be on the 10 yeah okay
okay shut up there were some people in
the chat who were also saying 10
48 there were more people saying 10 than
there were people saying
nine nailed it are these beds
I mean they surely take off the steel
armor to sleep right
so it would be nice if it was a little
bit more comfortable a little bit just a
little
bit hello who are you oh is this like a
medical
place the mark takes a little getting
used to doesn't
it some
scrier you must be the Ider everyone's
talking about I'm Linda Schuler if you
ever need medical attention this is the
place to
come oh oh I am hurt uh in many places
in my body I require medical attention
right now right here by you specifically
yes uh what I'm hurt am I don't no no
I'm fine actually bye
bye help me help me I need some CH and
some and then I'll be good
again don't shoot me thank
you ah German always works didn't even
speak German but what is this
door oo
I want to hack into these
Gates what am I here for
again uh the
Elder I'm looking for The Elder where
would the Elder be not in one of those
simple ass doors for
sure one a more special door
oh who are these
people
Apprentice initiate okay
no what why are they standing in this
like
cluster where is the
elder the Senai of all
Senai oh the principl of Fus as a
teacher not an elder right you're a
scrib the reports say Mr House's robots
are now using Tech we've never heard of
we need to send a team up there soon if
you're planning to take Veronica with
you be sure to have a good pair of ear
plugs with you I'm kidding Veronica put
the Power Fist down put the Power Fist
down
lady don't even think about touching
me don't worry I got Veronica under
control toilet
what about this door
huh
hey okay this is getting more confusing
what the hell is
this activate
terminal may I
cool don't too hard there ion seems like
they're speaking a different language
that I don't know the other door
okay ah the other Quest is to catch a
hacker is that why it's
like is that why it's like
that wait is this the door where it came
from or
oh oh dear
oh
my this is giving me Bowers gate
vibes from these
cocoons okay no person in here
though uh this
door okay
Outsider nice
scribe night Reports say Mr House's
robots are now using Tech we've never we
need to send a team up there soon what
the [\h__\h] is
that wait I can see it on the local
map but you know a little bit of an
exploration doesn't
hurt
uh go straight
oh wait
what wait that was faster than I thought
okay hello is this Star Wars or
what that is
interesting hello Veronica how goes your
mission we'll know in a second I wanted
to talk to you what about me say hi to
me this isn't about yes godamn it it is
but you're going to hear me out this
time we've been through this the things
I've seen now other groups succeeding
where we fail it's not too late for us
we've outlasted the end of the world
we'll Outlast these upstarts waiting in
a obvious wasn't the end of the world if
we must this is a dead end for us I see
no evidence of that nor do I see anyone
out there with a solution to our
problems what about me I have the
solution you're too scared to look let's
go we're wasting our time
completed okay cool that was it thanks
for the stream guys thanks for
watching uh I did all the things I
wanted to
do oh wait
what wait I'm still waiting for
something right are we leaving are we
pretending to
leave are we booking
it a sorry
it was red why are you not angry at
me oh now I talk to him oh
okay when Paladin Ramos informed me that
Veronica was approaching with an
outsider in tow at first I didn't know
what to think after giving the matter
some thought however I've decided that
an outsider could be of use to me right
now however I will not force you to help
us should you refuse you will will be
allowed to leave here though you'd
remain Veronica's responsibility what do
you say Outsider are you willing to help
us uh
sure then allow me to explain our
situation this bunker is currently
locked down allowing no
entry with you being one of the few
exceptions in exceptional cases teams
are sent out to investigate sites or
retrieve materials deemed too important
to ignore three such teams have gone
missing recently oh no and the news of
their disappearance has not yet been
widely spread to avoid undue concern in
order to maintain the peace and AD of
the lock I need to send someone else to
discover what happened to
them better suited like in an iron suit
am I right give me that suit
now I'm glad I can count on you oh and
one other thing the patrols each had a
holotape detailing their missions that
you can use to track them the shielding
of the bunker prevents us from actively
tracking them but their positions should
show up on your map once you get to the
surface should our worst fears become
realized please bring back all three of
the holotapes from the
patrols otherwise bring our brothers
home I've given the order that you be
given access to some of the equipment
our Scouts and patrols have scavenged
over the years you you won't be allowed
to purchase any prohibited equipment but
hopefully some of what's available will
prove useful to
you
not I am once again the only one like I
this is so weird like if I think about
this from a objective outside point of
view I'm this wow I'm this one
person amongst thousands of people
living in this world that is going
around solving everybody these problems
like they're all kind of like helpless
without me I'm the only one willing and
capable seemingly of helping
people RPGs be
like it's just like feeling
so more much more obvious and weird to
me right now I just had this realization
where it feels unrealistic
okay I'd slept him around but he stood
at my parents wedding plus he used to
make excuses to get me out of my
punishment when I'd slept through head
scribe Tag's lectures figure I own for
that protagonist Behavior means
well yeah the mask is uh hiding all of
her beauty I don't like it
either well now I'm not giving up he
wants evidence but he'll never go
looking for it he's scared I'm right
he'll never listen listen unless I hold
the proof right in front of his
face so what is it you're trying to
accomplish that's my question to the
Elder all these years the Brotherhood
has collected weapons technology and for
what to keep it out of people's hands
that clearly hasn't worked to defend
ourselves we can't compete with the
ncr's numbers or dragons we're fighting
a war for a lost cause if we're going to
survive we have to find a role in
society attract new
members attract new dragons do you need
Dragon
Riders do you have any blondies
around h o TD brain
rot for real I can't wait I think next
episode is the last one is it or is
there another one after that how many
episodes was it cuz this was the sixth
one was there seven or eight I don't
want it to end yet two more okay
and then we probably wait how long what
do you think one and a half years or two
years I don't think they can make it in
another year cuz this this second season
took them
over a year yeah it's going to take ages
for [\h__\h] sake I'm going to die I'm
slowly dying every day that passes by
I'm slowly dying
rings of power soon at least yeah I
guess that will also Bridge the time a
little bit and then after that another
season of
uh what was that called reel of
time also I need to watch the new season
of Vikings
Valhalla yeah sorry that was random
random little
tangent one piece yeah one piece next
season also next
year yeah there's a new season out I
haven't watched it yet for
Valhalla 2 years is a little life this
these days you mean it's a short amount
of time yeah I mean it passes by one way
or
[Music]
another yay one
be when when when though when
uh look at the Followers of the
Apocalypse they use their expertise to
improve people's lives they train them
to be
self-sufficient that expertise
cultivates respect and gratitude spreads
their ideals draws talent to their cause
they make friends like we make enemies
but they don't know a fraction of what
we know if we took on their role we
could stand up to anyone we wouldn't
have to
hide okay you think the Elder will
listen at all he's he a stubborn old man
but when it comes down to it he's got
our best interests at heart if he sees
some indisputable sign we're on the
wrong course he won't ignore it okay it
sounds
good I don't know I don't know we need
something that shows the Brotherhood
will fail or that it can do better a
different way the only thing that get
his attention is technology huh maybe
father Elijah had the right idea what if
I show him the bomber H our Elder before
mamera he had a nose for recovering lost
technology he'd send scribes out into
the desert chasing whatever leads he
found there were a few he only trusted
me with I can think of at least one that
prove my point if it still exists I am
not too far from here I'd use to access
messages from him I I can pull up his
research on
it
Elijah Elijah Woods
huh I'm with you being around here isn't
the same anymore now you enjoy the
outside aren't
you well well well I'm not going to do
the full Quest probably but we can do a
little bit uh axis father Elijah's notes
at the Comm terminal of ironica let's
find that thing
um is
it it's it's in the bunker though right
so you're the outsider that's been given
leave to wander around
freely desperate times call for
desperate measures I guess is this what
happens to your hair when you wear that
helmet all the time and I think we might
be able to help each other out for
theast I don't know what the Elder talk
to you about but I can tell you this
chapter is in trouble and he's at the
center of it are you willing to listen
to what I have to
say h oh okay as you may have already
heard this entire base is under a state
of lockdown no one goes out except small
patrols at night most of the chapter has
been sealed in here for years and those
few who are outside when the lockdown
was initiated are forbidden from
returning what morale is plummeted as
time has gone by and many of our current
paladins haven't seen combat outside of
training simulations oh and all because
of the elders explicit order that no one
be allowed in or out the only way things
will change is if a new Elder is
installed what about Veronica she seems
to go and come as she pleases yeah
that's what I was just thinking about
like we they are not allowed to go back
but what about Veronica Veronica's a
special case oh she the procurement of
if we didn't let those like her back in
we'd all starve if the Elder could
manage it he'd shut them out as well and
all in the name of security which is why
we need to replace him
you'd nominate yourself huh I
would Paladin in the chapter I won't
follow without any two others here
together I'd gladly support another
candidate but no one has the courage to
step forward and make the attempt so it
falls to me I would put this chapter
back on the right path if I could just
assume leadership I see some people
crying in the
[Laughter]
chat um
it's okay you don't need to be followed
you are my
follower I want no part of this I really
don't but how do you propose to do that
I don't know I've gone through our
records dozens of times looking for a
precedent regarding the dismissal of an
elder and come up with nothing the
people who are most likely to know how
it could be done C some more supporters
so they refuseed to help you
having me an outsider such as yourself
would arouse less suspicion asking
questions about of course of course the
fact that the Elder has some tasks for
you means his faithful won't suspect you
and you have a line open to the man
himself in short you're in a perfect
position to help
me will you at least think about it
maybe
no I I don't want to I don't think we
should I don't I don't think there's a
need to replace the
Elder is there a need to replace the
Elder he gives me power armor okay that
I'll have to do I'd recommend going to
see Ramos first as set of security he's
more familiar with our protocols than
anyone else here you could also try to
find something relevant in our data
store though last I heard scribe ibson
is having a bit of a problem accessing I
get it either way if mam should give you
any tasks I'd ask that you kept me a
breast of them report anything you find
to me
I can't get them to Al with the NCR then
oh but then guy can I tell you what is
it Outsider have you discovered anything
I I I don't damn
it if you
must damn it I just won't do it what is
this Veronica brings an outsider into
our home then has a private audience
with the Elder why is everybody talking
to me the two of you may have the Elder
fooled but we know better
Veronica has always Twisted the
Founder's principles to our own ends we
will not stand odly by and allow her to
corrupt our elders
thinking what what
what pardon sorry about that just
because I love them doesn't mean some of
them aren't
[\h__\h] oh sorry I just thought they
would like teleport me into a
prison I don't know freaked me
out scared me because of the I thought
because of the the the the black
cut I thought that that was was what was
happening I'm
leaving okay I guess that terminal that
I'm looking for is not in
here or is that not what the quest
marker is for
morning
what is there a door here
no that on
oh look at this full set of hair and
it's red too that's the kind of guy that
I want to follow keep an eye on Veronica
here she's a sharp one I'm keeping an
eye on you sir
[Applause]
[Music]
oh hello Reports say Mr House's robots
are now using Tech we've never heard of
it you guys too scared to go outside or
what
but it's so
far okay it's not that
far let me go there and see what's
up it's like behind the
scrapyard the lady with the
dogs yes yes yes yes this is
where this is where fuu was brought up
and raised
this is where Yago went and picked up
the dogs and adopted
them thanks yo for adopting dogs from
shelters what a good
man what a good good man
this little computer
H welcome Veronica download research
notes people
people okay complete can I read them too
maybe let's see what we've got here okay
yeah this is the one I was thinking of
the pulse gun
although maybe the rangefinder could
work too and it looks like the NCR was
onto some miracle farming
technology oh what's a PSE gun
electromagnetic weapon from before the
Great War experimental it never saw mass
production but they were building it as
a countermeasure to power armor which
they feared the Chinese were developing
supposedly a prototype was being housed
at Nellis imagine what it could do to
the Brotherhood we'd be on equal footing
with any idiot with a gun
farming
technology more or less supposedly it's
a vegetation enhancer NCR has a science
branch headquartered at McCaron airport
guess they found something guess
somebody wasn't very good at keeping
secrets either we'd never pursue it
because it's not a weapon but
self-sufficiency is fundamental to us if
it works they'd see the value of an
alternate
course n it's a targeting device for
some kind of Doomsday weapon based at
Helios 1 it was lost sometime after the
war we held helius one for a time lost a
lot of people defending it too many all
for this weapon they never got working
if it turns out to be a dud it would
show how flawed our goals have been
father Elijah said he thinks a scavenger
might have sold it on the
Strip
okay uh the rain TR might be a problem I
reactivated helious one and it's not
powering a
weapon oh hell
well how could you know right okay two
other options still on the
table oh and I did Vault
uhhuh the vegetation technology but this
one she somehow lets me still suggest
interesting yeah maybe they'll think
twice about engaging the NCR if they
know one of those could be floating
around the notes say a look around
Nellis Air Force Base He suggests going
through filing cabinets and computers in
the commanding officers
quarters I Chang my mind let's go after
the farming Tech but I don't really want
I don't know let's try okay what better
way to persuade them than to give them a
taste of what they stand again right can
I change my mind again maybe the best
place to start is to see what we can
find out directly from the NCR let's
head to their I office at
McCarron yeah I can change my mind
again uh somehow they let me do it even
though I thought I what can I so what I
would just go there again or but we want
the pulse gun right we could use it if I
do this I get a
gun try it can I do
both M I think the data and the vault is
deleted
oh oh oh but I have the copy of
it you aren't very good with energy
weapons but it could still
you you're being a little bit
up because I I talked about
headless hairless head
heads headless hairs
just
kidding just kidding yeah maybe they'll
think twice about engaging the NCR if
they know one of those could be floating
around the notes say a look around
Nellis Air Force Base he suggest going
to Cabinet Compu in the officers
quarters maybe we can start Skilling
into
it I like the way you
think maybe now's the time to get
started with
that vodka
lawn mower blade
men
cigarettes [\h__\h] he moved because of the
bottles physics in this game wait I
thought what what why is he
dead are we not going to talk about
that is that
Gibson Mama Mia
don't touch my WKA okay no problem I'm
not going to touch you WKA I don't drink
alcohol you're in
luck people die when they are
dead
interesting I did not know
that okay we could teleport straight to
Vault
22 or we go to Nell's hangers it's
interesting they give me both options if
I do one option is the other one
automatically then like
[Music]
deleted let's do this one first if the
other one still exists afterwards we can
also do
it I only need one okay you love my hat
thank you should we make a chicken
cowboy
hat I'm making some some cute merch from
my anniversary right now I've designed
something and they're going to base it
off of my
design I'm doing some cute things again
things that you can
use useful things that I want to own as
well
yeah very very useful
another rubber
ducky no no no that one is enough if you
want more then you you can buy
more uh what am I talking
to oh
okay Pearl am I supposed to talk to
Pearl hello friend
oh let me read my quest
thing uh look for my information about
the pulse gun well could that be from a
person or just lying around there's like
a
thing it's in the cabinet
or but it's red can I really open it
let's save
beforehand wait my my chat my chat is
scrolled up again my chat is being
up Karma penalty as long as she isn't
looking
okay she's definitely looking no don't
sit down
there go somewhere
else you've done us a great service
thank you thank you for your help may I
please just open your
cabinet come over here please Mrs
Pearl I can wait until she
sleeps oh can I sleep in her bed too
where's the
bed I'm happy that we managed to raise
the bomber in my
lifetime I can't sleep in that one okay
no maybe I don't know
six H oh I
canceled nine you're not going to sleep
yet but you're old I'm amazed that an
outsider has stop praising me and go to
sleep old
lady midnight why are you still sitting
there go to
sleep
n what is this
question what did I say I only saw the
bottom half of it if I'm doing any any
more
covers is that the question
English version covers oh I'm planning a
cover right now actually but it's not an
English oh there may be some English in
it but there's no English version or
so God damn it what's with her she's not
even moving from the couch
wait maybe I should go outside and wait
outside yeah I've got something in the
works right
now she's still sitting there she's
going to melt to the [\h__\h] couch
yeah I mean I don't I I just didn't
really feel like doing covers for a
while because I fulfilled my mission
with myth covers and um I did a few of
others that I wanted to do like with
waya and well you know I've been busy
with focusing on my own original
songs Mama
Mia I'd rather like put put my money
into an original song than a cover
generally cuz then I can also get money
back if I oh my
God why are you still here you've done
us a great service now you're getting up
thank you
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah if I make my
own music at least I get some money back
don't know how much but are you going to
take a bath there
uh what which one is the one I
want maybe this one take
both you didn't noce it right okay
completed
Yahoo uh recover the P gun from vault 34
if it still exists
34 that's a vault I haven't been to have
I
22 34 oh it's really close to New
Vegas is is there like enemies in
there is the
worst it's
hell
yeah might want use space suit
ghouls okay I think
then we might want to do it next time
but then we got a really clear goal of
what to do next time and that's
good
yeah then we'll focus on that doing the
whole Brotherhood of Steel stuff wa this
time we got uh the Boomers on our good
side and did some cool stuff regarding
that so I think it was really productive
now we're going to read Super Chat Yahoo
are aren't you excited you've been
waiting for my Super Chat reading
weren't you Loop you need water I got
water clean and fresh if you're low on
caps I've also got slightly irradiated
Wasteland water a little Fallout never
killed anybody a little Fallout never
killed
nobody right here right now is where we
stop Little Fall never kill
nobody but right here right now is where
we start
SC
SC we have a Brotherhood yes you have a
whole ass family in
here little party never killed
nobody that's an amazing thing she just
said like sounds like a phrase people
would repeat when talking about this
game m
bye-bye
exito the
game I didn't ignore ignore your pun
wait there's a I mean I know you mean
because of your name that's the pun
right I I got it I got
it I understand do you understand that I
understand are we understanding each
other I got
it okie dokie
[Music]
okay
um I think I finished the ones I read
previously but like where what what's
the one did I skip some again what are
we reading oh thank you myth one block
Minecraft day seven all right all right
baby let's move to
M well how about because of the
lake and because I haven't been using
this very much what if I go
here this is the lake that I swam in
today how about
that oopsie
[Music]
wait let me let me get
[Applause]
something
T this is the
leg that I lifted the the the machine
out
of oh oopsie what the [\h__\h]
fry W left some gummy worms here and I'm
pointing right at them like
this oh gummy
worms let's
go May if I take if I take one just one
she won't notice
right when she sees when she comes back
here you think she'll notice that you
going to eat
these are you are you going to are you
[Music]
these nice pointy finger yeah she'll
probably notice it's not that many like
you would notice that there's one
missing when there's just s so few of
them she's GNA attack me she's GNA try
to kill me again
I better not eat
them okie
dokie let's
see Super Chat reading from that stream
let me get the thumbnail for you
guys
uh
Na k i r a hey oh
no where is the thumbnail
here yeah we got 2 million on Chima
while I was busy so I couldn't really
react I might still do some kind of
reaction tweet to it but thank you 2
million thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you stream Chima
[Music]
we are reading the super chats from the
Minecraft finale as it has been skipped
it seems
skippity here's to two million more
hopefully yeah the road to 2 million
subscribers yeah that's also a
thing um I'm probably going to try I'm
going to attempt to do tomorrow's
stream as a short stream going to try to
format it like that I think the game for
tomorrow you don't need to see
everything you just need to see me
boxing I'm going to try
it uh because I want to have at least
one vertical stream per week if possible
don't even complain hokan it's for for
the good of my channel for its growth we
need
growth I'm trying to make it
grow I'm not going to force games like
Fallout or so to be on a vertical uh
format so I'm just trying to do things
that uh kind of work with it I don't
want to force
anything that like I don't want to cut a
game into several parts just to fit the
screen so I'm trying to find fitting
things hi smoothie poie now you
definitely went to the toilet didn't you
oh y you're doing a flop you trying to
be cute you stretch oh yo rolling around
on the floor
yeah yeah shake shake your
head what what you're talking to me
you're trying to say something
no it fits a vertical stream cuz I
checked like other streams and you know
you just really got to like if you
capture Miku in the middle and me like
kind of on top of her or next to her
Loki um I think it should be fitting you
don't need to see everything in that
game I think sua works in vertical yeah
but sua game is not really like such a
thing anymore I want to play the
multiplayer one to be
honest now she's just sitting in the
door frame looking away from me turned
she turned her back on me uh by the way
yeah yeah yeah one thing I've I need you
guys to remind me it's in my head right
now but I need you guys to remind me cuz
I'm going to Japan soon uh I want to do
the off collab uh to dama to stream that
I was trying to get to work previously
as an online
collab uh but now is the time where I
could do it as an off collab so I want
to invite some people who are in
Japan to play it with me uh while I'm in
Japan in August and any other kind of
um offline
collab kind of game please remind me of
its existence hello C
cat so that I
can so I can play it with some
friends
yeah finish Mario with Ina I'm not
meeting
Ena uh anytime soon no actually I am but
I don't know I don't think she wants to
play it with me anymore to be honest I
don't think she wants to
she didn't
seem so
motivated about
[Music]
it uh back when we were playing
it I don't think it will be
[Music]
finished it was pretty difficult
too kind
of
[Music]
yeah if it's like a oneoff kind of off
collab then I think it's more motivating
but this one
required uh either a long ass stream or
several short
ones and the the more you know the more
you drag it out the more I
guess it's not interesting
anymore we can play something else
again if she wants to but I don't I
think that game is going to be very
rried
forever
[Music]
sorry I have to bring my switch I'm
going to bring my
switch and my
laptop so switch games and any kind of
steam
game let's do
it you can also play worms on the same
couch ah yeah when you're together in
the same room that might be pretty funny
[Music]
too yeah I do think I can play more
Fallout while I'm in
Japan I think so sorry I'm robbing my
[Music]
eye y Yum Yum Yum
Yum meow you
again cutie
PTI why you playing on PC or your laptop
today uh on my PC cuz I'm home I'm home
Mario Striker oh is that should I play
as an off collab does it even does it
not have online
mode then I'll I guess I can use it as
an off collab game I guess yeah
[Music]
was that on the switch is there a switch
version I forgot that's why I was
considering it wasn't I because it had a
switch remaster or so not remaster maybe
just
a seven other people to play
offline wow so many but with less it's
working too obviously
[Music]
wow okay Mario Striker off collab sounds
fun what is it cat I'm streaming still
stop meowing at
[Music]
me
y
cute
cute so cute
[Music]
she's
purring she's purring and I have her
tail between my my my tail is right now
I'm squeezing them with my
[Music]
toes don't go behind all the cables down
there
Smo come
here come here
come
[Music]
here oh yeah that's interesting right no
why are you going behind again come
here come
here come here come here come here come
here come here come here come
here moving don't play with the
cables M Mia
she was rubbing her face against
[Music]
the thank you for sharing that with us
smovie thank you
[Music]
it's hard to hold
her she doesn't want to be held she
doesn't like the shackles of society
no sure okay I have annoyed smoothie
enough for her to leave the room so now
we can read you guys hear bgm
right you should be hearing
it okay take 47 dun and Jeff the Phoenix
tonian
dun ESC esec mysteriously appearing in
the sky has grown and expanded each ah I
see and expanded each day and now it
blots out the Sun from the view of the
village yet this new land of the heavens
exudes a warmth a warmth like that of a
phoenix and it has continued to sustain
a nourish our
lands a miracle accepted by the people
of Phoenix and as a blessing of the Holy
bird oh savior of our village accept
this
offering thank you
oh was
funny I wonder if they noticed an influx
of bees coming down from the
sky wandering around
aimlessly oh the bees the
[Music]
bees I'm saving the bee crisis
singlehandedly no five no 10h handedly
[Music]
I like
this oh but nobody can be safe from the
spelling
bee yeah I'm going to be part of the
spelling be from
amam uh I don't know I don't I I I don't
know if you like get something wrong if
you're like kicked out immediately I
don't know how the system will be um but
I doubt that I'll be doing really well
um at least it's not a pronunciation
be shut
up yeah I think she wanted to do it for
a while yeah it's kind of at a really
late time obviously for me but it's
probably not going to be an endlessly
long stream so I'm okay with it because
it's am and I'm literally like first I
ignored the offer like that was like a a
an offer to everybody just like hey who
wants to participate and I IGN igned it
because of the
time um but then am Amy DMD me and she
was like hey you don't want to
participate in spelling me and then then
I was like melting because I'm ask me
directly and then I was like oh well if
you're asking me directly now then of
course I'm
participating
yeah so now it just so happens that I'm
part of
it how could I say no how could I say no
the Gosling in me
yeah very predictable
outcome I got a personal
[Music]
invitation
basically I'm
I don't even think it was like M's a
personal invitation invitation she just
was like probably just checking to make
sure or so cuz yeah it's movie you again
anyway simplon thanks for two
pinkies even if it wasn't an invitation
I will still see it as a special
invitation just for
me yes I'm
coping simpleton says one block has been
amazing Kira we oh
sorry we all know love how you got the
gang together and appreciate all the
effort you put into making it real even
sacrificing your sleep schedule it's
clear you love your girls and all myth
fans with the care you put in I do also
congrats on the new Hol neighbors a just
reward for carrying EU solo for so
long I guess so those girls better be
looking
better look out though cuz knowing you
we can already imagine an EU tour in
your
future you mean me going around
Europe well it's not going to be much of
a tour there's just two of
them not much of a
[Music]
tour
uh just some small visitations Maybe or
or or they also welcome to visit me of
course might be better anyway that
way I can visit Aura and panko while I'm
at it
[Music]
h oh the ah you didn't really know yet
yeah you didn't know yet how many there
were be were going to be yeah you guys
assumed there would be
like many or all of them in
Europe La says she planned to go back to
Italy for a family visit in the future
yeah she told me about it too yeah she
even gave me already like a time
frame so
maybe we could possibly meet up maybe I
don't know if the stars will align but I
mean we're going to meet up in Japan too
anyway so but it would be cool to see
her in Europe as
well okay so thank you
simplon for the support very much
appreciate I'm glad you uh enjoyed the
Minecraft Arc so much cuz I did as
well py Dan world of Mona Dan thank you
the adest adrestian D Nathan thank you
for the red super chat hi attentio
thanks again for making this whole
series happened it's been fun to see the
whole myth crew together so much looking
forward to the finale and I'm going to
make you a little jealous I've got
lasagna to enjoy while watching oh you
really think you can make me jealous
with that when when I literally just
came from Italy and I did have some
lasagna there
too but this this was before I went to
Italy
[Music]
so but but
this is why I waited so long to read
these super chats just so that it would
be after Italy and I I could you
know have my lasagna defense up and
running ready to
go the lasagna defense is strong I'm
literally covered in
[Music]
lasagna wow 4 the
chess you cannot out lasagna me I am Las
lasa my skin is made out of lasagna
[Music]
sheets lasagna sheets
yeah pasta pasta Pizza Pasta Pasta
finito thank you
Nathan I recommend you to go to Italy
and get the real
deal SP wonderful dun dun 11
dun Kiana can you be at peace with Kobo
she love
you Ki can you be at peace with
coobo she love you
like as if there's like
[Music]
[Laughter]
what oh are you serious about this are
you really concerned about it don't be
concerned don't be worried I think she
she actually wrote to me a saying that
she I think she gave a gift for me to
her manager to give to me when I'm back
in
[Music]
Japan how sweet is that huh might be an
apology for her for her bratty Behavior
recently
so no I cannot be at peace with her
until until I get that gift maybe oh
smooy is behind me on the on the
treadmill I put like a cuz she's been
chilling on the treadmill so I put like
a like a bath mat kind of thing on top
of it and now she always sleeps there
when I'm in here doing my work but now
even though I'm still streaming she
decided to sit there which means she
really misses me fitting for the towel
hanger no no no no shut up shut up
no no I'm I was just busy how the [\h__\h]
can I use it when I'm in Japan and Italy
and all that shut
up I'll use it again maybe even this
week before I
go it's being used as a bed as a cat bed
right now I love that treadmill being
used as a cat bed just is such a cat
thing I like it that's actually amazing
that's the best use you could have for
it cuz anything is a cat badad
[Music]
I have too many cat beds in my
room I could do all Super Chat readings
on it h i could but why would I huh why
Mr uh v d Alexa d uh space wonderful
d
h interesting L random collos and thanks
for the red super
chat yay
yippe somehow I hear more and more
people saying yippi and exactly that
high
tone not just in like whole life but
also yesterday I heard someone say it
IRL so I'm like what is this trend of
yipping what is it oh my God she doesn't
know it's a meme
[Music]
I just hear people saying it it sounds
cute a German kid
[Music]
oh colon on fortnite Meme really is that
where people are getting it from
[Music]
now
huh huh interesting
[Music]
looking it up
now going to mute my desktop
audio for I think I know
it
ah
[Music]
yeah yeah I know it but I didn't think I
didn't realize because this is old I
didn't realize that this is why people
have been saying
it recently so
[Music]
much should I say
it did I say
it you guys want me to say
[Music]
it it would be maybe good for a YouTube
short if I can get someone to edit
it okay I'll say
it you want to say it I guess I want to
say it
okay maybe maybe in this kind of voice
because it really sounds like
him should I do it in a normal voice or
in in this kind of voice which
[Music]
one which voice would you prefer yippe
yippe both hi pitch one I don't hear a
difference hi pitch yeah it has to be in
a higher pitch Maybe
noal sounds better no
no no this is not how I talked in my
debut that's [\h__\h]
insane okay okay
okay wait wait I got it
wrong okay wait 3 2 1
cool
fortnite
yipp honestly I should do that with like
an asset of cola in my hand and an asset
of fortnite hands like a hand holding
the fortnite game in my
hand you know what for post edit I'll
remove my my stuff
oh spicy oh actually the
swimsuit this is like a natural swimming
Pond now this kind of
works do you want some green
screen but maybe not green uh red I
don't
know no color really works man
uh who
orange blue dark blue n but my my
necklace no no see no color really
works I've tried black before in OBS it
kind of
works animation idea
oh maybe
bathtub
streamer should I do black I wonder if
you guys
can uh use it with
black
okay okay here W
AET use it however you wish
fortnite
Dr
Yi wait one more time
cool it's a
forite
yipp
perfect now with
Expressions
yippe smovie still here yep smoovie
still
here
yippe and cut
yeah
yippe yippe how many yippies can smoovie
take until she leaves the room H smoovie
is like oh my God that high pitch is
piercing my
ears
yippe yippi
[Music]
nonh High
version
no why would you need
that you don't need that but just for
[Music]
you night on drink a cola
yippee
wow you don't like like 9-year-old Wawa
being excited about fortnite and
COA why do you hate small Wawa so much
what's wrong with you
what's wrong with
you shut
up if if you want you can use that voice
and put it over uh the previous screen
screen black
screen whatever I don't
care okay H thank you random collusion
for bringing us into this just by saying
yay just another kfp d d kazaki Channel
D rzy thanks for the pinky yay thank you
for organizing the series t h forever
yes yes indeed H my forever thank you
for watching it and following it it was
a good time I miss it already
M thank you Jim Tracy thanks for the red
super chat this series was so awesome it
was so great to get myth back together
again for Minecraft like in the old days
lots of great interactions lots of fun
and many new memories thanks for putting
this together k m forever thank you I
feel like because it was like several
days in a row and like many overlaps in
online times feel like it was almost
more than back in the day like all five
of us being online was a rare thing
unless it was like organized for like
one thing like the ender dragon fight
for for
example yeah and it was like in several
several days in a row isn't that
crazy so that was good that your was a
pinky did say red one I I see it's a
pinky yeah I didn't give you a kiss yet
right I don't think I did if I did then
well you get it for free I don't think I
did thank you so much Jim
Tracy good old Minecraft days yeah if
only Minecraft hype didn't just [\h__\h]
die at some point I wish it
[Music]
continued
to Jason dreams dun but at the same time
maybe it's good that it kind of died
because yeah it lasted a long time and
it opened the path for more variety in
in gaming maybe more people like the
members got a little bit more um like
forced to have a bigger variety in their
stream choices if you see it like
[Music]
that yeah it it's true like the servers
every time they reset them even it got
conquered really fast so
yeah I mean I feel like on the Ian side
we still were like not so
oh Advanced and I'm still waiting for
updates on the server like the next one
if that get up gets updated then I'll
jump in again to
explore yeah that was pretty
bad a few days ago
I while I was in Italy I slept kind of
weird and when I woke up I had this pain
in my neck that was kind of weird like
strained and it went up to my head and I
had a headache the whole
day even when I took pain
colors uh and then the following days
even though I got like my friends to
massage my neck and
everything it felt like it was still
going on
now I think it's kind of gone now but I
still feel like the remains of it deep
within a little bit actually no that's
separate yeah know my neck pain is
separate I have uh some weird pain deep
in my deep behind my shoulder blade that
just doesn't go away
either and now when I breathe deeply in
I also feel
it it just doesn't go away
either very very annoying and that one
has been going on for like one or two
weeks now
H it's weird but I am okay I'm used to
pain no pain no
gain cope s s d Jason dreams d m a Manu
dun mered Pippin thanks for the red
super chat and a dragon easy clap didn't
go quite as expected yeah this has been
such a journey and I'm glad we got to
experience it with you girls we truly
appreciate all the work that was put
into this from everyone and from you
espe now until packed summer yeah very
packed thank you that uh ender dragon
fight was so
chaotic oh was so chaotic and like weird
awkward cuz like it was
anti-climatic
but we figured it out one way or
another gooda just being stuck there and
who was it Ena Ena dying and losing her
armor and now able to get it back and
then me trying to like communicate
between them to get ena's armor back
because I think guda had it or so then
yeah GAA got GAA got
stuck and me I didn't I don't think I
got a single hit in that was
weird and then we ran out of uh arrows
and [\h__\h] I'm going set up the TNT like
for this the whole time and then didn't
even really get to use it so that
was I don't know what that was oh
man that was were that was worse than
our first in a dragon fight for sure so
I think uh certainly had a good dramatic
effect I
[Music]
guess
yeah
yeah abandoned the plan immediately
there was no abandonment of plans
because there was really no real plan in
the first place we went in there and
then we were trying to make a plan while
we were in there and that failed for
sure we didn't think we needed a plan
because we thought we were well
prepared
so yeah she just put it
everywhere she just put the TNT
everywhere it was like a
Minefield
TNT she was probably listening to that
song in the
background without like letting the
audience hear it she was just listening
to it and vibing doing her own thing
just like I'm a doob be like
that
sometimes yeah thank you Mary
Pippin you Max the first I am a
[Music]
d space waterfall
dun and with that the Minecraft super
chats are Basta
finito what's next
guys did I read the Austra versus
Netherlands super chats there's not
many it's just a few
I don't think I did did
I
okay GD help
help there we
go it's in chronological order now you
think
okay Jacob 47
Galaxy
D and space waterful d j monkey dun py
D and Hulu thanks for the pinky I'm
sorry wa I wanted to cheer for
Australia waa but I'm too tired today so
I don't think I'll be able to join
instead you'll use this to eat some
delicious P well good that you didn't
get to cheer for Australia because
Australia never played
so I'm sure you got it right in the end
and cheered for Austria right right
Honolulu
[Music]
right
H well
anyway thanks for the pinky and which
spring
R
is got this
right here uh apparently part four thank
you thank you
RP motion
peik
477 D unknown d s keep thanks for two
pinkies which is a red tomorrow is my
birthday and I'll be turning
30 hard to believe this is the fourth
birthday with you and kfb and I'm happy
that I've gotten the time to spend a
significant portion of my life here I
guess so it's significant by
now even if personally I've been more in
the background but I want you to know
that these have been very fun years and
I still enjoy that all that you do and
hope that you get even more joy and
success from here onward I'll be here as
long as you'll have me and I still love
you very very much I H have a nice week
thank you well then why are you more in
the background what happened
HHH h it's okay but like what
happened what
happened where are
you where are
you do so let's keep play
do
where
H are you
here are you here
now hey hey
Hey Hey listen ah there we are I'm
working mostly so I podcast more and the
ones you do have and the ones you do
have I don't have much to comment
on okay happy
[Music]
birthday kind of late but
congratulations almost a month late oh
dear oh no oh no
I hope you had a wonderful birthday now
you are almost 30 plus one
month
yab time is
ticking I'm Fred to
now let me try to do that math real
quickly huh is that is that
possible is that possible
maybe you feel like you are but don't
worry don't worry I think you're still
30y by my own
math moondock wait so do keep blade
KY py Rod thank you I said that I would
give my first ever super chat if Austria
won so I'm here to keep my word hello
from Spain oh
Amigo love your content and we'll try to
watch you more even if it's difficult to
me thank you so much I'm
excited tyon thanks for the pinky can't
Super Chat as much due to dog adoption
cost oh but had to say thank you for
reminding me of how much I love myth
with the collab and I can't wait to be
there cheering you at World Tour as a
lucky golden ticket met chicken yes I'll
wear a suit golden
ticket what's a Golden
Ticket what's that
is that just like the expensive one
where you get to be in the
front
oo
nice oh nice you got one too let's
go good job yeah you get the good view
on the
waa keep your eyes on me
okay thank you so much
what looking forward to it it's getting
pretty close now yabby it's almost July
is almost over holy
[\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h] oh my God the Mad
kitten Idol business
regulation the Mad kitten kuer
thank
you
uh hello
R more
cake golden thanks for the pinky W I
sent a pinky in for a polar but I had to
go to work before I saw the options that
day if was not too much trouble can I
still send my choice later oh yeah you
asked but you didn't didn't even send me
the
number so oh wait but you did number two
in the other Super Chat
okay
huh
yeah I probably because it's not in the
same
stream I
might like um not realize I don't
know uh worst
case you'll end up not being in the
batch and then you'll have to remind me
and then I'll make it
separately we'll see
huh oh it was a pinky oh [\h__\h] sorry idle
business regulation
director sorry it was not on
purpose I almost forgot to get the
merch you still have some
time but go do it okay going back H this
is a reminder that you have 10 days to
address the multiple violations cited
for your business or a or pay a fine and
face criminal charges your business will
be regulated also can I get a t k
chicken large
condo well you can't get it cuz you
spelled it wrong but I also didn't even
know we had that oh bgm yes let's turn
it back on
oopsie didn't realize we had that on the
menu but that sounds actually good
that sounds good so it's like Teryaki
chicken
yeah let's make it a burger though teaki
burger not just like the chicken
itself just just a a live chicken with
tiyaki sauce poured all over it no let's
make it a
[Music]
burger cuz I like the
tedak um okay that's not chicken though
the one that I always eat in Japan is
actually not a Teryaki chicken burger
it's just a Teryaki Burger but I do have
a chicken version too I think but I like
the normally I always eat chicken patty
burgers
but that's like just because I always
like when I go to McDonald's or Burger
King in Austria I always do that but in
Japan I don't quite
like the chicken burgers that much and
Japan uh from the big fast food uh
Giants because it seems like like I
guess in Austria here the chicken meat
patties they're like I guess like
grinded chicken meat or so
right but there and like other people
might definitely prefer that but in
Japan they're like they they seem to all
be like a chicken filet
[Music]
thingy
so I don't know I don't really like the
the texture of
[Music]
it yeah
yeah I prefer it to be like the texture
of a a chicken nugget
[Music]
basically so
so that's why in Japan I would often go
for the beef
burgers
but I I only go for very particular ones
at McDonald's I usually go for the teddy
Yaki Burger cuz the teddy Yaki sauce is
amazing with the beef patty
and then there's a
mossberger when I go to Moss
Burger uh I really like the generally
just the the main basic mossberger I
think cuz it has like this interesting
uh tomato sauce like all over
[Music]
it and Burger King in Japan I don't
think I there's not many in the first
place I don't see them
ever and when I tried uh a crispy
chicken burger at Burger King and Japan
it was something completely
different I think I told you this
before
Moss wait I should bring armor to the
Moss
B oh yeah but it's MOS not
Moss it's just MOS
but I could tell her I could just say it
out loud I could be like am do you want
to go eat a moss burger and she'll be
like what moss moss
burger and now if you subtitle this I
would be saying
MOS but purposefully making it sound
like
Moss's and when I'm a repeats it she the
subtit would say Moss s s right she's
like mossberger let's go let's have Moss
Burger yay moss and then we go to the
Moss burger and it's not a moss burger
at all oh
no oh no the disappointment in her face
will bring me to tears maybe I shouldn't
do
[Music]
it click baited IRL yeah
literally scam
[Music]
maybe maybe I'll bring some spinach or
something secretly and then when she
gets her Burger I'll like say I'm going
to go to the toilet or something for a
moment and then while she's gone I'll
open up her burger and I'll cover the
burger patty in spinach so that it kind
of looks like
moss yeah how about that how about that
she does like spinach yeah she she
secretly mixed spinach into um something
she cooked for me before but she didn't
know that I didn't like spinach and it
was fine I didn't really taste the
spinach so it's all all
good last time I was in Japan I did kind
of like thinking that I'm getting older
and my taste buds are changing I did
give uh one tiny Leaf of spinach like
cooked spinach or so uh ago I tried it
to just check if maybe I like it now no
I still hate it makes me frow
up so
[Music]
yeah if it's like mixed like grinded and
mixed into a sauce or so or into you
know like those noodles that I like the
Austrian noodles that you eat with uh uh
uh cheese sauce then it's okay
yeah h
but that's the only
way no I don't think it will change
there's some other things that I think I
hated before and I like now so I wanted
to give it a chance because life would
be easier if I liked more foods but oh
well oh well so yeah moving on Golden
[Music]
forever one free for me
than still your ra than for the pinky T
it a WIS you were happy but you also
felt sorry for Poland so un pathetic I
did feel bad this is why you're my
oi PS pizza with fries Lan should know
that the fries would get all soggy and
gross might as well eat pizza with
potatoes so I just want to say um I just
came from Italy so I can argue some more
with this um now said you know Pizza uh
uh fries on Pizza is common uh normal
thing in Italy but it wasn't on any of
the menus okay where I went uh on all
the pizza places yeah so maybe you guys
do that here and there but I mean it's
still it still seems
like it's definitely not on the main
menu up there with a freaking Margarita
Pizza uh-uh
[Music]
yeah I'm sure it's a kids thing and I
get it I mean I've seen also I've seen
um uh I've seen Burgers filled with
fries before that doesn't mean
that just because some people maybe do
it that doesn't mean that it should be a
thing
oh no I don't think it's a regional
thing is just as much as a fries in a
burger is a thing that's probably like
comparable I would
say a pizza needs pineapple not fries no
like I'm not arguing I'm not saying that
a pineapple on Pizza is an actual
accepted Italian thing to do but I would
say honestly it makes more sense to
me uh as a Dish as a meal then fries on
a
pizza just that's just
[Music]
weird yeah as a topping just makes more
sense like fries on a pizza it's just
like one of those things you do like
putting fries in a
shake just you just love fries so much I
love fries
too but I don't know I don't think I
would like fries on a pizza because it's
just
like kind of a
dry type of ingredient to put on
top and very filling I'd rather have
something refreshing like a pineapple or
you know
juicy
and or tuna tuna is
nice but I've like kind of stopped uh
ordering pizzas that have a lot of
toppings I used to do that I used to
want the most special Pizza I I always
completely rejected the idea of
Margarita pizzas I thought that's too
boring but maybe I've grown to be more
sophisticated because nowadays I'm all
in for margarita pizza I actually almost
always order Margarita now if I go to a
proper Italian
place if it's a proper Italian
uh place with like a proper oven and
Neapolitan style pizza especially that
got to be
Margarita cuz that makes it come out
even more the the flavors and you
know
yeah I feel like it needs to stay
simple yeah I like barbecue chicken too
I used to eat that
sometimes yeah but now I like it more
more simple also because I already have
troubles finishing a whole
pizza yesterday I shared one pizza I
only ate half of it and I was full thank
God I
shared so the more ingredients the more
easily I will be full the less pizza
I'll be able to eat so I I I'll just
take the simple one and eat as much as I
can I love that Simplicity of
[Music]
it but if it's not a na Neapolitan
proper pizza if it's like frozen pizza
then it's
different because frozen margarita pizza
it's not that nice so in that case I'll
go for tono or pineapple or I don't know
that's usually the choices I have from
the ones I like but if I if I see
something more
interesting I might go for that
too four cheese I don't like the super
cheesy ones
n the qu forti
no I don't really care for the the super
cheesy ones I I I don't hate cheese but
I don't like too cheesy things like
where where the focus is on the cheese I
don't like those kind of
meals you know what I mean but also now
that I was in Italy again I realized one
thing I like those kind of cheeses that
are like white and creamy like
mozzarella and
Bata and cream cheese or any kind of
like that kind of cheese there were some
more that I forgot the names of that
were on the
menus I prefer Those
cheese
cheeses rot yeah any of
those that's not what I meant though
there was another special cheese on
there I had that
padina yeah that is something about
stradella yeah I was like what does this
mean then I ordered
it is there stret aella cheese froo help
me out
here I know you're
Italian I need to look it up what's the
stretch of tail
jeez is that a thing
because it was on the manual oh yeah oh
yeah yeah I love that sella cheese is
composed of small shreds hence its name
which in Italian is a diminutive of
strata uh meaning little shred it is a
stretched Cur fresh cheese white in
color and made the whole year round but
is f to be at its best during the Spring
and some yeah I had that in
my
piadina I think it was a padina or
actually not sure because the um
[Music]
there were two
versions and they explained to me the
difference was one is that you uh the
ingredients are already in when you cook
it and the other one was you you put the
like the fresh ingredients in and all
that after you cook it so one has like
colder ingredients and fresher ones
while the other one is uh cooking
everything together I think
I had the one that is not cooked allog
together so that's why the cheese uh and
and I had like tomatoes and salad in
there that was all fresh and uh cold
while the rest of the thing was warm and
I really liked that balance of it the
contrast but I forgot what the name of
the other thing was cuz one was called
padina and the other one was called
something else
but yeah now I know strella cheese is a
thing and I know that I love
it stop laughing at the gigantic G
gigantic gigantic ass of the chicken
stop I had to stop myself for a moment
cuz I wasn't sure about that
[Music]
pronunciation okay uh where was I
where was
I
here uh here I
here oh yeah na from cotton thanks for
the pinky casual genius CH moment glad I
could catch your last stream before your
super short break this chicken will will
still miss you while you're gone though
just a little bit when I'm gone when
when I'm
gone you're going to miss me when I'm
[Music]
gone essential pack W let's go thanks
for getting
that
yippee now you got the essential back
and you can go to the RO tour
[Music]
yippee you Mommy said that you could get
the essential pack and go to the World
Tour oh my God
[Music]
yippe
I'm but I don't think you guys
will have to miss me when I'm gone now
because I won't be gone I'm planning to
stream quite normally so anyway thank
you Nathan back then I was gone kind of
Gone Gone
[Music]
Going that's a black gu PE
song Ed
Cru Jim
Tracy and
Kim
[Music]
Chong y you one
maybe thank you oh I think that might
have been cuz it's in Korean and they're
uh thanking me for streaming witch
spring again maybe they're one of the
developers could
be and d and space waterful d they're
going to be happy about seeing which
spring are on the schedule again for
this
week I'm
[Music]
I'm
you're okay there's a re broadcast from
the K thank you jenma that seems to have
worked
fine it has a few super
chats so thumbnail
[Music]
do I have a
thumbnail
[Music]
uh wasn't this the thumbnail oh
yeah was this was this
it is this the
one was there another
[Music]
one what I missed one H sorry I'm blind
I'm color blind today slightly color
blind a yeah okay sorry I don't know I
don't know man my eyes are getting
weaker because I'm getting
older Ed thanks for the red super chat
Aller one so here is my first
oh did you lose a bet or what also this
is in celebration of my new rise oh
thank you so much for making the last
almost four years so much fun you have
inspired me and motivated me to work
super hard and here are the rewards
thank you my beloved Kami thank you
yippe thank you so much sorry I almost
missed you congratulations on your
[Music]
raise oh yeah it's raise not rice here
now you know
you worked hard for it I'm sure now you
got to work hard at kfp
too earn yourself that raise I can like
endlessly bait you guys to work harder
for raise you're just never never going
to get it and I'm always going to say
well guess you should work harder and
you're going to come again to me and
you're going to be like here's my race
and then I'll say well you need to work
even harder and it's an endless
loop isn't that that
genius and you pay me that is
true of course of
course you're welcome to give yourself
the raise at any given time but just
know that the money goes to me yippee
[Music]
okay I hope this is the right thumbnail
for the right
K
uh Jack for7 and Susan please come back
there're my kids
too oh Susan please Susan come on give
this man a
break Chey and
G Scott Jackson d r d battle d battle
coak D batt and battle
coak pump up the gy pump it
[Music]
up and d asple d edisan d it was
different okay
whatever Joy Gamers face for r p my bank
account might regret this wait I forgot
to give a kiss
to was
it did I forget toiss a kiss for Edie
son now you get
[Music]
it so love you and your
singing thank you Joy
Gamers so how is your bank account
feeling any regrets any complaints
please send them to
HR and they will handle it
in the best and only
[Music]
way whatever that may
be thank you flaming pants D Psy d n
diesel D Psy
D
[Music]
okay
so oh wow the Austria turkey one got a
lot also I can turn off the waiting room
again I guess the W wa waiting
[Music]
room why do I always hear the those
Shredder
[Laughter]
[Music]
noises no more W waiting room W waiting
room no no no more yippy
[Music]
sad but that's a good thing that we
don't need a w waiting
room Wai waiting
[Music]
waiting what do you mean what was it for
it had an obvious purpose whenever I
wasn't streaming for several days you
guys were supposed to chill there cuz
you guys seem to like waiting
rooms take for the7 uh
that should wait I forgot the
[Music]
thumnail there you go and D hook on
D py py
lunch
alaro Maga generales
D Galaxy D the great Bly maze d CL the
Barbarian
D El Nan d space waterfall D Zer D so
many Turkish super chats this one
[Music]
time thank you where can you become a
kfp member uh you could join the
membership on your
own there is a button in the chat
where you can send super chats or get a
membership or if you're lucky somebody's
going to try to gift you one
[Music]
now click the dollar dollar sign
yeah ah wrong person I think
oh was what was their
[Music]
name super Pokmon collector
no no
[Music]
no
50 come on one of those got to hit one
of those has to go
in oh my God Jesus thank you
thank you Okami
Sensei I'm I'm
observing there we go oh did did we get
it really I don't see I don't see
[Music]
it did we get it
did the Pokmon collector get
[Music]
it yeah you better have that thing
turned
on don't make
this be a
waste you got to turn on the option to
receive gifts in your
[Music]
settings ah you didn't get it yet like
is it like it's like giving it out one
by one slowly in the chat I wonder if
that's
like if you write before
that if it would show you in green
before it announces it in the chat or if
you have to wait for the
announcement you know what I
mean so far nothing
[Music]
well well well we tried at least some
other people got some nice
gifts a you guys are still working on it
you guys are sweet we're so green we're
so green
today oh and another 10 and some some FS
before thank
[Music]
you we don't even know if they have it
turned on you better have it turned on
it should be on by default
[Music]
right you get a notice in the chat
really I didn't know
that who who W what
membership
STS maybe what what do you what would
you say guys if that super if that
Pokemon collector was just um planted by
me as
a just you know industry plant so that I
could get more membership so I could
reply to it and say oh too bad oh I
wonder if anybody you know could help
you out with that and then see wa it
works
stks another 50 thank
you a masterful genius plan of the one
and only takanashi
[Music]
Kiara only my brain cells could think of
such a devious
plan big
brain oh we're
colluding thank you another 10 thank
[Music]
you okay okay I have to read super chats
now so I'm turning my focus away from
this but it is beautiful to to see so
many eggs being born today the egg
Market is full of
stonks Galaxy still didn't get one Mama
Mia Mama Mia Galaxy you deserve one
[Music]
too you're always here how do you not
how do you dodge it that well
[Music]
crazy is it a brand
account why would you have a brand
account
what smooy okay smooy was making cute
sounds
stretching uh where was I I had T more
thanks for the double red Super Chat yay
K's back I had an awesome time last week
not only did I pass my driving test on
Thursday I also entered my military
service secured myself on apprenticeship
Germany made it to the quarterfinals and
I had an awesome time at doomi now it's
time for Austria footb
FIFA yay yeah you had a lot of good
things happening what a streak of good
things damn good for
you I'm happy for you nice
congratulations
oh I wonder what Apprentice ship you got
yourself good job good job U on the
military service
congratulations yeah unfortunately
Germany did not get to the finale but I
I'm sure Germany played well as
well congratulations for getting so
far I'll be working a lot istics okay
interesting well thank you for the big
big big red Super
Chat and your support unfortunately we
[Music]
lost it do be like that sometimes just a
raven
[Music]
VI HC D Migel Miguel thank you for the
pink
sticker thank you
Abella Nathan coton thank you for the
pinky you guys still trying huh hieno
welcome back you may not remember this
game but I started playing Star Ocean
second story only like a year after you
sponsored stream of it Oh you mean like
now has it been a year here already nah
really enjoying it so far looking
forward to your upcoming birthday thank
you I'm sad it's already over but my
merch is still on sale so my birthday
month so to say is still happening yeah
please please get the
merchandise link is in the
description has a really been a year I
don't quite believe it to be
honest that' be
[Music]
crazy why is everybody gifting
memberships uh because of you
[Music]
duh
du you guys got to buy this merchandise
because soon there will be a different
set of
merchandise you know
[Music]
get
ready you got to prepare for it but soon
yeah I mean I just mean my I just mean
my birth my anniversary cat skateboard
yeah some of you guys got theat
skateboard did you guys even see like
let me advertise it here then um just in
case you guys haven't seen it because it
looks really really cool it looks really
cool
yippe there are skateboards now that
even if you don't use skateboards I
think it's a really cool decoration that
you can put up as well and I don't know
who knows maybe maybe you could you know
get into it little new means of pro uh
uh uh Transportation maybe if you don't
have a
um maybe if you don't have a bicycle
here are the myth
boards so they are on the omocat shop on
their
website they are so
cool yeah I really like the
[Music]
designs they're so nice it's such cool
merchandise please consider getting one
of the waha boards if you want
omocat minus
shop.com that's where you can get it
yeah I should get one I wonder they're
probably not going to send these to us
are they cuz they're big
too would be nice though would be nice
decoration indeed
h Huh don't say anything about the flat
of
it would you rather like a wobbly
mountainous board
instead actually the the narissa one
looks really cool cuz it's so dark wow
shees
[Music]
damn I think my favorites
are mine obviously m
the good
one like design
wise and Nissa one and the fuok one is
pretty cool too I like the the
[Music]
grids I think those are my
favorites go get yourself a wobble board
yay please pleas
please consider
[Music]
it no I mean I like the ELO one too but
like I'm talking pure design like
thinking about it actually being a
skateboard and not just like something
to hang up I feel like the Garuda one
for example has like this skateboard
look to it because it's so cool you know
yeah
and then the Arisa one is also so cool
cuz it's so dark so it's
like I don't know I think people would
like it if you skate with
[Music]
that oh smoothie what what what did you
hear
that my sneeze woke her up she got up go
back to
[Music]
sleep what what what
stop
stop stop she's talking so much to
me did you hear
[Music]
that most of it is not being picked up
by the mic I think anyway continuing
while she's meowing down
there me
[Music]
have fun with Star Ocean sh Mario
brand for
nowu uh this person has no
name huh
interesting but they have a me
membership who are you they literally
have no
name well
Dun A man has no name
yeah Nashi m is that you
Brian K K SE thanks for the pinky
something in
uh Turkish
partially to
turn toin life reaction # Turk
kfp I don't know what that means but
thank
you movie is running away chunky won
also somewhere
there waffle Supremacy d d midnighter
Midnight Rider d m Thomas D El D Zer D
SE d dein marus
d space d Ranger J D Jimmy Boom
is D Galaxy D go b d Sherman D H and K D
Shy Boy D Ranger J D Galaxy D Bob the
fake D Danny D SE d d 7
[Music]
d a thank you football is pain sometimes
isn't it Marvin lint Amir Ed the nerd
El I
sound
simp thank you oh man GD D HD D oh you
flppy boy thanks for the pinky Austra
bringing home the title for the anime
Phoenix
empress a blissful dream that didn't
need to end so
prematurely anyway good luck finding a
nice Turkish restaurant in Japan maybe
go for some chicken PAB for your nightly
mukbang is that Turkish
too but I said I would eat like a a kbop
por so didn't
I did did I not
specify maybe I didn't
specify guess I misunderstood yeah yeah
yeah eh or did did
you did I
say oh
[Music]
so I still got to eat some Turkish food
huh maybe I
will maybe I
[Music]
will
no Shak Shuka for breakfast uh yeah I I
went to a restaurant before that has
that uh in the menu and my friend got
it it it just looks extremely Savory and
filling for
breakfast normally I go for sweet
breakfast I know like it looks really
good but I would like prefer to eat that
for lunch or
so because it's it it that's like
whoo it feels like a lot to me
very intense like it feels like an
intense breakfast you know what I
[Music]
mean but it looks interesting
nice
breakfast
yeah I've noticed that Italian breakfast
is just like they have so many like
cakes not like fancy cakes but just like
pretty plain
cakes at least in the like uh Hotel
restaurants I've noticed that in
previous years as well so many cakes and
quasa and little dut thingies and stuff
seems to be very common yeah I don't see
it that much in other Hotel breakfast I
saw like a big focus on the sweet
things which
honestly it's
Italy you get
[Music]
me we love cake me too yeah but I did
have a lot of uh I I mixed it I ate some
quasons I ate at some fruit fresh fruit
and I ate some a little bit of even even
the hotel eggs cuz they looked pretty
good this
[Music]
time I'm almost Dan okay I'm almost
dance
[Music]
movie
286 botom frer
BC CH for now Productions Mr Mrs S
[Music]
Galaxy ping Unity
Chad d Sean R Samuel Sil Evil Genius AEL
d
[Music]
h zipper thanks for the pinky we rarely
Super Chat because do not check the
conversion rate for USD to tr is it so
bad is it so
bad I picked up a flopped smoothie from
the
ground almost as bad as ARS
[Music]
oh my
God she's already escaping me damn
it she's too good at
this having lots of
[Music]
inflation um thanks for the pinky though
laser boss D Crono
[Music]
monkey uh the gamer cre D Lily s d 091
Overlord
D
drono
Cesar Junior dun z
dangun o second page roric dead beat D
or dead beat MF d z d samid Dum D fro
thanks for red super chat I can't
believe I'm enjoying to watch football
again and that's cuz of
you I can't believe it either
honestly thank you for making this so
fun
I'm hope you have a good time in Japan
too after working hard I wanted to write
something but the baby is stuck tangent
confused me now I don't know
either thank you
yeah that Japan trip was stressful I'm
so glad I'm done with the Japan trip
that was really stressful I'm done with
the Italy trip that was pretty
stressful I'm done with all those things
and the upcoming
trip is it shouldn't be too stressful
because it's more spread out so I think
I hope things are going to be fine ah
but there's a lot of yeah things
happening cuz yeah concerts concerts
many concerts are happen
happening
yeah so I I don't really know but I'll
try to take it easy when I
can and not stress myself too much and
not put too many things in my
[Music]
schedule
yeah yeah yeah
yeah I still need to record things I
actually need to record some
things um a voice pack and another thing
right after the
stream yubby yubby should have recorded
it before the stream but I didn't I
didn't now I'll do it
afterwards I did get more fan letters
yeah and a weird thing did I tell
you I got like normally jenma just gives
me the letters whenever I'm in Japan
but like I got
like I got some like a batch of like
five letters or so via
FedEx and I didn't know what was coming
JMA didn't know what was
coming and
usually
normally when they sent me stuff they
don't send me letters anymore unless
it's like mixed within a package of some
other things like when I have polar to
sign or whatever they sent me the
Polaroid and maybe they add something
else in there but they don't just send
the letters anymore cuz JMA just gives
them to me and now there was like a
FedEx thing and I missed the delivery
and then I didn't even know something
was delivered cuz I didn't get a
notification and then like really
late uh I got notified like hey can you
like try to get to this and uh it was so
annoying to organize because calling the
FedEx hotline of course I was talking to
a [\h__\h] robot again it was so annoying
to get to an actual human cuz things
weren't working with the with the robot
it didn't understand what I wanted
[\h__\h] annoying it's so annoying and
then I'm like this better be like
something interesting right and then I
get the package and it's just five
letters like I could have received this
in Japan it's literally just five
letters that look like they came from
the same batch
[Music]
very interesting
why why why I don't
[Music]
understand but yeah I think getting
letters regularly so don't worry I'm
receiving them and they're really sweet
and they're really cute
[Music]
lettuce and actually I was I bought some
um cute nice storage
boxes for my wall shelves the other day
and so I was sorting some things around
so that not everything was in the same
place I wanted to put some things in
those storage boxes so I took the
letters and uh because I was like
resorting them I read through some of
these old letters also and it made me
feel really
nostalgic read through some of the old
ones and and saw some names that I don't
really see around nowadays anymore
[Music]
too but it's still nice to read
good letters nice letters oh hello
smoovie you jump up she's getting up ity
she's getting really
impatient what is
happening why you so impatient H you
missed me didn't you I missed you too I
missed you
too I miss you too
[Music]
I'm here but only listening for now I'm
preparing for a long trip oh me too more
or
less just came back and I'm already
preparing for the next
trip I'll write a letter when I learn
how to write one what do you
mean if you can write super chats you
can write
letters only uppies oh I'd love to give
smoothie some uppies
[Music]
what I'll say is that by next week I am
in
[Music]
Japan
so you
know buy but I'm happy to be streaming
again now I missed streaming I couldn't
stream normally for the past
weeks so I'm glad that I'm
back and things are back to normal and I
don't have to go outside in the Italian
summer heat but now soon I'll be going
outside in the Japanese summer heat
which is not better at
all but I'll stay inside as much as I
[Music]
can oh no touching
grass my back hurts okay let's
go thank you
[Music]
froo just a Dan raven d SE D Aviator D
Spirit
[Music]
D quintus
tan Al bacon Slayer dun logical Paradox
dun om God 52
dun and D
watermelon waiter oh my God thank you
for the big red Super Chat K I feel
blessed that I share the same birthday
as you I will use my wish to make your
wish stronger you made me finally learn
German after I fell in love with the
song ballons as a kid than
[Music]
oh so now cuz of me you started learning
German good luck with that it's really
difficult it's pretty difficult as I
hear
from uh
foreigners good luck with it keep on
watching my streams to keep up the
motivation thank you and report your
homework to
me as much as you
can D sh and good luck
Mah thank you for the support also happy
belated
birthday yay
looking for the top d g d The Gamer D
Jones D fried scw D and spider thanks
for the pinky do your best angel thank
you I think this is about Japan thank
you very
much D I did my best I tried my best
cute spider cute little spider I forgot
we had a uh I think this is probably
Halloween a Polaroid with a chicken
wearing a spider suit perfect for
you perfect
representation oh I hear the toilet
spinning that
means one of the cats was on the toilet
5 minutes ago or
so why is she sitting in the swamp
excuse me I'm in a swimsuit and this is
my natural
pool this is my My Little Pond my
swimming pond
[Music]
yeah I'm borrowing it I'm borrowing it
from froggy waa oh yeah speaking up back
there says froggy W and frog
bird it I've
heard
[Music]
things heard
things
yeah Rock bird is not dead
frog bird
is maybe it's back from getting
milk I think he went out to get milk but
he's like he got
it yeah he
lives FY waa was kind of like secretly
crying about him a
lot thinking he was
dead yeah
she put out a missing frog report at the
police
station and they declared him dead
already but somewhere deep in her little
frog heart she still was
hoping for him to come back from
the the milk
[Music]
Mission T police
bro tried to play
Frogger i f frog bird was kill where
were you when you f frog bird was kill I
was in I was in my room froggy wa was at
the
pond foggy wa was like
No And they were like yeah and she was
like no
I was in wa Chad what about the child
the
[Music]
child okay smovie is telling me to stop
streaming and I just finished those
super chats I think we can leave it at
that I think I caught up a little bit uh
tomorrow we'll do a 3D stream I think
things are working again so it should be
fine
[Music]
yeah I hope you guys had fun today ooh
it's 6 hours Good Time a good time to
stop don't forget to get the merchandise
I know you already have it most of
you
yeah yeah I read the other ones before I
read the spider one
[Music]
hatu
tomorrow I'll be
boxing box box box a left and the right
and then upper and then I don't
[Music]
know got to make sure to stretch before
because my shoulders are so
[\h__\h]
whoa
[Music]
whoa an
uppercut
okay I'm going to beat up Hots in mik
yeah good kickboxing oh I should learn
kickboxing
that makes
sense yeah thank you for watching hope
you had fun in German v v z see you
tomorrow for kickbox no uh normal boxing
featuring HS am Miku fit boxing not
normal boxing fit
boxing
[Music]
yippee I'm going to jump into the pool
now that is the pond behind me
[Music]
did you hear
that did you hear that
[Music]
one you did okay very lightly I need to
I need to make my mic so that it catches
things more again I think I changed that
a while ago
okay I'll the in byebye
[Music]
n