[Music]
w
[Applause]
[Music]
a
around the world everyone says that love
is just like a
dream feel like I'm mounting from the
heat love it feels
so oh yeah just like that you know just
how it goes don't never stop you already
know you just a sweet my baby got me
wanting more so taste it yeah I no
worries I feel good good good why son I
want to go and part don't let this love
end now I won't pretend my best re for
love it's you me how want to try it now
try now I'm going one 2 one 2 free it
tastes so so so sweet when you go and
kiss me I'm taking the perfect
picture you stck to me like a
sticker I'm going one 2 one two it
tastes so so so sweet go that way
yeah keep going you know
me I'm wa to be in the heat so sweet
it's hypnotizing but you can sing to my
be you can't be my boo yeah now see me
see me bab I give me me no more don't
think twice cuz you're
mine me I want to go and party don't let
this love end now I W pretend my best
recipe for love it's you me I want to
try it now yeah I'm going one 2 one 2
three it tastes so so so sweet when you
go and kiss me I'm taking a perfect
picture you stuck to me like a
sck I'm going one 2 one two three it
tastes so so so sweet go that
way yeah yeah yeah keep going you know
me yeah yeah
pineapple pineapple pineapple P come on
let's go pineapple PPP come on baby do
it over over pull my head and let's fly
and let's take it to
the I'm going 1 2 1 2 3 it so so so
sweet when you go and kiss me I'm taking
the perfect picture
you st to me like a
sticker I'm going one 2 one 2 it tastes
so so so sweet go that way
yeah keep the you know
mepple
hey
waking up in shades of
blue I don't know where I am or how I
got to you try to reach out but I can't
move I'm like a broken instrument so out
of why won't they listen to me anyway
I want to be and I'm not going to say
I'm sorry just so you let me stay L
whatever you think of me leave it alone
I don't want to live in the shade of her
throne I keep hearing pieces of a Melody
playing in my head fragments of a p won
let me forget someone that I used to be
hanging on the bread of L silette I
wonder when you look at me who do you
remember broken memories time we s
together tell me honestly do you
recognize my boys
Bo so hard to breath the wall that I'm
facing is just too cold and too lonely
wish that i s feel s feel the things set
back then I you still there I ever want
it want to be accepted by you wish that
you and I still love say that's
something
will why won't you listen to me anyway
I'm going to be and I'm not going to say
I'm sorry just to say face whatever you
think of it alone I don't want to live
in the shade of her
throne I keep hearing pieces of a Melody
playing in my head fragments of a p that
won't let me forget one that I used to
be hanging on the Bri of very still and
I wonder when you look at me who do you
remember broken memories time spent
together tell me honestly do you
recognize my voice
voice it looks so off to me the picture
you PID a boss I don't need to remember
let me be take me just as I am as
everything disappears I shout to
[Music]
he let me take me as I am
yeah let me be take me just as I am yeah
I keep hearing little Melody playing in
my hair fragance of a p and it won't let
me forget someone that I used to be
hanging on the the blurry silouette I
wonder when you look at me who do you
remember broken memories that we spent
together tell me honestly do you think
that I could ever find a voice to call
my
[Music]
own Boys
Boys
[Music]
by
go
[Music]
for
call
[Music]
she
la
[Music]
for call the
mon
[Music]
good
[Applause]
[Music]
SU
la
foreign
spee
[Music]
fore
for
[Music]
speee
fore
[Music]
speee
fore
[Music]
foree
for
[Music]
fore
speee
[Music]
fore
foree
spee
[Applause]
[Music]
hello say hello
to
yes we dance R circulation together but
before that we dance with M Senai right
so let's get M
[Music]
Senai
okay okay okay I want to ask a
question
what was the thing you were most happy
about this
[Music]
year
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
her favorite thing was just being with
the viewers and hers was that you know
the being a crap maker which was really
good yeah for
me
yes nice nice
okay it's almost
[Music]
2024 what do you want to do with me next
year
[Music]
yes yes okay so maybe we'll you know
we'll get some cooking collabs next year
maybe some dancing and maybe I'll teach
them German who knows but yeah with that
let's move on to the next
section
bye byee byebye
byebye
[Music]
while
I
[Music]
fore
head
me
[Music]
e
[Applause]
[Music]
fore
[Applause]
[Music]
for
you can do it
[Music]
a you
you I there I there I am there am there
[Music]
fore
keep your head
up
[Music]
me I got
the
[Music]
temperat crazy theall ready like step
drop roll not going to break the sweat
at all light can
[Music]
theid
Frozen Never Back Down fre out fre out
now not about to B to you
[Music]
now this world smoking
miring changing no strange thing about
this he witness me H the
speed feel got the
[Music]
free passion Never Back Down freeze out
freeze out now about to you five St now
that turn it up loud five ni now this
world's smoking
[Music]
mirrors
in we're CAU up in the ey of a Storm
Flame it's not complicated but a Nuance
game A P you want gave me something I
can't shake the chance with some body
who moves to make so what you waiting
for you got to burn enough cuz when it
rain you got to earn love never never
get enough you you got it out now F back
down freeze out freeze out now not about
to B to you
fire this world sming
mirr
me
[Music]
thank you
everybody
T yay thank you so much everybody how
was it how was it you like it I hope so
we worked very hard on that that's our
brand new song our brand new song but in
want to talk talk more about it we got
to get down closer to you guys so you
can hear us right that's right guys
can't hear us properly here hello we're
going to jump right wait really are you
ready to jump it's yeah okay uh we don't
die are you sure
okay swag
he easy so easy easy such a high jump
there up there I can't believe we didn't
die it must be because of me that's
crazy oh man nice you guys hear us and
see us better now hello hello hi loud
and clear takamori takamori takam Mori
takam Mori welcome welcome welcome I
hope you guys enjoyed the song Oh I
think it was hype I think so hyp a
banger it's a banger it's a banger now
we can talk about the song and I think
you know the most details about it so
give me the dets well this song has been
in the works for about 2 years a long
time hey everyone's really busy in h
right right but you know what it was
finally time to finish it yeah cuz I
said I'm I'm doing this birthday live
thing do you maybe want to release it
and time for that and that kind of got
us finally rolling right finally got the
ball rolling got it moving and um it's
called Fire and Ice which fire no am I
fire is that a real question she's
messing with me she knows I'm the fire
you're eyes oh my God the song is about
us we're very different but when we get
together we make magic happen bangers
Etc yeah that that was the basic idea
and it's it's produced by Teddy Lloyd
who always makes bangers Teddy Lloyd
always makes bangers so thank you and
lyrics by both myself and Teddy Lloyd so
I hope you guys enjoy it the music video
is on my channel it came out like a
couple days ago so Che it's so cool and
the music video is really neat it's by
kanuru who also always only makes
bangers so be sure you check it should
we show
them should we show them the jacket the
jacket oh yeah that's show Che it out
you have jacket they selling jacket up
oh my God she's messing with me again
sorry check it
out there it is we're we're a meme right
now yeah we
are oh it's super nice who drew a jacket
it was by gum shrew thank you so much
gum shrew wow wow come down oh okay
we're running out of time but I also
want to say like
we came from you know small Takami doing
like little cover like w world and now
we have original song Thank You KY for
organizing it yeah no problem than soon
and yeah look at us being cute wow last
but not least we look nice together
P
huh how's it go she embarrassing bye so
thank you for supporting I guess we look
C maybe really cute than all right
thanks for having me thank you for
coming and dancing with me it was so fun
thank you I'm getting I'm getting kicked
out again yes sorry I figured as much
byebye see you soon oh well good luck
enjoy everybody byebye
peace and with that I still have a lot
more songs for you
guys you're going to like this next one
I think I'm pretty sure
enjoy
Lely
[Music]
call the
T
[Music]
fore
foree
[Music]
fore spee
fore
[Music]
foree
fore
[Music]
foree
for
[Music]
fore
passing by familiar
roads I couldn't
find the reason
why who I am you couldn't know stuck in
the
ruins my
delusion in between the
reality my own
desire Keeps Me To
You O moving faster than the light can
I'm in the
abair alone looking
B and I lose my way I can see to day and
I can reach you again then can I let
go I can hear your voice leading me
through the Bo F
away to the
[Music]
Grave I'm walking by the Light the my
eyes alone the silence steing still I'm
reaching out to you come sacrifice
life iive one day you life it will lead
me back till you see
me ooh
I am the
[Music]
Wonder I am the
Wonder faith is gone the well let's try
it no more believe it just to even it
ooh feel the daylight on the Ed
I can't feel
that fall back
[Music]
and and I lose my way I can see the day
when I can reach you again then can I
let
go I can hear your voice leading me
through the ho fade
away to the
Grave I to the Lan I'm walking by the L
the was before my alone the ising till
I'm reaching out to you
conice life myself so I'll survive one
day eventually life it will Le me back
till you see
[Applause]
me I am one
[Music]
girl
I am the Wonder ah ah ah ah ah
[Music]
ah
that was tgw the great wonderer you were
all waiting for that one where me too me
too ah I feel like the vibe was
definitely there did you feel
it great Wonder on my album POV point of
view right now so if you want to hear
more of that if that if that was the
first time you heard it then what are
you doing go listen to my album please
yeah I really like the coral so I hope I
can dance it again sometime soon um
actually I don't know if you know it yet
but right after this because this is you
know as you can see already ending
soonas there is a members only part
following right after this so please
check it out it's the first time I get
to do something like that so it's really
exciting for me my members I hope you
will enjoy what I have prepared for you
just a little bit you know just a little
bit extra ra yeah and besides that of
course I just mentioned I want to you
know talk about my album because
originally I wanted to do this live
during the time when the album was uh
released but didn't quite work out so
let me say it now
guys point of view on Spotify on Amazon
music on Apple music everywhere please
listen to point of
view hi and yeah besides that thank you
guys so much for waiting for this I'm so
so happy that today is finally the day
that I can show off some of my new songs
some of my old songs and have some great
guests over yeah did you enjoy
everything what was your favorite
performance what is your favorite
guest me too oh what a
coincidence yes uh well besides this
this theme is end of the year concert so
I want to say everybody 2023 was a blast
thank you for supporting me thank you
for supporting whole life English and
whole life as a whole and me as a
musician of course this year was all
about that me creating my album and yeah
more musical activities so let's see
where New Year the new year 20124 will
lead us to hopefully more music and you
guys are going to join me right m
and the last song next song is the last
song is also from my
album it actually didn't get a free DMV
so I want you guys to look closely at
the performance and at the choreography
okay all right then please listen to
sleep
talking
[Music]
it's been a long day will you call me
you got me sleep
talking sleep
talking talk to me boy I'm up late
already H
midnight convince myself I'm doing all
all right but you know taking one step
taking one bed when you text me saying
no way no fa no fair no fair you're
right they telling me come here now I
can't wait your body got me talking
breath still got me wanting oh baby
don't you know got me and HS like go I'm
breathing you in I just can't Forget boy
you got me stressed I'm just wanting
it what you
do you got me slick talking in my dream
I'm sleep talking all these nights it's
you no more hiding it n n cut up in your
bed sleep talking in my dreams I'm sleep
talking all
[Music]
this you got me all day I'm
sleeping yeah just like that baby you
might know hey don't you leave me
alone on the phone so B just going to
make a call and I'll know if you really
all in it give it to me now your body
got me talking breath I you got me
wanting oh baby don't you know me and H
like go I'm breathing you and I just
can't Forget while you got me stress I'm
just
in you got me sliping in my dreams I'm
sliping all these ni is
you hiding it n up in your b s talking
in my dreams I'm sleep talking all the
STS it's
[Music]
you sleep talking in the night yeah
sleep talking oh that's right yeah
BM you got me feeling so I sleep talking
in the night yeah sleep talking oh
that's right yeah
B you can make me S talk every day
hello baby who are you talking to yeah
yeah yeah yeah if you want to baby you
know just what you got to do you know
you want it just want look done so don't
prak
hello baby who are you talking to ooh
it's the moment I can't escape I'm
breathless I I can't deny
oh it's
you who made me this way
on
[Applause]
sleep talking all these nights you no
more hiding it C up in youred talking in
my Dre I'm talking all
[Music]
you
inow you got me feeling so right sleep
talking in the night yeah sleep talking
oh that's right yeah BM BM you can make
me talk every
day love is just like a
dream
[Music]
like be
Beach
[Music]
a
they you know that Meme oh
yeah
[Music]
ta give
me makes me want to go
[Music]
party
n
[Music]
p