[Music]
Mir reflection going under confused
Obsession I still wonder if I was made
for you if I could always
see oh please oh make me up the new
calul perfectly for you pretending like
it's old Jack we don't think so
life I'm asking why you see what I want
what I need oh do you oh do
you follow through let you super
now you s me on a mirage I told you up
into shreds I don't even know what to do
with this man AC cross it be good Play
Your Part my
Mir with told I do
anything left I'm s but i' be the king
and queen of
you I'm begging you to see I'm you you
are me it seems like everyone wants all
around run around on and on keeping me
captive escap my way you say I'm way too
fragile I'm just your perfect ID break
me shake
me you never see what I want what I need
oh do
you do
you follow through
you
now you sold me on a Mir I could you up
shreds I don't even know what to do with
this man tell L the cross it be good
play A Part my
[Music]
miring the light the and
on you make me fall in
my
me you so me on I you up into shreds I
don't even know what to do with this man
the cross it be good play aart my
miror sping dis on and
and Mir
[Music]