um
oh
is
later that's going to be yeah it's going
to be so fun
is getting ready to make some memories
for us to start rehearsals come on yeah
i guess we should i'm never gonna let
anyone forget you and kiara behind stage
[Music]
i'm
can you touch your
[Music]
a viewer won a special ticket to record
our live stream and performance yeah
wow
you guys must have missed the memo what
the heck
very lucky i almost killed you
i was not tagged i can tell you that i
checked my tags every five minutes i saw
nothing
maybe they forgot to listen to you guys
or something
okay
i'm not against it
[Music]
is
that's a really complicated name you got
there
begin the interrogation is that your
name chat
um
oh i guess i guess they're already
recording this stream so we're live
hi
hi everyone
it's like the exclusive guys oh god i
cute
yeah welcome to our backstage for our
live stream performance we're doing
a little performance today
oh
a special day
[Music]
i'll just do a quick chat
there's always been a henkai among us
[Music]
how is this backstage room how does it
feel to be in here huh
special pretty crazy yeah you're special
you're special
being in here
[Music]
we're just setting the boundaries here
yeah i'm always beating up you guys
i don't think
[Laughter]
[Music]
excuse me
okay actually this person this this chat
person is the first person to see us in
these cute outfits right that's true
[Music]
we all got them check it out
yeah i can't really do that normally so
now i can't
wow it feels nice i just noticed the
taco you got a little taco right there
[Laughter]
[Music]
practice
you promised
some new moves
yeah of course
well uh are we doing this in a circle so
that this chat person can be in the
middle
i think we'll be over here like in a
line and then you could be somewhere
where we can see you
oh sure
yeah yeah you know wait do you see me
yeah i see you i can see you kiara over
there that's a good okay yeah okay
i don't want to i don't want to just
practice dance moves though we should
make it into a game
thank you making a new game for
as if as if life is not already enough
of a game you want to play more games in
here all right well you know it is
important for gamers for
yeah
[Music]
be cute but it's also important to
follow instructions correctly are you
able to look at girls
no try yeah
sometimes you should it should be always
that's the right answer always
yes
[Music]
yeah yes
the original is kiwawa says simon says
it's just you know copy
naturally
naturally well
i will do some poses and then you girls
should
copy them but only if i say kiwama says
okay
[Music]
put your hands on your hips
sway your hips from left to right left
to right left to right
left to right
oh we're in the blanket
girl
i did not say cabbage
with your right hand touch your head oh
we're still doing that okay
[Music]
with your left hand at your head
boom
says touch both of your knees
um
[Music]
holy cow
this backstage is
put your hands up in the air
yeah
one leg the left leg lifts left leg
put it down again
wait oh no no no no
no no
[Music]
everyone's out
uh
move your butt towards the chat
what the heck
that's a little [\h__\h] up kiara have it
okay it's cute it's cute says turn
around with your upper body only your
upper body
oh
cute
wait i can participate it's cute
okay
[Music]
says
oh wait wait what i didn't i
[Music]
yeah yeah this is the dab right this is
what that looks like to the other side
face with your hands
like this
squat
oh lord heck yeah though i love squats
[Music]
like we're waiting for the train
my legs are gone
i lift the other leg yeah but if you
squat like right now
oh you're doing nice
okay come on
[Applause]
[Music]
just like your face
[Laughter]
[Applause]
she wins because of her extraordinary
endurance why applause
[Music]
amazing thanks for supporting me thank
you for the win kiara work out i'm
impressed
yeah
fix my skirt
[Laughter]
let me just recalibrate myself
oh lord all right let me t-pose for you
recalibrate i see the tracker kind of
turned around
and i can actually lift your ribbon this
is amazing
which means i can also lift your skirts
don't do that
nothing important
[Music]
oh god
and i was saying i was being insulted
and now
we're chasing her like a zombie we're
like ugh
[Music]
jar jar
mirror
oh my god whoa we caught you oh my gosh
[Music]
oh no whatever you do without any
function of your arms or legs
i mean it's cool but at the same time
what can we do to them when they're in
there
force them to watch his games
yeah
i can't even look at it oh my god it
[\h__\h] my eye eyes up yeah look at the
mirror
no no not ready for the power of the jar
sorry i'm not trying to insult you chet
and you need the cabinets
the cabbage patch this is the cabbage
patch
that works too
[Music]
oh it's like a fish they swim and they
eat their own
huh
you want to finish that thought girl
the hats is this the bubba's hat no
don't knock bubba's yet okay
oh these are nostalgic
ah that's pretty cool there's a button
here too oh god there's a button
there's buttons everywhere
thank you here you need this
it's a little hat and then it could be
later
what is that
[Music]
what is that things
[Laughter]
you want to come a little closer and say
that kiara wanna come a little closer
and say that
all right now be real quiet and don't
scream okay because
really we really can't have the police
involved here okay so here we go
like asmr
there you go
there you go see it doesn't hurt that
much
ah that's cute
they look a little embarrassed you'll be
fine don't worry if your face starts
swelling um and your lips get really big
like kim kardashian that's normal so
just don't worry about it
it's like the kim kardashian challenge
but on using mode you know
you like it so you should thank you
get that tick
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
needs the injection probably because i
i've been nerfed terribly please please
i'm nervous
all right you got it
thank me later oh oops
oh god never mind i'm putting it away
jeez back to the freaking hat
we were preparing this thing right
[Music]
just chill
oh she can reach i'm just so small today
why are you so small today
i'm a tiny smile whoa
you guys look weird
what the heck
maybe we should compare our height like
gonna said line up from top nice
let's see
how is the smallest should be kelly
kiara me no no it's it's cute
no it's not
you're getting on your tippy toes you
stopped that
yeah but if we both wear the same size
of shoes same height okay
[Music]
we're like a rainbow she's gone yeah
people are always surprised about like
how tall eena actually is oh is that an
ina hug
nina's not tall
you know short
what do you mean she's decently tall
you know what people can do with this
360 thing now they can do like oshie
cameras they can like clip oh yeah only
their oshie's into one wow
if you just watch this it might be hard
to find you yeah
true
oh
oh i'm not here i'm not here
wha oh my god what is that
[Music]
i can't hit
i live in such a small house chad don't
you guys have anything you know
anything to say for yourselves huh
where's the money oh what they do this
time
i want this what didn't they do
i
you guys decided to ignore me but i'll
go ahead and explain it again
[Music]
so this is an idea that we had for a
stream before right and i'm just now
remembering
oh
you said you were feeling me like
chicken legs
[Music]
wow what take a
is
[Music]
let me go ahead and cover up that
dangerous butt
and go long
oh i don't think i have a bat so you'll
probably have to use the crowbar
that's fine because you're gonna get
football who wrote these prompts
okay that one was mine
that's okay no
not everyone here is into sports right
i'll do my best here
you ready chad
you're ready to get out of the park
take me out to the ball game
if we don't win i'll beat
everybody with this crowbar and then you
chat cause it's one
two
three strikes you're out at the old
ball
game
bang bang bang bang bang bang bang
i'm sorry did i hurt you
are you okay
[Music]
good see just patch you up a little bit
you'll be fine
okay what a treat
all right get to pick the next nice job
okay next person
i choose
[Music]
go for
it yeah which suitor kiara's crossing
her fingers
well actually earlier today
actually earlier today i saw i saw i saw
certain
uh
pink
uh vancouver
confess huh
confess their lashing
bro that was a pride
you do will you give me the honor
oh hold on hold on there's something you
have to go on your knee
bring my ring hold on i didn't sign up
for a bunk hold on a second
will you do the honor
of being
my oh she
put a ring on it
it's not the same thing
yes i do
[Music]
happiness
that or this will return okay
wait wait thanks for the marriage
proposal yeah let's give them a phone
just make sure
yes
very nice we're good we're good
[Music]
i think it should reset hopefully
soon i think it takes a little bit of
time maybe
one two three four five okay
oh please don't worry doctor
oh boy that's perfect
promise yeah
yeah
good we got a lemon right here oh yeah
all right let me see
all right
get you over
i mean time to diagnose chat
yes please look at our x-rays over here
this is uh our nurse cali
who's gonna uh sometimes there's cali
here
all right so it looks like we've got um
this is the business chat
they have um
[Music]
accurate issue going on right now i
think they have a jelly body
let me see that thing um let me see that
thing
and also their hands have become paws
vaccinated okay just uh turn around
quickly for me
all right
[Laughter]
[Music]
how long do they have to live doctor
[Laughter]
[Music]
we'll give you guys
all right let's see what you got oh
but you don't have to
uh-huh
nice
you just leave it oh i'll pick it up and
then put it down
oh i don't need to water break
yeah stay hydrated guys
well yeah true we'll do
it's still doctor
oh i think it reset
oh oh nice
confession
to chad so that's
easy um
chat
um
[Music]
okay well i didn't think i would say
this today but now you're making me say
yours and just kind of i mean i don't i
didn't know
i didn't really want to do this while
everybody else was around it was kind of
weird you know i wanted us to be alone
maybe okay we can just think that we're
alone okay just just act as you and me
and me and you
[Music]
for um while i've been thinking that i
love you guys i love you
[Music]
go home
what i didn't see anything
they don't see anything i saw it i saw
it
like um
oh those are gross when they're soggy
[Music]
step back here there's another board
some area to draw you know
hi
by the way
if you want to pick a car oh yeah it's
good i almost forgot get up
oh now
[Music]
all right maybe try taking it out now
oh cute oh
[Music]
can you do it a little tricky guys okay
oh
that's cheeks
oops wait wait wait okay yes hello hello
chad oh
hello
he's always squishy boy are you so short
you're so sure
oh you're so cute
[Laughter]
their voicemail their car is going to
say it now yeah there's all their
notifications well done well played the
highest caliber
[Laughter]
[Music]
very nice all of us sounds fun yeah it
was all there
what else so what else did we have to do
before we start oh yeah our performance
actually is it's gonna we have 15
minutes until the performance so
um
[Music]
that's a good question ah hmm
do you have any ideas
how do i practice well it looks like
since we have no music you're gonna have
to sing acapella for me oh no
observation
that's true
what is your idea who should go first
yeah
oh i want to hear the singing chops of
uh
musical powerhouse kalipimori
[Music]
yay all right
i think we'll stand back here and cali
because you have the curtain back there
that's a good place for you
okay hold on but i'm missing something
for what i should sing i guess i could
vocally warm up really quick but
[Music]
yeah
yeah are you supposed to
usually i sing the song like three times
before i record it and i do vocal
warm-ups so that it sounds its best but
okay here we go
[Music]
if you find a note that you're bad with
you got to keep trying to hit it
do you have any requests for songs
[Music]
hold your breath guest is running the
show so come alive now
once again so i can chase you down
we are five seconds away from
the end that's come
from here on out it's only just me and
this bloodlust i'd rather just fade away
[Applause]
[Music]
um
wait can somebody else come before me so
i can pull some lyrics up thank you
yeah i'm relatively ready
okay
well okay i mean my my my thing these
are always wobbly but i'll try
come on
[Music]
let's go
foreign
[Music]
okay we stop now
[Applause]
love y'all
[Music]
nice job thank you yeah nice circulation
with all those different colors we could
be like sailor sailor moon rangers
[Music]
i'll just choose you right next to me
now with glow sticks
green lyrics i need to pull up later
sing violet how about your own song
yeah i still need lyrics
[Music]
lyrics
i'm gonna drink some oh no you're fine
that's okay we listen to it a lot but
you probably hardly listen to your own
voice when i when i have to i also never
remember my own songs lyrics so that's
why i chose lanai speculation
yeah i was like
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah heck yeah that was really fun good
job ladies
every song but the one that we are going
to perform
[Music]
we have one last thing
obvious though
what cute which one is that
i think it's pretty obvious our our off
collection favorite yeah that's the best
favorite one
[Music]
yeah that's a good one yeah nice
audrey
um
oh
i chose this one because um yeah i i
wanted to do like a dance school kind of
thing because uh i thought it would be
fun to teach everyone some
choreographies because i i have so many
choreographies in my head and i just
need to let them out it's been so long
even though it was really exhausting and
a little bit scuffed i'm glad everyone
participated in although is that yeah
dance school that's from like the that's
from the dance school right yeah yeah so
yeah i did like this one dude
did i do two yeah the first success so
you did one with all of us
[Music]
who wants to talk about their
do you need someone around you
oh i'm okay i'm good thank you um i
really like myth or treat because i
really love writing songs with you guys
and hearing you guys voices over things
that i wrote made me really happy even
if it was a silly a silly little
halloween song it it made me really
happy it made me want to do more things
like that and seeing the 3d mv was so
cool too and and cute it was like a
dream come true yeah so i hope we get to
collab on more creative stuff like this
together yeah yeah
remember we put it together pretty last
minute too everyone just said
can we
do this
[Music]
but sometimes it helps with the
creativity yeah
yeah
how about you email us you know when we
finally all got to off collab you know i
mean i mean i had a little bit of a
waterfall you know in the first year
collab and you know before the second
year we finally got to see everyone it
was really memorable
yeah
it was fun yeah and we could do it again
that'd be cool
yeah that's that's a minus two because
it was really fun and i love this
screenshot
and this is
this is the stream that started the back
trend huh
is really good
yeah
i think i don't know because this was
like the first big thing that we did
with council as well
[Music]
oh my gosh no you're a cute anime girl
now come on man
[Music]
what does it smell like yeah the picture
is so good it's like chakras
[Music]
it smells
[Laughter]
it smells like friendship it smells like
maybe not friendship but it smells like
something and i like it whatever it is
so mm-hmm
[Music]
now we can surround them with these
let's make a ball against
the memories
in the corners
even though they were great
[Music]
okay are you guys excited you guys over
there
see ya see you soon
bye-bye prepare the pen
if you're not there with him i'm gonna
be very mad
[Music]
bye
oh
five
[Music]
hey everybody
foreign
[Music]
hey
my
[Music]
oh
yo
[Music]
all right guys let's bring in the energy
real strong this time
hey hey hey all right let's go
[Music]
thanks so okay
foreign
[Music]
my
performance
[Music]
thank you
seriously thank you so much
you're so good
don't cry no i'm not tired
[Music]
went by super fast like super super fast
crazy look back it's already been two
[Music]
i didn't think i would stream so much
and i didn't think i would be here for
two years i think i think i was like
okay free free streams uh per week all
right uh i think i can do that free
streams and now i'm doing like million
streams per week
it's been so much fun that
every day is like you know it goes by in
an instant it's like a blink of an eye
and then blah next day next day and
suddenly yeah it was just one year
anniversary yesterday but suddenly today
is three year anniversary one
yeah so much has happened in one year
when you're busy busy
yeah this place was really fun right
it was a fun year though we got to try a
lot of new things
yeah
[Music]
i wonder if that means it's time
could it be
let me make sure let me just double
check that it's time
to ask the bartender
[Music]
i hope they expected it
i hope it's something good something
good always something you like
if you don't know what to expect with
the merch could you really call yourself
that you should know by now yeah
you've trained well by now aren't you
why are you moving up or am i moving
down
all right we'll just go backstage for
one second to get our little surprise
for you guys and then uh we'll be right
back
be right back
[Music]
uh which one who wants to take which one
we're doing these first yeah there's one
for each other center should take so you
know you know
you know just take this one this one
no [\h__\h]
because this is
[Music]
so i should go oh okay that one first
okay ina goes first okay make sure you
show them okay and i'll show the back
too i haven't seen it okay okay
ready can i go yeah yeah go
okay i'm pretty sure it's okay yeah no
speed racer go attack
look we have
our second year i don't know if they can
see it anniversary goods
[Music]
guess what
we're in these outfits
you guys are spoiling
[Music]
are we so cute
yeah you can change the order
[Music]
an idol theme this year because and we
want we want outfits like that too
right idle outfits ooh
now this is this is our choice
could
[Music]
what do we have what do we have why
don't why don't we get the big one first
and then we'll do the small ones
isn't the big one the one that has all
this one
yeah this one has everything so like
cool right
[Music]
i don't know should we do it
what does it say i actually can't read
it i can't read where am i let's see
acrylics
small plushie gargura and small plushie
watson amelia
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah yeah
thank you
everybody was waiting for these they're
like what are we going to see the small
plushies finally they're here
they're here
[Music]
your dreams are coming true
you guys made
[Music]
the website to buy it the
links to buy you're gonna be live at the
30 mark so in about 10 minutes you guys
can take a closer look at these and uh
purchase them even if you'd like so
uh make sure to check it out i think the
links will be down below in the video in
the description
[Music]
i get it that's on the back of that one
is there anything on the back of that
one
it should be um
oh
yeah they're individual sales yeah
yeah
okay individual sales too nice
all right is that it get excited guys
yeah yeah
i mean that's it for merch no not not
yeah
i'll just put this up
anyone
[Music]
yeah i guess i don't know no
i mean we already know
i
a reminder i had my anniversary stream
yesterday so the people who watch that
already saw that but i have a new song
coming out this sunday so i want to play
the trailer here if that's okay
it's the new sound is called do you
do you do you want to see it yes yes yes
i do
do you
do you show us really quiet
[Music]
i think you guys might be in the way
oh here we go
i don't see it is it playing somewhere
[Music]
[Applause]
it's not playing
[Music]
i'm not in control of phobias at the
moment it's out of control
but you guys can check it out do you
i've seen the well you know
i see some of this yeah
yeah it's really cool you guys should
watch it yeah when it comes to that it's
coming out again which date i think it's
it thinks it's the 18th it's sunday and
it's my first my first ever 3d music
video but it's not just you know there's
um
quite a lot of special things about it
and you will notice immediately when you
watch it so look forward to it
[Music]
oh i have a little announcement if you
guys didn't see i just uploaded a cover
to my channel i hope you guys will check
it out i seriously sing in that song um
and i tried my best
thank you
it's
one piece film red i hope you guys will
enjoy it if you'd like it please check
it out so that's all i have to say
anybody else
[Music]
i'm celebrating
i'm celebrating my anniversary tomorrow
yeah
tomorrow yes
so help i hope if you guys are free you
can come hang out yeah
[Music]
coming this weekend might be pretty big
so we're gonna have it but i'll announce
it as we go baby
[Music]
i also have wow anniversary stream
that's gonna be the day after tomorrow
uh
and it's gonna i have a small
announcement it's not anything big but
just a small announcement yeah so this
is the day after tomorrow
[Music]
the other
things maybe i should just maybe i
should just press the button hope it
works this time
we have one more thing
one more thing yeah here we go
is it working
here
[Music]
you can't see [\h__\h]
okay okay
all right let's do it beginning okay
again
[Music]
yes
yeah i think you guys will like it it's
super anime so get ready
yeah the music video is going to be
really cool
[Music]
coming
soon yeah yeah can you figure that out
can we play mine again
okay
[Music]
let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
huh
does that have any meaning am i gonna be
cloned is that like some kind of
future
union
yeah but more important was the audio
trailer obviously i would be so
they're both important
yeah it's important and i hope you guys
hope you guys should check them out yes
enjoy and join lots of musical stuff
going on and enjoy
yeah are singers after well i mean maybe
not singers
something close i tried something close
to idols
me too man we want to be we're something
like idols but uh thank you for the many
many incredible supporting comments to
our wonderful fans all over the world
you guys are the best thank you so much
we love you you're right thank you
everything yeah nothing we do would be
possible without you guys so thank you
thank you
very much
[Music]
thanks for putting this together
yeah thank you guys for trusting in me i
hope
[Music]
first year is the charm i'm telling you
i swear
[Music]
if not i'm gonna rage quit that's not
funny you do no
don't break anything
it costs a lot of directions please
i'm gonna flip
ah it's a nice relaxing music so we can
just relax there's some music
yeah we're not
on a huge time crunch i think if you
guys just want to spend a few extra
minutes maybe answering some questions
from chat or something like that i'm
just going to sit on the say goodbye
you're just going to sit on the air if
you don't mind my hair take the break
i'll sit
i was planning to sit on the edge of the
stage because it's like close to the
night like
a skirt view
yeah
oh and not here just cover it just cover
it
hi
what'd you guys think of the stream how
was the 360 thing is it
was it uh
kind of cool to watch so then i'm going
to fix something did it work well
yeah did it work
keep track put on chairs of your
favorite members were able to look at
them at all times
yeah you're oshie
it's cool so cool really okay is it
mm-hmm
i can't wait to see it
meet you i can't wait to watch it look
around
yeah
i'm glad i'm glad you guys enjoyed it
if you guys have any questions for us we
can read them out goodnight has a chat i
have a chat
i think callie's getting something
we can also talk about some more of the
memories that we didn't talk about oh
yeah bring some brings them out that's a
nice idea
so cool in vr oh yeah it's immersive huh
[Music]
one of us
welcome oh um
hold on i'll go check
you too can be a kawaii idol i believe
in you
promise me you will
or if you don't want to be an idol
that's cool too just promise me that
you'll
keep supporting us yet sorry
no we work here
hi oh my god i want to get a picture or
something hold on
oh yes create a picture
[Laughter]
so many wires knife my
idle tails getting in the way
take a picture from my perspective
[Music]
oh man i just couldn't binge
god i want to solve a
rubik's cube or something a puzzle a
rubik's cube was it is that just the
mirror right now
yeah
group is nice rubik's cube you're gonna
pull them apart can't you just stick
them back together really that's not how
you're supposed to do it
you can paint them though you know
modern problems
problems requirements even more
complicated yeah it's true oh yeah by
the way guys uh so there will be a hd
re-upload of this stream if you guys
want to experience it in vr because
we're streaming so it's kind of like a
you know it's called the bit rate and it
gets a little fuzzy and a little crunchy
sometimes but it's going to be uploaded
it was going to be in 4k but uh i had an
issue with recordings but it is going to
be in 2k so that i mean that's still
pretty good
yeah that's still really good
i mean half of 4k is still really nice
you know yeah yeah let's go
definitely i'm looking forward
um yeah but this will be difficult to
top next year
so yeah i was like brainstorming for
ideas i was like yeah this this is good
to top it but
we make it really difficult for
ourselves to keep ourselves like this
right we can do this
yeah
yeah we should do enjoyment
with our actuals yeah with our actual
parties
it's like we're evolving like pokemon
the first year
this year
models next year will be full 3d i hope
exactly
yeah and then in 4k obviously then in 4k
that was important too 22k to 4k
haptic feedback time baby
yes
that would be crazy some people do
something future is coming
yeah you wouldn't be surprised
that is true that's part of the reason
why i wanted to try this stream like
it's something that i don't think a lot
of people have tried like in in terms of
youtubing
so i definitely thought it'd be good to
experiment a little bit even though it's
it's kind of scary because i was like
thinking uh maybe it's gonna fail maybe
it's gonna look like super shooty or
something but it seems like you guys
enjoyed it i hope anyways we had fun
right i think it was worth
[Music]
apparently you can watch the stream on
the switch and you can like move around
[Music]
does 3ds have motion controls like you
can move it around i don't
[Music]
collab
oh
yeah friends we should collab with it
sometime
can we just boop people on the news
bye boop iana knows
[Music]
don't hug
a really really really sweaty
before right
you all saw me dancing for
[Music]
i put
[Laughter]
although like right after we did the
mocap stuff like we had to travel so it
was sitting in my room for a little
while and when i got home
[Music]
just leaving it
in there so
what
nothing nothing i didn't say anything
get some water
yeah that
let's answer some questions from the
chat but the chat is moving so fast i
don't i don't really see too many
questions right now his passion is
awesome
do something funny
what does inna smell like
what do i say you know smells good
it smells good because i uh there's a
part where i had to help her get in the
suit yeah yeah
oh yeah and the camera smells clean too
she just was sweaty at one time
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah i mean it was pretty hot so it
can't be happening
yeah good man
good i i never was able to say
that or i think that you told me but the
the remaining hat was not my hat i had
all my hats with me when i came back
so
that was yours
no no it wasn't i had all my hats what
kind of hat was it you gave it to me you
were like this hat is too small i bought
it and it was too small remember you
were like oh i went to target or
whatever
and you're like you you said you went to
the kids section
either it's like for a baby
[Music]
when i was on a vacation in in italy i
saw like airplanes flying by with
advertisements unfortunately
because it wasn't italian they've never
seen something like that before like an
airplane advertisement it was like it
had this big where's the homo plane
on it
all over the world i've seen like
any airplanes before come on dude can
you imagine live collab with like an
airline
yeah
or maybe we all came to japan and then
and then we all get on a shinkansen like
a shinkansen
print or something like that
[Music]
and then the inside is themed too with
all of us and the chairs are different
colors i don't know we sell the sweets
related to julian
yeah yeah it
okay i think that works probably all
seen so far like um fans putting us on
like buses
oh yeah yeah
that's true
that's crazy very powerful like it's
been two years but still like when i
hear stuff like that
really you saw one today
impressive with all of us
not on twitter but
um yeah
thank you it's in the tags actually you
should be able to find it i was able to
okay
yeah
which tags nice
the our tag
i think oh yeah all of our streams
recently there was like they had they
made like tuk-tuks with
with my advertisement you know what
tuk-tuks are they're like
they're kind of like crap
i thought you were saying like people
talk weird or something
they made you a special key way to say
tick-tock birthday tick-tock
give me that damn thing
wow
don't sever me
superior algorithm
i remember you telling me like your
algorithm you see like weird animal
stuff i don't see stuff like that when
i'm scrolling i see cute videos i see a
lot of this one
i get a lot of fashion
oh
that's a good idea how do we even get
like hard data like how do we even show
that on stream
we screen share um
[Music]
i would not trust like even just a bear
phone like factory new yeah no no
not happening
one thing that's in everybody's
algorithms is good as uh japanese
duolingo streams
[Music]
there's a few streams like that that i
always see like recommended yeah
i think that's one of my asmr in there
yeah like
yeah yeah like our babies are like why
is this someone recommended again
[Music]
yeah
that's funny i wonder why
what if we did a oh this is kind of like
asmr because you see what's going to
happen is on the re-upload guys there's
gonna be like spatial audio so uh this
is the front so you're looking towards
the front so this is gonna be on your
right and this is the left so when you
guys are re-watching this upload
you know will be
[Music]
you should go to yourself
yeah
oh yeah you should replace somebody's
here i'll do it for you wait oh oh god i
can't reach
come back
where are you
i'm right here oh there there's this
oh that's [\h__\h] furnished
[Laughter]
[Music]
your
yeah it's a little on my skirt hold on
this is a bit hard to zombie a larger
size
huh all right
he's fine i can do squats
[Laughter]
gonna
where is this version of the merch
okay this is the one they really want to
stand up because if i said extra big
anime
wait oh you're there my head
how horrific it's a nightmare
it's like one of those fair cutouts
you have to like lean forward
my hair is in the way oh there we go
[Music]
yeah
i like this movement
oh
yeah what do you guys uh what are you
guys gonna eat you guys gonna eat
anything soon after this i already ate
[Music]
pepsi
sleep is important yeah sleep is good
sleep is good
yeah i only slept two hours
[Music]
i have some homework to do yeah you a
few friends tomorrow
can i do it after you sleep
it's it's pretty urgent but yeah okay
thank you yeah because i reported like
two others three other things i think so
my voice is a little good
well you know as we said before myth
always seems to do things last minute
but it always turns out pretty good yes
yeah yeah that's true that's a good
point
okay can we can we make one promise to
each other for the coming year to get
our [\h__\h] together and do things a bit
earlier than we should then we've done
this yeah
because
it is us
yes that will save not only us from a
lot of stress but also the staff members
that we work with the producers
everybody everybody will be very
thankful to us if we just decided to
make up our minds earlier
sometimes it's us not just us
[Music]
the thing that we can do is that we try
to improve ourselves and because if we
don't then why would other people
approve their themselves you know that's
a good point
let's work hard let's work hard fight
them yeah
[Music]
we're doing this
number two
yeah i'm writing yeah like she's a
dinosaur
maybe we could do like one of those
things where we're like we're on the
floor and then somebody gets like on top
you know like on like something
on my back
you know what's talking about like a
cheerleader thing dangerous
just
like really comfy
i'm comfy
he's got it he's the family picture
right here
yeah yeah i guess big screenshots
yeah we're going to put the song in the
background
get rid of that
should get rid of that well i should
have some clean
the uh backgrounds
[Music]
it would be pretty good yeah
nice nice
[Music]
yeah
yay
oh leg ooze
yeah i love it
kick it girl through
nice i feel like i was gonna say
something but now i can remember
pizza
yum pizza sounds good right now food
yeah
i have some leftover pizza
but you're saying
like so like the one from last year you
know like so they can take the
legendary screenshot
which what
[Music]
okay we can compare it
yeah we can evolve can you can anybody
decide that dance
it's all good so someone will get a
fantastic screenshot yeah you guys
always get really good balance because
i'm a bit of perfectionist when it comes
to this maybe kuda can come like closer
she looks so tiny
she's so small
closer seeing he's believing
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you everybody thanks for
everything
thank you thank you
[Applause]
you're the reason we'll see you again
soon okay one more thing if it wasn't
for you it wouldn't be here
true yeah i'm sorry i kind of cut into
you for a minute there counting right
now
as a goodbye
[Music]
yeah this is good all right everybody
thank you for watching the stream i hope
you guys enjoyed it somewhat and uh each
hd version will be uploaded yeah
[Music]
promise you look forward to it
yeah and all the announcements that we
had today and not only that but you know
going on to our third year now i hope
you guys continue to look forward to it
because we still have a lot of memories
to make and a lot of games to play and
songs to cover and sing so used to have
a lot left in us and
yeah it's all because of you guys thank
you thank you
[Music]
so
you