[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
hello
hi guys
[Music]
howdy hi
hi
let me turn down
[Music]
each one of us introduce themselves
until we go by abc
yeah
okay
who's first
hello everybody i'm amelia watson
[Music]
you don't use that so often do you yeah
is that a new thing i like it i thought
it was new yeah yeah i thought you
headed into the um
club yeah yeah yeah
that was bad
i need to watch it
[Music]
howdy i'm next hello this is claire fi
mori from whole live english what's up
go all that good [\h__\h] hi nice to see you
guys
welcome
i am recovering i was i was a bit uh
under the very under the weather
yesterday i'm doing a bit better today
though and very excited to play with you
ladies yay anticipating
[Music]
i draw with a mouse
i find that hard to believe
yes
[Music]
where did you get them from
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
for introduction iris maybe could also
be enabled according to
discord is
oh okay okay discord um
it's iris i am
the
somewhat new um
hawaiian project hope v singer david uh
last month yeah for those who don't know
me
hi ris
uh i'm very excited this is my first
time collabing with all my new senpai's
stop laughing
i'm sorry
sorry
sorry that doesn't work
apologize
well iris how confident are you in your
drawing skills
ah oh yeah yeah yeah yeah i'm just as
good as that seems to be a mystery
yeah i haven't haven't drawn yet
actually but i've i've been telling
people my streams that yeah i'm i'm
godly at drawing but that was that's
just that's just me um you know put
giving putting a really um strong face
in front of them
i want to tell you guys the truth no uh
uh-oh i i i draw with mouse i mean i do
have a tablet too but like there's my
eye
i can't i can't draw with the tablets
no no
[Music]
awesome art yes okay i'm looking forward
to your masterpieces
are we gonna like when we play we'll
mute everyone else like uh it kind of
among us oh
that's a good idea
i think
but since it's like the first
uh holo full halloween collab since iris
joined i think for the sake of having
conversation we should not mute oh okay
as long as we don't like give away what
we're writing
um
uh welcome back
yeah welcome back
um yeah
i i like to draw
i'm looking forward to drawing a lot
today
uh i've played this game a lot now today
even today i've played it in a separate
stream
and i'm playing it three times this week
so i would like to say i'm the master of
guarding phone um let's freaking go
indisputable
and with this stream i think we would
all like to give a big big warm welcome
to iris welcome to live english
[Music]
i'm still i'm pretty nervous but yeah
because which is six people so the
rounds should probably be pretty short
we can try some other things too but
normal i think is the best is mm-hmm
it's the funniest i trust you kiara okay
[Music]
i'm really on the spot now okay i
already thought of this one since i was
a girl
i have mine ready
a hint by the way i feel like like very
wide broad suggestions make for funnier
outcomes
when they are open to interpretation
but mine definitely is not
[Music]
i don't think you gave anything away
wait we gotta we gotta we gotta go
fastball oh i've never played this i'm
sorry i don't know what i'm doing i
didn't do anything i didn't say anything
what
we heard nothing could happen you didn't
do anything
i heard nothing i really heard nothing
yeah
i was too distracted by my lack of time
i was talking about my roomba i think i
left my room by going in the uh
the kitchen
right
you're using a roomba
i have a roomba
i like to sit on it
oh dear
i don't know what i'm doing
i got i can't know what that time is how
much time is that we don't have enough
time
almost half time
oh
um this is the warm up round right
yes
we have so much time to draw so many
different things don't worry about it
right okay
hmm
i gotta warm up my
my drawing skills what the hell is this
what do you mean what the hell is this
i left my drawing brain somewhere i
can't find it
no way
yeah i feel so awkward drawing this okay
um
[Music]
if you add a little bit of color it will
make it so much easier to recognize who
you're drawing
oh i hope this is enough
also don't don't write anything to your
drawings
why didn't you tell me that
god damn it
well
why is there so many of them
[Music]
um
oh this is adorable
this is what i get from
oh you death you guys don't get to see
what i wrote here one sec i'll make them
go wait we'll see it at the end just
kidding
i'm excited why is there so much about
me
oh what the hell
oh i don't know how to draw this without
being
uh
[Music]
on the right side you have some tools
you can erase and you can also go steps
back
oh steps back okay oh you have a you
have a custom
picture as well that's nice i'm gonna
use this
nevermind oh yeah it does work i'm just
dumb
by the way today i'm playing christmas
music on live stream i hope you liked it
oh no
christmas music is so nice the bells and
everything ah make me feel so nostalgic
because it's music that i went uh that i
was using uh during the christmas time
so nostalgic
usual oh god i don't have time
yeah not a lot of time here huh
not a lot of time
can you zoom in it makes me sleepy uh no
i think
hey
hello how to draw my hair
[Music]
fan artists love this girl
oh
[Music]
it would look like okay so there would
be fingers okay
um
wow this is rough this is rough you guys
oh
[Music]
oh yes artiste
i mean uh
i forgot what what um
nice weather today isn't it yeah
it's weather it's very dark outside i
can barely tell
oh wait wait wait wait wait this this
cereal
now everybody will know who it is right
here you can always add more i just made
it
oh my god this is pretty bad
who throw this
i mean i like it i don't have a problem
with it
you guys can't
have me blocked
whoops
what i want to make louder
oh
what does this mean
i always felt this way is there like
points you can get like are we supposed
to be guessing what people are
like
no in this mode there's no points no no
oh all right
i am confused
so iris
how how does it feel after one month in
her life english oh yeah
i'm finally getting used to everything
yeah
but everything still doesn't feel that
real
yeah this is actually not real it is all
a dream iris wow this is one long habit
of a dream
there we go yes don't wake up the dream
is so nice i also don't want to wake up
i've decided to never wake up
yeah it makes me look inside
yeah we can't wake up
yeah
save me
uh
[Music]
what color is that
it's like this
so
oh my hair yeah it takes a good two to
three hours styling it get ready
yep i woke up super early for this
sounds rough i thought that was like so
set in place you don't need to like you
wake up like this i wake up like this oh
it's even it's worse when i wake up
oh god
my hair brush my hair brush it gets a
lot yeah a lot of hair just gets wanked
off when i'm brushing it yeah working
you've seen those videos where people
clean their hair brushes out after like
two months or so and the water is like
brown
well i can only eh
after two months
clearly
two weeks
oh my god
i like don't know what this is well
think i'm done this is a beautiful
island no one will understand it but
yeah oh we're done what we're doing
oh my goodness
i think
oh yeah
unactually we should do auto so we all
see it at the same time normally i do
manual but i guess auto display
three two
one
oh do you also mind yeah
oh
[Laughter]
scared of hope
i get it now hi i understand this game
now
stick thank
you please stick figures are godly wow
these are really good i like them
yeah it works
you guys can um save save the album if
you click on the button to say that oh
someone wanna be on save duty or i will
do it okay okay yeah okay so we got to
the next album i didn't draw the
presidency
santa missing suspect descendant another
santa theme
oh my god wait what is that
santa
wait
is
that was even still about um iris but i
just put her in there
so i guess i was right by putting her in
yeah made me think of christmas and i
was like hmm i guess i'll put iris in
there
because she loves christmas so much
doesn't she
that's my favorite holiday right yeah
yeah
you will like it much more once you get
to know these five santas
just
album
[Laughter]
oh
[Applause]
that is so cute yeah we really enjoyed
that beauty uh
i liked the plot and it was very
dramatic i enjoyed it
yes next the writing
next
[Music]
because i was playing with the discord
thing and it got me
attacked
[Laughter]
[Music]
she's
escalated a little bit let's go
maury's album
oh
[Laughter]
oh said it was cali
i thought it was now
i gotta finish mine i don't have work
[Music]
oh my god i didn't notice
beautiful there's a dolphin there what
is that surprise
oh i thought it was a dolphin
the realism
of the banana accident
[Laughter]
[Music]
i got that one yeah
what does blepping mean
i don't know what flipping is
oh my god i love this it's beautiful
super fast we shall do more
new turn
should we do another normal one
i don't know what are you to what are
the other moons
well
the others are partially pretty
difficult um for example um i think
maybe sandwich could be interesting
people have been suggesting
suggestion
sandwich a lot yummy
tasty want to do that one we can try it
out
and keep crying until the end finally
describe the last drawing we will
understand when it happens
oh is it gonna like layer all of our
drawings on top oh
yeah
oh i see i get it so oh stop though i
guess do it all right
you can give it a shot how many
okay
[Music]
i think that's good that's a good one i
think it's good
i can't think of anything yeah that's
the problem
i'm excited for your prompt everyone
yeah
let's go something simple
screw it let's just let's do something
fun let's go wow great
that was something crazy it doesn't
happen
oh yeah
i like this ah i see oh god the time the
time is ticking so quickly oh god okay
i had idea
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
shut up kelly shut up
don't shut it up kelly
i can't like i can't let you know
i just feel like making it curse
curse is fun do cursed okay you betcha
girl
you betcha
[Music]
um
oh yeah art skills coming at you
[Music]
yeah
oh i'm so
oh yeah
you're good
why does it not let you save your color
you should have like a custom color bank
you can say yeah
unfortunately
oh no i'm not gonna make it
i don't know uh
don't worry other people will finish
your drawing maybe
oh
oh that's a good idea so maybe we should
leave her for others oh probably yeah
i'm not sure
[Music]
wait no
okay okay at least it's recognizable i
think
all right
yeah
okay okay let's see what happens
oh [\h__\h]
um
this is really cute this is adorable
thank you thank you
wait what
all right i got it we're going point for
point here
yeah
oh okay
i forgot the whole drawing okay okay
i think i remember
oh my god i don't remember i already
forgot i have a heartbreak okay
how am i supposed to remember that
also i don't even know what was going on
there
oh yeah
oh no oh god
um
i'm so sorry
you wanted
you
can you have to click the big big swatch
okay
there we go
learn something new every day
[Music]
there was some something like that in
between wait once
i don't have space
hey this isn't that bad i think i'm
improving i think we're seeing
improvements
now you wait for me game you wait for me
or i'll be angry
i'll be angry you don't want to no wait
[Laughter]
oh what's happening
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
oh my god what is this
wait does this time count as well oh my
god uh
what
what okay okay okay what all right this
is a no-brainer
what
oh okay you notice there's a a bucket oh
wait
um
something like that
this is really difficult
i like
i also enjoy this game
simplicity simplicity is the way to go
what happened
also there's like someone missing
oh man
now i actually still have time damn it
we're supposed to make this like
as accurate as we can
or oh yeah
yeah yeah as much as we can remember
right
and your artistic interpretations of
what you saw
i'm so done
[Music]
i captured the essence of it
i don't know about this one
i actually had it
in early because there was no no more to
say
i guess the reference was just so simple
no no no no
no
[Music]
i really want to know what the what the
title to this piece of art is oh my god
no
i [\h__\h]
the tree gets shorter and shorter yeah
it seems like
is it
oh my god i'm pretty sure is it sandwich
i think sandwiches like that
yeah
all right we're going in yeah we're
doing the best we can with the tools we
have there we go
what is this
i don't understand what
okay okay all right got it i'm not being
able to talk about it because i just
want to make
jokes about what i'm seeing
i think you can make graph jokes about
it
also after the ones we see it anyway so
write it down
remember
oh thank you
thanks
yeah looking good ladies looking good
come on come on come on
beautiful and then there was a
something maybe later
was it like this
i don't know what happened here
uh oh yeah
can we get like a purp
pup
i feel like my drawing skills are
evolving through every single round yeah
yeah
i'm going to follow you i don't remember
when i was before
i don't know who this is
you you the time traveler out of all
people don't doesn't have enough time i
can't stop time
just go back in time and add some
drawing to it
that's cheating
that's probably fine oh okay
wow you're fair you're a fair player
nice
she doesn't use her skills like that i
respect
this is pretty accurate no but i don't
know what happened
there's one more one more thing to do by
the way five out of the six so
okay and then we'll see everything
[Laughter]
oh god
did you hear that oh that was my hip
bone
[Music]
i have the same issues though i really
want that brace that you were talking
about i want a brace for my full body
yeah the shoulder brace to make sure you
don't punch over like a hunch
it would be nice this is a good purchase
you can get one of those gamer rigs
should we go manual because it's been so
fast actually wanna go for it slower
let's do display mode manually okay and
you can open it up on your own no timing
okay
i was detangling her hair but getting
stuck okay okay
i think i did a pretty good job
wow
that's pretty cute yeah she has a lot of
things stuck in there
a lot of math stuck in there
so do we all get the same
i don't um well maybe we did i wanted
some people's images had to memorize it
and then like draw it
yeah
yeah oh oh let's let's check out goudas
wow that's good
did you know what was going on when you
saw that image did you have an idea
i know i just thought it was iris
singing
all right let's see watsons
beautiful my conclusion hold up by it
kelly's saying what
iris has some dope vocal cords though
[Music]
yeah
how about for each album uh each person
who led the album says next next next
and we follow that person uh you know
what i mean yes oh no okay
next is inna
okay
what did i write
[Music]
you know what happens when taco time
ends what
there we go
[Laughter]
so happy i think how i knew i know how
this one ends
[Laughter]
all the time there oh yeah the paint
bucket continued to betray me over and
over again
have an opening i can see them
hey
i didn't make it oh no i died
i wasn't sure anymore if it was alive or
not so i ended up drawing it dead
oh no well that makes sense according to
the first one
oh no rest in peace it went both oh no
this is what happens when taco time ends
i guess so
okay
[Applause]
would you like to read your prompt
underneath no i don't want to keep my
mind
i know what's underneath the detective
desks
[Music]
is okay i gotta i gotta blame eyes for
this one i got all these
very confident
i did it perfectly yes
i'm sure you did
[Music]
[Laughter]
and
what i thought when i saw that was could
i kill them
[Laughter]
very good i love it all right on next
one
oh man please read
good stuff being launched
ready for takeoff
is a missile
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
among us
is
well i kept it very simple
becoming more and more supportive
[Music]
the whole rocket thing just disappeared
orange underneath
that is pac-man
what a turn we've taken yeah
including the british but
it wasn't enough
yeah i love the face on on all of them
oh my god especially the amazement
yeah very well done
next one
yeah
cali
oh
hello and pillow fight show it to me
show me what you got yeah
[Laughter]
[Applause]
your hair grew out look how long it is a
bit of a tall order
long hair
i think my body is detached from my head
obviously some pillows
all right i had no idea what was going
on all right
i tried it was on the floor
there was no space but i made it really
small but it fits doesn't it i've been
trampled it's fine we can move
it's okay i think i think i saved you i
think i saved you kind of thank you
apex predator
apex trampled pretty cool wow okay yeah
okay all right how am i supposed to
follow up with this i don't know
note yourself maybe don't make a prompt
of six people
okay i see it you're also working out of
time
so we'll meet up with these people's
i mean technically that could be correct
because pillow fights are better
um
the fun guys
the fun kind of phase are you proficient
in battle
in bat what what battle all kinds of
battle oh
yeah yeah i have i have magic powers um
don't let me catch you killing folks i
will have to get you
you guys are the monsters you're the
ones who kill
i don't know
alrighty next up iris
please read your prompt you're a suspect
i'm an investigation
is
[Laughter]
i thought it was a spider
[Music]
yeah
is that your power we got so close
i wouldn't i thought somebody would
interpret it afterwards so i just
because i don't know wow
um
a bit more i think we can squeeze in
another normal round
okay because the first one was like only
15 minutes yeah yeah
all right okay let's do it
[Music]
okay
okay um
thank you
[Music]
chad got any ideas
um
[Music]
okay
all right
suggestions submissions
i hope i hope
so someone really good gets that prompt
this is gonna turn out amazing thanks
chad
okay so hydrated
party time
[Music]
mushy mushy
i'm on it
leave it to me
okay i agree
i ran out of time my prompt is possibly
interesting
no problem that's just that just makes
it better you know yeah chaos okay maybe
i left it really vague we have to see
what others
hmm
oh boy what does this look like
um
so we have this i need a reference
um oh gosh
uh and then this one
i need to write a letter in this
since this is a big right
wait this this pretty much true
and then oh though god
beautiful i feel i feel i feel it i feel
it i just feel it it's beautiful
[Applause]
i did not think of the composition of
this picture very well before i started
drawing it oh my goodness
can't wait to see everyone's screams
after this
oh
um
maybe add some more color to this oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
no i need a little more time
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah well i mean
this is pretty easy
[Music]
this might sound better does this sound
better it sounds better oh that sounds
better
beautiful all right
what does that word is
what does that mean oh easy oh i just
described
oh geez oh oh
i need to google someone real quick
[Music]
tell me what is that what is that i
don't speak this language of memes
okay i'll draw what i think is happening
okay um
i think i know who this is maybe
man if i could draw this could be really
cute
but i can't what's the turn huh
oh
um
i need to try
it
okay
[Music]
oh god
not to princess
[Laughter]
she's gone she's gone she's gone
she's disappeared forever
oh no
oh are you
good
we need to call an ambulance
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait
i don't recognize who this is
[Music]
just playing my cards real straight chat
check it out
who is this this is okay
okay okay
i got it
is that a sword i don't know what this
is
oh my god don't make me try so many
people again
i don't know what this means oh yes i do
of course i know what this means
[Music]
um
okay we can do this we can do this we
can do this
[Music]
nope i'm right
okay okay
um
uh
i think this might turn out again i kind
of
wanna google this
[Laughter]
[Music]
this
please
um i have given up completely
ah
never give up never surrender this is
what this animal looks like right i i
don't i lost help even though hope is
right next to it
i don't know
[Music]
everybody's gonna know what this is
right yeah
oh no
okay someone puffed unusually
[Laughter]
i expect greatness
that's good
that's
solid i feel like i know
[Laughter]
oh i think i know where this leads
to you love to see it all unravel
what is good
wow i'm always dead in these things
sama laugh please
oh my god did you practice that
goddamn
that was sick you're gonna say i can
hear this image and it sounds exactly
like that
i really just couldn't
yeah looks like a he looks like a sesame
street character
i guess because it's the only male 3
person that we would draw
[Music]
the one where i started dying by crying
oh no
no i also didn't know what tea bagging
was oh
[Music]
this is what happened
what the [\h__\h] is
[Music]
master of finance
[Laughter]
i my brain um
leave it up to your interpretation
okay okay
that's room for interpretation
i mean that's pretty cut and dry
oh my god
[Music]
it's the conversation
yeah i mean everything looks normal
that's your background basically
oh this takes the turn
[Music]
well you know it it went it became so
hot that they melted into one body
that's a baby a monster
misinterpreted
[Music]
oh
yeah just so we don't get in trouble
the right person got that one now
good job
[Laughter]
[Music]
nothing beats one
yeah
[Music]
oh this is a good prompt this is good
uh-oh this is good my brain i don't know
how to apply it and finish anyway
i mean same thing same thing
oh that's a good one
you understand each other this is the
the telepathy that we have after almost
a year
wow it showed it actually showed all the
letters capitalized
so uh i didn't know that there was an
eat a pun in there i just guessed
oh wow yes
that's my intuition
trained
domination with halloween yeah
with the homies he's cute
that's cute no time to draw so many
people again
we're done
[Applause]
[Music]
i will send them to you afterwards
everyone can pick one to upload on
twitter or five or two two how many ever
you want yeah we have a lot of a lot of
gifts gifts about okay by the way how do
you guys say it give a gift a gift yes
gif oh no
oh wow
[Laughter]
is it not
hello
i usually say gif when i speak german i
think and when i speak english i tend to
say jeff
[Music]
yeah
i remember this being a hot debate many
years ago
yeah yeah
it was it was the pineapple on pizza
before pineapple pizza was a thing
[Music]
okay
who counts down
[Music]
oh
it's the half your celebration mascot
plushies
it's almost one year we're finally
getting half years right now
very soon like what's 15 minus nine uh
wow that was fast
mathematical g who are you what have you
done
is taking over
[Laughter]
imposter
the booth and geekjack page is go going
up in approximately five minutes uh-huh
coming out in i think 20 minutes if they
don't decide to put it out earlier now
but it should be coming out in 20
minutes right um yeah soon
point big
35 centimeters that's big you guys 35
centimeters is pretty big
yeah they're hugs they're totally
huggable i heard they're really really
soft
yes
[Music]
do we have a picture of yahoo holding
them i wonder i don't think
at least not yet
but eventually hopefully
in the near future
this is only because we need it for
scale for for imagination
no other reason um
some people don't think in centimeters
we have a picture
really i thought you guys were talking
about one no no that's what we need
to pose with them not yet
yeah
hall life's number one model
these look like they would fit perfectly
in a t-shirt cannon
they'd be really good ammunition yeah
you could treat them oh we can have a
pillow
with these plushies oh
[Music]
throw them around the gods
no it does not come with yago
unfortunately we're sorry but yoga could
honestly like just quit his ceo job and
become a model at this point mm-hmm true
facts
g2 is calling
i was thinking
dq
yeah that's a good point when uh when we
all eventually meet we need to have a
big pillow fight with these oh yes
ladies
yeah yeah yeah stream it yeah cali
i don't really want to put them into my
luggage because they're going to be big
can you are you getting all of them yeah
of course
[Music]
um
is there anything else besides cotton in
there all right we'll find it out i
guess at the airport
cotton
cottage
i think it's more like the soft like
plushie
yeah they're really soft i've touched
them
yeah i've touched those as well they're
very soft
very good
all right well iris how how did you like
your first collab with live english it
was a lot of fun i loved like
everyone's art art levels are just out
of the world
yeah
yeah that's not me being ironic or
sarcastic they actually did a very good
job
thank you yeah
we're so glad to have had you in this
collaboration
thank you i would like to collab with
all of you guys again yeah
let's do it
yeah
yeah i think some of us just like me
have not done a one-on-one collab with
you yet
yeah was the first time for me to collab
with you
half of you guys oh
yeah
yeah yeah
i still went soon
give you an official tour of the en
server so you don't get that
looking at everyone's buildings yeah i'm
about to show you around
yeah
yeah let me show you phoenixten i think
you might have actually already stumbled
into phoenix
isn't it like the restaurant the
restaurant no no that's kfp but i've
heard you stumbled into a big village
that's phoenix
yeah oh yeah what were you doing the
golems yeah oh by the way iris the hole
that you fell into
because now that we're all here um i
fell into that hole uh a few months ago
several times and lost a lot of things
and i was always wondering who made that
dug the hole hold on
no one has any record of anyone ever
digging that hold on
on stream but i kept it open because i
was like well
well
i want the person who dug it to fall
into it but that iris fell into it
we need to know who the suspect is yeah
who was it
in me maybe it was hachiman
she's in the surveyor mm-hmm
okay so no one else you're blaming me
what is this
or something like that you were like
reacting suspiciously
oh god we need an investigation
maybe it wouldn't ha
who was it i wonder that
uh in kfp i will own up to that not that
whole
not different hold and i don't know a
different different hole that's like one
block wide but uh five million breaks
down
yeah it goes straight down it's out in
the middle of nowhere and when you're
just like really hard to get in there
yep
but he jumped straight down who would
have to do some investing
straight up no no it must have been
straight down yeah i am yeah
somebody got lost and they were trying
to maybe just uh make a landmark or
something or
no it's like really close to my house
what if you did it chiara and you did
you yeah okay
i'm blaming the others
[Music]
hole are we just going to leave it there
just the warning sign
there yeah it's a memorial it's an
important part of holo en history
yeah yeah emma what were you saying um
does anybody have any like uh individual
announcements like maybe a stream you're
gonna do or something like that
oh yeah
uh so tomorrow um i have a karaoke
stream with a special guest a guest who
is not in hololive so i hope you guys
will come and check it out we're doing
uh archived and also unarchived streams
so please come and check it out
thank you
that's all i have anyone else
um
i'm going to play
uh
the police officer officer gouda
oh
yeah and then we're going to come the
devil may cry finally so that's oh my
god
all right um all right then i'll say
next week i'm playing minecraft with my
real mother uh on my channel
it will actually be amazing because for
the people who don't know my my mother
is better at minecraft than all of us
here she's really good and she will
teach me um some stuff and we will go
get neva right together yahoo
you guys are welcome to join in for a
minute and
i want to say hello
i didn't say you guys would want to do
that oh i didn't think so okay go ahead
please
please and say hi
my mom knows about all of you she uh
checked all of your streams out
trying to think of some embarrassing
stuff to tell you
[Music]
[Laughter]
no i didn't have many feathers back then
it was naked
next
yeah
okay anyone else with announcements
uh
[Music]
i'll be streaming subnautica later on
today oh
my god
no no not your virus just some healthy
exercises
[Music]
a morning show that i'm gonna be doing
hopefully week weekly but uh i had the
first one to be on sunday but i'll be
gone for two weeks after that and then
when i come back we'll do another one
okay
cool
i'm gonna check it out
[Music]
yeah
my title
thank you
i will be watching it it might be
archived but i will be watching it yeah
yeah you can check it out i mean you and
me we are oh we have to come to orlando
this weekend
yeah if anybody's heading out to megacon
in orlando florida in the us of a uh you
can meet or talk to us or uh show up at
our panel i believe um
mine is tomorrow and kiara's is the day
after yeah i'm on saturday on friday and
uh
oh yeah if you if you can't attend it in
person if you have a ticket then you can
actually watch a stream of it so you
don't have to be there in person but you
still need a ticket there is a stream
mm-hmm
yeah
so everyone we're looking forward to
seeing you that is the the first one
that kicks off the halloween in america
conventions american canada conventions
tour let's go
should be up by now
[Music]
yeah boop is up now buffing check i put
the link in the description
we'll post it on twitter i guess
watching everybody yeah thank you
thank you thanks guys
[Music]
okay
goodbye
[Music]
you