[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
laughs
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
no no no no no no
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
sorry YouTube was being pretty weird
[Music]
when you start the stream on obs
then YouTube starting stream button
turns blue and then you have to press
the blue button and I did that several
times first I did it only once and I
thought oh yeah streams starting and I
waited and I waited and then I I got a
hunch that maybe it was not working
so press a few more times slap the
refreshing because after pressing the
blue button it grayed out
so I had to refresh the page and the
button was blue again so I pressed it
again
and it was again grayed out but stream
was still not starting then I did it
again I refreshed the page button was
blue again press it again turned gray
again didn't work again
I'm like what's going on I'm being
pranked by YouTube
nice rubber mat yeah this mat is from my
first birthday merchandise it's really
cool rat it's so nice
well guys
today uh if everyone
if you remember
I recently got appointed a new job
[Music]
here
because or or I don't know how to say
with Device rights 15th anniversary they
decided to point some ambassadors
I am one of them so I thought I should
try my best to as quickly as possible
show you guys some nice cards but until
they arrive in Austria that would surely
take a long time
so here yeah yeah
um even though this is not part of my
job okay I'm doing this uh on my own
terms it's my own decision but here let
me put this up there and flex because I
am the Ambassador might as well Flex
about it yeah
yeah yeah
so in order to bring this to you as fast
as possible a bit loud okay
um miss you
[Music]
I have gotten jenma to do it for me and
we will react to it live because she's
on standby Jen my
flow with your hands at the camera
shy come in come in
come on
yes oh no
[Music]
she needs help to open up the cards
probably that's what she means
denma prepared everything so that we can
do a nice card pack opening this is the
first time I'm doing this I saw how life
members have been doing this and every
once in a while before already because
this is actually if I understand
correctly
the second time
that
the second time that we know why struts
is releasing by struts it's releasing
some whole life packs right this is the
second time right right right right
China right right
is that right second time yeah okay
what you got there awesome merchandise
what do you mean technically the food oh
God that's from the that's from the
Korean Cafe the collab Cafe yeah cute
what do you mean eh what do you mean
technically the third why is it only
technically the third now you're
confusing me
[Music]
is a card game that has many many
different like collaborations
so the cards you know they got so much
stuff on them
um
uh-huh okay well then okay it was Gemma
did you hear it was technically the
third one
oh that was a premium booster box for
Expo uh-huh okay
well
we don't wanna look at all those
tacticalities no no no
ah yes so we got how many boxes let's
see one box the one of these boxes has
like how many cards does it say how many
cards is in one of these boxes
oh
does it say somewhere
[Music]
can we get an uh autofocus is that 247
140 ah 145 Plus 247.
slash one pack has nine cards in it what
so how many how many packs
and one pack has nine uh nine cards 16
times nine uh ten times nine is 90.
um five times nine is 45 plus no one's
um
54 so 154 cards and 44.
what
[Music]
like what
what
whatever I got clothes
oh
my God what two three four is it six
seven
I can't count I I was looking at the
chat how many is that one free
that looks more like three four five
five right
I think it's eight packs four on each
side yeah okay okay
wow
can we purchase these already
question mark yes okay even overseas
people
oh maybe that means not yet
why are you pointing at ninity
[Music]
is on my side they have catapulted me
from the bottom left to the top right
because they get it they understand
you're next to amen and I'm above Cali
I'm taller than Cali just by standing
higher than she does
hey okay okay we have many many packs
yeah oh my God wait so there's 144 packs
in each of these cards in each of these
oh my God that's gonna take a while
we'll start with one we'll start a
little bit slowly with one guys and then
we're gonna get a bit faster once we
opened one and when we see a special
card hopefully we'll see a special card
eventually I wonder if there's a
guarantee of how many special cards like
at least one special card per pack or
per per boxes
[Music]
one science come for a box
so we got eight signed cards oh
let's hope there's some desired ones in
there some
agenda actually uh is also kind of
looking for some cards that I will I
will gladly leave them to her if we get
them so Jennifer if you want this
specific card just you know point at it
and then you know we put it aside for
you
don't hold back yes okay
okay
so yeah it's 10 months debut
congratulations clap clap Gemma clap
clap clap clap clap clap clap
yay
demo can we get a hard pose
now with two hands
with twins
double double hand hard pose
two hands yeah yeah no I mean come on
communication uh shape one hand like
save one hand like a moon I guess or
like a half yeah and then the other yeah
there you
go nice
thank you okay let's get started now
that that was a fine heart that you did
before us kind of like Korean style
heart yeah
okay let's start let's start oh box
number one oh I think that she wrapped
off the plastic wrap it's difficult to
do things with gloves isn't it
um
[Music]
or she confirmed you little shits okay
what does it look like when you open the
box
oh okay many packs what's that gray card
is it like an explanation card or what
shots
turn it around
huh is that the signed card no they
would have to have it like in the
special what is this why why is there
like a like a random gouda on top of
that it's a bonus promo card
oh it's a gift
can you use this one in battle too
I wonder
yes
I was looking at the chat for another
thing Gemma is prepared oh we got gouda
right off the bat nice okay let's open
first pack
go go go go
hey
wait there's a bell assistant well of
course you can play with these cards but
I mean I think you know
um there it's also even if you don't
want to get into playing the game you
should get the cards anyway to get one
of kiwawa cards and then maybe keep it
in your in your pocket in your
um wallet at all times okay yeah because
they they look really cute they have
some nice illustrations I really like
the illustration they chose for mine the
hookah Papa first birthday Arts
um
I want to learn how to play me too
it's outfit let's open let's open let's
open
is she opening one pack
[Music]
oh are they gray ones
are they crayons
[Music]
they all gray
what oh
my Julie okay so every card will then
put on the
on the on the ground maybe put the packs
a little bit to the side
oh I think Denmark practiced how to like
uh
you know reveal this in the best way
starting with God she's bringing us big
luck oh and I see already a protocol
behind it
uh-huh oh
Nani what is going on there okay
not shiny though right tell me if
there's a shiny one maybe sometimes it's
hard to see with the camera ah I mean
you stand by with a water gun or
something like that
camera is like going crazy it's like
thank you thank you looks fine
bye okay next time
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's not another thing with like coyote
senpai
[Music]
we gotta keep count not that
accidentally we we don't see one of them
cards ah it's like the best card always
at the bottom of the pack
Jen was struggling with getting the
cards off of each other oh what is that
what is that a blonde is that made
yourself it's a shiny is it bye
kids
oh pretty
[Music]
wow not nice and nicer
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh you know that that necklace looks
like she has a cucumber around her neck
to me
[Music]
so the second to last card is always a
shiny or what
set the system or is it just random
we'll have the shiny cards in that
container for now I suppose
that's what I thought too the Cucumber
okay
next pack please yeah where do we put
those other cards General
then the other container or just to
decide for now
okay yeah just keep them there so when
people can see how many we've opened
until now
[Music]
free foils per box
ah free shiny ones per box and one
signed one per box
is that the guarantee can I get lucky
and have more is that just the minimum
or is that the guarantee like you don't
get more you don't get less
[Music]
bye I also have gone
no signed card guaranteed what
oh Luna
no no
[Music]
no that's the Pokemon cards oh
you you never guaranteed purple
I will show you I will show you
sparkly shiny Lisa oh my god well that
came out of nowhere
yeah
yay
okay
[Music]
not senpai
this is also test if I know all the
names of the whole life members surely I
do of course I do
because I like this cuddling one in her
pajamas oh there's one behind oh
oh
[Music]
um
look look I won't have Nancy ever got
her own card in her most recent uh
stream like she did a white spots card
reveal stream very recently like two
days ago or so I wonder if she ever have
a good one
I
uh you you I think you could request
everybody could request to get their own
card so she probably got like that but
look at me being lucky oh then Zoo
yeah but it wasn't signed it was just
shiny
a standard rare
because you say it like how you grill a
steak
um I would like to have a standard rare
please oh coyote really evil coyote smug
evil
we had that one before
oh yeah Iris a first Iris cardboard
wrist
now again out of paper yeah eating what
is that what's she eating
[Music]
are you killing me are you kidding me
right after energy I get a shiny
Chihuahua
hahaha
what
um
[Music]
wow
what oh my God what how much are these
worth
what oh my God
that's incredible
[Music]
oh my God I'm like what did we already
have the Highlight happening now in the
beginning of the stream oh shining
what the [\h__\h] what yeah
the signed ones are where the money is
sure yeah but hey this is really cute
wait so I wonder like you know there's
these ones that Illustrated once and
then we had the wait a moment wait a
moment then we had the one kiwawa like
standard pose that's shiny
is there is there like depending on if
it's like a standard pose versus an
illustration are the illustration ones
worth more or like better or more
valuable
or which how is it tell me tell me
[Music]
it's more gameplay value uh-huh
not necessarily Nova
there's different shiny tears
you're gonna sell them no no no I would
never do that as an ambassador
metal matters uh
that's the Rarity at the bottom of the
card oh oh I didn't see that yet
oh next pack okay okay that was already
the last card okay okay is this the
third pack not the fourth pack that
we're opening oh wow that's going fast
[Music]
now I can count
oh yeah I like the full art ones uh what
this is this is pretty right so there's
there's standard pose then there's these
3D new poses like funny poses and then
there's the full art ones
oh
I like the full art ones because they're
pretty oh crazy eyes
oh a little uh Senpai garlic senpai
foreign
[Music]
see through transparent umbrella
wow hey so what does it say on the
bottom does it say SSR or so
why does it say that
I don't see it I see the names
where where
[Music]
Arts are what no in my heart this is s s
s s s r
um
[Music]
bottom left above the power okay oh
spray paint Bales oh
copium excuse me in my heart they're
special on their own special to me
[Music]
next one two three four five this is the
fifth pack already and there's what nine
packs what no how many I already forgot
nine cards per pack or nine packs per
box
16 packs nine cards okay wow uh
that's a master to master the pose right
there oh I miss it with some fancy
accessories what's going on there are
these from the horogura episodes just
like screenshots
yo
[Music]
new outfit new design
they're from monogram Holograms Canon
apparently oh is that plus wait white
hair who is this
oh my God
this art is so pretty too holy [\h__\h] hey
wait there wait a look wait no wait in
the look oh can we get horotori all
shiny Maybe
and I'm getting all my favorites
cute that one's cute
[Music]
skin remember
somebody sent me like which cards are
currently on demand like a list and
Wayne was one of the top on-demand ones
with this artwork but I don't know if it
was this specific like version of it
fluffy onion
[Music]
pie
and horoguda style
with the tentacles taking up the whole
picture why
[Music]
um
yes yes
[Music]
today is not my day for pecora
impersonation
monster
[Music]
I I recognize this one the first time I
saw it I was like who is this but I
already know by now that this is
supposed to be my sister
[Music]
she's so pure and cute uh and so young
refreshing did she get like a lot of
Allure oh my man a lot of aloe vera must
have been consumed who is that
shiny and say so oh our first card was
Matsu Senpai after all
mom is moving that was one two three
four five six that was the sixth card
pack I think yeah
[Music]
going well so far wow wow wow wow wow
wow still waiting for a signed one I'm
sure we can get one in this whole box
surely Chihuahua luck stream of luck
Ambassador luck all combined
must bring us something good next pack
oh
I have a Mikko and Sora deck and a
Canada and money deck oh what
specifically like two members combined
deck wow that sounds like fun
how about you make a Chihuahua deck
though okay
[Music]
this is the second one we get from the
same time we're gonna get a lot of same
ones oh no wait this looks like special
special
[Music]
wait can I see it again like closer
closer and then over the over the
numbers
come on camera you can do it figure out
what we're trying to do here
maybe if it covers more of the screen
[Music]
that's an Sr that's an Sr well it's
really hard to see
whoa wait is that our most special card
until now
free per box oh
oh
cool Hollow x-card Holo XO looks looks
card wow
that was cool with all all five of them
no no no
is there a shiny Holo X Card almost what
another shiny one it who's that white
hair no
no I annoyed the Senpai topless
you're closer please Closer Closer oh
yeah yeah I want to see uh totally I
only want to see the the rating
I just want to see the rating
censored for Cecil Nest shortly
[Laughter]
I can't say because I can't say it you
guys know it what is this one
everything r18 probably
oh maybe maybe then my writing down for
me
that was a r
r r
[Music]
um okay
R but so pretty
[Music]
personally when I see her again
one two three four five six seven eight
next is the eighth pack what is really
16 packs in each oh my God that's a lot
of packs
[Music]
side sideways ones I don't know I don't
know why other sideways just because of
the illustration
pie what is that on her neck
and behind was a shin and now we have a
Louis Louis another bird yes we need to
get a shiny little smug Sora some boy
a director scarf
[Music]
cardboard crony
in in 2D form
is that corner is that a shiny [\h__\h]
corner
[Music]
cool school uniform that looks like an R
to me I think from afar
it's a oh it's an R
[Music]
whistle
let me drink some water
[Music]
yeah the art reminds me of your uni so
it's probably from
was that like where did that art come
from when did they draw for what because
the art is like all reused it's not like
specifically made for this as far as I
know oh oh imagine Senpai
um trying to explain herself in front of
the press
senpai
next pack oh we're already the next pack
oh what are some pie
[Music]
you guys enjoying this music by the way
is that is that Iris
oh shiny Iris birthday uh merchandise
Edition as far as I remember oh
hi Wiz it's
miris
first I thought that the right side that
it was like tentacles and thought is
that Ina but then I I saw some more
oh
and oh oh another shiny one
version shiny many dakimakura versions
an interesting fauna what is this what's
this illustration
oh it's like a card style I don't know a
card yeah a cardinal card
[Music]
climax phone yeah
um
drew me but never uploaded it because
it's part of asagi Mama's comica
released art book uh-huh I saw it
because I have the art book I
am from hollogura
yeah I think many of you guys haven't
seen it try to find it now
[Music]
is that our first Aqua cards
took her a while to show up here
[Music]
[Laughter]
nice so many cards
[Music]
random pink hair
too but oh that's a nice one
shiny full illustration
what rank is this also R looks like an r
as well
this feels like it should be an SSR what
with this is only an R then what the
hell is an SSR an Sr what
oh oh maybe our first Ollie card a
climax Ollie
Noel was SRO which one the naked one
[Laughter]
signed ones ah okay okay okay okay okay
okay
oh how many is that one two three four
five uh one two three four five ten okay
six more for this box
[Music]
it looks like ten to me it could be
wrong it's a bit hard to see
I think it's 10 right now
ah Olivia
differentiation there
[Music]
hello I think I know that one that woman
Senpai also I think first
possibly
senpai
what is going on in that pose hmm
shocked
squash
[Music]
Chloe
yeah exercising
wait is that
no way
[Music]
shiny oh my God it's pretty wow what is
this art
ois there pretty oh
looks like she really fits into a card
game oh climax School senpai
[Music]
getting confused by all designs
damn pretty we're gonna put these we're
gonna run out of space
it's an old one I got confused sorry
[Music]
now we have 11 packs
running out of space Oh no guys this
birthday Chihuahua met by the way
perfect playmat Maybe
the next bag
music is banging right yeah I I found
some more Mozart music
I've used it in tournaments oh nice
oh okay here we go here we go here we go
[Music]
classes are versatile and yet I can't
use my own yet because they're bugged
foreign
[Music]
I will get a signed Army one I will get
assigned ammo
shiny what's this blue is it blue oh
yeah oh
my God it's so pretty I love this
illustration
wow coming get it I love it she's so
pretty
pretty yeah
bye climax
[Music]
yeah in Wonderland
um
oh next pack it's going fast guys but
we're still on the first books
oh my god oh we made we may speed up
after this first box as I said again why
did we start off so often with this very
card
um
garlic senpai
eating something mysterious
yeah so many boxes oh my God what is
this
[Music]
um
did I call that person whatever
I think after saying so many names after
one another I get confused
[Music]
I've seen this one before this
artsama shiny hot
ah yeah
excuse me that is
[Music]
that's pretty
cute lovely lovely and no none of a
climax Will May
[Music]
how many cards I should donate these
after we're done with them don't need so
many oh more cats for three more packs
okay and then more seven more boxes
[Music]
yeah me too help just like me for real
for real
[Music]
nobody can help you
oh
[Music]
yeah
pet outfit
[Music]
nice ghetto there
La Plus
[Music]
is it fauna
[Applause]
[Music]
found that because of the green because
like who else is green they're like no
is there another green remember in the
whole of Japan
[Music]
we need more green we need more more
ah it's so beautiful more gives me more
it gives me more the image of yellow
you know hot yeah you know because it's
more like turquoise though like not
quite so green for me she's more
turquoise but she I guess she could be
categorized as green
yellow yeah
we need more green I think coin is a
nice color
more broccoli members please how about a
broken YouTuber or you know what it's
the season of asparagus again I saw
asparagus in the supermarket let's
[\h__\h] go go I love asparagus oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
grass oh yeah good ideas you can tell
all these ideas now to jenma surely she
will make them a reality for us
[Music]
yeah I hope I get some asparagus recipes
in my hello boxes
soon
oh she's so cute I love the art style
that her mommy draws
um
beautiful je'tem marvelous
oh climax Chloe I like this card on the
beach on the beach on the beach
yeah please give us a horse YouTuber
jenma Gemma what do you say about horse
YouTuber
is that is that desirable
I don't know about that horse I guess I
mean I mean the whole anime you know Uma
musume
I don't know you guys are also being
like but think about it
so can't be bad
hmm
we already have one she's called Coronet
she's a dog
next pack
um second to last I think
where's the sh where is the signed card
[Music]
s
so smug or emotionless
[Music]
bye
science card isn't guaranteed it has to
be oh bottom is it Waterman
very cute I'm feeling healed yes
[Music]
I love football senpai's singing and
music her OG songs I love them okay no
more help is desired it seems was that
do we have one more was that the last
one
and that looks like gesturing ah next
book oh okay let's put them maybe in the
Box for now yeah
[Music]
one box done so we might go
if possible a little bit faster for the
next box because we have many boxes okay
what's our bonus card
[Music]
the last card that we just saw from the
other box
okay okay
let's see
let's see look at card five only what
does that mean
what does that even mean a dupe
what a coincidence there's too many
weird coincidences here a sus okay first
pack first out of 16. wow
[Music]
just this card five is where the shyness
and signs can be
you mean out of one pack the fifth card
would be assigned one
there are 18 boxes in a case with five
signed cards per case
really
we'll see we'll see the fifth card seems
to be Sr or higher eh
or less right
[Music]
yeah I'm looking I'm looking because
Empire but I've already seen all these
before
am I pretty senpai
[Music]
something shiny
what is this is
I don't think we have a shiny Subaru yet
right we need a shiny Subaru and the
shiny movement and we have shiny horror
Tony
[Music]
really lucky
it's meant to be it's Destiny
[Music]
and I like this one too Louis in that
criminal really nice
[Music]
great RNG yeah I love all the ones I
could get I get my most beloved members
I love them all of course but you know
[Music]
shiny mom
ENT
I was just asked I can't believe it I
can't believe it this must be rigged eh
eh look at how many members are in whole
life look at the box look at all these
members
how can I keep on getting uh Tony what
the hell is going on
what's going on
mommy mommy
what's going on you would think that's
her Oshie it's not true though oh oh
yeah oh wedding shiny wedding or date no
wedding
yeah that's yeah I think that's like a
wedding outfit is it not sure
oh my God
beautiful
company
[Music]
romantic it's so romantic from a
birthday marriage oh my God wife wife I
bought friend
card obviously wife next pack
yeah I think Jenna is doing it as a
reference to the then the cheese card
pack opening
[Music]
wow me robot roboco
for Pokey
eroha
tawasama
[Music]
shiny
Barbie
that's a shiny goober
[Music]
[Laughter]
button
coroni
thank you
oh or shiny iroha oh pretty nice
[Music]
coroni
coroni pronounced English sounds like
crony huh
[Music]
no I I like this
bye
a shiny wife Corona in the wrong pile
did we put it in the wrong pile
is that true
[Music]
she accidentally in the wrong pile
or did I get one guide
you will go into the usual room if you
said something wrong eh
it was what there is a shiny fubuki on
the second pile
apparently there's really a shiny oh
which one is the second
[Music]
which from the top to second or from the
bottom the second ah oops
[Music]
my wife
my new wife thank you thank you for
pointing it out good good checking there
so you know what that means for Grandma
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh no no health is not coming well I
guess the chat was helping
laughs
one more chance
one more life support
[Music]
[Laughter]
shiny
oh
wow that art almost doesn't look like
her she looks like she's acting in the
musical
oh my God
beautiful
[Music]
Oh I thought it was a signature I
thought the balloon strings were sick
[Music]
it looked so scribbly oh oh man pastel
rapper Minato akua cute I think this was
also one of the desired cards
um
nice and oh and again a climax Ollie
[Music]
wow wow wow wow
oh
signature yeah I can imagine an aqua
signature card wow they're very desired
[Music]
[Applause]
trying to stay organized here very nice
very nice beautiful look at that
technique of How She lays down the cards
just like a manager should be next pack
[Music]
and I don't even honestly I don't even
need my own signed card in these packs
because I have a set separately of my
own cards
um
so like every version of all of my cards
I have
on
uh we'll see them at the end at the end
of the stream will show you in case we
didn't get them
[Music]
no no
it's about the joy the card gives you
exactly oh is that a shiny at the moment
now short hair
that looks like blonde actually
[Music]
our card sets so often
same card very popular choice
I'm a hype I'm a hype I'm a hype how you
getting all your favorites I don't know
could it be rigged but how would they
know without me telling them what my
favorites are
don't think it's rigged but damn I am a
lucky bird am I not damn
oh hey
it's so it's so is that e
H meals and pie
at the scene
not me though senpai
oh shiny incoming no
that's why it took some time
I apologize I guess I'm now number 1.5
uh Gosling I'm a Gosling
[Music]
oh wait not shiny but climax uh Cali
that's not shiny right we just signed no
it's not shiny it's not signed let's
just oh climax okay
if we have shiny yeah it was the shiny
of this pack right or was I'm in the
shiny of the previous bug
[Music]
cool car though yeah it looks nice
Comics Callie
a death card oh yeah yeah first Cali
card
oh took her a while too to show up
oh shiny
oh
say bye must be like some birthday art
or so oh pretty
nice
was that of this pack
or the first
ah of that pack okay okay I better drop
the Maury
[Music]
why is it called climbers because they
go sideways
oh
climax can be foil
some of them are ssps including Kelly
and good albums what you mean SSR what
is SSP iwoha
I'm for booking
senpai
I am a senpai
[Music]
SSP is okay oh
Hold On
Together at aquarium date cute
a very parasocial card
[Laughter]
the fine fingers yeah
I recognize that by the fingers of
course
[Music]
um
oh hey hey shiny biles
hey hey
baby
hey hey konkon
nice good pack good pack
yeah shiny shiny baby
oh next bag
[Music]
the suicide SSP is currently listed at
450 000 yen
000 yen
how much is that in USD
[Music]
damn Mommy
very expensive too shiny
[Music]
um
yeah there's actually not that many
black-haired members are there there's a
lot of silver-haired ones with black
hair not so many so I recognized by the
spiky black hair
cute Beach is this r or is it SSR
[Music]
out
and when do we get SSR
[Music]
tell me when we get an SSR okay
I had the yen is is ridiculously weak
for quite some time now I'm like what
the [\h__\h] my my usual head conversion
that I use doesn't work anymore for a
long time and I I didn't realize oh
shiny um
[Music]
oh my God is that
SSR Sr which is r that looks like a two
star
in the shower though wow
[Music]
that was beautiful
I almost didn't recognize her because of
the wet hair
so straight
[Music]
oh nice
oh are you listening ah
[Music]
no of course I looked at the face
huh
what are you saying next box
wait we finished another box already
this is the third box
no it's just it one two three four five
ah it's just the second half of the box
right
okay okay oh oh my God
why did I how did I get so many boxes
well chances are higher that we're gonna
get something like everything incredible
and then
I can play with a deck made out of only
shiny cards
um
[Music]
hydration always cardboard race
yeah
garlic senpai
foil this is what they call a foil
but it's like shiny and foil different
value does it does it say wait is this
is this an Sr it looks like Sr I think
it's an Sr it's an Sr
[Music]
okay so what foil is better than shiny
in general
[Music]
um
our second is oh is that me is that me
nah
it's
amazing shiny even the okay Papa art I
love this one so much oh lucky
hey more birds wait that's it did we
already have a shiny Chihuahua
I think so but maybe a different artwork
ah didn't we have like the standard pose
shiny Chihuahua before
[Music]
ah that was an Sr the default one was an
Sr I like this one more because the
artwork is just so badass
oh
yo
okay wait so we're still looking for a
shiny Subaru but the other burps we
already have right
[Music]
isn't sorting the cards I'm going to die
why what do you mean sorting
senpai
people who play card games a lot are
doing it differently apparently sorry we
are beginners
cute very cute cards but these are why I
use all the standard poses come on come
on now shiny incoming
you can't fool me with those ears
[Music]
birthday art drawn by Ina
um
those flaps
tell it immediately and another climax
movement
[Music]
and the hair yeah of course of course
birthday illustration
so nice
okay Nancy
when somebody is calling me don't call
me now I'm streaming
what the [\h__\h] is calling me
why
oh
senpai
pie
CE
[Music]
yeah the hair looks a little bit too red
but okay oh
is that is that shiny or for it no shiny
right yeah a little ah there we go
there's some sparkle some kirakira
[Music]
put uh R this in there our
pretty in pajamas
U
because you sign me down yeah
okay
for Miko P incoming where are they where
are they
signing Yago the rarest card oh they
should put that in there somewhere hmm
I have seen that card like so many times
too okay
mindset about that one too
Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy
yeah
me I said Mommy
where
is
[Music]
hmm
shiny no modern senpai
morning senpai
glasses
I fought because of the red look the
hair looks so red and the ribbons and I
thought eh I don't know this art but
[Music]
now the glasses make more sense too
[Laughter]
um
how wide is genma's job scope oh she has
many many jobs in her job
ah yes
oh guys do you have a do you have some
questions for Gemma and then she can
answer with yes or no wait wait let's
take a little break here
give Gemma a question she will answer
yes or no
[Music]
are you single sorry that's the most
asked question
of course she's single like how can she
even like you know she's working she's
not even sleeping she's working 24 7.
there's literally no way that she could
you know I'm sorry Grandma but let's be
realistic here
but it's okay you have me
she's not answering the question though
maybe she's writing down a really long
answer
[Music]
Denmark Denmark
I think maybe she's crying
do you have any other question
uh
Gemma uh what's your favorite food can
you like actually write it down I know
she likes the maximum spiciness level
for everything
I wonder what's the most favorite food I
actually don't know it must be something
spicy though
maybe really spicy curry
really really really maximum spicy curry
[Music]
corn Pizza
well
yeah yeah yeah but she always gets
maximum spice level she's she's one of
the Spice Girls yeah of
ah do you like pineapple and pizza
Denmark
don't disappoint me
[Music]
oh
come on come on
because otherwise how could we get along
so well huh it's impossible
[Laughter]
okay next packs four more of this box
okay who
bye
[Music]
not that I really care but show me a
peace sign if it's quinoco and show me a
thumb up for takenoko
oh
[Music]
peace
okay I really don't care though
um
okay owies papers
[Music]
Senpai God another God that there she's
also a god oh another God
many gods in whole life
[Music]
too
shiny
[Music]
pickle pickle yeah another one into my
favorite collection oh
oh
lucky lucky lucky lucky
Tina
[Music]
is
yeah
there we go there we go
sounds more like it
[Music]
yeah I sound like
okay Louie
lion
dog
[Music]
an elf okay let's say just what it is
a turkey
lion
well holocs secret agents I guess
probably oh
[\h__\h] is that LaPlace
[Music]
yes turns out um General I don't know if
I said desirable before General is a
huge okay you Senpai fan he has some
merch some some merch only song
take it take it this one goes on the
Denmark oh on the general pile
[Music]
the normal cards you can have the normal
cards too
[Music]
can I have some cards which one do you
want next time
we finally know Jen was awesome yeah and
you're OSI
[Music]
isn't it
don't you don't you say it like that
sheep a rabbit rabbit or bunny uh like
dagger Indonesian traditional dagger
Angel PowerPoint angel
oh
I feel like this is our second shiny
akidoso senpai
um
elf right like some some some kind of a
special
um what was it like uh not a
[Music]
um
of Elf garlic
a cyber elf
croissanti what
oh my god wow
Wow Let's Go
pretty ah so pretty so pretty hmm
shiny clock
tick tock I makura
in in the T-shirt
last pack let's go
[Music]
I got all of shiny Council oh
shiny fauna
I have a shiny band so shiny crony a
shiny mermaid do I
do I really have shiny all of them
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
one of this one
next one the next one is it
surely
[Music]
temple in the next one
if you want to play you might need dupes
[Music]
now we are in the third we're gonna
start with the third box now my God
go
we have eight
[Music]
I predict the signed pekko that would be
insane I wonder what signed card I mean
at least one there must be at least one
in eight boxes right
[Music]
yeah
third box counted wrong eh I think it's
now now comes the third box I think
roughly 30 minutes per blocks damn [\h__\h]
ha
I think the second box went a bit faster
maybe even though we had a small tangent
oh God
let's let's go let's go let's go
are you coming wrong okay
um
and but we have to go through them
anyway so I don't know if we should
really just show the SR SSR hello and
then jenma has to go for them anyway
special card is
[Music]
oh again
unless I don't know can we
and eventually you can just skip to the
rare card since we have seen all the
common ones okay
on Denmark can we do that
like uh sort open all packs and sort out
only the the special ones is that is
that really faster
[Music]
I guess I guess so I mean you can just
find the shiny ones quickly I suppose
not well General says not really faster
she probably is a bit slower because of
the gloves too
if you have the grip on your thumbs and
all that without gloves then I think it
works faster
[Music]
you just open the pack and skip the
first cards
I mean
let her cook yeah okay let's go
we're just gonna try to be faster oh wow
maybe you you oh
I'm gonna look for eurobeat music what's
how do I write you repeat in Japanese
Euro beetle
a little bit
are you sure
[Music]
it's wait is that shot r or s r is that
foil or just shiny
oh a shiny so it's R and we had this one
in Sr before it went I can't see
I can't see okay it's r
it's R okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] that's loud
wait maybe this one
what the [\h__\h]
wow that sounds like a new Morning
musume song
[Music]
oh
actually I like this it's kind of
fitting right now
I'm I'm watching by the way I keep on
like peeking peeking peeking shiny
where I need the whammy sticker on that
one please yes why me
oh
[Music]
vibing to the BTM you're a beat oh not
quite your beat though it's kind of like
more I don't know what do you call this
oh whoa what was that
low volume we wanted more higher
[Music]
one I love this one
oh my God okay but give me the shoe
bottle can I exchange two shiny wabas
for one shiny shoe bathroom
yeah
I should sign them per hand and then
girl raffle them to you guys
whoa
that's
baby baby
my friends
[Laughter]
double another double beautiful card
though
my sweats
as fast as you guys know the advice
struts means
white and black
anybody here who didn't actually know
that
yes yes yes no no uh
go that's why the logo is vicent uh
white and black
ah cute cute cute
very cute oh why are so many purple
members
free purple man but ah oh my that's Sr
holy [\h__\h] I have the same one in in
all right and this is Sr right oh
Mama Mia
oh yeah I'm pretty sure
lucky
[Music]
nice still waiting for the super to tell
more hello Tony
[Music]
oh wait I have this one already right
um oh now we're getting a lot of doubles
even though there's still so many that
we haven't had in Sr yet
okay pack finito next pack this is the
fifth pack
[Music]
is that one of the backs are gray or
black and white oh maybe
Maybe
or just a safe printer costs
who knows
to have all these fancy front cards
oh I already have
lopa
oh but where are we speeding up it feels
definitely faster
next pack six pack
six pack genma is getting a six pack on
her hands by opening all these card
packs
of course that works that's exactly how
it works
I don't think she's even hearing the
music but so I don't know how it can
motivate her but I'm trying to recreate
for oh
is that Subaru no way no way
all right that's it thanks guys for
watching goodbye
[Music]
somewhere so we can see how lucky I am
is enough and maybe the the SR Louis
[Music]
wow we got the cute bottle in the in the
kimono
oh look at them look at those birds
we're bird watching right now basically
blue
what does that mean Exodia of whole life
what does that mean
[Music]
yeah
um I want if if any of my homo verbs are
like a standard pose I still want like
an illustration one yeah okay so we need
a better movie
see she's so shiny that you can barely
see her
Sonia has five cards oh it's a Yu-Gi-Oh
meme what the hell I don't I don't know
I'm not the Yu-Gi-Oh ambassador
the mermaid too bright turn down your
brightness for me you're too shiny
wait isn't we need to wait where's shiny
Wayne and my shiny Wayne is so beautiful
[Music]
hard to find I suppose ah there it is
okay let's let's put
on the right
good good
maybe top row as well
thank you thank you thank you looks good
looks good can you put Wayne
um above kiwawa
[Music]
how pretty
pretty oh and even then you can see that
the Sparkles when it's like laying up
like that okay nice
[Music]
just so we have some space in the middle
it's more balanced that way
um you know graphic design is my passion
and all that
she moving
oh guys remember mume's new outfit is
coming out this week
yay okay let's continue
[Music]
what cards would be nice now that we
have a complete horotori I guess another
a different movie card would be nice
and
I already have this oh another shot
oh you have a shiny Oh Nana tea I don't
know I'm like pretty happy I guess a
signed card of course
um all of shiny myth oh yeah yeah we
haven't seen
do I have a shiny inner I think I have a
shiny inner I don't have a shiny Cali I
have a shiny armor
hmm
no shiny Cali only Cali left ah oh yes
that one is so cute
I mean ideally we want the shiny of
everything right and more more SRS
rather than ours
[Music]
cute
Cali is super rare why
why
okay let's continue
oh yeah maybe more gouda cards too so I
can give them to her
[Music]
again
such a popular starter
no the official holiday members are
those five in my you know in my I mean
you know that's how it is yes
Kyla can be oh special guest
as five members now no more please no
more new verbs please it's too many
already
five members is like the perfect balance
for idle units there's like certain I
think like free is a good balance for
like a smaller type of group five is
really good and then if you want to go
any higher maybe seven
um
for specific like units you know
yeah nine is nine is in my opinion for
idle groups too much
I mean there are some well how many
members does twice have don't they have
nine
but it's kind of overwhelming
it's like so much to
Port up I've seen this one before
haven't I
shiny
oh
[Music]
full pretty
that's so gorgeous
yeah five is optimal I feel like for
nine or anything higher than that
[Music]
um
I mean it can look really cool in
choreographies
but
it's overwhelming to me oh did we finish
the Box
or just half of the Box oh probably half
of the Box okay
very true Ryan
and the good thing is if you have like a
uh like you know three five seven nine
what do you call those numbers
uh an uneven number then you know it's
good for formation because then there's
someone in the middle
any odd odd numbers
yeah
looking choreography is if it's even
numbers you never I mean if you try to
put someone in the middle then the
formation will look kind of weird
you need like a center
and switch it out and have other centers
you know you know
um
now I know what Sr is because that looks
like foil to me yo
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
stinky
oh there's someone want to have this one
huh my R Ina
climax only okay
[Music]
going fast now princess you want you
want you may have to get yourself your
own kinds hmm but you know I would love
to give them to you
but I can't
sorry guys to disappoint you I would I
would love I would even sign them
personally if I could
I want the regulars too oh gladly you
take them
the sticker
my journey
oh
standby
[Music]
for you
okay it goes in the back okay
remember to get it for yourself okay
it's yours
this is your card now you have to take
care and give this cat a new home make
sure to feed her with lots of Kibbles
and lots of love yeah yeah
finally jenma has a pet of her own
adopted
okay you're adopted eh eh eh
how would okay Senpai react
smug
oh
mommy
when there's a little break I think a
shiny isn't coming but sometimes it's
just whammy with a sticker
it's like
oh
come on
the wami is like like you know like
Chihuahua becoming official name isn't
it
does everybody say wami at this point
does anybody still say Lami
I guess I'll also start saying wami
[Music]
wami always has been I say mommy eh
maybe if you watch more let me you will
eventually end up calling a wami because
that's how it worked with kiwawa I think
what a genius
[Music]
I think that's also my second one of
that meal Senpai in a specific artwork
and not to are
you oh
[Music]
again same Arts
um
I'm really lucky
I feel it I feel the side cards are
getting closer to me
let me eat some chocolates
it's gonna take a while here huh
I told my brother
it will only take like
two to three hours I was wrong
it's been almost two hours
because he's coming back one more time
[Music]
he had some more compartments
um what are you call it oh
yeah
I'm parking hunting yeah
so we have all of shiny myth now oh
third one but second
um R of dive type
um
nice
he's so lucky lucky lucky lucky
[Music]
I'm telling you why guys it's because of
the magical hands of jenma and this
gorgeous
best play mats underneath
it's all helping to summon more luck
where's the shiny oh there it is
ready okay
um maybe maybe I'll share with
amaze
teammates Maybe
investigators
where are you
um you want one huh
I could consider sharing if you
um exchange it maybe let's let's let's
uh exchange a straight I would like to
have a shiny Illustrated movie please
thank you
deal
someone having no probably not probably
not yet
incoming trade offer
oh
I guess I gotta
guess I gotta get my own Illustrated
woman
[Music]
I should buy all the shiny mummies uh
all the shiny almonds
last pack of the box
well how much are you offering
it's more for Millions isn't she
or is she not worth millions to you
I want to buy one shinyawa oh well you
can I have so many purple oh
wait go to General go to Denmark yay yay
nice soup
for you janma
for your sake we need all the special
you know what I think the best ending
would be if we could assigned the only
signed card that we get out of eight
boxes will be a sign okay card and then
I give it to janma wouldn't that be like
the best outcome possible yeah
[Music]
know when that's gonna happen ah
this one kind of hard to see the
sparkles hmm
[Music]
wait what's that was that the last that
was the last pack of the books free okay
okay box four no I'm getting there we're
getting there
done
let me tell my brother I need a bit
longer
um
from them
[Music]
maybe a bit more than that
spy
box four
yeah
um
it's not cold I think it's warm
how many boxes are there we have eight
boxes in total prepared which is quite a
lot let me tell you
that's like how many cards in total
[Music]
is
Chloe's Empire not senpai
1152 cards and we still have 70 20. yeah
okay but the first two boxes we opened
kind of slowly now we're already faster
okay wow that that's this stack is all
almost all my shiny cards
that's already like a deck easily
wow
okay
that's a really thick stack
damn
I gotta try the deck
yeah
trimming the deck the deck the deck the
deck for people who don't understand
it's a joke from my slay the Spire
stream
where I said trim the deck and I think I
accidentally said something else
I have to trim my neck
it's a fake deck
oh
and one of this one shiny care we
lucky thanks Dad
I wish there was a sheriff outfit card
but oh
shine Colleen pack number one complete
I don't know when I could ever play it
with some other ambassadors
if I go to Japan maybe and if they also
learned how to play the game
as the hand come stream possibly yeah
Muna is interested in playing I guess I
gotta go to Indonesia again then
we'll see we'll see how it goes
shiny incoming
no not yet next one
oh my God
I could also say bye really wants to be
part of my deck
please come to Indonesia said the new
please come to Brazil I've already been
to Indonesia and Brazil but I don't want
to go to both
places again eventually
um
oh yeah this is the third pack I think
yeah fruit out of
nine packs
no 16 wait no what I forgot again
all right I guess it was 16. shiny
colony I think we already had this one
too
I think so looks familiar
um
nine cards in 16 packs yeah yeah
I feel like this should be nine packs
and 16 cards in each but okay
and does that come out to the same
result
it's 9 times 16 the same as
yes it is
yes
I've been out of school for too long
okay
I feel like I already had an Sr
different artwork oh lucky
wow
music
[Music]
who's missing in in in in Council no one
right I already have all of shiny
consoles
y'all
do and I have a shiny Iris too so I have
a shiny alien everyone yeah yeah yeah
not every card but
um
okay I can have an En deck maybe
according
money meal
well unfortunately mommy there is no
sign on in these cards sorry guys
Council complete yeah
[Music]
lucky me
maybe give Jenna a break at this box nah
she needs no break Emma doesn't need a
break from this box Gemma needs a break
from work
I see that Gemma I see that
I saw that
[Laughter]
oh
Gemma what's your favorite type of bread
write it down please
what did that hand movement mean I don't
understand
it has to be it has to be you know the
right answer
I believe in you janma
[Music]
the virus
spreads to janama too I spread it
forcefully
[Laughter]
wonderful now I just wanted you to write
that so that you can just show it
whenever like you show the help cards
random Castle
random muscle here and there just a
console here a class over there all
right
right correct answer by the way
okay let's go
that card is so cool
oh
what on Earth is going on I keep on
getting shiny Louise
an
so many doing it shiny ones at that I
don't think I am I might not even have a
single non-shiny Louis card
they're all shiny
let's change bgm
no wait which one oh
but that one's very repetitive I think
because it's only 12 seconds
how about this one
[Music]
oh oh oh oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
wow
yeah
good stuff this is perfect
even though Jenna isn't hearing it I
feel like she's feeling it
[Music]
um
oh
again
oh I have so many to give away now
this is really good I need to download
this so long actually
oh
wait I feel I could make this into a
song
think I could write lyrics to this
because it even has like the
separation I feel like although it's a
it's a looping one though
it's a looping one but it feels like you
could separate like verses into choruses
and so on and the bridge
[Music]
and now okay the second half of box four
I'll soon I have as many cute wild cards
as Sally yeah
member stream idea yeah we did that
actually before a long time ago I tried
writing um
lyrics to an audio stock track
and I did I did it successfully
whoa is that that's shiny not foil
rights wait that looks like an Sr
this is
[Music]
oh not another pajamas over
a total project full style EDM oh
another noise senpai
well that's a that's a nice start
oh yeah now it goes hard
[Music]
sheesh
this is now an audio stock Library uh
window shopping
well I don't even have the windows up
because I have a subscription
stream yay okay I'll play the total one
now
give me a good card give me signed card
please
[Applause]
it will be in box five I think
it won't be in this one oh shiny sunny
yeah listen along
climax Scuba
I don't understand why Kelly will not
let me convince her to use the audio
stock she doesn't understand the
potential
that is in audio stock
I tried to tell her but she doesn't get
it
trust me
and she's still using like the old stuff
um
but he wouldn't get it that is a boomer
yeah she just stays with the things
that she already knows and already has
yeah dova Dover syndrome I used to use
those syndrome in the beginning but
audio stuff honestly has like
100 times the amount of tracks in it
it's way easier to look for the library
as well
Kelly please please come to your senses
here at kfb we understand audio stock
superiority Superior superiority is that
a word
get with the timestand
[Music]
cute
period oh and again no I also have like
four of those or free
put on standby shiny oh we're getting
really fast
[Music]
damn like jenma is like
running a marathon
because
she knows when this is done she can go
to sleep
terrible mode turbo mode active
active oh
okay
she's just you know put all the all the
cards on her Palm
put the cards on her palm and then you
know
what I mean
but then everybody would be like
oh again shiny one
that one is so nice
[Music]
I love that artwork so much
is it's from Lux Sensei right
pretty sure
it draws for they are so pretty
they're actual artist does their child
the most Justice
yeah with gloves it is rough I mean I've
done many things with gloves before and
when it comes to stuff like this it's
really difficult but she got used to it
she's had she had some secret technique
Maybe
oh
nice
wait that's an Sr even that's a foil
r s r s r s s r is literally without the
ah
without the uh what do you call it uh
the O and the a what do you call those
r s r s r the vowels here the vowels
two more packs
of the first half right I'm confused
where where are we at now
two two
two I don't know what that means we'll
see
we'll see ah oh second half already oh
my God
[Music]
double polka actually
zoom zoom we're zooming through it yeah
we have we have so many to open
is she crying
are there's Tears In Her Eyes
looks like she's crying don't cry oh
pretty it's so pretty yay
we saw a new artwork yeah
happy tears
so cute so pretty
under the beautiful blossoming cherry
blossom trees last pack
okay
here we go
at with the ball what
yeah
who is Gemma my manager are you new here
can my my beloved manager
hmm who will do anything for me
literally like buying me a swimsuit
[Laughter]
[Music]
I just snorted when I laughed
really smart
can we oh my God
it feels so weird to snort
[Laughter]
um
thank you thank you
box four done oh we're speed running
this now
card pack opening speed run
oh oh wow
honestly it was bgm I could imagine a
card game anime
like totally when they're like getting
down
throwing those cards at each other and
like a really really enthusiastic
stream battle
oh box five now right oh so we're
already in past the half points halfway
through past it
five out of eight oh yeah
I sum it
sum it up yeah like that I can imagine
just like the you you're fighting your
biggest rival right now
and your life depends on winning this
battle
because card games are serious business
that's that's more like Pokemon as if I
was a Pokemon
it's called standing and wise I just
read what Chad said
oh turn
[Music]
again Chloe
are these cards always climax cards of
the first ones
just like it
[Music]
okay first pack
signed one in this box I'm telling you
wait how high are the chances like
realistically
in eight boxes
should there be a signed one
[Music]
oh cute Canada
I should get at least one
at least if that was shiny again Louis
if one in a case that's very low you
know
I got one SP in my food
in eight bucks there's a high chance but
it could be zero depending on where you
bought them oh well I mean I didn't
really buy them
one in like anything gone for eight
bucks before never pull the sign cut
oh one in 18 boxes for SSP sign five out
of 18 boxes okay well I feel like people
are giving me different
uh information here
a master case guarantees one SSP in 36
boxes one case is 18 bucks or whatever
it's less than half a 20 aha
card games on motorcycles are the best
what
I am
I feel like
you know there's certain cards that just
happened to appear way more often than
others
um
and that's on purpose
maybe luck
[Music]
and oh is that another old meme
Ambassador tinfoil hat Woman calling a
signed Bloomer in this box now I want to
[Music]
would be funny any sign card would be
hype
oh much
yes that is much December yes
or cucumbers super sampai
called always ask them to sign into the
person yeah right but you know that's
like me just using my my position to my
personal advantage
I could sure but
[Music]
if it comes out of one of these packs
that's way more hype right
then assign your own card yeah I saw
she's never gonna sell it though there's
no way she's allowed to do that oh only
that's a first because I think we had a
different one
before
um
at this point we have everyone in shiny
at least so far
[Music]
is anyone keeping track
could we not have yet not everyone
who are we missing
you don't remember I mean just like just
our our cards we maybe have everyone
shiny earphones oh no shiny outfit okay
it will come now trust me
I will summon it
[Music]
ah
um
[Music]
I can do it better I can do better
if I practice a bit it gets better hmm
what if you get a sand kiwawa card well
I already I have one like we we got all
the kiwawa cards separately
just in case we don't pull my own cards
[Music]
again okay that's the third one of that
type I've been give me a different one
give me a different illustration come on
come on
I want different
illustration all right oh my God I'm
being spammed with
what it is
year of the rabbit after all
yeah it's a lot of
the car
can I make a no saggy deck of rabbit's
Army
only pecora cards
or maybe an usaken deck
s deck
cards of only members of us
yeah
and now shiny goobity bomb
that goes in there
I'm actually
oh
coyote
[Music]
mm-hmm oh [\h__\h] was so fast
oh
one two three four five six one two
three four five six seven
this is number eight Maybe
yes
ah
[Music]
um
some Japanese commenter wrote that
people have only seen one signed card of
each member so far
like online I guess
so
it's like super super rare
well you gotta buy a lot huh all right
here are some more second half
rare as it should be yeah otherwise it
wouldn't be so special thanks for the
pinky
[Music]
okay thank God
foreign
[Music]
please
any foil climax is actually kind of
weird not Danny uh yeah no I don't think
so that would be Sr right I think I
would remember one
don't think we had one yet that's
that would be nice too I guess
um
sideways
special foil up oh wait whoa whoa whoa
Sr of solar Senpai wow look at that RGB
rainbow wow my God
let's go
crazy
shiny Mommy
Whammy
s
Ina also comes out very often oh my God
is there even though ever a climax qawwa
I haven't seen the climax Huawei yet
does it not exist
only specific types right not everybody
has a climax card I suppose
[Music]
there isn't oh
oh what's that ah wait was there one in
the first one like
um was it the the hookah art of me in
that field of the flowers
I feel like that those are sideways are
so it could have been a climax card
oh shiny always
Cali has only one card oh the climax one
that's besides the normal standing pose
is that her only other card
hmm
ah
name
my way now I miss waiting I want to go
on a vacation again with Wayne
I just missed the Maldives that was so
good I want to go there again oh
Wayne
I was just thinking about it yesterday
about our Maldives location
oh
Bali calling yeah I guess that would be
the the quickest because she can get
there quickly hmm
I guess the money
maybe I'll go tomorrow tomorrow
you have duties over tomorrow is my day
off right
oh
again wife
and bounce I like this artwork too
ah good stuff beautiful cards Isn't it
nice you can play like a card game
with the one big fandom you have as your
hobby whole life
isn't that nice that that's a
possibility
true so true hang in there General fight
don't fight though we're getting there
we go go go oh smug
I can imagine oh that's a purse
I haven't seen that one yet in shiny
hmm
accurate representation of Jen monsters
she told me she didn't sleep last night
and now in Japan it's like uh
midnight it's past midnight I think
I mean staying up with weird times is
kind of normal for her I think
but you know
oh oh I feel I feel that the spirit the
way she shows us the cards it's like
she's really motivated
make a vacation Jen but she never will
Mommy
alarm mommy alarm oh God
yay
[Music]
we still have a chance guys we can still
get a signed one don't give up
never give up drag her to Valley with
you
I think realistically the maximum
maximum amount of days she could take
off
without brilliant like starting to work
in the middle of the vacation is maybe
two days
maybe not even
she will definitely work in in the
vacation as well
[Laughter]
[Music]
yo that looks really cool with that
effect
whoa even the the shiny thing in the
middle and her glasses
yo
sick Ness
[Music]
RGB glasses yeah gamer
gamer girl
oh and another
[Music]
nice too
one more pack I think for this box oh
and then we move to the sixth sixth
bucks no problem
[Music]
find one here it comes yeah it was
apparently it has to be in this box and
in this uh in this pack because that's
the last
that's the last of the fifth
[Music]
okay
is that it
oh
[Music]
all right
three more boxes guys
science card wasn't in here
[Music]
next one will be it for sure yeah
gotcha right up
is alive
ah
chocolate
no sign card yet um
worst case I'll sign it
too bad no maybe jenma will sign it
Gemma will sign a kiwama card
[Music]
that will go for even more than my own
signature
away
um
[Music]
how's it going
playing so much Minecraft recently
um
so many en members have been playing
Minecraft recently what's going on
I wanna play too but I don't know what
to do
what should I do
but we did set a date
for weather I
managed to get us a date for it
it's happening this month
[Music]
yay
I don't like oh my God pretty
it's an R rummy
yeah I don't like building so much I
wanna do fun stuff
um
all you have to do is log on tell Kyla
what you need him
[Applause]
or
[Music]
okay
I play once and when I played my whole
life deck you've saved my behind so many
times when I played you against my
friend oh kill a lot strong Phoenix deck
let's go
oh [\h__\h] that's bringing in that bgm gave
me a heart attack it sounds like it's
ringing in real life
okay here we go
box six pack seconds second pack
no no that was not a sign Kuda as if I
would scream we were we would be
screaming if that was the SSP goodo
because
pack finish finish finish
here for the membership renewal
oh okay
that would be a thousand US Dollars oh
my God crazy
in super shiny Sr wow I think I think so
why is that just R looks like a star to
me
oh yeah it is
ah I think that's our first Sr Lunas
Senpai hmm
Viva La Patrona thank you I haven't
heard that in a while oh
the two special cards in this pack are
are Luna and Sr Luna from the same
illustration
what a coincidence
coincidence what could it be could it be
no no
reverse cycle okay there's there's no
way that the side card would be in box
six because I don't want it anyway
and I would be really angry if it was in
the six bucks
oh yeah see I'm glad that this is not a
signed card because I don't care about
signed cards I don't want a signed card
like why would anyone want a side card
because that just messes up the
illustration
I can't look at it properly anymore I
don't want it I don't want this one
either because it's not signed no no no
no no
oh [\h__\h] my my
voice my real intentions went from there
forever
that's not what I was doing no no no I
want that because it is not fine yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I didn't go do a good job there
it's trying to fool myself and and to
censor yeah
while I use confusion it was successful
hmm
now that now the sensor is confused what
the hell does this woman want
does she want a signed card or not like
that I don't want to thank
you this is just right this is just how
it should be
[Music]
um
thank God that wasn't the signed card
otherwise I would be screaming my lungs
out and then I would lose my voice and
then I couldn't stream anymore
right that would be terrible
who would want that
[Music]
um
[\h__\h] it okay I can't play this BG I'm
just ringing does it have the same
effect on you guys that bringing and
[\h__\h] me up why me
how about this one
ah when I say bye nice that's SSR isn't
it
yes oh yeah
[Music]
uh-huh
oh beautiful
I don't know what kind of big Jam do we
still want to listen to your beat guys
or do you want to something else
I mean we're getting to the end here so
heck yeah bye samuta we're a bit hype
you're a bit hot
I wonder if there's Mozart hero Beats
[Music]
smug
oh
where's my own songs
here
[Music]
um
oh yes is that that's just R right yeah
nice our second
um one though that one that one's kind
of rare that one doesn't show up as
often as the others
yeah how about
how about this one here there we go
oh that sounds familiar what is that
from oh
what do you guys think about kiwawa
um imagine Chihuahua had an outfit
inspired by the people night outfits
in that uh
high high leg uh tights uh highlight
Cuts leotard
80s workouts
I feel like that would be [\h__\h]
incredible right right with like fluffy
hair
just like Mama Looney drew it back then
yes yes like workouts and this girl
dance but I'm not sure if I would go
more into a workout direction or in a
disco Direction because we had both for
FIFA nine Tammy bring me underneath that
that's what strobe lights yeah
mmm foreign I think that would be really
really hot and would have a nice theme
because at this point it gets difficult
like what theme I have casual I have
something casual I have something fancy
um I have oh half second half
[Music]
I love kimono
pajamas yeah yeah
yeah
pajamas also
something I I would want but maybe
I don't know
I mean I have casual outfit already so
that's pajama and Casual kind of close I
feel
[Music]
Mommy
I think about it oh
but
I know I wanna know what you guys want
because then I can decide better as well
because I'm I'm not sure what to do for
the next one ah
I did for 2020 free
I'm thinking I'm thinking but personally
I feel like the favorite night inspired
outfit would be genius
um
yeah I guess that could also be cute
pajamas school girl people not
[Music]
um
jrpg inspired outfit would be perfect
ah soda sniff
one more leaning to the part-time
Warrior thing maybe ah that would be
great too wow
boom
armor a lot of people saying that to
cheerleader honestly you could put
cheerleading pom-poms on top of the
fever nights outfits
I feel like that would work too
cute
racing suit oh
[\h__\h] no one's done that before Oh
is that it says oh our first uh s r
climax
[Music]
cute I thought she was like pulling out
a signed card because she was extra slow
yay looks cool
now
[Music]
what what are you saying why are you
saying no signed card in this box rip
don't don't already make decisions oh
cute
okay
you get free SRS per box oh
this
and we already had the three SRS in this
box and I can't have
free SRS and one SSP
oh okay well
whatever real continually
we have two more boxes
[Music]
unless there's a crazy Factory error
boxing
me
[Music]
hey I was thinking a little bit about
the business suit one like you know kind
of for whole talk but
[Music]
um
with the pacing of whole talk I don't
know
I feel like
I could use it also for like sponsored
streams and so on but I think I I want
to prioritize other ideas more than I I
find cuter
more prettier
hmm
and I have a Blazer on my dental outfit
so
yeah maybe that's enough
um I could always like if it's just a
Blazer I could eventually request it as
an accessory maybe to an existing outfit
like this one maybe I could add a Blazer
that covers the whole blouse
maybe oh shiny rat this one is a first
in shiny maybe maybe
then we don't have to have a whole
outfit on it and most of the time I only
show my upper body anyway so yeah it's
just a blazer
then yeah
oh
second one of this one really
summer dress oh yeah but I don't think I
think I can Kindle and this outfit are
already summer themed so like I don't
think I would spend another slot of an
outfit for that well now I'm having a
deja vu
I'm having a big Deja Vu now damn have
we talked about this before like this
also saying
more efficient
window clumps winter clothes will be so
nice but what if there's lots of delays
and it doesn't even get released in
winter season
[Music]
releasing winter outfit in summer 2024.
what are you doing are
thank you
[Music]
last winter in Australia I guess so okay
I guess it's winter somewhere yeah but
your guys is winter isn't even a real
winter is there any snow I don't think
so
can you really call that winter that's
more like uh autumn
facts french fries
swags two bags strings bugs strange box
James box James boxes
where and you're losing your way to take
a chance and dance and I'm just gonna
sing until I get a signed card
s
wow
[Music]
is that still the only
huh
[Music]
[Applause]
hey
um
[Music]
just go your own way
ah movies would be uh
the other one is the climax one huh the
the sideways one
okay that's what we're looking for
of your hair and happy show me what
you're making you're gonna be okay
[Music]
everybody
said fine that's the first yay haven't
seen that one yet it's so cute it's so
pretty come On Monkey Tennessee I was
not focusing man can't focus there we go
what is that that's an Sr I think
looks like us are at the bottom oh
[Music]
yeah
what RR
what do you mean r uh what the [\h__\h] is
an RR why why have we not talked about
rr's yet
[Music]
what's an RR is it r r s r SSR a double
rare
five r r in each box
whatever
did I miss some IRS so far what other
card was in our iron
[Music]
less rare than an Sr but rare rarer than
are obviously okay
[Music]
oh wow
oh
is that our our two no way it is
birthday one is also an IR
[Music]
okay
box number seven we're almost there Jen
Mommy let's go
[Music]
pirate Chihuahua
what's this pirate language
climax
oh the climax shiny ones are RR
oh
so the the football stands by climax one
was an RR
oh
you're an idol too
aren't we having an aisle meeting right
now aren't we talking now
okay
actually I also kind of feel
but I'm I'm waiting I'm gonna wait
unless if I go at the same time we're
really gonna
have eating
manager and Idol meaning I mean idle
meanings don't always have to be with
Island Idol they can't be with manager
and Idol because you know that's when
the the real work gets done as when you
discuss the most important things y'all
hmm
yeah what she's doing right now is a
manager meeting
no you can't have a heart now she's in
an idol meeting don't you see it
I am
[Music]
guys what kind of stream would you 100
come to
that you would never want to miss
that I can tease you with to come
all of them any
ASMR
oh that's art Stream karaoke
[Music]
interesting oh I never did that before
maybe I'll do that
soon bathtub
yeah
tangent stream idle stream dance stream
I mean you won't see anything you just
hear it acoustically
[Music]
never be your friends
oh wow
[Music]
yeah yeah okay box number seven oh
[Applause]
yay we're so close
ah
Magic the Gathering stream
oh there are eight boxes yes seven out
of eight we're at that now and the first
card is
ha it's a cold cold pizza net card can
the first one also be in rrr
can only be the normal ones
what to do oh
more Sims 4 streams
meant more like
um
non-gaming streams but
[Music]
um
those are PR only ah oh
so only decoration huh okay
all right it's all
it's over can we finish this oh shiny
shiny shiny Cali
feel like
15 more minutes until three hours we can
do it
we can do it maybe giddy giddy but
yeah shiny India
yo lots of whole life English
representation here
[Music]
I am
okay
you never did an ASM live stream I would
love the rain aboard to make a comeback
up what ASMR with keyboard you mean
I don't even have an ASMR microphone
that would pick up such sounds well
I was trying to get a ASMR collab going
in Japan but
time schedules didn't work out maybe
next time when I go to Japan I was gonna
do one with no other sample you know but
the schedule didn't work out
um
possibly next time
I mean I would feel really
um
weird about it but
if I ever get an ASMR microphone I will
use it to get some cat sounds for you
cat with the occasional Chihuahua mixing
and also saying
well really Softly
and I think that's only really enjoyable
for me and not for you guys
cat purring
yeah
oh
okay
although I don't know how long I can
keep my cats
like you know
at one spot
I would have to follow them I need a
portable ASMR microphone
oh
cookies
okay fruit pack done
going your hallway
[Music]
pretty foot microphone cable
cats would not call for it yeah like if
my cats were
um like lab cats
Maybe
but yeah it's difficult to keep them in
one spot for a long time
especially when I'm forcing it like when
I'm not forcing it oh nice for the
custom boy when I'm not forcing it they
they will say you know my bad when we go
to sleep they will stay for a while hmm
stay throughout the whole night actually
but if I want them if I need them to be
in one spot
then they will not
they will not stay
ing cheap and use catnip
even that the catnip effect wears off
pretty fast actually
[Music]
foreign
we didn't have an SSR yet right SSR is
just um it's not just a signed one it's
okay we only had R and S R okay we had
an s s r
I don't think so
SSR ah there's no SSR only SP okay okay
an SSP oh what's SP
there's SP
flat
ah it says
we've opened like like a thousand cards
at this point almost probably well
senpai
oh yes
that was uh you guys said that was a
r r
foreign
[Music]
but I'm happy with that I'm plenty happy
with ads
wait what
did I read the brain
yeah yeah yeah
Forest being 18. okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
you guys enjoy looking at
um
my thighs the whole time by the lines
oh respect
respect the fires
so far kind of bad luck no what do you
wanting I'm lucky I got all my birds I'm
still waiting for a proper mermaid doll
um
she's so stiff in that illustration
that goes without saying but thank you
this is a card pack opening stream yeah
look at the cards and maybe a general
sense it's obviously her debut stream
not card back opening my name is
okay okay okay are we going to
second half soon oh my God thank you for
the list there's so many what the hell
PR promotion that makes sense
[Music]
oh my gosh
ah I'm doubting it I'm doubting it now
oh here we go second half
we have to
um
do some kind of ritual
[Music]
all of this this just came out these are
new cards
I'm shiny eofi also still no shiny
eophie so we're just stand by
Johnny
sacrifice us
I will tonight I'm gonna
um do some roast chicken tonight oh I
never do it yourself
every time
God damn it
Lui Senpai and coyote Senpai I don't
really and don't really say it for kanoi
normally and you don't huh
you're already marinated in my fridge
you're looking beautiful very slimy and
slippery
that was an accident for Chloe
that was just an accident and
protocol
[Music]
shiny
no I feel like you guys roast me more
than I roast you it should be the other
way around though
[Music]
does that sound like her
mother
[Music]
[Laughter]
we have to use a really relaxed calm low
voice not bad maybe I can practice my
okay impression
foreign
[Music]
when when
helped me kiss Wayne
she brought Wayne closer to me
supports it
oh I was down to the seventh box
are you guys gonna get some cards for
yourself better say yes because I'm the
Ambassador we need to make sure to make
it successful
nice nice
I got someone Expo oh lucky oh Sr
clothing
shiny foil protein
I
have some already
nice thank you thank you very much
eat more Chihuahua oh
if it's salt in you then yes yeah you
can buy them online uh eventually
but easier to get in Japan I guess
go next go next
raining for Ian release ah yeah I guess
you want the English writing ah yeah
that's I I actually don't know in August
okay there we go I knew that
as the Ambassador I knew that
in August
wait for August please
good PGM boss thank you that is my own
music it's Sparks streams box
macholi
look at that huge fat stack of shiny
cards my God
so many
whoa whoa whoa
oh my God
that's a lot of cards
I would say we got lucky and we just
need you one signed card one one is it
too much to ask
[Music]
I'll tell them Ambassador Kiana and
jenma no
this is Jen was sent to me okay okay
thank you they must know
[Music]
[Applause]
I mean
[Music]
to be honest I'm getting baited every
time
something special is happening
[Music]
[Applause]
oh second to last oh my God
[Music]
one
I have a boom
heart challenge of time guys
let's go reminded to everyone who's
going to animate Boston to bring a long
lengthy narrow towel
actually not too long like middle length
but narrow
[Music]
s
yeah wear a scarf scarf last one
and then one more box
es
[Music]
okay this took us 15 minutes this box
took us 15 minutes
that challenge is my favorite song of
yours thank you
shake shake why don't you shake it
waiting
[Music]
what
honey
[Music]
hands oh she can't maybe she's just
struggling to take them apart
honey
[Music]
no we're not getting a sign yet shall we
nah
[Music]
wow
we're getting a heart attack
[Music]
oh
wow
what what what what what what what what
what
you said
this question is probably cutting off
all my screaming for
foreign
[Music]
closer please
okay
that's SP probably because it's not an
illustration one right okay
all right
[Music]
older girl yeah
yeah
yay I got the screenshot now I write a
minute
[Music]
energy
oh my God
[Applause]
do we even have to open the last box yes
we have because we have to see if we get
another mermaid
five for for Jen Mom sorry but but
oh my God
I can't believe we got an energy
oh my God oh my God what the [\h__\h]
it's a spinner inboxite is that still
like logistically possible
is that Logistics I mean it should be
right it could be it could be unlikely
but it could be
oh or just another SP oh
I'm losing hope guys I didn't believe it
would happen that's why it happened no
this is
[Music]
so pretty
oh
hello
Nancy was also like one of the first or
the first shiny card that I got today I
think
I think because I was like oh my god
orange luck what the [\h__\h]
right
she won
why now she's my first signed cars
blood out I summon you my queen you mean
yeah please
I wouldn't call her blood Aldo
Mommy
and I will get a side Kiana card because
you know
last
last box let's go
let's go
okay we're ready
I need a better move my card
want to be a signed Calicut oh I'm happy
with whatever oh
[Music]
here we go here we go
bye
Let's see we have 16 more packs there is
a chance
there could be
there's a chance for a very special
special
signed card still that I still believe I
still believe because now I was my all
my hopes and dreams have been fulfilled
but I will not give up yet
[Music]
yeah I think it's the hard challenge of
India
this is a good sign it starts with the
koala that is a good good sign our first
card to Wawa
that must mean something it's Destiny
oh
yeah
never okay we may not be getting a
signed okayo card but we're getting a
lot of shiny okay cards for General
oh
um
[Music]
yeah that's the guitar solo
true
there's no one else in this world that I
would trade for you
that's okay
[Music]
honey is there something
huh
no
okay okay we are waiting for that we
didn't have a shiny EOP yet in the eight
box we finally get a shiny UFC
all right all right all right I was
getting like scared for a moment how how
could you
give me give me some Shivers there
full Sunny okay so yeah now we have
everybody in Chinese one way or another
[Music]
um okay okay
oh
[Music]
we also have a climax can have that sun
yeah yeah that can also be stunned yeah
um
another one for the shiny stack Mommy
you had one job you had the job to be
shiny
booms
need a shiny owl
please
[Music]
oh
not nothing money
oh an S wait what was that r r r r no r
r
I don't even know anymore
okay yeah
climax
climax car hey
is a pirate
RR is the key
yeah that was the first two
first time we got that one the climax
cards I haven't seen many shiny ones hmm
let's go
[Music]
okay okay
that was the fourth pack
one two three
r r are more rare they feel more rare
yeah
what if you play Ain't No start oh yeah
I should play ain't no stars
when I only have to instrumental for it
now
[Music]
foreign
did you guys already watched the Super
Mario movie it's out now isn't it
I think
today since today
not yet not yet not yet not yet but it's
out but now I think
[Music]
tonight watching it tonight oh I want to
watch it soon too so I can talk with you
guys about it
um
I don't know if I should watch it in
English or in German because what I
heard from the German dub so far it
sounds pretty good
maybe I should watch both
because when I looked at like uh Cinema
um
like
uh you know different they have for
every time they have different like this
is 3D this and that pretty but this is
this has this and that and oh and s r
one me cute
there's no one else yeah and I saw that
uh in our Cinemas
the the original voices version
only
um
had like one specific type of effects to
it
I I think it was pretty but it didn't
have the other special stuff to it so I
want to watch the OV but also I want to
watch the two more packs
of the first half right
I also want to watch the
German ones with the like most
spectacular I don't even know which one
is the most spectacular because all of
them were a lot of spectacular sounding
versions of it
one of them is the last Sr oh okay okay
last Sr wait if I get an Sr can I still
get a signed one after that
no right eh
because we already had so that's why
there's still what
what that was not an Sr okay that was
just an R I think
[Applause]
I mean well you got one and a really
great one so we should be happy with
that
yeah there's free slots
oh
did you put it in the foil oh no no we
have to put it in the foil
is it in the foil
oh for this in the foil does it come in
the foil
oh no
sleep
yeah I mean a sleeve
it isn't a sleeve it's sleeved oh
yeah yeah yeah of course
Ah that's her own sleep you think
okay okay all right all right all right
all right all right
[Music]
okay three sleeves when
I used to get when I still played with
cards like MTG used to get cute sleeves
and then later
um I got really really cute sleeves for
um we could also cards
I got really really pretty once
from actually also the slaves were also
from wikoroso I think
all cards of all card games usually the
same size though
if yes if they're like roughly all the
same size and if they fit in a lot of
sleeves
then sleep merch would make sense no no
well then then it doesn't make sense
because how do you know what size we
should make it
[Music]
um
no
hmm
MTG size and Yu-Gi-Oh size basically oh
[Music]
oh oh
Vanguard yuvio are all Japanese mini
size cards everything else is standard
size oh
those cards are smaller huh well but
then but then I I would go for the
non-vanguard non-u-gi-oh size because
that sounds like the other card games
all roughly have the same size than
last half of pack let's go
but I don't know if I would do it as
like a birthday or anniversary merch
because
because this many non-card players
it should be like a official Ambassador
merch every Ambassador gets their own
card sleeves Hello by Sprouts mostly
MOSI Ambassador takanasikiara can we get
some like Ambassador only merchandise
going here like yeah I mean card sleeves
would make so much sense don't you think
please
[Music]
jenma is listening so write that down
write that down
just kidding it was just just but I mean
why not
oh
[Music]
I mean it doesn't even only have to be
ambassadors
can be all of us sleeps for every member
in a whole life oh man
um
just kidding unless unless
I have the Wawa deck box and card please
what from where
whole life secret layer cut was dead
[Music]
thank you
thank you thank you
awesome mate wow the efforts the
dedication
respected
Elena Elena always get the keys
[Music]
she needs kisses
I thought today would be a short stream
so much for a short swim Chihuahua so
much for that
we're already over three hours I mean
for me that's a short stream for others
that's a long stream
it's our Luna Senpai oh she looks very
very
determined in that one
oh
um
[Music]
energy too
oh it's a tiny one
um
not an Sr though right we didn't get an
another Sr yet right right
I mean Isis are
SSR wait no wait we did
oh [\h__\h] we did didn't we the Luna one
was one
[Music]
because we already got one we already
got to find one but mommy come
no not Sr that would be an uh oh yeah an
R I want an r r mermaid
oh
come on come on
[Music]
doesn't look good look at those whole
totally cards and then there's like four
Illustrated ones and one
cardboard Saucy sassy sassy Baka card
[Music]
I can't handle it
ah I'm gonna move
no no I want now please
really
I'm going to more
[Music]
I also need to go to I know meeting
oh yeah
he's so close
[Music]
and then I'm gonna cook some chicken
I'll come bake or grill some chicken
um
[Music]
shiny Chloe
come on
what is that
I'm fine
there's no one else in this world that I
would trade for you except a shiny mume
are our cards
[Music]
trade offer
foreign
[Music]
yay ah
ponya okay okay okay I'm sweating no
[Music]
[Applause]
no
please please please
Jenna can you hold this pack in both of
your hands
and like as you're praying in the other
hand yes yes like this and then now now
warm it up warm it up please
no we're praying first yes now rabbit
rabbit like you're warming it up yes
[Laughter]
okay okay that should do it that should
do it
come on
I'm hatching it yeah oh
last pack last last one we opened over 1
100 cards
Iris
I am a senpai
so I said bye
legal standby
[Music]
it's not coming it's not coming
it's not coming
Senpai Ash is she keeping the special
class at the end
[Music]
it would be the last one
[Applause]
[Music]
I got a little bit too
into it
I I didn't really care in the beginning
but now I got into it okay well
I wake all the way with a lot of really
nice cards
yo look at that stack wow and can we see
our most special one again please thank
you
oh nice it's signed oh wow wow
whoa Super Special okay last but not
least we want to see the special koala
card please
we got a full collection of all
Chihuahua cards
let's take a look at those
because there is a signed one
[Music]
yeah I can't believe I got an energy
signed one what
how many members are there in whole life
in total with ID and Ian
two men
two men tell us the chances to get
energy can someone calculate me
how high the chances are to get an
entity and not they actually don't even
calculate it out of there it is out of
the number of whole life members when
you have to calculate it out of the uh
like General card SP
SSP cards
yeah okay
all right
[Music]
why aren't they
huh what is that is it the back of the
card is that a sleeve
let's leave what why is there a sleeve
what are those sleeves
hey
I have sleeves
what are these like specially produced
for me or
did they sell these
you're okay
okay they sold those last yeah
oh okay
why are you why are you making this a
mystery genma
okay let's turn them around please top
left please
hmm I Choose You
oh are we playing a game which one is
the signed one
[Music]
I got the side one
oh wow
[Laughter]
pretty wow
I mean with the foil you know it looks a
little bit different I think it looks a
little bit extra shiny
mmm
oh oh
nice wow RGB signature too damn okay
what are the others though that's the
signed one the others are partially
normal ones right
or like yeah okay uh middle bottom row
middle bottom row I Choose You
[Music]
oh it's kiwawa Sr no R I think or wait
Sr Sr
huh I don't know
oh
Sr wow I'm going in the right order
okay okay okay oh nice no that's good oh
top right please
[Music]
oh it's a normal Chihuahua no oh no
that's also sparkly that's uh oh nice
too
okay the that one please yes the the top
one yeah
um
[Music]
such a cool card Ryan okay
oh this one is oh this one is
a Sr oh without signature okay so the
other one was R and this one's Sr I
think I think
same but Sr
cool okay
okay then the others too the other two
are just the default poses probably
uh-huh let's look at uh
wait is there oh there's one more
signature isn't it because they have
signatures for the standing poses too
right oh
left please left
I don't know
everything
ah it wasn't this one I kept it for the
last one okay that's the normal one
and then last but not least another
signature wow
wow okay please put that one next to
nenechi
yeah hello
[Music]
um shiny Chihuahua your shiny nineteen
we look beautiful together
wow we look so orange together beautiful
oh oh yeah okay I'll take a screenshot
of this too
oh what
oh look good looks good
[Music]
ah they're out of the sleep no no oh
okay let's see
okay I got it
[Music]
so true for real for real yeah
thank you again ma for helping thank you
for opening all these packs and yeah
using your precious time for this I
really appreciate it three and a half
hours of your life but you're not even
getting paid for this probably I will
invite you to some
next time okay
if you want
that's something else so good or do you
want a spicy curry
[Laughter]
oh yeah so yeah okay okay okay we'll go
for that
yay thank you guys for watching it took
a little bit longer than I thought so
I'll end it here and tomorrow's my day
off but you know let's say goodbye to
Grandma who's trying to trick us with a
okay sign oh oh gotcha I gotcha I
turn on
ah thank you thank you guys for watching
uh please maybe get some cards of your
own by sprouts get yourself a dick and
then trim your deck and hopefully you
get some nice kiwawa cards too
um
for uh giving me these cards and I will
continue my duties as the Ambassador
from now on and do my best to learn more
about the game yeah hope you guys
enjoyed it I'll see you soon on Friday
for two streams on Friday
yeah I'll see you there okay and in
German we say hahaha
I'll feed us in wait wait wait
bye bye thank you nice deck bro thank
you
oh nice wave elegant so elegant
she is beauty she is Grace
[Music]
laughs
foreign
[Music]