[Music] I've
been looking for a
place where I can say it's special
[Music]
Why did you choose me?
Your laughter has
stopped
Because you're amazing
[Music] I
feel like I can't lose No matter what,
you'll always be mine  Your voice was ringing inside me.
[Music] I'm
scared. I'm nothing. But I wonder if I can
do it. Let's do it together, but how can you do that? You're singing a
song with a blank look on your face. It's me.
No, let's jump into our world. Will we be able to
meet the feelings of the world? I want to sing, I want to
dance, so that I can laugh as much as I want to say.
[Music] I can
get lost in our world, which has no name. Because I'm with you, things will change.
Like, now.  We
want to have a drink with our expectations
[Music]
I'll sing about your future It's
okay to cry I'll
hug you and go to the world I want to see with you
[Music]