[Music]
do
bye
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
hey
[Applause]
[Music]
but we're finally all here
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
nice to meet you
yeah second up is me i i am the
first real real bird actually in the
whole life uh
[Music]
[Applause]
am phoenix not chicken phoenix
[Music]
look at look at my guarding phone
picture it looks like a phoenix doesn't
it
[Music]
yes i'm raining from hollow life
indonesia generation
i am peafowl not turkey
[Applause]
and after that mummy joined me please
introduce yourselves hello i'm nanashi
mummy from the second generation of
hololive english
i am an owl not a towel
that's a real one
yeah
it's not new never happened i'm not a
towel
foreign
[Laughter]
m
[Music]
new member nice to meet you
[Applause]
[Music]
what what kind of bird
hook
exactly really cool
foreign
[Music]
um
oh
beautiful
[Laughter]
so guys
today we are here with these horatoni
members and by the way if if you have
not seen it
[Music]
i requested for this sake
master
yeah thank you
for putting it on the screen i got it
because i got it it felt like ah we were
such a cute lovely group we need
something to connect one another
[Music]
thank you
the steps on the bottom so cute right
yeah it's so cute
don't leave it hey
i also think so um
be no problem of course
you better say my english no problem
bishop
international very good it's good
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah yes
[Laughter]
i think we should start with normal
normal mode but we can try other modes
too later maybe okay okay
and just a reminder uh the prompts
please write in english
[Music]
whatever let's just go with the basics
okay okay
i i don't have i have a mouse oh oh
i didn't need i i mean myself there okay
uh i have a mouse
i'm tired
um
how about
we
okay
oh
let's see how do i
let's see
how do i draw this oh i've never tried
drawing stuff like this before um
all right
we got the mouse here
sorry guys it might be pretty focused
it's a lot harder with the mouse i
forgot the nose
let's see can i
there all right
all right
how much time do we have
uh
me
yes me
okay
we're in my
feathers and a ponytail
all right uh i'll give myself half the
time to do this
all right
oh we're about to okay okay okay so
one
and that's the ask me
and we're gonna do
wait that's two star one d button yes
okay
she's longer lips than me
all right
louie i need to look at a picture oh
she's right there perfect
all right got the wings
and
here hair
let's see
like so her hair
cute
oh you might need some color though oh
there's not much time
oh i gotta go faster when i do this okay
we gotta do a heart
oh we're running out of time some brown
oh gosh okay
ah
okay it's a brown brown brown brown
brown that's me
oh perfect color perfect flamingo color
here all right
that's good good enough right
you tell your heart in a bit
make it look more like a heart all right
it needs a tablet when you have a mouth
i forgot her nose that's chilly it's
fine she doesn't need it um
oh she needs our lips
maybe i shouldn't have put myself in the
prompt i look um
um
confused
like so you think they'll get the hint
if i do this is it an even amount one
two three four five six seven eight nine
one two three four five six seven eight
wait was it no it's eight eight eight
okay not nine okay
is that the loading rule nice all right
we may confuse
oh i could have put loading right
floating
that's better
oh let's already go to ocean that's what
i'm guessing ocean all right here's the
ocean woo ocean here
maybe an island just to clarify it's an
ocean
we gotta work a bit fast here we have
five five of us to draw okay so we got
me
that's me
in the water
ow
okay
uh how do you draw a hawk
hawk here
like like so
in the water all right maybe i can give
her she have her wings up here probably
not but i'll put them there
that's louie
let's see subaru
is there gray here he goes
see if i can remember how i draw this
and then
here
oh what does her hat look like again oh
gosh i forgot her hat
is it yellow or blue
no red and blue oh gosh i forgot this is
the last
chicken
in the ocean in the ocean see i'm not
sure i'm cursed i'm drawing keystone
because of my mouse okay
uh schiada
her earrings here
there's
uh
i've drawn i've drawn her as a peacock
before let's see
we got there
there oh gosh it's so cute and we're not
drowning by the way we are simply
swimming this is how birds swim
blood in the water
in the water give her more wings because
he
more wings
so cute
that's adorable
all right
what if they meant ocean right
not drowning no everyone is fine and
safe
oh my gosh
oh tardy what are we doing
dance dance
[Laughter]
oh it's awesome
all right
um i'm gonna do try my best here it's a
lot of people to draw things karaoke
karaoke party okay maybe that's more but
dancing will be funny but you guys are
right it's probably karaoke
probably karaoke
hello
we need more more difficult prompts next
time
a lot of birds a lot of birds
yeah man
that's okay that's no problem um let's
look at it together
okay okay okay okay
okay
let's go we start with hollow birds down
hey
i'm saving i saved it
let's go get me next one from molina
oh
my god
[Music]
actually um before before the stream
started
me and reyna told the suburbs and the
others that we're going to the maldives
to make them yeah jealous
yeah and they were very excited to join
so for example i want to come too right
yes
dynamic title i surprised this
christian
[Music]
[Laughter]
everybody is uh there even though the
one that subado drew one is missing so
good
you added me again
[Music]
[Applause]
yes
you guys all know the mermaid loading
icon the membership
[Music]
it's you
[Laughter]
wow
[Music]
mucho
okay
um
[Music]
let's see
i i have no prompt ideas let's dip
something that's difficult uh i don't
want to put myself
how about
um
chat help i know i just said i wouldn't
listen to you ever again
sorry i wrote the first thing i saw
lately putting a sun milk on sun milk
sunscreen wait
okay
ah
we don't have much time oh gosh oh gosh
we don't have much time okay
um
how do i clarify who this is okay uh
well yeah i gotta hurry i gotta hurry uh
uh
how do i show that it's sun milk
sun milk that's sun milk okay
a swimsuit
that's a swimsuit right okay um
there's not much time
oh like oh gosh okay
[Music]
yeah that's weird enough right
how'd you do so fast wait what is it
though
chicken
what is she holding oh gosh
it's a pink bucket it's probably we're
not doing it
chicken
chicken holder duck
very cute
not paint not paint can
all right hold our balloon boy
okay
i'm a time for this
will i get demonetized
i gotta work fast oh i gotta work fast
okay five
we'll sign the rules
after wait no that's that's weird unless
no okay um
all right now we gotta give them hair
uh i say this is kiara it just feels
right
uh this one is a day
just just just feels right
um
what's that is everything on i think
it's a side okay um
this one's me
dude
i don't know what i'm very tall okay
we have flap flaps here
all right
bird eats bird world
oh my god
what do these look like
[\h__\h] oh gosh this goes by really fast
doesn't it
okay
that was so fast
yeah it's super fast
yeah
so many people use holy tony so i always
have to draw draw five people yeah
i know
sit on the beach
[Laughter]
i like this one nice elena has a nice
booty
on that picture the first thing i do
[Music]
[Applause]
so cute
you can hold that
[Laughter]
quiet
[Music]
oh
demonetized
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
nice interpretation nice nice night nice
it is a bird eats bird well
i like it
pac-man in a way
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
young
that's a good misunderstanding yeah
nice and nice
the rounds are so short because we are
only so few people
should we
play a different round a different mode
what is it what are we doing it's a
i just draw whatever and they have to
replicate it is that it
hmm
wait we have a lot of time
oh this is so difficult with the mouse
wait i wanna undo everything ah
oh gosh
there we go all right um
i wish i had my drawing tablet
it's a lot of time we have what if i
look up a reference
[Music]
oh wait go away um
i'm gonna lose all my time looking up a
reference
all right
let's see
what can we what can we oh my gosh all
right
i'm gonna be kind of focused
when i get it done
yeah
pretty
mm-hmm
sorry i'm gonna be very focused i think
well that doesn't look right though ah
oh so bad
it's very bad
i try my best
just gotta try your best and if you
don't succeed you're a failure
um
he changed oh you can change the color
that's kind of a pain in the butt for
them though isn't it
sorry
[Music]
oh
gosh
no they had these
let's see how much time we're halfway i
can't see chat by the way
i got some
teeth
is there a color selection tool aha
there is
that's such a pain in the butt though
if they're not gonna have as much time
like i did a hat and you look up super
just hat
let's go to the hat
that's not her hat
hold on
there it is all right all right
ah
let's do like
this is
there
it's
white here
got
the snap thingy here
and it's kind of blue it's more like
yes blue i guess like that okay that's
how that looks okay
uh
this isn't that creepy
this is a bit
see this is something that looks like
it's supposed to be creepy but it's not
it lost its soul i think
no soul in this
is this disrespectful
how it might not even be solo dude
actually this is a goose it's not even a
duck this is a goose that took souvenirs
hat
that's too edgy
let's see all right how about saliva
you get kind of cute
cute
ta-da
looks weird here
maybe like maybe there should be food
what's the strawberry strawberry it's
the fastest thing we can do
strawberry
mmm
yummy
csi has the heart too strawberry
here we go
all right remember oh we have to
memorize it
okay who's where
okay
[Music]
me
louie
everyone does peace sign okay okay
all right so
senpai
oh wait now the eyes were
hold on we can get her a better better
than that we don't have much time okay
[Music]
yeah okay first i gotta do everybody all
the time
so how she did
like that
oh gosh okay
yeah
and p sine
p sine
p sine p sine no p sign but i did have a
p sign p sun
sun she made doo doo
okay
mushroom
[Music]
here
wait no it's not the right color
okay
uh i got a picture okay okay okay
okay okay
he's there
blue
all right
oh gosh look at that bee
all right who is that
i can't forget the blush
that's chiata
are you just a random person
she's whispering in the ear
[Music]
airplane and what
airplane bro
do they have
what airplanes look like the windows
okay airplane
[Music]
saw
saw so saw the number
airplane
so
sad
so sorry that's so
my difficult
stressful very stressful stress yes
oh my god
yeah right it was it was very speedy
yeah so speedy
oh my
god let's take a look at
what what it turned out to be
my show
i was not sure what to draw
um
[Laughter]
[Applause]
the biggest problem was subaru senpai's
interpretation that's not right over
anything else
oh
[Music]
beautiful
it just looks like i'm sexually
harassing someone yeah
[Music]
why did you make them sweat because the
asmr was just too much to handle
oh
[Applause]
we need to put that up on the on my fan
art hashtag
yes oh yes
it was from that prom
my previous prom
because it failed
i'll save that one that one is
precious beautiful all right
mushrooms wow
mushroom i
like the mario kart stream reign
i missed something important i'm sorry
mommy left early
i'm sorry sorry
yeah she has something to do
sorry
i'm sorry
[Music]
oh my god
this is this is abstract yeah i'm
stressed
abstract abstract right here
you look at it and you think what do you
what do you see how does it make you
feel depending yeah depending on what
you see you can learn someone's
personality um
[Music]
arizona
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
style but no way she can do that with a
mouse
yeah
i had the time
oh
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
is that a cherry tomato or a strawberry
i was going for it i was going for
strawberry
okay okay okay
[Music]
one more one more one more one more okay
um think about what you want to draw
okay
um
[Music]
okay
what idea
um i can't tell you yet
were you doing knockoff again or what
yeah we're just a knockoff again by my
rant i was very good oh dang it um
and i'm not looking for animation
knock off
right let's see um
okay i was thinking of perhaps a hybrid
of every bird that we are
uh
let's see is there animation wait that's
a knockoff i don't know uh
well first get rid of this
um
okay so
beak
before we have time
eyes
all right
beak eyes we're gonna make it pretty
cute um
let's see what color should it be
maybe uh
subaru's color
looks like a pigeon
maybe we should just make a pigeon no
how can we encoura okay incorporate
louie
we'll give
wings on here
although her wings are more aren't they
more down let me see
they're more down
wings
looks like puppy ears
puppy ear
cute
all right and then uh
shall we give
should we put soup in his head should we
put my
feathers
could possibly do both but
it's everybody's love child um
all right
and then for a dna we can just do the
the p val feathers a little p files
don't have don't worry about it
do
yeah come here yeah yeah yeah
it's a bit
off
the screen that's fine
see if i remember anything about how you
do the feather i don't think i did the
feathers when i
when i drew her before just on her head
so
there should be one here ah no
that was a bit off it's fine
how do we incorporate chaotic can make
it breathe fire
can make it on fire
maybe make it on fire
or her earrings
there and
there on fire
all right
there
um
[Music]
could do the earrings if we have the
time
[Music]
nah
good enough
i feel bad if i had my tablet i could do
so much more but my tablet is not
working
see if i wasn't streaming i'd be on my
ipad but everyone was streaming so i was
like oh i'll stream too
it's pretty cute
pretty cute
still maybe
oh
no blushy
have time for the hat maybe a little hat
mini hat
oh mini hat real quick
real quick mini hat
uh oh
a little one
that's pretty cute
all right
not my best work but i think the concept
is cute
this is the final boss
you face the final boss here
this is it this is her
and you dare
you dare lay a hand on her
we're learning
the alphabet
very okay
all right um that shouldn't be too hard
let's see
oh gosh
uh no don't have much time okay
she point to
the chalkboard
chalkboard here
[Music]
oh gosh i'm spending i'm putting too
much focus on the wrong things
and then there's me
here
what was the order i don't remember the
order was it me i think it was in suburu
here
and then it was what
[Music]
it's like a puppy cute oh gosh she has
no legs
wait these are very similar
verb oh why are they so similar
did i
were they supposed to be the same thing
did i miss something here
gosh i need to hurry okay this time kiot
is teaching everybody
[Music]
chalkboard
blurb
okay
[Music]
oh gosh
one two three four
desk desk
pop
oh
yummy
toast
delicious
oh gosh
delicious toast i have a salad was a
sailor uniform oh so cute
yummy
ah okay
what's up
ah
i don't know who this is
i don't know what this was
really like hold shaking
hands that's those are hands um
okay
oh nice snappy
but everyone did their best i'm sure
power
[Music]
uh
[Applause]
[Laughter]
apparently in order to be a bird you
have to know the abc hmm
[Music]
maybe someone can recreate this and make
it into a proper fan art i want to see
it
[Music]
again yes of course i'm always thinking
about you
oh
my god
wait
wait who's that
i think we turned into survivor senpai
because of black hair
becomes
um i can do an art stream where i just
uh ship all the hollow birds
draw them in spicy scenarios let's go
let's go
that's not been used enough make use of
it yeah yeah spicy
spicy steak
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
face scary face when i panicked
because late
late
portray yourself in a cute way but no
you're the one who portrays yourself in
the terrifying way the most
when toast isn't hungry
[Music]
same
thing
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
please take a look at how
sampa is simple art um with even less
time i drew a bit more complicated
and i added the earring
oh yeah
[Laughter]
oh
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh yeah
nicey
[Music]
okay
okay what does if turd duncan is turkey
duck and chicken what is
turducken with hawk and owl uh
you mean flamingo
[Laughter]
oh
it's like a dating app for
i love you guys do you want to try
animation
sure
no
[Music]
oh god what do i make uh
is there no fill in but there's no fill
button excuse me i would i wanted to
fill this
like
get out of here guard dick phone
what
okay never mind oh
gosh what do i do what do i do what do i
do chat you have ideas chat do you have
ideas what do i do what do i do what do
i do
[Music]
now
all right
i don't know what i'm doing
a lot of birdies
all the birdies
all right
maybe instead
of this i do
actual beak
like so
this is not very good i'm sorry
we have big wing
oh this is not good i hope they have
better ideas than mine
just flying together
flying together
hmm
add butt no
uh oh
how much time do we have do we get the
same amount of time
here we'll have the
supposed to be animated so slightly left
up here what was the color of that sheet
was it this one
was it this is this show oh i think it
was was it no
this one
i think it was this one
do you have the same amount of time
i feel like that's kind of important
do you know okay only not even halfway
okay okay
good
oh good
see your heart
ah
[Music]
like so
sorry i gotta focus just a bit
chicken
oh this is too fat too not enough frames
per second with this animation here
of course the sweat
hmm
this might not be very good for
animation
right now
hands go up
wait
ah we
hand up
up
up here sorry guys i'm a bit quiet i
gotta focus
here here
oh you know maybe she should be more
it
she
says and
here oh no
there
may be hair bounce a little bit too
bouncy hair
she like this actually oh
um
she's confused
what's happening
she's going through the motions really
it happens to us all
let's see
eyebrows
oops
the eyebrows go up like huh
[Music]
all right
like so
i think we're good
is there anything i'm missing
no
all good
okay
ready
uh do i how much do i leave for the next
person there's one more right
i think there's one more
after this one right
this isn't the final
oh it's hard to ah
hard to
replicate
mouse
mouse makes it difficult
i can just imagine the sounds all right
uh
oh is this black i think it's black
actually
here
and
[Music]
got the blue
oh this all right
um
hair here
hurry up a bit
here
can't forget the heart to make the
hearts maybe move up a little bit
you know
well i'm running out of time already all
right ah wait those didn't move up
i care too much about the dumbest things
all right uh
there
wait
oh gosh all right brown eye
the blush the blush
oh i can't forget the blush
this is okay
something i feel like there's so much
missing
i'm about to tickle her nose
what on earth is happening here is that
a computer
what wait i'm so lost of what this is
what wait
seriously this is the last one
maybe cashier
she a cashier maybe
oh okay i think i understand
angry why is she angry though
she has a mushroom going overhead
what's this
what
then here everyone use the same colors
where did i draw again i remember
um
i don't know what all this is but
now i think that's too much um
ah
real chicken
chicken meat what
this
i'm panicking of it
all chicken
and there's drool
here oopsie
drooling
uh
i don't know i don't know what it is
i don't know is this enough
i don't think i added much more to these
drawings to be honest
yeah i died on time i'm done
i'm not sure what happened but
all right
okay
hello hello
hello
some interesting things going
[Applause]
[Music]
what's going on why is everyone drawing
such sensitive scenes huh sensitive
which one are we talking about what are
we talking about
[Laughter]
i think i think it's enough it's a lot
it's not
oh
hi
let's take a look
oh this is you you're so happy dance did
you get my idea
oh my god
oh you guys added oh
oh
and then music was playing so i wanted
to start dancing dancing
[Music]
okay i see i see ice cream
okay
i thought it was someone else's
[Laughter]
[Music]
this looks great in animation it does
crazy nice
like i got closer too yeah and the in
the end it turned into a little snake
yeah yeah
yeah
it's like what
what what is that
but it's not i mean it's
ah
okay
[Laughter]
exploding
[Music]
yeah oh my gosh drawing was very
important nina thank you for that yeah
yes you're welcome at your services
[Music]
i think
i
eating louise skin uh
foreign
[Laughter]
why are
thanks
[Music]
[Applause]
this is the best animation
very delicious did we taste do we taste
good
so sweet
[Music]
i want to try
uh
wait uh do we still have oh do we still
have time can we do one more animation
one more sure last last okay
i eat a lot eat a lot
[Music]
all right
i'm hungry
okay hungry
hungry
maybe afterwards you can have breakfast
mommy or you're gonna go back to sleep
i'll do both or i'll just eat more of
you guys
okay
i'll give you some substitutes from kfp
don't eat toto today eat kfp okay
[Music]
oh god what do i do now oh what do i do
now
um
i have an idea
i don't know if anyone will really
get it uh should it be though i don't
want to do myself um
let's do
i
don't like the watermark
all right
pringles
[Music]
my stomach is actually grumbling i will
eat breakfast after this
see
i want her okay it's the this is the
hope of what will happen she will
rise
rise rid of this watermark
get out of here watermark
i have the time
whoa she rise to maybe with the sun
she's been drawing suns a lot
hmm
let's see what should she ah
maybe like
what
weird maybe since it's animated
doesn't want you to
she rise with the sun
rise of the sun
so that is senpai
like so
i hope that's okay
oh my stomach is grumbling hold on
what i need my coffee wait what is this
is that a lollipop is that a spoon
oh i'm not sure what this is
um
look at this bee
oh it's a mirror how do you guys know
that uh what's this though
mirror
let's see
like that
um
then maybe
i'm
not sure what it is i don't know
i'm not sure how to i'm really bad at
advancing the story chiara was really
good at it
lifting her arm maybe
wait one two three four five okay uh
i'm gonna hope it's a mirror
how to mirrors work like that is that a
mirror okay i don't know what this is
i'm going to assume it's a plate
and uh i'm going to put kiara back there
um
and maybe it will just actually we won't
clarify if it's chiara or not it could
be any of us
it is a wing
i did her hair right oh here
here
like that
is that okay
oh i'm not good at this one
all right
hope for the best
hair
let me have a piece of hair on her
there's a piece of hair on the food
wait whoa okay that weirded me out she's
ordering chicken
okay let's see what can we do okay first
i think i'll make kfp deliver the
chicken for her
that's so cute i think this is kiara's
because of the eyelashes
is it
in here
ordering
i like i like the phone i love that okay
uh
do this blue
oh gosh i hope i have the time to
okay
yeah what no
we gotta meet kfp
show up
it might be too big
it's kfp okay
and they
bring the chicken
[Music]
the box of chicken this is the box of
chicken k
f i don't know how to draw boxes kfp
chicken inside
look at that
oops
louie will be happy too
oh wait she doesn't need to be on the
phone anymore ah wait the story doesn't
make sense just that fast delivery
wow it's that fast everybody
okay uh
okay okay okay
i gotta finish the
wow so fast
that's the chicken wow
super fast
what excellent service
do my stomach
wow
oh so cute
try to make them
move a little bit i don't really know
how to do this though
oops no
dude
i don't know how to dance i don't know
how to animate dancing
that's so cute
just lift your hands up higher
where do you stop
over there
over here
yeah
okay what should i do
maybe i'll go
like this
we know
higher
this is coordinated dancing right
yeah
okay
yes i got the glasses too
maybe i'll put my head down more
yeah head down
i hope this looks okay
well my stomach is not growing i'm
actually so excited i
pre-prepared breakfast last night for
myself actually
i'm gonna have a wrap i made veggie
bacon
and i have wraps obviously and then i uh
have arugula
i'm gonna give i'm just i've been eating
tomato just because i want to feel
healthier um
tomato
um what else did i have i made a
dressing
cheese
i think that's
i think that's it
i forgot the effects here
i hope this
actually looks like dancing
what
swimsuits
um
swimming suits okay
interesting
what did she lose her swimsuit
well she grew another and she grew more
swimsuit
um who is this this is kiara
this is
in it
there a ponytail i see that
all right
she's
what what are you what's this
in a changing room
i'm a little lost just a little bit
not fully lost is that a tomato
she balancing a tomato with blue
leaves
swim
[Music]
suits
they're in a changing room are they in a
store
she's about to fall over
yeah she's gonna fall over maybe that's
what's going on
nothing's fine
[Music]
i swim soon
what
i'm tired
i slept like four hours
better than no sleep
um
well
okay
a bit odd oh she thinks she threw the
tomato
hmm
oh my gosh my stomach i've been thinking
about my my wrap
oh it's gonna be so yummy
so yummy
[Music]
[Laughter]
see what masterpieces we have created
yes please
yeah
let's go
okay okay
shopping shopping for swimsuit uh-huh
yeah come on boy
where will this go
okay
what what turned into person oh
she turned into person she falls
wow
i don't know after eating after eating
the bikini top she becomes a person
and what's falling on the ground why
[Music]
i just wanted to see you dana try on
some cute swimsuits but okay this is
fine
[Laughter]
[Music]
what situation is this
dancing oh um
dancing dancing
joining yeah
i like it thank you
thank you he likes it thank you it's
really good as an animation too good job
[Music]
a little confused
cooking oh yeah
oh
[Laughter]
i didn't understand sorry well my my
implication was that uh comes pushes
away dana and wants the food for herself
i sound like
get me to eat something suspicious
i quit raining
no i i teleport
i can't push
it
i put
looks really nice though the way it goes
up it was supposed to be a single hair
but it's nice how it ended up
oh oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes
getting
bigger
surprise it's me
no happy
yes
okay okay
[Music]
yes
it's tough out there that's why no we
have to we have to
be strong together
well the strongest bird is is me because
i am a phoenix and and i will revive no
matter what
uh-huh
[Music]
that's a different story i cannot say
that one
but you know because the bird eat bird
world you know what we should collab
someday mina
super smash brothers
oh my god
i want to punch punch birds oh
[Music]
did you play super smash brothers before
i have but i'm not good at it
ah
then we're all bad that's good because
and somebody will never play before
yeah yeah oh don't play i am bad
we'll be back together but we'll smash
each other so it's okay yes
you would like to see that in a
different meaning too no
what you're talking about
why aren't we talking i don't know
yeah
yeah okay
um
i'm glad we finally got a collab out of
all of us
[Music]
we're the biggest
group of something i think in
really
maybe maybe we can do more stuff
together but getting all of us together
for this collab was already very
difficult
to get
[Applause]
yes yes yes thank you thank you
everybody for participating
thank you for recognizing
[Music]
[Applause]
you learned some good japanese there and
i said yes thank you
i'm so close to fluent now yes
you're getting closer you're getting
there fighting like you'll fight my
friends
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's simple enough one thing we can
remember that our ending greeting will
be otsu
okay
everybody thank you for watching today
and in holo today we say
three
two
one
[Applause]
[Music]
bye
[Laughter]
[Music]