Hey, hey,
hey, hey, Aqua-chan is cute. I
really like her waiting voice. She's a genius whose singing voice is not good. She
makes me feel glad to be alive. This is the reason for world peace. You
know, I
want to thank Minato and Aqua.  I want to thank you too,
but Aqua-chan is my favorite,
right? Love, love, love.
There's one quiet person in all of this.
Who is that? Ah, a
fairy.  I'm
in trouble because I
look like a fairy. What's good about being a real fairy? So what's good about me
as a person? Well, as a person, you're a fairy. So, like the
fairy incident, I
dressed up like a fairy at a gathering.  That's what I
said. I was saying something like "I'm a fairy today" on LINE, and I
thought I was going crazy, because it's been a while since we all got together.  So
when I got all fired up, I ended up
looking like a fairy, and I sent it to Shi, and
Shio was the one who came at me.What kind of fairy was she?
LOL Oh, she's a fairy.I
thought she had gone crazy.  It's
like a fairy, it's like a fairy.
What are you talking about? I feel like
Aa-senpai is the most
idol-oriented person in Hololive. I
don't know, but she's an idol after all.
Since I don't go to the toilet, everyone
thinks that I shouldn't go to the toilet either. I see. That's
right. Because I can't go, I'm stubborn. My
senior is in a diaper. Hey, I'm not going to go to the
toilet. Hey, I'm not going to go to the bathroom. What's wrong with that? The bathroom is so long, isn't it?  I
don't go to the bathroom because I'm an idol, so I
don't go to the bathroom either, so when I go to the
bathroom, I do it properly,
but only when I'm not streaming.
When I was told that it wasn't being streamed, I
told them I wanted to know about the stream.I
said I'd stream it as well, but I didn't know.What were you
doing?Go back to dreamland.  We
ate biscuits and had a tea party.I
might have written something like, ``What is this, what is this, what is this, this is so
dangerous, it's just
begun, it's just the beginning'', and I
saw it yesterday.  Before I knew it,
the person next to me was really interesting, so of business, business, business, business, business, honeymoon, first business, business, something that I've been wondering about for a while, and in this hour-long broadcast, this person has always been close to me.  Okay,
what's this? I'll let this person go home for a moment.
He's really crazy in the best sense of the word. He's a really
good singer. He's
also really good at acting. What's going on?
In a place like this, Shiso-sensei is quick-witted and
good at games, so it's
okay for me to sit in two rows.Oji-
chan is doing his best.Oji-chan is
doing his best.The teacher who is watching over me
should also watch over me during the battle.
Terda Kaze Acho -sensei
-sensei, a friend of the stuffed animal is a funny head.
Acho, I'm going to the bathroom,
oh yeah, nice toilet, it's fun, is
n't it? It's cute, it's cute, it's Sui-chan [Music] I don't want to imitate my beloved, my stuffed toy. Um, now Toa is going to the toilet.  I'm
going to the bathroom I'm alone with you I'm alone with Tan We're
making out We're not
making out It's a bad channel A It's
not a channel Oh well, it's already for today  I wonder
if it's the end, Chomizu Channel. The
timing is good, it's good. The two of you are a
good match for the channel. I wonder if that was a
nuisance. Hakusui Channel. We had a
choreography lesson on the day and night,
but after the lesson, we
went out to eat.  So we got together at the dot, and
when I was told that I had to transfer money today, that person chatted with me and said, ``I'm
not going out to eat today.'' Yeah, I want to
go.  I
said let's go, and I heard that Sei-chan was also going,
but later on, there was a white-collar dance,
so me and Chan-chan finished first and lined
up outside. There was a really long line, and it was kind of cold, and it was really
night, and I was a little thin.
When I was touching Majiburubul, Towa-chan
said it was cold and Towa-chan said, "It's
okay to be cold, Gyutto-chan loves me. I
was so sleepy after the Endurance Endurance".
After playing golf, I told Actor and Su-chan
that I had slept, and they said, no, I didn't take a nap.After
the golf game,
Toa said, oh, I'm sleepy, so I'm going to go to sleep, and Aku was
okay, so we did something after that.  To be
honest, I'm
not in that dimension anymore.
Everyone I know is not in the same dimension as you.
Toa is already in another dimension.
Don't put me together.  please  I
know you're sitting behind me with your arms folded. You're an
adult.
[Music]
Ask Aku-tan. It's true. I'll play with you
. I'll play with you. I'll
play with you.  It's my fault that
you're trying to play with me.
It doesn't matter if it's okay or not. I
won't forgive you. It's
not good. I'll catch you inside.
That kind of crazy love isn't good, Yomiko Akutan,
and I've never done that ball before
, but I guess I'll put it in. I do
n't need it, it has nothing to do with you
[Music]