[Music]
the song is really great
okay okay okay hello hello
hello first how are you I have to
speak German German German German
German German German
I'm missing
the game capture here
Moment
tired
best second channel of a youtuber
ever that's an exaggeration
[music]
today we're playing
through the German beautiful
[music]
it's over the plants
because I don't have any separate layers okay
yeah not that bad not that bad
looks good or
plays well  in German
oh oh do you link yes
[music] wait a
minute
first water need water
need a little water
detention
that Josh that's also Japanese and
I can't get out of the habit of that I'm
sorry
every time I've put my foot on it
since then I hurt myself  I haven't
streamed in English yet or GTA was
in between or my foot is fine,
although today I
wore shoes that I haven't worn for a long time
and then I
got a blister,
it hurts, oh dear, oh dear,
we thought, yes, I'll go with you
the public transport and then I
somehow walk for 15 minutes because there
seems to be no other way and then
BÄM after a few meters I already have a
blister on my foot, the one on my
Achilles tendon,
yes, but the one where I hit myself is
n't that bad,
let me  let's compare the size of
my toes
looks normal yes
looks normal everything was good it was very
painful but it got back
to normal quickly but I hit myself on the wall
so aggressively with such a swing
that I really
thought it was over now  I
actually broke my toe
because apparently people often break their toes without
noticing it themselves.
You know that,
I've already mentioned that, I think
milk is the right thing
[laughter],
yes, and I thought to myself  That's what
happened now but it wasn't that bad, I
mean maybe I
broke it but no, probably not,
but if it happened like that and you wouldn't even
notice it
then it could be that it does
n't hurt that much in your toe or if you
yourself  I wouldn't even notice
that I have to break my toes more often than not in my lifetime,
well the little toe, yes for me it was
more like the ring finger toe
oh Dusseldorf no you
want to trigger me again
and who did that ah you are you are sick
sister oh  what
oha oha I could never do that.
I watched a video today
that was a bit medical and did
n't show any blood or anything
but it was about a topic
that somehow made me feel sick
but there wasn't any blood at all or at all  It
didn't really show anything blatant, but
I watched it out of interest
because I wanted to have the information,
but
just thinking about it made
my stomach turn and
then I had to turn it off because I felt
really sick, even though
it was  Actually, it wasn't really anything bad,
no, actually it wasn't anything bad
that had anything to do with injections,
yes, because I actually don't have a problem with injections per se
[music]
because, for example, with the
vaccination, yes, that wasn't a problem with
such information  Thinking isn't a problem
for me, but when it comes to this topic
I just can't,
yes,
um, so I would ask you, it
's so sweet that you're
interested in it, but I would ask you
not to push me here on the channel
with certain people
Collaborate if I feel like
doing something like that then I'll do it on my
own, don't worry, I'm already
aware of other Youtubers who speak German
and if I take that into consideration
then I already have the
knowledge
that I need in order to  Inviting these people is
no problem so yes we
have just started with the
channel but maybe there will be
a collaboration then yes yes
yes okay well we are probably playing this
for about 2 hours now
a playlist of maybe a run
really has to be what I  should play because then
I can make it bigger
it's so small
[music]
so long about to play like I was about
to cancel the stream where are you
I was racking my brain as if
it was such an important decision,
it is now  not that important but it doesn't
matter what or but but no I
've been racking my brain but I
mix in English sometimes
no complaints yes here my
main base on the TV
English
wrecking my [ __ ] brain not a bad
choice really
music slaps yes
music is really cool  ever
I didn't expect a surprised about
that what is love it's a road like
welcome to
[music]
the only game show where your
biggest dreams come true
[music]
but will your dreams come true or your
nightmares no
no oh no ways that  night emote let
's find out here is our
host
[music]
no, that would be cool if I
could do a show like that too,
the wonderful Chihuahua is still coming
[music]
thank you very much, dear audience and
welcome back to my labyrinth
of  endlessly in terror, our
next participant will die big or
we could lose everything, here it is
ah I don't know
exactly my love that's how it works here
tell me warrior what inner emptiness has
driven itself to risk endless banishment
at my hand
most expensive why  Are you playing today?
Yes, I actually wanted to
win a monster truck and also
become the strongest man in the world.
How inspiring. Well, you know that
we here at Dyson Dungeons say that
luck doesn't make you great, but it
's too late to change your mind.
Why are you?  it dice click on the
box and go to you okay I don't have to do
that you can jump on it okay
oh a sword what choose
I didn't choose anything that was
there was nothing in the middle but okay
then I go back
who is who is  Space Marine who is speaking
man or woman hello player is this
the first person side to
start up the old plasma blaster again
put your die on the sword
oh so
great because you used a 5
you caused five damage
ahh okay cool cool now it is  turn
click on the end turn button when you're
ready okay I'm ready
Spongebob I'm ready I'm ready
something if the thing reaches zero you have
problems
okay
oh no
that's okay sometimes that happens
you can reroll up to three times per turn
oh that
Just got a special ability
okay okay fight so the
special ability is three times onions
okay
it's all scripted here
does
yes yes yes we're coming now of course
[music]
I don't want to really break out now
because then everyone will say it's so bad again
click on end the move I think okay
but quickly on
a
limit break on click on to
use other mint
doubled next action ready in
eight HP
so now just know how I already
activated or how so this will
now be twelve yes yes
yes
okay wonderful cool
apple doesn't make you healthy again oh apples
that have  I didn't eat at all I
thought he would pick it up automatically
when he walked past no okay
aha a
maximum of four because that's twice yes okay
what if I got a six I
said what if I got a six really
okay but now we can get them
exactly okay
what  there is a difference when I
go back and forth to the individual fields,
I don't lose any moves or anything
[music]
oh he's a fiery head
aha oh I can't use
them now I ca
n't use the chariots at all but there are  me a
here a selection this camera it
needs a lot or less yes good yes
[ __ ] man okay yes then I'll do it like
this and then we have
this in here
now I don't have a good
number again but not in this case oh
fuckingham yes okay  That's
fine, you're past it
Use status effects This fireball
is pretty hot,
yes Fireball fits well but maybe
not against that one or are you already using it
against me
or yes yes yes yes
I thought to myself because it burns,
oh what  a cube burned by me
[applause]
that times two is just sex
then I couldn't kill him
it doesn't just cost two hearts
ahh
[applause]
okay okay we'll do that I would say
[music]
okay well good
I forgot again  what that
means
so the one
I should have done before mine
he would have had it twice now
oh
didn't I plan well in advance [ __ ] yes
good yes
[applause]
we are small heads
is the learning profession
[music]
you get episode okay good that  we
needed it and to Gerlingen
better
okay yes next what should I
go here like once there
a match burns a
burning cube
but
okay we have to try that out
I would like to see that in action
[music]
number rolled plus one cool
okay  There's an exit but I have to
fight against the yard
of course I have to fight against the
one at the train station
that goes away so quickly
the what
[music]
has to infect it but let me tell you a
secret it's dying today
the equipment
is okay now  he's on the screen quite a lot,
okay, I can even here,
maybe it's a good thing that we've saved each other
because it doesn't seem to work too badly in the
following fight,
okay, so once
I'd like to re-roll it and again
very well,
so I would do that too  once again,
[ __ ], I don't have anything for four,
it's okay, it's okay, wait, I want anger
and then the doubling then the skin
[music]
then okay, he hasn't done it yet
but it's coming soon or one, wait
no
no, I was thinking of the skin too now
I just had more dice
that
[music]
thought of the skin then uh 6 + 1 that's
seven twice so 14 like that but he
just doubled the dice for me,
that's great, I can't use the rest
unless I do and that has
two damages
[  Music]
[ __ ] man snowflake
and what's up and Charlie these
[ __ ] dice on oha
okay
okay here mom there twice
the green I still don't understand
oh well if I were to put the two in now
then I would
get another two dice or
I need less one  yes, not, I
'm already done, then I can do a three,
oh, okay, yes, but now I don't need it
anymore, or did I misunderstand
[music]
make it stone-like, his
is also misunderstood, I
thought if one of my cubes
burns,
then that's what it does  burning way
but they didn't explain it well
I think put down the dice to
trigger shock what
[music]
sounds what
what a bastard
[music]
[ __ ] now I did it wrong
because
[music]
[ __ ] then I can
get in here and now if I do that but
convert the environment
yes good
[music]
yes good then I'll open this
here and do the treasure here
now I haven't used it again
but I don't know how
why not that prank  appointed
[Music]
oh no
I have to do it like him
okay okay what happens now if
I throw this in here you should
it should be a
sausage what a number I have on it
makes it only ever burn one cube of him
[Music  ]
has to be straight well
wait then I want a two
okay you can
try me out okay it burns once if it
was worth it we don't know
a little bit of damage here and here still
okay
[music]
he too that I hurt a little bit
when he attacks that right
[music]
and my HP is so low, my HP isn't at all
what's that now
[music]
I can't use these three
but it doesn't matter
a bit weaker okay here BAM okay
until then I could have sworn
that was dying was oh  oh, my watch is
with you, is it right now with
you,
no,
no, PM,
okay, home
and now it's supposed to be the lava,
where am I here, so I can
fight it, I can go to a shop,
I can have a marshmello, a burning one
Fighting Marshmallow and dancing, I don't
really care.
I'm going to go to the Marshmallow
[Music]
Tutorial complete first. There's
nothing scripted here now or was
n't it at all who knows but well
okay I understand
then let's put it in here
had a burn then  I put this
in here,
Bürkle, in the hope of getting a 4,
it's still a three but that
's okay, that's
what you would have
done,
what does the snowball and fireball do,
they can do everything
then the mom cinema 3 + 1  Would be better to
toast three
why oh well then I would have got a four
then I wouldn't
have had to change it here
[music]
anyway ah yes that's right [ __ ] is good yes
but
you don't like that that's okay
I would roll it again now
or would  give her that in toast
again okay okay okay and
again yes
and now just one
because then at least maybe we'll get
one more exactly exactly
okay okay okay okay
[music]
then we can kill now
is dead
no bad bad
yes, the music is really loud, actually there is something
so quiet,
so then I'll take it that
looks somehow more interesting
ah if it's an even number
then I do damage with its
odd number I do it really cool
I want the thing
I have the option  of the shield also
against
the beer what are you doing here you
should be on the sea
so I have one in here
one really new then I do that
then I do that then I do that
then I do another one and then
I do that
wonderfully
finished next
show me what you can do
[music]
are you a reason why I chose oil
because I thought if it's in German
then games are where there are at least
some kind of explanations then
it even brings up what it is
German is because then I understand
more easily than in English.
Maybe I'll understand more easily
if I had somehow just
played Mario Kart or something like that, then
I wouldn't have been able to take advantage of that at all. I
wanted to take advantage of my language, but there
's not that much text here  they
make you so the game then you have a
text in cele Mario cars
of the German anyway here uh one
in here ah yes that's true it doesn't work
wonderfully perfection again
wow that's that's not nice WhatsApp
back
it
that's [ __ ]
what do we have  Because
okay, we don't need that at all,
I'll save it because it seems to be
taken into the next fight,
okay once here,
why did I bump into a hair in my mouth
and I already have that? What's the point of
having that one again?
another extra option to initiate
Jolanda
oh a new adventurer walking in
I'm barely at the dungeon
I have some great things in
stock here do you need socks washed a
potted plant no who needs socks
I need them because I have some
holes in them I haven't had any for a long time
bought more
okay what do we want do I have anyway
how much money do I have only five
[music]
that plus two damage a
maximum of three different
[music]
poison is nice if that yes
present
okay I guess that's pretty cool
I can  Just go to a shop like that once
ah no I can go back in
okay we just don't have any money left okay
let's go
[applause]
[music]
larynx okay the characters are
pretty good
I'll go first and because it's
lower leveled
we would have gone in  Shock bought
but then we'll do it quickly
quick thing
once here
then
this will now do 16 more damage
or
yes
another good old one
that was very well rolled I
somehow didn't waste anything I do
n't think that's nice no no no no
no no okay  We can repeat that again
actually
oh he's already dead oh that's quick
you what
boring boring didn't even really
do any damage
okay I can strengthen something or
that's how it comes to life
I've also been able to strengthen cards
interesting
what am I improving here  It's best that
I have money for it at all,
bye Simone in
another one,
oh wait, I actually have to
switch it over to my equipment so that
I can get it at all, I thought
it was random,
what's the difference, there
's no difference here, there
's no difference
there  really no difference that's
a difference that doesn't have to be straight anymore
oh so it's about space
oh
stuff and carry that means
[music]
plus a damage
yes I don't know how long I would
carry these beginner things with me
whether I should go for some of the newer
stuff
[music]
yes, but smaller would be cool, yes then
I can take one of those in without
making any kind of loss, although I
don't really
have enough dice most of the time to really
take advantage of everything
use the maximum of 5 o'clock twice an hour
and here
[music]
it doesn't have to be a maximum of five anymore
ah I could protect myself very strongly
if I wanted to,
okay but no then first I'll do it
there
yes and then another time  I'll make the
sign
I think and then here I now have
space for
the claw
nice nice interesting
nothing
very Inter
okay something new here's a cactus look
how cute he's so scared
cute
I'll do
[music]
so
the numbers are all closed  high so I mean
I have
no like that and then I need
no that's not really good either
[music]
and the dice don't come with me on
the next turn right
or or oh so that's just
what I didn't think of
[music]
okay
cactus
he protects himself completely from me
I suffer three damage if I attack in the
round one for each thorns
three damage yes
I would still attack
I think
okay
[music]
now I'll just do it
no
[music]
I have an idea I  do it like this and
then I'll do it like this
and then it's
[music]
hey
Level 4
[music]
let's go
very good very good what's in here
crystal sword
5 three times damage once program
okay now it doesn't really come to me
much space I'll go
HP  we don't need it, we've just
ticked off the level,
it's that far, it's somehow
easier than ladies because who knows then there's
a bit more information
included
so it's quite easy actually
[music] let's
see
nice and yes the 6 is just a bit
wasted then isn't it  but
what should you do, I have nothing else
left
[music]
okay now I'm angry
burning light what are you doing
no it's burning it's burning calls the
fire department
1 2 2 what do I think
two dice oh
interesting I know it can't go any higher
Yes, [ __ ], if I'm in
Germany but in Austria it's already
122, I think hopefully otherwise
I would have a problem if there was a
fire in my place. Thank God the last
time the whole thing was automatic and
I didn't have to call anyone
okay
okay then you don't have to
worry
[music]
we still need six damage okay
yes so different in Austria but something
like that right that's confusing a bit
okay now we need healing here
and now we can buy it
[music]
I  can I could heal myself but at the
moment
our our
HP is actually not that bad but
maybe in the future
before the Future Baby healing
for the future
[music]
in Austria both should
end up at the fire department oh that's so oh
perfect for two  One yeah
I don't need that
okay I'll take that
at some point we might
need
Sunday
okay where are we here
kristallina
yeti and a branch
[music]
also a kristallino
40 HP holy [ __ ] and I'm not
even fully healed oh [ __ ] that could
get in my pants then let's see how
strong it is
okay let's start
here oh no here's right that doesn't work
here
then we roll the dice 1 9
perfect 3 is what I need then there is
that too and
I'll risk it for more  Damage
okay now I don't want to risk any more,
wait but I could still anger, should I
now or save it? I'd rather
save it when I can do more damage
yes okay
next
what was that again
air crystal
hollow Christa
not yet
okay I might do anger and  then
battle ax
then I have eight times two again 16
[music]
and then here these are the face
then there is again
and yes
how does that feel hey
you still don't kill okay
[music]
now we don't really have to
worry about it  break
[music]
easy easy that's gone
too easy too easy have too much luck
maybe
oh he would have even been weaker
with 20 HP
on
Hartmut weak against fire oh I have a
burn
match yes okay
numero un
o and here that and that
and that perfect
Not hearing it in German is
strange but it's nice thanks
for me it's still so strange
[music]
still very strange okay here are
the three again
[music]
nice then I'll just do it
no that's a waste oh  lol
[Music]
worse what okay what are you doing
here let them go here too now
what do you want I'm just winning
what are you talking about
a stick magic magic magic now comes
the magic here comes the magic
[laughter]
[music  ]
yes he lost and me loose
loser
six fire damage a fire die burns
one of my dice that's
somehow not so clear but you tell
me sure
show it
now you come oh [ __ ] ah I should have
put the fire stick in
everything is okay okay okay yes I
always doubt it well here
and here
[music]
and
okay no problem
[music]
circle people well ah yes looks good
I have to watch all the Marvel films
[music]
there are a lot of Marvel films on Netflix
already or I have to  Bingo
Action here, I've hardly seen any,
I think I've only seen Heroes of the
Galaxy once and
the first Spider-Man film used to be maybe
great, I even did that. Well then
what's your favorite Marvel film what
you favorite Marvel movie guys
ahhh
[Music]
love is strange Tor
Captain America Iron Man
giant man Deadpool
if you like to see Spider-Man watch
Avengers everyone
[Music]
yeah well
no choice
[ __ ] didn't go so well
a bastard that doesn't exist so
I'm killing him now  Of course, but that
's very close, yes, because
okay, then I'm not allowed to
attack you because otherwise I could do that
[ __ ]. Wait, that's actually wait, it's
not that easy because new damage with
two dice
okay, that's okay, I can do that,
okay, okay, everything's fine
everything oh my god
I can improve or shield hit
double a hit with the shield well
I want to improve I think ah yes
my HP costs then it's full again
I take that
and
what happens here more damage
and here it gets smaller
three times damage I  I think I'll make
the crystal sword smaller,
okay, do we want to put it in somewhere? Can
you get more slots or will
it always stay that
way? Good good idea, more
potential. Yes,
should I change my sword too?
Who's
good or
why is it eight? It's always 8.
Why  It says eight
sex damage here but why does it say eight
would keep the sword
so I need one
what I need
so I need a six and then
two or something
oh so or no matter how much
that's full of [ __ ] I have to roll more
dice than there is damage
No, then only when I improve,
maybe then
I'll keep the sword for now.
What is that, why is the green the
tutorial shop is
a trading station here you can
exchange things if you absolutely have to
oh but no, we don't need the healing crystal
for the future
Deal, there was once a TV series
on German television about it,
but it's probably all over the world,
it's one of those
series
I want to say I want to keep my healing,
what can't be done here 4 4 ​​5 okay then let's
go  first this way I would
sayor
4 5 4 and then to the shop what if they take
us
with the motorbike
Aurora
Aurora why is Aurora why did I have
such a design
music is really popping again
okay okay should I
wait a maximum of five when I'm clear
that you have one make it five rows
and before that Zorne
said that I would do it,
I wanted to put it in here but
somehow my my brain was somewhere
what the [ __ ]
well okay
yes okay
[ __ ] but I would still have no no
it's okay that's fine  yes never mind never mind no
we already had enough of that in
Europe
no no no no no no no we do
n't play GTA here
I would have them too I had Aways one hit
hurt and
the second something else we will never
know well well brain is what you
need
is the streamer problem
you are somehow distracted
he body for the first time
[music]
you just missed one and we
have
a
very German one here I've
never heard of it before so I always say advises
even when I speak German
you have well
Berry is one of those  a hat a kind of
food advises in northern Germany
[music]
improve or which poisonous slime
is only poisonous if I also have a 6
dice
I think I want to improve
and we said
I'll do the shield maybe
first or
[music]
you know what knows that  not who
is limited then I can do the shield instead of the
sword then I always have the
choice either six damage exactly that
I still have the choice if I
just have sex or I just do the shield
I think that makes sense
then at least I have that  Choice, that's
pretty good,
but wait a minute in the playlist, I can see
in advance what they'll do in the next turn,
but here I don't really see it,
so sometimes I can
maybe guess but or
so when do I know that I have to block
just like that  out of intuition
this way
that's why
[music]
do it again okay
he can do that
and I don't know what he rolls okay
aha
[music]
once
12 with three dice so what's
this he has to fill it up with 12 right
and then get it  but only five damage
and he blocks one dice for me
oh well I have to use the singles
if I have them okay but that's
not a lot of damage and that's just
okay interesting okay
in important fights I'll take a look
at it and then I'll see  should I
block
St
oh cool
like another five is cool
yes
the perfect move people
here the perfect move baby
perfect
[music]
yes come
here
[laughter]
[music]
she left me no
anyway that was amazing should I just do
that  talk
but it's so great you can
mix it up um all the whole sentences already here
separately in German and English
is it half full or not
prison Denglisch oh she she he blocked
my one DICE blockedm
oh so I can't even use that as a one
I  thought he would just
block me from changing that but okay I
can't lose him that's a good
one lonely and not that bad it
's not that bad I do
n't always speak English oh man you're stupid
[ __ ] okay that's not that good not like
that  ideal I would like to have that one day
but we have an almost down already
three times two
yes it's fine it's fine it's fine it's
fine
so I had
an important
professional
conversation today my dear people and
[music]
with the professor so yes a formal
conversation
one  Sun meeting in person
and
exactly it is a meeting where you
would sit and
talk to each other very politely
and I was a bit
embarrassed when my German failed like that.
I sometimes couldn't find the words
and in cases where I, for
example  Plural should have said something in the plural
I somehow
said it in the singular in the singular and so completely
embarrassing
[music]
[applause]
[laughter]
yes but I hope you did
n't notice it so much and thought
he was completely stupid
had none  Enjoyed school and the
rain
that's why I thought that's
good timing
[music]
you should
this [ __ ] gave me something
this [ __ ] [ __ ] cursed it and
that's why it took it away from me
[music]
I saw that  that she was
just a coincidence I would like I couldn't have
known or
yes music is banger
what a [ __ ]
what
incredible
I would like her I could
kill her but it's fine
I could roll the dice again
[ __ ]
but it's [ __ ] number come when I
roll the dice again then I
screwed up I can definitely
kill it if I make it angry but is it
the word
[music]
it
's better like this
okay yes
healing great I needed it
here too very
okay go shopping once what's
there
oh I've seen it before,
I've seen it before, yes,
I've already looked at it,
I didn't want to have it,
what should I get
or
fight against Sana here
ah that's gone
[laughter]
the hair length the hair color of the
pink one there  the stars perfect everything
perfect
nice to see you here
what's going on
hello first of all I don't know if we
already knew
okay now we always want to be
okay I
like it
okay is just about acceptable
yes ancient
comedian I don't know if he still
does comedy but yes
there  you can tell the boomer in
me again sad verses
what did she do
[music]
only now on the next move she would
try to fill it up from 17 but that's
crazy
she toned it down for me
[music]
unbelievable but I can handle it
yes yes a
maximum of three ey I would like more
damage what to do with
[music]
this one there was one left
if it's on you
we almost have it
goes down
it's at 1 p.m. you have to
bring it down to zero
[music]
everything is fine, everything is fine, it does
n't
ever get to that point. Unfortunately, I can't imitate the dentist's voice well for art. I'm writing a song about it. Orange, I'm looking forward to it. What are you doing?
I'm feeling a
little bit higher
yummy repeats the next attack
and the 12 means that I have to
clean up with 12 and have to fill it up
until it's at zero or something like that
[music] I
don't know if I like that, it's
somehow too much of a hassle for me, I
would have from on  I'd like to get
a result right away, okay, what are we doing here
[music]
au au au au I have a stitch in
my little boy's side
and I'm still having a heart attack.
Heart attack sounds like a fact, yes my heart
is a fact
but no, everything is fine on the right side. A stitch
in the side,
so it's stinging  Maybe that would be good, I
'm not thinking too much about it,
just do
the Internet
[applause]
myGodGirl Scout who
sells cookies
must still look so bad I had
the money in her hand and she
completely ripped off people,
it's Großkarl making big money from
the
I saw shitty cookies I know the Boy Scout
ride when the Boy Scout was but in
my world where I grew up
I never had any kind of so
now that's someone grown up I
was talking about but I never had
any of the possibility in my childhood
Heard that I
could have joined something like that or that
somehow one of my friends
was a Boy Scout at school and I think even
if that had been someone at
school I think they would
have made fun of it but it's
not like
that for us  one thing
for it i have never in my hould child
hard the opportunity
I actually find quite sweet but
annoying when I imagine that
someone would ring my doorbell and
kick me and I would probably
even buy it
I want to sell it myself like
that  yes completely practical actually
okay okay
my house and and
oh yes so chocolate cookies are really cool
why is there such an intermediate step here it does
n't make any difference let's go
boss doesn't have a level
depends on the cookies yes typical
chocolate cookies are really cool it's 12
years old and  she's here to win against me
how much HP do you have because
[ __ ] wait I have my healing so
no I at least have my shield that
's okay
yes we can manage it or or
I should have given myself the healing
instead of pushing maybe
okay
yes you have  Right, I already have the song
ready, that
means I heard it from last time
or is it always the case with boss fights that
you have it from the beginning,
that means 15 damage is really
cool oh y
EAH her last time I don't know
why
but she finished
it  Poor man, it
's okay, I'll just throw dice into her
face,
okay, let me think for a moment, I
would like to have the four
and then these,
of course, but what are you
actually doing? Shitty
chocolate biscuits, well, it doesn't look that bad
and then just one at a time and it
was well diced
bad
yes, you're going down now, I think, my
love,
okay here once
here once
but that will give you a damage to
the others
[Music]
congratulations
yay your first victory I am I
understood that now no but look
that's a good start  you have
already won a whole pistol yes
now there are only 35 more and more
difficult episodes left
like please what 35 more and more difficult
and of course now after each episode
the opportunity for cupid
and if the wheel points to a star
then you can leave the dungeon I
would say the dungeon but okay and
get your heart's desire fulfilled
what
if I don't
[Music]
oh shitstyle skull
that's always like that
[applause]
where is
that okay
it would have been very bold
S
[Music]
Channel
there are still a lot of people waiting especially
[  Applause]
[Music]
he's done he's not shooting anymore yes
[applause]
okay episode one warrior episode 1 is
warrior once one
next
character
[music]
at least we have an argument I could
n't do that with solid spire
okay difficulties
two why is that more difficult  I'm
not here to make new friends I
want to win shouldn't it
get easier if the levels
get more difficult
what does the different
title do oh [ __ ]
what does
your and level lover
can't re-roll the dice
let's try it out
I hope I don't lose then  but
I'll do another complete
round if I can,
a huge round of applause for the next
hopelessly
hopeful participant, he has big
dreams, unrealistic wishes and he has
contractually agreed not to sue us
[music]
here is the one
that you mean literally with the dice
I mean everything
literally
then tell me something for you in
my arena of mischief
okay a spoonful of what
he hears don't talk too much
so God my girlfriend doesn't take this
seriously but I do and I'll
win a trillion dollars
and whatever  you
do everything I want with all the money
and luck is with the brave,
at least that's what those who don't know me believe
up to days weather is [ __ ] today's news
are [ __ ] everything is [ __ ] go back to
bed hide on the your covers and never
wake up ever again good luck
so let's go
let's see
how this goes oh
what
's my attack no what I have
a plastic cannon
divide a die 2
so what two years for that do
I get two one or something oh [ __ ]
but do I still have that  Because
I have to set it up here, I ca
n't do it in one turn.
Next time I would still have it in the
next turn, sometimes not
from the whole fight, but he still has it
too or had two there
anyway, well,
until it recharges  I don't come,
I think with so few or so
crappy dice, I'd rather do another
attack.
Parts that
have one, I have what, then I have two individually,
no way,
really, that's how I'll do it, then I'll
win,
okay, here it's better, here
we divide  the
come on
yes then we load both up
I thought he divides it into three
and two is that a coincidence we also
divide
two if I now
what I thought
we are five in there twice or what
what is that we four individually extra the
41 with
4 4 damage or something
[music]
oh so okay
7 8 9 10 11 oh 7 8 9 10 11
I have enough to hit him
oh there I go
yes
let's go
[music]
okay but he also really pissed me off
Serpents
face magic Dice 2 1 what what does
he have with all his ones
I like that
well let's
see if that's helpful
so if I go in here now
smells two ones what the horse then
I could if that's right now
two more so  one more extra that
really works
okay
three and that's a maximum okay yes
again at least you can use it again
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
maximum minimum
so it's very different
okay I can get all the ones again
or
[  Music]
Parts are three and do it like that but I do
n't know then I could attack twice with
three it makes sense
but no maybe I want the
files because I can't get it anywhere else
no but I could get it in there
which still only makes
three  Damage, he doesn't do much
damage,
yes, well then we'll
do it like that and then we'll do it like that.
Now it's worth it
and then one two three a damage something else
that's not worth it
okay
no problem
[music]
is pretty cool so far then you hardly
have to  I have 22
a great too thank you very much
so the thief is doing very interesting I
'm having fun with it
okay maximum three
but
what's the headbutt I
stole an even number and then
it does as much damage as what I
got in
so the share  I already then
I get an extra one has to
be straight so I put the
two in
and then
we put in a few more
which was that I can't see it but
I can use it
but I can see it and I parts it
resets
the effect
[Music]
wait a minute put this in here
ah I can test it
wait a minute
[music]
and what is it then just blocks me
or throws it away if it didn't
work
even
that just blocks me okay
um
oh so okay it  is not exactly
that worked so it was
probably a one or a three
or white maximum 3 food that wasn't
exactly
okay and then I share
[music]
okay
that was a one oh so yeah I
could have seen the damage haha ​​I didn't
look  okay yes and that okay
aha there's always something there okay
cool
she's not again let's
try it out
where do I want to try it out
[Music]
no I want to but the parts
unless I hit snake magic
[Music]
ah to decide which
game I should play  I want to play on the stream and
now you're confronting me with a decision like that,
it's very difficult for
me.
Hey, you could always throw it in there
if I wanted to, but it'll be four of us
first,
then we'll try this, it
worked, what was it now
as it was back then  that didn't see
and then the four in here
and then the two in here and yes okay
cool it was three no it
's cool
[music]
for the accent do you mean I don't have an
accent
I don't have an Advent
but I'm surprised that I still
no udder slipped out because today
at the appointments where I should have been so polite
an udder
came out
but it doesn't seem to have bothered people that much
and it wasn't
but I was telling you about something and
that was my reaction  I
said something like that because of
you know or sorry
for the yes language
but it didn't bother them
okay so cannon fire we
stole
[music]
if I fill it with eight I do
six damage and for
burn one of his dice okay
then I'll split the fiver
[ __ ]
wait a minute five
[music]
yes okay
please wait but that doesn't matter okay it's okay
[music]
it's okay
maybe they
could have done it better somehow but well
mom mom
yeah I just wanted to use it no matter
how bad
[  Music]
but I think I'm doing pretty well in
general pirates had a maximum of five
come at 4 we if I put in a four
I can use it again cool
um and I can also do something twice
so no not double we are at the
VIP four  we have four extra ones
okay,
turn it over to me and
divide it into a 401, it would
actually be quite nice,
yes okay and then I'll put it in here
okay then it will be used again
then I can
[music]
it can be reused forever
good for that thank you very much
I can do it again with bad luck, okay
it's burning here but wait let me
think about it
at 4 can be used again you
can do it twice now
[music]
oh god
whether lythering
the sea is far away yes you're
completely wrong here you've probably got that now
hopefully noticed
lead
then go back go back
to the sea WiFi reward poisonnatel or
crowbar reduces all countdowns by
so and so
and poison
three times per round maximum two
makes only one there is what should I take then
there is okay
I trust you
let's go
now I don't know at all  which I
like better or these
are both really cool games
okay I like this one it's
easier for me to think here
I relied so much on the chat
while here I actually
make all the decisions myself except
maybe sometimes when I have to
decide between  what I buy
in this game I want Lions
yes the marshmallow will soon burn us up
okay what is this even number
we do so much damage and we
burn a dice awesome okay we
can't roll the dice again so
we have to deal with the four here
satisfy
and then we can have a few singles
[music]
sharing a maximum of two
use [music] three times an hour
and there three I think I'll share once
okay
yes I like it
but that's
good because I would waste it anyway
then I would  But it's better
to hit it in there then get an extra lonely one to
divide up a bit or
yes okay why
not why not
very good thank you thank you
thank you thank you I had to give them I really like the game
I also
maybe it's generally just very hype
and very loud as if you like it
a little bit  quieter would have a
quieter soundtrack
you're nice too but that's just the way it is
I don't care about the atmosphere of the game right now I'll do it
[music]
at most here we can't do it much
except that's two parts and then
attack twice here
yes
poison leaf for several rounds if you
keep stacking it up, I have
n't really noticed it yet,
but here too, [ __ ], we don't have to
do any damage because it always only does,
heh, now I have that was from four, that
's gone down to one to three,
but  only done one damage that has
only one use that in the round
or like so if I start a lot of poison
in one turn again still only
deduct one and we move on and so on
and so on
so it's worth it um it's already
done
but  it loses one of those there
oh okay okay then I saw it wrong
okay then it's worth it
so now it would do three damage on the next turn
but only go down to two
I understand that correctly
[music] it
says here he loses three health
oh
cool yes then we don't really have to
do anything more but I'll
still dig in
cool
interesting
to up to forever
only go down to free I will take up all
this
is you
[music]
Pickpocketing is just getting in on the act ah
okay if we know who wants money
to buy more items
I don't know if that should be our priority
I haven't been in here
yet
you could maybe upgrade then
come on in
pea gun 5 okay countdown 5
leather armor reduces damage but
I have to have everything in my inventory
so in my set or  like
a fake doubles a yes that sounds
good that's also so cheap why is it so
cheap
if God buy that already
that's more expensive if you
can use it again but up to five
charging no you
oh so you know it's so big yes you can
yes  Let's downsize,
I think it's good and then
I won't waste so much. I
could still go shopping.
I want to have another one.
I don't know. That doesn't seem that
special to me. No, let's
see what else I have later.
Hello  and vacuum cleaner
cute where am I hello here always
difficult to find myself the
magician hello
take off with magic
okay we even start with bad luck
before now but needs two
and then burns five damage
how strong is that
if I split it up now
then I hit  him in there and well it's
okay wait maybe that wasn't
smart wait I can at least
fill this up
um
yes
I can stand if I want not
I'll do it here
but go again
okay I would have liked to share that
but I'm just out of luck  also do
[music]
and then yes, well, let's do it so
I should do the individual
[music]
okay, he already has a good stack here,
oh what's that,
I'm also a magician
[music]
who blocked them for me,
okay but I  can again I can
use lightning no
and a bit of poison and here the three
not so bad quite good actually
said down nice
yes that's a lot of effects
ah he still has three wars now
two the human being so it's enough if I
hit him with that flex and  Just
finish it hopefully I won't do
anything wrong no I'm not doing anything human yet
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
and an upgrade would be no
hmm
okay what do we want here that's oh
that would be good
that I don't care actually
I still have space
oh so fake  Doesn't fit in
I could also take pickpocket out
and maybe put it in what does
fashion plus
double a small okay
I'm coming that
oh I should have done German
then I'll do that in German next time
[music]
cleaning
okay
wait a minute that's worth it  Don't
put it in two at all because there's still
only one available
then it would be the best to share because
I might just get
the ones
or I did I should distribute the film
Baby
wait a minute wait a minute
I'm hungry
he
okay okay  I want to share with you now
I'm
doing this and that and that we've
already had a stack
Lucerne didn't appeal to me that much
[music]
but okay it's okay we can
use it next time
we can use it next time
[music]
German why
does it do it  damage and the difference with the heart
I guess if he were to block, for example,
maybe it wouldn't be able to
block anymore or something like that
oh so no it doesn't affect me oh
well like in Pokémon there's something like that too
oh so I didn't check  That's
then comes to me
okay okay um
wait a minute wait here the dice are so
high
so I definitely have to divide something
on which five or a sex has to
divide
[music]
then I'll do that maybe
even more ones so all
I have left is  this one
and then I can divide it up
why not so much poisonous yes it's good
although no I think it's good but
only one of them is
okay difficult
I hate the
modern
yesterday
[music]
maybe
which ones double then I see both
not or like
okay that's not possible so that's more
more its four
so maybe share
okay what was it how much does that have
that still more oh so then that's
but less than we
one that was a one
you know why
are you  otherwise it confuses me
[music]
I'll do [ __ ] sometimes
yes, okay, yes, well then it wouldn't
have had any other use, it was good that I
threw it in first then
no problem and the one five well
the one with the five  I can't do anything
okay then we have the two here
and then here and
then you get one HP because then
we can do three more damage
doesn't work
[music]
okay at least I still love everything good
but interesting opponent
[music]
welcome or that  is such a
wolf can see
that's my my hate skill in the
game I'll try
it it worked
two I think I went from 9 to 11
know at least get some HP
back
new dice
[music]
box
now fill up 16
okay now I need it  that's not
oh actually has the level up so
I'm full again no
you're my opponent
in the German and
[music]
okay let's see what's the cauldron
get some damage new dice
so no matter what I throw in
I only do some damage as if it
something is going on that I absolutely don't
need, I can at least do some damage
with it and get something new
[music]
then we'll do it like this
oh I could
put the six in here or and then
[music]
do it like this
okay then do one  We can do a little bit
[music] we
can have money once in a while
[music]
we can also
pay in once in a while
maybe cover it again
if you have more,
yes Christmas
okay I'm happy for one time because in the
end that actually makes
perfect sense now I can't do it with a loss
do it but I can only use it once
okay but it was good that was
good that was good
wait okay
[Music]
it's not that bad the cauldron
it's actually really funny because you
can always try out new things,
let's do something  that and
then I do just that much damage and it freezes
her dice an
odd one it has to be okay
maybe I'll just do it with a 1
no I won't finish I'm if
[music]
what do you two say too good or something
like that and  so poison again, why not
[music]
once
more so there
are full pro gamers or you
could almost think that I do this for a
living
playing games
on Google
[applause]
exactly
are number eight, wait a minute then
she gets three damage so yes she has to  only five
damage make this move
[music]
easy it does
n't matter it's so cool that's
[music]
at least a little better than nothing right
then
I should eat a few of you,
you're chickens or are you
all from day Anna
can I eat you exactly
[music]
in the chat
the next fatal oh
[music]
but will I die now for sure next
time
one health star what should I buy
yes
[music]
no she is very busy translate in the
chat
yes die if I don't maybe
I think I would take the stick,
but I don't know if I'll use it
[music]
and now it takes up so much space
or whatever,
I'll take it and then I'll think about
it because I actually like it  I'm
really liking my setup right now,
I always find something
okay,
I'm so hungry,
clarifications,
sweet, oh cool, I can even get in here by
force
]
then I would put that in there now
I think
two lonely
ones in here
unfortunately one can against him but well so
now I'll do a few more three oh
wait actually double
one
and two and three is the question I'm
still using my bad luck against
Yes,
okay,
I'm going to
eat something frozen today, but at least I'll make myself
a fresh homemade
salad with a homemade dressing,
but we're out of it. I have
n't caught a frozen sliced ​​meat like that yet, actually spaetzle
with paprika sauce in a pan, something like that, yes,
you know that  something like that I really like something like this
these these pans for
warming up in the pan
the litter is my junk yes wait I
haven't really processed it yet
yes that's bad for me because I
work with a lot of small numbers no
numbers
um okay wait that's what we're doing here  in the
parts we
woah, you have to be able to work with it somehow,
um, there's something in there, oh [ __ ], how am
I supposed to
[music]
not now,
okay, [ __ ] man,
it's better to put it in poison
than in that,
well, I'll definitely do that
because at least it's straight
and that doesn't do anything for me anywhere else so
I put it in here I
at least earned money but
double standing
okay yes good good
let's fill it up first no it does
n't work infinitely
what do we have to divide here
[music]
he gives it anyway
My mouse is dying anyway, my mouse isn't working right now, okay,
everything's fine, everything's fine, yes, I
should have put some water on snake magic,
no matter, yes, because we need healing. It's gotten a
little more difficult,
but it's very interesting if you
use your head a little bit then
it's not all that  Problem so song
reduces damage by two from each
attack
but needs five exactly one 5
nope like that a thief a thief doesn't need iron
armor he already has someone a
thief with so have you seen they
usually have leather armor or
nothing at all
okay
what do you want
[music]
sorry, now I think maybe it's not
perfect but it's okay, the
main thing is that we do damage like that,
wait a minute,
I could have done that oh [ __ ],
yeah, okay, that's fine, I should do that now
four damage, yes
a few times
and that's
what he's doing
[Music]
dangerous dangerous
five damage locked in dice twice
there you can now then
[Music]
13 damage do the next turn 13
damage I survive but you mean you
13 damage
I can I can maybe
do something against him
[Music]
that there
[  Music]
[Music]
not that bad should I
listen to it again now or just full the
person
gives him four damage then
he has ten more,
yes we'll definitely get him the
next turn down but now it
won't
matter  It's the same thing
really
[music]
has done both now I was
n't paying attention at all
the gold
yes I don't need all that no
no no
at least now I should take the gold
okay yes good bye
still so much no was that just a
few  Opponents, let's take a look at the shops
here
[Music]
um
no, I need the lockpick, I
use it so much, but what's that
3:0 damage does,
no,
no, you, but I just
somehow hurt my thumb, but
I want that  don't have or
daudia okay
thank you for helping
mom dad what do we have here where to park
but two plus one okay somehow they
have a lot of equipment here
must things dice he had
something twice next round but I get
once per head
[music]
actually quite cool  I would
but if I, for example,
no we have to eat out which
situation I
would throw something in but yes I go with
my
latte and my lantern with me down
there the stars are shining down there
we are shining my light goes out I  I
'm going home, I've got the rubbish
out. I'm going home, I've got the
rubbish out.
We made lanterns back then in
kindergarten,
really nice lanterns and then it
was actually dark. We
went around with the lanterns
[music]
a real catcher
that was nice  I don't do that
anymore
so please share once or
what's the odd one oh yes
take this
okay
[music]
I want to have the two in the
next round or are fives
depending on what I want then the other has
double now
maybe
there or wait  I could also
get the lonely one here, I could now
get more ones and then I could
fill it up with six five and one
gets two single ones
or I'll just double the five
and second
[music]
OK, let's do that, I can do that
then I'll get the lonely one,
we'll do it like this, I'll get nothing at all,
nothing underneath,
wait, but I'll get it,
I could get another stake
back,
yes, why not two ones next time,
if not, whether that was really good,
lantern bath, it's on the 11th  November I do
n't even know who the date when it
was always made on November 11th
making lanterns that's a cute idea
I like these I like you these
craft streams but is it just that it
's a it's a
Roman Catholic holiday  or so
a Christian holiday recognize that
the English-speaking people
St Martin on the eleventh November device
[Music
] [
Music] [Music]
[Music]
inflict new damage or more
because I the next attack
yes  what
[ __ ]
[music]
but smart that was halfway smart
[ __ ]
if I die ham
[music]
less English more German okay so
I was just about to be okay
that's a good thing
if he still survives
[music]
yes here  If you have very little HP then
the music changes to a
heart-pounding
lantern festival, which is still an important
kindergarten today, so how do you know
that you are in kindergarten right now
[laughter]
so he gets ready damage
what what do I want to double
I have to see  probably in two
parts
but should I double the threesome beforehand
but then it won't do anything for me or unless
I put it in here but
well I'll definitely do that here
but like I want to double it before like I want to double it fully
maybe
twice, wait
But I already have one in here or
and then I'll share it
can regulate it a bit here okay
yeah okay so I should now I'm going to
dodge an attack or
actually I should now
survive in a relaxed manner
what happens what happens
wow had just
dodged damage or something like that
no okay that was I avoided the
silence or
did I avoid the silence
okay then everything is fine could
make it will
[music]
everything is good everything is good no stress no
do you know it all good I'm just
somehow so precise and straight
[  Laughter]
[Music]
yes well
back oh what's that showing
means that for example a
minimum 3 is no longer a minimum and
I can put in whatever I
want
two ones or others it's double
improvement
3 + 1
I need yours  Dice but also or
the lonely one I need you I have then
no
oh well that's free okay okay
good it
was so close
I have to say that I
might see a death coming on a bus in the future
[music]
now cowboy
sweet I would  first go this way
weak against fire
spot plus two I could heal myself
if I put a six in I don't
need any healing right now
but
you might still put the six in
because then I do sex damage,
wait a minute or I just divide
twice I divide once I  don't need
any healing here
[music]
[ __ ] that's not that good
ah[ __ ]
[music]
I can't actually get the two back then
oh I didn't know that in that case okay
okay okay
[music]
okay
not the best move but
yes, good, it's back, good, good, you're
very happy,
everyone turns green,
you know what, maybe now that we've
received so much damage from the last
opponent, it'll really
be like that all the time, then armor would
n't have been so unbeatable,
oh no, I do  I really
lost it oh so because it's here I
got two ones because of
course it goes in yes okay okay
the magician can fire that's actually
perfect that's what we should do
we have to fill it up with 12 okay
[music]
so and then so I think  quite well solved
then we'll get the ones here,
put the individual ones in here,
well the foursome is now useless
[music]
apart from that
I think it's good
haha ​​we burned two of them
didn't use them at all
but they he
[music]
[applause  ]
[Music]
OK
then let's go Gorgon,
what do we want to improve now
or do we want to save the improvement
in case I can buy something good
but let's see what we have to
use
[Music]
Put parts in three
Dice maybe that's even
surprisingly good
that
ah that wouldn't be once per
fight anymore but I can get each one
to choose from every round so I would say
either I should pick up
[music]
yes that way I'll get doubled again and again in the next round
[  Music]
or do I just want to get really crazy,
I'll do it, it's really cool,
I can be sure that I'll use it
too,
well now let's go
to the snowman first because it's level 4,
I can also heal myself. Baby
freezes  Roll the dice if it's odd, okay,
I only have even things
[music]
I have an idea, maybe I have
an idea, I have an idea. I want to
share it and
put in a single one, a six in the lockpick,
snake eyes together, but actually
I have to share these too  I have a lot
to drive I have nothing actually
that sucks
me it's pretty [ __ ] wait then
I'd rather double one
no it's all [ __ ] it's all [ __ ]
[ __ ]
what
but that probably makes the
most sense
[music]
[ __ ]
because the viruses  bring me there, well,
should I do it
[music]
I still have,
well, just give it to me then
Lucky this time
he just made a snow wave
okay at least
[music]
we'll share it,
we want to
have
one like that already  here
and
then and
want to double we
can still use bad luck
[music]
a strong poisoning he should
definitely go to the hospital
urgently ah [ __ ] okay that's
not so good now because I have nothing left
but that's still going to the next
round or
It's already over
as far as I know
it's not wasted
at least
[music]
should maybe
anyway
yeah yeah it doesn't matter we're
yeah I was just chilling no I
just let it happen like that
I need it urgently
here I can still 18 no I'll go
with it first  I don't waste anything
on the gargo, it seems very dangerous to me.
You
should I go to the cowboy first
because I think I would waste an HP
and that's what I don't like
because it's going to be so difficult, that's exactly what
I imagine, but whatever, we'll
just go up  something doesn't matter
[music]
at least three three damage rolls
again with a lower value
I get a new die and do
three damage but the new die will
be less than what I put in,
that's so
cool
[music]
what do I want next round
Maybe we made a threesome,
wow,
but only paid one poison, but
build on it until the next round,
please, what did I say,
you're so unfunny
[music]
that's why we have two dice, I know I'm
getting new ones all the time with the avalanche
[ __ ] man okay
[music  ]
what do I want what do I want when we do
it
[music] I
know I was here now somehow so
many options
but I don't think it's bad either
woah
[music]
given
it down I would say
[music]
but wait  Let's
do that
[music]
smart how smart I am because
I didn't take advantage of my bad luck haha
well done yes there is here
I can go home I don't need that and
that's an apple and then there's another
apple I think or maybe
not
yet  You don't need a lockpick, you
already have a trigger, damage
for every enemy, for
every bug, that's good because I work with
my
gift stacks
[Music]
interesting
so we double all the poison
I put that in instead of a
lantern  I haven't
really used that at all, not that actively,
I would say,
so
nicely organized, even
able to do that
and yes,
cowboy [ __ ], I don't have that much HP,
maybe we should get married after all,
maybe how much is that two gold, yes,
I need it,
okay surprise
comes along  Level Up Ball
would be good
HU what's the shooting iron that's new
his dog is behind his ears and
we shoot and his mother's shoes
because
he has two pistols
that's dangerous
you shouldn't give a cat two pistols Cats
are still very aggressive
danger cut to two Pistols
are you
let alone two
okay so
[music]
okay I don't have six
okay so put it but then I would
double heal and then share baby
[music]
oh
wait  That's hard now I want two
more in poison and then the many straight
or how I put the two in the ones
no I don't want that but
for example I want two maybe in there
and then couples then
[music]
so bad luck we record  In any case, okay
and then put this
in here okay okay then put the two in there
okay
but then I'll just do the count and
then we haven't lost anything a
lost left so well
[music]
use midnight clean food
this has to be done quickly here
[  Music]
[Music]
yes okay it always only takes a six
yes okay okay yes maybe
next time he won't get it was already very
lucky now
[music]
[music] there
is still more money yes well
[Music]
I would have a child
no
or
[Music]
I hope at the level up so yes good
yes once I can make a mistake
oh Erika
and a new command and what's here
now we get more of the [ __ ]
24 but
is
that's in harmony with the
other stuff I use but
24 an upgrade would be good isn't the next
level kind of a boss level
baby
what don't I use that often
maybe I should clean in queues
because if I really had that much
then  Can I always put that in the
plague
then I'd rather fill the plague
up with it too so queue and hopefully
if I still do that if
the boss doesn't come straight away and next time the
boss is oh it's expensive
[music]
yes yes
okay then  let's stick with it even if
it's in theory it's pretty
nice
okay let's see if I survive oh
FGO character
I don't know how to pronounce
that probably as a person
because now an iceland
I have a bad feeling
that feeling maybe  then I need a
first aid kit but 16
hey where am nice
i feeling
[music]
okay yes I hope I hope we do
n't mess this up
okay
I think I think I'm going to die
immune to bans and just I don't have
anything out of it
except I can freeze yours
use against you if you have something like that
we'll see after the breath of the wind
the song of the birds fighting
but also stock
market [ __ ]
[music]
I don't have it right now maybe
I'll get a foursome
okay let's start here
a foursome would have been nice
[  Music]
they're weak on the other hand looks a reason
okay yes well then
okay we already have five
and then I
just have that
can double them and put one in here
[applause]
at least
and then
[applause]
the 5 are totally wasted now too
[music  ]
Okay,
everything's fine,
baby, the game is very strange, I
'm just having fun with it, yes,
I made a mistake with the
fifth
[music]
3,
wait, it's full, the person here,
maybe one of them is, it has to
be a fiver, so that's okay  a
fiver in yes
that's not a not a five not a five
[music]
no okay cool cool cool cool cool
at least ah yes well then that would have been
if I hadn't known the others okay there
are no fifths
[music]
or I'll try it here
maximum 2
okay  that's that's everywhere two and
under a no it could be a six
or a 3 or 4 that's a
sexual 3 or 4 okay and that that went
so it was a second one yes that's
a sexual 3 or 4 and we have that
once in here
than I should double okay can
divide
but before I divide
I should divide then I
still don't see what it is
double 4
should I then put a four in there
but maybe I'd rather try it
first
and I'll divide one or  I should
try [ __ ] here once, okay, that's
not possible, so it's over a 2,
that's more than a two.
Should I try it here too,
that's more than a three,
maybe it's worth sharing
[applause]
no, that's worth it, wait, it's more
as a three it also has to be a 4 5 6
or something like that so
okay
now I have to think a lot
I share
I give this I put this in here
I think I'll put this in here
and then I share the foursome
so there
's
[music]
okay
and parts of it
okay okay okay
[music]
now she gets eight damage
you have to do it
no problem there isn't much done
tell us about monster man
yes then I would be unlucky
and try to put everything down with ones
but
then something will happen
Wait a minute then then then then then first of all
but should I have one a one
Dietrichshain so that I can divide it up again
but should I put the cheap ones in
or I mean it doesn't
actually make
much of a difference
individually
open the trigger first open it first like
that
[applause]
so she gets it  he now has a new
damage and oh they say already dead or
because
that's already
yes okay no
yes wonderful
[music]
cool
successful
[applause]
[music]
and that means it's time to turn
the wheel turn us out when it's on  one
empire shows then you get your
trillions and
it always goes to you where there is no
price. Version broke like and uh it
is always reset no
always like that
I'm a drum roll
[applause]
yes
don't worry, oh you'll be lucky again here
we'll be back soon with
more episodes when will I be lucky it
doesn't seem like I've
ever come
[applause]
yes that was so much fun
we can play that again
soon if you enjoyed it too
I had fun  made
yeah drive out i like this game like
you
[laughter] again again soon
soon now I'll make myself
something to eat
and we'll see each other tomorrow in the member
stream and in Pico Park on everything
channel I think in tomorrow Obi on  I
Mission
or
[Music]
History Thumbnails for a monkey have
time
Baby after opperson
Reservation modern 25 August
ine
[Music]
To-do lists and extreme
challenges
yes, so you don't know exactly yet
here you can't find out anything else
woah
Baby cute yes,
why think
[Music]
a magician a magician would be cool too, I
don't know what's next but I'm
very interested
okay then that's it. Thank God
I don't have to read super chats here
so now you can.
I think I'm waiting for the final list the
finalist the morning Fortress
[Music]
you it
should be
in en everyone
expedales and
[Music]
wait okay okay
Weather that
talk ahead that was wrong
[Music]
on each side that yes to that
[Laughter]
and in German we say a Germany
say goodbye
[music] it
was fun bye goodnight bye
bye bye well I almost wanted to
go to the English ending no no no
[music]