[Music]
Ah
[
Music] Ha [Music]
[Music] [Applause] [Music] Oh [Music] [Applause] [Music] Yo [Music] [Music
]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause  ]
[Applause]
[Music]
H
A
[Music] [
Music] [Applause] A [Music]
A
[Music]
[Applause]
A
[Music]
O
[Applause]
[Music]
A
[Applause]
[Music]
A
H
[Music]
O
[
Music]
Music] [Applause] [Music]
O
[Music]
DET
White Team  Everyone is here, so
display Display Are you in the front room?
Haa  Ah
Manekata-sensei Yes, sir, I'm not a teacher, but I can't come here by chance. Hello, are you all here? Is everyone there? It's okay, sir. I'm sure. Please take attendance, sir. Well, I'll go. Then, White group.  I
'm going from A, I'm
hungry, please. I
'm Hello,
Senpai. Thank you very much, Iame-senpai. I'm here, Kanata-san. Hello, please.  Temui-chan, yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa a
a a a a a A a A A Ame-chan Ame-chan, Ame-chan
is coming, I'm going to do it.  Yes, yes,
yes, B's Hotenchoco-sensei. Ah, I
'm
here. Izu-chan is Azuki Azuki.
Wish, wish, captain, hello, captain
Hello, hello, fight fight, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
[Music]
Yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, do your best to flow up
[Music]
Thank you, umm,
can I go here too? Those who went  I
'm sorry, I think I should go.Senpai: I'm sorry, but I'm the second most senior.
[Music]
Okay, so I'd like to cover Raden's text
a little bit,
so I'd appreciate it if you could help me out. It
seems that senior's horse has disappeared,
so I'm off to Holomen hunting,
Raden.  chan will be appearing, but I'll be
taking your place
as a hunter, and the maki
line will be a secret, so I guess it's a secret,
but what's going to happen is a secret.
I'm looking forward to seeing if Kanata is wandering around alone
or if someone will come. I'd
like to see her working hard on her own too.
Maybe she'll be taking everyone's camera.  There
's a spy here. There's a
spy here. There
's a spy here. There's a spy.
Go away.
Here in the white group's waiting room. This is the classroom.
So now everyone is waiting. Well, we're
good at competitions, right? There's no one here. I'm
really curious, but it looks like
everyone's here.
Good, good, good, good.  It's a good thing,
everyone gather together. Let's put the
board up.
[Music]
It's impossible, we can't do it. We
can't do it.
[Music]
So, what should we do?
How can we
use the two-handed signboard?
I do
n't know, I'm
pretending
[Music]
I've come to graduate school, everyone's here, it's amazing.
Yellow is so
amazing. Where should we go scouting?
Which one is
red? I wonder what everyone in red is like.
[Music]
Yeah, everyone's having a
lot of trouble
[Music]
[Laughter]
Well, probably the main thing is that even during practice, the Riguro
guys were getting into a lot of trouble,
right? It was all the Riguro guys,
right?  I
can't take the signboard that I'm holding in my left hand all day today, but I can't take it off. There
's a huge uproar and I can't take it off.
Well, it's not only good that I can't take it off, it's
true.  No, it's no good, but what the
hell are you holding this thing? It's terrible, everyone is fixed to the board. Is this really true? I wonder
if it's okay to hold it in a competition. No, maybe the
signboard has a reset function built into it.  I
think it's okay because I think it's working,
but when you're infected, it's probably your left hand all the time, but it's
okay because I don't know Minecraft.
As expected of one of the creators of Minecraft, it looks like it's happening again. I'll
debug it. Good luck
this time too.  I want to do my best as a dobaku, and he's
amazing and always tells me everything.Isn't there an
author included?I do
n't think there's an author, so it's true.  Is that
true? Is it
true that Minecraft made it?
Well, next time, why don't you
carry it?
But you know what? I don't know. It's terrible. What's wrong with
this? We're a little
camera.  I don't know, but I
can hear it. I can't hear it. I
heard a voice that sounded like Kasuri's senpai, but I'm
not mistaken.
What's wrong with the internal broadcast?
Well then, I think I'll call out to you.
So everyone in the morning,
please, the starting place is Annas,
so don't worry, let's
go, let's go, let's go, it's white, it's white. Merle
Meruru is red. Merle, yes, memeko
[Music]  ] It's
over there, it's over there, mememe, it's over
here
That dodging group fell
[Music]
[Applause]
Even now, you're a genius. Books are lined up.  We
're lined up. Let's do our best to
get in line. Let's get
together here. Let's get together here. Mom and I are here.
11. I say yes. Next, everyone from the white group,
please come in.
Yes
[Applause]  ]
[Music]
Yes, it's the white of power, that's good. Finally, you can take care of that yellow group.
He's
okay, Kashio-chan is hiding,
and so are
you.
Well, I just realized that it's me. I'm sure the
camera was set up for this route, but I
can't pass anything.
There are so many people who beat me up. It's crazy how many people are cracking up. The white group
is so beautiful.  Yes, it's a serious frame.
It's called a serious frame. Kanashi-chan, who is in the serious frame, is the only one
with a pink sign. It's a
book. It's a yellow board. Is that what it's about?
Well, there wasn't a white sign, so they
held the signboard. So, first of all, I would like to ask everyone from Polo Live Grand Sports Day to
give their greetings for the tournament. Hello
everyone!
Hello everyone! Hello everyone!
Thank you very much. I know you are busy,
but I believe that you have really helped each other, seniors and juniors, and
have encouraged each other in practice and so on,
but today is the real day, so I need everyone's help.  I
hope that everyone will give it their all and come out victorious. First of all,
everyone should have fun and aim to win.
So, everyone, please enjoy yourself.
Thank you very much for your support today.
Thank you very much.  Thank you very
much. Next, we have received a message from Mr. Yago, the president of Cover Co., Ltd. Click
here to see Ekononi Hai.
Yes, please take a look. Thank you for your
hard work. It's Paba Tori's Butashutita Sports Day.
Speaking of sports day, it's neck exercises. Hey, look at me Lulu. I don't know who's doing what, but who's preparing. Thank you very much for your hard work. At today's sports day, let's cooperate with each other,
encourage each other, and fight bravely until the end.
And as usual, I would like to say, ``
Thank
you very much. Thank you very much.'' I hope that you will pay attention to and support the hard work of the
members.To all the members, please be careful.I would like to
conclude my greetings for the tournament by saying, ``Thank you very much.Thank you very much.''
Masu
I'm guessing that you're hurt or not. It's a fist
fight. I'm going to
go, Mr. Chate.
Please do
your best. Good luck.
Kuite. This is my number one,
so there's no doubt about it. Please, please,
do it.  Please, do your best, please.
[Music]
[Music] Don't worry, my
ears are going crazy.
Usa Bells, it's
okay.
Please, I'll be fine. I'll come more and more.  It's
so bad, it's so bad, you can't listen to what the teacher is saying
Yasu Hasukamon come on
Hussu is good Good luck
Good job Good luck Good luck, do your
best,
okay if I ask you to act as a player teacher? Yes, please.
Sensei, all of us players are Hololive.
As a member, the teacher takes over the sportsmanship and
uses Dodo to fight.November
4, Red team representative virtue and White team representative A
yellow representative Hiroshi spells
Ye
[Applause]
Okay, it's
okay. Who threw the bread? Let's talk from
here. Thank you very much.
[Music]
Excuse me, Teru.
Masu Technician Channel White Team Contestants
Please channel.  I'm going to do it. The
sound quality of the sports day is so real.
The room is a little bit out of place. It's so realistic.
Kiara is in round 2, so I guess it's okay if she doesn't enter yet.
Eh, Channel Gancha 1 Comment Hunting
Only those who are in the first game will be able to enter. I'm
going to go to the channel of the white group contestants, so uh, Ame-chan,
Kaela,
Nerisa,
TE Bye, Baian,
Aa,
Senpai
[Music]
Hello, no,
I
understand
fine
DoNoIgettoI
pringWehaveagood
[Music]
time
SPUp
[Music]
GuysTeam
Team
[Music]
H
OKhandhave
leashCAPhave
on
O
WINwehavekylanonono
Please
carrynejnejnejIbea
sweatygamerTooLateI sleeplast
nightyouneedtobe
verycompetitiveTry
JustForYouYESYESYES
readyJAA
Batmanwhat
happeningWeGGet
instructionsrightJA
rightI
think
okayWhereismyMy
teammates
WeFNOT
SURE
[Music]
weck
mck
ON
Yeah, you mean over here? Hello,
hello,
hello, here.  I wonder
if it's here or here. It's the white group. So, the fugitives who run away are
on this channel. It's like that
. It's the opposite. It's difficult, it's
difficult, it's difficult today, it's difficult today. I wanted to do this number 1,
then it's
number 1.  That's the
biggest thing I couldn't do because I was like, ``I can't do
this.'' It's true that if I can get over this, I
can do it. Well, now I know perfectly well, so
please wait.  picture
What is clear is that at the beginning, Red is the hunter, and
all the members of the white group run away.Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, they
are all contestants.That's
right, there are two remaining Whites who look like they're going to be
infected.  I wonder if we'll break up because of the hunters.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[Music]
Only the hunters are
fine.
[Music]
Yeah, yeah. Only the hunters are good-looking. Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Hello morBaresavethe
dayAHIam
ready
What?
Whatwelljustus
AgainYeah
[Laughs]
[Music]
maybeckI
knowo
pry
You're passing by
Yeah, I don't know
Japanese I don't understand Japanese
[Music]
Down
Going
regev
JA
happ
least
SorryIformy
Cool
[Music]  ]
Kare
Cool
Cute
[Laughter]
areyou
[Music]
runningThankyoufor
LetMe
OnJiOaMizuSempaiMizuoSepaiIgot
stuffIknow
goodIthink
soYes
Q
YesGODNodamageNo
damageohmygodIeven
throwthestuffinmy
inventory
WAH
MoonminecSKYJA
BeautifulClear
Minecraft
SKYthatwasanice
SchoolWecameoutof
veryniceSchoolIwasa
littlesadTherewasa
thirdFLOORIwantedto
gochecktheThird
FLOOR bathroom
hanM
MDown
here
Theskyis
Clearbeautiful
[Music]
day
OhWellguessWe
registeredWhereismy
nameokay
okay
English
spidEnglishnono
NoNoNoNoMAH
[Laughs]
Fin
JAILIThinkWethe
huntersbutIthought
weweresupposedToBe
huntersSosurprise
I
okayokay [Music
] [Music] engl W JAIthink weweBreakOut anyway [Music] hveAreYouWhyare you knowIknow Nowwanttoprotect MeWhat is locked time [Music] [
Music]
nice
CageCage
Cage
nice crackle
crackle
[Music]
US
[Music] I feel
like O is cheering for me
[Laughs]
Dao should also be given a bonus with Kiara Kiara Plus,
no, no, he's doing his best.  It's
fun
Emou Hall Live English I do
n't think it'll ever appear again.It's
true that the same song won't appear twice or even three times.  I don't
know if it's possible,
but I think it's possible that there will be tall people.To be honest, I do
n't remember any taller people.To be honest, I
'd have to bring someone who is reasonably tall,
but there are very few people over 160cm tall.  From
Hololive, everyone is pretty tall.It's because they're short.It
's because of their eyes that they're 149.It's a bit strange.They're
following me, right?No, there aren't many of them.
Nogasa is in her 150s, so I would like to interview everyone from the white group.Yes, the
first attempt is Hae,
Nerisa, and A are the three overseas members.But I would like to
ask you about the second time,
Hunter.A, the
second attempt.  I'm going to introduce Mr. Hunter in the eyes a little bit.Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
How are you feeling?
Do you have any enthusiasm or a strategy? I
'm going to try and catch all of them, but if I'm off, I won't be caught. It's a plan. It's our second game, and we're going to use all our strength to catch everyone.  It's a
battle where no one will win if you hit it, but the money is
too much because you're running out of
money. The Wight team is that powerful.
Surprisingly, they're able to get through it with their help.
What did you think when you saw the topic earlier? I
thought I might go.
What about Amoiya and Mio-senpai, and
who is the cutest member of the group that Mio-senpai would want to protect
?  Yeah, who's that?
Yes, I was included, right? Oh
dear, how about that? Don't worry about it, you guys are in trouble
. I wonder if the rest is good morning. You might know this,
believe me.  Masu  That's
strange. Yes, please
do your best. Please do your best.
Yes, thank you. Yes, thank you. Who is the one doing the voice?
But, thank you
very much. So, everyone, please stand by. Yes, that
means yes, then no.
No matter what, it's only the people who watched the first game. It's
embarrassing. I just watched it.
Sorry for the rant. Sorry,
Noil, Sanka is from the original channel, White Group AB.  I'm
sorry to go back to your channel.
It's okay.
Please do your best. Excuse me. Yes, I'll be back.
[Music]
JGOacrossICEand
SN
[Music]
No
[Laughs]
[Music]
PRWeWhiteTeam
GO
[Music]
JELLYIwantto
eat
TastyMjell
WAstopagood
ideaILike
[Music]
That
Cute
SL
AlwaysGood
Ideas
you
VOICESSpace
[Music]
BAR
OK
ShootIknow
[Music]
times
YES
[Music]
K
ThisiswhydidThe
OtherTeamgettheen
membersonmakeme
[Music]
think
[Laughter]
Suck
manshorthairJA
ICEWeONE
[Music]
POINT
[Music] [
Music]
NEXT WOW
MheSoEasyto
remember
welltimetogohidein
Shame
JA
[Music]
JAJA
[Laughter]
[Music]
JATry
Team
But actually, that strategy was power.
Well, I'm using all my power. It's a strategy. I don't like it,
but maybe it'll work. I see.
So, let's
go to the interview. To the
white guys, how
was it?
Hello hello
Ha it was difficult
Dical Yes it's
difficult If you touch that board it'll be so signboard
Touch
[Music]
Oh touch Oh Holo kids got it
Holo Holo live kit
Holo It's
difficult Holo kids first time Holo kids Switzerland
Switzerland Switzerland first Holo kids o
Kizu Matsuri is Eroga Matsuri is No Holo Kids, Kino
Kids No Kids, What Festival is Shrine Maiden, I
thought she had a big sister feel,
but it seems like it is.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you, please do your best.Continue to
do so, and the white team
was able to catch two people.What is this?
What is this?
[Music]
needcckthe
sign
also
Yes
OK
[Music]
Worry
Hardyousomeweird
promsandlikeforthefortheshortcutdid
oneofyoutrytoputin for
shortcut
wasshort
[Music]
hair so-so
Mafu count no problem nononopno problem
yes no problem toUS
no problem you also like it
Kana-chan that 5th place nonoro
flame noroflam hey hey hey look
Please, look, look, this poor person is
feeling like this. What,
what,
dododo?
What kind of situation is this? I really want to do it.
Open this door,
open it, close it immediately, and the
eyes of the door are right in front of the closed door. If you
do this, you'll be able to get in. That's nice. That's amazing. That's
cool.  It's nice to have a smell of earth.It
smells like earth.It
smells so bad.What are you
doing,
Kiki-kun?
Wow, it's so heavy, it's a
little too
close. The contact between the two is too close. It
was so cute when they were lying side by side. Yes, it
was cute. They were so
cute. They were so cute.
They could sell them as cushions as they are.  It's true that these are really cute. They're probably
selling them. They're really cute. There
's no head.
Yellow Yellow Yellow If you run away, you'll
run away.  I'll
do my best
[Music] I'll do my best, I'll
run away. I
want to go to Korea, but I can't.
No, no, only those who run away, only those who run away.  It
might
be hot tomorrow.
[Music]
It's coming. It's
coming.
Run away,
run away.
[Music] It's
hidden even in the rocks.
Do your appeal
Nere, it's new, it's new, it's
changing, changing, changing, changing
[Music]
0 I'm sorry
Hey, that guy who caught me was completely ignored. There's no way
I can do that. Wait a minute, Nagashiro.
Wait a minute.
158 Please excuse me. I
wonder if it's safe. Oh,
hide it, hide it.
165 That's right. Hide it, hide
it. It came, it came, it came.  I
feel like there's something wrong here.
No, no, no, no. No
one caught that. It
was Chu.
But I'm sorry for the person who did it.
[Music]
Chu  Hey, you should
be neat and clean.
No matter what you do, you're neat and clean. I'm
starting to get dissatisfied with how neat you are.  It's
nice, it's nice, it's nice. I didn't get caught. I didn't get caught. That's why. I don't want to play games and run away from it, but I'm sure she's definitely in the group. She ran away after joining, so that's great. It's cute that she's so self-aware.  It's
so scary and neat. You're so neat. Don't you want to change your personality? It's
definitely neat. That's great. It's
cute that you ran away and are great.
Hey, Iro-chan, you have to run away, neat and clean. I
didn't think you'd get caught.
[Music] The
yellow color was really strong. They
caught you, which was amazing
.
Even so, you've made a lot of entries, everyone.
Stand up!
[Music]
Taru:
When I was an older sister, I wanted to be chosen because I was the group leader,
or because I was a sexy woman, or whatever. Do
n't say that. I'm
pretty sure I wasn't even chosen for my height.  That's
true,
but since Polka misunderstood me, I
was able to get a little closer to the cage, right? The
cage is really small.
Once you're caught, you
won't be able to run away during the game, right? The
hunters will have to do their best to run away until the next game starts.
Mio-senpai, who's thinking that? Next time, Mio.  There
was a moment when I didn't, oh
yeah, that's right, that's what I mean, I'm going to change it, oh yeah, I'm going to
change it, I'm sure it's going to change, there's a completely different possibility,
but I want you to
have it [Music] Oh, I want you to wait.
[Music]
Hey, okay, shoes,
shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes, shoes.  It's
kind of creepy that the slopes are trying to overlap next to Xiontepa,
but I don't like it, everyone is
looking at me. It's so cute. Are they standing side by side?
So cute, someone is mine.  Let's line up side by side and let's
set it up Oh, maybe we'll do it again
and try again Oh yeah yeah yeah okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
Okay,
ok, oh, oh
, oh, it doesn't matter at all, but Subaru-senpai
's nipples are missing. Yeah, they're
missing. Even though I made them, they're gone. I even chatted with him and
asked him things like how many nipples does Subaru-senpai have?
Why is there anything other than Sanani?
Birds are eggs, so it's no surprise that they don't exist.
[Music]
Birds have become specialties because they're eggs.
But it's 2019. It's 2019. It's
2019. It's 2019. It
's 2020.
Everyone, run away. Run
away.
[Laughter]
[Music]  It's
2019, and it's been a long time since I've been in the middle of a
long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time.
Oh, run away, run away, run away, run away.
There's a lot of people here. There's a lot of Tess here. It's a
difficult song and it's surprisingly easy. There are
more than 3 stations, and
I'm releasing an album that I didn't have the image of.
Artist: I
was arrested because I was interrogated, and I was arrested.
[Music] I was
caught doing Minecraft, so I
pretended I had been arrested before, and I was
arrested like this.
I've never been bothered by it. I haven't seen it at all.
Surprisingly, I'm surprised that I haven't been arrested yet.
[Music]
Nao also falls into the same category.  I ran away. No,
Suisui
[Music] I wonder if you're
moving
too. Thank you again. Only the hunters should stay here.
Please move. I understand.
Bye-bye. Good luck.
[Music]
Good bye
Bye, this is the prison you worked so hard for. I'll
give you this too. It's Korean. You're
giving it to me. You're giving it to the prisoners. You're
giving it to the prisoners. I've gotten used to
it.  The
shot of the candy that the teacher gave me in Korea is really, really surreal, but
this Noel-senpai has a great sense of lighting and photography.  It
's a net shot. I want you to
do your best in the second game. Let's cheer you on. Do your
best. Wait, wait, I accidentally shot the concentrator.
Wait a minute. The mouse is
drenched. What's the situation?
Last
time, I mistakenly fired a disinfectant,
and the mouse got all wet.
Hey, I was stroking that. I was
stroking it, and then it hit me.
[Laughs]
Hey,
cute.
Yeah, it's looking down, it's looking down. Wait,
cute. It's moving. It's moving. Oh, it's moving.  Oh so cute
, so cute, so cute, little Gura-chan,
that's Gras Graspa, isn't Gura-chan going to show up on the hour
? Are you sure it's okay? It's true that you're here. When I
woke up, I was a contestant. Maybe so,
maybe, a fugitive.  I am currently entering  It
was written that I was probably taken away automatically. I'm being
taken away. Pin, do your
best. A terrible scuffle has started
[music] It
's true. I didn't realize it. The one with the ugly Subaru statue
was taken. It
sounded like YouTube.
Teacher, yeah,
let's read
it, oh, it's coming, it's
coming, it's starting, is it starting? Something, something, something
? There's
so much of this, so much of this
[Music]
Everyone
Who should I catch?
[Music]
Come in, you're hiding here. Why are you
going to come in here? I
thought you were in a corner. You're in a corner. It's
unexpected. You're making a lot of mistakes. That's
right. Sui looks expensive.  Yeah, that
's true.Suchi-senpai seems expensive, but hey, he's here.Nice
, good, good, good, good,
good.It's early.Three people have already been caught.Go
and catch the goofy ears.Here we go.  It's
early, it's early, Fuwamoko-san, it's alright,
who's Fuwamoko-san catching? I ca
n't see her name.
Naekari-chan is tall, isn't she? She's tall, she's
tall, ah,
ah,
ah, she's
so good at catching cotton. It's
so good.  I really wanted to go to Nakemi.I wonder
if the Ekemi people have something like Mimimi.I don't
know if it's the one in Akome who isn't there unexpectedly.
Yeah, that's true, I'm sure, that's right, that's right, now I'm just looking at my ears, right, right
, that's right, Fara, that
corner of Senpai is not that of a furry guy.  There's a
lot of this. It
feels good. It's pretty blurry. The title is
good. It's
finally here. It's so good. It's so catchy. It's so strong. It's so catchy.
That senpai is also an idiot.
11 He's not even an idiot. It's so
good. Let's go. It's not like he's gone. No, he's just an idiot. He's just an idiot. He's on the
right, and Mercury-senpai is different. He's here.
I'm in a red place here,
do your best, it's so nice, so nice, so nice, so nice, so nice, so nice, that
's the best record, that's the best record, maybe the best record right now.
Tae
[Music] That's
amazing, isn't it?
Good, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, please
go away. Oh,
wow,
what happened earlier? What's going on? Wait a minute, Choco-sensei
's photo is too good.  This is really
amazing. I
just got it. I'm going to
send it to the store.
This is so good. Oh,
wow.
[Music]
Oh, it's
mostly blurry.
[Music] I'm so
tired. I'm looking at it mostly blurry,
but I'm really disappointed. It's surprisingly rare to have ears like this. I was
a bit surprised when a senior student called me "early,"
but
this is just for the record.  That's right, I see that everyone is a bit of a
blur, and they don't have a lot of senility.Maybe that's why they're not good at it,
but if Mio-senpai judges me, there
must be a lot of people who are not very good at it.  Maybe
it's because they're going to attack me with anything. That's right. Mio-chan, Kamio-chan
,
Mirando, in a sense, it was a bonus stage. I'm
sure they
were able to do that, but if they do it, they'll
run away all at once.
Don't run away, do your best, do your best, let's do our best. Let's go, oh, let's do our best.
After all, it was a little hard to catch them when they were all gathered in one place. It's
dangerous.
Hide it. Hide it. Don't hide it. It's dangerous. Hide
it. Hide it.
Seniors.
Awakening, someone has been caught, Aya, I
was told,
Hide it
[Music]
Hide it like that, I'm about 0 to 2 years old. That's right,
it's 4. I
'll hide it
. Be careful
[Music]
Kick me, I've been caught, I've been arrested.  I caught it.
Good
hair. I can tell when I see it.
[Music]
I
understand. I
'll protect you. Wow,
that's true.
Silver hair, silver hair.
[Applause] Oh, that's
dangerous.
[Music]  It's
the same, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I tried to
say no,
but it's
no good. It's a shame. It's such a shame. I have so much time. I have so much
free time. You can catch me. I want to be here. I want to be
here.  I'm sure
he's sexy, but I completely ignore the fact that he's sexy,
and I look at his name, which
I did
n't even mention.
I'm here
too [Music] It's so nice, so
nice. There were 14 of us here.
13 people.
[Music] I
really wanted to be a little surprised. No, I
should have hidden behind him. No, no, no, no, he wasn't
even drinking water. Then, I thrust in.
[Music] Well, I'm
disappointed in the person who explained it. Are you going
to go back to the team? Okay.
Move
[Music]
Oh,
oh,
next time, Lome hunting is over. Are you going to
tell me the results now?
What's the point?  I'm curious about the point.
Usually at a sports day, they tell you at the beginning, but they don't
tell you anything during the middle of
the day.  I'm
sure what's the next lesson, I wonder if it's a floor-up. Stop it,
stop it. My stomach
is fine, but I feel like I'm going to be nervous. I've
been practicing a lot, like I did today.
My opponent has beaten me, so I've had a lot of trouble with that opponent.  We were
practicing together, and we were
winning quite a bit.We were doing really well in practice,
but in real life, the actual performance
might be different.No, it's okay, it's okay.  It
's the same shape, but the first battle is really good.Mercury-
senpai and Miji-chan are
really good, and the dangerous battle is Roboko-
san.Oh yeah, but Roboko-chan, I was trying to teach her earlier, but she was pretty good
at it right away.
But I feel like I just started practicing today. I
see, it's beginner's luck. Yeah, I can
do it, I can do it, blah, blah,
passion,
passion, blah, blah, seriously.
It's scary that Team B and White are currently in 2nd place.
Yeah, that's really nice. Nice, nice, nice. Nice,
nice, great. The
information for Taohora-up has arrived. Hey,
yes, 6 contestants, 2 to 2 each, please move quickly.
For now, I'll go upstairs, or I'll go upstairs. Oh, I
see. The venue. Well, I guess I
should just go downstairs. Above.
That voice guy.
Yeah, the voice is like that, but that's it.
Chiara is moving. It's Chiara's second
match, so I'll see if she's okay. I guess I'll have another interview.
Well then, I'm off to
go. I'll be there, then I'll be
there.
Wow, this is what everyone's going to do.  Now that Chiara is
gone, I'm going to
say something that might put some pressure on me,
but I'm sure there are so many people here all the time.  You're
looking at me like this, you're crazy. That's
definitely true lol. When you look down, everyone is paying attention to you. It's
hard for people with phobias. It's
amazing. You really have courage. You've
been practicing so much.  Yeah, really,
yeah. It's definitely more difficult than just
practicing a little bit here. Yeah, it
was only
for a moment, but it was totally difficult. Where's that leg?
[Laughs] It's
definitely difficult.  I think it
was last year, or something like that with Birdman.That kind of
attention is hard, and it takes a moment of hard work,
or rather, a huge defeat is decided in an instant,
so in a sense, it's 300 seconds, so it's like 5 minutes.Yeah,
yeah.  I wonder what that was all about. I
think it would be better if Sa-chan cheered me on. Yesterday
at practice, I wonder if he'll come back after all.  I
can't even see up here
anymore. How far
can Boko-san and Chan go? I have to look up.
[Laughs] I'll do my
best.
[Music] I'll
make you a hamburger.
Happ
[Music]
Miss.
Instead, I became the
person in charge of the launch.
What is the best thing to do with Neo? Isn't it Nae?
Live Yakiniku or reluctantly
? That's fine. Nene-chan is in the book, but
there are others.
No, I
might have to ask for something every time.
Only those who can go
can do it first and add more later
.
[Music] I'm
sure it's
a bit off after this.  It may be that,
but after the line is sad, the voice is over, and after that, it
was like a spring chemical trille yes yes yes,
so it was surprisingly
certainly once.  It's probably
only once, right? It's only
one time, so it's just two of them. I
feel like I can go. It's
definitely
starting. It's a gentle senior. It's starting.
Roboco-san.  Do your best,
do your best, do your best, Roboco, do your best, it's going
well, it's going well, keep on doing your best,
Roboco, you're a woman who can fly, Dashi-chan is really good, you're
worried about whether it's good or not, because there are people who are good at it.
Oh, I've said it so much, I'm sure it
's true. Good luck, Roboco-san. If you
do your best and make it to 200m, Roboco,
Roboco,
Bokoboko, the
points will be determined by the last place or so. That
doesn't mean it's fast. Everyone
did 200m.  I don't think
so. Sa-chan said earlier that she felt like she was a senior, but it feels really good.  I'm
sure you're used to this kind of thing because you've competed in all sorts of competitions and competitions. It's
not like you're nervous at all. You're not nervous at all, Bib
. Good
luck, Bib. 4th
point. Nice and nice.
Good luck,
senpai.  It's
good that you're doing your best.
Even though you've been working hard and working hard, you haven't fallen down. You're
calm. Your
voice is definitely getting better and better.  You're going
to do your best, try your best, try your best, do your best, try your best, just a little bit more, then, you can go for another 30 meters [Music] You can go, Roboco, do your best, you've got a jet, you can do your best, Roboco.
Even if it's a checkpoint,
Be,
that's about it. I'm really calming down and there's
10 meters left to fall, 10 meters to go, and
6 meters to go. Oh, do your best, do your best,
Ravanice.
Goal is too nice,
nice, nice Ru Sui-chan and Ai-chan have a little more to go, but there's
still a little more to go. There
's still 90 seconds left, so there's more than a minute left. Mizu-
senpai does her best and perseveres, but it's
always the same in the actual performance.  After all, there's a lot of pressure.
Do your best. Do your best.
Do your best. Do your best, Sui-chan, Sui-chan, do your best.
The purpose of the game has changed somehow, but
I think everyone will want to do more.
Koreun Sui-chan today
as well, we're all cute and fair here.
PR is too high
Teunmin 200
Nice, kai is nice, Roboco senpai is nice,
Bib No, but on the contrary, the pressure is coming to the people in the second tier.
Hey, Kiara. Do your best,
do your best.
[Music]  ]
Nice this,
yeah, yeah, that's pretty cool, isn't it? It's hot, Neri
Ruaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
,, this is
where you can watch the battle after doing your best with my sparkling  It's
looking good, it's looking good here, it's looking
really good here, it's feeling pretty good, it's a little different, it's good, I
'm pushing it a little,
big
mama,
do your best in Japanese, do you want to see or see?
[Music]
Now, round 2, round 2, Chiara, Chiara.
Kirara Kirara, this is an infected
person. If I touch the signboard, I'll
tell you in the comments if it's going to be accepted. Is this the one
who completed it?
Where is the right person to press this? The
signboard on the far right
Entries were all doing this, so there were
n't many people like this Entry list No, it's the sign on the left.
Natoru Honmaya
Achando It
's okay, you're climbing smoothly. It
's scary. You can't see it as a competitor.
Ae Kono Sananka soft serve ice
cream Soft cream Ah, soft serve ice cream It looks
like you're climbing really smoothly It
's amazing Kira Now you
're at the earliest checkpoint
Mao,
there's a second check It's
nice
[Music]
[Music] [  [
Laughter]
[Music] It's
too early, it's too early, I've fallen even once,
but I'm trying my best, step by step,
definitely, definitely
[Music]
Okay, I'm glad to know that I can do this. I'm
grateful. I'm thankful. I just look up at the sky.  I'm
looking up at something that's completely different from the one I'm in. No, it's seriously different.
This is going
up fast.
Chiara-senpai is doing her best and it's definitely like this. Oh, I
didn't know, I didn't know.
This is placed in the spiral field.  I'm making a lot of mistakes on this one,
oh, it's flying all at once, it
's all colored truth from here
, but it doesn't matter where I'm going
[Music] It's
poisonous, it's
a little weird here
[Music]  It's
like you can't see us in Bolis.
Well, we're floating right now. We're floating.
Everyone's face is so
amazing. No mistakes, no mistakes
. I haven't fallen once.
This is the final point.  Well,
yeah, yeah, there was a scuffle here as well,
so I guess it was assumed that if he was dropped, he would get
mad.I wonder what it would be like, but it would be the distance he was at in the last seconds, so yeah,
yeah.
Well, that's the
point. It's better to
give in and give in
than to let everyone fall. It's
true that it's too likely to fall. Do
your best, 50 seconds left. This
is your whole life.
[Music]
Try hard, you can do it, so you won't fall again.
Asada, do your best, both of
you. Anio, you're here. You're coming. Are you both
going up together? Let's go
together.
Hey, black one,
do your best. Do your best.
7 seconds 4 A 3 2
I see, I'm sorry, it's a little more,
it's going down.
Yeah, next is the fang line or the fan
line. Yeah, let's go, let's
go. It looks like it's
going to be a mess. There are also pairs like A and B that are the same.  Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it looks like the
leader is going to do his best, but Choco-sensei wants to notice that Choco-sensei is
stuck in that butt.
If the thing on the screen that appears on the other side of the broadcast is the point of follow-up, the white group's
points are now 20 and the number 1
point has come out now, so the floor-up is probably the number
one point number.  Are you
here? I can catch up with you.
Nice fight, nice, nice,
nice.
Nice. You haven't come back yet. I'm
back. I wonder if you're still doing interviews. Yeah,
that's still not the case. Our white team.
Only the two of them are doing well.  I'm eavesdropping
on the mountain. I'm standing in the mountain, I'm standing in the mountain, I'm in the mountain, I'm in the middle of
the day, I'm in the middle of the day.  I didn't
make any mistakes, that's great.
Nice. The White team is currently in 1st place. It
was a pretty close battle, but White: 40 Yellow:
38 Red: 37. We did it. Nice, Nice. Nice
team: 4 points. Yellow: 38.
Hehe. Let's go!  Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice,
this is going to happen to our princess guards and
princess guards.  It
's a bad thing, isn't it? It looks like it's going to be a rele, because
there will be a general guard in the battle, but it's still a long time ago.  That's
right, I'm starting to feel
pressured. I wonder if there's a pair to put on the pressure.
Yeah, I was paired with Ra-chan, so I wonder what's going to happen. I
wonder what's going on. Thank you for your hard work, Ao.  Thank you for your
hard work. I'm
looking at you here, Mom.
So, here is the interim announcement of the overall specific.
Here is the first overall score. Well,
that's a good thing. 1st place was 40.
3 points for each item,
then let's move on to the next competition venue.
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh yeah, that's what they announced.  It's
out, it's out, it's out, it's out, it's out, it's out, it's out, it's out, it's out, it's out, it's out, it's going out, it's
going to be white, it's going to
be 2 overall.  I said, I can't
stop, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, please do your
best, I
'm going to ride, I'm going to ride, I'm going to ride, I'm sorry, it
's not the first, it's not the first  I'm the
first one, I don't want to do it, I don't want to
do it. Yes, it's on the right. I'm going to go here and there. That's cute, that's what I
did. Oh, okay, the first one was tomorrow. Nice, nice,
nice, cute. Nice, nice, cute.
No, it's not like you're going to ride on top of it.The
person who rides like that while holding the star.Ah
, wait, the
general may be on top.The general is on top.The person who is clicked should be the one who enters.
[Laughter]
[Music] I wonder
if that person will come already?
Will my partner come? Is
there someone there?
Your pair of ``Soruka''
wander around everyone like this
[laughing] It would be better to
prepare a cage,
but maybe you want a cage.
Mumble
[Music]
Please release the Kadaisho Dante
Oh, it's okay
know
Oh
[Music]
Be
Oe Kata-
sama Where's your eyes? In front of me,
here, here, here, everyone, everyone, everyone is
getting closer and closer.
Awesome, I can see where you are, here,
here, here, here, here, pain, pain, pain, here and there.
What, just press the same part again in that book
just
P
just nice
[laughing]
[music]
Nice.
Wait a minute, did you go there in that outfit?
Yes, you came in a suit. You look strong. It's
amazing how you can pull off a suit.  I'm
looking for a strong guardian who looks like a strong person.It's
okay.I won't charge a huge amount of money later.Maybe it's
okay.Thank you very much, Senpai.Thank
you very much.Thank you very much.
That's how I rode, and the one I rode seemed to
be the strongest.It was so scary, so I said, ``Oka-sensei,'' he said, ``Thank you, sir, for
helping me out as a pinch hitter.''Thank you for your continued
support.Ao-senpai,
thank you for coming.  I'm
going to ride, I'm
going to ride, I'm going to ride, you're going to ride on top of me,
and I'm
going to have you turn into a chair for a little bit.
Thank you for leaving it to me.
Nice ears and thighs.  I
heard it's in my butt, it's got a chocolate horn stuck in it. Leader, it's a horn. It hurts in the corner. No, it's better to fit it a little. Shono stimulation. Speaking of that, Mio-chan might be quite stimulated as well.
This is my senior's horn and it's
stimulating me. It hurts.
Thank you very much for today.  I'm afraid I'm going to be
taken away from there.That's
okay, so what do you think?I'm really
excited.I just learned how to do it.I
want to lead you to victory.It's
so cool.It's
fun.Please do your best.  Let's do our best,
everyone in the White group.
[Music]
Let's do our best.
Well then, at the end, I'd like to ask the
costumers. [Laughs] To the Teru-gumi or the Kumi-gumi guys, what's the strategy?  Do you think
everyone in the white group is going to be upset?
Well, I guess if you get the best kill, you'll
get 1 point added, so you'll
probably have to focus on the opponent you're going to attack while defending your zaru nada,
everyone.  Yeah, it seems
like we should all just wake up the guy who is approaching that general. It's better to
try and stay close to the general, but it's
okay to do it more and more. He's weak. I'm
sure.  Do it  It
looks like I want to go, so please.
Ah, first, stay close to the general, and
when you see 1 heart, hit it. It's a scary ball, and it's a ball ride. Okay, then I'll
probably start from here. Everyone will go to that pair's
voice chat.  I think
it will be, so I guess that's right. There are so many voices.
Well, I
think there's probably a name at the bottom, so now that I
think about it, it seems that there is a real person.  There
is no cooperation.
[Music]
That's right. Let's all do our best, using the general as our guide. We're both in the way.
We're both being targeted. Maybe we
should go cover. That's right. Once we
find it, it's
like that.  Okay, I
think we'll probably have to move from here.
Let's go, let's go. Let's go, let's go.
[Music]
Oh, it's okay, Lisa-chan.
Hey shoulder woozu VC oh
oh VC no cha I'm
number 1 and down 1
and will helpme it's okay okay
Loth
Oh
yes yes
[laughter]
I
okay
[music]
strategy
All
[music]
ATTSHIIknowSHII
Maybe
SHISHIIhaveanything
currently there
SHIELDIthinkand
[music]
hckSHIELD
H
JAWhoWethinkThe
Who
knowInoIDEarePartOf
The
Game
[Music]
AllhaveHP
have
could
tryingtheleaderThey
athandIknow
[Music]
MayI
see
Dead
[Music]
have
[Laughter]
notbeatingthe
horseOhsosorryamI
theonlypersonever
watchedSpiritNoI
loveSpiritmie
gettingallmyIdeas
fromsoCrazyNoNonot
at allSowrong
iway
horseTHEridingTHE
HorseridhorseandIam
ridingyouexactlyyou
aremoreofahorsegirl
thanmerightnowmore
ofaGirlhorseJASO
RIGHTiaGirlhorseand
youareahorsegirlJA
youaregirlWhoisa
horseandIamahorse
lovinggirlwholoves
youne
nehoris
PEROG
JA
GiveMecarrotsDoyou
likecarrotsorSugar
cubesIlikebothWhat
doyoupreferii like
TogetherokayWhoYour
Favoritemylittle
ponyponyRainbow
[Music]
DASHOGOGOG
I OG
GENisRainbowDASH
Twilight
SparkleSHIknowIthe
EPokaybutyouknowyou
likeRainbowDASH
isiteonethatIIsee
JAokayWhounspec
unspecIRIRIRMy
okayJumpJumpyouoh
TRUEokayMaybeWe
shouldgointoOhno
SorryGOGOGOGO goyOhShootTheyHit
YouIthoughtyouHokay
OhGOmightcomeafter
youokayWeGotONEI
thinkokaynicenice
nice
SH
Oh
HeartseeI
see
Her
Sorry
WhereIknowgoingonR
RunUSWemightasfor
funATTthemOhokay
TRUEifwecanprobably
notprobablyOFF
NowAreyougettingHer
NoSTRunokayjust
scareHerjustmakeHer
ScaredSYoushouldYou
ShouldBeafraidbe
veryveryafraid
GOODGOODallrightAll
enoughenoughlether
thinkaboutitlether
thinkabout
itletherlethersit
withthat
Sorry
IWekilledIthink
peopleWediedtceall
allyouingthat
allkillsUSWedidthat
TEWhyarepeople
sayingTETETE
[Music]
TEDown
UHgoingtoGivingInto
The
PRESSURETYAC
[Laughter]
M
[Music]
FdodoitagainWe
individuals
Again
know
okayStillThegirl
horseYEYeahofcourse
allrightOverHere
WaitingWhereareyou
BehindThesignwhere
youneedtogettheSLEI
seeyouwhatIdoyoucck
YouClickthethewhite
signwiththerightcck
andcckOnand
On
[Laughter]
M
NEbrokenNowAllHOPES
andamI
obedient
Whatjust
[Music]
KID
FfunnysohappyWepaed
Together
tosohappythatIcanbe
withSomeoneWhoseems
toalsobejustalittle
deliriousSuper
deliriousIhaveno
ideaWhereIamright
nowdidyounoiiI
streamedbeendoing
Marathonstreamsfor thepastDaysNo
youickmyphonelikeI
wonderlikeWhatgoing
onlikelookslikeniss
streamingandthenyou
knowkindofgettoitG
STREAMlike
Oh
[Music]
Stillgreatyouhavea
genjoyfor
hourImadeAMaybeBand
scheduleMOVEtoday
WhereIhadyouknow
[Music]
NeedmanLetdothis
ThingISTREAMbutIH
likeGOOUTIntoThe
World
mmIfeelabitTiredi
understanddefeat
your
enemiesOhniceokay
okayokayokayNEXT
is
whoevernot
[Music]
Friendprotected
youokayJumpJump
Jump
[lol]
nice
SASuperSuperSuper
SuperSuperSuper
Supernevergetyou
aliveWeworkTogether
JA
okaySHSorryI
wastryingtogo
[lol]
aroundbackfor
backweareFighting
todayOh
She
[music]
some
I
IkillIHer
[music]
apparently
anykill
[music]
Iwe
teamy
eat
horse
horseheacUSYesIdo
remember
thatknowii
knowe
okay
good
10IloveWarruinthem
ForMeLikeThatNoThey
veganFIknowwhatthe
the
CREAMpretendthatwe
OnTheRedTeam
JAAnother
Round
donotknowNEI
completely honestI
thoughtBeLikeAROUND
THELASTGAMETryone
moreIswearsomeone
switchedsoWhyyoutry
clickingitagainOh
youwantmetotryagain
OnemoretimesoIright
yourightClickonY
Whiteanything
okay Sokaytoldmethat
beforeWhenIClickyou
workWhereareyou
RightHereOhonmyhead
Ronmy
head
helpOhShegoneokay
ShegoneokayStanding
BehindThesignokayI
makenooneeversyou
againthe
SLEWhyisdoing
JAokaynowokayAgain
okayIKnowWhynotwork
okayokayIdoIdoit
H
HOhmygoshnarissaI
KnowWhynotworking
nissWheream
[laughs]
I
K
HEADIknow
Ihelp
[laughs]
[music]
guys
onsome
[laughs]
apparently
okay
[music]
[laughs]
husokayleft
cckrightClicktil
SHIELDokay
okayokay
girl
Thirsty
okay
OKWe
aream
to
ONEWeTwookayokay
okay
okayWeGo
[Music]
Backokay
see
okay
UH
[Music]
hur
OKhurhurnice
ok
[Laughter]
[Music] [
Laughter]
okayoveryoudidso
goodyouwere
amaz
WeNowWbeWeBewinners
OhmyyousogoodATEC
US
people
iipeoplethat
LS
Do
[Music]
FPS
hours
Team
MaytheTruthofLifeif
youtellpeople
somethingbugsyou
thenTheysayitmore
butifyoujustrealize
thatnothingreally
mattersandyoujust
stopcaringSuddenly
youlbehappierand
peoplewonmakefunof
youforasmuchShit
Stillmakefunofyouas
youknow
I
[music]
horse
know
I
HUMANph
sand
isSound
[music]
like
senior romeand
JULIA
know
Kiss
MOhWesupposedtogo
backIthinkIknowThey
gnadragUSI
thinkweGetoutohIsee
okaywehavetowaitfor
andkylaareonlythere
BecausekylaIthinkH
toleaveTheGame
Ohoh
NoScaredChangeVOICE
Channelnowembbutii
anyfinescared
[Laughter]
O you
[Music]
know the strong Very Strong Gozaru
Yes, yes
[Music]
Yes, the Roboco-san pair was amazing, it was amazing. I was
super sleepy.
I got 3 kills, that's amazing.
Sui Waitem is amazing, that's amazing.
[Music]
That's amazing.  I guess it's a good thing, isn't it? I wonder
if I've gone as far as I can.
I guess I've gone a long way.
In the second match, I was number 2, number 2,
etc. I had about 26 kills, so it was quite a
bit.  I'm getting scared of Lire,
Tamohime is shaking too, but now she's shaking more and more. Let's do
our best right now. It's okay, it's
okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay, it's strong.
When we were practicing, we were dodged by the yellow team
for about a minute and a half.But
yeah, they started serving us that food.However, it turned out to be a
complete mess.But yeah, there was an
update, and
Holomen Hunting started.  The content has
changed quite a bit, so I'm
wondering if there's something completely different about it.That
's possible.That's totally possible.Yes, I think it's possible.  I
really want to win.If I've come this far, I'm
sure I've come.How far do I want to go?It's not a big deal,
right?Yes, I
want to go there.At
first, I
felt a little greedy.  I felt like I was
winning a little bit. I'm
going to wrap my arms around it. I don't have any sleeves anymore. I did
n't just come here.
I tore it off at first, and now it's torn off around my shoulders.  You can't break it, you can't
break it, you can't break it, you can't break it, you can't break it, you can't tear it apart, you can't tear it apart, you can't tear it apart, you can't tear it apart, you can't tear it apart, you can't tear it apart, you can't tear it
apart,
you can't tear it all away.
Congratulations on the last 41 kills. Just kidding. I
turned bright red when Riki Shrine Maiden-senpai came home. It's
too strong, it's too white. What do you think?
Who was the person with the greatest number of kills? Who had the most
kills? And
Chiara was amazing too. At the very end, I'm
sorry, but I
defeated Subaru-senpai twice and Miko-senpai once. I do
n't like that. I was
insulted by that.  Tamon Kaera and others
came a lot.Kane
was amazing.That's why we went to the white team.It was great, but at the end,
thank you very much Nekomata porridge.Thank
you very much.
Thank you very much. Yes, this is what you think.
Thank you very much. It
was a pleasure to play with you all. I will continue to support the white team.
Thank you,
thank you. It disappeared in an instant. It disappeared.
Thank you very much to the agents.
Thank you very much to the agents of MAGA team.  Hey,
thank you, Senpai, too. I'm also doing a number kill,
so it's completely different if I have this or not. I
get it, it depends. Thank
you, really.
[Music]  It
was fun to eat, it was really fun, it
was fun, it was fun, it was really fun, it was fun, it was fun, but after
this I think there's going to be a lot of pressure in the competition. It's
going to be different if you work hard, right? No,
let's relax and hope. It's okay. I can
go. It's okay. It's
okay. It's okay.  I have to protect the princess when she
stumbles.Even if I have the princess to protect me, even if I make a slight
mistake, she'll catch me up with a relay.I'll put pressure on her, and she'll get
in trouble.I'm
going to practice.I'm already
climbing.
Everyone is talking about it,
but I guess I'm getting better at it.I can do it.It's difficult, isn't it?And it's not difficult.Didn't I
say that when I heard it today,
where did you do it?Don't tell me about running.
Well, it looks like the scores have been tallied,
so I'd like to take a look at the totals for the three games.  The
red team has 4, the red team has 46 points, the white team has 38 points, and the
yellow team has 23 points.  The
second half of the race
How's it
going? Okay, let's go to the next one. Okay, let's
move on to the next competition, everyone.
Let's go, let's go, have fun, look forward to it, look
forward to it, do your best, do your best, do your best.
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I wonder if
everyone else will be there Let's
be a horseman, do your best, do your best Fight yes,
do your best
[Music]
Masu
donewithall
myobisdonePR
ofce
kills
Oh, do your best, white team White team do your best, do your best
[Music]
Do your best, Okatan  has entered the princess
Ahi Hime
Hime The princess seems to be strong If the princess is the strongest, the princess
who seems to be the strongest is the one who is powerful Powerful Powerful The strongest Ki
Na
Thank you very much for your continued support. I hope you will continue to shake hands with me. Do your best, do your best, do your best. [Music] It's okay. You're cute with your tiara on. It's okay. I thought you were crying, but it's okay to smile.  I'm laughing, I
'm laughing,
Anakasu Hime is characterized by Ra-chan's way of laughing. That's why, love.
Yeah,
yeah, it certainly makes my heart flutter. Yeah,
yeah,
just
No.
meInevernoedthis
before
LoveohappTEhapp
happ that's good
[music]
[laughing]
ta
[laughing] I
wonder why E-chan is laughing like that.
Yeah, she's playing with her own 3D. She
must have been laughing. No, it's fun.
[Music]
Hey
[Laughter]
[Music]
streaming
[Applause]
Oh itsnowflakesa
FireB yeah pry this is just the first round
Yes, it was supposed to be yes, but it's scary. It's only the first round. It's a
one-time match. It's
pressure, pressure, and I'm kind of
nervous. I'll do my best. I'm going to participate in this, and
I'm going to be a princess, Mei-chan, and Azu-
Kichi.  Kazama-chan-chan,
Wow, I just saw the menu and
said, Yeah, yeah, that's right, the menu is
difficult. I've tried making rice before.
But yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right, I'm
doing it, so I have to cut things off, etc., and
there are various processes, so if you
can't share the roles, you'll end up wasting your
time.It's important to have strong cooperation.
Yes, that's right.
[Music]
But on the other hand, Minecraft has been doing this for about three years,
but he thought he could cut vegetables.
I thought so too. Yes, he can cut vegetables.
That's what I thought, and there was an item on the cutting board that said, ``Knife''.If you click on the cutting board and open it, you'll see a knife, and if you put it next to it, you can cut things like tomatoes, carrots, potatoes, etc.Oh yeah, and beef.  If you add it, it becomes ground meat. It seems that the minced meat is
the best. It
doesn't really come together. It seems like the regular version won't cut it,
so it seems like it's a special edition this time.
Yes, that's right, they're making it into a stage.On
the other hand, it's amazing that you can do that.It's a
setting that confirms Minecraft's potential.I
wonder if they're doing something like that.But we're
so impressed by it,
Minecraft is so strong.  I wonder if it's normal for Kara-chan to
say that. It's true that she's strong and strong, so maybe that's why she's smiling.
[Music] I'm so kind. [Music] I'm so
kind.
[Music]
Thank you, it's starting, try your best,
try your best, try your best, try your best, try
your best, do your best, I was watching you on the street
the other day, right? Yeah, that's right, you came here in the middle of the day.  I'm
stubbornly building a solid foothold,
even if it's slow, it's going well, it's fast, it's fast, it
's fast, it's so fast, oh, it's
so smooth, it's so good, it's so good, it's finally, it's really
good, it's really serious
Ogura, this is good, right? Go, go, it
's lined up with red right now. It
's not number 1. Let's go, let's go, let's go.  It's
new, so I wonder what they're making. I
don't know, I don't know from here.  It's
white, it's white, it's
pink, it's pink, it's so white, it's so white, it's so pink, it's so white, it's so white, it's pink, it's so white, it's so white, it's so pink, it's so white, it's so white, it's so pink, it's so white, it's so white, it's so pink, it's so white, it's so white, it's so pink.  I'm
really curious about
this. When I was practicing, it
was like making a hamburger steak, but it's a
homemade hamburger. Yeah, but what does it actually look like?
So what are you making? What are you doing right now? Oh,
but you're cutting it. Bake, cut,
bake
. You're cutting vegetables. You're cutting vegetables. Good luck,
good luck. Do your best. Looks like it's going to be fun.
So, good luck. What are you making?  I
wonder what you're making when you're thinking about it.The
food you ate afterwards is so good!Wow,
nice,
nice.I'm already up to stage 5.
Good luck, you're in second place right now, but red,
strong, red, strong, but fast, fast, fast,
go, dodge, dodge, defeat the zombies.
This princess is a gorilla, right? This
one's power is 50, so I'm sorry.  Do your
best, do your best, no, one chin,
one chin, one chin, there's a chan, there's a chan,
there's a chan, ah, it's coming out more and more, it's
okay to come out, come on, do your best, don't try your best, no, the boss is strong  It
looks like a boss, but it
doesn't float, it floats, it floats, it floats, it floats, it floats, it's really strong,
but it's strong, it's strong, it's
already a little bit more, it's a little bit more, it's
okay, it's
okay, it's coming, oh, it's almost gone, do your best,
do your best, boss, do your best, boss, just a little
more  No, but I can still do my best. 2 I'll do
my best. I'll do my best. I'll do my best. I'll do my best. I'll
do my best.
[Music]
Ta
Nice Nice Nice Nice
Nice Nice Nice That's great. Wow, I
wonder what they were making. I wonder
what the title was. I'll
ask you later. I
didn't understand the white one at all, but you
know, if you really liked it.  It's brown, isn't it? I
don't care what it was, but
it's yellow. It was amazing, catching up at the end. Before I knew
it, I
was at the very edge. It wasn't me, it was me.  I couldn't figure out
who it was right now. I
made a mistake.
Hmm, I'm so nervous. At this hour, I'm
not interviewing you to ask if I can go flower fishing.
Hello, today's air conditioner, it's an air conditioner, is
n't it? The sound quality in the room is so hot. Let's move on and dodge it. We can live without an air conditioner.
[Music]  I do
n't have an air conditioner, but I don't have an air conditioner at all in my house in Austria.
But what about the
weather? It's quite hot in the summer, so I'd
like you to turn on the air conditioner. Normally, my house is hot enough to do without an air conditioner,
but I can't remember.  I
don't get sick, but it's really hot. It's so
hot. It's so cool, unlike the book. Do
n't put it on. Even if you say "chokoda," you'll get caught in a hurry. Even
if it were now, I'd lend it to you and leave it on all the time.
Oaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Air Conditioner Love Love
La Is it being counted now? Is it an inter-count? The next one will be
Lillet and it will be the last one.
[Music] I'm
not good at actual performances, so it's
okay. I can do it. I know, it's okay. I'm scared of actual performances.
Yeah, Susue, but Lissa-chan and others are number one.
[Music]
Yes,
you're very nervous. No. 1. Even after that,
anyone can fix something over and over again, so let's make that mistake. No. 1.
Maybe you feel the pressure, after all.
Last Iroha -chan Last Last
Now, I'm on the way home. I'm going home on the
way home I can go to the bathroom. I
'll do my best. I'll do my best. I'm
nervous.
Yes,
this is somewhere in the middle, and I do
n't know why. It's not okay. I want to do my best, but I don't know how to say good evening. Because of that, I
can't do the things I used to do.
I know, I'm getting anxious.
Well, I guess the points in the relay are really high.It's the
last competition.I
wonder what it will be like.Even now, the red team is probably in a pretty good position.Oh yeah, that's right.I wonder
if it's going to turn around and get higher.
Noe is high at the end. I
have an image. I understand, I understand, it's a reversal. It
means that it's possible. Yes, yes.
So, let's take a look at the scores of the race.
Red team is in first place.
So 30 points White team 20
points Yellow team 10 points The
red team is a bit amazing, it's amazing.  I do
n't know. From
now on, let's move to the venue for the next competition, Shunshi Race. I know it's a
bit dangerous, so let's move. Is
it okay? I'm glad to be back.  I do
n't know, it's here, it's just here, it
's white, it's
white, it's here, it's white, it's white
, it's so hot, it's
so hot.  It's
eggplant. Yomu-senpai was an amazing cook. He was really quick. He understood what I was making. Ram Ram.
Lamb Lamb Oh, what was it? It was easy
lamb. Yes, it was sheep. Lamb. I'll have it grilled. I'll have it grilled. It's
special
. During practice, the mountains came out, so I was
sleepy. Actually, it was a high yield when I came to practice.  I
wonder if the
contestant was blown away before Nodoka-chan's announcement.
Stand -of -the -art technology I was surprised for a moment I was surprised to understand
how easy it was to
go to the flower. Go in the dash.
Then
open it and choose who you are, who is the master of White, oh,
come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come,
let's right-click.
[Music]
Yes, the entry list is okay, so it's the 8th
layer, ah, I'm a big troubled person who doesn't have a self, so it
's the chan layer.It's somewhere in the middle.It's the leader of the memory group.
And I'm having a lot of
trouble.Chan is 33.Okay, I see.I see.I wonder
if I was able to enter with this.I made it.I
made it.It's
okay.Oh, oh, that's amazing.Character contact again today.
No, it's okay. You can do it. Don't be weak.
Yes, I'll do my best. I'll do my best. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's
okay. You're going to be nervous. Even at the end.
I have the howhow
[Music] I wonder if it's
My  I have a senior,
so I went to an English college. Yes, I was able to do it. But I'm
turning into a 9. I'm turning into a 9.
[Music]
Oh,
oh
[Music]
Onana
Nice
nice, okay, okay, this water first, the turn of the contestants.Yes, the
first layer is yes, Nerisa, yes, next is
Choco-sensei, Cho-sensei, yes, the third layer,
Mui, the fourth layer is Captain Noel, yes, then the fifth
layer is Ame, yes, yes, and the sixth layer.  Even though the eyes are strange, the
7th layer is empty and finally it's
like people are getting to know each other like this, and
people who are used to Minecraft like this gradually
come in. I feel like I'm about to die.  It looks
like you're in the mood. Let's try it
now.
Everyone in the white group can
hear it.
Yes, I can. How do you feel about it? Well
then, who should I call?
[Laughs]
Well, then Iroha. When I
noticed that it was anchor 5, I
became the anchor.  But I'm sure things are going fast
so
I'm sure things will work out.I have faith in you, so I'm going to do my best.No, it's amazing.Then, to the
white team, I hope you'll take first place.Do your best.We'll
do our best.
Thank you for your hard work.Yes, that's
it.At the end, I was surprised and kept listening to it.Way to go,
I just came back from picking flowers.I'm
going home, I'm going home, I'm about to go home.When
Melisa-chan was confused about the cat, I
opened the book.  I didn't receive what the book
said, and it didn't arrive.It
's a man and a woman who had an embarrassing and embarrassing response.Let's do our
best.It's just luck at first.
If you're at the bottom, you'll be able to go back.Let's
do our best.Let's try our best.Let's do our best.Let's try our best.Let's
do our best.Ah, this is 2.Ah, I've fallen.Ruko.But
wow.
[Music]
Wow.I'm
so nervous.I practiced a lot, but that's a lie.  It's
okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it
's okay today, it's Korea, remember it and do your best.  It's
okay, I
'm stubborn, I'm really trying my
best, and it's like this, it's not going to end, it's going to be the end, I'm going to laugh at the end, right? When this is over, let's go eat some delicious meat. Let
's talk to the chocolate line.  I was talking to Azuki and the chocolate line.
Yes, meat, meat, meat, meat, meat, shabu-shabu is about to
begin.
Hey, do your best,
do your best at Redify. Let's do our best. Let's do our best, Sarisa-san,
do your best Gogogo.  Do
your best, try your best, calm down, come on, I'll
be waiting for you, come on, come on, come on, come on,
sofa,
famo kamonai, nice, catchy, nice, catchy, nice, catchy, nice, catchy, nice,
catchy, nice, nice, catchy, Bretta,
nice, nai, hey, it's getting better after all Oh, that's it, leave it to me, leave it to me.  It's
okay, it's running well, it's calm, it's
good, it's really, it
's really messed up There are times like that.
There are times like that. It's
okay. You can
go. It's okay. Kekeke, Kekeke,
wait and cheer.
[Music] Get used to it. [Music]
Oh, wait, this bread, bread left and right. [
Music]
[Laughter]
ノ Do your best,
do your best, do your best, do your best, do
your best, it's okay, I'll do my
best If you're a hard
worker, you'll understand.  Do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, let's go, let's
go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.  I can
go, I
can do my best, Ka-chan, I can do my
best, Nakaru-san, I'm going to do my best, and I'm going to
do my best, and I'm going to do my best.
[Music]
Guys, are you going to be sucked into this or that?
Nice, nice, oh, okay, let's do it, do your best, do your best, Azuchi, do your best,
do your best, Aki,
Senpai, it'll
feel like you're going to hit me, it's okay, it's
okay, okay, you'll hit me properly.  It
's okay
[Music] Do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do
your best.
Oh, oh, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, it's nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice,
nice fight. It was a
dangerous wait. I was
surprised. It was a
good run. I was so nervous. Go, do your best, do
your best. It's all over.
[Music]
That's good, you were strong
. I forgot to eat. I'm
hungry. I
want to be hungry. I'm
hungry.
Let's eat a lot when we're done
Yeah, nice
run, nice run, nice run, yeah, nice run, nice run, nice run.  Let
's eat
[Music] Let's
eat it. Let's all eat
shabu-shabu. Reluctantly, it's
beautiful. It's
cute. Let's go and make shabu-shabu.  The
Wachiko line is the Choco line, I'll
take you with me. Let's leave it all to Choco.
Choco-sensei.
Toys is Berry. Good, super nice.
Yeah, leave it to me, leave it to me. You worked really hard, too. Please, you
did your best. Interview. Oh, you did your best.
Yes, I tried my best. It was great. I tried my best. I
tried my best. Let's ask Iha, who served as the anchor,
one more time. Yeah, yeah.
How did it go? We started from the beginning.  It
was all right until the end, so we all
put together teamwork and got it together. It
's okay, it's okay. That's the result. There were
many times when I wanted to be passed, but I was able to finish
in 2nd place.
No, it was a wonderful, wonderful, nice fight. It was a very nice fight. It
was a
nice find. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your
hard work.  Are
you using it
well? How are you using it? Yoyoyo, what level of the test are you in? This is already the
first grade of the test. Thank you for your
hard work. You
did a great job! The level of proficiency in the first grade of the test is amazing. It was really good.  It seems like
everyone has already lost. Some
people are crying and crying. It's
so good that you're so sensitive.
No, I'm in 2nd place. I'm in 2nd place. I
tried my best. I tried my best. It's me.  To be
honest, at first, I was just like, ``I'm just having fun,'' and I was like, ``I'm going to do my best.'' But I didn't expect it to happen.I didn't know until the end.  Please gather in front of the school. Yes, let's
go to Aso. The first one to
go to is Aso de Gozaru school. There
was a colander wall. To my surprise,
we were sealed off.
Now,
let's go to Aso.  It is
[music]  It's
because of the ceremony that they were separated, and
it's a mess, so it's just the five of us who don't have a lot of poop. It's
true, it's
dangerous, it's
too bumpy. There's a lot of volka on
top of everyone. It
cheers up the volka bread that has the bread.  Is the bread
okay? Is the black one okay?
Yes, I have a little too much, so we're
fighting a lot, but it's okay if you let me move on.
Yes.
So, with that said, the closing ceremony
begins, but Miko-san, how was the year?
I honestly didn't know what was going to happen, but
yeah, everyone worked together really well and
worked hard, and it was a close race every year.  It was
really worth watching and I
thought it was amazing. Well, that's true. There was a drama in each of them,
or rather, there was. I
think it was a drama, including the practice. I
think it was really good, everyone.  I'm trying my best and I can't
line up my group at all.My
mom can't tell me, so Mio-chan was talking to me right now, so she's
going to tell me to get along.We
lined up a little nice, which was great.Yes,
yes, yes, so we did a warning ceremony.What
do you think?  I wonder if I'll be able to do it soon. I'm
ready to chat. I'm also connected to chat,
but that's just a matter of course right now, so I'm
like, ``Please wait for a while.'' I
think it's going to work.
It's okay, everyone. Has our voice
been heard? Has it been heard? Has it been
heard? It has been heard.  There
was a lot of moving around, but I would like to
say a few words to A and Nodo-chan who supported me so well.Yes,
yes, I-chan, Nodo-
chan,
thank you very much.Voice from heaven.Thank you for your hard work.  That's the
voice of heaven.
Thank you. Thank you very much for this year, and for this year as well.
Your hard work and
individuality are overflowing. And I wonder if the three organizers
did their best. We were able to see all the hard work,
and we were moved by it.  I'm Hishi
Thank you very much Thank you
very much for your cooperation
Thank you
very much for your cooperation Thank you
very much for your cooperation Thank you very much to all of you I
hope it was fun for all three of you to participate.
So, please do your best until the end.Yes,
thank you
very much.Thank you very much,
everyone.Then we will now begin the closing ceremony.First
of all, I would like to give a closing speech.I
would like a greeting from the chairman of the sports day executive committee.
Yes, yes, everyone at this sports day
had fun. Yes,
it was good. No, it was really good.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you,
Hololive has gotten really busy every year.
But even so, Nemiko and the others had already seen everyone come together like this,
everyone working together and
really taking the initiative to call out to each other and help each other,
so it
was truly amazing and filled with emotion every time.
Thank you very much for your continued cooperation.Thank
you very much. Thank you very much for taking
this opportunity.If you don't mind, I would
like to ask about the newcomers, or the
members of en and a.  I
think it would be really great if we could have more interactions in the future and make Hololive even more exciting, so please continue to support us in the future.  Thank you very much for
participating, and you did a great job! You
worked hard, you worked hard, you worked hard.
Yes, everyone is doing great. This
is the finish line again this year.
Thank you very much. Thank
you. Thank you.
Yes, Subaru is now Subaru as well, and I've been in contact with them in a lot of ways, and I've
been able to see the various aspects of the team, but all the
teams are already working hard, and now I'm sure the
results will come.  I think
one of the big things is that we all worked hard together like this.
Well, I think it will become something of a treasure,
so I hope that you can make use of the bond that we have in the future.
Please watch it.  It
was a lot of fun.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Nice speech. Nice speech. Nice
speech. Nice
speech. Nice speech. A lie. Embarrassing. Sen. Kyu. Yes.
So, finally, I would like to announce the general benefits.
Yes, yes. The announcement of the benefits
is 1.  I
would like to present three groups all at once in the order of 100, then 100, and finally 10.Now
then, Samiko, the Sports Day Executive Committee Chairperson.
Could you please announce the bonuses?
Yes, then I'll start by announcing number 1.
Yes,
then the red team is 8, the white team is 8, and the yellow team is 6.
Hey, what, what, what,
this is scary.  It's scary to make an announcement, but I do
n't know yet, I
don't know yet.Okay, then let's move on.I'll announce the 100 stakes
first.Yes, yes, the 100
stakes are here.Here you go.
Eyabai Yabaya, Yabai,
Yabai, I don't know yet. All of these
are all about 100. Yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah, I'm going to go last.
Wow, so the red hair got 158 ​​points and the winner
is the red hair. Congratulations. Congratulations.
Congratulations again.
[Music]
[Applause]
Sorry.  I
understand that it's frustrating,
but it's dangerous. Let's get along. Let's get along. Let's get along.
Friendly please. Please,
Freely. And second place
goes to the white team with 138 points. Third place goes to the wood team with 106 points.
Well done, everyone, do your best.  You
did a great job. It was
amazing. When are you going to give out the awards?
Yes, there is an awards ceremony this time.
Well done everyone. The yellow group has the same medal.
Okay, well, first of all, the
representative of the players and teachers of the yellow group, Hasbe,
Chanbe-chan, please
come to the front.
Temiko-san Miko-san
Ade [Music] That's right, I'm going to send it to everyone, everyone. I'm here. You've
prepared a great time.
Congratulations, congratulations!
Congratulations!  I see
everyone is following.Okay,
next up. Next up is Geo, who won the silver medal for the white team.Yo,
Azusa from the yellow team, please come to the
Izu group.Thank you very much.That's A-
chan, it's Geo who got the gold medal.Congratulations
to the white team.  Thank you very much. Thank
you very much. You did an amazing sweet eggplant. It's so cute. Thank you so much for the likes.
Congratulations. Congratulations.
Masa and yes, this is
Geo, the gold medal winner of the red team who came in first place.
Towa-sama
Thank you, Mr. Tojato, for winning the red team. Congratulations. Great congratulations.
[Applause] Stop it,
stop
it. Let's get along, get along.
[Applause] Let's get along well,
right in front of us. Gaga,
wow.  It's a shame that there were so many diamonds that disappeared in the blink of an eye.That being
said, I would like to
express my sincere gratitude to everyone who has caused a negative impact on Flo Live 4th Movement 2023.Thank you very much.  Well, it's not
like I'm buzzing. I
just want to take a commemorative photo,
so what should I do
? Should I put it on that stand in the middle of there?
Yes, please. Yes, on the moving table. It's
here.  Yes, let's move, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, let's
move, by all means,
everyone, everyone, line up, line up, line
up, line up, please line up, we can fit in, too.  I'm
going in.
Okay, hey, I can see you.
All right, everyone here. I'm
not quite there yet. I wonder if I've made it yet.
Kanata, here, here, here, Kanata, Kanata, here, here, Kanata, Kanata, wait a moment, please
wait a moment,
please. I'm
in.  Oh, it's on us too.
Everyone's lying. It's on us. Oh, wow.
It's
true. I'm so happy.
Oh, the
red has fallen. The metal
is gone.
No, it's
too
sad. If I do it one more time, I wo
n't be kicked out. There's no emikko left. I don't have any more. I'm sad. How can I give this to you? How can I give you this? Yes, yes, I can't give that, I can't give it.
Wait, why
don't you just touch it? Just left-click. That's good, that
's it. That's good, that's good.
That's it. Oh, okay, everyone. Let's
take a look at that little thing right in front of me.  I wonder if I
should look at Kana Koro-
san.Koro-san.I feel like I'm looking at Koro-san.Ro-
san, Koro-san is flying.Hey, you should look over there, villagers.Look, it's
true.That's the cameraman in front.The
cameraman is right here.  Here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, right, right there,
okay, everyone, can you see it?
I'll take a picture,
yo, hey,
mermerca,
mercari, hey, hey, hey, hey, who is this? Who threw this year too? Who
threw it just now? Who threw it this year?
Someone threw it again, Toto.
Stop it, everyone. It's all over the place. It's still throwing. Hey, do
n't throw away your trash. Please take your trash home with you. You ca
n't see it.
Thank you,
listeners, for watching that cat.  And to all the
management staff who helped out a lot behind the scenes,
thank you very much,
thank you very much, thank you very much.
Yes, let's meet again. Let's all
go to Hololive. Let's go to
Hololive.  It's been beaten up, it's
been beaten up,
oh
begnais
[Music]
ah
Ftime
falIyouguysenjoyto
SorryAgainforingto
ter
muchsleepybut
alsonotworkingmy
japaneseisgoodright
nowEspeciallyisnot
working
soyouknowItisWhatit is
people Ito take
aroundfornowGoing
herewillbeAnother
fortodayThankyou
guyssomuchforcoming
byexcitedtospend
timewithMy
bISTUpasThankyou
guysmuchforin
andINotification
havealoveldayJILbir
by
[Music]
Darling
DET