[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
because I'm feeling good
[Music]
and today we're gonna be um SMS can see
in the in the thumbnail
um I'm gonna be doing a top tsumashi
endurance of legit I I don't know how
long will this take
well until I until it finishes as you
guys can see
Zero out of 23 Tatsu it's 2023 and so
we're doing the 2023 edition of
totsimachi In which I need 23 people to
come
or else I'm not gonna be able to end the
Stream
[Music]
it is
also there will be announcements the
usual stuff you know
yet
is is
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
and my 2023 birthday like what the heck
you know what what in the world
what the hell you know you see
um
[Music]
foreign
by the way did you guys listen to my
newest cover
did you guys listen to my cover how was
it
how was it
[Music]
how was how was my cover
it's nice thank you
thank you so much
so much everyone thank you thank you
[Music]
thank you so much everyone else
foreign
[Music]
guys don't forget to stream my cover
um every day
do not forget
[Music]
you guys can always DM me you know if
any of my whole life friends want to
come Hollow proofreads you guys can
always DM me
my DM is always open DM me on Discord or
something
[Music]
all right
punch it
[Music]
is
happy birthday thank you so much thank
you thank you thank you for the birthday
wishes
[Music]
I swear to God
oh my God
[Music]
right
by the way by the way
um
[Music]
oh my God
the ideas I will be coming back
because
[Music]
bro bro no way right all the ideas love
me right
all the ideas love me right
even Jan made oh my God if if any of my
Shane mate
isn't coming
I swear to God
[Music]
I I swear to God
like what the hell bro
[Music]
I'm gonna be so sad the whole day
the hell back song yeah this is this is
a very birthday birthday CBM right
[Music]
this is a very birthday CBM
I love this BPM
foreign
[Music]
guys
happy yes
did you guys know that next week it's
already the fast we have been like all
of us have been pretty busy
and this is quite an amazing timing
like this week is my birthday and then
next week is it's gonna be the the fast
the whole fast
not gonna lie all of us have been pretty
busy it's kind of crazy
and me me I have been super busy with
birthday stuff and also and also you
know the first steps to as well so
[Music]
foreign
hmm
looking forward to adult anyone what do
you mean looking forward to I'm already
an idol every time I stream
[Music]
I'm already an idol every time I stream
bro what
ha ha
hmm
[Music]
Nations
foreign
[Music]
Hawaii
a little bit loud okay gotcha
um
should be okay now
shouldn't be that bad
[Music]
oh no
oh
[Music]
hello
who might you be
[Music]
um
this is
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
a system
s
foreign
[Music]
hahaha
um he is just terrifying
by the way by the way yeah
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
I see ah a yes
oh my God I missed the chance I'm sorry
again everybody
[Music]
and that was
my senpai
my channel
[Music]
foreign
she is full of surprises
[Music]
who is that
who am I speaking
hey what's up
thank you so much for coming for me
yeah of course I mean
even if I'm not at like 100 I wouldn't
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh my God it
doesn't know isn't it you're 100
yourself
[Music]
yeah I can only be 100 with you
I would say it's been a while but then I
I remember the whole stream but then
that wasn't you
[Music]
wow yeah but yeah yeah it hasn't been
that long we both like you know remember
like
project winter thing we were supposed to
do but like man it is hard to organize
that
one day we will do it bro that's like a
few months ago
I know right
and then like we're like we're gonna do
it and that's like yeah things come up
so it's like okay never mind
shoot like five times or something
[Laughter]
it's super sad imagine rescheduling five
times for a collab
[Music]
I mean it's because like there are so
many people that like it's it's harder
to do right but anyway that's that's not
the main point I like if if there is a
chance like I would like to collab with
you oh yes yes
let's collapse something do you have
like any game that you like to play or
something
maybe like operation Tango have you
played that oh I've played that but I
didn't play all levels I think
maybe don't even probably figure out
something but like yeah I mean anything
would be fun yeah I guess if you want
something similar to that we can play
Porto or something have you played that
[Music]
oh yeah I
yeah I played that okay but
it's fine we could probably do it it's
fine
it's fine I mean we only have so much to
work with yeah and hopefully the big
girl have also happened something
it will happen one day but it doesn't
even have to be like you don't even have
to wait until then we can just like
collab yeah really yeah hit me up
anytime
yeah how's your birthday so far it's
been really good
it's been really really good thank you
even better because you came
well you know my night is even better
because you're here
what's with your mic by the way
[Laughter]
yeah I've been meaning to ask
yeah I don't know it's it's friends from
the usual Colony you know
yeah but it still sounds beautiful
doesn't it yeah it does I know are you
flatter me too much oh you sound good
though
but not only that you always sound good
oh man
oh my god oh man
I don't mind like coming on too much I
don't know
yeah but probably the surgery man
for this long
yeah yeah thank you so much
man of course
and like see you around man I'll I'll
hit you up yeah please invite me anytime
yeah
bye
[Music]
foreign
like 144 feet or something
ah
let's see
thank you so much crony thank you thank
you it's been a while since we talked to
each other oh
who is that
hello from my TV
hello
thank you
thank you thank you
so much
[Music]
I know
um
oh yeah
you can help okay
thank you yeah my bad guys it's actually
base birthday today not mine
yeah I'm scamming like five five
thousand people here my bad guys
a bad guys
do I want to ask
[Music]
good
but I'm so glad you're having a good
birthday I'm so excited to see you
announcements
I listen to your cover
[Music]
thank you oh my God
oh my God I I'm like I'm like I listen
to your covers like a whole lot
[Music]
oh they're so good Style no
man like not gonna lie I think I think
you fit every genre of music oh
like like you cover a lot of changes and
like I think you fit all of them and
it's it's super crazy you know
[Music]
we probably should cover something
someday you know yeah
[Music]
your voice is under the category of
voices that I'm probably most jealous of
it's like naturally just cute and unique
it's like one of the voices that you
can't imitate because like I try to I
can I I do my best to imitate certain
voices but your voice is under the
category of unable to imitate because
it's a natural gifts
[Music]
so cute yeah not a skill that's you yeah
and this is what happens when you put
like two people who don't know how to
don't know how to accept compliments
though
dude oh my okay everyone everybody in
chat can agree with me okay everyone
categories with me no no me
no me no me no me bro
tell me no no me
no me
oh my God I'd love to sing with you one
day yeah let's let's sing together also
I can't wait to see your performance
next week
I said it first damn
uh I'm so excited to see uh your
performance as well
thank you so much I can't wait to see
your performance wait are you on day one
or day two
I wanted to we're the same we're the
same day
just go let's go oh my God I can wait
yes oh my God on the same day on the
same day kind of spicy not gonna lie
kind of spicy
it's so true for you for you
for real for real for real for real for
real for real for real for real
forever for real sorry for real
oh my God
for you
thank you so much babe
have a great birthday thank you so much
thank you
[Music]
man she's so cute they so cute
Bay is super super cute
the cutest full High
basically because I don't think we've
ever had any one-on-one collab which
which is crazy and I think I think we
need to get into that too
I think we need to get into that too and
also maybe a possible cover in the
future I would love to do it today
oh I'm sensei thank you so much for that
Casper
foreign
thank you so much
thank you so much slime
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
thank you
videos
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
your 15
can that be my birthday gift oh your
gift yeah you need what
um you need what with pictures from Miss
irony
okay I'm gonna send you after this yeah
yeah I'm gonna take a good good good
picture of my feet yeah
oh my God yes
[Music]
um
yeah let's go let's go
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
mama
Gila is
15 senpai
yeah you're not broken up don't be
something like that white leg
where's the sudden leg
s
oh my goodness not leg but bug
oh my god oh
mys inside
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you thank you so much
[Music]
I don't know
I know
boys
China
China yeah
[Music]
yeah
so cute thank you thank you so much
oh
the sauce
[Music]
foreign
close to me
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh no
nothing
foreign
thank you
[Music]
well yeah next week
next week there might be something
you know I don't know what what is it
but maybe next week next week in my
schedule you might see something spicy
I wonder what is it gonna be
I wonder what is it gonna be dang
dang what is it gonna be I wonder she
said that we're gonna be playing her
favorite game hmm I wanna watch game
well only one way to find out right
only one way to find out
foreign
[Music]
hello
who are you
hey happy birthday
hello I knew I knew I could believe in
my gen mate
gills I got a birthday present I didn't
want to get to make one for you last
year but I made one this year oh my God
what is it it's here it is time oh my
God
it's time for you to embrace it
[Music]
foreign
Papa
amazing amazing
oh my God
will you
what skincare is loving you
then should I love myself
yeah I guess that's why I'm so ugly
I'm sorry
oh oh so what are your plans for today
like do you have cake and everything oh
I'm definitely gonna be making my
announcement that's like one of the most
important announcements
announcement I wonder what announcement
I wonder what it could be I'm so excited
for it I know right yeah by the way
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
hey yo y'all been talking behind my back
oh yeah I'm sniffing I'm sniffing this
is
[Laughter]
thank you so much for always filling me
in OverWatch
over here I would pocket you any day
this little audition
s
oh thanks
[Applause]
oh my God that's okay I really like it
also it's so fun so freaking convenient
yeah oh hey wait has it been like five
minutes Mark oh I think so do you have
anything anything else to say
I just hope that you have a lovely
birthday I'll be here cheating for you
by the way everyone stream our new cover
Ravi
stream my cover right now
right now gun emoji
[Music]
thank you so much all you for coming and
thank you for having me
especially thank you okay bye
what what
[Music]
is
you know what maybe maybe it might have
been my imagination
maybe maybe that was just a second of my
imagination you know
hmm
anyways oh my God it's almost time for
our announcement
announcement
oh my goodness
oh my goodness I think I can announce it
like
um the announcement is supposed to be at
um 8pm but I think I'm supposed to
announce it like maybe two minutes
earlier
two minutes earlier I think that would
be nice
[Music]
Hospital
okay announcement
you guys ready for announcement
and three two
one Anya Anya on your announcement
three two one three two one three two
one three two one three two one zero
sit down
on your mouth oh wait let me do this
Visa
birthday celebration 2023
on sale today
one special voice set
and birthday merchandiser set
we have government
through the gardens glass
and a fast case
one school trip
and a glass
a drop of bliss
bonus or birthday merchandise set
autograph
whoa
this is our announcement everyone
this is our announcement
[Music]
by the way the art the illustration this
time kind of looks like a gacha
illustration right
and the the merchandiser's names it's
actually on purpose so that it kinda it
kind of sounds like a gacha card name or
something
yeah it's name on purpose
because the illustration this time kind
of looks like a five-star gotcha card
don't you guys think so
[Music]
bye
foreign
[Music]
oh my gosh let me let me get you guys
the link
sale
oh my goodness you know what um
I will be updating my stream description
foreign
[Music]
yeah
right now on sale yes
[Music]
here you go
special
[Music]
voice and merchandisers
naming
like all of the merchandisers are five
stars so what is stopping you from
getting my merchandises my five-star
merchandises
link for you guys
let me get the let me get the E and the
N Hollow Pro shuffling as well
[Music]
it's full
foreign
oh my goodness look at this
bro
bro like
bro look look at the freaking
illustration
this
is
what is stopping you guys from find my
merchandisers
let's go
[Music]
I will be the pleasing
Victoria hi
Daddy come on come on
[Music]
Aman
by the way guys I need you guys to look
at the glass
I have I have the picture here I have
the glass picture here
I know
[Music]
by the way the best case the fast case
illustration is also different
so the number man
let me let me Zoom okay so we have
rubber man and also fast case
both with different illustrations by the
way the illustration for this fast case
it will be available
for
membership wallpaper
soon
[Music]
membership
the illustrations will be available as a
wallpaper
for members
for all the ten dwellers
[Music]
and also look at the class so fancy
right
so freaking fancy
also look at the polaro itself from my
cars and this one you can only get you
can only get if you buy the the whole
set
we buy the whole set you can get this
with my signs my sign on the promote
card
the glass so fancy right
fancy
[Music]
and we have individual sales for the
rubber mat the pass case and the glass
and I have um we have the voice back as
well
titles Timeless oh my God so by the way
if you're not the type of person who who
listens like voice pack and stuff you
guys should definitely listen to this
voice bag
it is something Wild
well if you're familiar with my voice
packs my birthday voice bags I ride I
write everything
I direct everything
and this this one this one this this one
is super cool you guys should definitely
listen to The Voice guys
[Music]
thank you thank you
Instagram
you know
where is it
[Music]
okay
guys
[Music]
foreign
this is kind of an experiment though
it's like I wonder I wonder how many
people will come if there's like
there's like no no invitation
no invitation for the thoughtsu
hmm
social experiment
well I guess I got more time to to do to
promote my emotion dices
I'm gonna showcase each one of this
merchandises
while I wait for more people to come
[Music]
it's off
the illustration is fine or you Sensei
thank you so much oil is insane everyone
say thank you to all you sensei
[Music]
um
Mina
foreign
wow
look at this so cool
so cool
[Music]
yeah guys
I'm so stylish in this illustration
you know what not gonna lie
not gonna lie after seeing this design
this is the outfit is designed by oyu
Sensei I just gave like the the you know
the kind of like theme and like some
references
and whoa not gonna lie I kind of want
this as my new outfit
legit legit that's so cool I want this
is my new outfit
[Music]
it's so cool right
hmm
it is so freaking cool
[Music]
and also look at the past case
the illustration for this one is by Haru
or no copyright girl Sensei thank you so
much no copyright grow sensei
thank you for the cool illustration
available
paper membership
join membership
join the membership
thank you
fruit gloss new guys oh my God is here
[Music]
Danny
oh my God look at this
so stylish
it's got my ribbon on it
what is this
[Music]
oh my God
senpai
is
you guys can also use this as your Boba
glass
okay
hmm
[Music]
glass boba
foreign
[Music]
let's see
oh
hello hello good morning hello good
morning happy birthday
[Applause]
JP correct
[Laughter]
oh my God thank you so much for coming
thank you for having us happy birthday
happy birthday thank you thank you it's
been a while I think I think it's been
since
[Music]
that was so fun
we gotta we gotta play Astrid here let's
play Astrid here again I don't know if
the server is still there what is it
like
yeah I don't actually I just showed up
so I don't know anything about this
setup for astroneer like what it's like
yeah me too yeah yeah
oh my God no idea but
pretty much looks so good yeah
thank you so much oh my God is very very
stylish it looks nice to have some like
you know like some whiskey with it
chocolate that's what I was thinking too
bro it's like an alcohol glass to me I
know you said Boba is fine but for me
like like a gin and tonic or like a
whiskey like Jack and Coke or something
like that you know what it will be very
cool
yeah
well how's your how's your birthday so
far
hey thank you
thank you yeah yeah it's a good nice
food
[Laughter]
oh my goodness oh do you guys with Axel
you you have the the Apex tournament
coming right yeah oh yeah
that's so freaking cool thank you thank
you very much um
win it all for us bring it home oh my
God bring back the Toki for the video
yeah please win you have to you have to
yeah please win for us
I don't even have teammates yet but you
know
you know you know I wish I was as crap
yeah wait you don't you don't have to
mate
yeah okay okay okay
you could practice and hit Pride as well
you trying to recruit I'm like levels
left correct in Apex as you guys
what what games are you like crafting do
you have like a certain games
um
[Laughter]
which got your game specifically do you
like I don't know dude like I play
almost got a game I think all right well
gotcha games not so healthy for your
wallet you know I know
it's fun it's fun yeah are you into
gotcha gotcha game I I can't do anything
related to gambling because of like
trauma so like anything oh gotcha games
are not gambling but like anything even
like remotely similar to it was like a
game of chance and you have to spend
money I can't I can't I just get like
I get crazy
oh yeah I'm like I'm like a seasonal
player now though I'm like oh you get
free Jewels today
I only lock in when there's like three
guys
it's a thing being like a YouTuber I'm
too busy to play like you know
any game in general yeah it really is
yeah hmm
oh my God thank you so much guys for
coming yeah happy to be here happy to be
here thank you for inviting us and hope
you have a nice birthday you know hope
you have a good one thank you so much
I I can't speak Japanese
bye
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my God that's so chill
they're so so chill it's been a while
since I talked to them
like
oh
how how long ago was the astroneer
collab
it was like a few months ago which is
not gonna lie super crazy
not gonna lie super duper crazy
anyway
um that's eight people right
[Music]
oh my God at least one out of three one
of all of three of the gold reached
um
[Music]
and I saw
and I thought
it is
[Music]
foreign
I I can't speak Japanese
[Music]
foreign
that's like one out of three
go
[Music]
and oh
foreign
[Music]
oh my God
guys
um
wait wait I want to change this to the
I'm gonna change the
uh
do this
[Music]
guys oh my God you guys won't believe
what what just came to my DM
you guys won't believe this
one Bluetooth Widget
oh my goodness
you guys ready to see
three
two
one
[Music]
foreign
thank you so much
oh my God
senpai
guys by the way this this picture is
only for me not for you guys
don't don't sniff sniff this is only for
me
I take
I I take authority of this picture
guys
[Music]
it's not for you guys
for Anya and Anya only
[Music]
it's for Anya and Anya only
so on Twitter already oh my God
oh my God I mean satsuga
Yobe senpai
Sasuke yopi senpai
oh my goodness
in this car
my name is
[Music]
oh my God I wonder how how long will
this take
how long will this take
[Music]
your house
mom
ENT today
[Music]
well you know what that eight people not
so bad
not so bad eight people not so bad
[Music]
oh yeah I also got I also got some
some DMS from people who plan to come
but they can't
you know some people also wanted to come
but they can't but they can come so
well well it is how it is
yeah too bad
and it will drop our onion
um
[Music]
foreign
by the way
have you guys bought my merchandises
have you guys for my merchandises
merchandisers how is it
foreign
just came back home
hmm
Kyla kovals Kia I wonder if she is on
this court right now
[Music]
sweet
just reach home oh that was an hour ago
well okay
[Music]
laughs
but it is
she said
thank you so much
bro
[Music]
thank you
oh my God oh my God I have an idea oh my
God Kyla Kyla what if you bring your
family to my Tatsu and so I can count
them like multiple people can you bring
like KIA KIA gorilla Papa Ella or
something
yeah
guys
bro bro oh my God you should tell oh my
God you should you should bring your
whole family to my daughter too oh my
God this is it this is it
I've connected the dots
I've connected the dots oh my goodness
bring bring your family to me okay
bring your family bring your whole
family all right
it's fine
wait this is this is gonna be my first
time meeting meeting Kyla's family
I've never I've never met her family
come to sing of it
it's not the thing of it
finally
[Music]
don't know
guys
I'm so excited
I am so excited you guys have no idea
thank you
so much
[Music]
oh my God
amazing simply simply amazing wonderful
but I should get my my cover thumbnails
here let me see
[Music]
you later
guys oh my God there's gonna be so many
people
again guys
foreign
[Music]
from video
like that one was extra right but that
was that was also because like
I gave like I gave a heads up hey if
anyone want to come to my totumachi etc
etc
hmm
and this year I think I I wanted I
wanted it to be a little bit more casual
he said well in ID right no he said
I still remember
guys
oh my god do I still have the yoga video
oh my God wait do I still have the video
[Music]
oh my God
oh my God it's like
half a pound we'll see you guys
I'm trying to search
on
[Music]
me
oh my God
[Music]
um
I know a lot of you guys
um a lot of you guys are like new new
Peterborough fans
you know I wonder if I I'm allowed to
play them
I'll take that as a yes I'm done
I'll take that as a yes
I still have to feed
you guys want to see the Diego video
from a year ago
I know some of you got into whole ID
from the 13 for example
and some of you haven't seen my 2022
birthday stream
well I have I have the help of video
[Music]
foreign
hello
yeah
oh my God thank you thank you so much
for coming I'd say it's been a while but
not really
yeah
we met recently
oh oops I'm sorry
[Music]
oh no yeah my bad I was playing the yoga
video
[Music]
okay but you also have to add surprised
again okay okay okay
oh my God
who are you
my should be
awesome
it's been a while but not really
oh yeah I saw you a little bit in
Indonesia
[Music]
wow but that's okay we can we have many
opportunities in the future maybe so
yeah your birthday merchandise looks
nice thank you thank you I know right
they look so nice this time
so how you doing how you feeling on your
birthday I'm feeling so good today thank
you for asking did you eat some cake not
yet the cake oh the baby ate the cake
actually
what yeah I gave the cake to be the
whole cake yeah it's gone now
[Music]
what about me okay
oh shocking well well maybe your viewers
have to bake you a new one
but I would I would help out thank you
how's it going
it's been going well I think
well what's your birthday wish
my birthday wish everybody wish is
to eat lots of delicious food
um
to get closer with everyone in whole
life that's kind of unrelated
oh that's okay that can be a birthday
wish too yeah until your next birthday
[Music]
YouTube
hahaha
I don't really know what games are you
into
well I don't play FPS games oh
I also don't play horror games
what I do play is like for collabs at
least would be like you know party games
like Mario party stuff like that Uno
Monopoly
um I don't know like fun funny Nintendo
games hmm she'll definitely do Mario
party and then maybe invite some more
people
yeah because it's for four people
[Music]
um
is it Elena that started the whole spicy
thing in ID yeah find it right okay
spicy a lot of pain as well Everyone
likes spicy I only like it you know in
that sense but not in terms of spicy
food oh I see I was about to ask you for
some spicy KFCs for today because it's
my birthday you know
oh you like your food spicy yep
I can't well that's okay as long as I
don't have to eat it you can have as
much spicy food as you want oh then is
it okay to have some spicy KFC okay I
will send you the spiciest Fried Chicken
ever right now okay I'll I'll put it in
the post office and it should be there
tomorrow
okay I'll be looking forward to it
okay happy birthday
[Music]
you're welcome bye bye
me
[Music]
that was Chihuahua oh my God I can't
wait for the spicy KFC it's gonna be
spicy obviously because it's because
it's spicy I mean
I mean
[Music]
Indonesia
thing is it
is
hmm
[Music]
we're gonna
oh
happy birthday
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
for you
so much
[Music]
as you can see now
yeah yeah
happy birthday
um
Indonesia
[Music]
thank you
foreign
myself
[Music]
thank you
anymore
[Music]
Japan
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
okay
[Music]
thank you
foreign
China
[Music]
kimono
that's the money
[Music]
well you guys don't understand my love
foreign
you guys will never understand
[Music]
thank you so much
foreign
[Music]
famous
so
next person I wonder who is it
foreign
[Music]
hello
who is this
[Music]
is
Hello
nice to meet you
nice to meet you nice to meet you
oh my God
thank you so much for coming
more of the floors I I my voice is left
because I do like karaoke for like oh
yeah now I actually watch your karaoke
oh really
really say Bill you you have a very nice
taste in music
yes happy happy birthday
thank you
thank you so much
I think that should be okay hey hey yeah
it's probably because I'm dead too
it's okay it's it's like early morning
for you oh my god oh yeah it's pretty
early
thank you for coming though
yeah I really I really adore your voice
uh your voice is really nice too I'm
actually looking forward to your cover
the lobby cover is actually like one of
my favorite show released
oh really yeah
yeah oh my God I gotta listen to it
after this
knowing the song
I mean it's you know it's it's man I
love vocal food so I know I love full
color too
yeah
what can I produce her oh um I like
camel do you know oh
yes yes
one of my favorite songs like of all
time I know I love camos so so much
oh my God oh my God I knew yeah
yes yes I shake your I shake your hand
in respect
I don't really see I don't really see
like die hard for calorie plan
yeah sometimes it gets lonely you know
I'm here though I'm here though I love
vocalo you can literally probably be
like hey check out this producer with
like 10 subscribers and I'll be like oh
yeah I know this person
heck yeah
I remember I started listening to
Vocaloid like in 2000
oh about the same time I think mine was
oh really now about the same time
heck yeah yeah I remember I got
introduced to agree because of um kaguru
project
tiger bro yeah yeah
same what's your favorite song favorite
oh
my favorite's gonna be
um children's court and additional
memory oh additional memory is so so
good
ones yeah one of the newer songs
yeah yeah I like social Forest
imagination oh
and also outer science
out there yeah
yes honestly I love how it sounds like
like gin is a really good producer
[Music]
thank you so much for coming oh my god
of course
I could literally talk about vocally the
whole day
yeah I have like so many like unlocked
memories
but yeah thank you so much for having me
yeah thank you I hope you have a
wonderful episode even though it's like
early morning in your place nah no
worries it's worth it yeah thank you
thank you so much of course Happy
Birthday y'all and listen to your cover
now all righty
okay I'll see you later bye
oh my God
polka Boomer the full cup Boomer pond
it's not dead guys
It's Not Dead
I thought it was sad but no
what's that
the full cup room were born
thank you so much that was dancing hot
girl from Melissa's in temples
yay
I talked about Focus
but you know what I think rainy it is
also kind of a focal Bloomer as well
I think rain is also kind of a poker
Boomer as well you know she doesn't
really talk about it though
but I know she is
oh
all right
speaking of
speaking of Hawaii raining
[Music]
I mean I was when I I'm not wrong though
um am I
I'm lying
station I was just like damn you know I
was like oh it's fine all muted they
said I think you're not new yeah you're
muted at the start but I think you
normally now oh not muted now that's
good that's good that's good all right
all right happy birthday
yeah like you know what if anything yo
I'm sorry for making this like a
vocaloid totsu call but like if anything
like I know the older songs but like the
newer songs is where I'm like you know
am I off the grid you know I don't know
anything about the newer stuff you know
that's why I need to educate myself
well I I can always educate you
bro
uh
seven free rip seven free errors in
peace but it's all legendary AF see it's
a legendary
um
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
technique
[Laughter]
ha
Ola yeah
wrong
[Music]
oh God I heard about that yeah
I see
yay
[Music]
next time okay to summarize we will of
collab and we will play horror and I
will scream for her she will scream as
well she's because she's Pro and she
will brush my teeth just like what Ollie
did yes
have a great birthday
[Music]
by the way did I
did I update did I update the
did I update the toxic town on haka
so rainy should be the 12th person or
it's really like a 13 person oh my God
I don't remember if I updated
or not on hakka
did I update on haka
12 okay okay
it's not yet
it could be 12.
it is 12. it is 12 now
[Music]
oh
hello
[Music]
[Laughter]
definitely not Ina definitely not yeah
definitely not we know my enemies right
definitely help me with my enemies
you know my in on this doesn't sound
like
I don't know I often hear that I do
sound like her so I don't know yeah
maybe you know maybe I should have voice
acting
oh my God you know what
oh my God your impression of Nino my
innerness of following myth is perfect
oh thank you thank you thank you I've
been practicing a lot you see
especially
oh yeah yeah I paid really close
attention to you the very start yes of
the you know call wow very important yes
thank you
thank you definitely not you know my
innerness
ah you're welcome you're all come on
yeah thanks I'm sure if Nina my
underneath the whole English myth was
here she would wish you a uh uh very
very very very very happy birthday yes
uh and wish that you have a wonderful
year
lots of happiness and food and uh oh
yeah she made a little note here um she
wishes we could collab again uh someday
soon
thank you yeah
I know I mean I mean we didn't within
next year or so yeah that's pretty
that's pretty yeah
that's definitely not I mean yeah it's
not like it's next week or something
right
now
definitely not yeah definitely not the
case
yeah yeah but oh my goodness I feel like
it's kind of wants to talk to you it's
been so long I think I talked to you
like before break or something
[Music]
yeah so yeah that was like a long time
ago yeah I don't even remember what the
last Collette that we did with each
other
oh what's up
I know what
I can't even remember what I ate for
breakfast so remembering to look at my
thumbnail for
you know what understandable because I
don't even remember because I can't
choose between like yeah there's there's
a couple options here you know it's just
like which one happened first I know
good question better probably wait is
that the Mario Party one because that
was a long time ago
I don't know that because that was like
at 2021 that's like the only one of the
only collapse
no this a human fall flat was it
what yeah yeah yeah that was the one oh
my God that was the one oh my God it's
so long um I'm sure I'm sure you know my
internet is a whole lot of English myth
would love to collab with you again yeah
I'm sure yeah
um I'm gonna be collabing with each
other because you're not you know
or anything
the food came out really late like she
she planned it all up but the food came
out really late so you have to reach
back but yeah yeah but yeah yeah
definitely made it somehow
I would need all my enemies of five
English meds a good day so
yeah and thank you and of course have a
wonderful thank you thank you it's a
really good food
let's meet him definitely not next week
or something right because yeah yeah
hello who love English
yeah thank you very much okay okay
[Music]
wow well I wonder who that was though
she sounded she sounded too similar like
in a
I I can tell not gonna lie guys
not gonna lie I I couldn't tell who that
was oh
who is this
[Music]
ah
um
wow what a coincidence
[Music]
foreign foreign
foreign
[Music]
yummy
stay away
[Music]
okay okay
foreign
[Music]
okay
yep okay okay
[Music]
nice yes
jst
[Music]
[Applause]
okay okay
thank you
bye everyone
[Music]
no no
no
who's this
oh
yes
[Music]
it is
foreign
[Music]
okay this is pretty normal
okay
it's whatever it's fine it's what I can
fix this it's okay it's like I already
sent you
okay
[Music]
apparently it's pretty normal
yes yes this is pretty normal
um
[Music]
yeah I found this on the street
ah and I eat it so yes and I thought of
you and I was like uh uh I think Anya
Senpai would like this so
um
this is my half eaten fish
I see wait so it's just like
an indirect kiss
yes with the five and everything
oh my God oh my God
well I'll be eating then no no problem
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
okay do you want the ultra normal or the
oh yes normal okay Ultra normal yep
[Music]
okay this time I'm sending it to the
right person
oh my God
[Music]
oh my God you guys won't believe
this
[Music]
what is this
is
hahaha so funny
just for you special and then the
expired date is
like yesterday what's today
[Music]
I see
it's because we have different time
zones
[Music]
guys
okay I see I see uh you can use this uh
whenever you want
to feet massage
okay thank you so much for the kind of
view thank you
by the way I'm normal yeah
I think so yeah you think so okay
I'll hold on to your words if I'm not
mistaken wow
reception I I have a lot of I have a lot
of additional stuffs
guys you know what this kind of fits I'm
not gonna lie I like I like this
wait can you see okay can you do uh can
you give me a present because it's your
birthday can you can you say
yeah can you say
but I'm not a cat
cute
say say it again in a cute place
okay
from my color ID gen 2.
thank you
thank you I know let's go
let's go let's go
happy birthday
I'm so worried of you
no don't be worried I'm okay love you
bye
[Music]
huh what was that
my mom is better
[Music]
guys
oh my God that's that's so freaking
funny bro
bro that's so freaking funny not gonna
lie oh hello
who is this
oh
[Music]
um
I can speak Japanese
what is she saying
um
[Music]
I must
um
[Music]
how about you
foreign
[Music]
oh
my God yes
um
thank you thank you too yes thank you
thank you
no
[Music]
myself oh
yes yes
[Music]
um
um okay
I will give anyone yes
food yes
yes food food
[Music]
um
um pasta
[Music]
let me know
Ramen Ramen Ramen also ski yes
yes
go to Japan let's go let's go together
oh my God yes
[Music]
is going to Indonesia next time
Indonesia I will also take you we can
Ramen together yes
come to Indonesia let's go
uh
[Applause]
thank you again and happy birthday yes
happy birthday yes
uh I hope you have a fun birthday okay
yes yes
guys
let's go
guys see
today
[Music]
oh
hello
hi
hi nice to meet you nice to meet you
nice to meet you who are you oh my name
is
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
like a real quick
uh
foreign
I guess
thanks for coming
thank you two four four four invite me
um
[Music]
let's go
thank you
[Music]
are you are you okay
yes yes
um
[Music]
thank you
what was she giggling at
yeah
she's been super busy lately
hmm
[Music]
let's see
hi hi
beautiful oh my God
wait what is it buffering oh no
get in my place though
so
foreign
[Music]
so so happy
so so happy oh my God
[Music]
guys
and then also a lost cat
and then also lost cat
put it in
ID foreign
[Music]
foreign
I got a video
[Music]
I got a video with everyone
I got a video can I count this as 18
person no
no
[Music]
let's see
let's go
happy birthday
[Music]
thank you that was that was a video from
Minnesota
thank you thank you yeah he even
included the subtitle what that's some
kind of him
[Music]
there was subtitles
thank you thank you
thank you so much
Road
[Music]
they were also lots of Polo stars coming
today I really appreciate it even though
I don't really talk with them that much
hmm
[Music]
it was EXO of Alyssa escapee
Vesper of Pampers
and then hot cup of temples and also Rio
Sun omapro
[Music]
all right
hahaha
18 now if I count Rio can can I can I
count the video as one
can I count the video as one
hmm
18 is it is it okay
is it okay all right all right then 18.
okay so we need five more people
getting closer to the end
[Music]
well everyone's telling me to pound it
as one so
adios
[Music]
it I'm gonna store Yago stickers
on it
foreign
[Music]
next week we have
Expo and Ford Fest and so the JP the JP
talents are especially the little busy
hmm
I don't wanna I don't want to call it as
an unfortunate timing because it's a
it's a good thing I'm so excited about
the Expo and the forecast
hmm
[Music]
as yes
yeah so
so in this this kind and this timing
everyone is super busy
younger guys
[Music]
hmm
yes
all right
no no I I can't speak Japanese
[Music]
oh my God
what time is
JP for JP come to think of it
comes the thing of it
[Music]
foreign
I am so happy
[Music]
ah
hello
[Music]
Iris
hello hi hi did you enjoy my ASMR yes
holy
[Laughter]
what what song was that what is it was
it was the it was
um so I have like this mic cover on top
of my
um oh oh my condenser mic it's like oh
yeah oh yeah I have I have it too yeah I
was I was twisting it
yeah
yeah doesn't it sound amazing yeah I
love doing this
it's what happened oh my God happy
birthday thank you I just came home
thank you
pretty late
no no no it's okay
did you already announced your mirror
yeah it did I did it
um see performance oh
um
[Music]
I like the glass yes
I'm so happy yeah what sort of drop is
gonna be what what what is the drop of
bliss
um a drop of bliss
um well a drop of Happiness
oh is that saying that they're gonna be
using it for like wine or like Boba oh
okay I thought for a second the drop of
bliss is like I don't know maybe you're
here never mind
a drop of what a drop of I I don't know
double flank maybe I don't know liquids
um
it's very hot today
I was I went out shopping today
yes touching grass literally it was like
also pouch the Press
I didn't sweat that much yeah
so much that would drip into the grass
you know
well I thought
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign foreign
[Music]
you know
that you like the blonde
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
but like there is Anime that could
I don't watch Freya some people in China
are like free but recently I do watch
um Gundam
do you watch that ah iron blood orphans
does not really BL is it though
it's not I mean at least Canon wise I
don't like that one too well too like
wait did you watch all of blood orphans
yes
yeah because you know at the end you
know like yeah at the end at the end
it's like you know what I don't mind it
because I like I like the I like the
girls too yeah the girls are cool too
but I was surprised because like wasn't
he like willing to like
have kids with both of them
yeah
always spoilers I'm sorry oh my God it
just it bothered me that like you know
like he was like oh I could go either
way and I think it's just but the thing
is it was it was actually kind of pretty
incredible then you know because it was
it was he that much of a Playboy
nah I don't think it's not that I don't
think he just doesn't care that much
I guess yeah I think he just doesn't
care yeah he just doesn't care that much
I think the girls were just like I want
kids and he was like okay yeah bro like
he cares more about other guy than the
girls
the other guy went you know he yeah
[Laughter]
you should watch more Gundam I recommend
more Gundam to you I'm in the middle I'm
actually in the middle of watching seed
yeah how are you enjoying seeds seed is
amazing that's my favorite I'm selling
my um I'm still in the first season oh
you're running in the middle you're
gonna love it yes the seed has a nice
ship as well it's very yeah yeah I think
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
that's not canon but you know I feel
like there's there's this one part
though that bothers me when it comes to
that but maybe you can talk about
it when you get there yeah when you get
to that part yeah I'm still in the
middle of watching so yeah I like how
seed has ishirakida that's why I started
watching it
is
so far
that's great just maybe uh I don't know
Destiny see destiny that comes after
seed might be a little iffy but you'll
still enjoy it probably I see it well
thank you so much yeah sorry I ended up
talking for a long time
I hope you have an amazing birthday in
Japan I think it just uh is this is your
birthday like now or is it birthday like
oh no
um it's um in Chester it's like
yesterday oh it's today okay happy
birthday
thank you I hope it was a great one I
will get your drop of bliss
it's a nice glass I got the don't don't
sweat on it okay oh yeah yeah I won't I
won't I won't go ahead I don't know what
sort of situation it would be for me to
get sweat inside there but okay okay
okay
yeah don't don't ask okay okay
hahaha
oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah bye
foreign
[Music]
my goodness so that was that was Iris
that was Iris
Mother Day
um
[Music]
mosquitoes
gotchi
foreign
[Music]
I also recommend Unicorn oh I've heard
about that one
I'm really I only I've only watched like
two or three Gundams still so I I need
to watch more
Gundam unicorn
oh Mobile Suit Gundam unicorn
huh
wait is it a novel is it an anime
[Music]
it's the new one
I wish the new one I'm so excited for
the for the second season
[Music]
it's an anime oh thank you for telling
me
oh I'll add that to my watch list
I'm gonna add Gundam Gundam unicorn to
my watch list
I like Gundam
it's fine
I think Zeta was the best Gundam show
all I know about Gundam Zeta is that
apparently it's got the most death
counts or something
apparently apparently it's got It's got
the most deaths
that's like that's the only thing I I
know about that again
thanks for spoilers bro people dying in
Gundam is not spoiler what you talking
about
people dying in Gundam is not spoiler
bro
bro people die and Gundam
people die when they're killed
[Music]
bye
foreign
people dying in Gundam is not spoiler
um
[Music]
all right let me see
let's see
wow um only four more people
and closer
[Music]
yeah I think closers
foreign
[Music]
oh happy birthday
foreign
[Music]
a soccer
um
[Music]
everybody
foreign
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
I don't know
it is
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
soccer
Jonah Tennessee
[Music]
foreign
soccer
see you soon
[Music]
that's how
I see nothing
Freddy login
[Music]
haha
Biryani
on this
[Music]
hi hi
hello
[Music]
foreign
hmm
[Music]
what the heck
am I getting scammed
was it a scam
[Music]
Minecraft oh my God
bro hey yo
yo
hmm
[Music]
that's so good
by the way
have you guys about my merchandises now
on sale
encyclopedia all the pro shop and also
big cats
[Music]
have you guys for my merchandises
we have rubber mats we have fast case we
have Plus
case is
[Music]
also the voice said
foreign
[Music]
s are on the description of
Empire
[Music]
okay
Guru
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
hmm
ah thought isn't it
[Laughter]
let's see
um
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
hahaha
um
[Music]
foreign
ministers
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
on it is
[Music]
Monday I don't know why it was muted
because I never mute the output the
Discord output on obs
I I don't understand I don't know
[Music]
this is
tonight
[Music]
foreign
oh my God
[Music]
I got something cute
oh
you guys know do you guys know Silvers
um Phil first I I hope I'm pronouncing
the name correctly
um my membership emote artist
my membership emote artist
I got a little present it's so cute
[Music]
no
foreign
[Music]
haha
can we get skia and omella for the rest
dude I don't even know what Kyla is
doing
like she promised
but it was an empty promise
it was an empty promise you promised
[Music]
it was an empty promise I don't know
onion
thank you so much
[Music]
she thinks you're in a different time
zone again I thought she was the one
who has been in a different time zone
all this time because he's always up
streaming at this hour usually up until
morning
[Music]
like
like girlies living in the EU time zone
you know pilot Kyle is living in the UK
time zone
[Music]
see you
just Hollow EU legit bro
times okay
happy birthday thank you
okay
that was calling you time something
keep operating in every time zone you
know what true
you know what
very much true
[Music]
I am telling the truth Am I Wrong nah
am I wrong no
[Music]
it is
highlights the time zone oh my God
[Music]
hmm
Osama um
I told you guys
you need to start off behind her back
and then she'll appears you know that's
how that's how you fish a Kyla kowalskia
[Music]
hello Kyla from Whole Life EU
if I am Hollow jfp you are Hollow EU
Kyla
[Music]
hello
oh my goodness
and your other family
[Music]
it's not nice to lie to me you're Senpai
you know
[Music]
let's see
yeah I am for senpai
I am her senpai
hmm
[Music]
oh yeah
um
[Music]
description
yoga
I have a cool rubber mats I have this
cool test Case by the way the art for
this one will be available as the
membership wallpaper
and then I have a fancy class
ooh spicy right
yeah I was on the way out I was I was in
the middle of I was in the middle of
promoting my merchandise
[Music]
foreign
spicy
[Music]
yeah
come on come on the links the full links
if you guys want the gift Jack Link it's
on the description
[Music]
as well
it's available on social bus
by the way
foreign
[Music]
hmm
well you know what I'm happy that these
days
well now voice packs are accessible for
the Indonesian Bros too you know
see guys foreign
[Music]
I'm also happy
hmm
[Music]
you know um past birthday voice packs
the 2021 and the 2022 one
those are also available in tokopedia
not tokopedia social bus
well the merchandisers were available on
tokopedia but they're not available
anymore
guys
[Music]
out of stock already
thank you
[Music]
so pretty
so cool so shot is so pretty
[Music]
which one is your favorite voice pack of
Mine by the way oh yeah for those who
don't know for the birthday voice packs
I write I write all the scripts myself
and stuffs
[Music]
media guys
subscribe
then line line
happy birthday thank you thank you
guys
[Music]
who might this be
who might this be hello
[Music]
hello oh hello
hello
um
[Music]
foreign
beef
sauce
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
Melvin's
office
[Music]
my language English
um
[Music]
[Applause]
Europe
oh you're wrong
oh yeah
[Music]
almost on your whole life
um
one two continue
[Music]
I'm coming happy birthday okay thank you
foreign
I'm the last person maybe
yeah
[Music]
I I I I want to I want to swear I'm the
last person I yes you are yes you're the
last person yeah
I'm sorry I wanted to
um in this Tower not as the last person
so I apologize
where I'm very go out to say you
um oh thank you so much thank you thank
you
ah anymore
[Music]
no but hey
it's so good
yeah
yeah my pleasure thank you sugoi it's an
owner
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
congratulations
[Music]
hi
I can't wait I'm so excited yeah I can't
wait for it
yeah thank you thank you
thank you you can sleep well thank you
so much
for coming I really appreciate it yeah
yeah I really appreciate it
bye bye bye congratulations
foreign
[Music]
23 out of 23 people
not so much thank you Dawn
yeah
mama mama
[Music]
company
foreign
[Music]
but
this week well this week JSC
this week KFC
it's gonna be the whole Expo
yay
[Music]
don't forget guys don't forget to
support us in the Expo and the portfest
also see you guys in both of it
both of them I'm the Expo and also the
Ford Fest
welcome
we have Italian Guys
[Music]
um
so much everyone
hopefully it will be it will be an
unforgettable experience well it will be
will be one but oh my gosh I'm so
excited can't wait
[Music]
okay one more promotions
foreign
talk to your camera
well
sister birthday celebration 2023
I have one special voice set and then
for the birthday merchandises I have
rubber mats to the gardens Quest
packets a Whimsical trip and glass drop
a place and then if you buy the complete
set you will get the polluted style
remote card with a duplicated gold
standard autographs
on sale
by the way the the full links for the
merchandises are in the description
is
so cool all of them so freaking cool
[Music]
so cool right
come on
don't forget about the voice set
yeah the best case the best case got
different illustrations by the way this
illustration will be available as a
wallpaper in membership
for Members Only
this illustration will be available as
the membership for paper a wallpaper
that you can get if you're a member so
throwing the membership
available
join membership
[Music]
oh my God thank you so much to everyone
who came oh my God
23 question marks people yes
foreign
[Music]
guys
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you