[Music]
oh
w
[Music]
a
n
[Music]
oh
you
[Music]
K KY K oh smoothie
no there goes my cat hello oh my God so
cute
right yay it's better if you don't see
my arms but I'm holding one of you guys
and you also are dressed
up
[Music]
cute but the whole dress is really
pretty it's just it's going to let you
know that wa if I if I get rid of the
chicken just for now just for
now then then it's not so
oopsy not so bad
cute the holes for the arms don't
perfectly align but besides that
cute oh if I look down it kind of aligns
a little bit better
[Laughter]
[Music]
look at me so
cute o I'm a anime girl from the 90s
yay this dress gives me Little Red
Riding Hood little riding redhood little
that girl's vibes
making the dress bigger um not sure if
it's supposed to be
bigger
um
uh yeah yeah yeah I guess that kind of
works better but it just looks a bit
oversized
oopsie wow cute
thank you blue for making this o o oh
yeah wait now my arms Al line when I
breathe out or in not sure which one it
is O lag what what lag eh did I forget
to set the no it's ultra low
latency no lag subtle lag no lag YouTube
is up
tea he
yo the ribbon is so cute so perfect for
this hairstyle because my braids go to
the back you could imagine that the
ribbon is attached where the braids
are so waav is little goody two shoes
I'm going to make it a bit smaller again
[Music]
though and if I don't look if I look at
some other part of my body like if I
don't focus on the ribbon then the
ribbon just like on the corner of my eye
it looks like big foxer cat
ears
cute Okie
doky chicken is also with us wait the
chicken shoes are so cute look at
the look at those little shoes
[Music]
[Laughter]
a aren't you a cutie patootie oh wait
why is chat not on screen hello there we
go well well
well so cute
sorry uh today we're playing little
goodie T shoes um which I think is kind
of unexpected on my channel I don't
normally play games like that but
uh first of all you know it's it's uh
almost Halloween and I thought this
would be a nice game for Halloween
because it's like horror but the real
reason why I'm mostly considering it is
because it's set in Austria so I have to
play
it no no I do play indie games but these
kind of games not so
much not really like horror and this
like pixel from above storytelling I
don't
know but I'm sure it will be good
because the game has a a little bit of a
uh you know its own little fandom and
you know I don't know it seems quite
loved out
there uh yeah I don't think I can finish
it in this one day that's fine um we'll
see how it goes though we we at least
want to take a look into it yeah and and
it's not like like jump scare scary
obviously but it has some I think some
horror elements about it
nonetheless ah ah there we go I was
wondering if today we'll get like a DEA
moment DEA
death here you made
meeses celestes from astral shift I
don't know it might not be a DEA but
Astros shift is the is the company
behind the game
so some some
involvement
yeah um okay well then Dev make sure to
let me know if I'm doing something wrong
or if there's something I should um take
care of or so I would love that are you
a voice actor for the game and the game
mascot yo okay wow you're a game
mascot I want to be a games
mascot fun
okay cool
yo okay then let's
begin
whoops uh oh wait do I have sounds right
now or is the nor sounds you can change
your controls at any time in the
settings menu modern or classic uh
where's the difference
ah
ah I will do modern e for selecting and
R for back well the game will surely
tell me that whenever something pops up
modern please this is already so
[Music]
cute notice keep this control for yeah
yeah yeah sure voice why no German
what should I do which one should I do
is our our mascot voice actress in the
chat for the English version or for the
Japanese version English okay let's do
English Okie
do the HS are alive with the sound of
music
[Music]
[Applause]
welcome to
Austria oh yeah it looks like
Austria I hope this is not copyright
[Music]
stuff please go easy on
me why it's so
pretty who's singing this
[Music]
wow
wow who wait a second I know the singer
Diana I just recognized her voice
now took me a while
[Music]
this is
beautiful snake danger
noodle oh W
no it's
[Music]
like
oh little goody to
shoes I I think this must have some
fairy
tale like things about it that that was
really good animation and the singing
was so beautiful Diana Garnet
yeah I know
her
wow
wow what the
heck what the heck this is already
making a good
[Music]
impression whoo wo it moves
whoa press any button little goodie two
shoes Ah that's also Diana isn't it is
[Music]
it wow this
music
she the secret lies in the woods
says the
book The taale of little goody T
[Music]
shoes oh so it's like a fairy tale Once
Upon a Time in the heart of a remote
Valley an elderly woman ventured deep
into the woods and search for
mushrooms oh that's an old lady when all
of a sudden she heard a loud cry in the
distance but she looks like she could be
little goody Tes my goodness oh
oh
baby CR cradle inside of rope basket was
a cheerful baby girl bubble
bubble
wub oh oh my what do I do oh oh no it's
a
baby worry not my dear I'll name you
Ela oh cute and so holl holla and
Elisa's spent their days to together the
oh ke B sorry that was too fast but I
think it was Kea
B [\h__\h]
you as both grew closer so did their
love for one
another a
mommy carrots yummy look look grenny
look well done El such a good
child not all Bliss lasts forever and as
time went by she died I mean the grandma
right oh it's all German what it said
something about Egypt
[Music]
what oh so did
holles I I'll take care of
you I'll do whatever takes
granny don't cry my love you always said
you wanted it I'm sure you'll cherish
[Music]
it
granny a I love you Elisa I'm surprised
she's not an evil
witch
wow thank you for granting my only wish
of having a daughter or what
well
[Music]
well and the fire goes
out
cute for goodness sake there goes my
last match match match are you on Tinder
what for goodness sake oh is this Diana
still is this Diana or our our voice
actress girl in the chat sorry I forgot
the name
celestus is it
you oh no this is is this Diana wait are
you di wait what wait wait a second what
what is that okay you're
not get of
confused okay cool oh my God I didn't
realize that Diana was part of this
ah I'm so tired of this wait why am I
voicing it she said something but I
guess she doesn't read exactly the
lines oh yeah okay watch my sheets Elisa
sweep my floors Elisa Elisa Elisa
Elisa oh I show
them I'd make them scrap my pots and
pants my shoes even have them wipe down
all my windows every last one clean out
my Earth and F me some water better yet
I'd have them running around calling me
Miss Elisa all
day harf oh [\h__\h] oh if I only were rich
[Music]
man this is so
cute all the steak I could ever want all
the shiny dresses look at her
eyes it's the o o
eyes one for each day of the week with
shoes and jewels to match and mates all
the mates I could ever
want oh if
[Music]
only well one can
dream ala oh for goodness
sake Mama Mia as austr like to
[Music]
say on your way home L what are you
doing wandering about in the dark wait
should I give the an Austrian
[Music]
accent what what are you what are you
doing wandering about in the dark Elisa
you ought to know it's dangerous out
here I'm not Wonder should I keep her
austan accent too
now I'm not wondering about Mr
Ludwick I've been working here oh we
should say ha ludig I've been working
like if youd so kindly
believe uh you know better than you know
better than to put yourself in danger
El uh yeah lud yeah I've told you before
it's not Ludwick it's
Ludwick if anyone's putting me in danger
it's you I'd be home already had you not
stop me for an
earful uh come come now Elisa uh come
now e we've got good reason to
worry all this vigilance for what what
am I to be afraid of the witch the Witch
there's a witch there is a witch after
all there's always a witch and what your
what's your ver Elisa you're not to
question such
matters oh there's Hinrich too
Hinrich almost like the he maneuver
what do you say We Walk You
Home uh I believe I'll be just fine on
my own hair
hinr no more no more details Elisa it's
for your own good lest I come across the
wit I
know uh let us hope you don't come to
regret your words
[Music]
less becomes creepy now really
I can't stand these
folks okay movement interact e run up
button okay menu R
[Music]
okay I can't run with the up
button is it really the up
button oh shift
oh
I it's scary scary here here we go oh
can I use the other shift no I can't use
the other shift can I change that I
prefer using the other shift it's a
little bit too
close can I change
it maybe
not oh probably not nice menu though
very nice
menu Leaf jump scar I hate
leaves I I know I'm not supposed to go
there I was I was hoping I could run
around the tree stump okay okay I'm
sorry sorry
sorry do I still have to click can I not
skip that with the keyboard ah I think I
could with e okay
[Music]
um this thing so faded I can't even read
it
left right primor primor ah up ke back
Peaks so the left is
unknown wait what about it doesn't even
say wait there's four paths it says I
guess this would be
left and this would be up and this would
be right why does it not say where did
where did I come
from where should I go where was the
plan to go back home cuz back home is I
guess up maybe if do I live in Prim b or
in ke bag Prim Prim what
Prim maybe let's go up the game will
probably tell me if I'm going
wrong frogs I hear
frogs wow
cute yeah jump jump don't fall good job
platforming game now
wow what can I go up here
no and this is so
[Music]
pretty oh another sign but only the left
has a real sign Pine Tree this pine tree
that everything's about pine trees
around
here oh because Kea back is she saying
is she saying that because Kea B Kea B I
guess is like pine tree m
Mountain keep back Viewpoint keep back
Peak on the
left uh which way do does game want me
to go
[Music]
peek whoa is that a huge grape or is
that
perspective I think it's
perspective pick that up pick it up pick
it up
yeah come
on ah we got grapes oh grapes are
growing here oh
yeah okay it's
perspective
wow I'm so
fascinated oh
wow hello was that just the wind yeah
right I
know it's impossible to keep this
Lantern lit in this wind oh it went off
oh
no no
guess I'll be finding my way home in the
dark I
suppose a bird Twitter bird is it you
are you lost here can I save
you make sure you use up all your safe
slots to avoid too much backtracking oh
what why why would I backtrack am I
going to
die wait how to
save oh is this a safe point
uh is the bird a safe
Point
huh I feel so weird not having to use my
mouse my right hand is like
useless I want to use my right
hand I suppose I ought to chop some more
wood soon just when i' gotten rid of all
those pesky splinters and blisters
covered in age scars a tree tree trunk
sits bare its dry surface exposed to the
elements the
elements oh
[Music]
spooky the wind is so
strong is this my house we made it hey
yo there's something in the tree
here but I can't talk to
it sus
what in the lord's name what oh I guess
it's kind of
messy what in the lord's name happen
here I ought to find my
matches oh oh it wasn't a Tinder match
it was a fire
match oh I get it
now that's what she
meant ah oh how perfect she has a one of
these things
[Laughter]
oh thank goodness they didn't touch
Granny's Spinning
Wheel where should I go
first oh no you was going to The Pantry
what do you know what do you know where
your matches are when you lost them
maybe
[Music]
upstairs
ooh quite the nice rug and the nice
clock let's see what what time don't I
don't want to think about
it NY what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h] I'm messing but I think oh it
almost killed
me what the
[\h__\h] was that thing I I I was dreaming
or I'm scared
what was I thinking leaving it here okay
we got the match okay
Tinder wa
is is Tinder called Tinder as a joke
because matches are in a Tinder Box and
what is that a
j I never this what Tinder
meant what the
[\h__\h] the tea in the Lo is literally a
flame yeah but I just fought because ooh
hot spicy ooh I don't know man I I
didn't know
Tinder oh my God I'm so done already
mentally I want to light the fire
now use Lantern
preserve your matches light your Lantern
using matches be careful not to waste
them how long does one
go I don't like time
pressure this is a nice bedroom I like
it so comfy I really have to go through
all this junk sometime I suppose a small
wooden trunk filled with various
knickknacks knck
knacks very
German uh there's 10 different endings
are you
saying
[Music]
sheh whoever broke into my home must be
out there somewhere how am I to sleep
like this shattering in the Wind the
glass paines tremble in their wooden
frames oh damn this house is falling
apart is this game
[Music]
difficult oh it's been a long time since
I've gone into Granny holl's room not
that there's anything to see there
anyhow I'm going to go
downstairs now that we have the matches
what are we here for exactly not leaving
here until it makes sense of what
happened
here o sorry sorry sorry I'm not trying
to
here aha we got the broom H maybe we can
go fly somewhere with that that's a
really nice frame everything's so
[Music]
pretty I'm scared I'm scared I'm scared
I'm scared I'm scared something's going
to happen what is this good
grave what if it was that which the
town's folk have been going on about
keep it together
Elise it was definitely a
burglar H that said I'm not going
anywhere without my broom why do you
love your broom so much are you a witch
are you the witch are you the witch that
people are talking about
H who in the lord's name got into my
house okay can I leave now oh
yeah is this the back exit all
right is this your
open how long has it been since I last
used this thing I
wonder is her weapon you think stringy
cobwebs and dust cling to the old oven's
wooden doors as though sealing them this
is a perfect oven for pizza
oopsie I'm scared I'm scared I'm scared
I'm scared I'm scared I'm scared
I'm
scared oh is this a farming
plot
land not farming much right now this
isn't the time to be watering the garden
is it where did by time the wells wooden
structur strands sprayed and worn are we
ever going to be farming in this
game all right I guess we go this way
trying to fight the burglar or
what I think we should just ignore it
oh what a
view damn she's like on top of the
mountain and what is this is this my
what could this
be crazy dog
house oh
[\h__\h] what the
hello
moyy dare you are you Shameless be out
with it give me back all you took right
hurry
up wait
[Music]
please please forgive
me damn
out with it wait she's just a cute nice
girl she's the purple girl from the
artwork that I saw explain yourself you
I I keep
on
cute uh what are you doing in my
house wait you know so she reminds me of
uh a girl from Toho
project the is it P PTI
I
forgot yeah yeah P yeah yeah like she
even has Moons and stars on her dress on
the bottom and she got those twintails
and
stuff
[Music]
m p knowledge
yeah just going to get a
concussion well please don't hit me I
was just hiding there were these men and
I I won't ask you a second time phe
hurry it up give me back everything you
took right now I I didn't take
anything I was just scared oh man look
at her she's
terrified show me your
hands oh but I oh is this is this voiced
by the girl
maybe now show me your pockets and make
it get
quick ooh monies it's
you I
see matches your profile
picture I I keep telling you I I didn't
steal anything ma'am this is all I have
I swear coins and weeds what are you
doing up here in the mountains oh
that's I I'm a traveler
ma'am turn around you say you're a
traveler are you all by
yourself yes yeah I'm I'm traveling
alone I hoped I could rest for the night
in this Village
but I saw some people walking in the
woods I it frightened me so I ran to
find some place to
hide be that as it may you're still
please forgive me ma'am I I didn't mean
to make such a mess oh sh
it would you stop calling me that yeah
she's a girl a little girl she could be
maybe only 2 years older or so than you
I'm Sor for goodness
sake all right well I might let you go
if you can prove your inoc sense stat is
oh oh that's I I I don't know what else
I can do ma'am
H well you can start by cleaning up this
mess that that that that doesn't really
PR for innocence but okay
sure and then you can uh sorry I but I
did it yeah that's it a made all right
listen carefully now first you'll be
tidying up this mess you've made in fact
you can clean my whole house from top to
bottom they'll teach you not to go
storming into strangers homes I'm sorry
I I I ma'am complaining already are
you wouldn't you agree this is the least
you can do
yes of course I I'll gladly do it
ma'am huh good and in exchange I suppose
you can stay here but no more
feing I not a fief man I'll be the judge
of that thank you very much thank you
soon anyhow you work for me and I'll
give you a place to stay fair enough
wouldn't you say wait we still don't
even know her name why don't we ask for
her name first it does sound fair ma'am
and it is very kind of you but I I am
not a
fe fine you're not a thief now would you
stop calling me ma'am do I look like an
old hag to
you I'm sorry you you don't I I
apologize all
right my name is Elisa and you'd be best
remember it
yes I'm so sorry I forgot to introduce
myself yeah oh look at those shoes do
look like from
um the Netherlands though those shoes uh
Rosen Marie Rosen Marie Rose Ren
[Music]
Marina that's not the most German name
is she not supposed to be Austrian I
wonder my name is Rosen Marina Rosen
Marine I I don't know speaking saying
that in uh German doesn't quite
work I mean judging by the shoes I I I
could imagine she's not from
here yeah she's a
traveler
H maybe this is um yeah d yeah I was
going to say yeah cuz of um the
neverland
shoes yeah I got it right I got it right
okay I don't know how to pronounce that
in Dutch though
[Music]
unfortunately
Mar I don't know how to even speak like
a Dutch person so I will just forget it
my my my name is uh Rosen M it's a
pleasure to meet you Miss good sake for
goodness sake just Elisa is fine
come now you have a lot of work to do
yeah of course I guess even though you
admitted that I'm not a thief I guess I
will still do what you're asking of me
to prove my
innocence that I'm not a thief even
though you admitted for to me not being
a thief so there's I don't know I don't
know about the logic there but I guess
I'll still do it since I already
committed to it okay and cuz you
[Music]
cute all right
are we going to let her sleep in that
house too in that little
shed our
servant then we will be just like those
evil aunts in the fairy tales
[Music]
wonderful oh it's a chicken coop oh that
would be
lovely how could you even do all this
yeah I want an explanation too look at
my floors I'm sorry
those don't even look like footsteps
from her
shoes I'm I'm I'm sorry even Gran's
plates shattered to Pieces what are you
a wild boy I'm surprised you didn't
break my windows and Tear Down the
Walls yeah
H all right
well you know what you
did anyway anyhow here take this make
certain you you get into every nook and
cranny you hear oh
yeah while you're at it you can sweep
the chimney and clean out the fireplace
too do everything for me also make me
some steak wipe that stain off my wall
and wash all my windows all right I want
this place SP wow I'm evil why am I so
evil I was raised so well by my grandma
everything everybody my grandma and I we
were both so nice and now I'm like this
what happened how we the baddies how
much time has passed since my grandma
passed that like and what happened in
between to make me act up like this I
would like to
[Music]
know maybe I'm the Badd I would I would
not be
surprised cuz I got a broom and I live
in a little witchy
house girl boss she do be bossing around
the
girl of
course okay for goodness sake and I told
you to quit calling me that I'm
sorry come now let me show you the well
out in the back oh but I oh you can do
it yourself okay anything to make up for
what I've
done look here Lassie I have no good
reason to trust you
I like how her straw hat is like in the
shape of a witch hat who makes a straw
hat look like that what's the point are
you a
witch she must be a witch I didn't mean
to every single corner of this house is
to be absolutely spotless by Sunrise
dare to crush me even once and I'll be
having a word with the town's folk you
here are we clear
sheesh there's going to be a lot of
voice acting today isn't there I think
so yeah uh I'm sorry I'll um I'll do my
best be careful not to wake me either I
have Sunday mass to attend tomorrow I
I'll keep quiet okay good night
Elisa huh all right wonderful um we're
also kind of just pretending that the
thing upstairs never
happened my nightmares catch up to
me oh [\h__\h]
what now you've done it
Elisa there was hardly a need to be that
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah didn't need to be that harsh but
still what if she's dangerous
or Worse even what if what if she's
still which
uh well yeah I mean I was saying her hat
is shaped like that that sound we kep
been talking about oh what would granny
holler do I wonder she didn't raise me
to be like yeah yeah that's what I
said I even threatened to tell on her
too it's done is done I suppose I'll
make sense of it tomorrow it's best I go
to
bed bro she's really
me
sag cute that menu at the top left what
when food is gone I need to eat oh
cute
cute she's in a little night
gown it's morning
already I can't be late for Sunday mass
or f f h
will huh you can't be serious what was I
thinking
what she's probably taking everything I
own by now oh you're very paranoid now
aren't you no everything will be
sparkling I believe it managing stamina
you will lose one bread for each time
period that passes by that's six uh
Times bread a
day
what what i f one bread per day because
it looked like it it just took one bread
for one
day manag your normal food and key items
through the item
menu you can consume and use items
through the item menu as
well
[Music]
okay let's see how it looks a it's
[Applause]
sparkly or maybe not doesn't seem like
she took or broke anything
but hey Rosen Marine oh Rosen Marine oh
rosemarine she writes it differently
here
rosemarine was that her name can't
believe she tidied up and left just like
that but maybe she's in my chicken
CP I didn't even give her anything to
eat last night the poor
thing now where could she have gotten
to chicken
C maybe she is uh patuli by day and
chicken by no chicken by day and Puli by
night maybe she's the the manifestation
of my chickens have I ever asked myself
where my where my chickens
went maybe it's like a Shrek
situation is she a chicken
now I would like that oh okay she's not
a chicken but she is in my chicken
coop for goodness so maybe that makes
her a chicken cuz she's still there
there are you you
Elise honestly what are you doing here
I'm sorry I'm sorry I I really liked it
in here I decided to stay as a
chicken I was intending to leave first
thing in the morning but I I was afraid
I'd get lost in the
dark never mind come with me now I'm
sorry I are you taking me to the Village
who do you take me for some rat forget
what I said last night not exactly my
finest moment I didn't mean to be such a
brute truth be
told I'm sorry I'm sorry for what I did
to for goodness sake I got
it all that I got it all of that's dead
and buried now come I'm running late for
Sunday mass okay
oh how wa for me l i i i know that in
this game there is some like you know um
girls love going
on and I I think we have several options
maybe maybe that's also why there's so
many
endings oh oh they're so cute together I
like these pixel
girls
flock chicken
chicken
flocky
[Music]
[Applause]
flocky oh it's not a chicken what the
hell I was getting excited bro
fluffy
companion um in the pixel version it
looked like one of its eyes is like gone
here see oh I'm so
glad wait now this eye is fine
now where have you
been you know this goat random
goat you know this
go of course yeah
I met it on the way to Kea B we've been
together
since yes we were we were eh why are you
saying it like that oh he's the cutest
little thing isn't he I don't know I
prefer
chickens the CEST little thing you say
anyway anyhow I ought to get going
wouldn't want to be late for Sunday mess
yes
yeah I'll be back in a moment f
[Music]
all right so far nothing spooky has
happened in a while thank God I I have
to say you did a decent job tidying up
you did pretty much everything I asked
you to oh I'm so
glad I I wanted to assure you I meant no
harm Ela it kept me up for hours last
night thinking you oh sh it I get it
already know need to tell me here have
some bread you must be hungry yes
can I eat some
[Music]
too thank you Elisa you're really too
for goodness sake good grief you do
remember I hit you with a broom right
why do you need to remind her I thought
you weren't really proud of what you did
now let's just not talk about it anymore
I called your Fe made to do my bidding
and
whatnot most folks would have tossed me
right out the moment they found me but
you didn't I suppose I didn't anyhow I'm
heading out all right don't wander about
and don't make a mess of course I I
won't
laser oh my throat already hurts from
screaming as
uh what was my
name Elisa Elisa I'm Elisa I thought she
was Elisa for some reason right
[Laughter]
now pursue Your Love interests talk to
your favorite girl when you see a heart
above her head to schedule a romantic
date for
later what the heck can I um do like
several like if I date her I'm not like
messing up my chances for other girls
right now am
I I don't know not not really like what
what's going on between them right now
doesn't really feel like The
Logical path for from here on out would
be like getting
intimate before you go
Ela I have something to tell you I love
you you could come meet me later today
what what's keeping you from telling me
now um well it's important so I'll be in
the bath by Nightfall all right we can
have spicy time in the chicken
C for goodness sake it best be worth my
value
here I promise it's nothing
bed we'll see about that no we we will
we will see about that oh this is such a
cute room wait the the entrance was so
cute okay let's
[Music]
safe nice okay oh I got some m you've
got me would you like to revisit the
game oh H see no no no
no
oh the BTM has like pretty
voices do you hear
[Music]
it
wow W well the grapes look much better
now I'll get an info from father H if I
don't hurry
up unlock map menu ooh let's
go W grape vine path that's my house oh
and there's a chicken it looks like a
Mario Party game field
thingy uh the creek the
Viewpoint Crossroads Village entrance
Village
Square Village in Stables back at where
is the church I guess in the Village
Square
okay and then currently we want to
attend Sunday mass and then later we
want to meet Rosen Marina at the
backyard at dusk okay cool cool wao Also
let's see normal items
okay just some random
yapping wow such deep
lore that you will never
understand I'll eat this
[Music]
I'm not going to translate that for you
guys you better learn some German
[Music]
now okay was it uh not up there I think
it was down and then
right I
think yeah we went over the Creek and
there were signs before the creek that
said uh keep bag I
think over here I
[Music]
think
what not this
way
H wait never mind right was primor
[Music]
never mind maybe we do have to go that
other
[Music]
way yeah but no maybe it's
down guess it's down
[Music]
here
yeah for sure makes sense looking at the
map W
cute everything's drawn so pretty but
let me have a fro candy
grle ah no way there's a freaking
[Music]
grle oh it's a [\h__\h] grandma too she
has an orange cat chky wony is that you
come here why don't you she looks cute
she has bread oh does she sell bread oh
she has a black cat too on the left
side cute
yeah h ah is H her her am her
husband good than granny
gr oh on your way to the mass I see
anything to keep ah f h of my
back I have some fresh buns they'll
cheer you right up fresher than my buns
at least at this point you know get it
cuz I'm old why don't you take a look
look
Becca
[Music]
wow
cute yo the
bread good stuff lip kon's Bakery oh
lipk it is about time for some lip cing
soon uh lip cing in English was um
[\h__\h] I know it but I
forgot um
uh gingerbread yeah the bakery is called
gingerbread looking cheeky again today
dear whoa waa cheeks and buns and you
really focusing on something huh uh do I
have I have 10
money why is it not Euro if we're in
Austria or at least chilling if we're
playing in the past it should be
chilling okay what 10 bread is it 10
bread for 10 money 10
o and this one heals Health as well
though maybe we'll need that later huh
and also ooh matches I have nine matches
left wait so one bread I'm I'm not sure
the one bread for 10 he wait so only I
only got one not 10
oh for 10 money what a ripoff give me
some for
free oh my God how am I going to make so
much
money
she anything else so pretos baby I'm out
of money
lady we'll figure something
out a way to make money
[Music]
it's so pretty chicken
hello how you
doing wow you you look like you lost
some weight guys in this game you don't
look as thick as you usually do what
what diet did you go on why are there
eyes in the tree
[Music]
again
wow wow
at least my matches are not used during
the
[Music]
day what I missed a
hint what was the hint oh now I can't go
back oh no
[Music]
is this what what vibe are these
characters all giving
me like the art style from their
pixel uh
characters I don't know is it giving me
Maple star Vibes
no oh safe spot here sure why not
save but no if I could fail in any way
here but
[Music]
okay cute C cute little
Dogg all story events are marked with
the book icon if marked by the time icon
they'll skip one time period
oh so these will indeed skip the time
period let me talk to this lady
first everything all right Mrs
Linda oh elisea would you take a look at
my poor flowers that windstrom nearly
uprooted all of them from their PS Now
what Windstorm what what what
Windstorm I should remember the
Windstorm from last night has nobody
told you why you've seen all these
branches scattered about town I heard B
H's roof nearly came off oh it was so
frightening I
suppose no it was real I remember it
very well
[Music]
goodness Elisa you look
Dreadful good morning to you too Mrs
Bera I wasn't certain you'd come today
Elisa why wouldn't I Mrs
odelia oh my Lisa you my my Lisa you do
look quite tired they're all [\h__\h] on
me
wow couldn't I catch a wingk i wager
frightening wasn't it
oh it must be it must have been even
Dreadful up in the mountains not at all
it seems you folks had it worse than I
did my now that's hard to believe that's
was the watery R storm I tell
you how
so about had it with this nonsense she's
saying it came from the Woodland that's
what huhuh oh yeah it's no use
entertaining such Notions my dear don't
see
Mar all I can see is we're running late
for M the good goodness what has keep
back come to what why you all so
dramatic just because of a little bit of
a
windstorm after you releas it the
Woodland
[Music]
huh
wao beautiful
there's like almost only women in here
oh hello there pretty girl Freya Freya
Freya is a very Scandinavian name right
the goddess
Freya good good good morning
Elisa oh are we
besties chicken there's chickens on her
apron she likes chickens future wife
Evergreen sweetheart
H how are you always so cheery
Freya it took so long I thought you
weren't coming I overslept a little I
suppose um didn't get that much sleep
last night what can we do oh me neither
and all because of that Windstorm not
even my little spr could help me your
spr I keep a tiny spr of lavender under
my pillow you see sniffing it helps me
sleep better and it leaves such a lovely
keep quiet you
two oh I'm I'm sorry sorry yeah as you
should
be we best Focus now oh we we best Focus
now Elisa thought was you you're the one
wittering on
[Music]
Freya she's voiced by a vtuber
oh feel like nowadays especially maybe
for Indie Games YouTubers are
a good choice you know I'd love to also
voice a
game Jean
M well everybody would be cute in this
outfit look at my chicken even my
chicken looks cute in his
outfit look at the
shoes May the blessing may the blessing
of the Lord the father and the son and
the
Holy Father
ofen I remember that in
German m h s s take heed of our
prayers
amen this samag we will once again be
celebrating our
Patronus s
Vala as you all know preparations for
the festivities are
wait that's that's when the witches
every like all gather
everywhere
is oh oh
[\h__\h] we're in for something
mea oh
no as you all know preparations for the
festivities are already on the way let
us all contribute to the best of our
abilities bre friend bre friend
that said I am aware of what transpired
last night um Elisa bagged a little
purple girl and made her her servant and
is making her asleep in the chicken Cube
unbelievable several of our neighbors
were severely affected by the Windstorm
I urge everyone to lend a hand in
clearing out the
Alleyways let us all have compassion for
one another in these trying times
let us trust sanct P to guide our people
and keep keep beag out of Harm's
Way may the Lord be with you amen
amen
[Applause]
Cloud good
[\h__\h] oh my God what a beautiful Mindful
and Demir
none I am shook
[Music]
head maybe I should be
religious oh her name is Li wait isn't
the city no the the baker is called
Li took all you had to get out of bed
this morning at wager what what what are
you
saying I did nothing with that Puli
[Music]
girl it you very funny lip C CH
aside don't I keep telling you to take
your apron off for Sunday mass wow you
are fashion policing me
sheesh I'm certain the Lord couldn't
care less so why should you
[Laughter]
[Music]
sorry I got a little bit excited um
you're ring me up on purpose again
Li can you tell for goodness sake ah for
goodness
sake I'd best get to work now before it
gets lit see you later oh wait that was
so flirty shut up see you
later get out of here I won't I
won't no date with her or do
[Music]
we
H but this would be so
Unholy I don't think a nun would accept
getting spicy with another woman of her
gender that would be
[Music]
unacceptable I think that's the
point we can at least just um you know
go on one date open the locker to check
on your romantic relationships with the
girls
uhhuh couldn't sleep much last night
could you how about I also make you
night
Sleepless excuse
me I'm just joking I'm a nun why would I
do anything like
that explains the yeah what I don't know
makes no sense when I'm changing the DI
dialogue yeah you you're hopeless SL as
long as you keep indulging
me so it's my fault huh here you go
before I
forget yummy she gave us pretzels okay
okay girl you're so in you're so in okay
it might be worth talking to a lot of
people at least the girls they might be
giving me gifts like this that I might
[Music]
need Mr Bard said you were rather late
getting
why why is everybody stalking me and
like observing when I'm sleeping when
I'm getting up when I'm going
home is that so I did tell you it was
almost time for SAA when you stopped by
and I told I told you Mrs Elma worked me
like a donkey right up until
[Music]
Nightfall Mr Bard was fting over you is
all Mr banard can find better things to
do with his time I'm search
you really are so stubborn
Alisa anyhow it's about time I head out
say I'll be up at the bell tower all
afternoon if you'd like to keep me
company I'll be there Li will I be will
I don't make
promises I'm not sure if it's smart to
go after
[Music]
everybody oh
my I feel like I just got cursed what
the hell what the hell is that sign oh
[\h__\h] oh it's German I can read it
[Music]
highly okay so this is bad is nothing
it's basically
calling the witches over I guess oh okay
we get it in English
too uh hello Vala Sanctified by D name
may die will be Everlasting and die
Grace all embracing quenched do shall be
on this sabbath of the full moon May
this prayer find its restful place in th
life bearing growth of Prayer there's
something else at the
[Music]
bottom K back's offering lives in The
Crossroads beyond the mapole May thy
first be quenched thy blessings received
in the crossroads I wonder who dropped
this must have been some
witch freaky can I go down oh up
here
wow wo
oh the hills are
alive with the sound of
music I just like going up here to sing
sometimes you
know Dona raid oh welcome guys you
haven't missed much we just started this
little game that is a horror game but
also has
lesbians and um
we're in Austria as you can maybe tell
which is where I'm from and we just
started out so you're not you're not too
far
behind it's a nice little Halloween game
I not really but for me it's a Halloween
game I stopped lighting candles ever
since granny Hol passed not that they
ever did anything
anyhow kept burning in the wake of a
prayer each candle's flame flickers
for goodness sake see I'm kind of most
interested in Freya right now
personally thank goodness that's over
what a bore to think I'll have to work
all day until the
evening work what am I
working talk to me Freya
Freya Elisa I was waiting for you
waiting for me I almost forgot to give
you this bread bread oh
ointment you mentioned your hands were
feeling dry right oh you didn't have to
Freya I use it right before bed every
night it also is very useful for other
spicy F why is everything like going
that direction I ask
you I mean I added that but
still I mean
I put a little Lavender in there too
wait you made this yourself of course I
did silly that's Papa's favorite his
hands are always dry you see you do have
a knock a knu for this sort of thing
don't you oh so I'm told I
suppose anyhow I'd Best Move Along
before it gets late say Elisa I was
wondering I'm going to pick some flowers
this afternoon up in the
mountains flowers out
flower I thought maybe you might care to
join me if you'd like all right I'll be
there I already made like three other
dates for today but yeah have a nice day
[Music]
Elisa so anybody who played this game
before is it a bad idea to try to like
can you even go very far with every girl
or do you eventually have to focus on a
girl or ah dates from F and Le
[Music]
overlap Leo is the nun
right you shouldn't no
harm you can uh do one date with each at
least oh
really okay well I definitely want to
focus on Freya for now
though she's kind of the most
interesting to me uh uh I like her
[Music]
got to lock
in no I'm fine I don't want to harm what
the hell that wouldn't be very Demir of
me oh who are you time for work are you
work are you are you
[Music]
work
Ariana I'm so glad you dropped by Lisa
won't you lend me a hand I have my hands
full tidying up after that Windstorm you
see I can lend you a hand I can lend you
a hand with that Mrs Ariana I was you
could fetch me some eggs from the C my C
or uh we careful of the hands now I
think they have their own C cuz all the
chickens are here I dare say they're
riled up from last night
still
wa I heard cat purring when I was
standing there oh my God chicken fry
what is
happening
start it's a mini game
I love the music this is so
cute they should be a Ki version of this
game but if you if you squint you might
think it wait what am I doing though
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait what how does this work
ah wait wait [\h__\h] sorry sorry sorry the
controls [\h__\h] sorry I
uh [\h__\h] s that's taking hit
[Music]
me no she turns back to the other
direction sometimes even though I don't
want
that ah
ah I'm so bad at
this was that I fail the quest or round
two
what
um move chicken
H you're not going to I was waiting for
you [\h__\h]
[Music]
ah well got to try you
know take risks okay here we
go ah why why you pck me why you hate me
kfp that doesn't look very good see wait
if there's like AB bcde e f then that's
not bad uh but they make it look really
bad try again do I have to oh wait I
don't know if I can go it says five 5T
what does it mean I guess we're not
trying
again should pick a girl from the start
and focus on her okay I mean I'll gladly
do
that no money ah oh
at least it didn't cost me money
now how many eggs do you need H is going
to be rather
[Applause]
disappointed okay I still get 20 money I
wonder if I could have gotten more but
that's pretty
good oh my God I'm
starving I'm starving this game is
making me starve okay not yet we're
still chilling
meow meow meow
meow wa so when exactly is the date a
cute dog that looks like a shaa
hund look at the little
kitties
Nightfall for
Freya now for fre or Lisa Lisa I'm been
sh you're so boring
Ela no wonder you're always in such a
bad mood
Alisa oh I'll tell you who's always in a
bad mood you little
[\h__\h] yob please ala come play with us
she won't she's a
coward coward coward oh I'll show you
the coward is this a mini game
too huh oh [\h__\h] oopsie
oh the purring is so
distracting how did you do that Elisa oh
she's good you from so far away Elisa
you're making too much of it you brats
arm so longer this why cheater you're
cheater you asked me to do this you
little
[\h__\h] okay at least no time passed right
it
okay
uh wait so there's a date now does it
show on the map where my date is
Uh current meet Li at the church to
afternoon after at the Viewpoint
Viewpoint the the the thing in the
church or something else that's a
windmill What viewpoint ah
here ah okay all right sorry to all the
non lovers
but I'm more of a Freya lover
well I will
be who is she
though
cute what are you doing here
Mellie Ela I'm doing nothing stopping
herself full of Mrs Elizabeth's apples
again are you but but they're really
sweet
El keep your grabby hands off of me
Mindy what
oh we have a job but it will make time
pass right maybe after our
date and maybe we can do it on a
different day too when we need
money anyway uh while I uh how do I open
the menu
[Music]
again well that's the
map ah okay just ES esape then just
going to eat another
bread got to stay on top of my bread
intake uh you point okay we'll go past
past the creek I
think right
[Music]
no I got a girl interested in
me so fast I got actually three girls
interested in me
all right uh yeah I'm guessing this
way I'm
gatekeeping sorry for keeping them all
to
me
woo
pretty again such beautiful
views but you Freya are the most
beautiful view of them
all there she is I'll spend some time
with
her Elise Elisa I'm so glad you made it
made the
[Music]
time I was curious about the mapole I
suppose come now I've been picking some
flowers woohoo won't they wil if you
pick them
now I'm still playing with the colors
Papa's lending me a hand to dress the
Maple and Mrs marel and Mrs
Linda might as well invite all of keep
back to dress it at this rate right why
don't you help too
Elisa me you could spend the night on
Friday
and everybody wants to spend the night
with me what the [\h__\h] and we could all
do it
together uh I'm not too
certain oh it would be so much fun to
have you I'm not good with that kind of
thing
Freya what kind of thing
[Music]
n the hell are these implications
cute I used to make stuff with those
flowers too with
daisies I used to make like bracelets
and stuff
too oh it's
wonderful I new dais is would suit you
best Freya Freya
[Music]
stop
stop all in my head sorry uh I'm
imagining things right now a bit more
than what's really
happening what do you say Lisa do you
want to stay
tonight I suppose I could but I have a
chicken to take care of a purple chicken
it's all right if you don't want to
silly that's not what I you don't fancy
me much what
[Music]
no Freya what the hell how are you
getting that idea I chose to date you
instead of the
nun all I want is to be good friends
with you despite everything despite what
I do too you
know I wasn't trying to make you feel
for me or anything anything of the sort
feel feel for you feel sorry for you or
what for goodness sake for goodness sake
that's not it
Freya I I didn't
mean I didn't even say anything
yet but I trly didn't mean to her
goodness sake you're always
overcompensating it makes you seem
disingenous why are they fighting now
[Music]
huh he oh my God what
I'm I'm glad we're friends for I truly
am am I just placing that flower on her
head in that picture or it looks like
it's my
hand yet you keep trying to yet you keep
trying to please me day in day
out aren't you happy she's trying to
please you every day I me girl that's
not what I meant to do Elisa I wish you
treat me more as a friend
Freya what
okay okay okay rather than someone you
owee an apology to atast at Le I'll be
using that ointment you made me all
right
okay yeah tonight maybe I never meant to
overcompensate for goodness sake yet you
shower me with gifts every day of the
week which I absolutely hate how dare
you you don't do that to anyone else
what am I supposed to think uh that she
likes you I know that's because cuz I
care for you
Elisa she's
[Music]
blushing there there there's a reason
why you're
[Music]
dealing holy [\h__\h] I'm a dump
protagonist anyhow it's getting quite
late isn't
it is is everything all right Elisa
you're red as a
Beat Why it's getting quite
late nervous
laughter what are you laughing out see
you later Elise see you around town
[Music]
El leave us Prov oh we gathered a heart
piece are we still playing Zelda I
thought we were done with
that all right it's evening
wait I just noticed the the sign for the
nighttime is kind of
scary why can't we just keep the game in
this kind of vibe why why do we have to
go into a
scary kind of
thing help
me where are we going now anyway what's
my what's my tasks
[Music]
wait where do I see my
tasks
[Music]
H well anyway we do have a date I think
in the evening with uh yeah with my
chicken that'll just be the name I call
her from now
on my
[Music]
chicken maybe we should
save my purple chicken yeah yeah isn't
that a cute nickname for one of your
loved
ones I would think
so little chicken good to save in
different slots yeah maybe later but for
now I think we're still good I I don't
think I've really done anything that I
might
regret there you are FL I don't know
this this thing is sus I don't trust
this
thing not one care in the world
oblivious to everything
[Music]
just like every animal pretty
much
okay there she is my little chicken my
purple chicken how you
doing this will skip one time period and
then we'll be in the night oh my God and
then we'll
die let's
[Music]
go Rosen Marine Dare You Are Rosen
Marine Rosemarie yeah actually like the
German version of that name is more like
Rosemarie Ros Marie
rosarie I I didn't know you'd be back so
soon
Ela were you watching me having a date
elsewhere from this
Viewpoint were you stalking me I still
ought to head back to town mind you what
are you doing standing out here
just totally not trying to see what
you're doing from up
[Music]
here a little too early for stars don't
you
think I find it helps me air out my
thoughts air out your thoughts you say
I'm waiting for
the I don't know is it just me
like I'm thinking like I don't know
airing out waxing I don't know I don't
know it's just me
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay okay okay okay everybody relax
everybody relax calm
down calm
down too much lesbian careful careful K
too much lesbian as we like to say here
at
kfp important I set my side on LS to
come the sooner the better oh oh she
knows she knows about
[Music]
uh what do you mean
rosar you you see
Ela I've dreamt about you
before about ke be
too last night
or I know this may sound strange but I
didn't quite stumble upon keep back by
accident Marine what do you
mean do you believe in fate Elisa
well not really I don't think it's a
faithful meeting if you didn't stumble
into me by accident that would make it
more faithful but okay I don't know I've
never given it much
thought then you most likely won't
believe what I have to say but fate it
I've always known my fate was with you
Elis wow
she I'm so popular my chicken loves
me it's too soon to be having this
conversation if I'm honest I know I
meant to wait until you were ready but
rosem Maria I I don't understand
rosemaria ready for what you'll know in
time for goodness sake what's with all
this
mystery out with it Ros Maria what are
you trying to tell
me it took me quite some time to make
sense of it myself but
[Music]
um the 90s art style is just so
dramatic everything's feeling so Strang
and nostalgic to me nostalgic you say
must be the art style that's your name
your voice your home This breeze
even oh that surrounds you so much of it
Feels Like Home to me Frozen Marine
that's not possible rosemarine El it's
you the Stars told me about Elisa I'm
certain now romantic and kind of
concerning never in my life have I ever
heard such nonsense and yet I'm covered
in
Goosebumps I can tell you don't believe
one word of what I just said Rosen
Marine R Marine
[Music]
I the chicken cop is right there I'm
just
saying I think I'll stay out here for a
little while longer you know airing out
my
[Music]
thoughts I promise I won't be late for
supper oh right don't stay out here too
long you know yes you might get sick I I
I won't I
won't yippe
oh now it's scary time now it's scary
spooky time no no no no no no no no no
no no maybe not yet maybe one more one
more time period cuz that looks the most
scary the next one uh but yeah how do I
match my light again uh I think it was
CTL
yeah what do we do now I'm finally done
with work for today I'd best head over
to Mrs grittles to see
lip okay late at night like this are you
sure why do I have to go for my house is
there no other way and my house scares
me oh God you scared me
[Music]
bro should I safe
again check out the bakery yeah yeah I'm
I'm I'm going there I think
[Music]
I'll still save over
here let's go
Bakery and then spooky
time
oh
oops guess my stream died for a moment I
think we're already back right Scoopy
time did you hear what I said shouldn't
should I really be going to the bakery
now if um spooky time is soon CU then
the if the time
passes then I will still be
o kind of freaky uh in the city in the
village when spooky time hits maybe my
chicken will be in danger should I not
be protecting my chicken or is she the
one that I need protecting
from wait I'm at the Bakery should I go
in
[Music]
here did I
misunderstand talk to
lip oh that was the nun
right oh the and that is the none sorry
somehow I thought you were Freya in that
light cuz your hair looked Brown to me
oh I guess it is brown
too uh you're a little too happy to see
me aren't you oh I thought today would
never end that's all you don't look
tired Elisa these folks will be the
death of me that's what foreshadowing
fretting over this witch nonsense day
and night you know they're rather
superstitious
sis it's not that kind of spooky please
okay if you say so you're buying into it
now too what's next we all sleep in the
church together like chickens in a c
chickens in the cop
Mansion many chickens
[Music]
Mansions it's all nonsense live
everyone's losing their wits here's your
bread Elisa oh you give me bread thank
you what the hell Two Times
bread are you my bread supplier every
night or what did you make too much
today or something I thought you could
use a little more than usual tonight I
thought you sorry there's many Fem
voices but it's hard to make them sound
all different so hers is supposed to
sound like this you need to look after
yourself
Alisa lip C's always had a talent to
figure things out but is this her
intuition again or move along Elisa
before it gets late I'll see you
tomorrow
lib okay so actually time didn't pass
now
interesting is there anything else I can
do
[Music]
oh I can't find it what can't you find
gruna I hadn't seen you there my
dear the bear Miss marela gave
me oh that's what you get for being such
a CL scer
app Mrs M said she made it for me ah it
even had a ribbon on
it it may be best to head inside for now
my darling it's no it's no use looking
for it in the dark that's for certain
you're a clutch you're a clutch it's not
funny
up you have your hands full don't you
miss lth like you wouldn't know will I
will I search for it no well why don't
we help
[Music]
her Miss lb's apple trees seem to be
doing well this year huh fillter the
brim of apples the barrel stands on Ying
despite the visible between the
planks oh sorry that was that's scary I
think that happens when I press the the
running button while there's a story
going
on for her
goats okay can I not find what she's
looking
for yeah it's like fast forwarding
during the dialogue
[Music]
M my Alia why you still wandering town
is everything all right miss
odelia it clearly isn't is it what if
that Windstorm picks up again this
evening there's only so much an old
woman can do
Against the Wind against the Woodland
Elisa the
Woodland I hardly see a reason for all
this fretting if I'm honest uh oh I'm
well aware what you trying to stay last
the windstorm is no urrent I'll have you
do oh this
is getting on my
nerves you don't mean to say it was that
oh please don't mention it for goodness
sake what what what what what what what
the the witch or
[Music]
what
you thank
you Mr H's been keeping himself busy it
seems cover in dance and scratches the
Anvil smooth surface glistens in the
sunlight
sorry three times
sneeze
M okay should I go back
home a ah I can't go there because of
the the wood
okay thank
[Music]
you oh oopsie
sorry buy some bread you think I'll need
that much
[Music]
bread need to find a do no it didn't
seem like a
quest I think cuz yeah it didn't give me
a quest
six bread a day well
[Music]
okay I hope the economy in this game is
not too
harsh
uh I have 20
[Music]
money let's buy it no maybe not cuz it's
also too
expensive okay
oh it is what are you
saying I'll die from
Hunger there's a secret free bread
behind oh thank
you I'll check it
out was that the hint you were trying to
give me
huh not this side I guess maybe that
side
[Music]
ah difficult I have to press w d and e
to look in that direction and get the
bread
okay nice bread do I need to eat one
right
now oh yeah I probably should no no no
no the Press no no
the
bread and another
one damn she's on a bread diet like all
she eats is
breads so far at
least her life depends on
bread oh there's a safe Point here too
interesting certainly motivating me to
Safe
oh oh the Woodland why would I choose to
go to the Woodland does the game why is
it not stopping me to go I don't want to
go to the Woodland I hear bad things
about the
Woodland as long as the game doesn't
force me to go I will stay away from it
let's just go home and talk to our
chicken of course I believe the
[Music]
rumors
chicken
hello hello yeah you're still standing
there are you cooking something
[Music]
at at least welome back I brought some
bread let's s down and eat oh
okay would you like me to start making
dinner from for us from Tomorrow Elisa
does that does that only work if I date
you
or that's not a bad idea in itself
but will you be jealous if I date
another woman I I to know you won't make
a mess of it last thing I want is to
spend my evenings in the
ouse oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] literally I'll have
you know I'm a proper cook Elisa never
once did my sweet granny disapprove of
anything I
prepared well I suppose it can't do much
harm all right on that note h m you're
to sleep up in the attic from now on not
in the chicken cpop you have been
upgraded can't have you hanging around
the granery and bringing all the dust
and cobwebs inside but I yeah especially
after I aired it out so much right
sorry I've had my fellow running about
looking for you day and night but oh
Anda I wouldn't want to be a
b oh sh it and I wouldn't want you
nesting with the mice and the geckos
geckos you're sleeping in the adding and
that's final you hear I know atct is
kind of creepy
too I'm letting sleep side wordss
perfectly warm
and did
you did you did you did you hear that h
m I heard that I heard
a I hear that I I hear that I'm
scared here
what at least I'm not alone I'm taking
the brim you stay here just in case
[Music]
no okay it's just
you just a cute girl oh my god really
cute it's
you bro I'm
scared please spare me
Elisa what in the lord's name are you
doing here
mippy you
know I was having in the St I swear I
swear my Auntie's name is that so and
you just so happen to hide behind my
house I see who doesn't you sneak about
FX homes every now and then too don't
you money doing here Mandy why do I keep
on giving her different
names is it like cuz I'm not remembering
her name or I'm pretending not to
remember it
[Music]
I'm I'm bad at names am I tell me right
now or I'll scrub your mouth with soap
this very
minute it's getting quite late it's
Alisa I best move out with it I saw her
that girl your house sing Alisa why is
it not me shut up and
me that's my chicken nothing special
going on between me and my
chicken oh she's she is not from around
here even I can tell just look at her
shoes oh no the shoe the shoes were the
other girl you were having supper
together and everything
Alisa you keep your mouth shut mby more
I'll why don't you share some of that
bread you've got Elisa I might keep
quiet if you if you do for goodness sake
oh I should have guessed that's what you
want
it do I have
to bro I only have one left
left Lea
yes
anyway it seems like I don't have
to should I
have is she going to die now imagine
imagine the the result of this being so
extreme that she just dies and she won't
be part of the story anymore from now on
oh [\h__\h] she should go to the
bakery and ask and beg for some bread
there
sorry I want you out here right this
instant hey you want a pret tomorrow now
that's even worse because that's even
more
valuable you better get me a pret why
why why why what makes you think that I
should give that to you I'm certain Mrs
Laur has plenty of food at home now
sh you're so mean Ela
oh suspicion up and I got like a little
witchy hat suspicion as you guys think
if I'm mean to you you guys think of me
as a
witch oh I see my
decisions my
[Music]
decisions Muffy gossips at Town that's
exactly why she doesn't deserve the
bread load save or continue no no I will
continue this action will have
Consequence the butterfly I know exactly
what you're referencing ref referencing
life is strange I've been watching the
playr of
that this action will have consequences
mhm anyway okay can we like make up or
like I guess if I give her the pretzel
maybe we can undo it the
impression I
wonder oh I can talk to the villagers to
uh oh okay do I have to talk to the
other villagers
too and don't come back or else for
goodness sake this is the last thing I
needed I'm sorry I
I is is she gone this could be bad
Rosemary I'm sorry at least I genuinely
didn't see her I I would have told you
if I had don't you start fretting now
too do you think she'll tell anyone if
she does we could be in
trouble I know
rosar oh she's correcting her now it's
it's Rosen Marie not Ros you oh sh same
thing I'm heading back inside my chicken
has no right for to correct me in her
name
pronunciation all right muppy spying on
you fulfill her daily requests for food
items to keep her from snitching and
raising suspicion oh
[Music]
man muy can kiss my ass mind what you
say and do your best to avoid raising
suspicion towards Elisa or bear the
consequences
H maybe that's one of the endings though
a bad ending wouldn't that be
[Music]
fun okay I guess we got to go
sleep and have our nightmares haunt
[Music]
us oh bad ending RTA
yay you left that goat in The Granary
I'm hoping of course
I left the door die so he can go out and
about if he wants I'm telling you the
goat is evil what makes you think he'll
stay put oh why the bed I made him of
course I ought to you ought to see it at
least I'm not going out of my way to see
a goat's hay bed Rosemary Rosemary H up
you go you need to make your bed
too oh cute little attic you'll miss do
I'm certain oh it's perfect is it you'll
get I'll get you a blanket too I can't
have you sleeping on
Hay oh why not her goodness yeah you're
not a goat I was about to
say I could be a thief yet you trusting
me with a blanket I've trusted you with
way more already so I mean I don't see
what's so funny you truly are kind Elisa
I you truly are kind Elisa I can see
that clearly now you well done tell
Muffy you tell Muffy about
it I'll be glad to take the blanket Ela
I get you some matches too and a candle
oh thank you Ela it's bedtime now night
El guess she has accepted her name
now okay here we
go
oh
dramatic for goodness sake she keeps on
saying that
[Music]
why is there so much hay
hey what am I getting myself into I
first agreed to house rosemarine now
myth is C wind of too I best make sense
of this all by
tomorrow if only I could leave this town
go somewhere far far away from here a
place where I'd never have to fret about
money or going hungry like a castle or
Palace somewhere where I can live the
life I deserve wow she's got quite a lot
of
confidence oh God I'm
[Music]
scared
uh it's already
weird
no oh oh now we are in our Palace
I see what the
[\h__\h] what where where am I is this a
dream are there different girls in this
world that I can date or
no
wait give me an item it's
locked damn I bet there's something nice
inside
[Music]
what the hell Golden Girl
rebirth that's what I wished for long
long ago you wanted to be
reborn somewhere safe somewhere far far
away I went through all of their trials
gathered all of his gifts and indeed I
was reborn my wish was granted yet yet
to think I would end up like this wait
what was that
I got grips from talking to that nightly
whisper find a golden
Maiden n
what stay sane keep Elisa from feeling
frightened with sanity healing items or
she might go mad uh I don't think I have
sanity healing items is it is it is that
grapes it's so bright but there's no
flame an intri intricately designed
golden lamp stands by the bedroom door
it's bulb shining
bright okay I mean that's just
electricity I feel like I'm in a
princess bedroom if only I could live
here just like I've always
[Music]
dreamed be careful there all sorts of
dangers looking in the shadows that
wasn't a shadow though was a mirror use
healing items to persever and survive
what the [\h__\h] man no here we go this is
this is the spooky part of the game I
like how there's just this like shjo
dating pixel game and then there's this
horror side to
[Music]
it is that just part of the soundtrack
the door creaking anyway we got a silver
key about using items the item in your
inventory can have effects on the
environment try using the hand on it
okay do I have to go to the inventory
for it though I'm locked in here I
suppose
okay can't say I'm mind okay so we go in
here I mean we could eat that bread
right
[Music]
away and we use
this most sane lesbian experience can we
open the chest oh you think maybe ah I
thought it was for the door it's for the
chest
ah
ah oh many dresses another key I want
know what it's for okay that one's for
the door then a golden key well why
don't we take the dresses
too oh sorry
I keep on thinking I could just like
automatically activate it if I have the
[Music]
item such a long
Corridor it really feels as though I'm
inside a palace um no no Elisa no we're
we are in the horror game
Nightmare I'm scared
on the wait these were in the opening
left is a crow and right is a snake
danger noodle what what is the meaning
behind
them strange statue it's going to attack
me it's going to attack go back go back
go back go
back sorry that was
just the
winding ah
wait
what I'm scared
too I'm a bit too
scared why did they do
[Music]
that hold me chicken why am I holding
you you should be holding
[Music]
me but wait should I should I pay
attention to what this says let me read
it again do I need to remember this okay
I don't really know if I can remember
this
anyway does this one say something
else yeah okay this one I can kind of
read AEL or
AET should I remember
this MIM and AEL MIM I guess so
okay sounds like Gigi's last name
[Music]
oh it's a safe
Point wa what do you mean you can't see
anything a blinding Crimson glow pierces
the windows glass panes tinting the room
in reddish Hues you know but I want to
[Music]
Safe guess I'll die
I have a bad feeling about yeah me
too don't have to
run what's going
on
a it's pretty
though what what in the lord's name is
this place what are those
things feeling lost feeling lost don't
forget to turn on your Lantern and keep
it IE out uhuh what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] it's
flying it's flying it's
fly what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] I think so if I'm in
the circle of the light of the of these
weird floating thingies then they will
will find me and attack me and follow
me so as long as I stay out of the
circle maybe we're fine I wonder if I
should like look around a little
bit the books can make sense
[Music]
okay four key
holes I have to find more keys
okay I'll do my best H what was that I
saw
something key no bandages okay cool will
be surely
useful okay let's oh why is my light not
here anymore what the matches go out so
fast it's not even that dark here
anyway it's no wonder their weol is
being left in such an awful room h wait
this chest can I open
it key fantasm key it's nice it turns
out when I get hit
aha okay okay that's fine then I'll just
um just try to not get
hit okay one
key oh [\h__\h] uh uh
echola I wonder if there's any like in
these
bookcases no no again same
[Music]
description what about here upholstered
luxuous blue velvet beautiful the broad
sofo rests surrounded by similar luxuous
Furniture
okay
K I'll still check all the bookcases but
cuz I I feel like one of them might have
a
key chest in the top right was there a
chest that I missed
there top
right he I opened it already you mean
that
one so I guess I'll just I guess if that
one was in a
[Music]
chest wait wait wait wait
stop did I am I still going to get hit
please reset reset
reset reset oh I think maybe I did reset
it okay okay this is kind of at the
bottom left so maybe there's something
up there oh god oh wait there's
something there an item normal
item oh okay more bandages good good
good good good we can afford getting hit
again
maybe oh a
chest oh that's a portrait of another
girl me
nah let me take a closer
look oh
well it's jammed I could try to pry it
open
but I mean we have to it has a key but
this is kind of sus like what's going to
happen
what maybe it's an maybe this is not
it did the painting
change no no it did not looks the same
to
me is it a
mimic kind of sus
[Music]
I'm scared it's a mimic isn't it oh what
the [\h__\h] a curse oh it's
a but this one's not in
German is this Latin I think this is
Latin oh she can read
Latin sick she's so
educated what the [\h__\h] why can't you
read Latin the key to one's dream is
found within
oneself as for yours it's in the Very
Room the core of your inner most desire
it's not knowledge you seek but gold
bathed
Glory
huh I already have two keys are you
saying one of the keys is like specially
hidden oh God these voices are kind of
like the voices when you put on the ring
okay still what do you mean these are
you can speak Latin and
German sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry
oh
[\h__\h] well I don't see any more chests
though is there a map no
um n still wait to use
that although we could use how much does
the bandage heal one heart
okay do I heal somehow automatically
next uh like after a night passes or
so in the bottom right by the sofa you
checked hidden chest in the bottom
left a crack in the wall at the top oh
my God so many things you noticed no
damn it
okay so what wait wait wait so many
options
um it's gone what the door oh yeah sorry
I wasn't really looking for the
door
uh open the heart locket during the
witching hour there secret
art heart
locket heart locket
what we heart locket
how to open hard
locket the
bro I can't use it
though ah can I go down there ah
oh cute it does it not open normally
oh my God they're so
close is there a reason why one's red
and and the others are
blue
okay go away go
away go away give here go
away the red ones seem to activate when
you touch them and the blue ones too
though no
okay you guys were saying there's still
something
here basically you were saying there's
still something
[Music]
everywhere I already looked at
that bottom right still has a chest
but it can't only be bottom right there
must I guess also be one more thing on
the left side or no I guess not no I had
two key two things from this side but
one of them was not a
[Music]
key
oh oh [\h__\h] it's hard to pass here
[Music]
two kids on the right side one follows
the hint on the no
[\h__\h] they're so
mean wait okay push
I should walk slowly okay bottom
right wait this these books are
golden were they always golden yeah yeah
yeah they were saying something for
gold
ke yay I knew it had something to do
with the bookshelves yeah was it always
golden though wouldn't it have stood out
to me before as well or did it only get
golden after I got the
note we
SC so we are in the bottom right there's
a
sofa you guys said something about the
sofa oh wait what what the hell what did
didn't see
it I am
blind okay we got all the
[Music]
Keys it's a
key we got four
[Music]
Keys time to
leave let's not Bonk into another one of
these things
[Music]
um easier said than done but
okay I made
it okay
use all of them please this is it don't
make me do it four
times
okay it's too
quiet what is
this you love this cut scene I don't
love it yet I must be dreaming
don't follow
it
oh what the
hell yep yep that's that's maybe the
castle I think I'm in isn't it also in
the background of like when we look at
the on the viewpoints at where we are I
feel like there's something like that in
the far
distance yeah
[Music]
right oh now it's
disappearing enough of that can we leave
the [\h__\h] are
you hurry now hurry now H hurry
now we're late for his banket
okay who what are
you hurry
hurry
uh oh we're running now I don't even
have to do anything
there
pumpkins pumpkin people
wa by pin
not okay it's kind of
[Music]
fun no
yeah I protagonist seems to
be you know followed by nightmares just
like me
IRL can can can very much relate a dream
that left me feeling a little
queasy same girl same Rosen
Marine it's funny how the voice over
says it correctly but the uh the text
doesn't she's most likely still asleep
anyway or she's dead no point in waking
her this early I
suppose but what if she's
dead col fireflies one what I don't
remember collecting a firefly
[Music]
how do I get up to the attic
anyway is it the can I cuz it's there's
a ladder here but I don't
really seem to be able to go up
[Music]
there she making breakfast or something
oh she's right
here y good morning Elis I would have
got a head start on breakfast if I knew
you'd be waking up this early
since when have you been up oh I'm
always up and the B before Daybreak I
can't sleep in if I try I didn't notice
you coming down from the
attic I I brought the ladder up with me
last night so I wouldn't wake you and
the hatch doesn't Squak if you do it
slowly right I took my shoes off and
used the ladder to shut it back up easy
you're smarter than you look huh
[Music]
I think our
chicken is very
sus she's a witch obviously duh and we
start having nightmares when she's
sleeping over I
mean I
mean I look as smart as I am Elisa is
that so anyhow I'm heading off to the
garden
the garden you mean the field just
outside is it that obvious that I
haven't touched it in years been working
like a dog since granny hola has passed
but uh now I have you to fret about too
so I can't sit on my hands forever can
I what you d a star join me as a maid of
all work perhaps you trly are kind
aren't you you ah sh I'm heading out to
see what I can do about the garden okay
so we are going to be gardening after
all I'll call you in for breakfast in a
moment then does that heal up the
breakfast and the dinner does that heal
up my my Hunger
though oh bread is randomly here
yippe oh you still don't let me go to
The Pantry
okay thanks for the membership
[Music]
renewal for goodness
sake the worst way possible what do you
mean I'll start to like her in the worst
way possible what
I've neglected it for so long it will be
impossible to
dig anyhow this is no time to lder
about okay can we put uh hay for show to
make bread not wheat I mean hey yo what
what's this a pair of
shoes for my
chicken how could they possibly have
wounded up in my garden oh they're
wonderful
are be careful
Cinderella those shoes are going to turn
you into a pumpkin and they fit me like
a glove too these
[Music]
shoes it's as though they were made for
me nice wait what was I wearing before I
did it I of keep back needs to hear
about my shoes cuz it's so important
that I have new shoes let me run around
town and annoy Everybody by yelling I
got new shoes look at them you you
what's the word again
[Music]
forant yeah
Pleasant what's going
[Music]
on
for it's like a second opening
[Music]
uhoh [\h__\h]
okay that was really fun and nice and
cute but honestly what's wrong with her
is my question because she was raised so
nicely how does she turn into this kind
of very shallow
girl who wants so much attention and a
palace and these shoes make her feel
like you know the princest
princess and she stood Su and kind of
man what
happened what happened to her she's
Austrian so what I'm Austrian too what
are you trying to
say maybe we're missing some lore so
anyway we we ran to the Village to show
up our shoes and we fell on the ground
we stumbled is that what happened
man uh on on your feet
[Music]
honestly I'm sorry but the way he's
designed he looks terrifying he looks
scary doesn't look like a very nice
father explain yourself it what is there
to explain father I'm living my '90s
anime dream my magical girl dream
okay could you not hear yourself last oh
oh there a guy y pack heading into sanct
P's place of worship howling and
shouting like a please hold your hand
what of vtis and vanity disdain for your
fellow
folk oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] I've always known
you were Wicked you arrogant L wait wait
wait wait I have criticized her too
about her shallowness right now but what
about this made you think of her as a
wicked arrogant
Lassie excuse me she's a young girl
honestly for a young girl how old can
she be like 12 or so 13 I 14 look at her
for her to be running around singing
kids have done weirder [\h__\h] way weirder
[\h__\h] way more concerning
[\h__\h] she's 18
oh but even an 18 year girl year old
girl is allowed to run around in her
pretty shoes and sing okay now I'm
defending her but like come on
you old gezer
you oh oh wait is this is this the
result of me losing one reputation point
so to say a witch of old holl skin I am
not a witch you oh listen here you old
Rich that's enough enough old Yan has
overstepped his boundaries I ask you to
Pardon him yet his concerns weigh heavy
Elia oh I wasn't aware singing and
dancing was forbidden now father I have
a
idea of what the lore of this where
where this is
going
um this whole game is Just leading me to
become the witch that I was meant to be
I guess
theug stuff the nightmares and
everything it's just kind of like my
[Music]
Awakening yeah cuz so far she doesn't
seem to be aware of the possibility
possibility that she's a witch right but
that's where we're going
my Awakening as a
witch I mean it's coinciding withus so I
mean it's it's right out there in front
of
me yeah was no way dancing and singing
is illegal father your singing was
riddled with
sin was it I don't recall the lyrics
being rled of
sin that oh vanity and L go hand and and
with greed your oh sh it what does any
of this have to do with sin father
before you call me out on that look at
all the lesbians that live in this
Village and call them out on their sins
first I guess so that is a good argument
this whole village is filled with
lesbians after all uh but anyway compose
yourself and come inside your temper R
is a sin in of
itself h
I guess I shall follow and be a good
girl I guess I repent for something I
didn't do if it makes you
happy yet there's something I'd like to
make clear to you all you have stood
witness to this
Foolery you've all heard old Yen accuse
me of
wiery that's enough Eliza you asked me
to Pardon him yourself father and I will
yet I demand you folks understand this
once and for all out with it I am not a
mere mage of all work I am one of you
and I demand right here right now that
you start treating me as
such okay everybody has been treating me
like [\h__\h] so far is that what you're
saying not everybody though feel like
there are plenty of people nice to
me very well Lea you've made yourself
heard oh oh
what what the hell old
hack without a Shadow of Doubt
BL um what the
heck at last he's made his move who are
you an old acquaintance of yours last
grandma what you favored by him Elisa
frightfully so you're clad in his will
from head to toe inside out and those
shoes my
shoes those very shoes Elisa are a
testament of his gift to you who is he
listen carefully now my beautiful
ass get away from me yours is his
Heritage his flesh his our door don't
you understand Elisa what in the lord's
name what what what do you
mean His blessings his will he himself
is with ring in your veins last what do
you want for me you old HG rude My AG is
in demand young lady but you must listen
carefully now my beloved do as I say and
he will make your wishes come true what
is this my wishes you say why yes
opulence Splendor Fortune your deepest
desire is unlike any other
Elisa I I don't
understand you do Elisa tell me what is
most your
desire My Desire speak it Elisa what I
most desire
forun fortunate you are
Elisa same girl
same deep in this Woodland there is a
patron
saint whose Blissful words bestows a
blessing upon the faithful all that's
requested in Return of free gifts made
from the Testaments to one's desire
reach his dwelling with all of these in
hand and your wish shall be
[Music]
granted scary a w carrier of Life your
basket is to hold all that is
sacred all the
crows the tender flesh of Earthly
desire what
spicy the sweetest nectar to be drunk in
Earnest you are to arrive in good
company oh oh my choice of
[Music]
[Laughter]
lesbianism
oh interesting will she be sacrificed as
is that going to be like the shocking
ending the woman I bring shall be
sacrificed oh [\h__\h] that would be
terrible I hope not why am I coming to
this conclusion I hope it's not
[Music]
true you are to reach the gates of his
dwelling carrying all free gifts so they
are forcing me to find a
woman voice your in a most desire
surrender yourself holy to his
grace who the [\h__\h] is it
Satan and Fortune you shall
[Music]
attain for such is his Blessing and such
is your
desire El
diabo
Elise El are you listening
uh yeah I was listening to the old
hag what me no no no I don't mean you
sorry what where did she go
El are you all right
Eliza or let that old hat go Elise Elis
what's the matter with you
Le Diana you you could have just called
me and asked me how to pronounce Li k
close enough though close
enough close enough pretty
good
cute it's best we lunch and rest for a
while we can sit with you
Elisa it's best we give her some space
yakob I'm all right I I I found a little
dizzy as
all I I can bring you some water
Lisa it's momy I'll be in the church
waiting to have a word with
you oh
no yeah honestly I'm not really into
like nuns I don't know man like you're
you you are
like in the
same place
as the creepy father so and I'm a witch
we're not meant to be although maybe
that's exactly why I should go with the
none if if the person that I'm
bringing at the end is indeed a
sacrifice then as a witch the best thing
the best person to sacrifice would be a
nun and then I wouldn't have to be sad
about it I could just like fake seduce
her as the evil witch that I am
but no I shall be naive and continue to
believe that it's just about love and
not about sacrificing someone and then
go for
fre wow that's evil or you guys are such
haters he's such
[Music]
haters wicked wicked well maybe I am
because I am a
Witcher youve done it now ala
for goodness
[Music]
sake okay morning is past
already hi chicken good morning
K all right let's save
good so far very good me likey um the
story
event where are we meant to go now I I
guess I I said I would go into the
church so I guess I'll
go don't really care about what that guy
has to say to be honest but oh he's over
there oh with the evil
guy those
[\h__\h] I'm not so certain I want to
talk to these two yes same I'm hoping
you had some time to think Lisa keep so
Fellowship H it needs stability we can't
keep going like this going like what
you're well aware that I'm talking what
I'm talking about L let's keep a cool
old y Anda spared it some f I'm certain
let's say I
have you ought to listen to your elders
last shut up wait so I thought there
would be some more story here
[Music]
do we want to talk to our
nun suppose so I'm here for my oh I get
my earful from
her you're no child Elisa for goodness
Si spisa you're aware you've said too
much I couldn't have stayed silent you
know that I agree it was their FA Elisa
but we both know this will only get you
in the wrong kind of attention old your
hints to be exact I'm well I'm well
aware Le there's no real need for you to
fret over this you know there is the
utmost need for me to fret over it Elisa
I'll keep father H from dwelling on it
too much all right why don't you meet me
here at desk Elisa I'll think about it
we could use a little downtime wouldn't
you
say I'll be here no no no I I won't I
don't think I
will but it's good to have an objective
as a choice in case I have nothing else
to do with that
fancy dress today thank you it's so cute
ride blue drew it for
[Music]
me OHA you scared me stiff earlier I did
it takes a great deal of courage to put
those two in their place oh those two
you did well at is that they're the ones
being
unreasonable Mrs mlda
mlda they'll be babbling on about it in
church at wager would you say they'll be
wanting a word with me Mrs
s oh they might but you have nothing to
fet about Elisa I can assure you not one
soul in CUA back thinks ill of you my
dear thank you Chad besides the town's
folk are still shaken by that wind storm
and they say I'd say they'll forget all
about you and your shoes by Happ my
shoes my shoes should I do like one of
those quests again to earn some
money there was another thing to do but
where maybe let's explore some more if
they will let
me press e to see M and then e ah oh
yeah there there it is investigate the
notes you
found help M with the apples help L to
chop some
wood okay where exactly is the apple and
the wood
stuff maybe it is here oh oh there's my
girl
my Ela look at those shoes red trly does
look best on
you oh you have to weite them to the
festival
Elisa now time to find yourself a proper
sutor oh that's precisely what we were
chatting about with f but will it be
accepted of me to come with a female
sutor you don't need 16 M money worth of
bread each day to not die but you should
look around town and visit with NPCs
before committing to anything yeah okay
60 that's a
lot aren't I a little too too young to
be looking for a
husband why the sooner the better I'd
say that's not exactly what I'd like to
be doing with my time I'm honest I used
to feel the same way until I met Flynn
you'll see I'd say freya's got a good
chance of meeting her future husband
soon why are we talking about
husbands oh oh Miss B I wouldn't say
that I am
heterosexual what did you just say of
course you are oh yeah sorry about that
of course I
am oh in truth I do feel the same as
Alisa my just light else oh there she
she's saying
it you don't
mean s
suing I have my hands full with the
festival too this really isn't the time
oh that reminds me would you come and
meet me by the well today at that's also
dusk
okay sure
[Music]
mhm
Shing okay here we got a quest I think
when is dusk is dusk before evening is
dusk the sunset
time mom will let me chop wood okay I'll
chop wood uh can you get some wood for
the her uh yeah I hope I'm not going to
fail really hard
again
okay why don't ask fya to chop it for
them instead or why would they is this
not a mini game is it or this a mini
game oh God how does it work I need a
tutorial why is there no
tutorial oh okay we can handle
this chop kick
kick why would I
[Music]
kick if I'm done chopping I I have to
kick it away 2 1 go
[Music]
ah what the hell give me some wood oh
[\h__\h] sorry
[Music]
[\h__\h] no chicken chopping no chicken
chopping no chicken chopping wood
chop wood chop no no yes this is easier
than the other one
man man let me do it again oh round two
okay okay oh God it's going to be more
[Music]
difficult what the hell why the goats
that's so
cruel [\h__\h] no [\h__\h]
[Music]
sorry oh nice
nice nice got some good amount of wood
in round
two yippee is that better than last
time
yo thank
God yo we got a SE last time for some
other
Quest I'm so relieved I do wonder if I
get more more reward if I do better for
a mini game does somebody
know yeah you get more money oh okay
certainly we'll get more money now then
yipp Y how much money how much money how
much money how much
money 40 okay okay one more Quest I
think yesterday we only got those 20
wait is it already
dust no that's that's just the afternoon
or noon or so right yesterday we only
earned 20 but we got a lot of free bread
so oh not you I thought I never find you
Lisa goodness what now myy it's
your my shoes my shoes I don't have food
for you sho
Sho my shoes what oh oh my friend oh but
I'm busy I want to make quests do
quests the last what the funny hat she's
right
outside hurry it up take me to her
moolly right now oh
no I was busy making quests making
[Music]
money my your cupet in dirt last oh but
I'm
she's so funny looking she's so funny
looking look at her silly hat Angel
Angelica don't be so
rude you're not this SL
[Music]
Elizabeth Elisa said she's from
primor oh I'm not from Prim do I never
had
a uh why have the
idea I'm looking for ala Have You Seen
Her Elisa do you know
her we do happened to know Ela but how
do you know her last Ela said she's
adopted
what well I'm adopted or she what I I
guess yeah I am
adopted what what what does that matter
why are we bringing it
up if you please tell me
where look mama she has a tiny
scarecrow forgive me but does anyone
know where I can find
Eliza you're supposed to stay home you
shitty chicken
Mama
Mia Frozen Marine M I'm mad
too so much that I wanted to sneeze in
your face for the
[Music]
disrespect thank
you I'm sorry goodness s what are you
doing here you little
[\h__\h] uh yeah
[Music]
keep it together at Le a distance cousin
from
primor why you don't have cousins
Elisa I don't recall Al H's mother had a
sister but I never met her mhm yeah
exactly Ros Maria is my aunt's
granddaughter oh but I uh it's shut
up oh is she having uh interest in
fancying my chicken cuz she had the the
heart
icon all please meet you no thank you
anyhow it's getting quite late we Best
Move Along before Oh but do tell me my
dear how long have you known you had a
cousin
uh wait is
huh this is a lie and it's lining up red
but it this feels like
[Music]
H like it could go wrong it could give
me the the bad vibes
again but I
[Music]
mean if I want people here to not be so
concerned about it well well I did meet
her this cousin this cousin this
Saturday so that doesn't necessarily
mean that that that she's not my cousin
which just me for the first time so what
okay this is all very much new to me as
well you see my I must say that's rabit
strange Elisa oh why did I say
that how did you know to find El leer
l oh I looked at the moon and the
stars don't you dare say that Auntie
knew we lived in Kea bag we exchanged
letters before auntie auntie knew we we
lived
[Music]
we who's
we oh well well I'm saying
that uh that's all rosemarine knew when
she came about to meet me right uh
yeah un she never visited did she my
auntie was rather fragile Health you see
oh sorry I don't I'm mixing up the
there's too many freaking ladies I can't
do all these voices all the
time
[Music]
M I do remember old holla mentioning her
family from primor but uh stop dobling
me just leave me
alone old holl never left keeper bag
after settling down and if you say her
family was rather distant Do You Believe
Me Do you believe me it's confusing yeah
just stop stop putting your nose into my
business would you look at the time yes
I think I know what you mean
Elisa uh that's all right you two we
wouldn't want to keep you yeah yeah I
need to make money otherwise I will die
I will starve because of you guys
holding me up for things that really
don't
matter suspicion
up I was telling you guys I should
probably
lie you guys made me feel bad about it
no
[Music]
man [\h__\h] it's your guys' fault Chad
why did you come out here in the first
place you
chicken I'm sorry Elisa I knew you had a
bird's nest for a brain but this is too
much oh well you know what you did I'm
sorry Elisa I didn't mean to I was
chasing after the flock you see for
goodness sake oh yeah she was on my
chopping block a few
times why not let him F about that's
what good still he took the laundry I
was tending to right out of my hands I
couldn't let him ruin your
sheets all right well truth is we made a
complete mess of it and I don't even
want to think about father Hun's
reaction I'm sorry I didn't mean to
trouble you forget it Rose M it's all
right I'm telling you it's
fine feel I've done only troubling
you uh well that's true right
and I do enjoy your company and you cook
for me so at least anyhow we ought to
keep our story straight maybe if we tell
them I came to lend you a hand with work
this is it that's it that is a perfectly
fine thing to say now after we already
said a lot of different things all right
all right listen carefully you're
grandmother is Granny holl Auntie the
one the one that never came to visit
am I supposed to remember this for being
like quizzed
later that makes you my distant cousin
of sort you see you came about to meet
me but we could have simply bumped into
each other and you asked me if I knew
anyone named H I'm sorry I don't
understand Elisa how does that relate to
what I said why you liked Kea back so
much she wanted to stay and Lear a hand
oh you're a kind charitable loving soul
who wants to help with the festival that
will keep them from asking too many
questions I'd
wager yeah we should have had this talk
beforehand all right this being said
Rosemary you're going home right after
Nightfall you hear I don't want you
hanging about these folks too much all
right Elisa I did it we're making it
happen right now then let's go
[Music]
yes
okay um
we still have time right I can do one
more Quest right cuz this says later
anyway help o again with the chickens oh
there I can do the chicken thing again I
don't know that was kind of difficult
with the controls honestly play Kiss the
rat with the kids great sounds sounds
great but also it says head back to work
for the main quest do I what do I have
to do that like at least that doesn't
seem to pass
[Music]
time um but where where is
that head back to
work on
um is it at
home how do I
know where the location of that
[Music]
is help
broom ion no no broom ion isn't that
where the the side quests
are oh is that what they mean if we head
back to work just do the side
quest
oh wait but now it's not letting
me is it just because I had to talk to
the
girl anyway I'll already buy some red I
reckon looking cheeky again you too can
I sell
something no uh could sell that but
what's the
point not
a hopefully we'll find something useful
later on in the game in the next
nightmares or so I suppose that we can
sell something of
value ooh plus free oh wait is
this ah know there's no sort of like
upside to buying that rather than the
bread cuz it's it's still the same price
in the end okay and I only have four
matches left how am I going to afford
all this
[Music]
[\h__\h] but you can can you brute force the
nightmares without matches at
all
uh cuz I I only got four how can I buy
is it is it 50 no wait ah ah wait one
for one one money for one
match
damn that's still a shitty price because
that will mess up my like even money cuz
I could buy four breads now if I buy one
match I can only buy free
[Music]
breads sorry that was accident
I do want to buy but I'll be coming back
later anyway I
[Music]
guess okay well for
now we got the
bread also I wonder if she'll really
come back to us for some pretzels I do
have one pretzel that I could give the
girl
later do I go game over if I'm fully
suspicious to
them that' be really unfortunate cuz
we're already already have like three or
so in terms of
Suspicion oh
man I want to make sure that doesn't
happen but I can't
promise anyway let's try to play This
Kiss the rat game or whatever if I can
find it where would it be oh
nice it's not here right it's like the
but this is look looking pretty I want
to check it
[Music]
out hello it's the little girl
Guna you know Guna that's not something
you usually you're ugly Le say you're
Ugly oh wow okay is this
your wait what is my my chicken doing
here with me you're supposed to I don't
know not get in trouble
[Music]
oh that's such a sweet name say
cook it's it's
uh's why is there a scarecrow in your sh
Mommy uh oh this my granny made it for
me when I was just about your age I keep
it with me always because she isn't with
me anymore you see oh I'm sorry it's
quite all right corner since when are
you so good with children no
M you're an ugly old Crown Ela holy [\h__\h]
why is she so rude she should learn from
your cousin wow
uh baby Daniel big no sh and become nice
and Tiny like
mine bro my nose is beautiful have an
anime nose all our noses are pretty
normal to be
honest oh she wants to play with r Mar
not with
[Music]
me well I don't want to play with you
either I just want to play with the cat
that you have in front of you
wonder if there's any more like secret
items like the bread that we found
behind the
[Music]
bakery wait I can go up here where are
we
now oh back to the vage square okay
[Music]
what
nose I have a
[Music]
nose oh it'll cost your free bread each
time but she'll make tasks easier and
avoid raising
suspicion free
bread how much money will she earn will
she earn
money I'm fine doing this one myself
though I told I told you I know what
it's
what did you tell these to maybe it's
it's best maybe it's best we don't annoy
her I see like automatically everywhere
where I go now seems like
it you shush it
Rosary okay this will skip one time
period yeah I know W you and your cousin
play Kiss the rette with us she doesn't
earn money she just makes a mini game
easier and hanging out with her prevents
her from causing trouble and raising a
suspicion don't bring along yeah I'll
die from Hunger I don't have enough
bread for that that right now maybe it
we'll get easier later
on but wait so this game
automatically I can't do it alone it's
with her
always
[Music]
so H can I do a quest that
um uh that doesn't
I will ask you first if you oh okay but
this kind of implied that I'm bringing
[Music]
her okay we'll
try
e stinky
rat I hope this game is
easy the rat she's kind of there though
what the
[Music]
hell I don't understand I'm not paying
for her am
[Music]
I it's kind of the hardest it's the
hardest one in my opinion oh
no blue pass yellow
pass going to insta die what what the
[\h__\h]
3 2 1
go what am I what is this
game
[Music]
ah I
see what
[Music]
I'm what I'm pressing it I'm pressing
the right one even but too late I guess
I'm trying to do it pretty much on
bro I'll just press it way
[Music]
early and I'm going to die for this
you're telling me I'm going to die for
[Music]
this now it was too early okay well I
had a feeling that would be too early
but he wants me to do it so early anyway
I swear I'm pressing it it's just like
they wanted really
early wow that's
fast oh
[\h__\h] oh they can fail too or that was
just the end of it uh well well D holy
[\h__\h] well I was wouldn't mind dying now
if I can go back to the safe point where
I it was before I played this
[Music]
game I lose what do you mean I lose
you're not giving me any money for that
even but the game wasn't easier anyway
this was kind of oh 10 bucks wow
N I kind of want to Safe
scum
[Music]
H it sucks I want to save
scum I want more money but it seems like
she didn't take the bread from me right
yeah only I consumed the
bread uh
load yeah is this before we got so like
a lot more suspicious to
everybody I'm not
sure is
it first time is free what do you mean
free what's free
[Music]
ah she was free the first time to
demonstrate the mechanic Ah that's also
why they didn't even ask me okay that's
kind of
[Music]
confusing okay we'll do better this time
hopefully I'll press everything earlier
then we should be
[Music]
fine got body musle
that was the easier version that was the
easier version okay I'll never be
playing this mini game again afterwards
so
probably what what easy about that blue
pass yellz okay I was doing it
[Music]
right okay here we
go BL blue
[Music]
[\h__\h]
I uh better them before but still
blah do the egg game I sucked at the egg
game too I hope there will be more
games fck
[Music]
bro
bro safe scum I'm not letting this stand
I am not letting this
stand I want to try again
I want to try again come
[Music]
on double
bees not the kind of Double D that I
would
appreciate you prefer this one once you
get the ribbon down it's not that
difficult yeah I'm sure but yeah for now
it's still kind of rough
and in a situation where bread and money
is really
[Music]
scarce that is not very
nice I'll try one more time if I still
do so badly then I will do the egg
[Music]
game the toughest mini game okay
well well
well at least we can speed for the
dialogue like
that very useful
now let's
go I'll try to lock in can't promis
[Music]
though h three 2 1
go h
[Music]
yo yo yo that got faster and I still
managed to do it okay okay okay okay
three two one
[Music]
go kind of the rhythm game
bro ah what she helped me
[Music]
help why didn't you help me now
girl why is the help
[Music]
limited don't give me a d
still see bro
bro that is very different my score 111
versus 46 that's so different and you're
only giving me a
c that's that's 20 bucks that's enough
to buy enough bread for today but i'
prefer to have
[Music]
more 20 right yeah I don't know about 20
I don't know maybe I want to try one
more time do you guys
mind you have to be a rat hitting Pro to
get an A I don't even mind a b like a b
would be nice just because maybe should
I try the chicken game again last time I
got a se but that was only the first
time I ever played it maybe I can get
better I did get better in phase two a
little bit
maybe chicken game
H but the controls kind of felt weird
there also is the chicken game not where
it was last time cuz last time it was
down here
no m is tied in this game especially
starting off watching you practice the
Min gam fun really you think it's fun
but yeah it's definitely tight I need
to I wish I could just play this game
twice the one with the
chopping that' be
good where's the chicken game
now why do you change
location where is
it
[Music]
h does she follow you on your dates too
good
question looking for secret
[Music]
items not all jobs are available each
day oh thank you hope you can avoid
kissing the r it seems like I
can't like it says help or with chickens
but the quest does oh wait maybe up
there oh The Stables never mind never
mind never
mind the Stables might have it am I at
the Stables
yes oh they got a nice crop field going
on can you guys give me
some are you the Chicken
[Music]
Guy collect eggs okay
yeah okay so even in this game I guess
she will help us one
time let's see how she will help us
played this before without her though
chicken friendy how does it work again H
hold the controls ah move pck egg
[Music]
okay okay let's
go 1 go
what like it just doesn't react
sometimes oh [\h__\h] oh she saved
[Music]
me yo yo yo yo yo I got a lot I think I
got quite a lot actually definitely
compared to D my first time playing this
game way
better oh come
on come
on oh come
[Music]
on these chickens can't be trusted
okay second round somehow was worse but
they definitely act a little bit more
strict oh this doesn't look too bad a
really an a with
that okay chicken game way more doable
now especially like I was doing pretty
badly that's quite nice sheh 42 for S
rank oh I feel like it was kind of close
then cuz I had
36 I'll get better at this this game for
sure even though the controls are kind
of weird feeling weird like not so
reactive
okay all right wait did I get
40 I got 40 Before 40
now
nice okay we'll buy some bread and eat
some bread for sure
uh okay where's my going home sorry I
think I'll be skipping more a little bit
more dialogue now we're reading faster
cuz like it's really tiring um doing all
these
voices for a long
time okay
eat
eat eat maybe one
pretzel we'll need it anyway okay but
we'll keep one pretzel for the kusogaki
absolute kusogaki
maybe there's some secret items
here
cabbage
no no free food hello please maybe a
carrot can I go in here ooh wow horses
cool and the inside of this place is so
pretty maybe free
egg remember seeing a snake or you
hiding in this head oh
[\h__\h] would the snakes hurt the the the
horses I would be kind of worried about
that corn I love
corn tomatoes in there no that's apples
smells awful many blood is just colored
wrinkled apples waiting to be fed to
life
oh they don't get the good food
sad conversation simulator in the horr
game consider how much l Lees yeah
there's there's a lot of talking for
sure like if I was in streaming I would
like go for it slower and talk to every
single person but so far I've pretty
much talk to a lot
people anyway but from now on maybe be a
little bit
less we've had a feeling for it now oh
this shop by the way is it different
what is this shop does it sell different
like bandages so oh
my
mommy
mommy I get so lonely all by myself in
this
thing well then I shall work here maybe
instead what do you
sell matches bandages ointment
grape
juice uhuh Aus oil a ball carrying the
oil of sental put set to restore one's
good J oh but it's really expensive you
got to be really good at the quests at
at the mini
[Music]
games I just oh wait no never mind I
thought this was for getting the
suspicion away but actually it's not
this is just a hardcore version of this
one then okay
which will be needed for my sanity I
guess
[Music]
okay well I did want to buy some matches
just to make sure I don't run out of
them and yeah bandages do you think
we'll be fine with
one H maybe let's buy one I I will I
still have enough money for enough
bread there's uh maybe not
maybe not dungeons usually have
true but I I kind of had to buy some
matches I feel
like well now I can buy uh wait I'm back
up to 36
money then I can still buy free
[Music]
bread wor guys I can alsoo sell
things Le gives you bread every night
okay just one though right but yeah okay
if that's every night then I appreciate
that oh now we have a date don't we oh
you also have a quest what's your quest
not that I'm going to do it now
but don't cop cleaning a cop we also
have a cop
Quest a
well yeah right now is not so good but
maybe
tomorrow so
uh meet Freya by the Water Well ah it's
down here I saw oh we haven't gone there
yet I'm sure it's beautiful and
romantic oh yeah oh
yeah I'm coming for you he wait where is
the path
here that way
[Music]
maybe wait is the bread trop still open
at night
I'm worried that I can't buy enough
before
um okay I still have two but still yeah
okay
um let me look at
this okay no free stuff this is
beautiful there she
is I'll spend some time with
her oh it's
wonderful or Lea they're
wonderful they so me rather well don't
they your legs are so long it's like you
were made for those shoes or those shoes
are made for you
maybe you're exaggerating ba
stop nothing of the sort Elisa you're so
elegant oh wo wo wo W
huh I always thought you were So
Graceful even when we were younger Freya
I'm more of a Farmland last you see make
to chop wood and draw water from the
well I wouldn't put it like that fya
you're different Elisa you're so
confident and poised not one of those
folks would ever agree with you f you
always know when to stand around and
what to say which is what gets me in
trouble to begin with and I can't help
but admire the way you carry yourself
you're truly such a kiss ass how I wish
I were as Brave As You Are
huh I could never talk back to Mrs Wilma
or to anyone else for that matter you
are too a little too forgiving that's
true that's why they keep praising me
left and right I
suppose what's keeping you from speaking
your mind for
you I'm too much of a chicken another
chicken there's so many chickens here I
thought my chicken was the purple one I
guess you're are my green
chicken you'll never change huh keep a
back truly is where you want to be isn't
it real I know Elisa I know I'm sorry
this was rather silly of me wasn't it no
being this hesitant I know it's
frustrating anyhow I better get going
hesitant about what what do you mean see
you later about kissing
me she didn't seem to be too happy about
[Music]
what no
can I Still Still wife her in
time is there like a timing uh a time
limit for the story like oh you have to
have a wife uh until this time suspicion
up why because I didn't get her to love
me reload but then I have to redo the
quest as well
[Music]
no you didn't give mey the
pretzel I thought you would come to me
to receive the pretzel
later and do I have to go to
her well okay a dusk or
what bro I have to find her oh my
God okay chicken
cop and then I'll safe after chicken
coop got to save after
everything Chicken Coop Chicken Coop
Chicken
Coop one one tiny item at the corner of
the map locked out TR
[Music]
what corner of the map you mean corner
of the well
map locked
out what oh maybe we got s this time
that would be sick oh was that a joke I
hope
so maybe there's a ring there you know
and the ring is necessary for the true
[Music]
end actually I just realized I was like
better at this than last time but this
time uh my chicken was helping me so
next time it might not be so easy
anymore when it wasn't really easy
anyway either
way is she just blocking the damage I
would be taking from the
[Music]
chickens 2 1 we got this I don't got
this
[Music]
really saw that coming
honestly [\h__\h] sorry sorry Jimmy ah [\h__\h]
sorry should have known
[Applause]
oh okay
okay okay okay not bad might have been
the same as last
time Jimmy have mercy on me I'm just
trying to take your eggs but don't worry
they're not
like they're not fertili F fertile they
wouldn't become chick uh real chickens
anyway it's just going to become I'm too
scared to take it ah scrambled
eggs [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] sh sh sh a
[Music]
[\h__\h] okay okay I was I was egg maxing at
the
end
uh oh same not okay okay okay but how am
I going to do this without my chicken my
purple chicken I mean my purple Chicken
Helper
[Music]
o maybe the
other um sorry the other mini game maybe
that one would be
easier
H oh I win but actually what it cost
five money to play a mini game again but
it also it also makes a Time move one
more time right
[Music]
yeah I'll go make a
save a No Time Advent on
retry
ooh that might be good cuz if it only
costs five and I make
40 okay I make 40 only with her help but
[Music]
still okay um first of all let's eat
bread
[Music]
okay now we save and we find the
kusogaki
this
way crunch crunch crunch crunch oh there
she is well okay then I'm I'll
um should I give it to her now I can't
mess this up can I M I hope
[Laughter]
so I kind of don't like
her it's prel time Elisa you're so full
of
[\h__\h] for goodness
sake she's
um what's that word
again
uh PL H uh what's that word when you
have something against somebody yeah
blackmailing yeah she's blackmailing
[Music]
me I I won't even read your dialogue
because you're such a mean mean
girl not your cousin yeah yeah yeah yeah
uh she's my
cousin yeah here's your [\h__\h]
pretzel hope you're happy with your
pretzel I best make certain I keep some
aside what what does she want tomorrow
[\h__\h] okay but the suspicion went
down
huh grape juice yo it's getting more and
more valuable each
[Music]
day okay time to find a safe
Point uh where am
I the back alleys the back alley isn't
that also like a horror game
[Music]
I do have gra ju like one at least
so on the back rooms that's
it is there an option to accuse Maffia
of being a witch oh well that sounds
like fun I'd love
that okay um um oh we still have to meet
fya okay okay this time I know what to
say I'm coming for you my beautiful wife
my future wife or my future sacrifice I
don't know we will never
[Music]
know all
right I'll spend some time with her
again
djab
uh there it
is
really I got sticky keyed this is
ridiculous wow you've lost your wits and
it's only
Monday who's to tell you what you can do
or not do
it's not as though I can simply start
only it truly is that simple
F you're so capable and gifted I know
how much you love this town
but even you have to admit all it does
is hold folks
back I know Alisa yet I can't seem to
get to the bottom of it ke bag is my
home after
all it's not as though you can't build a
home so okay interesting because I was
thinking like our girl she really wants
to leave this place but in the previous
option Elisa was kind of set to just
stay and now we're encouraging her to
leave and I was thinking when she was
just set to stay I was like how is this
relationship going to work right so this
makes more sense if we want to make our
relationship work she's going to come
with us so now she's more open to
leaving maybe if we encourage her more
yeah I know this is where my father is
where you are it's yeah but I'll be
somewhere else
it's where my memories of my mother are
[Music]
too I thought about Primo do or even
going beyond that
but I must say I'm glad to be here in
this moment right where I am we feeling
keep all damn it we're supposed to leave
though
girl aren't you Elisa you'll make it
more bearable I suppose ke back wouldn't
be the same to me without you if I'm
honest yeah but you girl realized that
once you do your your
spicy thing uh the church people will
kick us out of this Village right they
will not accept us
anymore
so unless we can somehow keep it secret
but that's kind of sad if we have to do
[Music]
that capable and gifted I heard you the
first time Elisa why you say I'll be
home all afternoon tomorrow tomorrow
I'll be
there okay so now we got the heart
right
yipp and now it's already night
time so again I don't think I saw an
answer in the chat before but is it time
limited the story like I have to get all
those free things that they want from me
in a certain amount of time and bring it
there on
time yeah one week oh okay I was
thinking so because like they probably
have a limited amount of nightmares to
offer to me as well is
this is it a firefly oh no it's a oh
golden girl what the
[Music]
hell oh last oh oh last to think I would
be surrounded by demons on my death
bed that fateful even
I was taken to his dwelling under the
pretense of
[Music]
Glory his Blessing his Blissful word you
oughtn't believe any of it uh obvious
hint to not do what they're telling us
to
do oh
nice that's useful ow ow ow ow what the
hell what just happened my sanity is my
sanity going down when I meet these
Golden Girls
okay let's check is there is there a
ring on the bottom right of the map like
somebody said
no should I check out the
fish I was washing clothes here
okay Goen girl FES give you lore and
items but oh those are five lines but
always cost you s sanity they're
optional don't impact endings
oh okay well the item she gave me does
help to uh fix the sanity by quite a bit
so not going into that shop This Time by
the way going to the bread shop
only that was worth it look at those
cute caty kitty
[Music]
catties okay saving my progress
yay bread I got so much fresh bread
today when I went to the
bakery um they said oh we have like
fresh things baking right now you just
got to wait like 6 more minutes and I'm
like okay that should be worth it
normally I just eat like one croissant
in the morning when I'm having a
croissant day and the one croissant will
already like fill me up enough but I
thought oh maybe maybe just this one
I'll have two c cuz they're they're
piping hot and fresh and the chocolate
the inside is like all melted it's just
like it's so different when it's fresh
so I got two but
um turns out two fresh
fickles were kind of a lot to eat in the
morning which is kind of weird I've had
bigger breakfast before but somehow that
felt like a
lot but it was so yummy the chocolate
was still warm and melted m
[Music]
should I buy one of
these maybe one one of these days the
girl will want a lip cooken
instead okay I'm out of money wait I
didn't buy the matches
[\h__\h] I didn't buy the matches do you
think I'll be fine with four matches how
necessary are they really
you'll be okay okay it did seem like I
could brute force that other nightmare
without the matches honestly it was
still somewhat
bright do you reckon she might give me
something for free if I talk to her even
though we we we're not having a date is
she going to be mad that I didn't go to
her don't you start lip cooking I'm not
explaining myself again my lips are
sealed you can stand there looking at me
all you
want she's so B sweet last I must say I
know you Elisa she's my cousin there's
nothing more to it oh could you say that
again she's not you know no I don't know
what he said that's why I'm
asking now that we got that out of the
way I won't tell won't you tell me who
she is eh oh we're telling her the truth
now she says she's a traveler I found
her hiding in my Granary on Saturday a
traveler
I'm not convinced e but I felt sorry for
the poor L she says she'll be leaving
right after the festival so it's only
temp how how perfectly timed she's
leaving after the festival everything
seems to have a purpose
here she won't tell me much herself I
had no intention of bringing her here to
Kea back but she graced us with her
presence I suppose I had to think of
something right there and
then I shouldn't be housing a stranger
let alone put myself in wait for her but
I understand Elisa oh
oh I I also understand what you're
telling me is a half Truth at best but
here's okay so we do have bre
yes I was hoping for that two y yo yo
life saavor okay she's a good
girl have trouble okay no I don't think
I can I'm very much in
trouble the more I proc progress in this
game the more I'm getting myself in
trouble
basically free bed for H truth I think I
pretty much told the truth of what I
know one for you and one for your
grill so this n uh left
side this game really is so cute and so
stetic L
[Music]
pleasing really such a nice
game oh
hello so I talked to her to progress for
the night I guess
right really cutesy yeah so
lovely all right
girl I
guess I sufficiently today well only at
the night time
really in this game I
suppose there you are Lisa it's quite
late isn't it for goodness sake spare me
the earful Rosemarie what's there to
sweep out here after Nightfall
anyhow I'm sorry I was just keeping
myself busy until you came home and pluy
here was amusing himself chasing after
the broom fck where' you f yeah
cool what's for supper then have you
cooked grape soup that's just
wine I I figured we could both use
something hearty that's not I don't know
we have eggs what about the eggs eggs
eggs eggs of course I cooked those too
in the grape
soup I hope it's not in the grape soup
did I do something wrong eggy toast a to
be enough for today I suppose let's head
inside Rose
Mar it's nothing
oh I why am I like
that looks like the same food from
yesterday so is she just like drinking
grape soup all this
time she has the right color for grape
soup maybe that's why she's
purple anything tastes good when you're
hungry I
find I suppose to day went well all
things considered I best keep an eye on
her L these those fults sorry I sayy
Elisa I have meaning to ask you
something H those shoes you found this
morning now that you what about them you
still haven't taught me much about them
well they're just shoes totally not
magical shoes or anything else I've seen
them before in my dream ah you seen my
shoes maybe she's the designer did you
see the new YouTube preview with the
highlighted chatter section what no I'm
not sure I did doing different art for
the food on different days takes design
time yeah yeah yeah no this is fine I
like all the all the art they did they
made plenty of beautiful art I'm sorry I
is there something you're not telling
me I don't know what you
mean I've been avoiding thinking about
it but uh this morning ke b
i f they're finally starting to
Aline you're just horny for me
H never
mind why is she spooky like
that she told me about this patent Saint
in the woods that he grants folks wishes
if they bring him
gifts help me help me guys chickens get
me out of this game so it's true after
all creepy you've heard about all the
before carry on carry
[Music]
on she said I must bring him free gifts
the tender flesh sweetest nectar and
good company why did the music
change why is it happy
now
okay oh Ela that's wonderful what else
did she say did she mention your fa for
goodness
sake you're you're scaring me with all
this nonsense oh there's nothing to be
afraid of how do you know about all this
anyway it's an old folk tale my granny
used to tell me a folk tale carry on now
what what else did she
say she mentioned finding a dwelling in
the woods that he will grant my wish if
I bring him the free gifts made from the
Testaments you told her you wish didn't
you I did but it's nothing out of the
ordinary it's you know don't tell
me I'm sorry oh Oh you mean ah you mean
don't tell me as don't tell me not don't
tell me don't tell me let me take
another another frog candy I'm also
really hungry man hi smoothie over there
by the door
frame did you go to the toilet or
something oh she looks so fluffy guys
I'm going to get fluffier and fluffier I
think they're already getting fluffier
again here sleep on the
bed oh
yeah she ran over when I was petting the
bed
[Music]
make yourself comfortable
smooy stay stay
smooy anyway out with
it okay tell me what's going on oh all I
know is what my granny told me but I can
tell you all about it at least I can
help you the Marine I need to think
about this
I'll be here Tiding up you can ask me
anything you'd like H
okay cuddle maxing why are we all using
these words now I I only started cuz you
guys told me about cat
maxing oh what's going on today I'm sing
so
much okay well then let's talk
again you don't have to look so
frightened is it it's all very
overwhelming as all oh Elisa isn't F
such a wonderful thing enough of that
what are these Testaments and
Gifts of course thank you in order to
meet him you're going to have to gather
The Testament to your result these are
tools and ingredients you'll have to use
when crafting the gifts it's common
courtesy to bring your host nice gifts
when visiting isn't it h there's also
are the trials but I can tell you all
about his FK tale later who is he anyway
Satan come on clear it
[Music]
up oh there we go um well I know the
good company is a nice lesbian
so what is the sweetest
[Music]
nectar uh it represents Your vitality L
it your essence you don't you don't mean
all that matters is that it carries a
part of your mortal body
[Music]
a part of my mortal body huh I know what
you're thinking Elisa that could be it
if that's what you're inclined to bring
him I I don't know what I'm thinking
what am I
[Music]
thinking blood or pee how about
PE what is it
was these are meant as proof of your
resolve first and foremost it's your
deter ation it's most important at
[Music]
Le okay tender
flesh uh how about the tender flesh
couldn't all of that just be from my
good company the Flesh and the blood
H you're you're the one making it sound
so bad Elisa I guess I am the T of Flesh
represents your body The Vessel for your
soul so to speak a representation of my
own flesh then all that matters is that
it carries a part of your mortal body
M it's nothing to be afraid of it can be
a nail clipping yeah I was thinking so
yeah what's important is the connection
between you and your symbolic vessel
M what is good company I don't know what
to think of this one oh I I totally know
you should meet him when your soul is at
its most vulnerable laser H grny used to
say good company brings one's innermost
self to light one's true fa in in other
words was Mar I'm not sure I understand
why it's love
El love reals all wouldn't you say h i
need time to think I still can't wrap my
head around this nonsense
Rosary that's all right Elisa I'll be
here if you have any more questions I
think I need a moment or a
night I'm supposed to find these
somewhere but where yeah where I'm okay
the nails are on myself I can just the
body parts is on
me the I think it's pretty obvious the
lover we're working on that the juicy
stuff I don't know is that really my
blood not sure about that
[Music]
one one thing I'm like relieved about is
at the beginning of this game you know
when I was in that room here the hand
was grabbing me but it seems like
generally all the bad things only happen
at night so now I don't need to be
constantly shivering and freaking out
about what possibly might await me
because it's really just at
[Music]
bedtime okay she doesn't
know at least for now
[Music]
no all right night time
everybody oh I woke up at night oh
[\h__\h] can't stop thinking about all this
nonsense if I don't sleep maybe my
nightmares can get
[Music]
me everything that old hag told me about
the test ments the gifts about him what
Rosemary told me too I find it hard to
believe but maybe maybe it's true if I
do gather these Testaments if I do find
my way to him maybe I can finally leave
this wretched town and live the life I'm
meant to live now that you mention it
start a you someplace far far far away
this could very well be my chance for
happiness for goodness sake let's go
let's go I ought to at least try I have
to go to the Woodland oh oh now we're
not letting the dreams come to us we're
going to our dreams all right oh
no
okay
um but won't it be very dark
[Music]
outside
y I hope I don't scream too much because
my cat smoothie is sleeping next to me
now and I don't want to disturb her too
much I no I didn't B buy matches I still
only have four because you know we we
restarted and then uh then I bought too
much bread by acci
accident but okay I kind of know the way
we'll be
fine find your way into the
woods what's about the investigate the
notes you found I can't do that now
right or do I just have to go into my
inventory and look at the note
again oh
bro there's something written on here
hello po satified by the name yeah we
read this before though right yeah yeah
yeah ah ke's offering
last oh my PC lagged beyond the
mapole made I first be quenched okay
interesting yeah we read this before I
guess but maybe I
know but I don't really know
yet I don't I'm not really sure yet
about that
[Music]
oh
down down down down
[Music]
down I am excited for what awaits Us in
the scary scary Forest now actually
interesting that they let us go there
before already but maybe not as far as I
thought it would let me I was able to
enter but
did you check out the cave at the
Crossroad no I guess
not huh maybe should I do it at night or
does it not matter is there a
cave where cuz that was a Viewpoint
right can do in the future
okay above the sign
oh here oh my God all
right yeah I didn't see that at all but
I can't seem to go
in maybe during the
daytime okay okay oh come
[Music]
on no jump scares
please don't jump scares
please oh she turns it on herself okay
wasting my
match let's see if what that old hack
said Is is true together at least after
at least give it a
try um
okay ooh yeah I like this while pus
Vibes they're very much uh are similar
to The Mad magika Vibes I wonder if
that's a
general like visual aesthetic for vus
stuff cuz I don't really know anything
about it besides
from I guess maybe it came up and
Charmed once but it didn't look like
this
really oh Rosen Maiden
too is it like always like uh
represented like
this or is this just inspired by it m
mag I don't know ah it was one of the
inspiration okay cool cool cool then
that makes sense so this is the Woodland
I ought to find him I ought to be
brave we don't even have the things yet
why are we already looking for
him should we what that
sound what does that
sound what the
heck is that a dead
body what what is this wretched place
huh i' best be careful this could be
dangerous okay what exactly am
I being careful about do I not want to
get hit by the
butterflies are
like I'm not sure what what are we oh
God a
[Music]
hand how do I Dr all those mobs here aha
we want them to go into the fire all
I've got on me is my
Lantern well
there's I can jump down nice
oh ointment cool what did that do again
for okay was just going
to oh okay that's how I bring them there
I wanted to test out what happens that's
what I get but it it was necessary
apparently heals Health
okay it seems to be necessary to hurt
myself this got their attention I
suppose i' better be careful moving
forward yeah oh my God what the
[Music]
hell matches oh
nice didn't have to buy matches huh
H well very
funky very interesting combinations of
like art
styles wait
what
oh wait there's a golden thingy here
right how do I get there maybe from
above a bit more from the
top wait I I see I see what kind
of puzzle is
this a mushroom oh that looks very
poisonous
okay uh wait what uh up down here up
here uh down here
how do I reach the golden thing still up
here and then down I
guess uh where was the golden
[Music]
thing I can't go there maybe here oh
yeah I got
it there was a dress on the floor a
dress well first we take this Golden
Girl take heat she's taking advantage of
you
the creature she goes hungry it's you
she wants
she you
flesh don't allow her to interfere with
your
wish her interference she
says what the is it the old Hack That
was talking to me or what do you mean
fancy
handkerchief my sanity
is is it pretty by
now can we
still go on for a
while where was this dress you talked
about previous room previous
room I didn't see a dress at
all oh that oh I I was too scared to
touch
it oh that's also sity lady ah
have you met the Witch she's still very
eager to meet you again would you
believe your PS are bound to cross
before long but have my doubts you last
long in the black
[Music]
Wilderness we're still
fine can I take the dress with
me Mo eaten and freid an old dress rest
in its blood so this is [\h__\h] up is
this what's going to happen to
me I would be very concerned at this
point seeing that and like obviously
another witch who died there talking to
me and warning me all these witches are
warning
me yeah she sacrificed her blood and her
flesh
right this crazy
stuff can't be trusted it I don't know
why I'm doing this I'm so naive oh a
save point wait no let me save
first oh it's a sign the lord's
name there's so many I must find a way
to distract them again the fire do I
have to hurt myself again or is it
optional you're the main character
nothing bad can happen to you plot armor
[Music]
get it oh another very poisonous
mushroom not the kind of mushroom I have
in my garden
thankfully okay we got some fire here
simply lighting is not enough
yeah yeah I mean I got to leave them
there
oh there's so many items here oh not
here
okay oh there's
two does it matter which way I bring
[Music]
them okay follow me
ow there we go ow what the hell ow ow
what the
[Music]
huh why are they suddenly hitting me
this much I thought that maybe okay I I
got to run with them to the next one now
but I learned to many at once got to do
what do you mean do
both ah it's two groups [\h__\h] I'm dying I
think we're just going to load cuz I
just saved anyway
cuz that's a lot of Hearts how do I just
lure some of
them I didn't try to get all of them I
didn't even realize there were more than
one they agitate out the first light so
drag them first to the
[Music]
right is there an optimal
path oh that was a Dap it will woke up
smoothie for a moment but she's got so
used my cat's got so used to the apps
they were first like also like what the
heck now they're they wake up maybe for
a moment but then they're like ah it's
just the the weird Dapper that our mommy
got a while ago for whatever reason the
weird tennis
racket okay
so huh well let's try okay I did only
get one group that
good
[Music]
okay and
now the rest oh wait there's another
group then I still saw some
there but I didn't see another
light but it opened up so what I just
run
[Music]
through oh no now gone let's inspect
this as well looks like a do remains ooh
I've never seen such a thing before the
pristine skeletal remains of a dough
every bone Baron of any kind of life is
that also supposed to be some
sacrifice see did
[Music]
I many saves
not like that would be so difficult to
redo but
yeah what do we got this time matches oh
so many matches okay I'm glad now that I
didn't buy any matches I'm not even
using any this
time uh what are these signs of people
on the
ground oh there's more butterflies do I
have to lead those too
those are drawn to flesh it seems I
ought to lure them out of the way but
they'll keep following me if I don't
turn off my
Lantern if I don't turn off my
Lantern I'm encouraged to turn it off
now wait so if I walk through with my
Lantern off it's
[Music]
okay no I'm not okay I mean and they
didn't follow me but I couldn't walk
through Lear them to other bones
ah there goes one match unnecessarily
but okay I see bones
here here here here did you he what ah
why did my light go off anyway I was
leading you here
[Music]
what did I do wrong maybe I wasn't fast
enough cuz I wasn't dashing for a
[Music]
moment yeah I wasn't fast enough what
what what they they're not sticking
they're not they're not sticking to it
they're what the
[\h__\h] n come on
turn oh turn off after I lead them to
the
flesh
bro but I still have to have it on in
the
beginning as far as I can tell so that
they follow me in the first
place
okay let's
go [\h__\h]
am I not stuck in here
now took you an hour to figure it out
cuz you're dumb no don't worry I'm dumb
too I would be dumb
too I do it again I want to lose less
Hearts
[Music]
please let's just save here
okay well we look at
this more
matches we study their
behavior now can I do it without getting
caught behind
them okay okay okay okay nice I still
got hit once but it's almost inevitable
I think
mushrooms they do give me at least
plenty of
matches grape
juice
[Music]
nice I want to it might be worth solving
the other side too because there might
be items there
too even though it's
optional m
M well yeah these are definitely hiding
something I could lead them to
here
h ah did it not work [\h__\h] that's too
fast or like I I turned it off too
[Music]
early what why are you not staying there
am I doing it wrong is that not
considered
bones I guess down here
then but you made me lose heart one
heart
[Music]
man
ah I can I bring those up there is it
not like like like a limit of how many
can be in one
spot and then after I get the item I
lead everybody down
[Music]
again did they go did they go I think
they
went nice but is it worth losing all
this health no because it's just [\h__\h]
matches that wasn't worth
H but over there there's still some
stuff over there
guys there's even a door the hell maybe
my path was the optional
path or maybe it Loops
[Music]
back I really don't like doing this to
be honest because I it it seems like
almost like I can't not get hurt kind of
annoying
[Music]
and now I have to do it twice because
it's two
groups ah that was so not worth
it if I want to go past at least the
Golden Grill is on the other
[Music]
side huh
okay right so I'll lead them to
that's so
far that's so far you want me to lead
you cuz this doesn't count right what's
down
here has to be up there
bro save I don't know do I even want to
save I kind of want to load back in
again
[Music]
almost cuz what did I do since the last
save I only put these as
side and and they had matches here and
maybe one mushroom or so 's a different
[Music]
one I don't know if there's a
point all right um I really hate doing
this oh I didn't get hurt yet but I
totally will oh wait I managed to do it
so I'm a genius
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] huh okay that's just the door
there's maybe behind that is this the
main p no okay that's just the girl
ni I want to lose my sanity we golden
maidens aren't to be sared at you'll
understand in time I'm
certain my you can't possibly think
he'll give you his Blessing
oh such naive F how amusing you are I
can't wait to welcome
you I don't find her that
infuriating Le purse okay for
what
interesting you should um sign the
contract and become a magical girl just
saying
[Music]
mea okay so now I still have to lead
them down to here
twice also was this
something no okay just the same
stuff come on come on
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay oh I
made it I did it again with no
damage m
q I haven't heard the voice in a long
time so I actually don't know what it
sounds
like
okay wa was something
cutesy O Come with Me o o
they're not following
me
[Music]
why maybe the green ones nope
no should I try walking around
them wait they're deving the thing huh
maybe they'll clear the path for me if I
lure them all here but they'll keep
following me if I don't well okay that's
basically just the same stuff so you are
saying that this is treated the same way
maybe I was just unlucky but man my
hearts and but if they are close enough
to touch me and they should be close
enough to follow
me attract all groups
here
[Music]
what no no no she she said that in other
places too there're just said she said
she says that in all of the like she
said the same thing down there as well
e didn't she you mean everybody needs to
go here
bro to eat the W oh because okay well
[Music]
[\h__\h] doesn't make sense to I think
so at least the one couple will be up
there then
still right ah
[\h__\h] wait wait wait wait that's not even
let me do it again
but yeah they need to go up then let's
just bring them
up I forgot about
them okay 3 2 1 go
ow
okay so ah they aren't here in this
timeline they're still down here fine
whatever ow hey I wasn't even ready yet
okay but I can turn it off quite far
away quite distance
still good to
know and when they say all of them do
they mean even the ones
[Music]
from all the way
here no
[Music]
way
yeah
okay follow me
yo yo yo yo what what you
mean you [\h__\h] kidding me why
did oh why did they that's my first game
over yay oh headless reference to a
certain
mommy yeah of course I'll continue but
um that was not fair was that too many
groups was it two groups I don't think
it was two groups though that's just one
group why did it hurt me so
much maybe I need to drop them off
once can I not do it in all in one go I
wonder well okay
go these ones are
fine and
then 3 2 1
go these ones are also okay
okay then I guess I'll try to drop them
off uh although they kind of started
hurting me really badly here already
maybe I'll drop them off once
here get just heal yeah but I don't even
have that many healing items I will heal
eventually but like I'm not going to
heal up all my [\h__\h] hearts and just
like accept them you know almost killing
me in exchange you
know the mushrooms heal they're [\h__\h]
poisonous
what no way those mushrooms heal
me yo I don't want to eat those you know
what they should do they should let me
heal me with that but they should also
take my sanity when I eat
them that's why they gave me so many of
those okay are you guys ready
butterflies I don't know do I should I
drop them
off let's drop him off once
yeah okay ah oh I didn't think You'
right away go for it okay yippee don't
tell me I okay I was about to say Don't
force me to get rid of them again as
[Music]
well very nice very nice
yeah let me see
did you get all the items I think
so that part was
stressful wait that's isn't that me the
[\h__\h] bro that's me that's my head I'm
already decapitated I guess that's
already one offering huh
uh uh
uh uh you've you've come to me at
last don't be frightened Elisa come
closer I had the Golden Girls I got the
Golden Girls I must have gotten the
Golden
Girl what is this
what in the lord's
name you've done well to find your way
into these
Woods it's just one of those fake
Halloween costumes I've seen that before
in modern family and stuff like like a
decapitated head in a basket that's so
easy especially with the stump
underneath the person is just hiding the
the whole body underneath like somehow
did the stump is hollowed out so yeah
yeah it's fine it's fine don't don't be
so scared guys it's a
costume it's imperative Elise that you
listen to me
closely he's once more or is it is this
the hag talking I thought it was he him
talking I don't really
know maybe maybe it's the hack talking I
don't
know what
the is the hag okay he's once more
trying to take you away from me but not
for
long take this basket now you are to
gather the gift I yeah right my
basket find your way to him deeper into
this Grove of mine only to then may only
then may your wish come to fruition my
beloved is this yeah the H is definitely
the supposed to be the the old grandma
that raised me right
I will guide you to him Elisa you ought
to trust my word your precious wish will
be safe with
me how am I to find
him you Elisa are my king my Triumph my
yeah my beloved progeny yeah is it not
Prodigy what what he's done to me is no
matter all I want is you
uhoh straw basket progeny
pren different word
oh there goes my
head I will allow him and his pets into
my Woodland once more oh oh there she is
they never they they didn't explain why
my head was in the basket though what
the
hell I will allow him to tempt you to
talk with
you what are you all for the greater
good my beloved so that we can be
reunited so that I can bear life in my
womb once more I'm losing my
wits so I can retrieve what's
mine oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] my
echo ah ah what the
what wait I'm to die I I lit don't know
am I supposed to run straight uh I want
to redo this please what why the hand
what am I what
what
what there was a path on the left
side
huh my
okay too bad I can't save after the
conversation come on
[\h__\h] what is
this sticky keys that's what that
is that it's not working
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] and my controls aren't working
now wait the Speedy thing is not
[Music]
working what is this fine I'll do it
this
[Music]
way
uh I'll probably die again
right
oh ah
[\h__\h] oh oh no oh no ah oh no what the
hell okay uh oh nice oh nice oh [\h__\h] oh
nice oh nice oh
nice kind of on a roll wao did I make it
oh no almost bit more a bit more just a
bit more g g g g oh I made it fly like a
butterfly what in the lord's name what
was that thing it together at least I
need to get a grip and go home to
Rosemary should have slept after all
should have taken some meds to sleep and
not go here to the
woods but at least we got our basket
priorities oh the
goat I don't trust the
goat flun what are you doing
here um it's kind of creepy now I
thought you'd be in The Granary or out
and about goodness I don't feel so
good um
oh Satan right is Satan the goat I think
I heard something about
that oh goats are
satanic I don't like the way he's
staring at
me oh yeah Lucifer
yeah what are
you oh [\h__\h] thank
godine your goat is creeping me out
now it's acting normal okay [\h__\h] it's
they're both they're both
[Music]
Satan I was out on the
walk but did this late at
[Music]
night you little
[\h__\h] what what is it
FY come let's go home W momy I don't
want to stay here a minute
longer oh
wait
what
what money what the what did I wait
for it's morning
already maybe it maybe my purple chicken
knocked me the [\h__\h] out after she said
wait that's why I don't remember
anything I suppose I really did go to
the Woodland didn't I I don't know what
to think of all that but both l m and
the old hack neither weren't lying it
seems I ought to pull myself
together it's best I head out for work
now I'll lose my wits if I keep
uh get out of here you little
[Music]
[\h__\h] are they
outside oh they
outside are they doing my fields
they better make themselves
[Music]
useful they would redeem themselves a
little bit for
me look got breakfast
[Music]
though I don't trust that girl me
neither I'm surprised she's a a like
option
for making
her well they're not here maybe they're
in the front
[Music]
check if we got The Leather
Pouch I'm pretty sure that save that I
loaded was a save after I came back
[Music]
no oh there it
is maybe sold for low price oh nice oh
these are all sellable items they're not
good for anything else then nice
[Music]
okay all
right this is a game where you can lock
yourself out of good ending early on oh
[\h__\h] then it must be if you if you
Romance the purple
chicken it must be because she's evil
you two are always making merry huh good
morning El good morning El I don't trust
her I don't trust her I'll never trust
her someone said Wednesday is the
important day huh the important day of
locking myself out
possibly good morning to you too FL you
little [\h__\h] I picked some mushrooms this
morning to poison you even further the
more I make food for you the more I'm
poisoning you you know I you're just
joking right but you put flock away in
the granery last night right of course
oh I think he's taking a like like into
it too I always leave the door a little
adart just in case I see is that so is
everything all right yeah maybe you
should close it completely you seem to
be on edge last night too there's
nothing Rosemary I just had strange
dreams I know you went to the woods
Elisa I'm sorry you don't have to tell
me about it but you know now don't you
that I'm speaking the truth about
whate anyhow come along let's head to
work all right but yeah if she always
helps me with the mini Quest she seems
to have plot
armor she must have plot armor
[Music]
then well I guess okay but if you do
romance her then the game is just over
so I guess it doesn't matter as long as
you stay neutral with her her that's
just my brain worms
[Music]
anyway that's just all in my head all my
imagination so I don't really know
anyway what do I
know let's
[Music]
save okay so so far I think we already
have the date thing like in the
afternoon yeah meet fre at her house so
we don't even have to make a new
appointment with
[Music]
her want to say thank you for checking
out this game of course I had it on my
mind for a while planning to you know
get PS for it and then play it for
Halloween cuz I don't really like super
super super spooky games as you guys
know but I thought this is kind of a
nice like compromise because it's also
in
Austria and it's a very special
game very unique and Charming maybe we
can go into the cave now oh no it's kind
of close
now weird
maybe maybe the
evening for sure
[Music]
how you doing
granny I yeah we need to make sure to
not miss the kusogaki
is she always in the same place I
wonder wait sorry uh want to sell
[Music]
there we go
fdie yo this one's a bit on the cheaper
side but yeah good already 40 from the
getg go without doing many
[Music]
quests okay and we'll already have the
juice the
the grape
juice so we just need to find her is
she does it show where she is on the
map probably
not where's
everyone uh do folks usually gather here
I wonder if something happened maybe
they conspiring against me in the church
come on now we must find out what's
going on and do some quests yes
mhm they're surely inside wait there's
some people outside there though I just
saw them
oh not here
huh I am
surprised okay can't
[Music]
go where else could they
be maybe they give me a
[Music]
hint oh Ela um Miss leg hor St oh then
they're probably all around the farm
talking about it there everyone's acting
strange that's natural myaa this isn't
something to take lightly I even heard
some folks saying they were hag ridden
hag
ridden
sorry actually let let me look at the
log not witch okay just talking about
witches
again ha Gren I've never heard that
[Music]
before Oh you girl are
here Ela
Rosary good
morning youve heard I'm
assuming uh about Mr oran's horses yeah
oh it's been awful everyone's been on
edge folks don't know what to do with
themselves for a good reason I'd say but
Mr Oran was so invested in his business
too old yin's Foolery isn't helping any
one I can already tell
and and they were hack what that's not a
word
is are you saying the hack was riding
the horses away they were hack ridden
away the [\h__\h] that's not a word right
tell me if it
is uh uh something tells me you know
what that
means maybe it's a word that only exists
in the game
oh no it is a
word r the tormented what the
hell why why is that called hack
ridden where is the origin of
[Music]
that she wouldn't know I'm
saved I I suppose not what a way to
start the day I think I'll take a look
about
town better be careful so folks are
getting R nervous about this mhm they're
getting up is that what you're
saying can I do any quests yet or is it
too
[Music]
early find out what happened okay ah
there we go yeah that's where I thought
you would be
oh now he's a full body art okay well
that guy actually we didn't talk to him
yet you have heard I'm sure yeah though
we're trying to figure out what
happened I'm rud that's what
happened as I said before again we will
do all we can to help we'll gather the
lads and send them out to patrol the
outskirts are we absolutely certain they
were stolen maybe they were just ridden
out by the Hat for a nice walk in the
park those horses were Hager and I tell
you not this nonsense again I tell you
lad there's a witch and Kea back oh
no should have
[Music]
saved what's not suspicious I don't know
I don't think either of those sounds
suspicious who would you say that is
even if they were haer that's kind of
like
avoiding talking about who the witch is
the left the first
one yeah he will point it point out that
it's me if I say
that are you sure
[Music]
are you
sure if you're so confident old Yan why
not come out and say it don't provoke
the old man at least uh no you mention
it what were you doing last night I was
in the forest or what was your little
cousin there doing that's a good
question I don't know sorry I
I'll ask you not to try folks patience
old
y yeah Chad come on you little shits I
thought you knew what you were doing I
thought at least one of you played the
game gave me the right
answer
bro what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
Chad I don't want to load my save just
for
that cuz I yeah have to skip for all the
conversations again
someone had to do it no two ways about
[Music]
it all there was when I got here this
morning was ban Hat's pig in a saddle
wait what why why is it in a
saddle don't rope me into this lad I
already told you I had nothing to do
with it where am I to blame them then
the witch let's keep com now
folks h
can't fall to poor ladford can we folks
Flynn
got and I will take a look around the
outskirts I'll go with you gust and we
should ask or again if you'd like to
join us to is there any way we can help
Mr gusta girl keep folks calm ala and go
about your day as you normally would
okay I don't mind
that Sassy options races fish
I did feel like yeah that's just asking
for trouble maybe you guys want me to
ask for trouble and get in trouble are
you oh is it cuz I'm hungry
oh I was thinking just eating a li cook
for
now that's so messed up
okay it's telling me to just do side
quests again apples wait help Elmo app I
haven't done that one
yet is she ah she's over
there is that one
[Music]
difficult oh wait oh we have to meet out
date now though I have to do the quest
afterwards oh isn't this like a fairy
Circle thingy when the mushrooms are
like in one Circle
I should have put a secret item
[Music]
there yeah is that a real thing
oh do you want your
item oh wait okay it's really cute how
she's peeking but I still despise her
woo let's go 10
[Music]
bucks you
that doesn't take time
right
gra I cannot afford being more
suspicioned by these
[Music]
people she literally talked about
blackmailing me that
[Music]
Bach well if we now avoid getting
everybody's suspicion and continue doing
her thing then eventually we'll be back
to
zero did she read what she wants
tomorrow no but she probably wants Leep
cooking
huh it's okay I'll buy one I expected as
much somehow I had a
[Music]
feeling here we go than time with my
beloved my one and only my true
[Music]
destiny I'm coming I'm
coming ah
hello wait you no no no oh no sorry I
misread wrong
girl I'm ignoring I mean I guess I could
but
but no I'd rather work I think we don't
want to even try continuing our love
[Music]
story might get us in real
trouble fetch some apples
okay I hope this one's
easy yeah I saved just a moment ago
before I walked over
here but yeah we could
try and like from what I'm getting it
seems like if I do her date then this
will lead to a bad
ending I don't know if it's right but
yeah wait oops [\h__\h] what did I is she
helping
me a [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I press ah I think I did
it's raining app oh no well well will I
even survive that I think I
will will
I oh this is an easy looking game though
you just move around back and forth and
catch the
apples really don't need her help
huh or will
[Music]
I okay I see this are really
fast oh Apple [\h__\h] Apple
I'm good at this though I'm pretty good
at this
oh [\h__\h] he's like aiming for me with the
[Music]
Anvil no more
animal oh I think that's pretty good I
really don't need her help oh I might
reload and then just do it without her
[Music]
pretty
slow oh nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice nice fake
out oh I'm I'm I'm not even they're not
catching me at all with those purple
[Music]
ones
oh
yo he was that a monkey dropping I
didn't see it
fuing monkey rank a I totally don't need
her
[Music]
help I might even pay extra to do it
twice what do you think about
that but do I have like if I am on zero
and I get a rank and I get 40 money will
it realize that that I already have
money now and let me pay the five or
do I have to get out of the wait oh
never mind I already had 40 okay never
mind but my question still kind of
stands I missed rank s by one point ah I
think I can do it then I try again sorry
sorry sorry we're reloading we're
reloading I want to do it again without
her help and then maybe we'll get S rank
and then I might do it twice hey you
only get paid
once oh then what's wor
[Music]
what's the point maybe that if you do
better on the second try you get the
money for the second
[Music]
try
okay a okay can't just safe
scum
okay let's not do worst
Taki you've done so well don't mess it
up
[Music]
now I should be better now
definitely catching less purples this
time oh yeah I'm doing better I think
I'll good S
rank you like them apples
c yeah little too late to get me 3 2 1
go
[Music]
very slow start
again the Anvil yeah
B oh [\h__\h] okay I'm kind of out of the oh
that almost got
me
dangerous oh my other second round might
may have been better oh [\h__\h]
but in total
maybe in total maybe CU you guys see my
score is that good no
no no how many points is S
rank missed 29 [\h__\h] yeah my second round
was kind of bad oh well it's pretty good
wouldn't mind doing that game again on
another
day yeah we're
fine that's that's it's doable
[Music]
but that might be one of my best mini
games they can give you the cool stuff
for free sometimes and even some L drops
what I should talk to everybody every
day
H the L drop sounds nice but I don't
have that much time to talk to everybody
so let's just open for an item
you guys can speed read
it we can kind of get an idea by speed
reading right I can kind of get an idea
it's not that
[Music]
fast good that we have
LS what from here how go let's going
into I don't really know I think it's
because of the goats I don't it's not
because of the goats what is it that I'm
not telling okay great
[Music]
um let's be nice can't force you
but like this is an optional
conversation but there's still a risk
that if I [\h__\h] up this will get my
suspicion up so
H it went
down oh wait
nice that's the first time we had a
suspicion go down by talking to one of
the random people
okay they didn't give me
anything what of all these fancy
people they they're all like susing each
other
[Music]
out that both of these answers are kind
of bad maybe I shouldn't have talked to
them in the first
place oh
[\h__\h] cuz like this is
me like making basically like not taking
them seriously and this is kind of being
[Music]
sassy to is more sassy we'll see we can
afford getting our suspicion up
again that's what I'd like to ask you
old hag be nice to each other come
on why you this work about time truly
oh yeah okay well chat chat what is
wrong with you
chat chat come
on I I thought both of those options
were weird but if anything maybe I was
leaning towards the right
one why you safe before talking because
too much safe scumming is also a bit
ridiculous
[Music]
okay I'm going to go to
Freya oh
oops especially for the suspicion that's
still very manageable we can still fix
it um meet by the house where is she
where's her house oh there okay
[Music]
you used up all your safe
slots is there a limited
amount maybe we can fix it with these
people going where uh we're helping out
the Stalls and you should join us I'm
not certain I have the time that's all
right we' been busy wonder the going
[Music]
on oh man they didn't even give me a
choice to cuz I guess they like me
[Music]
old
requests
[Music]
oops the hearts are even at the entrance
of the
[Music]
house yeah I also thought like cuz we
that right option was kind of
invalidating right I I I thought so so
both options were [\h__\h] but okay maybe
maybe both options would have lowered
our raised our
suspicion oh pleas oh
cute why are you opening up there is
this a little shop a flower shop I
guess Ling about home are you Freya
nothing of the sort in fact I've been
rather busy you did say you'd be at home
all afternoon I was going to get a head
start on the festival preparations but I
couldn't bear seeing all of Kea back on
edge like this more than on edge Freya
the town folk are rabbit oh El
Le all this witch nonsense she says it
again it's only making things worse too
that's why we ought to bring some cheer
ourselves to
it cheer you Saye that sounds friendly
right this is like kind of like you know
she doesn't I don't think she
appreciates me [\h__\h] talking the folks
where she grew up for goodness sake you
know better than to
wait what that's not how I implied that
imp
that's not how I took that option cheer
you I I thought it was more like a cheer
you
say yeah sounds good all right so what
the hell I know what what what's wrong
with me why is she so rude why is she
sarcastic don't say that El a look does
this mess everything up come
on I've been baking pies for everyone oh
ad oh my god let's go pies but she
doesn't seem
like upset about what I said at least
last time she was upset that's so
many I mean I have gotten carried away A
little maybe give me one of those pies
for healing item
please it was a good excuse to try out
my mother's recipes your mother's
recipes oh yeah she used to keep a lot
of journals oh it's wonderful for
sealing and baking and making ointments
anything you can think of oh she's the
perfect wife so that's how you know how
to do all of that
after all I was too young to learn from
her in person
Freya oh right before I forget grape pie
was it oh that sounds better than grape
soup you got some for
me wait that's so
cute
ah
cute cute you favorite silly it was grap
pie wasn't it now that you mention it I
suppose make sure you shared with
Rosemarie your purple
chicken you baked an entire pie for I'm
doing it for all of ke be I couldn't
forget about you could I but I get a
special one I know you going sacri I
don't know for sure if I'm sacrificing
if that's the only the vibe that I'm
getting but
[Music]
um Maybe not maybe not sacrificing her
maybe we'll be happily ever after in
afterlife uh you
truly movie she's doing a stretch
continue sleeping no no why' you decide
to leave
girl
a she's walking like a little zombie
cute fluffy
dumpie trying to show you how I feel
Elisa
oh goodness you're red as a beat sh it
you whose fault is that you oh El I
didn't even say anything that bad Sil
but it seems like we're we're going into
the right direction here one more word
and I'll tell allly about these pies for
goodness sake I truly did listen to what
you said to me on Sunday Elisa and
everything I've said and done since then
I've meant it so I'm well aware F huh
right say I'll be landing Mrs VMA Hand
by in by the in tomorrow at desk all
right all right I'll be there oh you
could be a little more genuine Elisa for
goodness sake you could be a little less
cheeky
for oh but it's so much fun getting you
flaster
Elisa why
you okay stop this is I'm cringing a
little bit cringing a little
[Music]
bit but okay seems like the answer was
the right
[Music]
one it's already so
late can you even do quests at this time
anymore too much
less she'll be such a cute
sacrifice seems like they're back from
looking for the horses
but of course she scattered about you
say found him just past the logging
grounds
but why the lord's name would anyone
remove Hors
[Music]
shoes is that some something like a
witch would do or something a Satan
would
do wake up lety we ha and I tell you
this isn't the time old Yan we must keep
calm ah thank you for your time to dland
I'll be moving along now I've had enough
wondering about okay chill they'll come
back for
sure I've never seen him so disheartened
say till thank you Lads didn't even find
a trace we looked everywhere miss m the
Peaks the lake Henrich and twist you did
you guys look in the forest perhaps I
will find them in the forest tonight H
but dead and eaten
H might be something in the wishing well
you mean the thing right there next to
me is that a wishing
well okay oh
oh what the [\h__\h] you found the
horses I found the horses right
outside what what are you saying Maggie
Maggie
Maggie seems like I'm not the only one
getting her name wrong is it alive take
us to it Lassie bro
oh my God it's not dead but uh oh no man
its eyes do look ha
ridden oh [\h__\h]
name oh my
God yeah
B he's exhausted that can't be we've
only just made it back we would have
found it more and more I must say I'm
the Lost Lads and they were H they were
haer to know two ways about it look at
it gasping for breath ew look at its
eyes yeah I have to
[Music]
agree I'm taking him back to the Stables
right now I'll in the
hand don't touch Lord knows what the
witch has done to it come now lad let's
go fetch him some water
H poor horse man always feel so bad when
like in in movies and stuff there's like
in medieval movies especially when
there's horses going to battle and then
they're either just
like also being killed in the battle or
they're Riders are being killed and then
they're like aimlessly sadly confusedly
lostly
wandering around always feel so bad poor
horse yeah what the [\h__\h] do I do
now my rider is gone and
dead what the [\h__\h] happened what is this
anyway I want to go back to the nice P
pet
pastures anyway broke off the rains and
ran back to ke I can't think of nonsense
bard
oh oh oh God he's doing it again I'll
have it said right here right now folks
it's best you show some restraint old y
isn't this guy's creepy but at least he
keeps on trying
to this is like the this is like you
know the why are you gay like he's the
they both suck but he's the TV show host
who's like you know kind of iffy about
everything too but he will try to
restrain the the ri [\h__\h] up
guy literally okay but the pastor in
this case the father is the better
one why are you gay why are you wit why
are you witch why are you
witch oh Stefan warned us about
this you want to show me something with
some fruit hm tell me
about why are you witch
[Music]
who is
witch does Austria celebrate Halloween
not really
celebrate um definitely yeah there's
some
trick-or-treating uh with like younger
kids but I haven't done it in in many
many years and I haven't gotten trick
trick-or treated by kids either
ever who is witch why are you witch
why are you witch why are you gay witch
that's even worse oh my God can you
believe
how how mind [\h__\h] the pastor would be
if he were faced by not only a lesbian
but by a witch lesbian that is like
double shock to his
[Music]
religion oh
no oh boy that is too much for him to
take
why are you gay witch what the
[\h__\h] I love that Meme it's a good
[Music]
meme this like M
to I I I
guess we need to keep calm fo arguing
about this won't have you no memory of
his word Hans gustaff he spoke of the
ill Fortune we we'd have of the witch of
folk livelihood slipping through their
fingers old Stefan was a tormented lad
on his death bed all
Yen H there is worse to come folks mark
my
words what are we to do with him
father just wait for him to tie himself
out that's all we can
do come folks let's head back to
town but that was only one horse what
about the other
horses are we just going to
chill and forget about it accept one
horse things are starting to get a
little out of hand aren't
they
yeah
oh what I thought I was getting a bad
ending just
[Music]
now is that what was that like a
midpoint why did I get that screen
it's like a
cutaway title draw like an anime
intermission act break oh okay wait what
do we have to do oh we can still
[Music]
do later later as in tomorrow right with
Freya um but we can still do another
Quest it seems kiss the rat or what more
app I can do apples again on the same
day I won't get paid
[Music]
right if it's like a separate occasion
like
not like directly
afterwards are you the rat guy
or yeah think it's a rat
game uh I don't know you I will take
okay then let's play the apple game
[Music]
again why did why is he changing
locations is is it the same apple
[Music]
game H seems like it okay nice another
40 today today we're doing pretty well
on
money cuz people don't say the same yeah
but the apple trees are elsewhere it
made more sense where she was
before all right here we go more apples
Apple all
day we're Appling now Apple
maxing
okay apples are really not my favorite
fruit though I'd prefer to
be catching some other stuff maybe we
can get S this time I'll try my best wao
uh-oh ow no [\h__\h] should have saved no I
want to redo I want to
redo do we have to hear the whole horse
talk
again maybe I'll still get a if if I
still get a I'm okay
W
[Music]
go good good good good
good a [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh it's not always the same pattern
right you can't learn it by just
learning the pattern right is this
a please please please please
yeah hey
okay then I'm
fine K is voice way too hard and no
extra no extra was there ever extra
payout but yeah I'm I'm fine not doing
the red game it's like doable
[Music]
but okay what do you mean absolutely not
Ed it's fine I didn't need
s people move around and and they change
their dials yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's nice they wrote a lot of
[Music]
scripts okay already night
time we're focusing on one lady so we're
not um losing
time wait I I okay I'm I'm fine I
thought I
died by starvation
why my heart so low is it still from the
boss
[Music]
fight
okay now you can find the secret at the
other
well
oh you don't this
[Music]
one you mean the one where we once had a
date the water well
[Music]
or the water
well can I fix my susp even now with
like a single
person Move Along
[Music]
okay here I
go I hope it's a good secret I I feel
like I already got what I needed from
there
I'm rather lucky to have my own well in
the backyard huh can't imagine having to
come all this way just for some water
covered in closes of Ivy keep's water B
overlooks the valley down
[Music]
below what do you mean do you mean like
down here the the ghost I already got
the ghost down
here this well is after tumor Secrets
not unlocked
yet
huh no it was like two guys I
think
okay you have to do the cave first ah
okay I I want to check if we can enter
the cave now
now saying we've always made the best of
this
[Music]
Festival all right it's
hallowe wait right but PO is not just
supposed to be Halloween right or like
Halloween is supposed to be about P now
wa it's so perfect that I'm playing it
today I was just thinking to myself when
they were talking about we always made
the F of this Festival I was thinking
like who who even cares about that pugn
in the real world like that's not really
a thing but now now I reminded myself oh
that's just the
Halloween yeah I have the
note Elisa oh what this what does this
old hag want
now don't stab
me where do you think you're going Alisa
at home I need to have a word with you
what's this about Miss Bera your cousin
that's what this is about Elisa the last
has been wondering about town you know
she's been helping me out Mrs Berto no I
don't think so Li your cousin's been
telling folks there's no fief in keeper
BG okay oh [\h__\h]
uh maybe I should say this one because
it's kind of like a reference to someone
else that she should be
trusting he's been insisting on the hack
riding hasn't
he well it's one thing but your cousin
has no right to be spreading such
nonsense Elisa all right I can have a
word with her I suppose
up I don't get it a lot of these like
answers also like are hard to tell what
exactly Elisa will
say what you have another question she's
also been recommending builda herbal
medicines okay let's not go for that
then let's say because she cares I
understand she shouldn't have been been
doing this but I'll let her know she
that's not really what
she that's that's not at all what the
the the thing I chose is
[Music]
saying you get these events if you don't
take her to work
[Music]
oh
bro but she she cost so much bread to
take her with
me as long as you understand it l and
one more thing last you cousin told Mrs
Elizabeth she could have look a look at
her goods for
her do might be able to help what so bad
by my cousin making her oh God that's
that's sassy that's
sassy a
bro ridiculous I almost want to redo
this
so
unfair not even going to bother talking
to your ladies
[Music]
now oh PO is not on the Halloween dates
oh
was that the right one yeah right but
then this one is this
one okay we're fine this
[Music]
time yeah left right left okie dokie oh
are you going to give me bread again
please I thought you never come about
Ela oh spare me here's your bread thank
you
[Music]
yay I guess I could afford like if I do
two quests with a rank I could probably
afford
taking um uh my chicken for
one but I mean if I can just nail the
questions or like safe scum the
[Music]
questions then I'll end up with more
bread in the end so whatever right
[Music]
okay I'm selling I still have something
to
sell I'm surprised this is that the the
sellable items those special items are
mixed in the same bag as this
one I one of fre
money
[Music]
yo so much okay okay buying a lip
cooking for
tomorrow and I
[Music]
guess couple breads maybe
free and
then maybe one
[Music]
pretzel is that enough for
now I think I still have a couple of
heating items the mushrooms and the some
bandages so probably
fine matches I still have enough from
last
time definitely should be
fine oh yeah okay let's eat wa one
bandage oh yeah yeah I've got healing
items these two and then more
mushrooms okay only one but still and
the grapes also
yeah okay I'll actually eat one
grape and one bread and now we're back
full are you liking the game I like it
did you did we talk to M yeah yeah yeah
yeah she already wants the next oh hey
didn't they carry him away also the crow
up
there holy
[\h__\h] it's golden though that's missile
against
oh you've come you've
[Music]
come you're wearing them you're wearing
them shiny shiny shiny shiny what's the
meaning of this who's
there the hex the hex the
[Music]
hex you're the bear of the
heck oh hex with
hex hex hex hex
hex you've heard of it you're wearing it
as we
speak stay
away show it to me show me your
feet I don't want to show you my feet go
away why yes you do your desire I'll
even pay you for showing me your feet
fent greed your boundless hunger for
Glory show to us show to
us yeah B
oh oh [\h__\h] he poked my eye or what my
eye what have you done to my eye die
show it to us show it to us girl out
with it you
rich I thought it was game over for a
moment maybe you are which oh definitely
I Am The Testament to your tender flesh
is awaiting you in my Grove
oh a
testament oh my eye bro you took my eye
why didn't I get to choose what I wanted
to be my
Testament great thanks could have could
have gone easy on me and just taken the
strand of hair or a fingernail as we
said but no had to go
[Music]
hardcore I'm a waiting you Lisa in my
ceramic Grove of
wheat does that mean we mean we get some
bread there anyhow I ought to let Mr
again know about this
horse it they will 100% think I did this
again
H oh the nun is
gone
hello
hello where's everybody oh here you are
Mr again good Le Elisa what's got you in
such a hurry there's a horse in The
Crossroads are you certain Ela yeah yeah
I'm
certain the last says she uh she found
your horse
again take me there L I'll go f the
other but it's dead Mr I and I didn't do
it it matters not let's take me there
okay okay
oh wow did we need everybody oh it's
gone
no what in the lord's name it was right
here I
swear good Lord
Elisa would you tell us what you saw
Elisa there were crows and the horse
was no we're going to be we're going to
be told this is
witchcraft are you certain this is where
you saw it yeah I
am you're tired at I'm I'm certain this
was just oh when people tell you like
when you're trying to convince people of
something and they're like oh you're
just tired yeah they think you're insane
they think you are not to be trusted
anymore there's only one oh yeah you
going to say it you going to say it
Point your stick at me you're lying Ela
oh sh it I'm not lying you old fool if
you let me explain I could tell
you you said the horse was dead Eliza oh
that was a lady and and it
was How could a dead horse shot away
would you
say it's no use to try reasoning with
her CH she's
lying well
great it's the
truth I've had enough I'll be in the
Stables
great I think I chose the right girl in
any case tell us a Las why you speaking
the
truth maybe I should say
this cuz otherwise I'll just sound
[Music]
crazy the people are saying too who of
you played the
game Double Down screw these people
[Music]
chat I'm so done with you you always
give me the wrong
one I hate
[Music]
you I told
you bro
did I skip that did I save before this
convers oh there's more let Us's say
there was a horse loser what's this
about
[Music]
Crow well both of these options don't
look very good to me isn't this the same
thing
basically double down
again what did I
say uh
uh I don't know man at this point I saw
what I saw I won't deny any of what I
said please Alisa I'm just shocked to
see there's nothing here maybe I can't
make it worse anymore surely I wouldn't
lie about such a
thing you think you've got us fooled huh
you shouldn't make such accusations it's
best
we can't folk see she's trying to
deceive us do you know something Alisa
what I don't know what it is but I'll
have it said Lassie You Can Dance with
the Devil all you want but you
won't that's ridiculous that's enough
we've all had difficult day today folks
we're all exhausted drained and on edge
are we
not why you trying to defend
your no Li is quite right old Yen let us
turn in for the night we can come back
to this
tomorrow okay
that sounded like kind of demonic you're
going home Elis and you should think
long and hard about what you've done
what I've
done what what have I
[Music]
done Gaslight girl keep girl boss what
gatekeep gas light gatekeep girl
boss go away sticky
keys I'm worried about leave but I ought
to go home until Marine what I just saw
I don't think we should be talking to
Ros Marine at all anymore but
okay I'm just going to take it I think
the suspicion this thing
is s salvageable still can't go in am I
supposed to like just open the
item in front of
it or is this the same
[Music]
oh no doesn't
help it's too
late
[Music]
no this was very bad it's not only
suspicion this game you think I [\h__\h]
up there's another way to get into the
cave is there can I walk around
well not
[Music]
now do the other option yeah whatever
you tell me I'll do the other
[Music]
thing it's not needed for the good ends
but it has low and unlock uh an optional
bad end oh what you're saying that I'm
so um fine for the good ending
[Music]
oh okay uh in terms of the cave but what
what about in terms of the the town
meeting we just
[Music]
had okay okay okay so good
okay whatever I would be even kind of
excited about a bad ending I wouldn't
mind too much would be funny as long as
the bad ending doesn't come too early
and ends everything too early but in any
case we're not finishing today because
the game takes like 12 hours oh sorry
they would have found out about
everything about the woods about what I
did that's right I best get to the
Crow's Grove The Testament they have the
T of fles I should they have my
eye are you right no I don't know where
to start
I'm so tired it's this this rotten pixie
of town for real I would want to leave
too at this
point I saw one of melan's horses on the
way home rosemarine it was dead but it
was riddled of crows and oh sorry I
don't understand at least you should
tell more importantly what
me there was a golden Crow and he said
he's got a
testament oh yeah
yippe not so much yippy my my
[Music]
friends this is too much for me but what
else did he say Elisa I'm so
tired H I went back to town to tell
everyone about the horse and
they they humiliated me
[Music]
Marine each and every day I'm treated as
though I'm some rat no what I do or say
I'm always
always oh she's so frustrated having a
breakdown this wish of M know my I can
can I truly trust him to granted no no
no no no oh God she's so on his
side if you devote yourself to him and
do his bidding you're already aware of
the sacrifices you'll have to make but
it's I'd sacrifice all of Kea be if I
had to oh [\h__\h] that's evil talk
I can't stay another day in this town I
have no choice but to find him oh but I
I take me with you though you're going
there again tonight aren't you to the
woods well I I'll let you know when I'm
ready uh is that optional too cuz like
do we really want to take
[Music]
her I safe
not optional
okay double
down I'm sorry
I let's go
yes keep close to me whatever happens of
course leepy
okay I know that way follow
me are there repes your
relatives obviously not but Austria
is represented by the beautiful
mountains and the style of the village I
suppose now I wonder what kind of
challenge we will be be facing
today hopefully it won't be too
difficult this is where it happened Ros
Marine a look n
oh
interesting Hors shoes there are so many
too these weren't here earlier was M it
doesn't make any sense they FEA scar
scattered about it too are these from
the crows you said you
saw uh yeah I guess they do look
golden
[Music]
okay yeah I I really um you know
normally Austria as you say it doesn't
really get to be the place of a game or
so very often and movies as well sound
of music is a big exception that's why I
wanted to play this it's special even
though really a it being in Austria so
far really doesn't matter it could have
been anywhere this could be playing
anywhere but still for goodness sake got
to pay my
respects s she must have wanted in all
by herself oh great Marine
great here we
go it's only Dean [\h__\h] I thought we were
already on
midv
Wednesday
[Music]
ooh uh what what the
hell oh
what she just accepts it instead of
getting scared and jumping
off cool cool cool
cool yeah no problem this is
fine Rosen
[Music]
Marine for goodness sake where the
lord's name did she go I best carry on I
suppose there's no going
back can't
[Music]
run interesting music this is making me
feel like I'm playing Diablo I
oh pleasant surprise pleasant
surprise how pleasant it is to see you
here last I thought you were the ones
that invited me K not every last who
gets these shoes wind up in here they
Happ in others you're not special you're
not
special I am special obviously
[Music]
so far quite nice oh what the hell is
that like a portal or
something Rosen Marine Rosen
Marine for goodness sake what were you
thinking wondering off like that you I'm
sorry I'm I'm sorry I told you to stay
close to
me I got a little distracted as all
you're such a little [\h__\h] I'm so sick of
you H this isn't the time or the place
to get distracted Rosen Marine ah we
don't even know what could be in these
Woods bro bro she never looked like this
before hurry it up calm now we can't sit
around all
night
um wa I thought saving Point yeah
should I look around a little
[Music]
bit wait is this where I'm supposed to
go I thought I was going to try to go
through these things oh nope never mind
that's nothing I can go
through I see it's a big
Crow feel like I'm playing Diablo
matches
again
hi tell me cor where are we exactly I'll
tell you nothing I'll tell you nothing
oh why do I bother this is my laun room
where else could we be so do you know
where we are never said I didn't did I I
suppose not great I learned so much from
that
Nest yeah NE neatly carved ceramic po MH
MH mhm bird nests
oh
okay
he it wants me to place something here
huh uh a bird's claw there's something
missing in the center isn't there
slightly hinting me towards the solution
totally not
sus yeah I kind of avoided the middle
thinking that wait am I supposed to
place that it's a ring wow so
pretty what I'm not going to ask you to
marry me so don't even think of it
that's the crow what did you
say [\h__\h]
ow
oh so it didn't really take my eye until
now or
what you come you
come look who it is look who it is you
brought me such good company too out
with it but it's not my lover don't
misunderstand what are you wittering all
about you
wret you've done well in coming here
last
year you'd best give me what you
promised Crow what he
Pro The Testament The
Testament where is it
Crow come a little further into my grow
CL why you little [\h__\h] I didn't hear
about
this show it to me show it to
me what is she to show you Crow Rosen
Marine oh
[\h__\h] give me back that
[Music]
ringu show me how far those Ruby shoes
will take you all that your desire last
it's all so close yet so
far could at least tell me your name
Crow If you have't it's written on the
floor
girl that's a secret that's a
secret can't you read why you at bird
that doesn't answer
my enough chatting enough chatting come
find me if you'd like to know
more wait yeah yeah yeah yeah shut
up yeah we're like what the hell got
into
you uh when is it starting you guys
should be watching it
yeah I'm excited for it I want to see it
too thanks for the Super
Chat H okay oh he opened up a path but
wait why when you didn't even even let
me put the thing on
[Music]
here yeah what you
say
okay oh he stole it from never
mind that little [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay well then we got to
follow no
[Music]
choice do I have to stay close to the
not moving
trees wait what's over here aha
[Music]
you're going forth with his invitation I
see I was once in your shoes H quite
literally Hess and all oh but it won't
be long now will it your eyes are forced
to open then you'll see that this
mimicry of theirs isn't without raising
girl I know when I'm being mock thank
you very much you're not being mock girl
you're just getting a reality check
[Music]
am I getting this right cuz this kind of
reminds me of the the kodok
forest sorry that was moving so yeah I
think that's how it
works uh is this safe
here I want to touch
that I I wanted to break the vase not
talk to you
Acorn is that food or something okay
what's not
moving what the [\h__\h] I
grow but at least I immediately
understood how this is supposed to go
just kind of unfair I'm doing it
correctly and you're still hurting me
kind of
[Music]
rude oh there it is
for goodness sake I thought we wouldn't
see the end of it come now let's get out
of here I'm not sure it's that easy huh
no it's nothing let's
go uh do I have to take the same way
back no okay
good got the ring
back I'm the ring bearer now who's the
ring bearer now it is me
can you just place it in or do I have to
pick it from my
inventory
okay oh ring of gigy
MIM want to rule them all want to lose
my
eye let's go I'm so excited to lose my
[Music]
eye he will be pleased he will be
pleased hurry it up
come furland for goodness
sake Frozen Marine it's better to not
speak to him like that the
[\h__\h] all the answers you seek lie deeper
Within These Woods GL
year Meet Me in the wheat field show me
your
[Music]
resolution you have my word you have my
word you reminding me like I'm never
gardening after all am I I thought I was
was going to be gardening in that game I
was
deceived they're taking the W to Eisen
guard taking the W to e and guard it's
4K that red bird is playing with
me Marine I thought we were going down
the elevator here or is that the exit
it's nothing we're going to go after him
she's not nervous she's hiding
something I'm so naive and oblivious
Mama Mia
H which way how dare you give me two
paths oh
aha RPG instincts let's
go how I love you naive sheep following
his Blissful word into this moonless
Hellfire of ours well you did the same
didn't
you R fed his gluttony one after the
other other our since Unearthed made
into a spectacle for all to
see your fate is one of us is sealed you
foolish
girl ah my fate is one of
[Music]
them might be time to eat one of those
sanity things at some point
[Music]
soon so it's true so it's true I'll
never get used to you FEA R
screening but I might have to she's here
she's here it's best we move along oh
she's so so messed
up she brought the witch she brought the
witch Oh you mean the girl next to
me you know yeah I'm really curious
about what happens if you do romance her
there seems to be something wrong with
that what are they going on about
now you're you're in our you're you're
our L you're our L which you have no
hand in this room out with it you've got
the wrong L CS now let us go through I
suppose it's because of the
Hat you're in a lir the lir of Lord M
the lay of Lord M the lay of
[Music]
Lord oh
[\h__\h] do you know who that
is you know him too he's un
merciful what
what Maris
it's best we move along now mov
him she's speaking in
[Music]
tongues what the hell the light is
freaking me
out what's this extra
path
[Music]
s
ah I'm really good at finding new
French style of nobility yeah I think I
heard it
before
cute W that looks
yummy better than the stupid purple soup
okay I think I'll take one of the
medicines
now
um I don't know how
much uh it is like I guess I'll take the
big one cuz I don't have
any
other okay it didn't fill it up fully so
at least I didn't waste
anything very
nice that's cut
off your total sanity point is 100 okay
so I guess each time I lose something it
takes
10 and now I filled up
half hello oh there you are I like how
you always brings that Rose like I don't
know what is he trying to do being
flirty I'm not into Birds
okay except
[Music]
chickens up ahead Lord Mo if you give
the rest of your own whining I've had it
with you when
your oh it's supposed to be a maze
maybe the crows tell me hints
then an
offering am I
offering a they they all are just
crazy oh
what I didn't realize it could come out
again what the hell okay reloading twice
I don't accept once I accept twice no
[Laughter]
so wait um what was the hint that that
was the bad path oh it's already dark
okay then that was pretty
obvious H there's something
there I'm going to reach
it oh my God is that like some kind of
like what is that if I go straight up if
I go if I go fast oh yeah okay okay it
goes like in One Direction and then
Bonks
it itself
again can
I I mean I understand how it works but
this still kind of um
difficult um okay we'll
go really
fast okay nice and then we'll go really
fast fast again nice what the [\h__\h] is
that it's so fast I can't really
tell oh
no and Oaks
what
uhoh eager to meet him eager to meet him
blah blah blah blah blah they all kind
of say the same
stuff don't think it's worth talking to
them can't catch me oh I think this one
I can only reach from around I don't
know if it's above or
below oh oh I got it yippe a level purse
okay cool extra
money
shush I don't want to miss any extra
items but outside here that doesn't
count right so it's only in here
probably what the [\h__\h] now I got a
little bit of a closer look oh yeah oh
okay stay here wait there's oh there's
so many
there fast fast oh
hold okay but that's kind of a dead
end I can't pass through the middle some
maybe on the right
side oh
yeah cool I like this like so far all
the games I mean some of them had a
little bit of frustrating moment but
generally it's
like uh everything is different every
phase is different every night is
different and everything's challenging
but um not too frustrating
woohoo right I I like it uh where did I
go now I was want to make sure I check
out every side so I don't miss anything
oh there is something
there give it whoa
whoa
wa
matches uhoh
uh
okay I wasn't sure what the best course
of action was
there yeah oh yeah can I go up yeah okay
[Music]
they should give me healing items not so
many [\h__\h] uh uh matches or can I heal
with the
acorns no way they give me a heart it's
a freaking
[Music]
Acorn all right I'll take it
um up angered
them Side Run
Run that's the exit it seems I hope I
didn't miss anything I think I got
pretty much everything unless I maybe I
missed
the I wonder if I missed a golden ghost
[Music]
thingy down here I wasn't
very proper cuz I
ran check your locket
in what's there to see ah you mean like
this
ah
aha now I understand
oh oh oh look at her she's so [\h__\h]
up wait why why do
they oh do they only look like this in
the witching hour that's what the person
before
meant they only look like this in a
witching hour probably if I look at the
locket at that
time I think we made
it please don't tell me that this also
ends in me running all the way out being
chased and having to go for the forest
again trying to find a safe
route he sure likes being chased around
huh come now let's go before he decides
to fly away
again is there still stuff to find oh
yeah oh there's still the horse is still
a crow
slate oh maybe I'm supposed to find
these things for whatever reason oh
that's surely that floor is not
safe I can
tell oh there's more unsafe
floor
oh wait I want to check can I not go up
there I I wonder maybe the floor is fine
woo but there's nothing there I think
huh why is this game suddenly Crow UPS
say before it was butterflies maybe it's
something else each time maybe next time
it's um it's the the
snakes I must find a way to open all of
these ah oh wait I'm fine it's step by
step
huh
oopsie there you go
[Music]
okay
oh I thought this would give me another
like area to discover but no it's just a
[Music]
PSU oh
[\h__\h] all right I see one oh the crow is
there what the hell what are you doing
there grape juice oh that's not what I
expected fancy seeing you fancy seeing
you you're resolve you're
resolve provoke me provoke me follow
your instinct last pain no heat to this
creature you've brought along
oh
spicy she's no creature you wret yet in
since you
insist a
okay in this case I mean I can't get
like uh sused out right so it doesn't
really matter maybe I can ask all of
these who is
he you ought to know him rather
well his name is to remain unspoken last
oh
Voldemort whatever his name is isn't of
any concern to me Crow all I want is to
know more about him and his intentions
what about him what about
him quite right L he's gifted them to
you PVE your way to meet him on the
night of the full moon with nothing
other than a
hex on the night of the full
moon Sanel pgar Eve the day of the
festival we're to Feast upon your greed
to Feast upon your
bra he's gifted me a hex you say
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh we really could only ask one
question just
now man and he didn't even leave behind
one of those
plates where do I find the next one okay
ah can I use nah I can't use the same
one each time right that would
be lame well I can
try this isn't the witch I remember yeah
and also not the Winks
either what where was
it all it's gone okay
so really need to find W how did I dodge
that one
woo they're they've got the
Zoomies hardcore
Zoomies H maybe there was more up here I
thought I O I thought I saw it all
careful
careful yeah there's there's a dead end
here ah if I can remove it
oh after putting it
[Music]
in yeah I was thinking it will close
again oh maybe then the the what I'm
supposed to understand from that is that
that is a dead end the the wrong path to
open I shouldn't be opening all all
paths but the just the particular ones
ah I see ah there's a there's one there
so I open this up and then I get an
extra
one
oops I wish just for some quality of
life they should let me use the items
without going into the menu like the
game should recognize I have the it and
then just put it in it's a bit annoying
to go into the menu each
time okay uh now can I get it back yes
now I have
two interesting so then maybe somewhere
I need two to get a thir and so
on I I don't remember how it was down
here was there seemingly one to
achieve Maybe
possibly if I zoom like they then maybe
I can be
safe got to be
fast ah
[\h__\h]
[Music]
yes use but not and it doesn't look like
I get another one there
over here
what wasn't that reachable by oh my God
I didn't see okay go grab it that is
just
open to
take you got one more out to watch oh
hell
yeah I didn't realize I could even go up
here okay maybe now we can get further
[Music]
ow ow ow
ow can we move on now here or
not oh sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry
okay and oh might be the last one
actually if we we're
lucky
oh
oh time to lose more
sanity how long has it been I wonder
tell me how long has it been since you
were Bamboozled what by one of us what I
wasn't Bamboozled what are you talking
about I'm not like the others I'm not
one to share my sorrows you'll be
joining us soon enough whether you like
it or not look at your face look at your
face I'm so dramatic about this like
they're really fine nice to talk to like
I should appreciate having some extra
input from girls who've been through the
same
[\h__\h] yeah she's so
dense you tied is it okay 6 hour already
just really hungry
TBH so and my voice is tired me myself
I'm like okay but I think after this
I'll I'll be done for
today oh by the way for tomorrow I still
really don't have a real plan I kind of
thought I had I wanted to mix like Koke
with uh
Callins but I wanted to make sure I have
some call cins like set in stone but I
don't really have many so I don't know
but I guess I'll still do it even if
it's just like two
people maybe one will join spontaneously
or
so yeah yeah
yeah yeah I really just want to I don't
know pounce
around no I got two
RSVPs I just didn't an open like hello
anybody
available available during this time
like I totally understand if like girls
don't have time especially if they're in
the Japanese time zone or
so impressive Blass impressive glass
what's gotten into you
rosemarine who's rosemarine who's my fro
[Music]
hurt hey
girl do you think maybe she got hired to
find
more uh
sacrifices you're just time for the
tender flash L tender flesh
that's Testament The
Testament what the [\h__\h] can you stop
hitting my eye can you stop poking it it
hurts don't come any closer R peckish R
peckish oh yeah you are hey hey hey I'm
telling you to stay away from me what
the [\h__\h] they're killing me eat a horse
go eat a horse no way may I FL serve him
may I FL serve him did they really take
it let be isas from now on
holy holy
[\h__\h] and I can honestly not imagine
oh they took my my hair not my
eye if they took my eye I would not
understand how she would continue with
this
quest after being hurt so much that'd be
ridiculous what is this is this the
flesh my own hair a part of me my mortal
body just like rosemarine told me Rosen
Marine I'm must find her Lord knows what
those crows did to
her
okay man they should have taken my
eye that would be way more hardcore and
that's honestly what it sounded
like what's over there
secret no
ah fro and Mar
Rosen
Marine uhoh are we fighting her Elise is
she going to turn
evil can you hear it Elise the Woodland
my gr it's aching what are you saying
Rosen Marine You've Lost Your wits the
moment we got
here even under their influence it's out
with it I'm serious that's enough it's
aching for what was taken from its bosom
at least now that you're here it's
[Music]
reacting can you hear
it here what these roots the
[Music]
earth
oh is it a horse head skull
the visuals are so on point guys they'll
guide you to your rightful place out
with it I don't have time for this
nonsense Rosen Marine I've done what I
came here to do we ought to leave to the
W
Al where you were conceived where you
will go to meet your fate Frozen Marine
you're not listening do think he's once
more trying to take you away from me
turned my bosom into this parched
Wasteland found in yet but this womb of
mine still responds to your presence all
the
same her wom is reacting to me I'm so
flattered what
what I will bring you home Elisa I will
do everything in my power take my hat
girl
um what in the lord's
name I I I will oh she's hiding her eyes
now I will bring you home
Elisa come with me rosemarine we have to
get out of
here nah we've come this far I want to
see some action what the hell it's on
the
wheel
oops okay so one hit
I see how it is I really want hit or did
I have low
HP yeah I was I was a little bit
hesitant
sorry how do you skip this for goodness
sake why can I not speed through
it
wait I'm losing my witth
yeah I should have saved out of this
[Music]
one no there's no full skip on this just
have to press e as fast as I
can so we'll watch this bloody scene
once
again no
problem your neighbors like my voice
really thank you
why your neighbors did your did your
neighbors knock at your door and were
like hey who's that anime girl you're
listening to like what the hell tell us
about it frozen
Marine at least she sounds like an anime
girl can you tell
us of of your holy knowledge and drag us
into the rabbit
hole spread the good word yeah all right
we saved so I guess this is again an
escape thing not a fighting
thing because Rosen Marine I got hit
like a truck almost got
isied this is already the eai okay again
no skipping so I'll no no fast
forwarding so I'll just do this
again but if it's one hit I feel like
I'll fail more than once
[Applause]
[Music]
only up down left stay diagonal oh okay
okay a is it doing the same thing as
those other horses Frozen marine and
then bnks and then stops for M and then
moves
again what in the lord's
name but how far do I have to run all
the way out of the dungeon again
o h be I'm going to I'm going to going
to get
dog
what okay here it goes
again that's anticlimactic ah that path
is open now W it come from
there should I I should
save they brought me to the safe point
for a reason perhaps
it's going to come right at me
right okay behind me after
all I love the
music no you didn't tell me about like
what the
[\h__\h] what the what the [\h__\h] man no
[\h__\h] hell [\h__\h] h no no no no no uh no
wait I was going to I was going to eat a
nut
but we're fine maybe we're fine we're
fine this part took you a few tries
really I first started I mean I still
got hurt a lot because that those those
blocks really come in so sudden
holy [\h__\h] right in front of you
literally what was that that thing
anyhow they're preparing for your
arrival it
seems what is this that's me oh nice a
statue of me as I deserve don't I
where's my usual confidence huh wanting
to be a princess and stuff
then I deserve a statue a pretty one at
that I've never seen I'm this eager what
in the lord's name so you saw this
before so are you actually like a
recruiter or something crazy
girl you'll slip away if I don't hurry
I'll lose you frozen Marine what's wrong
with you at least at least out with
it I'm sorry but her voice lines after a
while they get repetitive so it just
feels
funny h
ah
Acorn are we going that way should I
look at my statue
first trying to wear you in is he isn't
this what you most desire yeah I say
yeah she gets it let's get you out of
here rosemarine what the hell you freak
here he comes again
right yes oh [\h__\h] wait was there a safe
Point what excuse me I was run maybe I
need to run more straight this
[Music]
time cuz uh I wasn't bonking into
anything okay we we have to do the first
part as well sorry
ow ow what the hell they ow F oh my God
oh my God oh my oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] ow ow oh even his scream can stop
me ow I'm so dumb what the
[Music]
[\h__\h]
damn yum it it's
confusing when I get so close to him I'm
like oh oh [\h__\h] am I dying or am I
okay and how close can I really get to
the
spikes I'm so
dumb and then they really like they give
me no space
ow let me go
oh oh
[Music]
actually worth like taking a step back
if it helps instead of running
diagonally into it
really yeah I see the Shadows but it's
really so fast got to take a step
back doesn't seem to be able to catch
up was there a safe Point here that I
missed the lord's name Rosen Mar
out with
it one [\h__\h] Acorn yeah that's all you
give me after all that pain I must
suffer there is no safe Point holy [\h__\h]
okay at least I don't see one am I blind
no no
checkpoint damn that's messed up okay
but more straight this time more
straight left I don't know maybe
sometimes oh okay we're
fine who whoa what I can't see
myself okay he's done
for oh Frozen Marine what a coincidence
they both
[Music]
fall come quick you have to get
on I thought that was going to be like a
Sho
moment reaching out my hand but the hand
that come came back was the hag I will
lose you again my Bel if I don't hurry
you'll slip away what in the lord's name
you not
[Music]
mar ah a yeah so you definitely should
not romance
her escaped the Mari lud draff got an
achievement oh I also fell down
no
[Music]
huh oh what am I to do I feel so
confused I I'm too confused thanks for
the raid
hello I don't know what I'm doing or
where I'm going that wasn't Rose M
either oh what am I getting myself into
I'm so utterly
alone oh get away from me get your hands
off of me right
now let me guide you Elisa no no no
no hello hello welcome welcome
oh
another nice
interlude oh it's like a ending for that
character because maybe she's out of the
picture
now wild and
wanding
fistler well there's so
many musical things in this game
[Music]
wait is she the legitimate child of the
grandma of the
witch not an adopted
one this one the purple
one
for speee
[Music]
that [\h__\h]
goat I hate that
goat Evil
[Music]
Goat no is this me coming home at the
end after she's gone what is she gone
now that's what I want to know I mean I
would not want to talk to her and house
her in my house anymore after all that
that's for sure she better be
gone what did I get here that dream I
had about o Marine it was not a dream
girl
bro it was not a
dream do not let them fool
you have to find
her you [\h__\h] insane my ey
the r Crut so it was going for your eye
after
all I ought to find
her bro what the
[Music]
heck that wasn't her of course it was
her I don't believe that
[\h__\h] gas
light always gaslighting
Me Maybe she's in the chicken cuop
again I don't
know I think I heard steps
the [\h__\h] goat you little
[\h__\h] what am I doing talking to a goat I
don't know I'm wondering why the goat
isn't with her
owner let's see maybe I'm
right RPG instincts as always too
[Music]
strong Rosen Marine very interested in
this now good morning of these uh-huh as
if nothing happened I
see have you completely lost your wit s
mine last night in the woods oh so now
I'm not thinking I
dreamed what you thinking say I'm sorry
I'm sorry that wasn't you weren't
yourself right what do you mean oh we're
giving her the benefit of the doubt that
that that she was just like well maybe
she was okay maybe no I don't no no no I
don't don't trust her still out with it
don't give me that now how are we not
just shoving her off the cliff at this
point
though like that would be my reaction
after all
that I would run up to her if I see her
on the cliff I would shove her
down I mean come on don't don't taint me
as such an evil witch
guys have we just experienced the same
stuff hm
H I didn't even step foot in the woods
yeah yeah yeah yeah we went together
girl we went together you asked me
before you lost your mind if we could go
together and then I took you with
me I'm sick of this gaslighting
game Rosen Marine fans crying
well well
well if it isn't the consequences
consequences consequences of your
oi I wasn't though I couldn't Follow You
Into the Woods the trays blocked my path
yeah yeah am I supposed to believe this
you went on ahead no matter how much I
called for you and I I did wait for you
but you never came back from me yeah
yeah yeah no no no no no no no no no
no if that wasn't M then who the lord's
name are you all right
Elise
don't don't you don't don't talk to me
like that
don't you look a little
Frozen you can talk to me you don't have
to keep it all to yourself you know I
had a dream about you it it
[Music]
was don't get Clocky just because I
dream of you that doesn't mean that I
like you I saw you and your grandmother
and it felt like I was seeing
[Music]
your my path to finding you and keep
fate say it's
fate fate you say you still don't
believe it do you yeah I'm glad that my
character is also not buying it yet hard
not after last
night oh did you get it
huh test
well I've got it you mention
it that's wonderful all you need to do
is prepare to be eaten
oh remember these are gifts you're
giving him
Alisa uh okay they want to eat my hair
interesting taste but okay not going to
judge gifts for the host food drink and
good company well that sounds honestly
reasonable but
are you all right Elise oh don't give me
that [\h__\h] again you look tired Elisa is
everything all right I feel like I'm
losing my mind
Rosine Elisa come now let's head out to
work everything's falling into place
Elisa you'll
see
[Music]
I'm I don't know
I don't trust her still I'm not going to
let this I'm not let I'm not going to
let her sweet talk me
oopsie wow rude really
[Music]
rude
H well you're in luck because I'm ending
it for today
[Music]
I'm sorry if the game is giving me that
impression it seems like you played it I
guess and so you know but to me it's
giving me that
impression and I like to give my
impression all what did did I propably
save I did right
yeah um
[Music]
good well um um that was
fun as I said very very cute game very
Charming very
Austrian very
European very wild yeah crazy and as I
said in the beginning I never really
play these games but it's a very very
fun adventure into a genre that I
normally don't go
into very
demure yeah maybe we'll play it again I
I don't know but I think we got like
maybe maybe halfway through I mean you
could tell me I'm completely wrong now
but feels like it maybe I mean okay
maybe not exactly halfway F cuz we only
have one offering but the last offering
is just a lady so we're working on that
too yeah I'm not even a third through oh
my God what I thought it was 12 hours
I'm like 6 and 1/2 hours
in I mean I understand normally I take a
little bit longer but
what
what what not even a third are you
[Music]
sure thank you I'm glad that you enjoyed
my playthrough at least even though you
played it before I'm glad that you liked
it okay well my my um neck is like
really giving me a lot of headache again
now
so doesn't feel very good and my neck
hurts uh my throat hurts also so I'll
see you tomorrow I'll try to prepare for
something
interesting
yeah
[Music]
um okay
sorry I'll leave it at that in Germany
say I'll be in goodbye goodbye goodbye
[Music]
d