foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
hello
hi everyone
I'm downloading something right now is
everything like looking smooth
[Music]
the download is almost over though
is there anything to move looks fine
okay good and downloading
bgm for the Super Chat reading
I'm downloading the new uh remixes of
some whole life songs you know the bossa
nova versions and stuff
yeah
downloading it right now
liveware
no
ah yeah yeah they had
um Lo-Fi and chill until now but
yesterday they released
um Bossa Nova and guest versions
foreign
yeah I love Bossa Nova this is so cool I
didn't listen to them yet so during the
Super Chat reading we'll listen to it
for the first time I will listen to it
for the first time I don't know about
you
welcome
oh welcome welcome welcome
thank you for joining and renewing new
memberships thank you we got new remotes
I don't know if you've noticed but we've
got new ones
um
foreign
[Music]
thank you
a new week has started a new month as
well it's August and it's Monday
I hate Mondays just kidding I don't
really I don't really have a problem
with Mondays but I like the idea of me
being Garfield
ah Ice movie everyone say hi just moving
everyone say hello
it's a good meme yeah because I do love
I I am an orange cat sometimes and I do
love me some lasagna
ah there they go saying hello to
Smoothie cute we got those cat emotes
now so everything is possible
um today I will play some Minecraft
because uh I got an elytra I have I own
I am uh wait let me change the window
size here a little bit
sorry we'll fix it uh
I am one of the lucky people or the only
lucky people
with an elytra
[Music]
and uh today
we want to use that on screen on stream
to go on an adventure because I I
couldn't help myself back
and I did a little bit of an adventure
uh the other day on my own
but okay yeah I just couldn't hold
myself back and you know what happened
there I mean if you follow my Twitter
uh then you know what happened and I
think I also
were explained it in the Stream the
other day
uh anyway
uh
reach down a little bit too loud okay
okay there we go is it better
yeah I'm into the rescue yeah
so so so cute
[Music]
also I want to turn my things back on
my shaders
uh video
[Music]
nice
nice they only didn't really work at the
end but besides that they're always fine
so I think we'll be fine using them
[Music]
mending what
oh oh yeah so let me show you when I was
I didn't show you that on Twitter but uh
when I went on a little tiny Adventure
on my own uh
I got some stuff so let me show you what
I got
another heart of the sea
and I I got I got this respiration for
everything that which was useful for
going on the water I got this luck of
the sea fishing rod I also got a luck of
the sea one fishing rod when I left it
in the chest because I got the luck of
the C2 fishing rod
um
uh I got some TNT some gold a lot of
iron I had some treasure maps I got some
emeralds these are these are all new
yeah that's that's about it though
but yeah I'm excited about the emeralds
and we finally got some new coal let me
use that right away and the fishing rod
the fishing rod I don't know if I'll
ever use it though
I'm not a big fan of fishing
lure mending can we combine all of those
please
uh and uh yeah I don't have Unbreaking
yet because
I don't have that
I need it I know
uh how
I should I should just bring in oh yeah
I'll let me show you
let me show you I actually used my house
my new house for once
it feels a little bit laggy or like FPS
look
uh one choco box missing I'll get
another one eventually uh but there's
some stuff in here
uh I have more fireworks and stuff I'll
take that because I gotta make more
fireworks I also need more paper let's
be real
okay and I
yeah special stuff
uh uh-huh
and we got nothing we got some diamond
stuff
I want to use this apartment a bit more
so
that's what I'm trying to do we got this
oh wait I can I can actually make
another shelter
Okay so for our travels I guess we could
take Ashoka with us
yeah I also I died all of them I made
them pretty colors
I added some colors to that so let me
take this one with me maybe
uh-huh okay and
[Music]
um
let me put the heart of the sea in there
and the gold we don't need the gold
and
um maybe the iron for now
nice thumbnail thank you
thank you guys adorable adorable
chaos inventory yeah yeah I didn't do
anything after am I rescued me and I
came back to this place I logged out
immediately because of regrets
oh wow it's lacking
uh but my download is done
uh well if it will lack too much then
I'll turn the shaders off but for now
it's okay
so what was I saying oh yeah I didn't I
didn't clear my inventory
give me give me give me ah there's one
missing here
okay
yes
looks very laggy on our side
oh yeah I could turn down the chunks oh
yeah I made them quite a lot higher in
the end right
true let's make them a little bit less I
don't know how much should it be
um
[Music]
15 or so
12.
okay
now it should be oh yeah way better way
better
okay
[Music]
much better okay good
so let's see
what can we do here is that anything
there we go that's that's what I like to
see
okay
so and let's make some fireworks we need
a lot of fireworks I used up so many
fireworks already on my little Adventure
I think I used up one stack
oh well maybe a little bit less I'm not
sure
[Music]
um
maybe a paper fish paper Pepper Peppers
please
and then fireworks
I think we get more than enough
gunpowder from PPP to be honest
okay there we go
okay okay nice
let me put
um
I think that should be enough for now
TNT
[Music]
do you guys think I should keep those
treasure maps by the Light even though I
already used them is there any reason
why I would want to keep them
and that's a lot of followers more than
enough
[Music]
no
decoration oh
[Music]
um
I mean
nah I don't need it
you're not gonna burn
weird okay
yeah
all right
I will put that in here and we shouldn't
bring all of these right I should keep
some this is too much anyway I would say
let me put that here not here that and
that I got a lot of uh wood planks
because I found a bunch of
um
should bring an energy oh I guess so I
have a bunch yeah yeah yeah and what did
I say oh yeah I found a bunch of ships
shipwrecks
and uh
oh I said I had a bunch because I placed
one uh for free at the community chess
place so I can I can bring this one I
have gotten I just put like a bunch of
them in here how about that
and then I I went ah here I have a [\h__\h]
ton yeah that's right okay so I'll just
take one of those smites yes okay
[Music]
um
uh-huh keep on forgetting what I have
where
now hold up okay chest reception
okay
yo yo okay
okay so what do we want Adventure and
when do we want it now but what do I
need some food
[Music]
I want to take like one stack
of something maybe the bread or
[Music]
hungry free I still wanna I need to
pickaxe yeah oh yeah yeah yeah [\h__\h] I
gave mine Thomas and I mean I told her
it's okay to break it wait do I have
another one
[Music]
this one I just have to repair it
okay uh I ran to a repair correct
where did I put my iron
I put it I put it I put it into the new
house
[Music]
soda
that's that's what I need
EXP
what do you mean what do you mean
[Music]
you want me to bring an anvil for the
for the pickaxe
[Music]
I I have a diamond pickaxe as well what
do you mean I'm bringing both
for the elite trap how do I repair an
elytra
I mean it has Manning button like
wouldn't that need exp why why take the
um anvil
[Music]
foreign
for our mission of killing the ender
dragon and her making potions yeah I
don't think I have anymore well we'll be
fine honestly last time I already had
quite the adventure
um we don't have to use the elytra all
the time we can use a boat in between
um
it was fine it didn't get close to
Breaking last time either up but I have
to repair it now I guess
I'll repair it now before we go
um
and I mean worst case we can also just
kill some mobs
wherever we are oh yeah or it gets
picked up by Amy again
[Laughter]
[Music]
so
um
let me put that in here I I so oh my God
so off screens let me show you I found I
don't know if I want to go there again
but I didn't touch it on purpose but for
the first time I found uh wait I took
photos
I found
[Music]
I found a geeky old geode amethyst
thingy
that's why I got the call set but I
didn't mind it yet because I was like I
gotta mine my first amethyst on stream
the other thing that I found but I don't
think we wanna do that today
um
[Music]
it's very close to that but I don't I
still don't really I want to have a
stream that is like about that
I found a big big big big Monument
ocean Monument
So eventually we'll have a stream about
that
but not today I mean we'll get close to
that if we want to go check out the
amethyst and at the amethyst stuff
um I mean those are everywhere I guess
but
[Music]
um
no it's not near good ass stuff so I
think it's something that she hasn't
seen yet
uh but anyway
um
I found this this is where I died but
this is when I'mma picked me up wait I
didn't die I didn't die never mind but
but this is where I'm gonna pick me up
anyway there was a like an ice ice
um
ice area and I was wondering the reason
why I went there when I saw it was
because I
um I thought maybe it has blue eyes
because I'm up until now only found
packed eyes and I found I thought maybe
maybe that's the right by All Me for
packed ice so I tried getting it but
then I kept getting attacked where does
packed ice blue eyes show up again
[Music]
there were polar bears so I don't know
maybe that's the red area it's located
underwater
is it in the Deep
is it in a deep frozen ocean
[Music]
because look like would that be
something on the right side
there was a [\h__\h] ton of that but I tried
to mine it but I didn't I wasn't able to
mine anything
it just disappeared
but that would be it would that be blue
where I get blue eyes then I might want
to go there to get amethyst and blue
eyes
silk touch I guess I wasn't using Soul
touch
okay
so shall we go there where I went off
screen in that direction
it's actually not that far away imma
reach me by foot in 30 minutes
but I'm Gonna Fly hey
okay
you're so nine pack makes one blue eyes
yeah but that's the lace when I have
blue eyes why not use blue eyes yo
[Music]
okay
rabbits whip up with my ship
Ram the iceberg with a takamori ship
yeah I have some touch I just repaired
it here there it is uh well okay so
you know what would be nice to have the
shulker if they would make it so that I
could like do this and then it would
find its way into the shulker
instead of having to place it
so let me put in some stuff
um
I put in some extra food I guess right
now and some iron
and um
[Music]
that would be great great right that
would be convenient
a hopper for your inventory I guess I
guess kind of
[Music]
what's funny about the Super Chat blue
eyes blue eyes real nice
[Music]
I don't know what it's trying to tell me
it's not funny
[Applause]
[Music]
what what I don't know
what uh anyway you guys are confusing me
let's say it's mine is my stuff
is my food finished where is it
okay we'll take that
and we'll add some more food here no we
don't eat it we don't need it
that is enough I think well tank we
don't need the water pumpkins but I'll
take one I'll I don't only need I only
really need one Arrow because I have
Infinity but okay uh
another Shield
or repairing The Shield wait do I need
do I need iron for shield
laughs
it's vegan yes it's vegan of course it
is
okay one iron okay
[Music]
can I make one out of my little thingies
yeah
okay
and
well then Shield
new Shield
I wish they were more of a varieties of
shields like there's so many like
different materials you can make weapons
with but you can make only one type of
Shield like that's a bit
a bit lame
um yeah personal opinion
your opinion May differ from mine
should I keep these things like I don't
think we need it because well I'll find
a lot of wood anyway yes keep it there
have a bigger inventory correct opinion
thank you I already forgot what I said
you can put a banner on it yeah but it's
not about that it's about this thing
being weak as hell because it's made out
of wood mostly
I want more different kinds of things
anyway anyway I'll put
um this in here
and I guess I don't need that now I'll
use my respiration hat I think
it needs Unbreaking you mean my hot
wings I know wait what I don't have
Unbreaking oh wait you mean on my shield
huh well I would like to have fun
breaking on my wings anyway we got to go
to TTT to mend it first
um but I guess from from TTT on we'll
just leave
so let's let's try to be ready so 64
more we have more in the Ender Chest
so we have a for whatever reason we have
an orange wait why don't I need a
should I bring why we have one oh well
iron Shuffle good enough
uh
I mean PPP
I mean
it's confusing
a little bit confusing
what else do I need
to travel nothing
I'm just gonna go and look for a packed
Eye blue eyes and Amethyst I guess
that's my goal for today
oh
[Music]
okay chest plate
you mean if I don't fly I should change
all right I'll take it with me
all right sounds like a plan okay
I don't know yet what we'll do with the
amethyst but uh I'm sure we can use it
for some good looking builds uh yeah
it's bringing my bed a boat
I guess so
do I have torches nah
uh I mean all these things I can build
later on too but one second at boat and
the door your door for underwater stuff
MFS can be used for decorations and
Spike spy class what is a spy glass
a boat nice boat
nice boat
[Music]
telescope
ah like this but official does it zoom
in like that
I see look by the way that's that's the
in the chest that I placed there that is
I made it into a community entities
unfortunately no one besides me has an
interest right now so only only I can
really use it
double Zoom it zooms in more than that
but it's like is it is it something you
have to place to use or can you use it
while like walking
that's right she already got it she just
doesn't have the Electro
oh
[Music]
while walking
oh well done okay
I'm interested in at least filling that
once at least once
sing what the hell this is annoying
can I destroy it oh nice
she'll find it soon enough
this one and up next time she goes
she'll find it immediately and then
she'll be like [\h__\h] why did why did it
take me six hours seven hours last time
and now I find it like
in the first 10 minutes that that's
[Music]
why okay never mind
whoever passes there next we'll have to
deal with it
at least it didn't explode otherwise I
would have to repair [\h__\h] again
no thank you
[Music]
you have a talent for this
for shooting
yeah I feel I think uh I might I might
have shown good shooting skills in like
Minecraft
and so on
but
I think anything that's not Minecraft
I'm gonna be in trouble that was totally
not me
the second Festival that is something I
will never forget
I'll never forget that and I'll always I
always boast with it
yo you guys it's it's a new weekend this
week I'm going to Germany
I'm excited
and I said I said I said barely any
streams
but
I think you guys saw the schedule that I
uploaded
it turns out I'm only taking two days
off but but I mean that one day uh will
be on Twitch so I won't be on YouTube
I'll upload some smaller videos probably
like um um something something
to not anchor the algorithm and to show
you guys that I'm still alive
and we're probably gonna have like a
waiting room
uh like we had during digically
and Cube
I guess that would be relevant now and
never relevant ever again so if I were
ever to do it I would have to do it now
huh
I'm Cube what what sound am I gonna make
no sound at all
just be like quiet and then
I'm cute
is that is that what I should do
it's supposed to be an animal series
[Music]
should I go all the way up again and do
the thing again otherwise No One's Gonna
Come huh yo come down
yeah I have to do it again
I think I have to do it
no problem I'll go up
go go
I'm GameCube
okay
cool start cool story bro M Cube
[Music]
oh my God that's giving me a little
surprise
foreign
[Music]
or can I just leave already alone there
well what is that
[Music]
who's building something then what is it
that's probably from Amber right
Emma's fun house that sounds interesting
really close and dance what's so fun
about it
foreign
[Music]
ago
interesting interesting how to go down
oh God
I don't like this
okay
oh I hear them I hear them
I hear you
it's dripping it do be dripping oh wait
wait how do I wait wait wait guys
don't die yet how do I go down from here
again
are the water here
[Music]
down down down down we go and
pyeon
[Music]
I love that they named it too
okay here we are
hop EXP
[Music]
erience
you're trying they're trying to aim and
shoot I mean that's that's not happening
okay full
it's it do be full again
okay nice
[Music]
can we get one more I think it's uh it's
full though
it's full
I'll do it anyway
I'll do it for fun
yay hello creepers
your life is my life now I own your life
I own your destiny and everything
that's valuable to you
[Music]
aqua affinity
you get a lot of gunpowder from here
anyway so we don't really need a creeper
thumb we have PPP
it's enough
all right so I guess we'll go
let me see
um my coordinates
we shall go to
[Music]
here okay the coordinates that I wanna
aim for are minus
and 4 x
and then set
is
minus 100 no not minus plus
117. that's nice
[Music]
indeed it is it is nice it's it's a nice
air place I'm breaking I don't have I'm
breaking right now unfortunately I I
don't know like uh don't you like either
have to get lucky with these but I'm low
level now or you have a book well I
don't have evil
so
okay
minus
two thousand
well which direction do I go
this direction this direction I think
[Music]
right
this way this way this way
this way
okay
okay do I still know how to fly
I'm not sure
let's go I'm scared
let's eat
[Music]
I wanted to fly from here but I have a
minecart
I'll bring the minecart back
I love this elder sound yeah that
reminds me of the fact that we played
Zelda yesterday I are you guys watching
my Skyward Sword game play through
thingy
if not why not
it's been a lot of fun playing Skyward
Sword until now yesterday was a bit
short but
we're gonna we're gonna get more of that
this week on Wednesday I think
I'm loving it thank you see see all that
positive feedback from the people who
are watching it what do we learn from
that you got a lot to kill dogs
okay let's go
minus two thousand okay
oh
wow
am I going the right way
[Music]
oh
yes what the [\h__\h]
oh yes hello are we back
phobias was trying to be a little [\h__\h]
here we're flying over our hometown
right now
and we're leaving it
yeah
we're going further away from home
[Music]
it's so easy when you have an elytra
unbelievable
how is the health then then die double
[Music]
ooh send
so much sand I hate sand oh my homies
hate sand oh
[Music]
Heaven yeah I've been here before right
I'm gonna check it out
[Music]
is it is
passed through several times already
not sure though oh it could be any any
could be a new one but
um probably is
it's like demolished
oh okay
all right
yo minus two
let's just go also the other one should
be a bit tired
let's focus on One Direction first
because I can't I can't do two
directions at once it seems
yes anything interesting here nope
yes
oh minus minus one thousand now whoa
thousand more
ouch
[Music]
let me eat
huh
why won't it let me eat
because of my [\h__\h]
I don't understand let me eat
why can I not eat because I had full
I had full health a full full food full
hunger
[Music]
okay yes
back on track
where
oh
that looks interesting
dude that's so big it's such a big
Village let me check it out
a big Village looks like a city
[Music]
has anyone been here before
give me that that's really precious to
me papers it's really precious to me
damn looks like Game of Thrones man
is
yeah
has anyone been here before well I love
those dogs gonna
I'm dead I'll take it I want a lot of
those
I want them all
what's in here nothing
yeah I think no one touched this place
before
oh
it could make a map but I'm not not
quite the map person
[Music]
Badlands by Omi I don't know that what
is that
[Music]
like a dirty um dirty sense by all means
oh bread I will be I'll leave the bread
to you
red desert red desert
huh
not interesting
[Music]
why does it hurt Wings wait did I just
go through here
that's another Temple right
[Music]
by all means
have we never found that before
[Music]
did you know Red Bull comes from my
country
Australia wink
I want to sleep there if that's okay
when I have my own bed actually never
mind
foreign
knows that but it is true it will be
true
[Music]
it's one of the few things from my
country that are that famous that
they've made it like worldwide
although I personally don't like it that
much unlike other
um energy drinks more like monster if I
had to like I normally don't drink them
but if I had to drink
anything
uh like energy drink lines I would
probably go for Monster or I would go
for one that is like a budget
um cheap as
uh energy drink from a supermarket that
we have in Australia called Spa
I like the the budget energy drinks that
they have they actually and they taste
better to oh taste better to me than
um monster and Red Bull and all of them
I like them a lot
oh this is really dangerous guys today
like
how many people have died here until now
uh
[Music]
yeah I was trying to help come in
momentum
I have no more
I could he can he get out anywhere
can I help you is there any way for you
to get out there whatever I don't care
hello
no one trades of you said did I miss
anything I want more of those pretty
stones
I was in here before
this place is really big man
I really think wait so my question has
any does anyone know of anyone of whole
life English has ever found her Mesa by
Omi in our server before does anyone
know
or Calcutta I know I know no I don't
think so are they that rare why have we
not found it we must find it
[Music]
dude I just is it just really randomly
placed is there no way to don't think so
they aren't really rare
claimed his place is Phoenix will
it would be a nice base to work off but
it's so far away
[Music]
and to hunt for myself now well now of
an elite fight would be easy
kind of want to find that what what
makes it so special
do they have terracotta
[Music]
good place for map art ah because it's
just flat
really really flat
terracotta and gold Red Gold
they just have gold like randomly
everywhere
or like outside
[Music]
a Phoenix Hotel chain interesting
I want the gold
that sounds that sounds fascinating
[Music]
none did
it
you see those stones
my Phoenix eyes have
found something interesting it might be
nothing but I think it says that there
are Stones over there
[Music]
used to be a portal
or so no what was that what is that
sauce
wait someone was here before
[Music]
that
oh my God
[Music]
wait do you die yeah immediately lava I
forgot I haven't been in lava for a long
time
do you die immediately
it should be a chest oh let's check it
out oh let's check it out
not not immediately okay okay
chest oh crying obsidian
I want you to cry cry for me oh it's so
pretty
[Music]
should we mind these
oh my God sorry I thought it was lava it
I thought I was gonna die I overreacted
[Music]
where's the where's the treasure
where is it
[Music]
this is really buried huh
what is this structure
could it be under the red stones as well
[Music]
my iron Shuffle is almost dead
chest isn't guaranteed oh well maybe
this is the best thing about this place
[Music]
uh
a ruined yeah well I see it's very
ruined
very interesting like was this supposed
like aren't they normally like like that
it's on the ground that's like really
interesting to me are there signs huh
yeah it's like sideways
it fell over
foreign
[Music]
do I want that stuff do I want that
I guess I'll take it
yo there it is there it is
do we want maybe only the crying
obsidian what was that good for again
[Music]
takes a while
perfect timing for a new shovel yeah
although gold breaks so quickly
decoration lodestone never spawn look
respawn anchors oh okay
well I guess I'll take it
[Music]
my God
why is everything surprising me so much
right now
all right awesome
[Music]
I'll put that in there I'll put that in
that and
that
and that and uh
and this here
yeah the rest off-road I'll throw that
I'll throw these things
away
I don't need them thank you
oh
you missed the chest I did that I
already took it
[Music]
and up
or is the end you think there's two
I think there's another one
is that a thing
take the chest
eh
you might have missed the chest no you
don't just one right yeah
all right
um
[Music]
okay nice isn't that aren't you
impressed that I saw that from so far
away just randomly looking One Direction
and be like ah I see some Stones suss
ex eye
if
[Music]
on it
ah
okay
never mind
[\h__\h] I forgot that
[Music]
and we gotta go back because now I don't
have to shulker either
without the shulker
like I don't care about the energies but
the shoulder like we need space
ah make a new one yeah oh
wait what do you need for an ender chest
again
wait you can't make them lose weight
[Music]
does anyone out here have a crafting
table
crafting table ah no I can't do it now
then blaze rods and the Pearl nah not
happening uh we're going back now
are we going back
well if we're going oh if we're going
back then we can repair my hot wings
again I guess
what's up what a short trip no we're
going here again of course but we gotta
go back and get my another good that I
have so many Energies
uh home coordinates uh
uh where do I have home coordinates
[Music]
[Laughter]
no problem no problems
uh
fine is this my coordinates no that's
not it
that's also not it
what about that no that's not it what
about that that's
uh 300 volt minus 400.
ah I no that's not it
is it is it so is it so
I'm looking for my screenshots
[Music]
just kidding I don't need help
okay let's go to 300 minus 400 I guess
I'll I'm gonna trust you there if anyone
knows it's not there then let me know
now
I want to waste of fireworks as well oh
well we only use what 20 no 14 no way
only 14.
okay uh which way
uh when it goes It goes down we wanted
we wanted to go down
turn it down so then it's plus so
this direction
[Music]
let's run
we didn't go that far yet it's okay
oh
I like how the sand is so shiny
sometimes
[Music]
three wait was it was it 300 minus 200
or what was it
[Music]
the woods are burning it's so hot there
apparently 300 minus 400 okay thank you
[Music]
you
huh
that's how it seems familiar for some
reason I feel
some familiarity
they're streaming spikes
[Music]
this oh because they're starting a fire
today oh no
do I have to stop wait which way is this
way I have to stop recommending to
stream Sparks is it that dangerous
hold on Sky Zone
[Music]
hello I have arrived I need a
ouch I need another one of my endertons
unfortunately
oops I have lost one
but don't worry I've got more
like you'll find responsibly
there we go
let's take another stack of that okay uh
while we're here I guess
um
here I have some obsidian
oh wait that's
oh that's so sad I know that it only
gives you like the obsidian bag and
nothing else
that's so rude
uh let's leave some sand here I guess
and uh
ow
don't meow at me like that
okay
I guess I could
in order to make though and the chest
emptier
because I could take that out
um
yeah
could take that out
and that and that and that and oh
and I put that in here so
we already found something
so we'll put it in here nice now we're
standing at zero again let's go
I'm still preparing for the adventure
that's right take another and you want
me to take another one
in case I do the stupid thing again
do you mean take two
and then take two in the chests or
okay let's take another one
at the Gold block oh yeah
laughs
[Music]
guys
elitra Adventure
okay uh it was somehow this direction
oh wait do I want to mend it again yeah
babe we're already so long
on
[Music]
it really doesn't hold up much I need
that I'm breaking
I really need it
[Music]
all right
well I'm breaking I can get as a book
from a villager right if I'm lucky
from a merchand in Phoenix then but I
then I would have to make more
librarians
all right that's my next goal I'll make
some more Librarians so that I get
Unbreaking that's my next mission
leave it to me
I'm breaking yeah it's definitely worth
it um
yeah
so okay I'm ready for the creeper
Korea
make some books for now huh you can also
enchant
enchant books
wait if I put the books with what lapis
are three
then I can enchant the books and get
like random enchantments
I have to be level 30. oh
oh what what kind of far from that okay
you know what the the place that we're
going to is really not that far away so
for today we'll be fine but I'll work on
those enchantments
click on it
I do have a bunch of lapis naturally and
a [\h__\h] ton of books
we have books at home Brookshire's home
[\h__\h]
get the creeper
where are you
come to Mommy
did he despawn
what a cowboy
she got hit by my error once and he was
like
Phoenix [\h__\h] in town I better leave
the number one sniper in whole life is
in town
gotta leave
he's scared he peed his pencil
yo
who's that
so touch on your main pickaxe so you
won't destroy the energies of accident
oh
but sometimes I don't want to have silk
touch though right
and that was not like an enchantment
that I have that was on the pickaxe
already so yeah
I'll wait this time I'm not gonna bring
it with me
okay
[Music]
is it is it night time
it is
an egg
[Music]
hi this broken egg is too
it's like touch is now a bed
that might be true but I think there's
instances where you don't really want to
touch
okay we have to do the thing again
we have to do it
okay going up
myself
[Music]
oh
is it
yeah I don't have I don't think I even
have such touch as an enchantment
separately
[Music]
sharp pain
I I when I first when I was young and I
first watched a High School Musical I
didn't like her but now that I'm older I
appreciate I appreciate her as a
character
[Music]
who's with me
who has the same experience
Ashley Tisdale yeah
she was okay
no
we all got so going on
[Music]
looking good all right and again we go
that direction
now wait was it that direction huh
no it was not
I fold that way
okay
ready
[Music]
minus two thousand one hundred
I've never seen High School Musical what
do we watch it together
[Music]
I might have not seen the last one
perhaps yes please God no you know what
I actually agree that's not something
that I necessarily want to watch of you
guys feels like a waste of time
it could be fun but it also feels like a
waste of time
[Music]
Monty Python I've never watched that
what is that I've heard of it I've heard
the name before
um which way are we going this way
what British comedy oh that's perfect
for my dance
I'm so sorry to my British audience
so sorry it's all right
British comedy movie I want to watch it
I would like to watch it
foreign
I want to see what's up here
what the hell is that
[Music]
oh
would I recognize that Mesa by Omi
immediately if I were in it
[Music]
oh that's a ship that I already looted
this one
I looted that one
I would very discolored I want to say
[Music]
it ah [\h__\h] emphas let's go for it just
kidding that we're crying me to have on
breaking on it I think
okay we're getting closer maybe I should
take the ship now
foreign
[Music]
we're not going the right direction oh
wait this this way this way this way
minus 12 100.
[Music]
is my boat sinking no it's always like
that because of the shaders
oh yeah
what is that
is that sauce or is that just a normal
[Music]
Mountain
oh yeah I checked out that Village
before I think
perpetually wet boat I never use that
word but does that mean that it's like
always always wet
[Music]
remove the shade that I don't wanna
yes what that goes Zoom
Chad is excited to tell me something
about their language
you guys must feel very smart when I ask
you something and you know the answer to
it
no
no no
put on Armor oh I guess so
you know what I'm hoping for you know
when
um I panicly logged out and asked Amma
for help
um it was at the time where a polar bear
and uh and then Trident dude was
attacking me
and I I really wanted to log back in to
kill that dude and get my second first
try trident
but I couldn't when I looked back in he
was gone
who knows we'll find one more maybe
we'll find another one
[Music]
polar bear oh
is that
a temple
yo yo yo yo
yo
always gotta check out those because
they got some Treasures
what was it again what was the rule
again what was the room again
was I here before
I don't think so
it looks fancy looks cute
interesting where do we enter from
uh the center yeah there's a pressure
point somewhere don't dig at the center
oh yeah ah here we go
I'm scared I'm scared
uh should I
[Music]
know I know it's not my first time but
what
help huh I'm scared
hello
[Music]
oh my God okay um
wait so wait what I can go down right I
can't I can't go down to that level
[Music]
and then just don't dig the purple one
right
[Music]
now
foreign
[Music]
like this
oh
why it's so Dyke I should have brought
some torches oh well
um
let's make stairs
so that I can go back up again easily
the professional Minecraft player
takanasi Kiana
I'm an adventurer
I know I know how these kind of things
go
[Music]
I am extremely easy to startle today it
seems
there's a iron iron
is that the pressure plate
no more you no more no bamboozle here
not today
all right she'll look what's inside
uh-huh no interest aha
[Music]
you're free
bring me I
returned that uh trains loyalty for
loyalty but not loyalty free I think
y'all
[Music]
and horse armor
I'll take it I'll take the strings too
[Music]
I never seen diamond toy zombies okay
the rest is kind of [\h__\h] but the
Loyalty free is nice for certain people
and there is a dynamite below right
okay
is that Dino one I can't see
okay it is
[Music]
do I mind that with some punch
yes it works I'm scared to go down but I
can go down now right I can go down
I can go down right
[Music]
okay okay
foreign
[Music]
level above that
wow
nice I like doing stuff like this this
is my favorite part about Minecraft the
saddle I don't care about the saddle
yeah
I have Saddles at home
[Music]
that you really want me to get the
saddle huh okay
that was rare
uh where was it
oh
only one right ah no way there's one
more okay
going back up work out with stairs
foreign
[Music]
work those legs yeah
well future 3DW
okay sleep we did it we did one cool
thing that was just on the way this was
not even what I was looking for
specifically but in in some way I am
always looking for stuff like this this
is the best part about Minecraft
okay uh let's get the shulker
[Music]
let's put in these things
Yo the book
what the [\h__\h] is it
oh my God what the [\h__\h]
the [\h__\h] do you want from me
oh my God they gave me some Curry okay
chill it's all good it's all good it's
all good I thought it was being cursed
or something
y'all
oh my God
I'm too old for this [\h__\h]
don't worry I'm not gonna do it again
don't worry don't worry don't worry I'm
not gonna do it again here so touch
[Music]
yes
uh-huh
[Music]
thank you that's mending my oh I don't
even have it on God damn it then it
doesn't Bend anything also a trash can
please
[Music]
ah
this Temple is now mine and therefore I
make it into a trash can
[Music]
how do you like that Temple desert
temple how do you like that
You Belong To Me
it's not littering this is literally a
trash can now
ah the casters oh yeah right that's
something that people use for Minecraft
trash cans right what where's my book
my boat oh it's somewhere
somewhere close by from which side I
came from that side hello
[Music]
oh I got it again damn that was good
I only saw a tiny bit of them sniper
attack
[Music]
boom Hedgehog
all right where are we going uh mine is
2100 and
park I
171 okay
let's go to minus two
thousands and this way
two thousand
[Music]
oh okay I'm almost there ah sorry
for disturbing you in your ocean okay
now we're there now we need to go to 200
something right
oh 200.
oh there we go
that should do the trick
y cute
[Music]
oh
don't worry if you need to sleep then
you need to sleep good night
dolphins dolphins
uh are we here yet
a bit more
there was like a little island there I
remember and actually I saw so much of
these amethyst guilds on the ground so
we should be getting stacks of it uh I
already looted that one when I was here
last time I'm pretty sure about it
yeah
are we here
wait now we're not at 2 000 anymore wait
wait wait wait this way
[Music]
uh wait we're not we're not quite there
somewhere
this one goes up this one goes down okay
that's correct
somewhere oh
I think yeah that's it that's it I
already looked into these things and I
think over there was the monument the
ocean Monument
and over there was the The Ice Area
yeah oh and that's enough
mine
oh
I didn't know I left it there
so and here
[Music]
hello where was it again
wait I think I'm gonna turn out the
shaders for this because without the
shaders
it's a bit better to see
in the C
better to seem the thing funny
[Music]
okay
yeah
let me turn it off
[Music]
please bed good idea good idea
back to game okay
[Music]
and eat some stuff
probably nothing okay I think I saw it
somewhere
we're here oh yeah
oh yeah
they're from me oh yeah that's where I
stopped and was like wait that's my
first that's gonna be my first time I
ever amethyst I want you guys to be part
of it
okay
let's go
is it in there
it's there look at it yeah
should I mine it with uh that's fun did
I not do it huh
should I wear it with a silk punch
or does it not matter
[Music]
go inside
I play I didn't sleep on it oh
I thought I did
uh where is it
a couple of moms
[Music]
wait a second wait wait where am I
where's my door
[Music]
wait can I breathe inside yummy I'm so
scared
I'm scared
other side
oh yeah
[Music]
do not break the purple blocks that the
crystals were on why
boy makes a sound
ah
sucks me in oh I can breathe in here
they can't be mine you suck touch
[Music]
what's good it's Hollow come on
foreign
[Music]
that's nice
it makes pretty sounds
Apollo Live
when you're when you watch so much whole
life that your life feels Hollow what is
that that looks different why does it
look different
[Music]
it's so dark
is that even possible
now when you want too much whole life
you can only be happy don't eh don't
take the different one okay is that like
one where this thing grows
Puma Thurman
[Music]
okay
it's very hard to see
and I make it brighter
and that feels like it did pretty much
know the friends
uh is this is this one of the different
ones
ceiling turnouts that use torches
all right let me go back
[Music]
uh oh yeah there's a sea lantern oh yeah
and I already looted that looted
[Music]
did that work
huh
yes okay
useful wow thank you dolphin I don't
need your speed right now thank you slow
down slow down you don't want to go back
you don't want to go in here with me
trust me
okay let's place it
uh here whoa
whoa
there's a chest
it is that normal noise that because
it's like merging with something else
who saw oh my God
because it's merged oh
[Music]
nice it's so much easier to see now good
idea with the sea lantern thank you
gotta be careful here so this that the
sand doesn't fall on me
and when I open it
ah
I thought
oh
okay nothing really super special but
I'll take it
cute
[Music]
wow
how much do I want there's so much
he's so pretty
it's so pretty
but first i'm amethyst
foreign
oh I could make torches huh
oh man it might be actually a little bit
useful
I thought
I don't have wood with me right now but
we can probably mind something outside I
think there was something made out of
wood there
hello
I need you thank you
um
uh
can you make them Wait no that's not
gonna work oh whatever for now whatever
[Music]
I need to wait for bread I don't need it
I have enough food
it ain't necessary
[Music]
fancy
foreign
[Music]
yeah today for some reason yes
thank you so much
I don't want to break the wrong ones
um this one is okay this one is okay
this one is okay
are these okay
[Music]
this is okay this is okay this is okay
this one's not okay this one is okay
this one is okay this one is okay this
one is okay this one two this one too
and we got more wood
[Music]
chilled until I'm I'm trying
I'm trying Hey today I am cleaned up my
apartment again and I feel so much more
refreshed it's actually
really refreshing
to clean your apartment it really does
something for your soul too doesn't it
yeah
I coined it because a friend came over
before the Stream
[Music]
so
I did some pretty uh big uh necessary
cleaning should have done it long ago
yeah also I received all of the
furniture that I needed for my oh my I
mean not not everything I still want to
add some things but I received my table
for my balcony
and my my two chairs for my balcony now
I I am not gonna build that on my own
I'm gonna wait until my mom visits me
again she's planning to visit me
um next week perhaps
[Music]
so when she does that
I'm thinking
we even do nothing
or we maybe if I get permission we do
the Minecraft collab maybe but I don't
know if it's better to have her here
while we do it and she'll just be in
another room and uses my laptop
or she should do it from her home
I'm not sure
[Music]
we can totally do it from her home as
well she has a decent internet
connection and an okay-ish PC
it at least is able to handle Minecraft
oh
[Music]
stream which is today I wanted to show
you guys the screenshots that she sent
me
oh wait where did she send it down to me
I think on WhatsApp
oh wait a second
my mom is quite the Minecraft player
uh let's see I think was it was it there
[Music]
no it was her email
which one did she send it to I have a
million million mail accounts
was it that one oh it was this one
one second I'll I'll try to uh let me
let me log into that email account
on my PC
a male a million
[Music]
and
my name is
[Music]
foreign
useless but pretty amethyst charts
useful only gronyx blocks
so how do I get those
[Music]
um
okay so those broken blocks
I wanna get a little silk touch
[Music]
doesn't weigh the crystals is
you can't you can't I mean how how can I
get them the Xbox is on but I can get
the flower on top of it whoopso touch
foreign
[Music]
oh
ah for the spine glass I need the the
crystal ones
[Music]
uh-huh
okay I'm downloading the screenshots
yeah let me show you what my mom makes
on Minecraft is quite quite good
yes okay
[Music]
myself
and yourself and okay
okay are you ready for this
base mama
where do I start
oh look at this
but it starts out like this
she built us all along she plays her
alone right so keep that in mind
stands out like that that's like a
general overview
wow
that's uh her trying to
uh rebuild that was her trying to
rebuild something
and then that's that's her like big
I think
trading no way that's not something else
I don't know she has a lot of things she
uses different textures for the for some
of the blocks though
you go in there and then you're here she
built this all alone
foreign
[Music]
just for you to make a screenshot she
was flying around but
that looks pretty good
yeah on the left side she has like
inside she has um I think kettle
uh but like coming up nice and like it
looks really pretty
um and that big thing is her house but
then she got bored and she made another
house that's what she said
uh I think that that is uh
oh yeah that was her dog that's so cute
that's such a cute idea I want to do
that too like she that's her ship like
dog for ships
you can go in on one side and you can go
out on one side or so
you see how that's in the water and she
decorated it with uh like Corelle Coral
Coral
stealth that wasn't there from the
beginning she put it there to make it
look nice
look to make it look aesthetic
that's her summer house another house
that she made
because she was bored
yeah that looks good I like the looks of
it looks like a nice vacation house
[Music]
and she also has
a trading house she didn't send me
screenshots from inside you should have
showed me that
ah but if you look actually if you look
through that window
you kind of see it she has like these
these like dormitory rooms for each uh
Trader in there
they all have a little tiny tiny tiny
tiny room
yeah but still that's another house
yeah the usual rooms
foreign
so she really knows what she's doing
when it comes to Minecraft she also has
uh never ride armor and all that So
eventually I want her to show me how to
get never right that's our plan for a
long time I'm trying to get permission
right now
[Music]
but it should be fine
you missed the tour you just came now a
second ago I was showing it maybe watch
the archive maybe remember the the time
so this thing
I want to get a silk touch
oh
small amethyst bugs
this this is it
yeah okay
does she speak English as well ah she
does she her English is pretty good I
would say
hmm
I haven't heard you're speaking in a
long time though so I don't I don't know
how good a reaction is but when we do
the collaboration we won't do voice chat
anyway because I feel like that's too
dangerous
she'll just be in the normal chat
yeah
and she she's she's really excited about
it she's been bugging me a lot about it
she's like when are we gonna do it when
are we gonna do it
if we're gonna do it you have to let me
on your server first so that I can
prepare and get like my uh like all
kinds of stuff from Phoenix then she
wants me great extend to get prepared
and I was like well I can just give you
myself no no I'm gonna prepare it
she's really excited about it
[Music]
I'll take everything that's here but I
guess since it's not useful for many
things we don't really need much of it
how fast do they grow when I mine them
once
[Music]
mama doing the grand yeah
we're equally excited as her for sure
she always watches my streams too
and uh she always of course I stream a
lot every day so she the Minecraft
stream she seems to check out live
um as much as she can
and to be honest dreams she like goes
through the stream tags
that are posted in the YouTube comments
usually
she goes through the living that's so
funny she looks for the interesting
stuff
because my streams are too long
[Music]
yeah
you guys are familiar with those huh you
don't just watch the whole stream you're
gonna use the tanks come on come on
week
[Applause]
[Music]
okay that's we already have a lot should
I take more
I don't know if I want to take like all
of it
also my stream hard Challenger pickaxes
not doing that well
[Music]
got the big one
they're different in size wait do they
what is the difference
where is the difference
what what does it change
wait do they still grow
you just want the large one is this a
large one
no I think it was not a large one
[Music]
all right it's not a big one
don't break them
that one
[Music]
place it in the Xbox ah
where's the small ones
ah
[Music]
foreign
okay now I only have a big one
you don't really need to grow them now
yeah I don't really care that much about
them anyway but
let me get some more of the normal ones
is this a big one no
it doesn't look very big
[Music]
the ones in this series should be good
oh I need some money some Stones then
wait
foreign
[Music]
should be enough I'll try to
go up here
nope
are we close enough I think we are
okay we'll still touched is this one is
this one these look big too
[Music]
wow I almost used my sword
this one looks big
Not Silk
really
[Music]
not silk touch okay
and get off again
[Applause]
is that a fish oh
the fortune
ah I don't have a fortune oh well
this is a big one
so sometimes they drop something huh
okay that one over there looks good
I'm not close enough
girl
that oh that one is a big one
[Music]
um
let me mind you
[Music]
okay
I don't oh it dropped it whoa
whoa and I'm sorry it's so pretty
[Music]
oh I got more yo yo
wait so I have to plant these again and
then mine them again
a dog
yo I got so many how many do I need for
one one thingy
[Music]
what
what's up boy dropped it
[Applause]
that one was not big enough
you know when you're gonna when are you
gonna grow I'm gonna look at you until
you grow two for a telescope
that's not much
bro come on grow bigger you can do it
grow
I'm looking at you everyone's looking at
you everyone's counting at you count
countening counting at you counting on
you counting on you
think of glass for tinted glass you need
you need a tail
um this one should be fine too
yeah
this one this one looks big too
the grill definitely that one was
smaller before but maybe it's not the
maximum size just yet
let me get that one
I dropped nothing maybe it was not big
enough
that's a large one that's one that one
[Music]
see one there
but that one looks rather small
[Music]
no that's too small
are you vegan
are you big enough
we can compare
[Music]
are you big
and large ones take up the full block
and this one this one no that doesn't
take up the full block I guess wait I
don't know which one is lines
I want to buy this one
what about this one
every check
oh why does it say
ah large amethyst buds
oh what about this one large okay large
is the one right or extra large
larger large isn't the full size oh
fudge cluster still a bud
oh well then then there's no right sizes
now
but no cost against
a bud
closer cluster closer cluster oh
so big
[Music]
yes
so once you once you have one of these
geodes and you mind the amethyst blocks
you still want to go back here maybe
sometimes
and if you really want those
those clusters huh
no bud
but that one looks crazy
but
all right all right all right I'll take
a few more of these I just can't get
enough of it
I Can't Get Enough
of these beautiful Stones I like purple
I like purple it's one of my two
favorite colors
orange and purple
what's your favorite color everyone
[Music]
purple red
green black black and purple
now we can have a discussion whether or
not black is a color
I went to uh
I saw you growing I went to high school
for a while
and uh we had discussions like that
[Music]
then should I get some of the concerts
too can I do anything with coffee
call site probably not counted
oh we can't find him you're probably
laughing about me
call site
and trans decoration building okay not a
whole dough
okay
well well well
there's so much here
I don't know where to go
so many oh bud
yeah like I actually do kind of like the
look of girls like outside
let me get up here
oh
I actually like them
I should not stand under it because sand
might fall on me
[Music]
kind of yeah it does look like marble
wait is there any other stone that looks
like marble maybe
um
what was the one uh
uh uh uh the one that you get like in
the air in the never quite yeah but this
one seems kind of Cheaper like once you
have a note like this
it seems
cheaper wait can you also make like half
blocks and [\h__\h] with calcite as well
or like stairs is that a thing you can
do too probably not
sad block noises I'll be sad nope I
thought so damn
that's the catch
there you go you have a catch
I saw you coming
you can't get me okay
how many do I have 60 all right let's
let's get four more and then we have one
full stack or let's get the whole wall
here
yeah
hey pretty stars Minecraft
yeah give me more
[Music]
the good stuff
are you big enough
but
my pickaxe look at my pancakes
foreign
[Music]
cluster
fun
okay I'm gonna I'm gonna leave I think
this is enough
my name is
[Music]
that was nice oh wait that looks like a
classic
I got the costume
fresh air
burn [\h__\h]
start a fire today
okay uh
all right let's see let's place
the end chest let's take out the
chocolate box
all right we gotta sit down of amethyst
blocks but I am not 100 happy yet
because I want
and
maybe some although I don't I don't
really care that much about the blue
eyes but since we're here I want to get
it anyway oh
fire starter
but I'm scared about my pickaxe right
now there's a little barely tank uh I
need to kill some enemies I guess
hello Enderman
enemies enemies
there are no enemies
that is a problem
kill the Enderman do you think it will
give a lot of EXP
wait a second
um
[Music]
will it take the gravel wait how do I do
this again
should we just kill it normally
do you think I can do it where did he go
on Terry
[Music]
um
I thought so I thought it would take the
gravel
okay I'll kill you
[Music]
happy
heal heal
[Music]
where's the EXP
erience no EXP
[Music]
where did I get something and I just
didn't notice
because it was so Ripple
exb local
[Music]
killing bunnies
a little bit right
[Music]
um
round pickle
uh
well we'll we'll go to let's just go to
the blue eyes area first
and uh there might be some round there I
finally remembered what they're called I
kept on calling him trident
foreign
[Music]
that's right that's true that's true I
guess and we got some we got some some
iron if we want to amend it but we would
need an anvil first oh well let's see
how much we get with that and I can
always come back it's not that far away
anyway so yeah
and okay oh
[Music]
um
okay we're going to our second
destination guys by the way did I show
you though that the monument is here
foreign
I have found something interesting it
was somewhere here ah is that it
no that's not it
[Music]
water temple
what
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
well I do have the coordinates for it
just in case
we're not going to clear it now oh yeah
I can't find it that's weird
it disappeared it despawned
no problem we don't need it now we don't
need a temple now thank you for the
membership
I know I still have stuff over there
don't worry
I am aware
well done
I hate that I hate that thank you
dolphin I think you fixed my bug
[Music]
s
um hi and do it with the silk touch
nice okay
and bid
okay we're leaving and I think it was
super close
uh but I'm gonna grab the coordinates
uh
percent
uh well well uh app data
percent Minecraft
screenshots
and you know what we're using them for
the blue eyes when I get it I want to
use it for the Never
gonna give you well
not funny
[Music]
okay
oh cool coordinates
two fat man's 2500 minus 187.
okay minus
I guess we can take a boat probably but
I'll walk a little bit mine is wait did
that take a boat I didn't I did not
I gotta take my boat
[Music]
blue eyes white dragon
why am I cute am I pronouncing it so
badly
no way
am I saying it that badly
foreign
are you just trying to be funny
[Music]
pickle pickle pickle pickle it's just a
meme okay
okay
then then I'm not mad
oh and bunnies
aren't your ass is burning
should I help them I think they need
help they suck
foreign
[Music]
just don't die
I
attack
savior of pickles
[Music]
so sweet
no I'm not gonna kill them they don't
have much meat on them anyway
[Music]
the different by Omi
by all means take me to the biome
never mind
um that was nothing
round round the phone
[Music]
is there anything interesting here
no
okay so the question is do we have blue
eyes here
it should be here right in these kind of
things oh wait I think
oh
that's the last
I see blue eyes
the last time I came here a polar bear
attacked me so I hope that doesn't
happen again that's blue eyes too right
blue eyes
usually at the bottom but here we have
an example of it being outside in the oh
in the wilder wilderness this is the
tower that Alma built to have a lookout
for me
polar bear wait what
throw bear
oh ah should it be polar bear
is this blue eyes
[Music]
no it's packing
this one this one
there we go
pull out pull out there
sounds better
[Music]
why does mine so slowly I want a diamond
silk touch pickaxe
[Music]
okay
well uh um
a door would be good yeah
you know what let me set my spawn
because if I die here I'm gonna kill
myself which is funny because
if I die here then I'm already dead
let me set my spawn
because I already destroyed my spawn so
it would be a problem
die
and we have to sleep anyway
okay people die when they are killed
[Music]
what is that may never die
mongolis
everyone
Vala [\h__\h] more goodies
what the [\h__\h] is this thing oh
is that everyone is so excited about for
no [\h__\h] reason is this is this what I
think it is
packed ice the hell
[Music]
I see some blue eyes it's really not
much but okay
let me in thank you
Axolotl why do the Japanese girls call
it oopalupa
is it because they're called in Japanese
I could have brought the sea Lancer in
Folk
[Music]
Ah that's that's it in Japanese
that's the first time I've seen one
[Music]
I think this is blue eyes
yeah
[Music]
or is that not blue eyes
blue eyes blue eyes Flies why am I why
am I not mining it correctly
[Music]
thank you
now I got it
okay
did it go out oh
well
um it's gonna take a while I won a lot
of it I want a lot of it please eat my
horsey
oh guys go into my door
oh
Axolotl is a different yeah if I were
going to write that in Japanese it would
be Hannah
Maybe
[Music]
my cats are actually in a bucket
can I bring it with me if I find another
one
uh cactus
yeah see that's why I brought the bucket
I knew it from the beginning this is
what I brought it for
are you blue eyes no it's way too much
practice this is so rare oh there you go
blue eyes
[Music]
oh my God what is going on what I want I
am where am I where am I
where am I
where am I where am I
and it was scary what the hell was that
I was suddenly in a in a cave but I
could even breathe for a moment though
what was that did it like freeze behind
me is that what happened
wow that's so scary
okay I can't find any blue eyes
I was in I don't know what happened
I only saw Panic me too
I just take my door
I'm gonna go elsewhere I'm gonna mine
the blue eyes that was outside
because that's easier to see
the blue eyes
so much enough for everyone
[Music]
I kind of wanna if my wings allow it I
kind of want to go
I mean I could walk back home honestly
what am I hearing I wanna go find that
mess up by all mean with my wings
you feeling me
[Music]
I want it now that you guys told me
about it I really want it
[Music]
yeah with my hot wings that might take a
while but you never know it's random
right it's not like it's always like
next to a certain biomi
um
[Music]
it's random so who knows when we're you
know what I'm quite lucky in Minecraft
we have seen that until now it has been
proven
what the [\h__\h] is [\h__\h] sound did you
guys hear that
poopy
ah blue eyes okay
[Music]
do you hear that
scary ambient sounds
[Music]
that is even spoopier
nope
just placed my door
nah
[Music]
don't go down
what
um
foreign
at home
I can't totally make that into blue eyes
also because it's like I guess easier to
mine but
um it is to have a little bit of blue
eyes inside I saw it around careful
ah come at me drowned I'm waiting for
you give me a trident where is it where
is he
I want to fight a trident
I challenge you
yeah it's hard to mine it it's annoying
[Music]
nine packed one blue
yeah I've heard of the special formula
[Music]
check out the door mine from there
[Applause]
just gonna make sure it comes to me at
the moment they're going up okay
also is that blue eyes that's blue eyes
right blue eyes
foreign
[Music]
ate it for three days
Curry Burger steak yo
[Music]
what's for Tuesday it's Tuesday
it's Tuesday there
already Tuesday then what did you eat
what did you eat until now
[Music]
but someone boarded my [\h__\h]
okay
the lasagna before the Stream
you see I actually I don't know if I'm
doing it for sure that soon but I put I
put a cooking stream let's make lasagna
into my schedule so that do be coming
soon
I just gotta make sure everything is
safe
but I really want to make lasagna on my
own because I've been only making like
um I've been only eating
uh Frozen already done lasagna
I want to learn how to make it myself
and I don't think it's that difficult
pickaxe is about to break
[Music]
okay how much do we have we already got
two stacks
can we get free stats
foreign
[Music]
that would be good
wait I haven't well I can do it right
now really yeah
wait one second okay let's let's take
off
let's take it out
before before myself a silver touch silk
touch pickaxe
breaks well we need this and this
nice
[Music]
dog okay
that's good enough for now
Oh My Stream hot Challenger
ah in my other hand oh
need help
[Music]
okay
now we can probably get some more blocks
but let me sleep first I'm scared of the
dark
uh where's my bed ah over there I see it
thing I like ice skating
are there any
any drones
no boring boring
I want some action some Adventure
[Music]
and not merged yet no
it's probably uh good because
um
I've heard that it would be smart for us
to kind of loot our own devil
as much as we can first
and to get as many leeches as possible
[Music]
and and nothing ever
so I do also want to get
another elytra before I lose this elytra
I want to use my elytra to easily get
another internally trap don't worry I'm
gonna be careful
don't worry
I'm going to be careful but I think I
should get it while I still already have
it in later because if I lose my later
then it's going to be difficult to get
another release one foreign
in my mind
I believe in you guys thank you I know
people are like don't usually join the
end it's never no in the end it's gonna
be you're gonna lose it it's dangerous
no no no no only dangerous for stupid
people
sorry I don't want to insult anyone but
you saw my skills the way I was floating
around from one Tower to another Tower
Kiana is in control at all times
[Music]
you get me
how much do we have oh
[Music]
we got free Stacks Free Fall stacks
now we got free full stacks
huh let me just mind the rest of this
that's right
[Music]
okay
I don't
random topic have you guys noticed how I
yeah
yeah this is really random have you guys
noticed how I pronounced my name Kiara
and everyone else in her life English
pronounces my name Kiara
like really in an English way
[Music]
I just kind of pronounce it Japanese
what's the difference at the r
Kiara and Kiara if you don't hear the
difference
[Music]
my name is takanasi Kiara
hard R versus like a soft iron like a
Japanese pronunciation
[Music]
yeah I mean it doesn't bother me but I
just thought it was uh funny
I know it's not funny but
I mean the whole name takanasi Kiana is
like Japanese anyway so
I don't know I feel like to me when I
when I you know uh kind of choose my
name
I
I decided that the pronunciation would
be Kiana
but yeah from an English speaker of
course they're gonna pronounce it
differently
but from the official Source aka me
let me just let you know it's Kia Kiara
good
if you've ever wondered about that
[Music]
probably I haven't
I still don't really let me think about
Cali's
it really confuses me because of her
Japanese pronunciation can't Collide
Calliope or Calliope why you feel
caliope
Calliope it's the one that sounds more
like cantaloupe right Calliope Kelly
Kelly
open
Holly like in Japanese they pronounce
her name very different than from
English
that's all I know
okay is it number one Calliope or number
two County
number one can I open till karaoke
number one Calliope okay I will never
get it right
hahaha
I'll never get that right
I'll also always have issues pronouncing
good as last names
[Music]
what a weird name
cute though cute name
[Music]
I should say calling to avoid the issue
same same same same but also like
I think I think she
I think she isn't really bothered by it
anyway I'm not even about the different
pronunciation I mean there's not much of
a difference between Kiara and
Kiara
also I noticed though that some Japanese
girls like nineteen they don't call me
Kiana they call me Kiana do you hear
that difference
they pronounced and they emphasized the
the key
yeah
some of them call me Kiana
[Music]
this is so annoying
Kiana with the keys
is this blue eyes though no it's bad
guys I think on the ground there's still
some blue let me try to find some more
that's reachable that one is reachable
from outside
[Music]
I hear no other friends
there's a big difference but it's okay I
don't really mind about that either
I don't mind at all
[Music]
there's a lot here too is there there's
no Treasures in this kind of place right
why why is there no ice temple we need
to win some Elsa running around here
singing Let It Go Let It Go
can't hold it back anymore
she pronounces it like a girl
um
that's true yeah I guess so g-o-w that's
how she pronounces it sure that makes it
easier for me to actually now that you
say that
saw that you write it down for me like
that oh
guys
I'm a tiger
Steve
so [\h__\h] cringy
I used to write XD so much when I was
younger but now it's like no way in hell
I'm gonna write XP only in the really
rarest rarest cases but it's interesting
how like back back when I was younger
also everyone in my age
fact that using really modes from from
like Messengers and all that was lame
and they they don't look cool they don't
look edgy enough
or whatever therefore every
well that's okay
[Laughter]
that's okay we still have enough space
tonight
[Music]
that's only okay if I'm okay with
leaving my end of chest here because my
elytra is in there
Oops I did it again
also I can't mine anymore anyway we're
about to silk touch figures
you know what if I ever want blue ice
again I can come here so I'll leave it
in the chest here and take my elytra in
the fly off
I'll just leave one here because I might
come back for my blue eyes
[Music]
what do you think about that
yes I have a lot of them
[Music]
uh let me let me find my bed uh where
was my where the hell is my bed
oh man yeah I already have the chords no
worries and also I'm gonna have made a
tower there so I want to put my under
chest over there
yeah what am I doing what am I doing
what am I doing Plus
you know what huge
wasn't it here
oh okay
ah no wait I have my dad okay
but I need my boat
at my door maybe
[Music]
I'll take my door
do you have children
it doesn't look like it
oh God don't attack me don't attack me
please
where did you chew and go did they die
that's what you get for attacking me
okay I'm talking
right here
I will sleep first one night
near myself
[Music]
hmm
that's a dangerous thing to do but
[Music]
I guess I'll do that
wait I want to exp for this one right
that's really scary
wait
I know
I need to have it in there okay
how fast are they
foreign
[Music]
this is Minecraft this is Minecraft
High Ground ah
[Music]
laughs
oh I'll pick that one up eventually
come on
so I mean that happens doesn't it it
happens it happens
can you get me from here
you could kind of clamp up now let's do
this
okay
remember the coordinates oh it's here
[Music]
okay
uh how much does that even give me
probably not that much
it doesn't even see me
[Music]
no
foreign
[Music]
I'm so stupid
[Applause]
oh man
okay
um
all right let's put it in here uh
everything that we don't need
and I shall leave oh I'm gonna take them
not all of them let's see that much wait
they're still there's still more in here
[Music]
I'll I'll take one for I don't know what
now do I need it
I know should I I can't mine it the only
thing I want to do now is
um
[Music]
go around a little bit uh try to find
another
and mess up mess up for emergency yeah
okay I want to find a mess on and
something something
Mesa by Omi
okay
it could be everywhere though it could
be anywhere
should I get the shulker ah
okay
uh I have my pickaxe don't worry but I
don't have my suit that's big guys
anymore because there I'm smart
I should take one more in case I get
real you really lost really really far
away uh but then I would need to
whatever
um
special okay where are we going
we wanna go
maybe more into the minus
of x
but I'll try to go into Only One
Direction
I guess
I mean it could be anywhere so
go home first
[Music]
why
race race chunky a little bit a little a
little raising would be good
[Music]
keep going out I don't be safe but like
what what would I do at home
what would I do
getting a new look pickaxe or
resupply repair
um
all right so we like when we go back
though after we're home she'll be passed
by here again and rescue my under chest
in that case if we're going home anyway
then I don't need this energies right
now
okay rescue the end of chest get to the
clutch
and it means I have to go to Phoenix
then
all right uh
and we have the coordinates for Phoenix
wait I don't have the emeralds yeah
let's just go home minus what was it my
400 and minus 400
300 minus 400.
[Music]
right
Discord is here
what did I do no rescue only so I would
love to do that but you know
you know you know chat is not quite as
adventurous as I am
but if we were only to go by my morals
and stuff we would have to have uh
Amelia pick me up again probably because
that would get lost again and okay 300
300 minus 400 right okay which direction
goes up
[Music]
this one no this one
this way okay
okay
[Music]
oh it's so nice to fly
wow is that a ship
did I check that one out already I need
to check it out now there's a ship that
I have not checked out yet oh my oh wait
I might have been in here before
[Music]
yeah I think I think I'm ah maybe not
um no I'm not sure
no I guess not but there should be
another chest right
let me see
oh
[Music]
all right
nothing too special I guess yeah that's
normal right oh what let me know let me
let me let me see before before we go
home
[Music]
doko
oh
I don't want to go there I don't wanna
is that there's no children there right
well I have my every track and fly away
if necessary eh how do I go there
yeah I'm on the top left
I thought they were gonna attack me
top left
[Music]
I know I know the x is treasure I know I
know
Southeast B treasure
oh Southeast uh wait where does it say
itself
this way this way east south
itself itself this way
right
[Music]
it's not moving at all which is probably
a good thing for now
that's the place where I was before
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
stop stop stop
it
it's here
found it I found it
good job chat good job I know
[Music]
I know treasure map of this place
I already off screen I already got one
that led me here and it already kind of
looked like this
but I kept on digging I couldn't find
anything
but there's no way that someone was
already here before right I just
couldn't find anything let's try again I
guess but is it under
is it also under
um
is it destroyed chest no I didn't
is it understandable it's not under the
stone I mine so
on here
I understand Stone
it's not here though
may have been there
hmm
yeah it really looks like it because
this was already the first time I came
here or it looked a little bit less like
this but pretty much like this
um yeah I think I found it before
only on the regular scent oh but I mined
so much granular sand already
[Music]
well I don't I don't think
I don't think there is anything here
[Music]
so how many how many treasure chests are
gonna give me this stupid map
again and again and again
I don't want to get this stupid map
anymore
um
[Music]
chess spawns nine by nine block go on
top of the X make sure you're facing
north while doing so stick out the
bottom of the cursor make sure the rest
of the cursor is not visible under the x
what
look for X9 z9
[Music]
X X9 what
what
X9
yep what
[Music]
nine
up here
no I think it's gone
[Music]
yeah but shouldn't it be here again
shouldn't it be where I stand right now
it's gone okay
someone was
for
eign
anyways but we're going home anyway so
I don't really need the area XP right
now okay
uh let me get rid of that
treasure map
s
which way
um
ah let me fly
oh there we go okay where are we going
uh
uh is this the right way I think it is
okay
hey suddenly you all came after me
[Music]
that was scary
beautiful sky
take me home
close to
see you next time
broke mine I'm stupid
[Music]
right
oh
it's the universe
am I still going the right way wait uh
this way
my space travel
first in whole life English to try out
space travel
pretty impressive huh
which way do I go
[Music]
trains in the way
yummy
okay 300 we're super close
like uh minus 400 uh wait I need to
chill for a moment
chill okay and we need to wear like a
300 need to go mine spot maybe I'll just
walk for the rest
I mean the problem is still fine but we
don't want to risk anything
sleep
last night
good night
[Music]
all right you like the TV I didn't
mention it at all isn't it cute
drawn by Christina Manzanita
cute it's me with my elytra
where am I going and I need to go
this way
a little bit only a little bit more
but this way when I go
when I go I don't I don't want X to
change too much
sometimes I don't understand how these
work
[Music]
ah kill mobs I guess I could kill this
dude
but a tiny bit
come at me tiny bit of EXP
[Music]
erience there we go
that did almost nothing but it's still
it's gonna be something
foreign
my bad okay I have it
jump twice I'm trying
wait
[Music]
okay down twice okay
we're fine with that double don't be
scared guys and wait
uh this this way for 600 going down yeah
yeah
400 going down to going down both going
down okay
I'm both going down
we're going down
I see a village wait is that
Cali's uh
house
[Music]
that's Kelly's house
oh God my only child
so we can't be that far away
[Music]
her long dance cabin oh oh what is that
who's that
like super close now I think
so let's walk
holy [\h__\h] that was close or Cena Skype
the starting point
oh
but wait is can we finally open the
chest we can finally open the chest but
there's no no
[\h__\h] in there okay
we made it back home safely why are you
not repairing it that's
what that's what I came back here for
don't worry
[Music]
I just don't have them breaking yet but
I have mending so
don't worry I'm gonna repair it now
you're looking beautiful today
as always
don't look on the new skirt we're
respectful gen mates
I'm not gonna look under your skirt if I
don't worry
not looking
foreign
[Music]
just taking a rest under muna's legs
now we can run
[Music]
no look don't look
don't look at the zombie legs no no ah
oh
I see someone stopped and got off in the
middle of the road
what happened
Ma I'm back
I'm back back I'm back back yeah
I'm on the Rainbow Road
Mario Kart flashbacks
Italian
let me on my way get some sugar cane
I broke it
[Music]
wonderful beautiful I was grave and
someone she built the grave for herself
foreign
funny
okay I'm back the first thing we're
gonna do is I don't know what what are
we gonna do we're gonna take uh in the
chest
and put our valuables outside of the
interest
but let's take one and put it into the
other house
and then I'll fix my Elite trap don't
worry I'm on it
[Music]
um
my beautiful house I'm finally starting
to use it
okay we're just gonna place it
here
and there we go some beautiful blue eyes
goes into the blue box that makes sense
doesn't it
and take this like that and yeah
I see it I don't really know what's in
the other ones I don't really have a
system for the other ones
let me get some emeralds I have some
more in my other house right how many do
I need for another silver pickaxe
[Music]
I wonder
oh
uh what am I putting in here
are you
[Music]
nice hat thank you
also
[Music]
here beautiful
oh my God
oh let's make something with the Sharons
what what uh
uh what was it called telescope
oh
what's it called
[Music]
oh
I need copper as well
[Music]
and that's about all I can make right
oh
[Music]
ah bless me
I'ma have some copper it's okay it's
okay I'm not that like oh
I'm not that stressed out about it let's
put those in this one
to the purple one in the magenta one
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you
and let's put this here
Diamond Horse I still don't really have
a horse of my own
I know I know I know I know there is
someone that wants to be rescued I know
we could go there too
[Music]
we could go to circles
we could try to go to circles
[Music]
mmm
circles well the people who don't
remember because it is quite long ago a
long time ago I went on an adventure by
foot and I found a horse I saddled the
horse and I traveled with it for a while
and then I left it in the desert but I
put a fence and stuff around it so that
it would be safe
it's let's be real it's probably not
there anymore we're gonna like go really
really far and then we're gonna be like
[\h__\h] it's not there
is it really gonna be worth it hmm is it
[Music]
never lose help
have hope have Iris
um
well at least I still have the I think I
still have the the coordinates what am I
doing I don't know what I'm doing
I don't know what I want to put where oh
wait
[Music]
what else what else
this goes here
um
maybe maybe
a full wonderful food is one empty
I don't have no empty ones well this
um
[Music]
oh
there's stuff in here too I forgot about
that
oh
oh I hear someone
[Music]
who's intruding our home
did he go invisible already
well where is he
is he in my house perhaps
no
[Music]
the diamond
heart you say
oh I'm not sure about it on my roof ah
[Music]
how the hell do they get up those places
on that roof
no
oh there you are are you invisible yeah
you're invisible right now uh honestly I
sleep for you
they never do they ever have anything
useful they don't
[Music]
even if I don't have the screenshot
anymore which I think I really don't uh
if you go to my stream then you should
be able from back then then you should
be able to
find it you are useless and you should
be able to find the coordinates now I
don't know how long that's gonna take to
find it
[Music]
um anyway
we have them
[Music]
kfp
as expected
[Music]
okay
I think um
done sorting
for now
[Music]
Rick Rick my second voice
oh my
oh my God hey it's not that far away is
it well going back will be annoying
because wasn't there an ocean in between
and we can't horses can't go into into
boats either
[Music]
make uh so class I don't have the
enchantment for success I just have one
trainer in Phoenix that trades iron and
suck touch pickaxes
but I'll go get them now and I'll also
fix my
I'll also fix my my my early trial
horses can't swim but you need a leash
[Music]
go ahead put it to sleep at least end
his suffering
can you drag a horse by flying that
would be really cool
membrane in the first chest it's okay
but I don't want to waste it for that
uh
should I bring some iron do you think
it's gonna be enough
[Music]
let's take some iron a little bit
Adam Sadler tragedy in the making what
do you mean
I ain't ready I run I win I wait why
would I take I can't uh to Phoenix and I
should take
my Highway
it's a bit faster
don't fly with wait wait I can't fly
with them with him anyway
Callie hanged her horse
oh my God wait how
by having him on a leash and then going
somewhere with a boat
oh dear
that sounds horrible with a minecart oh
God
oh God
only Channel Minecart earlier
well there's there's many many
voices in Minecraft so I don't think she
should beat herself up too much about it
[Music]
she was on the rail from the spawn oh
okay
I see hello everyone I miss you guys
how's it going in Phoenix then yo yo yo
what up
give me those sexy emeralds who has a
pickaxe again also oh yeah wait I wanna
do
I wanna do more of these you know what
can we change the rest of the stream to
uh uh Phoenix and Improvement
uh I'll do the other thing the biomi
search another time I wanna get the
um
the thing I want to get the thing the
thing
you know what I mean the thing
I'm breaking free
yeah
okay then just give me as many
emeralds as you have right now wait I
already don't have any right the drop
Island
no way I used it all up right
and that thing yeah I'm breaking so we
need we need more more
um
of these what are they called again
lectern
I finally know how to do that
lecterns what I need for lantern
books and slabs all right I'll be right
back I got a [\h__\h] ton of books
we should put a uh and a chest in
Phoenix then perhaps maybe
a sick touch guy yeah that would be good
so we need an Unbreaking and silk touch
anything else that is useful let's make
like a [\h__\h] ton of black lecterns
shouldn't have like things
maybe more beds too they were lacking a
few beds I think
let's bring them a few a few more beds
we are the mayor and the creator of
Phoenix then we gotta take care of them
let's just make some bids
um yeah white is okay
uh uh and uh
um let's go with that and make slabs out
of it as well and uh books I have
downstairs
hole
[Applause]
okay Papa came maybe that's a better
name
[Music]
with those books I can make
a bookshelf right and then make a
lectern out of that
[Music]
book shelf
okay
[Music]
um
oh
oh that takes a lot of wood
foreign
[Music]
bookshelves
how many
many
24. shall we make 24 lanterns
oh and that's a lot
16 is okay
16. we'll get 16 new workers
they're not gonna be useful right some
of them
I put the rest of the wall
ah you know what now I'll keep the wall
uh black
[Music]
um
I'll trade it
UPS more jobs
[Music]
let me put these in here for now because
I don't need them only truck you can
stay here as well for now will I ever
find you again who knows
okay let's work on Phoenix
ah it repairs it when I have the later
in the hand
it does yeah right because I get
experience from it ah
oh
that is again very smart oh I can just
wear it right
can I I could wear it okay
I'm scared
for some reason so let's put it there
for it this way right now
Mama I'm scared
and hold the pickaxe
[Music]
it won't funny break
they can't break anyway
oh
that's interesting I didn't no
Oh I thought they just poof
poof and then they're gone
I had any thoughts okay
wait I don't have anything for you
anymore
and maybe bedtime
um
okay
should we have the beds outside right
now I'll I'll build a new house maybe
here around
these beds
okay
I'll be a dormitory but that's okay for
you guys right
you don't mind do you
up
nice day like it already oh they needed
so many new beds
okay and then I'll Place appetite should
play selecters like further away so then
I know like
who's is who's when I want to remove
them right let's Place one here
anyone gonna take the job right now
probably not huh
okay let me sleep
good night don't eat house just need
food I know but it looks better oh I
don't like it when there's just random
beds there hello
foreign
[Music]
I have to level them anyway in order to
okay let's just have 14 useless lectern
electron guys librarians
[Music]
it's gonna be a pain in the ass
I don't have to level down
all right uh there's like two times
right there's like ever like
um these types who don't have a magical
book right in the beginning and then
there's honors to have it right in the
beginning
was that it
[Music]
[Applause]
okay okay okay good good okay thank God
thank God
I'm not gonna spend
[Music]
useless amounts of emeralds and
materials
okay
if the same guy takes it though is it
gonna be the same Godzilla well I'll
place it here for now
you want it don't chat
[Music]
what is that llama doing there
hello you guys are not very excited
about the job song
I lost his trained it changed it I
didn't lock his straight I didn't trade
anything
yeah
um I'm still waiting for someone to get
the job hello
is it like not reachable of course it's
reachable come on take it it's right
next to you it's
too much time
oh you aren't you the same guy who took
it before lack of the sea
do you guys want to keep those we have
enough leg turns
I also have enough I don't know should
we keep it
interesting interesting though it's bad
okay oopsie I
think
[Music]
um
what is that llama doing
oh that's so sad I should I should pick
it up later
as a lectern okay a new one
maybe this one too but then I won't know
which one is which huh
ah
aqua affinity right now now I don't know
which one is which
and let me Place one here Place one here
Place one here Place one here
Place one here
oh that was fast
foreign do we need thorns points too
anyone
[Music]
one's here one here points is bad
no points okay
uh ah that one got a job
respiration free do we oh
we have so many like why the hell not
you know what I'm gonna keep that one
but I have to trade with him
[Music]
like respiration free
oh I have a book with me and emeralds
you know what I'm gonna take that thank
you you are locked in now you got a job
[Music]
knock back we don't want knock back
not knock back one at least what do you
got flame we don't want flame delay
sounds lame
Riptide free
[Music]
okay
guys
[Music]
playing that spider oh okay is there
several levels for that though anyway
it's too late look at it again probably
okay you are locked in so we have
loyalty over there and we have Riptide
here
piercing I don't want piercing
without you
being off ah that was something useless
right
the pain do we want the Bane
respiration too we already have
respiration free
users are spiders oh that was that was
you right
okay getting rid of that
noise what did you have or nothing
okay okay okay this is going well
what do you have nothing
go away please
[Music]
oh that was it for now I think okay
we'll play some new ones
[Music]
and one
one here
and one here nice
wait who's gonna get it first who's
gonna get it first yo you took the job
away from your friend that is Juice Plus
cursive binding
foreign
no thank you what about you
though
no one taking this one what about that
one no one anyone
[Music]
let me play some over here one and two
two
and three
oh and
[\h__\h]
um one over here okay
[Music]
let's see
one at a time is better
no no no no no no no this is good pacing
I'm gonna wait for them to take the jobs
right now
[Music]
no one's taking the jobs right now
why why
oh here we go
foreign
[Music]
might be good too
foreign
[Music]
but let's take that for now
Fortune is good okay
powerful five five
power five
maybe for enchanting my sword or so
loyalty too
but the other one is only loyalty zero
right
[Music]
our power five is good okay locking him
in wait where is he where'd he go
why why
I don't have enough
16. what
see
wait how long how long is he gonna stay
like that because uh I need to lock him
in
that's not working is it
by the bookshelf
[Applause]
okay
but it's always gonna be that expensive
though what the hell
[Music]
well I mean it's okay you can stay for
now if someone really really really it's
maximal there's no one really really
needs it they can get it uh what about
you what would you again
oh I wanted to check
and the other guy that had loyalty
[Music]
um
let's see he works somewhere here is it
real infinite ah wait no
loyalty guy works here oh
mending cursive Vanishing on it Infinity
wait did we know did we never lock him
in
yeah Infinity was here uh before but
wait did we never lock loyalty in
I know he has mending I know I know
we've had him before
I did
efficiency
it's not you
it's is it you
Infinity
[Music]
respiration
Riptide
[Applause]
a fish let's see efficiency is good yeah
I think that one is not locked in wait
where is he is he a view respiration
wait where is the efficiency
this one he's not locked in easy but I
also don't have enough things I need
paper can I make
paper out of the book
no
14 is a good trade pool try the ball
oh they're already going to sleep
haha
[Music]
is that enough
wait wait do they lose her how fast do
they lose their job
[Music]
replied sorry for waking you up where
did he go
[Music]
one percent until I break it ah okay
this deal sorry for waking you up
important thank you
efficiency
[Music]
sleep well
oops
okay
um we still don't have a breaking though
I would like someone breaking I should
sleep I guess
okay yo one of those bags belongs to me
hey
good night
I will not stop until I get I'm breaking
um I placed a new one somewhere this one
is new I think
did anyone get this down
do I still have one at 15. I have some
white wall
I mean let me trade some white
with uh
foreign
no
are you a wool guy
yeah
oh that's it that's it already
okay okay can I try books for someone
wait I only have nine numbers
I could bring I could bring some more
wool
I think I'll
librarian's Bible said the ones that I
got rid of right the ones that don't
come with a uh an enchanted book
hi Sean wait do you wait no no wait I
oh four full that's nice because I got a
[\h__\h] ton of books yo
actually that's fantastic
that's fantastic Sean Mendes you are
beautiful Shawn Mendes yeah huh please
go refresh
please go fill up again I'll be there
again soon Sean my darling my sweet
sweet boy My Sweet Summer child
I need more people to get more jobs
[Music]
you don't want to get rid of anyone more
power we kept that one we locked it in
we locked did we lock you in for some
reason loyalty to I ah I still don't
find the Loyalty guy did he disappear
after all
who are you fortunate did we look look
Fortune to win
no right
that we wanted him right
well the two isn't that good anyway we
would want to have loyalty free right
I mean I personally don't need it that
bad because I have a book anyway I have
a loyalty book anyway
for Fortune free
[Music]
you might get free oh well for now for
now
um okay
let me play some more lanterns maybe
over there with tetsuo
let me give tetsuo's friends a chance
because they'd be looking for a job and
they can't find it because they don't go
very far away from this house I don't
know they're scared it's like a like a
High School uh
click click
why you call that in English
and they click it a high school group of
like these are the popular guys that
think there's something special so they
don't they don't want to mess so they
can talk to the normal guys
click click click
is that how you pronounce it
in English as well
did you just get the job
oh
no no no no
click yeah
lock up the seat too
it sounds interesting and it's golden so
it's like kind of special looking but no
foreign
let's see let's see what happens here
another one
[Music]
oh okay you're that one aqua affinity
taxi free what did I did I have uh
one wait can I make this uh freaking
free somehow
but he is
should we keep it I bet I have
efficiency free already
then I'll get rid of him I haven't tried
since before okay good good getting rid
of that
you can combine I'm breaking one is not
worth it damn it damn it's so close so
close but we keep our club finishing
is there no ranking of that too like
aqua affinity one I'll go for 92 I'll go
finish it ready
[Applause]
[Music]
yes no yes no no ranking no rank for
aqua ah okay
we're gonna call you onion when I have a
name tag for you I'm gonna call you
onion
onion onion
not everyone's gonna get that joke
immediately it's gonna take about a few
seconds for some people perhaps
you gonna take the job take it take a
ticket I know you want it I know you
want it I know you do
and I know you guys get it but I mean
like other members that come by at
Phoenix then
[Music]
Garfield hello Garfield
give that back to me
all right
[Music]
and we have Riptide free no thank you
I'm quite lucky with these I think but
I'm not getting the one I want
it glitched yeah it happens sometimes
[Music]
I'm waiting don't set your attention
wait for too long
I don't have any patience oh
look
that would be good for a rock Maybe
[Music]
maybe any level of Unbreaking you can
always combine to get the max ah I guess
so
but we'll we'll try we'll try to get
something better for fishing good for
Ina wait for nursery okay
okay
that's fine with me
ow
oh that was fast orange still again
no
[Music]
wait I had you already did
up yet
you guys are so slow you're slow
go slow
stop baby that for you no
you sure about it once in a lifetime
chance or he's coming back oh he's
coming back
you got my hopes up for nothing oh but
you know one you're the one that I think
yeah efficiency one no thank you
what are you doing by the way no where
is your left turn I want to destroy it
is it this one I will destroy it
useless
I think that was
it maybe not
it
do you guys have an overview of what I'm
doing here
where's John hey hi Sean
oh
I'm sorry that was creepy I'm sorry I'm
sorry
[Applause]
[Music]
I have no idea what's going on I'm
having fun regardless that's nice what
I'm currently doing is um I'm replacing
these lanterns in order to get these
guys to work for me and get a job but
it's like a gacha like they they change
and
they changed what they offer me each
time I reset them unless I lock them in
uh please please please get more get
more emeralds please
stop looking at me
is this town is an absolute messy I mean
I have to agree it's starting to get a
bit messy um even for me it's a lot of
jobs maybe I should get some kind of
system in it
who are you again fortune tell we locked
you and didn't we
punched a new one here
anyone who wants to get it
yes yes yes
[Music]
baby
no you'll say
useless scum
[Music]
static
the only way to fix this is to start
from scratch
no no no no
I don't like it we can do this
no no
let me sleep
[Music]
flame oh
you guys wanted me to keep that one I
actually didn't log in and you know what
I'll I'll take it thank you
[Music]
Place time thanks for the lectern with
good dress yeah I did that before I did
that before I think generally that's
okay because they stay close to their
electron anyway
ah yeah there's no levels of flame so
good
hi no did you guys hear that like I
think the microphone picked it up she
made like
noises
cute okay where's Sean where's Shawn
Mendes
where's Sean are you Sean
no
my kidneys yeah my babies you Sean no
are you Sean no
who is John
oh wait you're new I think are you fire
aspect one
what does that do
I fix my pickaxe oh you're right wait I
haven't been holding
my hot wings are fixed
pretty much almost fire on sword do we
want that
not worth it okay
thank you guys I trapped you guys
I trust you with my life
which doesn't mean much because I can
revive anyway
no Eric the cleric sorry a little mix up
hello okay
[Music]
it's fine here I'm sorry
as you guys like to a certain extent and
uh you guys are you are yeah quite quite
special to me like even if I wouldn't
trust you with my life like if I was
Immortal
and not Mortal Mortal is when you can't
die right
[Music]
we have a lectern why did you not
restock yet
wait yeah I know I think he doesn't
because he also
no wait are they do you have an electron
or not
[Music]
wait on it
do you not have a lecture
could see
he's not
he's not restocking and loyalty is here
did I not make a sign for mending
[Applause]
wait is this yours and that's actually
not loyalty
oh
oh I think under I understand no we
didn't lock him we didn't lock no I just
made a mistake with the sign perhaps
that's yours huh
let me change that into mending
met uh Sean Mendes
mending
Ah that's yours
oh
yo
books
wait I thought I can get ah wait is it
like when I place them and I how does it
work again
how does this look again
[Music]
Ah that's how it works okay
foreign
[Music]
yeah funny pun isn't it
I would like to say that it's a genius
idea but I probably didn't come up with
it myself did I wasn't it the chat who
thought of it
well I'm pretty free that uh Emma Rose
now let me play some more
one here
again
let's place
let's Place one here
[Music]
I want a place that's where I can find
it again easily I already forgot this
one this one
um
one here
places are around here what was your job
nothing
I'm getting reveals right now
what are you respiration we locked this
one in
[Music]
mm-hmm
come to Brazil
why
why what did I say that made this
request happen again
[Applause]
I was actually in just a few days ago I
was looking for uh some pictures that I
had from the time I did go to Brazil
foreign
[Music]
a bit expensive though
do we want him
sharpness free I think it's good for a
sword no not worth it too expensive
Max is at five oh okay okay okay well
then I'll get rid of it oh thank you it
was someone's nice anyway
um you did a good job I guess but
I'm getting rid of you anyway
[Music]
it's always time to ask that
oh
rip that oh why do people really want me
to get Riptide
these guys just keep on offering me
Riptide there's a lot of guys here
looking for a job here hello nah I'll
Place only one it gets confusing if I
plays more than one in one room
take the job I won't look at you because
you seem distracted when I look at you
damn why are you looking at me
I'm not interesting
don't look at me
I Leave the Room
and then they do it
I figured I really got distracted
because of me he's into me
[Music]
[Applause]
hello
foreign
[Music]
get down Frost Walker but only level one
but you can walk on Ice faster right no
wait is that the one that makes the
water in front of you and dies well that
was a different one way
[Music]
it makes it makes ice
oh should I keep it
it goes only up to two so having a level
wait where are you
[Applause]
meh brush Walker pogies
all right as well guys fake eyes yeah
but it's cool get down
18.
you would want to have that on your
shoes right can you put it anywhere
besides his shoes
expensive for one a little bit um I'll
think about it I'll think about it I'll
keep you here for now
don't guys don't don't let me forget
about him
don't let me forget about him
[Music]
so many
name tags honestly wait who had the name
the child Mendes have the name tag so
was it Eric the cleric
not you what you don't have a booth do
you because he has been sold out on end
of pearls for weeks
I think he has no booth
uh I gotta get one for him
like his Swan was like broken or stolen
by another villager if
it don't exists
wow wow
I there he is he was hiding from me
[Applause]
name tag
um
I want I want more
[Music]
okay I'm coming back I'm coming back
with materials to trade well
um
um question do you guys remember if I or
uh hired anyone else that had uh
infinity
today well that was loyal
[Music]
okay confusion
averted
okay okay okay okay
I am
I'm confused
what did I miss well I don't know when
you left hard to say it
let's put some books soon
[Music]
let me put them downstairs
my library
[Music]
okay this is my library Fortune 2
efficiency of four respiration free aqua
affinity flame bane of art why the [\h__\h]
do I have that oh well
knock back to Riptide I think I got that
in the treasure chest or something
Riptide free knockback two deaths right
of three respiration free I know where I
got that one Riptide free well we have
two of those
damn and loyalty one okay looking good
[Music]
is it too much to ask
books
now you know what let me keep the books
out I'll take other stuff
although that was quite a nice price
it's gonna be a while
[Music]
let's get some more iron
some book
s
and uh oh oh could have taken white too
but gray oh not much Gray
not much Brown let's get that let's
uh
foreign
[Music]
let me sleep one second
bamboo for the sticks as well yeah
let's see
[Music]
yeah I could find some wood I guess
but that's it's boring
I'll do it off screen but right now I
would like to save some time we have a
lot of white wool
okay all right uh for now that's enough
I think
[Music]
am I
am I tripping on
can I not Dash anymore
I'm not dashing right now
am I
oh no I was dashing okay
I got so used to it now it felt slow to
me
[Music]
going up
and we go into the ball turning around
beep beep beep beep let's go let's go
[Music]
okay you're in the way
move
dama
[Music]
okay
a pumpkin farm in Phoenix and would be
good
hello
would you like to create some uh I win
with me uh
thank you I'll take one for now
hi flame
should I already give some of I have uh
one name tag
there you are
[Music]
named at 19 okay
we need some name Tang Zoo
oh wait we wanted to go to PPP to get
some stuff too fresh Walker do I want it
or not I'm still not sure
[Music]
sweeping Edge you are new
we don't need surfing Edge totally
it works here I suppose
[Music]
they nerfed pumpkins oh
now sweeping is good it's man it's okay
okay that doesn't sound too special so
I'm gonna get rid of it
is
Discount are you kidding me I want a
discount discount
foreign
[Music]
no
okay
31 emeralds
[Music]
you don't get me discounts anymore
either right you used to give me
discounts
why don't you do that anymore you used
to give me discounts
why don't you do that anymore
[Music]
you can only mean one thing okay let's
go back to what's name
what's going on over there this I
finally disappeared okay we have two
name tags let's name some people who are
the most important ones that came that
are new people or maybe even old people
who do we want to name
[Music]
um
when you have Infinity do we want to
name Infinity
why do I need an ah
oh I have to put the name on it first oh
yeah right well someone wants to have an
anvil
someone must be working on an anvil
there's an envelope in here no
what's up I might not do it
[Music]
hmm
anvil
Temple and no
animal is not a workstation oh
[Music]
okay well then before we name anyone
I'll continue my mission hi
jab jab jab jab jab yeah
disappointing
[Music]
um
are you new no I already locked you in
I'm not looking
you make a decision on your own and not
putting any pressure on you where did
you go where did you go
power
[Music]
how is that what you want
Phoenix 10 people of Phoenix then you
should not look for Power you should
look for wisdom
how is not the way to go trust me
wisdom that's the one
that is the one
ah you're useless where do you work here
you work here
[Music]
[Applause]
you work here
time you don't have a job anymore
congratulations how's it going in here
how's it going
sad Virgil voices
here dab
[Music]
foolishness Angel well huh you wanna you
wanna challenge me I'm the high
Challenger
you know if I challenge your heart
there's not gonna be much left of it
afterwards your height will be mine
laughs
I don't know that ended up kind of cute
[Music]
by all means take it
challenge challenge you want a challenge
but it is not much of a challenge
because I already have your hearts
don't die
[Music]
foreign
you know what I'm getting really hungry
really really hungry I actually
baked bulked a bread before the stream
so that it's ready to be eaten at any
time
smite it's my Kiana
will anyone take this [\h__\h] job of
what I guess not okay let me take it
[Music]
hungry
oh
multi-shot we had that before
not bad but the bed
ever been to the bunker week
get booked
bread ASMR I can give that to you that
is something I can give that and give to
you I can I can
I'm just waiting for the right moment I
honestly would like to have I'm breaking
free first before I eat anything
[Music]
sure what that is but no thank you
melon bread do you guys like or have
ever eaten my own right okay answer one
question first
who has eaten melon bread before melon
pong
answer that question first
uh that would have been good for the
Trident [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
me me no no no okay everyone who has
eaten it before
do you like
you like melon bread
[Music]
I don't like it don't really too sweet
did not like it yes yes it's okay
yes yes yes never had it too sweet no
oh there's a lot of people saying it's
too sweet for them
well I mean I can eat it but I
personally wouldn't like if I'm at a
convenience store and I have to choose
something to snack on some bread or so I
really probably wouldn't go for the
middle and bread
um
foreign
there's like so many different kinds of
melon ponds in Japan don't like
super good even for people who don't
like menopause
well I like that super fun too but
that's like a like an interesting choice
to make because like that's something
you would get like at a high school or
so
before you break Japanese High School
food
get the job did I link
no distract you from getting your job
please take it
oh thank you
noodle sandwich
[Applause]
I like yakisoba
then I'm pretty sweet but Kiana is sweet
too LOL
ah you tried you get an A4 effort
[Music]
Bread Cool interesting
I know
[Music]
tonight
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
it can be combined into three with some
work
Go for free
[Laughter]
You Gotta Have It
projectile projecting
it you can make free with it all right
how expensive is it
so expensive wait do I have to combine
two I'm breaking two combine two of them
get free all right that's cheap enough
now I have no [\h__\h] books
let me go get some books quick he'll
stay there
you'll stay there
foreign
12 12 emeralds is cheap buy books from
Sean what with Emerald now
not gonna waste my envelopes
I have some books
in my home cat boom
[Music]
[\h__\h] kid
help help help
I'm breaking four doesn't exist yeah I
think so too
okay
get into the [\h__\h] boat or move
mom
wait I do have no I have no more fish I
could have given you fish go away
[Music]
okay
man that's a lot of work to get on
Breaking Free huh I'll I'll take I'm
breaking two now
maybe eventually we get some others too
but
um
for now I'm happy with it I just need to
pull my hot wings
and then I'll I'll go get a bread and
we'll bring super chats I think
books
[Music]
that's all I need right
okay
[Music]
uh
um maybe
[Music]
maybe maybe get some more emeralds
though for a few more name tags so we
can name a few more people before we
leave
foreign
touch I already had it
I got that one
I took care of it let me just get some
sticks
let's try to
um trade lipsticks
[Music]
foreign
I'll fix it
[Applause]
[Music]
okay oh
bring fumble of the sword faster oh
is that so
is that gonna work
[Music]
is stick more
okay we got two stacks of sticks
okay
putting that there putting that here
I will have to
clean up this place off stream at some
point and get some more organization
going
the answer we're starting to feel
inhabited doesn't it what made you feel
that way only Iris joined recently
that's like one more person well what
what made it feel that way because we
are more active again or
[Music]
are we are we though
I've always been
my activity in Minecraft has never
really changed that thing
[Music]
Ender Dragon more buildings hmm
huh I mean good at coming back
I also feel like I never left
I don't feel like they ever left though
and I came here for Sean
[Music]
and uh wait oh [\h__\h] let me lock in the
other book first I guess
wait wait I need to train
some of that
and six
who goes for sticks the Aerosmith
[Music]
[Applause]
was it the Fletchers yeah yeah
we're sniffing
[Music]
wait what does he look like do you
all right
okay we got 18. how much did they want
for the one book
it wasn't that much I think
nine eight one one to ten under ten I
think twelve twelve okay
let's get it
I'm breaking okay
foreign
yeah I want to wait I have um
I'm missing one white wool
I don't have enough stick let me let me
go find some trees real quick damn it
there's so many people here go away
no one got outside right oh this is this
is a bad place
the
pickaxe is doing fine Again by the way
okay I'll keep it a bit more
[Music]
making a gate that you can see the doors
ah yes I've considered that yes yes I
wanted to do a lot of things with
Phoenix and we're still not done I want
to make a Kiara statue I wanted to make
um
like bigger gates at the entrance but
also inside I guess
and like for specific houses or like
areas in Phoenix then
[Music]
for example to make like people like
tetsuo easier to find for first time
people like if you've already benefiting
them before then you kind of know where
tetsuo is
but these are so tall
[Music]
that's it
oh yeah and the K of b a k of B in
Phoenix then
eventually eventually these are all
some of the goals
but we've worked already so much on
Phoenix Suns I don't know we would have
to do another full stream I guess
to to do all of these kind of things
do another Phoenix 10th stream
and I I do is there something left now I
do
want to get a little bit more of like
organization
going in Phoenix soon like have more
like hmm I don't wanna like imprison
them in tiny tiny one by one
houses
just to make them easier to find but
maybe like decent sized houses
and then keep them in there
well to have them stay
by their heart
but not everyone's only the important
people
only the important people
not free by free maybe like six by six
or something like that
I think I think we need to have it a
little bit more humane
Humane Solutions
black snip Street oh yeah something like
that would be nice but like I don't I
feel like moving the
the
um workstations
seemed like kind of bothersome
like how are the right people gonna find
the right workstation again if I get rid
of the workstation
like how can I make sure that for
example Sean Mendes
is gonna find that workstation
um
any any advice on that
take them by a boat
well I guess I guess I would have to
name them all first the important ones
then it would be a bit easier to
organize blow out I would be like ah
this guy there he is there's Shawn
Mendes I put them in a boat
I mean it's not necessary I guess but it
would make it easier I suppose
[Music]
are they looking at me
[\h__\h] off
small Stone
yeah
hello
well that was fast yo dude good job
nice
very good at protecting new people I see
[Music]
comboed good job golden and
Eddie
sorry sorry I'm drinking give me a
moment for God's sake
yes
okay we have come for what I want to
make uh six do we have a workstation
here
no I'm gonna go outside then
foreign
[Music]
there you go you killed yourself was
that worth it
was that really worth it huh
[Music]
Spruce blanks
uh sticks
[Music]
noise that's so many holy [\h__\h]
I dropped some
and make some more
that is a lot of sticks
I tried them again
[Music]
okay
yo noise it is over the wall the spider
can attack him but but he can attack the
spider
foreign
[Music]
that was
strong
damn we got some good Golems here good
reliable Golems
[Music]
um
no
oh let's jump
around please
discount please no what is that is it
random them giving out discounts is that
a random thing
well we've got 18 now I can get another
one of those yes
about all those books
Golem strong eat
not quite a Pillager thing
if they like you they give this song
when you buy from them a bunch if I feel
like sometimes they don't they don't
um
object out protection
you
I'm breaking there we go I got a second
one
lines
yeah we should name him I guess
what would the name a fitting name be
for him come on give me some good ones
someone who sells Unbreaking what would
his name be
ER Brook Brad
[Music]
Kimmy Schmidt
that is funny I watched that show where
am I going now
but to our home
[Music]
I like that I'm gonna call him Kimmy
Schmidt
Unbreakable
[Music]
I I liked Kimmy Schmidt though that
Netflix no was it Netflix
that show was pretty good
it was pretty funny I mean it was very
it's exaggerated I prefer comedy shows
that are a bit more natural
than that
but it was still it was still bearable
do we need an anvil
for what I'm trying to do
yes right
okay
yep
I'm always using Amazon wait I shouldn't
always I shouldn't always use Amazon
[Music]
because it will break right I keep on
forgetting that and those break
why what do I need again to make an
anvil let's make my own one
[Music]
iron blocks not a hotel
um
gosh those are expensive
[Music]
Kimmy is unbreakable Anvil is not can we
put Unbreaking on an anvil I know you
can't I know it would have been too nice
how much do I need again
31 iron you are amazing you know exactly
you already wrote it in the chat before
I was even asking for it
yo we had this before though
I asked this before last time I think in
my last Minecraft stream
mind readers you guys know me too well
you know I would ask that question
[Music]
um Iron Block free was it free one
um
[Music]
I think it was free
Google yeah
all right made it scooting Master it's
someone yeah
[Music]
you are here now
um
book
oh
[Music]
then
I had enough explain for that too nice
stop it
no what did I do
it's fine
couldn't have been cheaper I could have
mixed the books first oh oh it's okay
it's okay
give me
Schmidt
my name
hmm
[Music]
oh I'm out of Bixby now yeah but I don't
need it for doing this as I do all right
oh well what we got one we got one we
got Kimmy
[Music]
we got Kimmy for now let's put the rest
in here
[Music]
okay Kimmy
yeah
Michael scottwell who would you name
Michael Scott
[Music]
I love Michael Scott I love him with all
my heart with everything that I've got
with my whole body I love Michael Scott
[Music]
I want to marry my no you know what that
would be so obnoxious I don't want to
marry Michael Squad I don't I take it
back
no no
but I would love to
have him as a friend no never mind uh
probably also not
I just wanna I just want to see other
people suffer from Michael Scott and
that is probably the best way to enjoy
Martha Squad
is not being close to him but watching
other people that are close to him
suffer through his deeds
can we kill me
that's not that's not sad sad sad is the
Moon
[Music]
it's not the same thing
who's Michael Scott yeah the the main
character from The Office
what did I come here for ah
oh my God everybody
said forget what I'm doing are you the
right one and I'll stop moving
I'm breaking
[Music]
okay uh you know one more thing that I
want to do is put up a few signs
it's never ending never ending Minecraft
stream oh my God it's already been
four and a half hours
past midnight oops oops
by the way teacher Aberdeen tomorrow is
on my channel
just to let you know we're um rotating
now
what am I doing signs it might it might
take a while though
[Music]
maybe a few more yeah
a few more
excited for the ttrpg
which he makes me a bit nervous though
um well I do enjoy it but it also makes
me very nervous about the whole
role-playing thing what do you do again
power
hour five that's the max one right
keeping that one
um why are they going to sleep
[Music]
I'll come you mean why I'm nervous
oh I have a lot of stuff in here too
and because uh I I don't I don't think
I'm doing that well with it
oh what the hell
I forgot I had thoughts like actually
useful stuff in here
uh yeah
um
you guys say I did well but like
it's really difficult for me like
um
it's
especially it might it might have
something to do with English not being
my first language
um
it feels a bit difficult to come up with
words
doing the ttipg
yeah
um
who works here
yeah
Fortune you work here
friendly
[Music]
yeah that's why it's probably good that
I have this character that is supposed
to be shy where are you going you really
work here do you
you you you you you
[Applause]
respiration okay no
Chris
respiration hurry
okay
[Applause]
Sean Mendes mending infinity guy
but the orange lead you
he definitely try role-playing in third
person it's so much easier
Tiana is a clown character yeah
yeah so it should be fine but
um you know I was just really impressed
with for example how gura was
role-playing
and I was like damn I wish I I wish I
like could come up with stuff like that
like out of nowhere
I think in German I would really
have a little bit less issues
and Unbreaking too
we don't really need that guy huh
[Music]
yep that will be your name once I name
you that will be your name very original
I know I know tend to have confidence
thank you
yeah good eyes are natural
she is
Grand took it like a shark in the water
oh
not bad for the no no onion onion onion
[Music]
onions
who are you Frost Walker we locked your
head right no we didn't ah I'm still I
was still thinking you know what um I
don't have emeralds right now so I leave
it up to the lock when next time I log
in if you're still
uh a frost rocker guy oh I should call
him
what are they called again on the other
side of the wall
what are they called again
Game of Thrones
why it walk yeah
I like that
blame you awake here
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh
[Applause]
everyone and wait
um well okay for now iron
wait you also worked there though don't
you
[Music]
Ariel Smith you work somewhere here
wait no your work right hand okay that's
perfect then okay I got one more sign
who else needs a sign ah maybe that
house over there
isn't here where my man is Eric
declaring you
Eric wait you don't have a bullfight I
need to fix that eventually sorry about
that okay but we're done we're done with
that
we are done guys
[Music]
I think today was a productive stream
we're gonna Read Super tags after this
but what did we do today what did we do
we got I'm breaking
we got a lot of amethyst we got a lot of
uh blue eyes
we got some Treasures
uh we left some under chests hanging
unfortunately
we got on breaking though
we learned that the elite foot doesn't
break but I still think I'm breaking on
it yeah so it doesn't go down that fast
well well
but wait but wait
now that it doesn't break that no I need
to find I need to I need to learn how to
stop I need to I wanted to say how about
we quickly fly over there and get the
Ender Chest but but I need to learn how
to stop
[Music]
I need to learn to stop
I I could
free my homie circles
do it
just for that stupid and the chest
I don't know I don't know man I don't
know if that is worth it
[Music]
not sure
I think we're just gonna read till the
Dead
hahaha
[Music]
yeah I also want to eat a little bit you
know
bread it's bread time
and it's already
uh almost midnight so
you know
we don't want to stretch it out too long
foreign
[Music]
okay
okay I'm good
I'll take a five uh three minutes three
minutes four minutes five minute break
to make my bread and to go to the idle
meeting and color my cats
I gotta read the ones from yes third day
two yeah yeah because I didn't read them
after Zelda
uh oh yeah I could AFK again that's
right
AFK so that more wool and more iron
makes its way into the Farms
I'll pull that species thanks for the
stringing thank you guys for watching if
you're staying for the silver chat
rating I appreciate that if you're
leaving then thank you for watching see
you next time
thank you
[Music]
okay I'll wait here
a few minutes
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
yum yum yum
welcome
um I made tea as well
mm-hmm
some more tea
and now I'm eating my food a little bit
almost done
[Music]
huh
the first time I listen to this
stay from violence Sunshine version
I love it already
[Music]
foreign
y'all
vibing
[Music]
yo I love this
we're gonna use this as karaoke at music
as well like if I want to sing to it
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
no chat replay or
replay
now that's nothing I can do anything
about that's YouTube
I have it turned on but
that's YouTube wait how long has it been
since silver chat reading
[Music]
we did that on
oh wait that's just yesterday oh I just
dreamed so much it says first of all
this
[Music]
yeah I know that sucks but maybe soon
maybe we'll come back soon
oh
[Music]
foreign
for my tea
she gave me that I told you guys before
she gave me those uh really cute pink
cherry blossom Starbucks uh
firmus cups two of them
before I left Japan
[Music]
foreign
couple
orange
wait we can do another orange live
with that what was it yamaha's Yamaha
rooms oh
I need to learn how to set it up why
don't you guys even know about that did
like you guys even knew about it last
time I I talked about it
yeah Yamaha sound room
sink room sink room Yamaha money use
that word really
[Music]
it
I thought they did it in person
but then I can ask her
oh you know before I forget that Aki
uses it a lot
let me ask
um
[Music]
let me ask maybe and
I don't know why I don't know which
channel to use to ask that
does anyone know how to use Yamaha
synchron
okay now at least I put it out there so
I won't forget about it
should I mute Minecraft is going so much
[Music]
I'm using Minecraft last time it was
nice but today I don't like it
today I just don't like it I don't want
to listen to it
okay
oh wait it's repeat
uh it's repeating safe on fire wait a
second
we don't need we don't need that let's
next one you should
smile and smile go smile and go smile
goal
Sunshine version Oh I like that
reminded me of uh Super Mario Sunshine
there's a what's an instrument
harmonica or no
[Music]
you hear that what is that
thank you
this one accordion
oops sorry makes it feel
really nice
I like that one Accord accordion
um
[Music]
very tropical yeah this one is really
the the drums as well not the drums you
call them drums
China
I'll turn it down a tiny bit because I
guess it's a bit too loud but I just
want to enjoy it
oh
my outfit fits it kind of does like I'm
in a vacation mode right
and I'll let my other drink actually
fits better
than that uh unicorn
drink that I have here
uh where is it what is that oh no not
that one I got a better one do I have it
on this screen
hmm
not this one
I really one thing that I really
changed ever since I started whole life
is a
being a more organized person than I
ever was before
and I mean
it could uh need improvements
but
the amount of data and stuff that I have
to keep organized
is pretty big
where where is that
where is that be
uh where do I have my special fancy
drink
God damn it you know what let's go to
the gaming screen
copy it from there
because I have it somewhere here there
it is okay copy
yeah a great Improvement yeah it really
is you guys just put it on smoothies
I just put it on smoothie
ah she moves too much put it on chunkers
let's turn it around
uh
uh flip here we go
hey I just realized there's no straw in
this
no strap
or a cocktail like that
it's okay it's okay but
[Music]
okay I just took a sip so you can you
guys can can use the sipping sipping
emote use it I just drank something
use the sipping him out now or never Now
or Never There It Is there it is
yeah I love the pineapple bird holy [\h__\h]
I don't know
[Music]
please please chunkers don't move too
much
chocolate sleeps so much
these past days tonkers has been
sleeping next to my pillow all night
right next to my head like even though
there's not that much space but she like
squeezes squishes herself in there
uh it's like between my pillow and the
edge of my bed
[Music]
at the very head of my bed
that's why she chills and sleeves and
she sleeps so much
oh
a cat cat's tension
cat tangent uh I've recently finally
bought
a laser pointer for specifically for
cats interestingly oh my gosh I should
go to a little get rid of the pain
comments
it didn't happen for the longest amount
of time and I just used normal toys but
it's kind of exhausting and I realized
I haven't been playing enough with them
and that might be why this movie is
being obnoxious
so I got myself a laser pointer and it
actually
smoothie [\h__\h] loves the laser pointer
so much there's nothing else she loves
more right now she's so into the laser
pointer
yeah she loves it she Zooms for the
whole living room which is quite big she
runs from one end to the other she loves
the laser point and I can make her go in
circles and circles and circles and
circuses this is really fast
she loves it however
chunkers does not care or even
acknowledge the laser pointer
that's the lazy [\h__\h] I love her but she
does it's really hard to get her to like
play and work out
[Music]
yeah she doesn't move much she doesn't
like moving that much
circles oh
she's really lazy Tonka is really lazy
smoothie really uh excited there's we
really see a difference like for example
this is also
kind of really shows their personality
when I in the morning when I wake up
wake up in the morning feeling like
potential and I wake up and
the moments movie hears even the tiniest
movement of me reaching for my phone or
turning around from one side to the
other and she sees my eyes open the
moment she sees my eyes open she gets up
and she goes
[Music]
she walks on top of me and Walks from
one side to another and she keeps on
going wow wow wow round the whole time
the moment she notices I am awake oh
hello hi junkers
you heard my meows no it's all good it's
all good
and meanwhile chocolates just chills
with me in bed until I actually get up
she doesn't care if I'm awake or not she
also doesn't care for any specific Foods
moving is only like that because you're
really really really really really
really really really wants the wet food
immediately as soon as I woke up she
will not leave me alone that is
literally why what she's living for wet
food
yeah wake up and feed me I saw your eyes
open now feed me you're weak aren't you
aren't you I'm joking come on come on
stand up come on come on make me food
come on come on one more food come on
come on come on come on come on
chonkers is just like chilling stronger
just like I slept 12 hours I don't mind
sleeping five more
so cute
[Music]
hmm what
not as hot as hot wings but quite hot
[Music]
so much
foreign
[Music]
version Oh I really really love the
Lo-Fi version of that I was singing it
for you guys too
Gotta Sing The Sunshine version too
[Music]
oh
nice
[Applause]
um
Bossa Nova really be hitting yeah I kind
of want to post a Nova remix of all my
songs we have one of Hino Tony wait I
should add it to my playlist
it's my ending song anyway but
wait where do I have it
[Music]
why do I have it
wait
the one that I play at the end is a
Bossa Nova version of Hino Tony right
or was it from heart challenge John I'm
going crazy right now
[Music]
da da
so there it is
let me add that into my list
ings
foreign
who can actually do that
possibly
[Music]
you know there's also you know last time
for the low-fat versions they only use
the songs that they were singing In
Bloom right
YouTube YouTube no
YouTube no don't take the superchat
reading away from us again
on YouTube
fine for me okay here we back we're back
don't do this again YouTube now that the
Super Chat reading
we're back okay so what I was saying was
that for the previous one for the Lo-Fi
Arrangements they only use songs that
were in bloom right
[Music]
I think and for this one though they
added a few like solo songs for example
they they added Nana's lunch with me
they added uh
heroin auditions
double brain
as well
so that's pretty cool
yeah Japanese members only yeah
[Music]
I don't know if they have a plan on
adding some of Ian's solo songs I don't
I don't think so because it's kind of
like separate project that they do in
whole life Japan I think although I
wouldn't mind I would love to have them
arrange a version for me
spikes Bossa Nova remix when when
yeah that would be that would be
interesting I also don't I can't imagine
how it would sound like
[Music]
um
so hot
[Music]
outside
what
version
[Music]
I can add some cold water
da da
a
should we try to sing this
the first time I heard it so it will be
difficult to adjust it but hey let's
have some random karaoke
[Music]
candy gold
Brown
where does it that doesn't start an
immediately does it there's an intro
[Music]
can I sing this
ah they skipped the first one the first
part ah
[Music]
wait
I think they did
[Music]
yeah it sounds like it
okay
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
Daddy
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
please
[Music]
come on life medical and candy girl I'm
ready to go like you may know you're not
speed all day
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
who would have known that they do the
whole last two courses again
I didn't know
it's seven minutes long
that is definitely well all of them are
like over six minutes they
they really added some time to that
they added some uh Arrangements huh
yeah some of them are seven minutes most
of them are at least six minutes damn
you're funny we're going crazy listening
to Petco random right oh my God I'm
looking forward to it now and I can't
imagine that Sonic Bossa Nova because
it's like so hyper and energetic
normally
it's it's the uh it's it's an um this
this the second next song is that how
you're saying it comes after the next
song
so this sign and one more song and then
pickle down down brain
looking forward to it all right we
should start reading super chats then
after this little karaoke session
what did I miss you missed I was just
singing
before we start reading silver chats
no it's okay uh let me see let me see
let me see
oh that is not
not refreshed
it's fun to sing these different kind of
versions and really is fun although I
didn't know what was coming
mostly mostly they're the same mostly
push 10 tails off no no no
and The Legend of Zelda the team makes
me think it's tails off
I'm going crazy
[Music]
yo what is this part I like it
whoa
yo who's making these versions
amazing
absolutely amazing really refreshing too
and a good way to make use of songs that
already exist for a while
and that people might have been a little
bit tired of listening maybe maybe who
knows
um thanks for making the day better man
thank you for watching British versions
she said versions eh oh my God
I said versions
you thought I said who's making these
okay
[Music]
let's see yeah you you really misheard
it that was not on purpose I see that's
okay that's okay it happens it doesn't
make sense when it happens
yes
where is my thingy
[Music]
where is my where's my thing oh there it
is is that it
um
might be this one actually oh
[Music]
yes okay
yeah let me put the super text is where
they belong to
isn't this super relaxing
[Music]
oh that wait
am I what's going on what's going on
wow what's going on what's going on
[Music]
I have like a million of these Excel
sheets by now because I keep on
recreating them like copying others
because I don't know what's going on I
need to be organized
where's my organization
[Music]
okay yes we got it
reminds me of Final Fantasy 7 at Costa
Del Sol well I can not judge that at all
absolutely [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay and then we're gonna start reading
from yesterday's Super chats
Legend of Zelma
[Music]
I like this I like this part
yo
psycho
[Music]
too bad I can't really sing this song
did I put it here
I'll put it here okay
[Music]
thank you
how are you Kiara
uh are you are you are you asking that
because you really want an answer or are
you asking that like how some people ask
it in English language and don't really
accept an answer because they just want
to say hi and just use it as a hello
well I am fine right now I'm in a good
mood I'm doing well I ate a little bit
of food so it's all good um I'm a bit
scared of this week because I wonder if
I can really make it for all the streams
um I want to apologize ahead of time in
case I cancel any streams
for whatever reason because I still
didn't have a day off in weeks now
uh
[Music]
but
I'm really feeling fine now so okay
[Music]
oh
thank you thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
yo good stuff okay
hope you're doing fine
thank you for the lovely clips
I really like your clips
of these songs
[Music]
foreign
must watch a movie broadcast for sure oh
yeah I kind of want to do it this week
but I wasn't sure about what time to put
it in yet that's why I didn't put it in
my schedule but
um
I think we might want to do it on Sunday
but I'm not sure because I I wanna I
want a time uh that is like
better for those people who didn't catch
it the first time
um
I I'm still thinking about it oh
and I might have to I don't know
because I'll probably not be around to
push the start stream button depending
on what time I choose
so maybe someone else has to do that for
me yeah I gotta think a little bit about
it a 12 hour 12 hour later
ah
12 hour later
oh
that would be Monday
oh wait we did it at 4pm
the first time what is that plus 12
hours
what's that plus 12 hours
spikes and drums yeah wasn't that like I
already saw it a while ago
like on the first day it came out 4 AM
[Music]
4 AM
so either I would have to wake up at 4am
to push the button
maybe Nana can start it for you are you
saying that because she hijacked my
channel previously
are you referencing to that
[Music]
foreign
for me I could have like I could give
her the data the videos she could put it
in her OBS in a separate scene and she
could just start the stream for me I
guess I'll think about it I'll think
about it
and Jim Tracy donkey and Gigi thank you
for the pinky
but then hot wings it was a 10 out of 10
singing performance your singing was
divine and exquisite I enjoyed it very
much thank you mate thank you
sorry uh sorry what's wrong with me
sorry I have to catch the Vlog for Zelda
because I have to be up in 3.5 hours
work oh please don't worry about it
there's unless you live on the same time
zone as me I think it would have been
pretty difficult to catch all of all
three streams yesterday also you might
have like stuff to do in your real life
and have like a job or
some other thing to attend to so it's
totally fine if you didn't catch it a
lot that's totally fine
oh
[Music]
ran out of battery come on
that's a rookie mistake
thank you foreign
[Music]
pretty good for ESD
and yesterday was wild king looked at
the horsey demo
still haven't someone just asked me in
Japanese but I just realized I still
haven't sent King even once for you guys
I'm not planning to ever put out the
cover on that so I might as well just
sing it in karaoke next time
[Music]
I did
now come on
[Music]
oh I keep on forgetting about that
thank you for the pinky
everybody I bring you also for the pinky
thanks for the great color I'll get into
that last song really blew me away I was
surprised you guys were so
so
like you guys gave me so much positive
feedback about that last song because I
felt like I was doing
not very good
that that tone by the way was really the
maximum of my range
I was barely able to get out a decent
note
[Music]
it was even higher
or something like that
what the
doctor that's really [\h__\h] high
and I
I even that's not even head that's not
even yeah that's not even the head voice
there we go I want to listen to this
quick time
pick a random brain in Bossa Nova
[Music]
oh wow this is cool
I need to die
[Music]
oh yeah
it still has that fun anime vibe to it
though I like it
foreign
lifting up uplifting
[Music]
hi
bow
[Music]
foreign
interesting interesting
[Music]
already thinking about how to sing this
a little guitar solo all right no
singing here
when does it start again
[Music]
nothing
um
wait I think that we're singing here
wait where do you jump in
[Music]
um I think maybe at the piano you're
supposed to jump in
[Music]
da da
very dry
[Music]
lyrics again
does it really go here normally it does
[Music]
which part is that which part is that
oh
okay
[Music]
oh thank you
I'm gonna try anyway
it's gonna be interesting
[Music]
oh
my God
[Music]
London
Sheila
[Music]
foreign
foreign foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
Tamil
that was probably not it I will just
chill
[Music]
it's good
my name rainbow
[Music]
hello
yes
[Music]
oh okay one part that I absolutely don't
know what would go there
but but but yeah okay
like it started I I felt
I figured out the melody afterwards but
that was like still like it didn't
really sound like that part in the
beginning
oh well oh well
that was fun
foreign
[Music]
that's like Lo-Fi and Bossa Nova
versions of whole life songs only
so the previous Lo-Fi ones mixed with
the current Bossa Nova ones
yeah
that would be such a chill kinda
curry [\h__\h]
hey
foreign
[Music]
attitude Suki
there we hope for some deep voice it
depends on the song doesn't really
depend on me when the song is in a
certain key then I'll sing it in that
key
[Music]
how did you learn to sing
I didn't really learn how to sing I mean
there was a time where I took some
singing lessons
but besides that it's just me singing at
home
really
foreign
[Music]
that's funny how did I never say that
joke yet ever before
one ticket for the children okay you're
all welcome to come for free guys
isn't saying Eva you got it or don't see
that's something that we discussed
before in my stream and I think
partially it is and partially it isn't
um yeah
it's an interesting conversation to have
anyway everybody are thank you for the
pinky
motion thank you as well for the orangey
orange thank you soon
you probably told me before I had to say
your name I'm sorry thank you soon
Skye thank you for the red silver chat
I want to stay from the bottom of my
heart you are a kind girl left cave
people never be my option no doubt ah
leaving Cafe okay seriously now you're
very considerate of kfp so let us as in
the pool should also consider you
relatively I promise I will become more
cookie oh
I don't think you ever did anything
wrong but thank you
thank you that is a good
good thing to do trying to read the air
always good
it's not always possible that's okay but
I don't think you did anything bad
before so thank you for your support
thank you for your kindness Skye
don't worry too much about it though
just glad to have you as a supporter
thank you
unknown thank you for the pinky thank
you for the kind of look at angel that
was so much fun your voice is beautiful
thank you I'm glad you enjoyed it I feel
like you know because this time it was
uh the members only kind of will get
because it was members I felt like
it was okay to just go for some random
songs and that I didn't really know
whether I could sing or not
I hope that was okay next time I'll
prepare better
fro fro thank you also for the pinky
Kiana
um
[Music]
foreign
something that
caught my eye
oh
[Music]
yeah you're everything nailed it you're
amazing thank you so much
thank you
[Music]
thank you very much for your kind words
I can see not everyone was happy with it
but
I'm glad you enjoyed it I had fun too
like just randomly choosing songs that
come up in my mind and also taking some
requests obviously I won't know what
requests you're gonna tell me so you
can't be 100 100 prepared
um
but uh I think this was fun like for me
this was fun sometimes I prepared
sometimes I don't
yeah there's many ways to do it thank
you cocoon thank you also for the pinky
thank you so much for the Kiana okay
you're welcome
Mr Brightside
lunch with me is next
a good morning
[Music]
thank you I had fun too
and your mama streams are always so
worth it the last song was especially
awesome it was a wonderful hot wings as
well
thank you everybody
Jeff the Phoenix told him yeah
nice to see you again very fitting for
today's stream to read your super chat
now
and oh holy bird
oh holy bird sincere apologies for the
late tribute for the day of your birth
all of the villages celebrated the day
so passionately with so much bigger that
they passed out and missed the Harvest
oh no
so belated wish of happiness and a small
tribute for the day of your birth Oh
Holy One
may you always burn pride and continue
to be the powerful and caring
deity
of Phoenix and for years to come
see what I like about Jeff is that
evil place and adds like something to
the Lord of Phoenix then without
making it more difficult for me because
he's happy with it
he says Phoenix is happy and all that
and they like me so it makes it much
easier for me
thank you you're doing it right
thank you Jeff I always enjoy your
messages very much
thank you for two pinkies
take a look I'm a big fat chicken now
nice looking good looking chunky
I guess you can't see it in the Super
Chat yeah I can't but I believe you
anywhere else oh there you are
[Music]
anyway I'll take this opportunity for
new my pinky promise I did a few months
ago thank you for being a source of
happiness for me and many others your
streams never fail to bring a smile to
my face you're doing great keep giving
it your all and I'll keep supporting you
the best I can also good luck and talk
to me maybe one day I can go to one of
these conventions to embarrass myself in
front of you why
yourself
thank you doll
[Music]
I hope that you know I can visit more
connections all over the world
not only America and Germany other
places would be nice too
so thank God it's the magic for the
promise very very sweet of you I'm glad
to have you still in kfp glad to have
you forever
thank you
no no no need for spilling some
spaghetti eat your spaghetti what a
waste to spill it
[Music]
what
mom's spaghetti his mom's there
anyway don't spill any spaghetti oh
[Music]
foreign
to that
[Music]
oh
I still I still need to learn her songs
to sing them properly I will I will I
will until the next kind of okay I want
to learn this life with me Sunshine
version
[Music]
how much for focusing
thank
you thank you I couldn't Super Chat I
could I could not super chat after you
sang discotheque earlier it's time with
massive wonders for my favorite music
Nana Mizuki song oh
hello
Bravo baby keep being brilliant and
banging out those
why is that censored B bitching bitching
Beats
You Beautiful bad ass birth did you just
wanna
use as many words as side with b as
possible Bravo baby keep being brilliant
and banging out those bitching beats You
Beautiful baddest brood boss is that
what you were doing it really sounds
like it what for funny though I like it
alliteration
a little alliteration
[Music]
it's a b attack help me I'm allergic I'm
actually not allergic I actually I don't
know maybe I am I was just never stung
by a beam before
[Music]
what is this Bossa Nova music is really
good for lifting up one's mood holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
is there some magic in this
in these Arrangements
I really feel it like it gives me such a
good mood
even even when there's something trying
to drag me down
the Brazilian magic baby
that Brazilian that's a Japanese girl
singing a Japanese song
[Music]
all right all right
come to Brazil
okay okay
first comments on the jam-packed excited
weeks 1 million spikes 2 million goodbye
declaration tails off streams great
collabs true a lot a lot of stuff was
going on holy [\h__\h] you you make it even
more obvious damn
um
[Music]
a busy busy busy week wait a second I
want to do one thing uh
[Music]
okay and
your bubbly and simple personality makes
my day brighter would you ever consider
doing a kfb cat review stream thank you
for being my Oshie I think you're not
the first one asking me that I Really
Wanna
damn I want to but I keep on like
forgetting to plan it uh huh Can you
guys tell me on Twitter after the Stream
so that I can put it on my calendar
later on
cat review stream please
I mean we could also do like a pet
review stream
because there are some cute dogs and
stuff and cute owls and
this doesn't have to be a cat no no but
I don't I don't really want to see more
cats
[Music]
huh
pet reveal would it be better
[Music]
cats and owls only
dogs dogs I only have a dog oh man you
can put cat ears on him and then send me
the picture and be like that that's my
cat she's the cat the dog wants to be a
cat let it be a cat when a dog wants to
be a cat then you let him be a cat Okay
so otherwise he's gonna be really really
sad okay don't tell dog he can't be a
cat Okay adult can't be anything
yeah a pet review would be more
inclusive but didn't someone already do
that in honoluliano am I going crazy
okay of pets oh wait that's already a
hashtag you kidding me
foreign
would do
all right let's do it then if no one in
Holland did it before let's do it
#k of pets
sounds good sounds good
moondock leave it to me thank you for
the red super chat
[Music]
random spot thank you for the pinky
thanks for the karaoke I just want to
say I love you and before sleep s-e-a
pain
have fun playing I'ma watch archive
tomorrow good night attention kfb thank
you thank you for always supporting me
through archive thank you thank you I
really appreciate it archive gang very
important everyone who's watching this
as a VOD what's up thank you so much for
supporting me
I see you guys you guys are really
important too
archive views are just as important as
live views thank you
thank you for taking your time out of
your busy schedule days
to watch my content thank you
[Music]
Arc black 45. thank you for the pinky so
many pinkies what's going on
hello my middle right thank you
that sounds better yeah so many thanks
for the karaoke how can you be so chill
and so hype at the same time am I
and that last song oh and this since the
chickens had Reflections on the stage
and you did not
ah do you need to make an M vampire
video
oh
I I could probably
make it so that I have a reflection on
it I could probably make that work
[Music]
realize that I didn't even pay attention
to that couple couple
would Mel like it hmm
[Music]
hmm and vampire I have a vampire
coverage
then also goes up high a lot
and see if I were to do a m vampire song
cover okay I don't know what the actual
the actual song title is I think just
vampire
um and I were to commission Yuna to make
me a simple video where it's just you
know the the sideways face the profile
and just lyrics to it you know what Yuna
would do you know what Yuna would do
although I don't know is there even a if
there is a choreography to the song then
you and I would probably put it in there
[Music]
what
if Kiana doesn't reflect how will she
ever singuda song
[Music]
I do want to sing to that song
Eventually I really like that one
it's really dope
must be so much fun to sing
[Music]
Okay so so that's notified thank you for
the red super chat Angel I've recently
started practicing to drive a car and my
instructor always blames me for driving
too fast which makes me very nervous and
stressed I really hope I can get my car
license oh a lot of my friends recently
got a car license uh and some of them
have been having struggles some of them
haven't
uh oh
people some other remix we have reached
it
it's the end of the stream ending ending
time
no no no just kidding open nothing
this one is also really good
[Music]
anyway
um
yeah I wish you good luck good good luck
do your best after you have the license
your life will probably be much much
easier
because being able to drive in a car man
there's so many moments where that would
have been really helpful for me but but
I'm not getting one
so good luck to you you can do it
ah
awesome breeders
with that one before I think
[Music]
paying for the car is pain
yeah I guess so
[Music]
super sad wow thank you thank you for
the member stream I almost cry for you
sang The Last Song it was beautiful it
was so beautiful and I love you Mama
thank you I'm really I already said it
but I'm really surprised about the
reactions
so that song
I didn't think you guys would
say it was that good it was literally me
just like trying really hard to get a
high note out there
thank you though thank you thank you
I'll try to do more exciting members
streams for you guys
thank you thank you thank you thank you
chat
I I feel very blessed
that's for sure
[Music]
Thai tea thank you for the pinky love
Emoji X5
did you ride it like that so that I
would be able to read it in the Super
Chat reading reading
oh thank you Titi Loof Emoji five of
them
acknowledged thank you for the Pinky
Okay is all
ks0514.
thank you for the red super chat second
thing Moondog question why are you
revealing to the klb cat review stream
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
I'll try to implement it ASAP okay
I want to see cute kitty cats too
everyone's cute kitty cats and their
stories their names and how how they act
and stuff
hmm
yeah I'm excited we'll probably be a
pain in the ass to go through all of
them though and save each each image
oh God
yeah or takes like like the last time
the last time we did something like that
um was with the chocolate right and it
took me hours because in order to give
credit
I couldn't just save each image from
Twitter I I wanted I did I took those
screenshots right so that I could give
credit to you guys but that took me so
long oh my God
yeah but then wait didn't I end up like
giving up on that yeah I did and I just
went for Twitter manually
yeah that's what I did I was like for
hours I was saving the screenshots but
then I realized oh my God my stream is
starting in like 30 minutes and I went
in into the chat and I think I even
asked if for you guys it's okay
and then whenever something was in the
tag that shouldn't be there
I tried to just
scroll over it quickly
well we we might have to we might have
to do that again for the kfp Pet review
because I can imagine it's gonna be even
more than the chocolate because like
I think it's a way way less effort to
take a picture of your pet and to post
it on Twitter than it is to make
chocolate take a picture and post it on
Twitter
yeah it's probably gonna be more people
this time
and when you're a pet owner pet owners
love to show off their pets
so they'll be all up for it
I listen to the K-Pop song oh it's the
one who's singing the members only
stream
[Music]
I like it like it
is
[Music]
and then I sang one twice song
they cry for me but that one wasn't
English in the end
I wanna I wanna try more if you guys
don't mind I want to try
for the Korean Bros
sing a few more Korean songs for them
yes I sang a sumi song you missed it did
you not watch the archived screen the
unarchived Kadoka stream I'll try to
stream it again mamamoo I love mamamoo
I love mamamoo
[Music]
is one of my favorites
K-pop groups Kiana pup yeah K-pop means
Kiana Pub
I don't know how to pronounce her name
I love her yeah
she's the best
[Music]
um
KDA is not quite
my thing I don't know
never really
Katie I never really spoke much to me
I mean the music is good and the girls
are cute and the outfits are cute the
envies are great and all that but I
don't know it never really interested me
piqued my interest
[Music]
anyway continuing
who said the red one you know what
happens when you send a red one
[Music]
thank you for the pinky let's say that
Ina tells you she has been cursed with
blindness
oh dear what's what's coming and this
casting a spell to cure it a side effect
of the spell is that it will send tecula
to Finland and Subaru to Sicily
what would you do to make sure they get
home safely
[Music]
what was that question
well somebody wanted to go on a vacation
anyway so somebody will love it
somebody will really enjoy that
um and I I wouldn't mind joining
somebody in Sicily but Finland is also a
place I wanted to visit so I might just
if I have to I guess I'll join them both
hahaha
and Savannah can fly south for the
winter
[Music]
that is a very strangely specific
question yes
that's my [\h__\h] self
oh man
um well okay you know what I'm gonna
join them
I'm just gonna help Senpai and silver
Senpai to get around those places
yeah
it's a good it's a good way to
hang out a good excuse to hang out with
tech without standby so probably really
want the help because she doesn't speak
English and any other language that
is spoken in Europe so
she's gonna have some issues
[Music]
foreign
Ohio
[Music]
cancel for me you are always top left
because that's where my heart is
that is
so cute
cereal X7 Dunkin
William XXV I thank you
you did the cat he's twenty dollars
thank you
it's not really a cat though
foreign
there's a poem again
or is there is that a poem
oh
[Music]
I will catch them on for this but let me
say this you've been on a light and our
Muse others may be blind to who you are
but the day will come when they finally
see with a true game
gem you can truly be and understand why
it's you we choose to stay and support
continuously you are an incredible
Talent here that nothing can change as I
love your attention thank you welcome to
the membership
again
hey Raven house thank you for thank you
for that I heard you're short on money
it's in the game in the game
here I have some our beloved boss thank
you
uh P.S from that very streaming
perplexed me that you were placed in the
left corner bottom left corner you mean
yeah it's absolutely not where you
belong and I say that more and more
people realize it now too even outside
your audience thank you
[Music]
um
yeah I I think a lot of people who use
that bottom lifestyle deepen their heart
they know
that I'm not like they just use it as a
joke I think yeah and and they know and
some other people they don't know so
you said I am stupid and horny as hell
uh and those people maybe we can manage
to change their minds eventually and if
we can't then that's okay you can't uh
really control with everything everyone
is thinking even even when Kiara is in
control
even when I'm in control
ah I wouldn't I wouldn't blame it all on
Clips because there are a lot of good
clips and there are of course some bad
Clips or like clips that have bad titles
and bad thumbnails
um but I don't wanna like
put it all into one box and be like the
Clippers it's because of the Clippers
they're working hard too and I just
don't want to like blame it all on them
um I think
um there's many factors that played into
that becoming such a deep deep
um
what's the word in English
[Music]
rooted wow you guys with your
dictionaries
yeah deep rodent uh mean
and I mean in some way I do and as I
said I didn't do it too sometimes and
um I think it's cool that we have our
Insider jokes it's funny
hmm you just gotta be able to understand
at what times it's uncalled for
[Music]
yeah yeah but it's okay I'm fine
I I'm all good
um
that's
even if
um it sometimes annoys me that's still
one of my Littlest problems
foreign
[Music]
gotta love ice cream
and thank you guys for trying your best
to help out and collaborate thank you I
love you guys
thank you
thanks for being honest with your
feelings gentle you're welcome uh you're
welcome
thank you for appreciating that
[Music]
love is only
Raymond house did I give you a kiss
already now you have it
the Kevin cave beats action
I wish I had let your spanking Persona
occupy my soul earlier that is a very
interesting sentence
and I'm glad that for time you burn your
way into my heart feeling with me with
passion thank you and I love you thank
you that sounds funny
Chris Howard Anderson
and I've started once in whole life for
clips and the first one I saw of you
showed me how thoughtful and sincere a
person you are I fell in love with your
streams ever since I can't imagine which
clip you watched
even if the bottom left joke stays
around I'll think of you as the sweet
fun passionate potential well I'm proud
to call my Aussie thank you that's a
good way to do it thank you so much
[Music]
thank you thank you for the sweet
message
lizard wizard thank you and whale boy
donkey
[Music]
breath of the wild oh yeah because
breath of the wild too releases next
year maybe
yeah it would be good if we could
[Music]
squeeze it in somewhere before breath of
the wild too but
um
well we're on the lab too probably not
gonna be released that early in 2022
right
well maybe maybe I'll play whatever the
world one at some point but
that's gonna be an extremely long
play through huh I do want to play
breath of the wild too though
so I gotta play do what wait do I have
to go think about it I've watched
free full playthroughs of breath of the
Wild Ones
I think
like in terms of understanding what
happened before I can totally go into
breath of the wild too immediately
that would save us a lot of
a lot of hours of streams
um but for the sake of completion of my
channel
might want to consider during breath of
the wild one anyway or maybe instead of
doing the full thing we could just do
like a few episodes
an RTA
no not really an RTA but we could just
kind of like
yeah I don't know do a few
without even without the goal of
playing playing it until the end but I
guess that controls and stuff are gonna
be similar in breath of the wild too so
since I only watched a million
playthroughs of it
I I might know a lot of things about the
game but I have never played it myself
so it would be a good way to maybe like
get a feeling of the game before jumping
into breath of the wild too without any
actual knowledge of how to play the game
if you understand what I mean yeah I
think that might be good
anyone else watching from the beach
you're watching from the from the beach
nice
I am not jealous
[Music]
it's a pretty easy game are you sure
we'll just say it's easier than Skyward
Sword if it'll I mean it's really really
different but
[Music]
I said it's insanely different but
laughs
I guess in some places it's not very
special to be at the beach like if you
live in certain places huh I'd say it's
harder
uh way easier
[Music]
yeah it doesn't have motion control so
Ohio
[Music]
um
breath of the wild is very intuitive oh
I see
[Music]
okay
um
[Music]
oh thank you for the pinky Hi boss love
you and your content by the way is there
any chance that we can see a takamoy Aya
right I reacted to that super chat
during the stream I really liked the
idea
double date stream some days in the
future
just asking don't love it I love that
idea it is it is in in my in my list of
things that I want to do now
thank you for the idea
the next two Oreo shake ones thank you
foreign
[Music]
games right I know he isn't for some of
them
uh not sure if he is in Skyward Sword he
might not be he might not be
it might not be I I I know
it's not about spoilers I already kind
of like a long time ago I already
watched the playthrough of Skyward Sword
of the full thing
I barely remembered but I have a feeling
that he was not the final boss of
Skyward Sword
I have this feeling
I might be wrong I might be mixing up
things because I want to play through of
every Zelda game
thank you for the pinky well well if it
isn't our middle middle Queen how are
you I like how you guys are putting me
in different positions now
thank you I'm doing fine thank you and
Ashley this Bossa Nova music is really
doing something for me here I love it I
hope I don't get sick of it too soon
it is it might be good to switch between
Lo-Fi sometimes
yeah
but Lo-Fi sometimes felt like too too
chill
so
this is this is good stuff
um
thank you
happy belated birthday to Alina
foreign
[Music]
have just sent you
oh is there like a convert a convert
conversion wait how is Minecraft going
by the way am I still alive I am okay
eh
I have just sent you
5956.35 rupees equals 100 Canadian
dollars what
what also thank you for your hard work
but please try not to burn yourself out
it's ironic because I'm a phoenix
um
[Applause]
it's based on the Indian rupees really
the value is Indian rupees or is it
really or did you just like
is it is it like officially self or did
you just convert it to Indian rupees
[Music]
rupees are real but they ain't ain't
gems
so that's not not an official thing they
aren't
foreign
[Music]
big brain
you will find that I wonder if there's
about I mean I guess you could kind of
like
guess it
like seeing how much a shield costs
and see how much that would cost now
although who who buys and who sells
Shields I mean there's probably not much
to go by and it might be difficult you
would have to because the value of a
shield now is definitely different from
like a value of a shield in medieval
times
it sounds very record to your local
shoes sounds very complicated
the spontane ous
[Music]
a replica no that's different though
because obviously like game merchandise
is going to be more expensive although
maybe not necessarily because that might
just be out of plastic but if you have
to compare a real Shield
a real Shield's price to the price of a
shield in Zelda I don't think you can go
buy plastic merchandise from Zelda games
hahaha
because that's that's just gonna have a
ridiculous price even for the fact that
it's made out of plastic but that's
nothing not something that that uh link
could be using like I don't think link
is gonna The Shield that he buys in the
game For What 100 rupees
is strong against fire or whatever for
example I don't think you can take the
plastic Shield that they sell out there
in the real world and bring it into a
lava dungeon
let us that's gonna melt that's going to
melt
this is a really interesting discussion
[Music]
uh what else could you compare because
the stuff that they sell at the shop is
ridiculous maybe bags like how much a
small bag made out of fabric or leather
costs in the game compared to how much
it costs outside of the game in real
life
um
don't really know about potions I guess
you could compare to energy drinks or
sell or or smoothies not this one
bombs
I feel like the price isn't going to be
all over the place
[Music]
no arrows emeralds arrows might be a
good thing to go by
a stack of arrows
I think you could get a realistic
pricing out of that in real life too
because people still use arrows for
hobby uh uh uh what do you call the
hobby again what do you call that again
uh
uh uh what was it what was the name of
that
I agree archery archery I think
I think it's going to go by okay Jackson
got it
I'm counting on you
[Music]
I want an essay on your reasoning too
and on your calculation so you might
have to send me um a doc file a document
Yoda School
sork 787 thank you
Skies of Acadia on the gameplay was
wondering if you know about it
the eyes of Acadia well well well let me
look it up Skypes of okay dear
nope I don't know this
uh you know during GameCube times
[Music]
no that made me think of something
see that looks like a classic and I
believe you guys but um it probably
didn't come over to Europe or not to the
German speaking area did it
I don't think that there's a German
version to that that's probably why I
don't know it because what I was going
to say is during the GameCube times I
was getting into this whole jrpg thingy
and all that but I could only really
reach so far uh because there was not a
big choice of German translated games
and
did my voice sound like a dog bark
because I was like or something like
that
yeah no I got excited because you uh
tell me what Skies of Acadia made me
think of something I wanted to tell you
for a long time so let's go
um
[Music]
I wanted to tell you about one game that
I played back in the day with my brother
and this time I actually because I keep
on forgetting the name of it I forgot it
again I took photos I think of it last
time like a screenshot or something let
me see
[Music]
and I want to just hear if I have it I
want to hear if you guys
played these games
I wonder if I can put the images of the
cover of the game covers
on here
okay I'll I'll tell you the
top three
um the top three games
that I enjoyed the most
in my
childhood I don't know how old I was for
these
[Music]
whatever I'll just do it
number one
hahaha
this this one was so good do you guys
know this one
it was so good
it was so funny
it was so it's a Playmobil game do you
guys have Playmobil over there it's like
a bigger version of Lego Lego
do you have Playmobil
[Music]
yes
yes see it says playmobil at the bottom
it's like a Playmobil game and you like
a knight and I don't I don't remember
anything else but it was so much fun
playing those huge in Canada
oh it was a big like
um competitor to Lego in my childhood
it's like a bit bigger version of Lego
kind of
um
foreign
this was so much fun my brother and I we
played it so much I would I would love
to Play It Again
wait is that on PC probably right the
PC's answer to the legend it says
[Music]
the PC's answer to the Legend of Zelda
you sure about that I mean I have to say
it [\h__\h] rocked this game was amazing
but this is apparently the answer to the
Legend of Zelda
I want to play it again
[Music]
that's that's quite a big thing to say
man that's quite a big thing to claim
yes okay let's see the other one
the other one
um
where's the GameCube game
okay I'm curious if you guys know this
one I think this one is really niche
[Music]
oh did I play one or two
I think it was two
[Music]
oh yeah oh this was so much fun
oh this game was so much fun
okay
number two
daisy Daisy what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
Daisy
how the [\h__\h] did you know but it's
number two not number one I think I only
played number two
so this one you guys know this one
you guys know this one
I played this so much I don't think I
ever finished it but I played it so much
I was just running around with my cards
all day
I I never really know what I was doing
in this game
is
this was really fun
I don't know this game wow a lot of
people who don't know it I've heard of
it I know that one never played it the
GameCube is one system I missed out on
damn
not this one either no I would say this
is this is probably not like a really
legendary
revolutionary game
but I did have a [\h__\h] ton of fun with it
and it's one of the games that I
remember the most from my GameCube times
one game per year growing up oh man that
game I played that one really
never owned a Nintendo let's play it on
stream oh foreign
I would have to get a game kill again
[Music]
just to try it out just for the funds of
it
[Music]
oh
okay and number five
for the third one
I really don't remember any of it
just some Vibes of it
but this was the shiz and I'm gonna try
playing it again I want to play it now
when I'm able to understand it because
now I have a fully developed brain
so the first oops the third one
that me and my brother played all the
time
[Music]
is
I think this one might be might be more
well known this is not on the GameCube
uh although I don't know did I play
number one or number two
I think
[Music]
this one
yeah I think I played number one
this one this is it that's the one I
played okay it's a game from 2000 from
the year 2000.
[Music]
on the PlayStation 2
oh that character
[Music]
I remember that one
oh oh my God
okay
[Music]
Daisy
what the [\h__\h]
Daisy what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
Daisy
baby what is wrong with you do you have
where are you are you my brother
I'm a huge Boomer are you calling me up
over again are you my brother
meme
this one
Dark Cloud
I I recommend it because I think it was
actually really good like I was so young
I don't know what I was doing I don't
remember any of it but
I don't remember
damn this wait this came out in 2000 and
now it's
wait I don't know if I played it in 2000
though actually I don't know in which
year I applied it
foreign
[Music]
yeah in the future
time travel oh
[\h__\h] wait this way they're fragrance but
there's one more
um that I played a little bit later
where I had a somewhat developed brain
um also Dark Cloud is something I I
might want to try playing on stream if
you guys are up for it there seems to be
like a version for PS4 actually that
looks better but I need to look into
that anyway Daisy help me out I don't
remember the name it was a GameCube game
it was uh
um it had it had it had a hovercrafts
hovercraft
boats in hovercraft
[Music]
GameCube game with hovercrafts and
there's a there's a sequel coming out
Beyond Good and Evil I think that's it
foreign
[Music]
I think that's it because I'm still
waiting for the new one
[Music]
yeah that's it
ah Beyond good and evil one yeah I'm
waiting for two come on that
that was so much fun but scary too
yeah do you guys know Beyond Good and
Evil
that was a good game two is never gonna
happen don't say that they're working on
it
it's on PC I plan on getting killed
[Music]
it's happening
two is a mess shut up even if it is home
if it's a myth too what do we exist so
hello
the PC on the PC is the remaster oh
it's been 20 years and when did that
game come out
[Music]
when I Google Beyond Good and Evil
the Google gives me like like questions
and stuff right and it says is beyond
good and evil canceled two canceled
during a 2020 investor call Ubisoft CEO
I've confirmed that the publisher would
be releasing five new AAA games in 2020
to 21 was confirmed in a follow-up q a
that Beyond Good and Evil 2 would not be
one of them so there could still be a
while to wait yet
all right
and uh
Bianca and evil came out in Europe on
the GameCube in 2004 I'm not sure when I
played it once again might not be in the
beginning I don't know when I got it
you cracked my
dream but they were working on it like I
said I've seen footage of it they can't
just drop it I'll I'll finish it
let's finish it kale Fields finish it
let's invest in it wait they need
investors right that's what they need
we got the stunts we got the kfp stocks
let's invest in it
can we invest in it they're looking for
investors
there is no hope shut up
friends
I want the game I want the game how much
do they need
is is uh one thousand dollars enough
I know it's not
[Music]
what 50 million 100 million
um
this is gonna be a problem
it's gonna be a problem I can't I don't
have that money
[Music]
I don't have that money I'm never gonna
have that money so am I never gonna have
Beyond Good and Evil 2.
you guys have never really like that up
to date on like game News until it comes
out so if you guys ever hear any news
please tell me please let me know
because I I know I never I never hear
about these kind of things until way
later
if you ever hear that they're working on
Beyond Good and Evil till I need to know
it please let me know
last train that was 2017.
[Music]
flip
2023-24
says Ubisoft guy
[Music]
what Peppa Pig
it was that one of the characters is
that the pink character
I barely remember him
what happened to him I don't remember
the game at all I just know I liked it
see I really have the worst memory
that there was a pig yeah I know there
was a pig
there was a pink and a decently cute
girl
that was in the whole Hoover craft and
then I remember around like later in the
game
the city was like taking over or
something oh I remember I remember that
like Factory
well it really scared me
that game scared me
please
you guys remember that factory
you know what I mean
it was scary that was quite the game was
pretty scary
yeah this is heroino audition
a kind of a stealth game yeah
[Music]
did you start watching they don't no I
didn't
we take diesel EQ well we take it
had some sneaking stuff yeah yeah yeah
yeah
oh man
ah like thinking about these old games
really gives me some damn Nostalgia City
[Music]
some hearts is something I never planned
never
just like Final Fantasy I only played
the highly acclaimed uh nrpg Final
Fantasy 14.
foreign
[Music]
I want to play Xenoblade at some point
yes let's read super chats it's almost 2
A.M
Ray Smash Bro 176 donkeys
and we've been going on a [\h__\h] of
tangents today man
foreign
[Music]
what's up with that are you hiding
gaming skills uh-huh
foreign
thank you for your first time Super Chat
thank you
welcome to kfv Lord ebook thank you soon
this is
cheap white bird Duncan Stephanie
geminal Duncan
[Music]
but like all those bosses that he
mentioned
even though I did well of them I was
inside filled with panic
the way you slapped that Zelda bus was
inspiring
he really wasn't much of an issue but I
guess like I one thing that didn't
happen in the boss fight at all and I
know that this boss can do that I I
figured it out yesterday because I I
watched someone's playthrough of it
after I played it again to see like what
what what how does it usually go and
I've seen that he usually like steals
your sword like if you if he comes to
you with his hand and you don't do like
what you're supposed to do then he
steals your sword and you have to get it
back by
um like blocking him with your Shield
yeah and that didn't happen at all in my
case and I guess that's what you guys
thought would happen because you said
you said you you guys think I would be
uh struggling with the boss
it didn't happen at all
the Magic Hands yeah what are we talking
about Skyward Sword
for once it's a it's a tangent about the
actual game that we're reading currently
and
yeah
[Music]
point I think we're done with the
Skyward super jets now yep
[Music]
so something up anyway
I just put it up
I love this art so much
it's super boing boing but like it's so
beautiful like wow
not because of the boring boing but
because this artist is like so talented
so good so skilled and I love the
beautiful face
[Music]
and I really mean it like I'm not
talking every time see this is a good
example every time what I appreciate the
actual like Aesthetics of someone and
I'm like this so art style is so
beautiful and all that often you guys
would be like oh yeah all right we know
what you're looking at it's not true
like in this case for this piece of
light I really like the way he drew the
hair and the hairstyle that he gave me
and the beautiful smile like it really
looks happy
and the pose and everything the colors
the colors is so vibrant
is is Art is good height
I really love the
this person's height could annoy
[Music]
Hunter
I should ask for this hairstyle whenever
I get a new outfit
I want to ask for a hairstyle like that
like where it's like half half of the
hair is about like uh bounce bounce
together that's definitely not how you
say it in English
and ended in the back and like kind of
yeah uh uh curled
um
[Music]
you're kidding me
yeah I couldn't connect it
can you wink like that
[Music]
of course I can
yes
okay it's not so many let's go kill
Julie dinosaurs
today's my birthday
the contract requires me to show you my
appreciation it doesn't take thousands
let me just say it doesn't but okay I'm
so happy that I hope and spend it
together with my Osteen why did you say
your name there and carefree your
happiness and smile is gift enough for
me
thank you thank you for always being
there in time of need love utensil if I
can get a little greedy can I be
released from the ER or at least get
head pads
baby aren't you the one uh who can come
aren't you the one who wanted into the
usual room to begin with
weren't you literally asking and begging
for it
and now you now you are out
okay I don't understand
here wait
you'll stay in the usual room because
you you don't know how to behave
um
[Music]
thank you
I want to put the chicken in
ah wait do I have normal chicken as well
this is a birthday chicken
oh well I want to put it under the table
wait a second
[Music]
it's not my birthday today but
foreign
[Music]
can we have the laptop again do I have
the laptop here
[Music]
there it is
let's look at the super jets together
hmm
IO
I am so cute
yeah
[Music]
you guys can sit one after another
oh
[Music]
okay here is good I think here is good
and now we're gonna put this back up
here
oh yes I love petting my cats but we
want something different every once in a
while
pull up in English looking chicken right
[Music]
so cute
I have legs for a few moments
it's like your real mama Phoenix I am I
am I raised you guys I'm I am raising
you guys still
hmm I love you
are you still streaming it's been oh
seven hours we're almost done
you abducted us that is
that is slander
and it's slander looking fun time
just letting you know right now last
warning
last morning or I will have to punish
you
so thank you
[Music]
addicting
so I have fun in Minecraft right now I'm
watching uh catching up your uh
when I say t-lo that I always wanna read
the tales of something something
The Legend of Zelda archives and they
were so much fun I guess one of the
positives of watching archives is that I
can watch two episodes back to back yeah
also 10 11 out of 10 for the funky
swimsuit thank you it's a really cute
film isn't it
such a pretty art
I love it the smile is so cute thank you
Felix thank you
good luck catching up hope you're
enjoying it having a good time
thank you for your support as always
thank you for always
tuning in and saying hello
thank you soon
thank you thank you insanity
thank you
[Music]
Felix yeah
hope you can watch a stream live again
so maybe tomorrow maybe tomorrow should
be a decent time I don't know I don't
really know what time zone you're in
anyway Rick James thank you for a red
Super Chat as well wow no text for that
but thank you for the support and your
generosity I appreciate it thank you
Sean motion thank you for the pinky so
glad you enjoyed your gift as much as
you did
[Music]
I wish it could have been on time but I
didn't know he had skip boot until June
3rd oh remembering you fangirling over
his reply a long time ago and finding a
skip I needed to do this as a fellow
medical fan oh thank you
foreign
yeah
um I really really love this though art
style and the things that he worked on
every freaking character design is so
gorgeous
he has this
um insane sense for
a feminine designs feminine clothes I
know he also does the he kind of
produced an idol group and does their
stage outfits and stuff
um he really knows what he's doing yeah
it fascinates me
yeah very delicate touch he has this
soft soft art style it was really
interesting to see myself in his style
yeah so thank you so much for doing that
that was really really a highlight thank
you I I can't I don't know you can like
skip such like huge artists
I kind of want to do it myself but I I
explained before that it would be kind
of weird I guess I feel I feel weird
about going on Skip and commissioning
people for a fan art of me you know it
just kind of feels weird but if you guys
do it it feels a bit less weird
so thank you
foreign
[Music]
I would I think I would like have a good
excuse like I'm a fan so I want him to
draw me
that that still kind of makes sense yeah
draw me like one of those German girls
thank you soon
I played Italian because of his art yeah
for me I think also that the art was a
big reason of why I got into Atelier
games in the first place no I'm a sucker
for a cute and as as Aesthetics
[Music]
what the hell that sounded really weird
now that I think about what it just said
hey hey when I was stumbling all my
words
a big fan of that a ass yes sorry that I
didn't really want to say that type and
thank you thank you I'm glad you can now
fly and join us in the sky without
angering you papa okay success honestly
kind of weird being one of two flying
birds in this Army of chickens
it does get lonely up here with just me
and that owl
now we have you our fireworks assistant
phoenix flying high too
I was that was close to heaven
broken TV 2004.
thank you for the pinky
I missed your streams off the whole talk
and well I missed you glad to catch you
again Monday is saved
[Music]
welcome back
which whole talk though the most recent
that's not even that long ago
you didn't miss that much but thank you
I hope you catch up with the archives
too thank you
Bishop astonishing the pony gamer
donation putting channels
Alex Perez donkey and Aaron G thank you
for the pinky Adventure good luck on
your Expedition today thank you may you
find some interesting sites on your
travels today I didn't
that Temple for example and then the
amethyst and the the ice the blue eyes
and then we worked on Phoenix and so I
think we did well today I want to go on
other Adventures though I want to just
randomly go in One Direction
and find things very randomly with you
guys next time we'll do that
[Music]
no chicken
oh yeah Woodland fans I want to find a
woodland Mansion the wood mansion yeah
yeah and I don't think anyone has ever
found that before and in
mm-hmm
and merry circles making
um
thank you for the pinky let's go thank
you thank you thank you thank you for
the rest of the chat wait no wait that's
not a red one
ah
something moved around again I think
that's yeah because I'm still using I
don't know which version I'm using right
now from the Excel sheets
I think the one above is a red one
[Music]
see free kiss
is it queer Ramos Duncan I think this is
a red one thank you for the rest of the
chat yeah I can have been lurking since
December recently got around joining
membership really love all your content
and I'm excited to see what you do every
week hope you are as happy with what you
do as we all are seeing you gave me so
much joy you made make me a happy person
oh that's great to hear thank you
welcome to another tip I hope you enjoy
your time at kfb
I'll try to bring out more and more
content for the members
thank you
very much appreciated
in general
Harris thank you
guys you're waiting for me have I been
swimming for too long I'm sorry meow
seven hours man okay my voice is also
feeling a bit worse out so let's do this
Tian Muller dancing
Anonymous 247
whoa thanks for listening to spikes
is an fg8 magic face thank you soon
function
I wait
Korean
[Music]
um
not scratchy chair no no no
no no
[Music]
um
midnight thank you for the pinky
[Music]
thank you for all the fun streams
yesterday I love the karaoke it was
really fun everyone at kfb loves you
boys
[Music]
thank you for coming to my members only
streams and all the others too
thank you for the continuing support
thank you also for the pinky yeah
Minecraft is a blessing especially
hearing or say things like iron Pulau
Uber and biome well for Wyoming I know I
know it's not like that but I'm going
with when I first went with because I
think it sounds cuter
it sounds better
and polar bear and iron is really deep
in my veins so I can't really
I mean I could try but I don't wanna
you know we're gonna we're gonna if we
are too perfect if my English is too
perfect then you guys might think I'm
fake Australian but I want you guys to
know I am Australian and not fake
Australian okay I'm not a faker
if you know what I mean
iced tea I see
thank you thank you for your
understanding thank you
bones Malone dancing baby little low
donation
um congrats metal metal Enthusiast 41
dinosaurs
[Music]
you got into the meet and greet yeah
you you you you you
I was going to say you're gonna be
sitting on my lap like that chicken but
no that's not actually what's gonna
happen
it's not actually what's gonna happen
unfortunately
what
climbed up my out of nowhere
[Music]
baby
hmm
foreign
[Music]
you have fun up there
oh she's so cute why are you so cute
[Music]
yeah
yeah hi smoothie
this movie has joined the chat
they are getting impatient
uh amperature engineering thank you and
Wesley Wesley altaruki
foreign
thank you for the pinky had to rush home
so I can Super Chat you for your short
renditional twice cry for me ah if you a
short rendition if you were a member and
once the members only stream then you
would have heard the full version
unfortunately but I might sing it in a
public uh on the archived karaoke stream
not not members only again for you so
hopefully you'll be able to be there for
that thank you for having such a
well-developed taste in girl groups
hands to fall in love with you all over
again
ah thank you
well I I do listen to like girl Kpop
groups no no male cable groups at all
unfortunately I'm sorry uh I don't know
any of them
I mean I might have heard of them but I
don't listen to the music uh I prefer
girl groups
a million times
I don't know what it is but
I I just see all the charm in the girl
groups and no charm in the boy groups
I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry there's this one there's
one a few songs that I know like old
ones like Lucifer
and like something that goes like
okay no way that you know what I meant
with us
how the [\h__\h] it yeah
freak
sorry sorry sorry sorry
yeah yeah I know a few ones but I don't
really listen to them I like the girl
groups they're they're so pretty and
they sing so well and they do they dance
so well and I like the song so much
I just I prefer songs being sung by
females in general
most of the time
um
doesn't matter if it's K-pop or J-pop or
English pop music anything
most of the time I prefer a female
singers
okay some exceptions like Bruno Mars or
so or uh what what else Maroon 5 I guess
in the past not So Much Anymore now but
also a black got peace in the past as
well
yeah
yeah yeah Rick Astley
Shawn Mendes
I don't listen much at all to Shawn
Mendes
he's just a character in Phoenix 10.
okay
Crazy Taxi I don't know what kind of
game it is I know the girl is gonna play
it though you used to get
junk color
and thank you thank you
foreign
[Music]
with a 40-minute takamori video
and have been watching you and Cali
since I respect how open you are with
your emotions the good and the bad
and the compassion you show to me you're
The Shining Idol of Halloween wow
thank you but that's so interesting to
me to like the algorithm showed a tackle
a 30 minute takamoti video to you you
decided to watch it and that's how you
got into it
yeah I don't know if you know but I
streamed near automata on my channel
you're welcome to watch The Archives
uh did you watch that yeah did you I see
you in the chat did you watch the my
near automata playthrough
you seem to be a fan so become as Kiana
wait that sounds like you did
it sounds like you already caught up on
their gun because
I think you did you seem brainwashed
we are not okay yeah you you are
brainwashed indeed okay I think my work
is done here
I did yeah okay okay
thank you
welcome to 60
yeah
please enjoy your time here I'm glad you
decided to find me and support me
become as Phoenix become as Kiara
we are not account we are not a cult my
name is
Jesus moral is dancing
thank you for the red super chat
thank you sir no no message again it's
okay
you're shy it's okay thank you for the
support nonetheless
hey crystals dancing
[Music]
um
and now I just have to refresh
and hope that there's not too much ever
since I copied and pasted it for the
first time
uh it should be
okay ish
squirrels
foreign
[Music]
questions
I love listening to you singing so much
then Joe thank you for posting this
movie awards thank you
compliments about my singing
really mean a lot to me thank you
thank you
foreign
ew
um
[Music]
keep him vacation
I thought about it for a second
uh
[Music]
hello
how insulting
on something hello
fun Habsburg
loved your recent holidays changing the
format and the content really makes it
feel like your show and it was fun
letting us be sing to an audience was
cool to watch excitedly waiting for more
episodes come back thank you yeah I I'm
really proud of whole talk now
the singing
[Music]
um the stage really gave it another big
push in quality so yeah
oh
he called me a chicken in German okay
unforgivable cannot say that aloud out
loud don't make me read that
unbelievable anyway the rest was nice
thank you
[Music]
oh let me skip the bless Jets thank you
guys thank you thank you
and
um
thank you for the red super chat and
listen to your K-Pop song I love it so
much that I listen to it every day
congratulations on 1 million views
Oh you mean for uh spikes thank you
yeah yeah spikes reached 1 million
thanks to everyone's support thanks to
everyone listening to it
while I was annoying you a little bit
thank you
I hope you guys are not sick of it yet
please listen to it whenever you feel
like it
yeah thank you thank you title nickel
please continue to support me
in the future as well
please continue watching my streams and
listening to my songs thank you
[Music]
aimless
thank you for the pinky sorry I haven't
been around but I'm finally free
from wherever did I put you into the
usual room in celebration to freedom I
commissioned a friend who's a popular
artist on Twitter to draw some cute
title art whose titles
a better potential
and miss you and look forward to
watching all the archive on my week off
thank you
congratulations on your freedom whatever
that means
thank you oh I can't wait to see the art
[Music]
yeah I wonder who you commissioned
popular artists on Twitter I wonder is
it someone I follow I wonder
I Wanna Know
[Music]
don't tell me I guess you don't have to
tell me I'm looking forward to the
fitness project
thank you for the pinky
thank you for the pinky hi on that one
person that asked if you'll be streaming
in August the 2nd because it's my
birthday oh yeah happy birthday
I remember I just wanted to thank you
for everything you're a wonderful and
kind person and a very smart one too my
days are better thanks to your streams
it's lovely happy birthday I hope you're
having a great day
and are able to celebrate with friends
or of a family and are able to eat some
cake some good food
and treat yourself thank you for
watching my streams on your birthday
it's an honoring thank you
[Music]
donations
me too
rainbow boy dancing November 2022 2020
2022 2022 sounds funny thank you
developmental
Randomness and Spyro the Dragon of
course I played it actually got the new
one too but I never played it yet but I
played the old spiral of the Dragon
in my childhood and I loved it so much
yeah that was a good game
the good old times I don't know where I
played it was a GameCube with a
PlayStation was well I don't know what
it was
I I bought the new one though I guess
it's a remake yeah
that's so nostalgic I want to play it
for the Nostalgia
will you stream it you guys want to see
that really
I don't even know for what
for what platform I bought the new one
yes really it's it's a it's a platformer
though in some way isn't it but I I do
want the Nostalgia
I want to play it
maybe we should try it out I forgot
about it totally
it's a 3D platformer yeah that's how
how but I have it less painful In My
Memory than like for example Super Mario
Sunshine
as painful
it's also on PC and switch then I
probably bought it for one of those then
you also want to play already yeah
that's right at some point I'll play it
whenever I feel like playing a platform
game that's gonna kill me and my nerves
[Music]
much more forgiving than Mario yeah I
can imagine I feel like I feel like uh
Spyro was probably targeted at a younger
audience than
Super Mario Sunshine even I might be
wrong but that's the vibe I got
all the saves everywhere don't worry
um
crash no thank you if you want to watch
someone play Crash Bandicoot watch
Callie
it might be right
you remembered Sunshine being fun I did
I mean it is fun but it's also painful
and suffering
yeah it's a baby king
[Music]
I also suffered in Crash
quite good at games though
[Music]
one five one four thank you for the red
super chat wow thank you for investing
into Beyond Good and Evil 2. I guess you
also are a fan of the game
post so it feels like it you have good
taste I'm glad to have some people here
who played the same games that I did in
my childhood and I'm glad I was able to
share those those old games man you guys
need to play that that's uh
version PC answer to Zelda
please I wonder if you
get it
could you get it if you wanted to I
wonder is there there's probably no
digital version you probably have to buy
the city and insert it in your PC but
who has a city case now
who has that
[Music]
oh man
you see winning again yo
[Music]
is it not on theme probably not
abandon where what does that mean has it
been abandoned
[Music]
what does that mean you can't buy it
anymore
[Music]
a legal gray area
no license
you can't buy it anymore
oh
that is so sad
no license equals you can't Ahoy it
doesn't mean it is allowed
nobody owns it
nobody is getting money from it
I guess it is because it is not being
sold anymore
[Music]
maybe my mom still has a CD lying around
somewhere
[Music]
I might even find the second hand
version though
I mean it's gonna be a tough search but
yeah
[Music]
eBay
yeah well this is not really the game I
want to play on stream anyway I wanna I
wanna try a dark cloud on stream Maybe
and Spyro yeah well thank you G-Man one
five one four
thank you for enjoying the stream today
with me thank you for spending time here
[Music]
is
Hello thank you for your super chat you
also
y'all sad that I can't wear your work
outfit yet oh man that would have been
perfect if you had the apron already
it's okay it's okay you can make a
self-made uh kfp cosplay by wearing an
orange T-shirt or something like that
or
or an orange orange cap hat
all right or a cooking hat
wear a chicken mask no
[Music]
no no no no no no no
no no no no no no
yeah yeah yeah
no she know
so
[Music]
build the building stem aspect I barely
remember that but yeah I guess there was
something like that like some building
building aspect was there yeah well I'm
looking forward to seeing you at docomo
soon
[Music]
I'm sure at 87 thank you for the pinky
dinosaur and queen burp I'm an American
who booked a trip to Greece next week to
meet up with a Dutch friend womp womp
they just got oh oh now I just made the
call to keep going solo Oh as a
multi-continental bird what advice do
you have as a soul Traveler
wow okay cool
um I can uh uh how I can tell you in
Greece
everyone speaks English
everyone they they this is one of the
countries in in Europe where you'll get
around with English only easily
and uh also they are extremely sweet and
kind and helpful the Greek people are
some of the
most welcoming and cool and chill and
kind people in Europe that I have ever
gotten to know and I know a lot of Greek
people from work as well from previous
work
so I think if you ever lost or so you'll
have no issues because they are super
nice and they speak English generally
they do
um
now I don't know to which island or so
you're going but
um try to like try to maybe go on a trip
um
uh like don't don't only stay around
your hotel
that would be sad
uh try to go on a trip like uh there's
there's always some bus trips that go uh
over the island to some other special
place
and
and see some more beaches some different
kinds of beaches yeah but I it really
depends on which island you're going to
some islands and green Greece are more
like City tourism style islands and some
are more like beach tourism and some are
more like party tourism it really
depends
but please enjoy and don't worry too
much uh just make sure that you have
everything prepared when you travel to
Greece at the moment you have to
this is really important you have to
sign up uh 48 hours before you have to
let them know that you are coming to the
country otherwise they will not let you
board your flight
so make sure that you do that early
enough make sure please look it up I
messed up and I had to book a new flight
and go one day later
yeah um
I hope I hope you got the message I
don't know if you're even still here in
the chat
but this is really important this is
really important are you listening tell
Grace that you're coming
there's some kind of website that you
need to go to uh it should be easy to
find the info
I think you're probably the airline or
something sends out information like
that as well
don't end up like me and also don't
break your neck in Greece like I did
[Music]
all of them thank you
please enjoy Greece
[Music]
I want to go there again
I want to vote her again
it was so nice
uh last time I refreshed
[Music]
looking for the top foundation
any rooms vacation
[Music]
soon
album thank you for being here Diego
carizo donation bellstar thank you thank
you for the pinky hate Andrew here's my
first ever attempt at a pickup line hey
there Kiana you are glowing orange like
a rare drop item because that body is
legendary
[Music]
what
I'm so stupid though
like I can't imagine someone saying that
to me in real life that would be kind of
cringy I guess
but here it's okay here I like it
nothing better you could say here on on
in in a Super Chat
thank you everyone for watching I'll
leave now I'll see you tomorrow
[Music]
yeah let's go bye
phone
I still have to figure out how exactly
to do that but the participation is
going to be members only
but everyone will be able to watch it it
will be a public stream but
participation members only and I will
probably like post the the code or so on
the community board and then you guys
can try to join that's how it's gonna
work tomorrow
garlic phone
she on phone
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign