[Music]
so
do
[Music]
lagging sorry don't mind it guys let's
be fixed soon lagging
here we go no no one more time repeat
after me
kick kick
[Music]
[Applause]
you know what that balance
[Music]
i got to take the apple away i already
put an apple on you you shouldn't have
an apple ant
it's funny how i'm lagging but you're
not lagging but that's okay last time
um you were not moving at all this time
you're moving
a lot noise
[Music]
hello i'm probably also gonna um at some
point start moving normally don't worry
guys don't worry guys
and guys we are here once again to teach
le shark some wisdom
and some language because knights
yes deutsch yes exactly dodges today
because
sharks have lots of potential sharks are
very smart
animals so yeah yeah right
right hit that chat sharks are very
smart
normally we're gonna see if that's right
we're gonna see about that let's see how
many apples you can earn
this time i got a lot of apples for
yogura
do your best to get them yes
okay and uh gouda
actually has made uh an amazing
observation and told me like one minute
before the stream and i'm absolutely
blown away by the observation do you
know what i'm talking about you want to
tell the viewers
yes um uh i was like hey kiana this is
like deja vu because the last time we
had a language
lesson and it was f what did i say
because after if people are saying f
give it a moment this is uh hello
what can you do
[Laughter]
oh we're not back oh we're not back tell
me when we back are we back oh we back
we're back really
quick
i said
i still have some very passionate
feelings about youtube because of the
past
10 days them being very mean to me so
you saying youtube is shyster makes me
very happy
it's true i speak the truth oh i just
remembered it
actually i actually have as a
as a membrane
we barely use that yes
thank you thank you uh okay it seems
like we're stable now i'm also not
lagging anymore but knocking knock knock
knock knock knock
knocking on one yeah my big wooden head
[Music]
all right so where were i yeah you i
don't think you finished your
observation
please uh repeat your observation go
down
nah my observation last time we had a
language lesson right
just it was it was a similar a similar
what would you say
time time uh time timeline time frame
[Music]
you explained it to me much better
before the stream
will you help me yeah okay so right now
this is the first stream after my german
re-debut yesterday
and here i am collabing with gooda
teaching her is he looking so angry now
teaching her gym and uh
you remember the last time i taught her
japanese was exactly i guess
also one stream right after my rew was
it really but yes
it was at least shortly after so yeah
thank you
yeah it's such a coincidence that here
we are again
once one stream after the debut is
our collab so maybe exactly
if i ever die again and never do a
re-debut again we have to schedule
a stream to keep that going it's a
tradition now
yes but this time we slip into an
alternate dimension where i'm the
teacher
and i teach you actually
yeah let's do that next time you're
gonna teach me i'm very curious to what
you're gonna teach me besides shark
facts
which you obviously ran out of already
ah you're gonna make me laugh i'm
thinking
you get hiccups from laughing yeah
because i suck in a bunch of air
that's pretty cute that's pretty similar
to oven
looks cool you two drunkards
[Music]
let me say my intro uh in in deutsche
uh yes
okay yeah ha good talk
it's been high gal guru
this
[Laughter]
yeah that's pretty cute but um i just
want to put as a side though
that before the stream she asked me what
shark means in german so this is not
she she shouldn't she didn't know that
or
spoiled again although i think i
mentioned that before when i taught you
japanese i think i
mentioned to you before that hi in
japanese which means yes
actually means in german um shark so
yeah you should have they've come full
circle
it all comes back to shark hi
hi it all comes back to shark
what's that that kind of uh illuminati
music starts playing
how does that go again
oh it's just the x-files name oh oh
that's the x-files
oh
that's it have you seen x-files no
oh that makes sense it makes a lot of
sense but i know
i don't have melody but right now i just
can't remember the melody goddammit
[Music]
anyway okay i'm gonna teach you i gotta
teach you
dutch yes okay okay basically for
everyone
who was here before in the japanese 101
we're basically gonna go
for the same phrases pretty much and
but yeah this time just in german so
let's get started
in german by the way uh it does not have
the same meaning as also
in english what oh
in german yeah it's the same writing but
it's more used like
uh so like a film word uh
so for example so let's do this we i
could say i so lasses
beginning i saw a beginning
yeah yeah
why are you so good when you speak
german god damn it
goddammit okay okay so hello let's get
started with hell
let's see how much you remember because
you claim to know some german
i think this one you can do what is
hello in german tell me
hello
[Music]
is uh exact noise
that was not hard also it's very very
similar
and do you know however
how to say uh nice to meet you
no we're doing german germany
but i'm really proud that you remember
what i taught you in japanese
uh the east they're good
to meet you
[Laughter]
okay i gotta say one thing here um the
keyword i'm using is the japanese
keyword so i can't write the german
umlaut
the ones with the dots on at the top i
can't write them
yeah but um let me let me explain for
everyone
basically oh it is the o with the dots
on top and a is the a with the dots on
top
and is the you with the that's on top
understand all no what
is
okay repeat after me that the a with the
two dots on top is an
and the u with two dots on top goes from
[Music]
i didn't know we were speaking in whale
language
oh wait
[Music]
it's pretty hard to say actually yeah
is
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah that's why you used it
but you can always if you don't have the
proper keyboard you can always
um write
oh oh yeah while we're on it um how
about before we get really into it
how about you and me sing the
german alphabet song yes
um i i don't know how the melody
uh continues at the very end but we're
just gonna
go with the flow go to the floor we have
some two very
uh artistic melodic
people here right ah yes
ye okay so uh
we're gonna we're gonna uh i'm just
gonna
i'm just gonna sing it slowly and you
maybe try to chime in
i don't know how we're gonna do that
obviously
yeah okay i'll
[Music]
ob
you don't remember that
wait wait my view my german views are
making fun of the way i pronounce
create cool whatever cool i guess
whatever
for you
[Music]
how does it continue
god doesn't know the alphabet surely
[Music]
oh
okay and that's when i get lost with the
melody then i just go like x epsilon set
[Music]
and then set
wait do you have the same melody for the
english alphabet song
yeah oh then how does it go in the end
w x y and z now you know
my ain't no enough
now you know yeah oh my now i know
my everything is next i want you to sing
with
[Laughter]
okay okay okay
this is already too much for me
[Music]
oh my god
okay so you think you can do it together
with me
[Music]
we actually don't include that
that's very kind of it i was very kind
of you to include
wait wait you just you just include
right
now but we don't include that those are
uh outsiders we don't want them in that
song
once but they're part of the alphabet
but they suck and they can be easily
replaced also by the way did you know
that there is you should know probably
you do know
there is a shaft s have you heard of it
it's the ss no no it's a b
no it looks like a v it looks like a v
yeah like a big v
yeah uh actually some people write it
with double
s some people i think you used to write
it with shabbos s but these days people
write it i think
everyone ranted with double s because
shotface s can always be replaced with a
double double s
and do people even know what i'm talking
about here
some people are writing it in the chat
so that's what i'm talking about
yeah okay shop is as maybe we in
australia sell shoppers as the new
germans
the people who are going crazy right now
say esthet but we don't say that in
australia we say shop is okay
it's um
okay okay okay now we got the important
things down i think we can continue
so um yes so nice to meet you
was uh here this is uh
supposed to be a uh or you could say net
that's this canon to lemon
let
[Music]
so directly translated means pretty
means you the canon means no and sulanen
means to know
[Music]
wait what can i can sue
from australia yes i can teach german
very well so
whoa
what
[Music]
that is that is
don't make fun of the majestic german
language
oh nice you said that so beautifully i
was just about to ask you to repeat it
and there you go
i don't even have to ask you
all right and i was you nailed that one
and that has to get nothing the money is
we like to say um we like to say
when you say i nailed that one you say
captain
habitat yep
one more time
[Music]
is
no okay actually um in german that is a
slang
word to say um to do someone
to nail someone actually i imagine in
english
probably some people like there's so
many words to say that so i feel like
in english maybe anyway let's move on
my name is okay you know that one come
on
uh my my name
is
do you know that one call me from
well i guess you could kind of stay from
um
in some in some situations but usually
you would say
come outs
[Music]
where do you come from again atlantis
right wait what
wait what atlantis yes
wait really wait i'm getting confused
i think i would say atlantic i think
atlantic is that the same thing i think
atlantis and atlantic i think is the
same thing
atlantis is the place it's not no no no
no
oh wait what wait what's it like
[Music]
atlanta
i don't know what i'm saying forget this
forget it whatever
you come from um from from heaven
because you're so pretty cell you say
it's coming out
east
um as you can see many words are very
similar in english than they are
in german so actually uh you know the
angel in english in german we say anger
so you say
ich bin ein anger
angel mm-hmm
[Laughter]
[Music]
damn it can't fool this girl damn it no
don't think
i'm a chicken
that is i will not tell you because okay
even if
even if the chat will tell you you will
probably not be able to pronounce it
oh she's gonna oh no she's i hear you
tell me
i forgot about my cherry red keyboard
i hear you cheating oh that's the sound
of a messenger that
people used to use did you know that
you're you're a very old shark
[Music]
do you want your freaking apple why not
do you want your apple or not
uh yo yes
you better be real quiet daddy we better
be real quiet
okay so i i have one special thing to
teach you
um australian dialect hello
[Music]
and i might something like that yeah
yeah i'm pretty cool so
actually it's called uh it's uh
um s-e-r-v-u-s
services
[Music]
yeah or you could say you could even say
grasty
[Music]
why are you laughing no just because
it's so stupid
okay i was like oh is there something
what do you do no no
no no no no i would never teach you
something wrong
[Music]
[Laughter]
with savage
[Music]
another way to welcome
australian people is um
no one really says dad but yeah
that was
like that what do you call that like not
the upper thighs but like the under
like under under the knee hello calves
it's like hello calves yeah
hello to your cuffs yeah it's a weird
greeting isn't it
[Music]
i'm actually all right i think maybe
maybe because like there's a there's a
weird
like dance uh it might be australian
when you keep on hitting your calves and
make sounds with the
cuffs
[Music]
and i i think you hit your calves in
that dance
repeatedly and be like
you guys are weird you're weird
you're weird
i love how well i've been lagging the
whole stream
but you're moving smoothly that makes me
happy no more cardboard
although it will be hard to now place
the
the apple that you have obviously uh did
you obviously deserve now
it will be hard to place it on you when
you're moving so
keep still good don't move you have
earned an apple
an outfit and yet has to
either now you have einen
[Music]
did you say that on purpose yeah oh
yes when you say yeah it [\h__\h] kills
me
because you're not like yeah you're like
[Laughter]
y'all
[Music]
[Applause]
can you count um past ten
nine nine
oh my nine oh my god this is killing me
okay
moving on next slide
we're gonna do the following phrases how
you i'll find my
i like my favorite colors and i added
this one i don't understand because we
will need this very often
um how are you i think you know this one
i think i heard you say it before
uh uh
[Music]
oh scrambling in her brain putting words
together sweat and sweat in shack
[Music]
she wants that apple
you thought i said that i don't know how
can i say that
maybe i'm maybe i'm giving you too much
credit huh
oh
yeah you can also yeah you can just say
the kids that's like a short version
wickets
um
the e in the v is a silent
it's like a lo long we call it in in
german we call it
a language i think uh-huh how long
it is yeah so it's a it's silent
it makes an eye longer
so when i say you can say
i am fine in german i think you know
this one though
it
[Music]
yeah you can just say good i guess but
the full sentence would be
mia kid ask
me
yeah actually saggled is also how we
call
um like uh like in school when you get
uh an a we say actually
we do it in numbers by the way we don't
do abcdef we do one two three four five
six actually in fun fact in australia we
only have the grades one two
five and in germany they have the grades
one two six
where's the rest of them where's three
four
one two six one two five
wait did i mess up
no i think i thought
wait wait i'll
[Music]
okay
okay so what i meant is
i gave you the benefit of the doubt that
you still don't understand what i'm
talking about
is that we have in australia we have the
note the grades
uh one two three
four five which is one
two five
[Laughter]
such a stupid idea that's so
[Music]
don't ridiculous oh my god and then in
germany it's one two three four five six
okay so that's that
okay and then number one the the eins
we also call fairgoot uh yeah it's very
good
anyway you don't deserve this knowledge
good hug
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah it's like um it's it's going but
yeah not really
okay oh my god and then
if we want to say i like something
you can ask this question i like
it do you know how to say that
the plural of apple is apple
um
yeah yeah good job
good job but actually no i shouldn't i
shouldn't i shouldn't praise you too
much right now
more praise give me praise okay
okay okay if you're gonna do the next
one well then maybe
um do you know how to say some my
favorite something
is my
no i have no idea okay that's okay
[Music]
links oh actually yeah in this case i
got
capitalize glee brings faber and
something something like
at the end and then liebling sleeping's
in front of it
mine live
[Music]
yeah or for example uh my favorite
school subject mine
my liebling's [\h__\h] is
are you laughing he's a [\h__\h]
not funny oh [\h__\h] okay you're losing
your apple in this round my dear class
no
[Music]
is
okay okay that's extra homework good job
wow nice
i'll praise you for that sure
and i don't or i do
understand you can say do it wait do you
know how to say that
nine okay
uh
if
however i don't
i don't know if you deserve an apple
affair
please avail on my only if you know
how to say please
[Music]
okay okay okay i
[Applause]
how do you say brain
[Music]
um please don't believe her that is
obviously a lie
is
[Applause]
and in japanese uh gehen someone
some japanese we are a reactivities now
gehen means like um
like dirty dirty or something so don't
you worry the dirty person
yeah we're talking about
[Applause]
oh my god we really you
um entertained me so well that i have
i am uh inside problem i have a time
issue
i oh yeah thank you you know this one
come on speed round
oh oh i say it every time in my streams
in the super chat readings
uh obviously that's
that's
which people when i used that in my
super chat reading they thought i was
saying
feelings
there's many ways to say that but yeah
uh thank you soon is the one that i
always use thank you
and by the way the oe is supposed to be
the the oh with the two dots on top yes
yes
just can't type it with my keyboard
right now got my japanese keyboard
because i'm cool
you're welcome now you say thank you to
me so i gotta say you're welcome which
is
i i'm disgusting you don't know how to
say that
um
it's not always your welcome it can also
mean please so
depending on the situation and it's used
differently
yeah petition or you can i guess you can
also just say
[Music]
what
pretty good pretty good actually okay
and then uh i am hungry
it's been hungry um close very close
just because the words are so similar
okay let me try with a german accent
it's been hungry
yeah hungry
hungry nice nice
hello hello hungry
i am kiara
[Music]
[Laughter]
no no you are my child good act
did you see that the conversation i had
the other day
on on twitter uh where i was talking
about your drawing and i was like
um you don't want to take me to the
aquarium every week
yeah i saw it it was fun
it's fine we'll do whatever you want to
do then that's fine
it's respecting the aquarium is an
educational and fun exciting
you know places sightseeing and stuff
it's fine i understand
i understand you look good yeah are you
throwing a tantrum do you want to
have house arrest house rush
house
[Music]
i wouldn't mind having you know one week
um
stuck with you and in
yeah that's it but we can do more
thank you
okay and then we say you are beautiful
you know how to say that
[Music]
yeah you know how bitter we say peter
directly translated means please please
pretty but yeah we use it as you're
welcome
so means you're you're pretty
actually i guess you could also say do
this
okay and then uh shark fact
is high
[\h__\h] but i feel like that sounds weird
so if anyone in the chat has a better
uh what
if anyone has a better uh idea for that
why are you guys even laughing it's so
similar to the english one anyway
shark fact hi [\h__\h]
hi tips
[Music]
you could also say hi i listen if you
because you guys are being too immature
and you're like hahaha she said the [\h__\h]
word
i'm gonna teach you some [\h__\h] words in a
moment you you watch out
no and then
let's go to the aquarium for example
we would say lass
here we have some german grammar that
everyone is so scared of
if we say aquarium then the tsu turns
into a tsum
tsum a clavium but for example
[Music]
i think it's always some actually or
not always okay for example
uh it turns to that you are if we say we
go to the school
or ah or if we go to gouda to gooda's
house then we can say
lessons two without the r without them
yeah so yeah it's very complicated but
we don't want to get started in the in
the grammar
uh thing here why does it do that why
well why shouldn't you know that didn't
you study german my lady
i don't know
it's okay we don't think too much about
it
okay don't have to be so exact it's a
you know
grammatic on behalf
grammatic is tricep
[Music]
okay we've learned that so uh yeah
i actually thought we're gonna we're
gonna do this all in in one hour but
uh wow it's taking a bit more time in
the future
no problem though no problem we have a
few more things to learn
and oh wait oh wait the apple do you i
think
you didn't do that bad this time i'm
gonna i think i'll give you yeah
i'll give you an apple here uh how many
apples do you have now good huh
[Music]
all right all right you're getting all
those apples you can make some some
accessories
[Music]
i want to see where it's from originally
it's not german it's australian plus one
for the australians
yeah we
[Music]
dude
so one day if you come to australia i'm
gonna i'm gonna
uh bring you to lots of restaurants
where we only eat desserts
schnitzel oh that's not a dessert but
yeah you were trying to say that one
hmm actually i can cook schnitzel
stay
actually there's um there's a funny
there's a funny swear word in german uh
that includes the schnitzel word
um it's called um
fiction it's in it
[Music]
yeah i don't know it's so random it's
just a
[\h__\h] schnitzel like uh yeah as
i don't know for some reason that exists
that's even funny in english
[Laughter]
[Applause]
yes
okay i had fun let's continue i had fun
in there
[Music]
yeah no normally you would say you would
write the double
s with a sharpest s with the with the b
looking s but i don't have it on my
keyboard so i'm using double s
e he have it he had the sparse or
in in uh this is past tense but in
in
[Music]
presence it would say
right now you say ichabeth
oh god it's so cute when you speak
german oh my god
all right let's meet again if we say
goodbye then we say
you could say um
i guess you could say auf wiedersehen
but you can also say
um
[Music]
i guess it's kind of weird i guess we'll
just say auf wiedersehen yeah i always
say that at the end of my streams
[Music]
yeah it literally means
on singing again
[Music]
there's an easier way to say goodbye oh
do you know it
the most common yeah cheers
just just just it sounds like a kiss
like too
but it's just did i i feel like i just
heard your stomach growl
did you hear my stomach i feel like i
heard it
a little bit what do you what do you say
what are you saying
when you're hungry do you remember uh
[Music]
is
you're not getting back that apple
you're not getting involved
[Music]
certain people gonna question my ability
as a mother again so
oh here you go i'm not letting your
stuff she already has two apples okay
i'm not letting her starve she's not
important to the boy development for the
board of
education normally you should keep
humans anyway shouldn't you uh no
if you go back in the poi uh people
watching without intent to eat people
are fair people are friends
not food okay yes
actually that is a misconception about
sharks
that we want to clear up we want the
people
to have some um what do you what do you
say
we want some uh
come on help me help me out here
sharks are so misunderstood so we want
um
some uh god damage
we want to raise raise awareness
did
that is so far from what i wanted to say
we want to raise awareness for sharks
because shanks are being misunderstood
day by day right
yes day by day
[Music]
what good eye is a vegetarian shark
i guess that's not true sometimes
we like our apples and our veggies and
our fruit right veggies
yes you guys are veggies i told you many
times
this is why you're so small
[Music]
this is why i don't bring you to the
aquarium that often go down
that's not gonna that's not gonna work
this time
no
[Music]
you're trying to speak german here
anyway i think we can get rid of the
farewell uh because i don't know i don't
i thought i thought i was going to say
alfie that's in there whatever ah good
work is a good
or
[Music]
yeah and you know how to say i love you
right
[Music]
do you know how to say i hate you
no okay wow that's so
disappointing
[Laughter]
yeah yeah that's how you say i hate you
but you would never say that to your
mama right
nice
[Music]
[Applause]
hmm
[Music]
please give this my iphone
it's not moving i can't put them on you
keep on moving stop moving
stop moving it's okay
very good yeah
[Laughter]
all right next up they have some swear
words hell yeah
okay there's this there's really really
really really bad
swear words in german language but i
don't feel
so comfortable teaching you such really
bad ones
so we're gonna try to stay somewhat
uh safe pg i see yeah
if you don't feel comfortable saying a
certain word
let me know uh
okay although they're sometimes a bit
more extreme
in the german language i feel than they
are in the english language i feel like
maybe that's just me because english
language isn't my first language so i
use these words a lot in english
but in german it feels like much more
rough to me
i don't know sounds too real
too close yeah yeah maybe that's it
anyway so crap would for example be
saiso
[Applause]
well let me add one to there uh uh
dammit is
out no no we're not speaking
japanese here not
[Music]
what we often say is for them to
scheisse which is which means damn crap
damn [\h__\h]
[Music]
they're down to shyster
[Laughter]
wrong classroom but
you can literally just say idiot it's
yours
yeah it's just pronounced differently
they're dumb did you
or you could i guess also say dumb cop
which means stupid head
coach yeah that sounds a bit uh sweeter
than saying
idiot it's like a more childish way of
saying it
do i say don't call friends
don't
[Music]
i can't reach over there
well you should have eaten your veggies
right hmm then you could have raised
over there probably
it's gonna stay over there let's see if
you can earn them back by the end of the
class
otherwise you're going to stand at the
corner of the class facing the wall for
a little while
no not the idiot corner
the old
okay continuing efu um
[Music]
see i feel uncomfortable saying that in
german now that's such a [\h__\h]
i say [\h__\h] you so often in my english
dreams but saying it in german i feel so
bad about it
i think yeah
[Music]
what am i doing wait what did you just
say
okay okay okay i thought you said
something different that was very
worrying
okay okay okay continuing
stupid cow is there a is a bit more you
know sweeter
and don't make cool that's
uh only children say that what like
there's a cat meowing at me
[Music]
he repeat after me tell me
yes he's a stupid cow i think like
children use that a lot
[Music]
do me cool my cat is so sad
hello baby say hello to gooda she's a
very bad student unlike you
see we say hello oh she's she's running
away now okay she won't say hello
she doesn't like you gouda well no
now i think if you would ever meet her
she would love you
[Music]
how do you say it's how do you say cat
in gym and you know that right
is the female word and kata is the
male cat there's different words in us
yeah it's katsa and katya
cuts it nicely
ow
good job good job learning some proper
german in between but now we go back to
[\h__\h]
yeah you knew it already yes
i learned it from a book oh good book
good book
very good book and now here i am
the word um [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] yeah um and
there is a bunch of them i feel very bad
for you for saying
them but um for example you could say
yeah or you you could say um
[Music]
um yeah that's that's looking good let's
keep
let's get without that yeah um
[Music]
you have absolutely no reservation to
say that
it just means um it describes a person
that who is like uh like
messy also me
no please don't call yourself
a slump
[Music]
did i hear you better than um yeah you
don't don't call me no
[Music]
adjective i guess is uh pig pig
slam pig pimp yeah some pig yeah
and a messy person would i i guess peace
love it but no one really
uses it that way even though it was like
the original meaning
yeah anyway oh so yeah go
die would be um
[Music]
yes yes that one is not so bad i'm very
relieved
um or let me
skip the the second to last one one
moment let's go to go to hell
and you can say that good to cali
because she likes going there
um
oh
yeah that's hell that's how
we say hey yeah we say actually for go
to hell we say
drive to hell
i don't know how you would drive to hell
but i guess i also don't know how you
would go to hell
like but anyway for some reason it's a
drive to hell in our language and then
thank you for saying that then i don't
have to say it it somehow seems more
acceptable when you say it because you
don't you're not fluent in the language
so i feel like we can forgive you
thank you thank you for taking that off
of me
and then in an australian dialect
there is this fellow word that i use all
the time
and that literally i guess would mean
old person or like a dude
and we say oyda
oh yeah yeah i say that all the time
but it can it can be used in like when
you're angry you can say
or the fictitious but you can also say
like when you're happy you could be like
oh my god this is so kind and so i so i
use it all
the time it's like a fiddle word yeah we
use it all the time i just wanted to
remember
[Music]
it's an australian australian dialect
filler word
very useful in any situation
[Music]
don't make it
oh no
i'm so sorry guys i feel like
when people learn german they all want
to learn swear words and if i wouldn't
teach you swear it's today i feel like
people would be
you know angry
wonder if i don't it's like you're like
like a small child who picked up a sword
and just cannot stop saying it even
though you shouldn't have
learned it oh like a parrot who keeps on
saying this
hey i've actually seen parrots who do
who say that
oh god well i think we wanna
we wanna finish that off with um
homework
um i will give you uh um
an offset this is outside of english uh
um how do you how do you say in english
of
something like a long long essay
you have to learn this offsets by heart
and then
come back to me in next time
oh okay okay uh now
repeat every sentence after me
okay we ah wait wait you
you definitely deserve a bunch of apples
for for you know
saying all those squares
[Applause]
we have to reward children saying swear
words obviously
yeah he had so many apples okay
now repeat after me
via sinned
[Music]
you can still
is
[Music]
hanging
hey
[Music]
yeah last time you really took a long
time to understand what i was doing
yes this time i think i made it i mean
obviously because i did it last time it
was obvious i was going to do it again
but it
it had to happen it had to happen so now
you remember this essay yeah
yeah and then next time you sing it for
me
yeah it's like a it's a
this is not what you think it is
this is a famous it's a famous german
love song
yeah sung by rick astley with a lot of
80s syndromes
i don't know no i don't know what you're
talking about
this is sung by a certain
fog chiara
i'm surprised you mixed it up with
something else obviously this is very
very very famous from a certain singer
who
by coincidence has the same name as me
but
yeah um how
[Music]
yeah it's good it's very famous
i guess all over the world that one is
really famous yeah
that one is an actual german song
and everyone a family
moscow
wait wait moscow is uh in russia
but it's german song i guess it is was
it
what's that actually really german why
is that batman
why
[Music]
you can actually really on my channel i
have challenged dmca so many times and
nothing really ever happened because of
that so you are welcome to sing all
kinds of songs on my channel
oh god oh boy uh
hit me with jinger i'm
out of the jinx i'm bad with jinx though
i'm going to keep my mouth shut
actually i only know like a japanese
version of that song
and from like an idol group called bendy
squibble who covered that song it's
really weird i don't know why they
covered that song but
yeah there's a japanese version of it
yeah yeah it's really cute though it's
my favorite idol group actually
benny's combo have you heard of it
yeah no well i will send you the song i
said they have some really
weird songs actually i will i shall
educate
how about one day we're gonna have an
and japanese idol culture 101 for sharks
okay yeah i can teach you about all my
oh my favorite actually they're
mostly all from hello project a certain
idol agency
and i i would love to teach you about
them because
i i used to go to like a [\h__\h] ton of
concerts uh
of that my idol agency when i lived in
japan
and i bought like tickets in the first
row for like several hundreds of dollars
and and i walked yeah and i was wearing
like the t-shirts and i put like
i put pictures um printed out pictures
like i paint them on my t-shirt and i
put like a
uh the scrive a merchandise scarf and
and merchant i merchandised everything
and i had a [\h__\h] ton of pen lights and
all that
i was like a real real real bad old taco
and i was dancing every i knew every
freaking choreography
that's dedication yes yes is there any
group that you or like uh artists that
you
feel like just like so passionate about
like i'd feel
felt about these idols
no i mean other than hollow life
no oh my god is the only one oh
sweet sweet and now you're part of it
though
that's great that's great maybe one day
you know we obviously want to sit and be
on stage like
like the other senpai's and sing
together with them on stage and maybe
one day go down we can make our
dream come true of singing this german
love song together on stage
and then cry on stage together
yes cause it's such an emotional
beautiful love song
i need some tweaking it needs some
tweaking here definitely
a little bit it'll be perfect in no time
all right
you have completed once again a shark
class a 101 shark class by takanashikiya
congratulations
ah thank you so much
i have to say you i noticed some
re rebellious face in you today
wow every now and then you seemed to
have challenged me takanashi kiana
she said through clenched teeth uh-oh
i'm gonna get my butt
then we will we will talk about that and
to
see how long uh you're gonna stay in
your home
or how long i'm going to throw you into
the ocean without floaties
[Music]
okay you can leave a flower for your
killer
okay okay yeah as long as you say so
then now i won't give you those floaters
but when you act up too much then the
float is poof
[Music]
be careful okay
i think that is the first german thing
you said to me when i first asked you
like about your german skills i remember
you said i'll be good
to become and i cracked up oh my god
i need to know that they're coming yeah
[Music]
isn't it nice to hear that from your mom
thank you for coming to my classroom i
hope
we can do something similar again i i
can now only teach you
english maybe uh maybe i can try to
trick you in english
or or we can do like wait after one on
one
does it continue with one or two or does
it continue with two or two
uh uh i i i don't know
we can make it up we can do one or two
okay okay
apparently it's one or two apparently
yeah
so maybe we can continue with german or
japanese one or two at some point or as
i said i'll teach you about idols
someday or
as we also mentioned you can teach me
something too
maybe if you managed to teach me
something new i would love to hear it go
ah
i'll teach you the language of atlantis
oh looking forward to that
all right then thank you very much and
very fitting
my ending greeting is actually and in
german we say
we design so let's say it together shall
we
yeah okay and in german we say
au vinasie
everyone i'll see you tomorrow for near
i'm streaming near automata and there's
a
members only stream tomorrow as well so
look forward to that see you guys thank
you for watching
thank you thank you cheers
[Music]
bye bye bye
you
[Music]