[Music]
la
a
[Music]
la
a
n
[Music]
Kitty I'm so
excited I'm so
excited let's
go hello hello hello how you
doing this music oh my
God I remember
this I remember this scenery from okay
so I think it was like early like spring
2019 so almost like what 6 years ago I
totally I don't understand time anymore
it feels like 10 years
ago um but like yeah like six five six
years ago is when the alpha I was
literally I've never been in an Alpha
clo I think it was even closed it was a
closed
Alpha I have never been in a closed
Alpha of anything else
before yeah that was pre no it was kind
of wasn't it kind of at the beginning of
Corona um and I've been waiting on the
development on this since before the
alpha because this is an anime online
mmpg
from Bandai NCO purposefully to be made
in the style of tales off games so that
is combining my two favorite things when
it comes to gaming tales off games and
mm especially anime mm
RPGs so I love both of those things and
M and then after the closed Alpha they
went so quiet it took them
ages to finally bring this game out
which seems to be one of the issues that
lead to the state of things now because
it just took them too
long um yeah and then I guess they got
like you know kind of like outshined by
other things uh it just took too time
too much time
um but I've been waiting so long and
honestly I lost hope at some point that
it would ever come out because it was
just too quiet around it and suddenly
like what was it like last year they
announced the launch of the Japanese
server first which uh I think the
Japanese server started like end of 2023
or so maybe so a little bit less than a
year ago right oh my God didn't even
didn't even last a year but well it's
going to last a year because so for the
people who are out of the loop this game
finally came out right and they said
Japanese server first but it totally IP
locked can't even get in there with a
VPN apparently yeah people are getting
banned um so like really blocking the
outside world from it as much as you
possibly could then they said Western
like Global release in summer 2024
I've been waiting so long for this
[\h__\h] sorry I love this game I love Banco
so I'm just sorry I'm just really upset
with the
frustration um excuse my language we're
not sponsored though so whatever um but
I've been waiting so long this like
positive and when I say I've been
waiting so long for this [\h__\h] it's me
saying how positively excited I was for
it to come out and then they say oh you
got to you got to wait and another half
year I was like okay that's going to
hurt but I just I'll just continue
thinking of blue protocol as a thing
that you know in my world and that it
just seemed like it disappeared so just
going to ignore its existence the
Japanese existence like that the server
exists it just doesn't exist for me
because I can't play it anyway and I
wait I wait I wait until summer and then
summer was here someone was here and
just like I'm like hey it's June where
there's no information yet no update hey
it's July still no details about the
incoming server for Global hey it's
August what the hell and now two days
ago two days ago they announced the
death of the Japanese
server saying that it will close in
January
2025 less than half a
year and that the global Service will
never happen
bro I feel like I waited my whole life
for this because okay for anybody who's
like into the same stuff you must
understand anime mm RPGs they used to be
so popular like what
like
s eight years ago 7 to 10 years ago that
was my [\h__\h] I was playing that kind of
stuff all the time and you know they
don't have to be super a like high
quality like those anim M mm RPGs a lot
of them were really like hm like not
high
quality games right but we still enjoyed
them and it was so fun like I've played
so many of them and like a new one
releases like every few months and then
you jump to the new one you go up you
you grind your way to the top of the
ranking and the next one releases you
start from the beginning you keep on
grinding grinding and that was you know
my favorite thing to do and there were
so many and then somehow it died because
of like games like that that kind of
quality of a
game now because those I guess because
those anime Ms were always like pretty
low quality they eventually fought oh
why not put this on a phone like a phone
can handle this kind of low quality game
but none of I don't think any of us
anime mm RPGs enjoyer MPG enjoyers liked
the prospect of that because we wanted
to play the stuff on the PC because it's
easier to grind and like syn everything
into it if it's on the PC it's just not
not really like we don't want it on the
phone like I don't think I don't know
anybody who liked it to be on the
phone um and I wanted the screen to be
bigger not on the [\h__\h] Mini screen on
the phone but then everything like
started to be on the phone and I I was
just thinking ah it's not going to work
people are not going to fall for this
people are not going to enjoy it uh
they're going to come back to still like
release things on the PC right but like
it really [\h__\h] disappeared I did not
expect this the whole genre just
disappeared
and I don't know that was so sad for me
because like a big part of my gamer life
just like disappeared with that um
maybe there's still like a few small
ones popping up here and there but you
hear
nothing and I mean there's some some
games that are like Reviving right and
they're like Reviving these old
nostalgic classic anime when RPGs like f
for fun has the server uh but like I'm
not getting primed for that somehow
because it seems like they're not
answering their emails please let me
play your freaking games um but H eat an
eternal F fun please answer your
emails um anyway
so when after the big drought of no
games no anime RPGs to
play when they finally when I heard that
there's a an anime I can't [\h__\h] say
it anymore anime morpg coming out that
is oh my God in the style of tales off
games by B Namco my favorite gaming
company
TM oh I was so excited I was so excited
but this is how things have turned
[Music]
as a legit xgm of fliff in Thailand I'm
glad you like the game you know I I had
this like core memory of mine
re resurface the other day that you
won't understand probably but um I I I
had this memory Reserve I have to tell
tell you about it it was like um I was
pretty like high level well and in like
um a high-profile Guild back in the day
and so anyway um I I was like I had some
issue where I had to contact the GMS so
I was like at GMS in the chat like at
GMS hello I have this problem and they
actually replied to me oh my God and
like back in the day you just felt so
special when the GMS would talk to you
and and and then so there's this thing
like if you have a big problem the GMS
they will actually teleport you into
like a world that nobody else has access
to the GM world and once you were in
there once it was a huge Flex it was
such a flex because no one else can get
there and you only get there under
special circumstances so I had this
problem and they were like oh okay are
you fine with us like porting you
teleporting you right now and I'm like
oh my God
yes and so
yeah then I was like teleported into
this like World of nothingness it was
like this huge desert or something empty
as [\h__\h] and it was just like two GMS
like standing there and like talking to
me about the I don't remember what it
was but like you know yeah GM Island
literally yeah it's an island yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah they helped me with my
issue and then they teleported me back
and I was at that time F of one had like
this Arena this was like a while after
the release where they already like put
a lot of cool stuff in it and they had
this Arena um this like relatively small
fighting arena PVP Arena like you kind
of have to teleport so to say into a
different world it's not connected with
the rest of the world where you can just
like walk through no you have to
teleport and then you're there and then
it's PVP and I like teleported back in
there and I was like I just came from
the GM Island and everybody's like wo oh
what good what was it like what did you
do and I'm like I have connections
now Court memory man may be so happy to
remember that recently like oh my God
yeah that happened feels so
special yeah ain't you jealous like wow
yeah it was such a privilege oh my
[Music]
[Laughter]
God I saw Tails remaster project yeah
yeah yeah but like I already played
Grace's F so I don't really you know I'm
not like um like I would have preferred
like a Fantasia like one of the older
games first Fantasia rebirth please
those kind of games no what GM is game
master god do you know nothing
my
God sorry I'm this has you know this big
story like I need to tell you guys about
it do you guys want full screen though
maybe I should do full screen cuz you it
is a beautiful game it turned out to be
pretty beautiful and I need you guys to
see the glory of it there was an opening
that I already I guess I don't think
I'll see it again um so I guess you guys
won't see it again it was like a low-key
tutorial was a pretty flashy interesting
mysterious opening and
tutorial
um I think this Window Des best Lots ofi
H okay I mean I don't mind because like
I can show more of my body to
you yeah so right now I'm playing on
today I'll be playing on the Japanese
server because I am in
Japan so I'm in Japan I'm going to play
on a Japanese server it's going to be in
Japanese obviously because there's never
going to be an English release at this
point so hon originally like literally 4
days ago I was still thinking there will
be a western release but I thought well
it's still going to take a while right
because apparently it's not happening in
summer anymore so let's just play it
once while we're in Japan and then never
play the Japanese server again just like
as a kind of like a taste and then two
days later we get the announcement that
it's never going to release I'm like
okay well then I guess I'll play maybe
even more than once we'll see
Insanity can't believe it but yeah it's
because Bandai Namco online apparently
went
bankrupt which made me really worried
about Bandai Namco as a whole but it's
very separate I suppose hopefully bco is
not going bankrupt
right
right and they didn't no that's what I
have heard that's why they're kind of
closing no okay let me not that if it's
I don't know that's what I read I read
that people were writing
that wait are you saying Bandai Namco is
not but Bandai Namco online
is cuz it's like a different subsidiary
yeah yeah yeah yeah B an ancle certainly
is not
[Music]
of course yeah that's what I'm saying B
not yeah yeah yeah
yeah remember sh know Alice yeah I
remember that's a long time ago too ah
yeah B onine filed for
insolvency isn't that um bankruptcy I
don't know
[Music]
it's not the same but it's still bad uh
okay in
insolvency ins is that even how you say
insolvency insolvency I don't know but
okay
well let's ikim my show guys let me know
if it's like too quiet oh we do get the
opening tutorial thing again oh let's go
all right cuz they didn't say I went to
the character creation a little
bit and I suppose they just didn't save
that that's good see this is so
mysterious it's very
mysterious I guess it's kind of quiet
let
me do you hear it h surely you hear this
you're hearing
this just is it better
now you want louder it's stop much going
on right now here she really want lava
okay blue protocol baby let's
go so excited I can't believe they're
taking this away from me before I even
get it I'm so
salty who is this what what is this who
is this R soul of a person I don't know
shattered pieces what does this mean
what does this mean the enemies are very
very tailes off but like futuristic
tailes off
Vibes isn't this too loud I don't
understand how this is not too loud for
you guys let me make it quiet
again okay well I already know this
anyway so we just got to like get a
little bit into it this is the tutorial
before making a character which is
interesting I don't think uh I saw that
in any other anime mm could
before I knew it was loud you guys are
like me me me me me
me but it's a bit
quiet it's normal it's not loud yeah
because I turned it down
[Music]
again so this is like the guy on the
cover will we meet him will we become
him will
what who who
knows both too loud and too
quiet yeah this looks awesome I
know but the character creation is
awesome
too I'll try to like translate things
that are important but I mean generally
anime RPGs there's not like like usually
there's not too deep of a story and and
menu is just a menu and you know
if I feel like something needs to be
translated I'll translate or ask me if
you want something specifically do we
translate
it
so we dissolve is it us is that us and
then this Soul goes into the new
character that we're
creating makes
sense will we'll skip that we'll skip
that because I don't know about
copyright on that one that's the opening
song If you want to hear it it's
probably on YouTube but say this the BL
protocol we yippe the world is on the
brink of Devastation now is it this is
English now is the time to unite march
on with friends and strangers and defeat
foes beyond your might travel for space
and time to change the future Beyond
this fight is this purposefully rhyming
unite might
fight just purposefully
running let's go character
creation I I don't know if I should try
to do my current self or more like my
default self because you can do
two-toned hair
color oh no no no no uh all uh uh
what yes oh yeah here okay so let's see
there's like
different like things to start off with
and we can change the size of us of
course we can change how thick we
are and the boobies I I'm surprised they
don't become much bigger than
that we can change the light here of
course
cool and it seems like we can make
ourselves NY but I'm not going to push
that oh cute we have different poses to
look at we're just going to go with this
basic one for
now wait isn't this game shutting down
next year that's what we talked about
literally for the first 20 minutes of
the stream
welcome what is
[Music]
this
this this gives me a taste of the
physics I see
oh is that all that's going to be moving
huh the hair and the bbba well okay fair
enough okay then there's these
hairstyles and the cool thing is
something I haven't seen before in any
other character creation we can mirror
the
hairstyle that's kind of cool gives it a
little bit more like
variety
so I is there ponytail is that a
ponytail that's a short ponytail huh
yeah so I thought that this one looks
the most like my standard
hairstyle twin tails are cute I
know but like you know if we want to
look like Wawa it's got to be more like
this and then so
here in so many MPGs or or not even MPGs
but like other RPG games where you can
do character creation I've noticed that
like orange or other the cool colors are
always so like ugly but here look the
anime colors we can actually get a
proper Orange going this one also looks
pretty Orange um depending my orange
tone in my hair is different sometimes I
think I'll just go with this and then
here my only problem is that the the
two-tone hair it just starts too high
and I can't adjust where it starts I can
adjust like the grad GR see ah this is
the no sorry that was
the the brightness of the color as well
but I can adjust here like the the the
blending of it but it's like you know it
gets lower when I blend it
less but it's still not very low like
it's so high and the most of my hair
will be turquoise like that so [\h__\h] I
don't know if I really want
that instead I I don't know but that
won't look like me if I do a different
hair
coloration and then like I noticed for
the twin or yeah like here example in
theory this would start lower if you
imagine the hair to be let down that
would be way
lower than if we look at this that
starts already above the
ears so I wish it was like
that this hairstyle is so cool this
gives me like Fire Emblem
Vibes very Fire Emblem I put a lot of F
Well the the thing is there oh wait
there there's a
ponytail they're they're like triggering
me with like giving me uh a gradation
and then gradation I don't
know this
is can
i a
should we do ponytail on
default I don't know girl that's an
ombre like we could if we did ponytail
it's got to be
blue but
that's see nah it's also too high it it
starts that's relatively low but like no
cute cute but this makes me really
indecisive I'll just I'll just do it uh
you know what I'll just freaking do it
like here and
then as low as
possible before it becomes a straight
line it will just look like there's so
much
turquoise anyway face shape can be
adjusted uh all right let's go with that
oh actually that might be pretty similar
to my 3D face shape and then oh oh no
see that's
cool what's my skin
tone kind of
like kind of
peachy I'll just go with that and
then I don't it's pretty peachy just
anime anime girl baby I'm an anime girl
H okay eye
shape let me let me perceive myself
that's that's actually probably spot
on this one's spot on pretty
much and then the p h no this is the
matuge uh
lashes that
one's that one's pretty spot on oh you
can make these brighter too oh they can
become Orange
huh
interesting oh you can change the angle
here too oh well M mine are not
that angled but sure and then the pupils
my P which ones are the
closest there's no skulls no skelington
I have never officially acknowledged
that those are skelington I've always
said they're
not but it would be funny if there was a
choice like that
this one maybe cuz I have that line
yeah it doesn't it doesn't really matter
no it does not oh those are kind of nice
and
[Music]
clean
oh see maybe maybe if they would have
sponsored me to do a stream for this at
release time maybe maybe things would
have been different ah bco I thought you
love me I gave you so much
love and then you repay me by canceling
the release of the Western version of
this
game just release it let me like do a
stream on it and I'll I'll bring all kfp
to the server you
know that's all you had to do that's all
you had to
do um oh perfect I
mean yeah no I would I would do the yeah
here
mhm or you can do odd eyes if you wanted
to on this oh oh
interesting the the contrast I
think oh actually that's maybe the dark
contrast is better oh
saturation this is saturation oh
yeah nice is the game out only in
Japanese only on the Japanese side and
they cancelled the Western release and
they're killing the game January 2025
already all
right that's a little bit too fake
that's a little bit too F I need I need
an in between to be honest
but if anything I'm probably on the
Finish side or the
angle e can't get friendlier than that
huh all right
nose honestly I don't see much
difference in these anime noses but it's
cool that there's a
choice the illusion of
choice can you tell a difference guys
not much it's more like a shadow that's
changing not much else but yeah there's
a tiny difference but not really and
then the size like how wide the mouth
opens actually oh wa wait wait we can
change expression that might be more
helpful because
yeah it's hard hard to
tell I don't know default is fine I have
a pretty big mouth
though uh yeah this is lips and uh you
know
here beauty marks and tattoos and you we
could have uh sprinkles on our
face uh oh yeah you would make them like
darker PKA dots on your face whatever
you want to call it but no we don't have
any of that there's some more ah the
blush I do want to have I feel like this
blush is very similar to mine we're just
going to make it Pink see that's exactly
my
blush that's exactly the style of blush
I have
like this that looks like me that is
100%
me
oh oh those are
cute yeah cool stuff but no need and
then there's voices in my head see now
now especially from the view in the back
you can
see it's way too high and I would like
to give it more of a blend smudge
smoothing out but then it's like the
turquise would start even higher so that
definitely bothers me and that's what
made me think like maybe I should just
make it fully
orange
M
oh no no no no no no no and lighter is
also like bro
M but you know who knows how long we're
even going to play this you know we
don't have to think so hard about it but
like this is how oops
it that that literally looks like milky
Queen that's cool that actually looks so
cool but that's not my
hair whatever okay more like but that
looks
Brown is that does that look orange or
brown to
you how about this that's that's
good oh yeah wait isn't there a okay
okay there still there's still more to
come
cute brown is just dark or
orange I mean not exactly but
okay okay so we have voices but let's
see
which one sounds the most like me yeah
I'll give you an
evolution
no
no byebye I also thought the first time
I heard these that free is more like
me byebye
it's between these two
maybe it's too mature actually oh maybe
maybe that's similar to
me I like it though
[Music]
[Laughter]
most people say free I think for sounds
like
p
no no no it does
[Laughter]
not okay let's go with this
one so you can change your starting
outfit
and this one's obviously much cuter so
we're going to go with that uh you can
also kind of change the combinations
though you can make a combination of the
two starter outfits which is pretty cool
too like we could do this one but then
with a sure it ah with no tis
oh but no I want this oh but I can just
take off my hat okay I will do that wait
I can choose to take off all of these
huh
well I mean no we will wear a bottom I'm
a part-time
Warrior when we will wear shoes but I
prefer the boots I think so we can do
this combination what do you think bar
legs actually feels kind of wrong to be
wearing bar legs how about tights with
this bright I like it with the bright
white outfit do I want to click here do
I want to see that oh okay it's
underwear wait what do you mean I'm
having underwear turned off does that
mean I would be naked underneath let me
at least okay who knows what what that
would lead
to all right now we can choose a class
but I heard that you can change class
already at level four again if you want
to to any
class um so this
is yeah kind of a a tank I guess
this looks like a damage dealer two axes
twin Striker this is a blast Archer okay
damage dealer but
distanced this is a spell
[Music]
Caster Is A Healer oh what is
that heavy
Smasher a heavy Smasher
what is that weapon what is that weird
Hammer that's so cool I guess this is
also kind of
distanced yeah no like
close combat but also mid-range
combat Blitz Lancer
wow cool
Lancer beat performer beat oh B it's
called beat
performer well obviously if I'm playing
alone that's probably not going to be
the best choice I don't know heavy
Smasher sounds
cool
what it was a big popular class on
release no surprise because it seems
like the most unique one to
me although
maybe let me see the other skills
here it feels like pretty slow combat
maybe for us it would be more fun to do
something like twin Striker because
that's more fast Speedy
combat you
know just for the sake of streaming it I
don't know it looks like my true because
it has a sword and a shield in it
true heavy
snipe oh oh she charges it all the
way Rock body ooh but
storm wall W yeah cool but kind of feels
slow maybe I should go with a faster one
I also would like to try out Archer
stuff but like oh I don't know like we
should maybe go for close combat okay I
will just go with this
unless yeah ler
maybe seems to be
close close
combat oh yeah oh yeah okay what do you
want Lancer or twin
Striker
Lancer looks cool I want to be a
Lancer let's go Lancer
[Music]
yeah oh wake up let me pour some
water everything for you please say save
this world you want me to save the world
what a
surprise star future the future of the
star open up your eyes wake
up
okay good morning
[Music]
[\h__\h] save BL protocol yeah I'm
going to save flue protocol
single-handedly maybe I don't know could
we they already announced the closing
they're not going to go back on it will
they I remember her she cute
do you have a billion dollars will bring
them
together they want me to translate this
guys it's like oh going to buy you
time when I give you a sign attack him
from the side
okay who are you don't worry about
it we'll just run
away
yeah oh
music person what are you
doing what I don't know what that means
that seems kind of like a poetic
phrase SOI okay
information
information uh yeah y uh uhuh
uh space okay middle click middle
click show CA ah okay uh focus with
middle click left click for attacking
normally and I learned right click in
the tutorial yeah dodging a c around
uh are you basically tell me to not
press space while dodging
ah
ah wait I didn't focus on him
ow ah that hurts doesn't it Mr
Goblin wow I like this combat with the
land I think we did the right
choice is there more wait the camera
moves too fast for my taste I need to
get used to
this that was already
amazing right is
yeah she's praising
me thank
you oh oh ah was too much for
me I literally just woke
up what but this is
Paradise bring me lead me to
it I want to go there
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
yeah do something about the future yeah
yeah yeah GM
Island how are you good
morning oh it's kind of laggy do you
know me I'm
[Music]
glad once again my name is f y School
do you remember
fainting it was hard to carry
you that those ruins were discovered
recently and most people don't know
it why were you
there now it's not lagging anymore
interesting oh what do I do did you hit
your head when you fell from the sky
oh you don't seem to be really
hurt oh what's your name what's your
name
Ki besides
that oh she has a voice yeah yeah I
don't
remember I see so you
too am need your
classic you're alone even though you
remember even though you don't remember
anything that's lonely
me too I also don't remember anything
from the past so we're the same
huh live translation
by okay I know I'll help you get back
your
memories since you help me at the
ruins so let me help you
too in that case let's go
when you seem uh more healthy then let's
go there again and we can find maybe
some
hints okay before we
go can you please oh oh don't sign it
it's a [\h__\h] up contract that you'll
never get out of
probably oh she's evil wait I forgot
yeah I forgot this one even though this
was in the closed
Alpha oh suddenly her voice changed
she has me as her I'm the link from
today
on excuse
me [\h__\h] how did I
forget
ah she says that I I was so good at
fighting it would have been a waste to
let me
go ah she says her name is f but she's
also known as beautiful woman
Eternal beautiful
woman oh but she'll help me she'll still
help me regain my
memory little [\h__\h] you little
[\h__\h] okay we have to greet the owner of
this
Hotel on the first floor
okay what my blue protocal bus what the
the the dawn c i I thought it said the
the the what the blue what the circus
what what that font is hard to
read wa there's
like whoa what's
whoa huh cursor mod
[Music]
yeah want
to
wow do people see my
message
he say I'm a little chicken do you see
the chicken icon at the bottom
left should I maybe I mean everybody
knows H life right should I write in the
chat I'm from H life please give me free
things see I was I was always
streaming somebody has acknowledged me I
think a TW
twinkler is sending
stamps oh oh pimp someone's
name they're name oh oh they're reacting
to
me SK
wow wow wow wow oh w w wow I want I'm
trying to like stab the windows and
stuff but doesn't seem pass Possible Oh
reacting to me wow but yeah when I asked
on uh Twitter in Japanese if
anybody
kaky do they know that I feel like these
people know that they're on stream right
now but like it didn't seem like
anybody uh on Twitter like was playing
the game cuz I was asking like hey
Japanese BRS can you help me is
that I'm very good at this game oh I'm
sure you
are inter ah interact F the okay
F Pro level mhm for
sure you oh but that person is answering
things I'm saying on stream they're
definitely
watching we oh I'm up here
yippe
[Music]
yippe hello sir nice to meet you now I
can't read the
chat oh you finally woke
up wasn't the bed so comfortable not as
comfortable as a hotel I stay in in New
York
for
real you little [\h__\h] I don't know how
much I helped you until now just forget
about
it now you got to now you owe me even
[Music]
more what you're an idiot for going to
those ruins alone
[Music]
it's hard to to translate so much oh my
God you're so in love of me aren't
you it's okay this person from now on
will um do everything for
me seems like you got with the wrong
people in trouble oh
no h why didn't talking about I don't
know
[Music]
oh where are you
going I'm going to you know help her
find clothes for her
memories all right take care it's
dangerous outside of course it
is
uh listen to everybody around you for
your memories yeah make sure okay
okay sounds good I remember this
part oh
whoa whoa okay my PC lagged I saw OBS
lag I don't know if that's from the game
oh okay here we have like the
manual
interesting wow so much
nongo High hand skill
board tactical skills class abilities
bace abilities uh you can see the videos
and the details of it every skill BL
blah
blue sure okay so
oh do I have these
H do I have this
skill and then next I I can upgrade it
okay outfits can I get some cash shop is
there cash shop outfit cashup
tole that's my
inventory where can I get cute cashup
outfits please tell
me Lego Nas leg Lego NASA store that
sounds like that sounds like it oh but I
don't know like how to even pay for it I
probably couldn't unless I maybe if I I
think the Korean stores have like pay
safe cards kind of stuff like that you
know something like
that is it even worth it when I'm like
only playing this for a day probably not
oh okay it's like the newest like
promoted
outfit uh GMS can you guys give me some
of these like things
please I
mean I mean
promoting your game even though it's
already announced to be
killed what are
[Music]
these season
pass season
rank
[Music]
huh what are
those thanks for the
membership what do you mean it's a trap
I always like make use of the cash
drops AA I notic this GAA in Japanese
they call it
gasha oh gesture oh I got a
gesture
wait so much so much to look at I can
get 11 times for
free okay much
yeah laggy
whoa wa OBS
lag wait this is so
cute the game is making me
lag are you hearing me normally
though oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh I got a
veil wao wao
[Music]
did I get this
outfit oh my God I got to get through
this so the lag is
over w w w
w okay are we hello Mushi
Mushi oh my God
audio lagging a bit too oh
no maybe I'll turn down the settings of
the game the the the
quality I I think I got one of these
outfits in the gacha just
now wait
what oh oh wait your reactions are
pretty slow
guys I think wait M wait I can go Goa
for the mount too it's a flying carpet
oh but I don't have okay this one's not
free this one's still
free apparently the first time well it
will lag again though
guys everything's lagging hey
still oh are you back
okay I think I got to make it lag again
because I have enough another chance at
the free gotcha 11 times for this Magic
Carpet I I H I'll have to lag lag
again I'm I'm sure it will lag
again it's fine now yeah it will be
laggy again probably the gacha makes it
laggy so so please hold I'll try to skip
through it
then okay here I
go I could like turn this off the end sh
too late oh oh oh
oh oh it's not lagging is
it oh my God it's so
cute you get to see
it
yippe oh it's lagging this time but I
don't think I have a special one this
time or do I H
H celebrity gold Choice B okay what are
these season
pass okay okay I didn't get the flying
carpet but I can do one more free and
for the one I couldn't also do one more
but I think I got an
outfit who is
she a blue one
okay she's cute I like
her celebrity gold okay
interesting uh you still owe me a free
one over here let's go
[Music]
what on my screen it's blue maybe on the
other screen is
purple my two screens are very
different this one's white/
silver I don't understand any of these
items yet they mean nothing to me so I
got an outfit if I leave this and I
go
here can I wear
it ah I guess it's in
my
inbox
oh
yeah what are these things see this one
think is the
outfit
oh item perfume box F
Papa drop
drop what are
these what are these I got the same
thing twice
here I got some poses I got an item
getter uh bookie G
oh this is like for crafting I think
like making the um success rate higher I
think if they have
crafting IM imagine relief time
some
ability I don't understand any of this
it's
okay A dro gives you drop rate
really oh season two of friend oh [\h__\h] I
guess it's out now okay oh season pass
the one
seak point tamalo season rank got Ichi
aali
Royal
Pass rank rank K
Banas rnas store ay Rose orb the cocan
the rank of
[Laughter]
I don't understand what I just read
because I'm focusing too much on reading
it
funnily I'm yatan yeah I'm
Yan reading like Callie wait does she
read like that on purpose
though Royal passo sudo Royal Pass
no Hoka shun Kiku
[Music]
ohas what I don't know it doesn't matter
probably because I'm probably not going
to really make use of this will I
um ah is h ah this is uh no this is just
information on everything I
think uh communicate another H oh it's
like a like a card yeah yeah yeah
Adventurer
card photo photo where is my photo well
whatever oh that's my friend called I
guess H it's out there
now a do B board Quest okay here is
Quest this my first Quest my main quest
cool
nowo very nice Quest oh side quest oh no
this is okay this is like gcha daily
like phone game kind of daily quests
like log in you did it you freaking did
it what is
that land Fox imagine is that a pet I
can
summon w w w w wish
list wish list
[Music]
doesn't matter probably again I'm
probably not playing this for very long
okay here we go oh wait
this
no
Mount okay imagine seems to be things I
can cast and this is Mount I can mount
this
fox
she It's
Kind okay so now I should be able to
wear these things
though H where's no what where did that
thing go I thought I got an outfit I
only see the
veil I don't want to wear the whale
necessarily where M ah yeah this one ah
do I have to open it oh I have to open
it ah it's like this so I'll probably
like as long as it's in the in the in
this like present box you can still
trade it but if you oh wait it has the
cuter things if you open it then you
can't trade it anymore maybe it's bound
to you at that point could be the
case
oh wait it's orange too wait a [\h__\h]
second how come it's orange how did they
know that it's orange
[Music]
what that GM's are watching me that GM's
no
let's
go cute let me look at that then
um did I not save do I have to save it
oh oh I have to save my
choices
hi W I like it it kind of fits the
Lancer like Vibe too I
think
okay um okay let's let's go out and do
stuff can you zoom in a
bit maybe I can will I though well I am
H oh
cute oh this this like Quest Place
mhm it's a big
town take your time to get used to it
yeah I I I remember running around
during the alpha test a little bit um
doesn't seem like much
changed seems pretty same
where the monsters are you can fight
there as much as your heart
desires cool I have more of a main
character energy now I like it hly we do
look like Fire Emblem
characters okay before you go outside
you have to prepare
something first of
all let's go to the gate place thing uh
the place that you saw before uh there's
no need to hurry uh take a time to look
around if you if you want to it's
lagging oh my god oh oh something things
make this game lag wait let me try to
like uh lower the quality or
[Music]
so uh
shift okay
okay no no it's not YouTube because like
I see it already lagging in OBS oh my
God there's a lot of people
here wait does that make things lag too
huh
shut
up
H lag lag lag lag lag
lag lowering quality
now um but I guess it's really just on
the graphic oh my God wait maybe I can
uh turn off the names of
people
party okay
let's get rid of that cuz that's
probably making things
[Music]
lag
hello guys I'm I'm trying I'm working on
it right
now oh my God there's so many settings
okay let's see oh my oh help help the
lag I think these people were are
looking at
me wait the lag y it wait let me get let
me sorry guys thank you for the welcome
but I need to go somewhere where it
doesn't lag
maybe M can you Max the number of people
View
is this lag like because my PC is too
weak or it's just the game being way too
heavy how about low quality no I don't
want to go so
low turn off the people no I don't know
if I even
can
thing or
[Music]
lower the random range
mhm ultimate skill
FPS
FPS okay
and let's see oh oh
no I changed the size of my screen too
now it messed everything up but that's
okay um and I lowered like so many
settings it's not lagging right now I
hope this will help right now
let me replace things you can lower the
amount of people that you
see which is interesting oopsie
uh where is
this I low with the amount of people I
see to 10 people
so where the hell is
is ah there it
is game is
back it was just gone out getting some
milk now chat where are
you there you are hello big do let make
you smaller oh that's too small sorry I
changed the the overall resolution of
the Stream
although it seemed to already um help
when I changed another setting in the
game here I don't know if it's really I
don't think it's necessarily resolution
of my OBS but overall everything
together you know seems to be helping
it's weird how this layout is like
slightly not the right size for my OBS
window whatever this this doesn't seem
perfect but um I'm just going to go with
this pocket size cute pocket chicken
okay let's see if it will
lag oh oh oh oh oh see they like this
display and undisplayed people when I
move around that's
funny I'm sorry if you're not within the
lucky 10 people who are being
displayed it seems to
work looks better wo what is that
guys give me free
[Laughter]
stuff but I want to try like okay it
didn't help when I was lowering graphic
much so can I make it higher again I
feel like it was other
things um postprocess Shadow like maybe
can I have a few shadows and a few
textures just a few it's just one one I
want one Effect one Shadow one texture
one grass please this is grass amount of
grass can I have uh oh enemy H I want at
least like
here
scaling okay let's see did that is that
bad is that bad oh I'm not lagging okay
this is acceptable one grass a crumb of
grappies how come K you will not get
banned I'm in Japan right
now I'm in Japan
otherwise I probably would get banned
what is that cute outfit you look like
so cute you guys are so
cute yay you're also in Japan well I
think we all are okay let's follow this
Quest
marker I wish I could show you guys in
like the best quality wait let's see how
far can we see how far we can
go you know I just want to test the
boundaries maybe post I I don't know
what that does what about anti
no not anti-aging
anti-aliasing can I get a bit more
texturing a bit more of this I think
anti-aliasing makes the borders look
nicer right stress test oh oh okay okay
here we go that looks more beautiful oh
that looks actually so much
better it could be even better but we'll
do it like this look at my look at my
fans and this is capping them to 10
people how many are there in reality I
don't
know F to to wait it says I have to
speak to Festa is she really
there welcome to Japan wait is Japan a a
ban word what the
hell why did you get the car carpet I
didn't get the
carpet wait let me look at your mou what
is that cute little
pig oh cute
kute wait did I also get a mount ah but
it's like the Imagine Mount it's
probably different from their mounts
what is that bunny it's like a it's like
a Australian bunny kangaroo bunny Kango
bunny well maybe it's called it's
probably called Kanga bunny I can
imagine game master what who's game
master there's a game master here that
would be crazy wait is this a is this
person the game master it has a wait it
has H what h
they look too op to be a normal person
but I guess like in M PES you can end up
looking pretty op what is this a
chicken this is a blue protocol chicken
they look very
special I'm staring at these people
interesting
okay
cute wow shiny
Mount woo
look at those dorky
eyes okay sorry guys I'm I'm so
slow colorful book
book can I run oh yeah is is that
running no I guess it's not
different oh wait what is
that cute that looks like it could be
one of our mascots like a YouTuber
mascot what what what wait no
that's it's a watermelon but cut on the
sides and for a moment I thought it was
like
the the thing the the that game the
the drum game or the S
thing a reference that wait wait wait
wait where's my a here what is that
fish so good
talk to me f yeah t yeah why did it
remind me of that is there watermelons
in that
game this is the um
Plaza of the gate uh before you leave
one thing I have to tell
you aha this thing right in front of us
it is
probably a teleportation portal that's
probably what that means
means you can teleport around in a
moment be somewhere else yippe well you
should uh try it out right away it's
easy just touch it oh these portals are
everywhere in the world
surprise I did not expect this game to
have
portals
okay uh I guess I'll touch it with f oh
nice still no lag right guys we're good
right I think so okay then let's go out
in the world into the world we
yippee we have fast travel now
yeah okay wait what does my quest even
say what we're supposed to
do just kill like a certain amount of
mobs or something I didn't see
[Music]
Asteria
AIA that sounds so tails
off uhhuh a lot of
ruins you might find Clues to your lost
memories I met you over there in those
ruins so you should go
[Music]
there justy found it recently so I don't
know much about
it how come you've been there and you
must know a lot about
it I don't know
anything I only know what I
[Music]
know thank you oh my God why does this
person look like
me uh a in the f
there is
enemies okay so there's their they turn
red when they when I see them as an
[Music]
enemy their levels and so on yeah sure
seems like uh oh M imag oh wait all is
it not like a one time only thing
okay hi they're telling me to use my
imagine Mount how do you know I have one
I got it from the
gacha oh I can set it as that
oh awesome we have a mount already and
press
G oh okay
cool wait
so oh look at
[Music]
that nice wao what's with your Mount
though that looks SI
Jee I me I I I kind of want to walk
though
wait what the mount I have is a freaking
mob everybody's watching me fight I feel
nervous yay but they're not stealing my
mob I remember in the alpha test there
was so many people fighting over the
same mobs it was like really rough hard
to like find a mob to fight
there's something to pick up
there how to pick
up what is
it thank you is that working on me too
even though I'm not in a group with you
no I don't think it
is you just want to flex your skills huh
wait this person is just like chilling
there sleeping sunbathing in the night
who wouldn't wa what's going on why do I
hear battle music why do I hear battle
music literally have you have you had
your eye on me
bossan you are dead to
me mats mats no a mine why would you
take that you're high
level makes no
sense I think even if you're not in my
group you could at least heal me right
probably so guys you can heal me that's
what I'll let you do
okay wait does it tell me where to go ah
okay look at that view look how the city
looks so beautiful from here lit up so
lit I'm surprised there's so many people
following me even though nobody replied
to my tweet hey my mob you guys don't
need these tiny baby mobs anymore
[Music]
oo this is so nostalgic I I don't even
know was there even a quest during the
alpha test because I had no idea what I
was doing I did not know what I was
supposed to do at
all I felt like I was missing some
critical information what is that is
that because I opened the chest or is
that someone's
skill I am
unsure probably someone's skilled though
because that would have been way too
flashy how that pig walks is so
cute wait I have a skill that I never
used before maybe I shall use it
that dude's on another level which one
they all look kind of crazy to me are
you an
NPC nah that's not an NPC
right this an
NPC look got
the you're sending me
hearts someone's twinning with Kata yeah
twinning hey what are you
doing my mom wait it looks like they're
fighting it but it still has full HP
what does this
mean maybe they're not fighting maybe
they're just poking
it see guys we could have we could have
if they made a global release of this we
could have
huh wa could have been playing this
together wouldn't that have been so
nice I was dreaming of that for a long
time was my plan all
along yeah I would single-handedly serve
how about you can continue like getting
rid of the Japanese server but just make
it a global
release I I don't know if I can save the
Japanese server I don't have that much
like Japanese influence oh what is
this oh
tree
n but maybe I can save the global
release I could bring in other Holo
members too from holoen and and then we
we would have even more power not just K
of power K of
power
yeah
man I think honestly I I think it would
have
worked not just kfb would have joined
all all the fandoms would have joined
guys am I going into the salon or are
you guys able to join this huh is it a
dungeon
oh oh seems like it I don't think
they're going to join me on this one
still
please okay they're telling me now to
use my skill which is funny I haven't
used it yet so I shall do that thank
you H
okay
oh can I use it again oh there's a
little cool
down what I was using it but it got
canceled because he hit
me oh there's more
oh nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice
easy oh oh there's half an hour of
time what to clear the whole ruins wait
oh no it's already done I had half an
hour of time to press q no more pressing
for we're pressing Q now
M ah it seems like I was right with you
you are
strong yeah you were you were uh fainted
all all the way over there in the Deep
deeps of the the
ruins press Q for quas
quas
quas early W good afternoon hello oh oh
the people are back okay guys I'm going
in
bye I'm going
in Festa is here oh there's talking me
why you want to burn me stop burning
me uh um sorry I'm having a
conversation around here you know oh
something's on the ground I'm having a
conversation with
fer oh it's imagine seed
oh you even forgot about the Imagine
seeds well you really forgot everything
huh yeah well you know that's what
happens with
Phoenix's you
understand imagine seeds
are stones of your will I don't
know
[Music]
angram that's really complicated
uh they do cool
stuff there's no downside on having it
so anyway you find anything here
no let's go back to AEL because there's
nothing here we should not be here if
it's
[Music]
dangerous the voice is in my
head damn it what are they trying to
tell me they're telling me to save the
server oh he likes her oh one the
coincidence that we
met his name is Jake he's the best
Adventurer
here uh but but like allegedly like on
his own he gave himself the
title well I already went through the
ruin so you're too late go away go
away what do you mean what's with the
monsters inside huh well with my strong
hands they were gone and dead by an
inant ah he's doubting that she did
alone that that person is amazing I
don't see his face around normally did
you just come here where's your
adventure
registration she didn't register herself
yet blah
blah oh we welcome cool people all the
time so rookie you have to uh register
yourself then you can count on me
because I'm Jake and you welcome anytime
[Music]
he's such a [\h__\h] boy as always
um uhhuh okay well registering you might
be easier with this guy so uh let's go
to us police he seems to be someone cool
who I don't know I can't translate so
fast oh oh you're you're you're in luck
for meeting us here
yeah yeah yeah my memories
yeah why you don't think they'll make
that the official translation oh
money oh I'll get rich for your
work so let's register you they also
have all the information there so maybe
something will lead to your you
regreting your memories
so we know what to do let's go to Jake
even though I hate
him I like how her hair
moves he's
jiggling oh I get it uh this is when we
got to use the
teleportation oh remember when we touch
that teleportation thingy all right
let's use it right
now okay you're going to teach me how
right okay Escape and then go to map
okay well guys I'm leaving now you know
that you can stop showing off
now map map list
uh
T
Simas uh map W map
rest
okay we going
here I'm leaving on on a Jet Plane
that's right not quite though on
a me wait jet you wrote jet
plate teleportation plate
yes uh is anybody here who was awaiting
me because they knew I was going to come
here no no all right you guys are also
teleported last one last one they will
never find me run run if I got all my
pet I'll be faster no no they're chasing
me they're right behind
me this this reminds me of the time when
we played World of
Warcraft it's a little bit laggy
oop ah okay you get jobs here
if you become an adventurer you can get
requests here and become rich M sounds
good
okay what's this pose today in my dance
lesson I had to like literally take this
very pose and like stop in
movement just like you I got to talk to
you huh Jake what's up
Tokyo patent
office your coughs in the massage yeah
my coughs man
Mo what's up rookie welcome and ases if
you as if you want to become an official
Adventurer
uh and and and do stuff you have to
register here uh
[Music]
okay for now you just like temporarily
registered so to do it uh properly um
you have to oh prove yourself uh and
then you'll get the real registration
oh oh oh muie muie the hot and cute uh
girl will teach you everything come
on hot and cute
it gives me more Mommy Vibes I don't
know ah you're the new one hello um I am
the I don't know how to translate any of
that I know what it means but I don't
know how to translate it and put it into
words but just call me
mu uh first of all um let me explain uh
how to uh navigate yourself through
here um there's many requests here that
you can take from killing monsters or
finding items for others that they lost
and of course you're going to get a
reward for everything um and it gets
better and better the more difficult the
quest is so that's the rough explanation
which totally wasn't obvious from the
GetGo especially since you are totally
not an mmrpg veteran um but you know I
can't assume that from the GetGo so
let's uh register you shall we don't be
so stiff about it uh uh I will get you a
request that suits your
strengths what is this what you have an
imagine seed oh yeah oh
yeah oh yeah we got this at the ruin so
I don't really know much about
it can you show me for a moment I will
totally not steal
it this
is a goblin battle imagine oh we're
disappointed this a goblin
ah what uh well here you can use it
right
away you're lucky that you got it in
this form I think it will help you um so
now let's go ahead and do your
registration since I've said that five
times already um so when you're ready
talk to
me uh yeah
whatever uh yeah of course are you
speaking English for us
okay you have to do your best and pass
the chest all right otherwise I'm going
to have issues too with that mhm I need
you I need to use you good luck do your
best thank
you oh they're all
dancing oh they gave me Goblin imagine
like a pet
huh you know a few days ago I bit my
like the side of my cheek so hard it
still like
hurts it still
hurts it do be like that sometimes right
uh batt
[Music]
imagine no okay basically I I I can use
them okay mhm mhm Quest cleared me to
hanim Mu to Hani
shimo all
right toilet why is there a toilet
sticker H do do you want to do it yeah
let's do it and do it and do it and do
it do it do
it
ski ski toilet culture moving over to
Japanese side let's
go all right all right so um what do you
call someone who recommended you like
suggested you um uh what's it called
again there's a word for the
uh [\h__\h] when you ah referal yeah okay
and then is there a word for the person
who refers you the
referer you refer what Shake huh um and
you already took care of goblins wow um
[Music]
whatever um uh let me explain uh now you
will go to a dungeon and check it out
and then you will do this and that we
will just follow just follow the
freaking golden thing that's in front of
your nose all the
time
Rito oh yeah sure sure we're going to go
there okay yeah I'm just going to mhm
mhm there too much too much too much to
translate yep yeah it's all pretty like
uh obvious usually so no
worry uh o oh that's really
far w l
i
indeed let's go guys and my whole
Entourage
easy keep my show
Everybody follow me wait let's get on my
pet follow me
hello
okay it moves too
much my
show am a more PG's
man it's just like that
[Music]
blessed gameplay man I I I really want
to like go back to the Other M P that I
used to play back in the old days can
someone like tell them to answer their
emails because I really think it's just
a a matter of
that they probably like see our emails
that just look like spam I do think they
probably look like spam they just send
like the same kind of template email to
everybody and some com iies what the
hell is that that I should not attack
that should I some companies will answer
and some are like oh level 20 oh yeah
yeah flex your skills do it yeah yeah
yeah kill
it who okay you guys took that down
immediately oh this person is still here
but she moved a little
bit
H instant
death I'm sure they see them as spam I
think so too I have an interesting
business proposal to
you totally not spam or
scam also not the kind of spam that you
would like to
[Music]
eat can I get this while on the oh I
can oh I think the foxes want to attack
me wait did I go the right way
wait I think I went the wrong
way I went the wrong
way sorry it's it's a little bit
difficult to navigate this fox that way
that way
oh now I confused the people they they
lost track of
me we're going so far like what's with
everything in
between it's all the same like level two
mobs it seems but like why is it so big
why is this place so big what is this
what the hell is
this what is
this
joho joho I don't get any
joho can I like what is
this
weird maybe
lore World Rift yeah
something like that wait wait a second
was that where I had to go ah
ah h f my f is not work isn't my
keyboard being weird no no
right that voice line means Let's uh oh
hold it oh The Voice line means let's
hold hands
maybe that's what he was saying hold
your finger
down um ah see I thought that thing was
weird that is
actually no wonder it stood out to me
that's where I had to go I just thought
it was a random thing
same oh okay I have to remember these
kind of places it
seems uhhuh that this is connected with
the lake L
whatever she says we should go in there
oh we'll see how strong I am in there
are you ready not worried about you
let's
[Music]
go
oh it's a portal oh well now okay now I
can use it
oh oh oh
oh I can go in here with a party as well
it seems but I think we're fine going
alone cool and I guess there's a this
like matchmaking system
generally oh let's see if I can match
with myself wow I did it it's a match
she's so
dramatic oh well it seems I'm not
completely
alone wa well never getting out of here
anymore but since I have destroyed
stairs no just
kidding no
wait where's the path this way okay
ah
ah ah oh you can't use your own items
while you're in the mission what you
have to use the items that are provided
to
you is that really all items like
I don't see any a there F2 that's
probably a healing
[Music]
item oh manit I feel
like I feel like I have I been in this
dungeon during the alpha I feel like
maybe I have or that was what I was
supposed to do and I never figured it
out
okay in most cases you'll never need to
use those items don't worry
okay yeah my health is pretty
full we're good oh you can get revive
two times it seems on the top right it
says Revival left over two
[Music]
times who's shooting oh hello get
down get down here y' strong
lady here new
attack oh that's
strong hey yo is this green stuff oh
it's a little
heel nice
cool yeah dungeon is timed but I think
there's no problem with that it's
probably usually very generous
so oh little
chest am I right Fester huh little chest
huh
oh we got some item I
think let's turn this
waym
supplier oh you get a buff from these oh
so the red one seems to be an attack
buff interesting
but you know what I feel like with these
kind of things did I get it ah no like
they
probably you
know like uh what's the
word like when there's something like a
bath Force are
like I feel like it just evens out
probably
probably the enemies are
stronger just like the same percentage
as whatever the buff giv giv you do you
know what I'm trying to say I feel like
it's like it's not really making you
stronger cuz they probably make the
enemy stronger too and then it even Z I
don't I don't know watch your HP what my
HP is
full yeah like scaling mhm is there
nothing else
here okay maybe not but in some
cases I get this feeling
feeling oh wait oh you mean it's not you
mean my oh I was looking at the bottom
left
oh ha what is that thing bottom left and
is this just a random
line I've alwaysed my
exp aha aha I can climb
walls if I press F on them
oh and then I just go up okay cool Festa
are you good guess I guess we're leaving
you behind no
worries I will send someone to pick you
up left or
right
oh oh I had a
lag
fun
parkour the lag was just for a
moment I think we're good
ow oop ah [\h__\h] oh wait wait wait wait
wait I was trying to figure out how to
move my items around oh you get revived
like a little bit uh before ah nice oh
wait but now I didn't need to
heal I was just trying to
learn damn it oh he's fighting
faster can she die she has HP too huh ow
oh
lag
lag please no lag in the middle of a
[Music]
battle okay cool battle area clear was
that like a mid mid
bus was I supposed to go the other
direction first
[Music]
maybe I don't know
okay but now I know how to use wait I
need healing
again what
up
oh I'm too weak do I have any like real
armor to put on like to replace what I'm
wearing now is
there cuz that's just outer like visual
armor
o not sure where equipment actually
is or does
no APPA
where this doesn't say anything
about stats
so this is my Goblin imine which I guess
I could be using
but there is no
armor oh interesting so I guess it goes
only by like defense stats then
huh interesting not sure if I personally
like that but that might be one of the
critique points from people I don't
[Music]
know huh okay wait this spot there just
had no enemies what does it go up
no oh it's interesting though because I
don't know any other game that tried
that before and and
generally it's not like automatically a
bad thing I would say
it's an interesting way of doing
[Music]
things
imag there are gears but it's not that
early
H okay I don't even see slots for it
though oh another ah this is a healing
point
oh ah okay no worries I
understand easy to
understand okay here we go oh this is
like an
ogre that's a cool
ogre very different from the ogre that I
know living in a
swamp here we
go oh he's trying to go at
F no no no no oh no [\h__\h] did it hit me
you could hit
me a did I accidentally heal again no oh
[\h__\h] ah
oh okay wa he didn't have as much HP as
I thought he might
have what did we get oh and Elder Dragon
Elder Goblin Elder drag Elder Goblin
imagine Kaa imag oh we got a bunch of
these like imagine so I can cast these
right
Fury Adventures oh
recipe n oh
hold I'm taking those things
automatically with me I
hope imagine
these nuts new
skill
nice sor I had two dance lessons today I
had like 3 hours of dancing yesterday
and 4 hours today like learn two dances
one was relatively simple at least but
the other one killed
me so I'm like also mentally very
exhausted like the [\h__\h] dread that I
get when I like first I'm like motivated
when I start learning aoro and then like
20 minutes in or so I'm like realizing
holy [\h__\h] I can't keep
up but both of the dances I learned
today hey were with other people so
other girls were involved you'll find
out afterwards
though and I have another dance to learn
tomorrow but tomorrow is is my new
original songs corio that I'm
learning and this one's the one with the
back dancers so that's going to be
interesting I
think yeah but you know I'm busy I need
to like get a massage at some point
because my coughs are killing
me for real there's some dance moves
that have been like really getting into
my cops and I keep on stretching them
trying to like work against the the sore
muscles but yeah recording is soon so
Galu
Galu any free time for massage yeah I
mean I don't have a single free
day but I can squeeze it in for
sure yeah I wouldn't I didn't expect
that something like that would show
up but yeah that's that's uh yep how it
is
uh well you defeated it as expected from
you I shall praise you uh this is the
end of the test let's go back to Mu
who is that cute girl what the hell
who's that who's that who's
that are you NPC or
not W you're so cute she's is she
reaching out her hand for me wait I can
hold
hands yeah wait the people that kept the
saying that that's actual action who I'm
holding hands with
her it's probably a
wait High chance that there's a guy
behind
that wait I feel awkward
[Music]
now let's just not think about
that you know people might think the
same about me when I'm in mm
RPGs I want to collect all these
things to
cooa
Grass yiy Grass ah that I couldn't pick
that up could
I mine did I see the same things if I I
pick it up is it still visible to them I
wonder girl guy in real
life hey thanks for the membership
welcome I just want to collect things
there's a chest over
there I got to get all those chests it
will surely be very useful to me for you
know the future that I'm going to spend
in this game
[Music]
oh no the fox is going to attack me
defend me my
Army protect
me
[Music]
please yes very long future ahead of me
hey I could have teleported back oops
well I like moving like
this does K not know
what that I can teleport or that that
the game is going to be killed I know
that the teleporting I legit
forgot uh where is my quest marker
here isn't this a nice
Town look how much
detail so pretty
wasted potential
Doo than for membership
[Music]
gifts bull shoot bull
shoot Ms regenerate stamina now oh did
they not do that
before welcome back I was waiting for
you um like you since your life that it
worked
out yeah so wasn't that kind of
difficult
though because I was a freaking ogre we
did not expect that that too tough for a
newcomer H an ogre what I talking about
I have no idea about that like for real
though H was that not part of the
test oh yeah I mean um ogres are very
difficult enemies so there's no way we
would put them into one of these like
you know registration test
thingies wait so wait you killed the
ogre oh well I mean well yeah my my my
servants did huh why for real
oh even uh Advanced adventurers have
problems with those
ogres so there was an ogre there oh my
God I will tell my
Superior so please
wait they're going to kick Shrek out of
his swamp yeah no don't do that please
he deserves to have a home also stop
trying to pressure clean his freaking
swamp he likes a
dirty anyway wow you're really amazing
for killing an ogre um I hate ogres man
so I'm pretty surprised
[Music]
M ah you're
passing the test yipp uh
welcome
mhm you're an adventure now wow you can
have uh take all the requests you want
now oh we did it servant let's make a
lots of
money from Chile thank
you don't forget about your
rank keep that up
too yeah uh
uhhuh okay uh-huh you can rank up if you
clear the things on the adventure board
and then and then when you get out of it
um for example you get more requests to
choose from that give you higher Rewards
uh BL BL
blue thank you for what you just gave
[Music]
me oh I get a
bonus because you killed the ogre so
there you go GC Glory coin Glory
coins hear that
guys because of the glory I have brought
Upon This Town
yes I can use the glory coins next to
her let me check that out
Glory corns no
glory glory corns
what I they clapping oh look at the
standing
ovation oh someone wants to play Jun and
pong rock paper
scissors
mhm uh-huh m
[Music]
oh there's a sticker and more healing
items
[Music]
okay this complicated do I have to do
this yeah cool new
[Music]
skill Su palette at a
thank you they're still
clapping oh thank you wow oh I I got
login bonus now wow I was not I was not
entitled to one before oh look at this
we got another cool thing
oh
interesting D
pwn what what's yours
wait they didn't choose anything n the
hell you didn't
choose you asked me to play Rock Paper
Scissors with you and
yet
mang ah this girl you said right next to
you but it's like the next next person
liar yes see let's see what you have and
what you give oh oh so it is like more
like Cash Up Style
outfits I think like but like more
simple things like
hats and yeah these kind of
like
items
oh oh that's cool what's this ah
frames GC oh earrings well I mean you
really don't
see it wait a second
4,800 wait I have
1,500 wait is that even the glory coins
because those don't look like coins they
look like cards and it says
ticket but yeah it seems like it well
because that's it says GC
here brah it's
just a [\h__\h] ring
expensive must be real
gold real obsidian huh that's more
interesting but
16,000 a ring okay
uhhuh well okay there's a lot of stuff
all these tiny tiny things oh wait a
second here's like some
clothes this one's cheap compared to the
others probably it's just a recolor of
the
original uh starting outfit oh this
one's this one's more expensive
28,000 not okay there's like all kinds
of
stuff well well
well oh
baia what are those this is like similar
to The Bunny we saw Outdoors outside
M imagine
relief
mhm it's a login bonus
mhm interesting
[Music]
okay now now you also want to play you
all want to play bar paper sisters
now I don't have time for that I need to
talk to Jake where's Jake a
there Jake I'm an official Adventurer
now aren't you proud of me can't wait
for this game to get on global soon oh
you're lacking critical information
congratulations I was waiting for this
kind of stuff
I shall
accept oh my rank is too low for
this you are still rank one you have to
get your rank
up uh okay tell me how on the adventure
board
okay sorry ich
to she go
back
oh what it's okay she already told me
how to do it let me let me just do it I
think I'll I can do it can I do it right
away eh he's
cabading
Jake
[Music]
hot um adenture
bir uh let's just push all the buttons
probably that will
do well what did I do challenge
M wait I'm not sure what do we
do what did I do
how to do this did I accept it
I cleared
this he's there he's dog ising
so I just like what I just let it happen
[Music]
What
trans yeah but like it's not oh wait I
should just like yeah go and do one of
these I can't really like put it like on
my quest so to
say I
think uh have a quest to smile dance get
the sub Quest smile dance or if this one
is uh put on an enhanced imagine
okay uh yeah I guess we can't get around
that how the [\h__\h] do I do that
enhanced
imagine let's see
uh what a enhan imagine this is a an
imagine but this is is an enhanc imagine
not
really but
enhance
imagine
oh
op yeah
oh oh who we can feel like almost every
single one of them so wait what does
this do can I summon them or is this
just like upping my stats battle battle
imagine oh I can't have the same one
twice right okay
CL okay well I did it not sure how it
works but I did it board
Advanced
uh here no uh Quest Adventure
board
oh oh wait I cleared the other what was
the other one I put a batt imagine on
this was enhan imagine this well because
it's called enhan imagine I suppose it's
not something I can summon it's just
something that enhances my stats yeah
yeah yeah makes sense right
yippe only ah oh okay she gives me a
quest that says uh up your rank and with
that I will be able to finish that rank
thingy wait
mu are you m yeah I forgot sorry I
forgot who you
were uh this it that's
it oh
oh wait I have to kill more
enemies how long does it take to match
with
myself I had to think about that inside
of my heart deeply do I really want to
match with myself that's just the kind
of thing that a cat lady would do
wouldn't
she you're putting me up against the old
again and there's what is that explosive
no
way
ow
ow I B
ow I should
Dodge how do I use uh ah uh but I have
no healing
[Music]
items what do you mean I have no healing
items
what
what I died
H that was really kitty kitty I
think Cody
young I thought I died I think we died
at the same time pretty much that was
deserved though I am I right very
deserved thank you you guys are so
nice yeah I know I could have dodged but
I'm still like you know it's little
confused with all the
buttons you can play this with a
controller apparently and maybe it's
easier with a controller but I don't
know I don't want
to oh oh they put me on rank two like ah
so it's always a quest that will like
really um let your rank up it's not like
in the manual Okay Okay Okay
[Music]
[Applause]
Okay evan Vibes oh woohoo yippe
you standing evation why is this one in
a snowman
costume sub skill set I can use a sub
skill set now I can use the the this
palet so to say uh uhhuh and then switch
around interesting so if I have too many
skills I can put them up
there um Mount
Caravan oh oh didn't I already do this I
[Music]
probably I think this is nobody just
supposed to show news but I like how I
just started playing the game imagine
someone unknowingly starts playing this
game and then the news literally right
in front of my eyes now says game uh
service is going to be ended
notification of ending of the
service that's all the use your have
wait why are you showing me this
here gets me depressed
[Applause]
man what what are they just like
reminding me hey you're enjoying this
game now but just so you know just so
you know this game that you're enjoying
right now will be killed
soon well thanks for reminding
me thank you hey Jake did you know that
you will disappear soon
because with the game you also disappear
do they know do these NPCs know that
their whole existence will be
deleted where will you go I saw this
tweet from
Ludwig asking where do vas go when they
graduate now but the real question is
where do NPCs go when their game
graduates that's the real question
I wanted to answer but I did not have
any funny or interesting answer that has
not already been said by all the other
replies all the other YouTubers
answering to that
man I couldn't think of anything funny
or so or
insightful yeah I I literally opened the
reply window and had it open and then I
was thinking like oh man I can't think
of
anything damn it and I gave
up the psych ward
wow excuse me why are you saying we're
crazy and when we graduate this the
moment when we finally finally realize
we're insane and everything we've been
doing so far was just voices in our
heads and we're just like imagining
everything and that's why we got to go
to the psych
ward that's probably not at all what you
were saying but I feel like that's
that's what you what it truly means
anyway we did it we're Adventures
Now new new
Quest wake up
wa who are you talking to we're not
real you wouldn't say that to me if you
weren't real if you weren't real you
would try to convince me that you are
real it's a pigment of my
imagination is that right really I used
to have trouble saying that I really how
you say
it okay what's the new
Quest okay no
problem
wait wait wait sonini
[Music]
take
okay okay let's go
oh wait
police a
police police
Doo okay guys you ready to
go you ready to go yeah follow
me they must be so bored but they also
must be so happy because you know
they're high level so they put like time
into this game and surely they enjoyed
it because they're still playing it so
they're happy that someone's covering
their game that literally just got
announced pronounced
pronounced pronounced
dead H sad I'd be happy
too all right let's follow the
mysterious golden marker in my screen
which I totally have in real life too
don't you guys also have a marker like
this leading you for life is it only
me defective helicopter thank you for
the
memberships you
do no I'm just an NPC I was like
literally just thinking about this the
other
day when I was
sitting like in a taxi I was feeling
like
me as like cuz I was feeling like I was
like in the taxi
um you
know after the concert basically I was
thinking like man I just performed in
the
concert so I don't know I feel like when
I worked in a hotel I had a don't Mis
don't misunderstand me I had like a lot
of fun with like my
job but don't you like feel a little bit
like this you have this NPC
energy and then obviously when you have
a job like performing on stage then it's
like more of a main character
protagonist energy but I wonder like you
can still feel like your
protagonist of your own life right even
if you have a more normal job but maybe
only if you're happy with it you have
like a 9 to5 job or so and it doesn't
make you happy then you might feel like
an NPC and your own life and then you
want to change life right that can make
you feel really
depressed so I hope everybody can feel
like they're protagonist of their own
life important the most important
character I find it so interesting to
think about the fact that like I have
thoughts I have thoughts in my brain and
voice voes in my
brain and I can control my body
right but it's just weird to think about
other people having the same thing you
can only control your own body and and
you can only hear your own thoughts is
this is am I saying weird things I feel
like I am it's hard to put my thoughts
into uh words I'm
stuck yeah in the uality is
wild yeah like cuz like sometimes
there's like literally not like an
illness but like this what what do you
call it like this this way of thinking
where you're like
absolutely astonished by the fact
that like or some people really think
that everybody like H but some people
think that everybody around them is just
like a simulation or something like that
and you're the only person living this
life and what
what exential midlife excuse me not not
midlife
Solis cpis oh
interesting I find that very interesting
because I mean I don't think that's true
but I understand why you would think
that
way the quality no that's not Phil
philosoph philosophy philos philosophy
philosophy the view or theory that the
self is all that can be known to
exist solipsism is an idealist pieces
because only my mind exists and Tails
only mind's exists what does this
mean what do this mean philosophical
things self-centered
delusions no but it's like hard to wrap
your brain your mind around some things
in in life
and I mean it's a weird way of
thinking do you guys know anybody who
thinks that
way imagine you have a friend who thinks
that
way wouldn't you feel kind of
insulted so you think I'm not real
that's what they're saying then right
you do what do you mean you do you have
a friend no but like literally you're
not saying like they're just a
self-centered person right you are you
saying that they really believe in the
theory
that like they're the only person who
exists and everybody else is like an
NPC a that would be insulting I think to
the people around you so
sad but if that's how they think like
you know can't be helped
that's basically psychopathy well I
don't know is
it okay I got toas
wow W the Buffs the Buffs where am I uh
Jake to wait a second
what was that my quest finding a
camp I'm confused I got I got distracted
by my yapping let me move away do I see
my quest marker oh oh Jake you're here I
didn't see you because it said talk to
Jake in my quest I thought I had to go
back into the
city you followed me Jake hey oh uh
waited for you uh I will be with you
from here on out um so the top of the
top will show you how it's done now
my servant um steal
everything yeah because that's free uh I
hear
you well anyway uh if you want to become
a good Adventurer you I will make you
the path for
it why why is see these people are
literally NPCs they're all treating me
like a protagonist
wow they need to they need more
protagonist energy they should stop
caring about me and and making me a path
to success and and more like maybe care
about their own success and like why am
I the only one completing quests huh
complete quests by yourself come
on but if you think about
it MPGs at
least have more than just you and a
million NPCs there's other people who
are playing this game if you're playing
a non MMO RPG just appp and you're the
only one
then then you just I don't know where
I'm going with this but maybe
it's maybe it's maybe maybe it's a
simulation of
life I don't I will I don't know this
was not very
wise I'll I'll just continue playing the
game wrap it up mhm oh high level d d oh
it's a high level
dungeon okay I will check my skills
don't worry my throat hurts why does it
hurt I keep on drinking water but it
doesn't
help must be the air conditioning maybe
that's maybe one thing
that would speak against getting air
conditioning cuz it's not good for the
fro
M yeah yeah let's challenge
yeah let me go let me go in yeah yeah
yeah I'm using my new skills don't worry
about it Quest updated okay let's go
guys
cute oh what is right behind
here matching with myself once
again
bye-bye let's go
in that's why there are ones you can add
air conditioners where you can add water
to
really wait this game is from out well
it's been out for Japanese people for a
while and it has been announced to be
closed again soon never to be back never
to return no Western release ever sorry
to let you
know it's going to be out of service
yep was there a dash button and I just
missed it
cuz like oh wait I run a little bit
faster maybe when I put the weapon
[Music]
away nice wait I should zoom out again I
was so zoomed in can we get up there
wait do you still
alive almost fell down I wonder if I can
fall
down from here surely
yes yippe cool that was a healing item
maybe
M practice dodging I don't like to
Dodge I don't think in the old memori P
that I used to play I don't think
dodging was even a thing what is
[Music]
that
wa see I a little bit are you proud of
[Music]
me
nice this one's
strong
woo oh nice nice nice nice
nice pressing all the buttons
yipp blasted him away
well oh I'm I was like focused on the
explosive t
t
t by the way I did end up watching the
Nintendo
Direct
um on on I think I yeah I watched like
the archive of it on the airplane I got
myself internet on the airplane on both
back and forth so that's why
you may have seen me tweeting at any
given
time I mean okay I was also sleeping for
a lot of it
but what the [\h__\h] is going on what is
this
thunder holy
[\h__\h] what are you
doing I was just so bored at times
I couldn't help but get myself the Wi-Fi
it wasn't even that
expensive also like for 2 hours like 29
bucks or something like that but then
for the whole flight 35 just like six
bucks
difference so I just got the full one so
yeah I saw the Nintendo Direct I kind of
be honest even though you guys are
saying it's like very woba cor and I
guess I would agree with that but still
it it didn't really hype me
up it didn't really hype me up like the
tales offing okay yeah that speaks to me
but at the same time I played that game
already and then like a lot of other
like RPG things
but nothing really that big or
interesting I was kind of the newl yeah
that was like the biggest announcement
unless you don't care about RPG jpg
games um but if you do I would say that
was almost the biggest announcement they
had and that was the first time
announcement wasn't
it I don't think they announced that
anywhere else
before oh yeah an older Yakuza game on
switch
H yeah so an act announcement is hype
but as I said in Pre chat I don't know
about this one
doesn't the I I I don't know I might
still like play it on my own but I
prefer older like previous ones I
think but we'll see maybe maybe the
sidekicks will speak to me more
[Music]
wow waa I just spawned the the battle
imagine the like Goblin thingy I'm not
sure if it was the goblin that suddenly
did so much
damage or if it was a combination of
everything but that seemed very
strong Castlevania
[Music]
main athl girls are usually fluffy I
don't know would you call Risa
fluffy
uh but yeah I know what you mean
generally I agree they're often more on
the fluffy
side she's just like so mature looking
and that's what I think it is usually
they don't look that
mature and
like I don't know
and then what else was there I don't
even remember ah I think there was
um there was
one game damn I have absolutely no idea
how to describe it anymore cuz
everything left my
memory
um huh one game that gave me Vibes of a
mix between
aie and something
else but that one looked interesting um
what was it I think if I say ay you guys
might know what I
mean what the
hell maybe I should heal
uh the ah yeah yeah the great Studio
game that one looked good to me I might
even stream it when it comes out to be
honest Nea yeah never that's like I
think the only game that really I felt
like was special in that sense like to
me interesting as a streaming game too
perhaps
M mhm
[Music]
and y'all look at
this this one looks strong
uh-oh yeah the art are the art yeah yeah
didn't it look like is it the one that
looked like pretty
funky oh I think the other game that it
reminded me of like um I thought it was
a mix of Orie and um what was it the
cult
game yeah why is
this
goodbye oh [\h__\h] what am I
pressing
ow uh yeah cool Keep On Healing
oh
okay got to like get rid of my lock so
that I can properly run out of the
circles oh
[Music]
hey
ouch
ouch yeah this is B
are my friends still alive goodbye yeah
he says goodbye but he's fine
oo okay oh I like kind of downed
him oh oh oh oh there we go I think I
did
it not bad I did it first try
oh I got some new
ones
wow see of stars okay I forgot what that
one
was but also um what was it that Square
Enix
game that my oi also played the other
day the Square Enix cute jrpg the new
one I like that one
yeah visions of Mana I keep on thinking
of like like I combine game names and I
call it Trials of Mana in my
head it looks beautiful
[Music]
wait but Trials of M actually exist I
thought of us Trials of something else
and I'm just like combining two
games
oops it'sa
[Music]
hm so yeah these kind of like dark Aura
enemies are a problem it
seems evil
[Music]
interesting I
am
which I guess is something like the
chosen
one like you're you're but I don't know
it so he's like
confused I'll tell you my
name because we might meet again along
the
way me
me Mello loaf mellow loaf of
bread bye well that was fast
rude meat love
that's a weird
guy ignore these kind of
weirdos just because they're being nice
to
you don't get in trouble with them
okay why are you staring at
me Cas he called you something like the
chosen one
right what that mean what that mean I
heard it before
I don't know I can't
remember any case before we forget it we
should go get our reward let's go
yeah I agree give me my rewards go go
has it already been like almost 3
hours maybe I should start reading super
chats before it gets too late again
again and I get too
tired wait this person has my hair wait
let me look at you why does yours look
better than the way I did
it got the messy hair could I have
chosen the messy hair or is that like
special
one you look like me did you do that on
[Music]
purpose this is kind of like the kimono
version of me cuz my Kimo is white
are you cosplaying
me it's
me y'all should be cosplaying me all of
you if there's a salon where you can
change your looks anytime all of you
should be cosplaying me why don't you
look like me yet let's make an army of
waas the TU an
army the tuen
Army okay uh is Jake back back in the
city or
what is he back in the city should have
just teleport he's probably back in the
city yeah y y y yep
y Tak on Army Key Arsenal
if only was open to non JP players yeah
I
wish that's where I hoped we were going
towards an mm
RPG start
together
kfp on the new
adventure m
I wonder like I'm capping a 10 people
visibility I wonder how busy it really
is I mean
the are they doing this for me
nah they just ran lied there
right cuz the main city is always going
to be busy right but I wonder like
how how how full does a game have to be
to not be
cancelled
huh can't be that empty right it looks
pretty Lively to
me but maybe
D much more of a boom hey
[Music]
h i they use a lot of
money um need more whales more whales no
whales no gain Oh My Stream died for a
second oh it's probably you know the
Town Square killing
[Music]
things how you like the game so far I
like it honestly like I I don't know
what people are criticizing about it I'm
I'm sure whatever the criticizing is
legitimate I have not however met
anything yet that would ride it off for
me and kill it for
me it's the end
game you know what solves that problem
keep on making new characters never go
to the end
game that's what I did with World of
Warcraft but not because the end game
was just because I skill
issue kept on making new characters max
level was
40 or 42 or something like
that that was my highest
character it just became kind of
difficult and I was too young that was
my first M RPG and I was like really
young I played since the like the
beginning of World of
Warcraft until like the blood elves Or
Nah after the blood elves still a little
bit yeah I was I was mostly running
around solo too
so yeah I I did enjoy classic well of
brra leveling I mean at some point I got
sick of the [\h__\h] mini goblins
whatever that was in the
beginning in certain areas ah especially
the [\h__\h] desert area that I that's
where we end the world of Ro stream
previously remember know what I mean wa
the [\h__\h] Cobalts no but uh and the
murlocs but no that desert area was
rough there's a bunch of areas that were
kind of rough I
think give me my [\h__\h] reward or
else also I need to pee
hm my mer
impression what the [\h__\h] is that oh I
was I thought I was looking at an animal
but no it's a sword and a shield
okay P
girl it lagged when I said that did you
hear me
you guys are funny wait I became level
10 what it's lagging
again
lag new level new
skill board
Advanced oh my God we did
it how you
doing cute suddenly
pose is the lag gone
think standing in the hub will just do
this yeah possibly it's okay I'm not
even mad I feel like I remember when I
was like exploring the town on my own in
the alpha test I feel like I saw
kitties kittens cats all
over here and there but I can't see any
now this is why the game has failed
because they've patched out the cat
snow hey you want me to go in
there
huh sure okay I'll go there what is
going on here why are you so tall you're
standing on this guy how are you doing
that can I stand on
someone don't get naked on my
stream I'll ban you GM banhammer
new
Quest get to
D the inside of my mouth
hurts put in my finger into my mouth so
that my teeth Don't Touch the wound of
my mouth
[Music]
what they talking about I kind of lost
track maybe became some like yeah I I
bit really hard
I beat my side really
hard
no taste of metal no doesn't taste like
anything do not use salt did someone try
to hurt me to the usual room whoever
said try salt to the usual room with
you five months
bye-bye you know usual room has been
kind of empty
so okay I think we'll probably leave it
at this uh for today I don't know if
we'll play again maybe I'll play in my
private time although I don't have much
private time while I'm in bad uh
yeah but I want to read super chats and
I feel like level 10 and after this
little look inside it's a pretty good
point to stop for
now and I need to pee so go piss girl
[Music]
I'm glad we got to play a little bit and
Adventure as an adventur in
here I even if we don't play again
during this trip uh I'm coming back to
Japan within this year still
so I could play again then if I wanted
to really unfortunate about the you know
the fact that they're banning all IPS
besides Japanese
IPS but they may ban Japanese IPS but I
will sorry I wanted to make a fun segue
into
IDL you see where I was going I just I
don't know I don't want to say it like
that I don't really want to say it like
that
they're making what they're really
making a mobile game version like for
real but you can't transfer your like
account and everything can
you I mean okay then it's at least not
completely lost but will it again be
like Japan only wait a second there a
aqua by
cosplay what
so
good see Ludwick when you asked where do
YouTubers go when they graduate they go
and yeah show up in mm RPGs
randomly I don't apologize what are you
apologizing
for what the no Ludwick what how do you
guys say that's literally like kind of
German game name I think I don't know
Ludwick that's how we say it in huh how
do you say it that's how you say it in
German and in German we say
Ludwig how would you guys say
it I'm saying it right right oh you guys
say
lwig oh that's so stupid you say Ludwig
oh I didn't realize you guys say
Ludwick sounds
dumb okay I'm going to uh go piss girl
and please stay because we'll read Super
Chat I need a
[Music]
massage anyway was a pleasure B Uncle
please don't kill this game let me like
bring all the people into it come on
give me a
chance give me a
chance C
all just leave it to
me okay
BRB uh where do you want to go
[Music]
guys here it's too big now
ah what the
hell why does this not not work anymore
this like combination of
buttons well my outfit here doesn't
really fit this look does it but that's
okay let me get rid of the set list
oh
sh do you hear the
bgm thank you for playing this MMO thank
you for
[Music]
watching I don't have the kitchen right
now also I won't fit the kitchen
either okay then have fun with the bgm
cuz that's all you'll have for the rest
of your life I'm Gone Forever bye
[Music]
why thank you and yes I washed my hands
it's just really fast because the uh
sink is built into the
toilet which is you know common with
Japanese
toilets can I say another thing that's
common with Japanese
toilets um which really annoys
me toilet paper in Japan is so [\h__\h]
thin
that you need to literally roll I'm not
joking like maybe 5 m or so off of the
Roll to get
anything
significant in terms
of
thickness so
thin it's the like the thinnest ever and
they don't even sell like thicker ones
as legit considering bringing my my own
toilet paper from
Austria I think I think in America I
felt like it was also pretty thin but
that might just be in the
hotel but in Austria we have properly
thick ones and you can get a thicker
ones if you want like there's like
either like three ply or four ply I
think but here is like legit 0.2
ply why I don't understand
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah for the hotel it's probably cheaper
to just get the thin
ones but like you're going to end up
just using more
[Music]
[Laughter]
this thought it was because of Cheaper
hotels thing no it's
[Music]
everywhere ah or maybe it's for somebody
said um in Japanese that maybe it's for
like uh for it to be easier to um
[Music]
dissolve yeah that could be they try to
just make it easier to dissolve in the
in the waters underground for the sewage
for the sake of the sewage
[Music]
interesting makes
sense but it's just like to roll so much
roll roll roll
[Music]
roll rolling
DIY reasonable toilet paper kid just got
to fold
yourself it's just like when it's that
much it gets hard it gets hard to
fold M mentioned buying some exclusive
fi to really she mentioned that
before I visited her place once I don't
think it was really thick it seemed
pretty like standard to me but I'm I'm
not sure it's been too long I need to
check her toilet paper I guess I'll I'll
I'll hit her up I'm like M Say
by I need to check how fake your toilet
paper
[Music]
is
oh oh really long information here
[Music]
okay it seems really to be something
about the
sewage okay that makes sense then I
shall not complain about the toilet
paper anymore because I guess depending
on the country and continents sewage
systems are very different
H that's also probably why like you know
like in
Brazil I've been to Brazil before right
so stop telling me to come to Brazil but
there I was
so
confused about
not
like having
to having to put the [\h__\h] toilet
paper that you used into a
[Music]
bin and like kind of like having to
shower your butt and then I guess Dan
you're supposed to I don't I can't even
I can't even
cuz like I stayed in a hotel room with
another girl and so maybe if you're
alone in that hotel room then it's not
so awkward but the fact that you're like
let's say you're in the hotel room with
someone you you not you're not like
family with or so just a friend and then
like
ew
[Music]
they sorry that's just so weird to me
also rip um I think Brazil can't use
Twitter
anymore that's normal well normal there
not for me it was weird to the girl I
was with too because like for both of us
it wasn't normal in our and we didn't
even know originally there wasn't even a
sign we just like flushed it normally at
first and then people um like somehow we
found out somebody told us hey you got
to you got to put it in the bin and I'm
like that's what the bin is for oh my
God go yeah cuz it clogs
easily we can still use Twitter still
really oh seems they're still alive for
now let's
[Music]
go
wow by the way my my
bro my bro is taking care of my
kitties right now and you know
both like first it was my my um bestie
and her boyfriend taking care but they
switched because you know it's a really
long time frame and um it's just been so
quiet cuz I'm so busy and apparently
everything's fine so that they have no
reason to really like write to me um so
it seems like everything's fine with the
cutle so I asked by myself like hey
haven't heard from you guys in a while
how's my cat doing so now my my brother
sent me
pictures and in the background I was
able to see that like my veggies my
garden veggies are grown I hope they
don't like die without me having a
chance to eat them because right now
they look very
edible hope they stay edible like
that
yeah yeah but the cats also look
fine I think I hope I hope that movie is
eating her food properly because you
know when I'm not there she's often
weird about
it but last time I
asked I was told yeah she's eating just
fine
so yeah I'm using the White
Version you know I kind of forgot about
it I got to use my RPG outfit again
yippee
oh by the way guys just so you know
tomorrow I or today depending on your
time zone I will be on the official
Channel official whole lifean
[Music]
Channel I'm going to be on the channel
of whole life
Ian it's going to be a 3D
program yeah quite a big bunch of
us m
yeah make sure to watch
it
yeah yeah
fre full freed mhm is it in English or
Japanese English of course because we're
talking about that mysterious thing the
mysterious project I've been seeing so
many
[Music]
um so many like assumptions of what it
is and I don't
know
if the reality of it will
be satisfying or disappointing I it's
just because a lot of you guys have been
making crazy
assumptions uh people don't read the
scriptions I guess because I think you
could understand what it is if you read
descriptions
but well it the description of the
teaser it said it's said like what that
it's
a
Sandbox game
right well you'll find out everything in
that stream so I'll just leave it at
that I don't think we're really
necessarily you know we 100% have to
keep it a secret but let's just keep it
under the the you know
locks
uh but it's more than any it's more than
just that of course like they they want
to do like yeah many things with it
so in any case I I think it's really
cool but I feel like a lot of people are
making crazy things
up about what they think it
is and that worries me
cuz you're getting your your hopes up so
high don't don't don't think about
it but I do think it's very ambitious
and um exciting and
interesting but don't
don't all she said was focus on the
sandbox part and yeah yeah yeah but
well there's there's definitely
misunderstandings going on from what I
can see in the
assumptions I'm hyped for
it but it worries me that people are
misunderstanding a few
things yeah the teaser was really cool
the animated teaser there's so many
scenes of me like fighting and stuff and
me with my sword and my shield of course
with a sword on the left hand
H yeah I think we urgently need a
misunderstanding
Corner uh but yeah um it'll be fun uh
the program will be fun and very
interesting
um and um
yeah yeah I'm
left-handed I don't have much
opportunities to show it off but
[Music]
yeah I can't believe C made their own
console for the 40 VR
[Applause]
MMO are you still the only Lefty and Ian
oh I actually I don't know I have not uh
indeed I have not perceived anybody else
I think who's left but there might
[Music]
be left handed kid
yeah generally like creative people tend
to be left-handed or like left-handed
people tend to be creative um so that is
a
thing I need to figure out a good time
for massage I was thinking maybe
tomorrow after my dance
lesson or the day after tomorrow but
probably tomorrow cuz like my stream
slot so to say is that one 3D stream
tomorrow which won't take up much of my
time so like tomorrow is a good
time no I think Ena is not left-handed
no no feel like I would know
[Music]
that okay um what Super Chat should we
read I know I skipped something before
uh so we probably should go back as far
as possible
also by the way can I just talk about
the fact that I literally didn't even
have time to do anything on the bingo I
mean I may have like naturally uh
cleared one or two things automatically
but didn't have time for anything and I
think it's like
ending now is so I guess I'm not
participating I legit didn't have time
like I went to freaking
America I've been doing so many
things recording dance lessons this and
that
[Music]
yeah yeah in the beginning I was like oh
I'm not going to participate and then I
was like oh maybe I will just
participate actually and then bam it hit
me the
busyness I don't want to speedrun it
either cuz I don't think I
would be cuz I see now that P Senpai has
a res no is she streaming right now oh
yeah is a waiting room or is she
streaming or is it over but she was
doing like last minute
bingo I guess yeah I think it's finished
H um so that to me means probably that
it's going to end tomorrow oh wait what
my about also doing a last minute Bingo
like tomorrow but I don't even I don't
have time for it and like ah one thing
I'm sad about though is that I didn't
even have time to play the that like
stacking game again that I wanted to
play the whole live stacking game
[Music]
thingy um I wanted to do it again I
still could but I like I wanted to
combine the mon the impersonation thing
with it and like some of my cute artists
prop artists already drew me props but
now it's like I'm too late for the
bingo so the impersonation thing doesn't
even I don't have a good excuse anymore
for that to do that I
wonder but they made me like a wet shirt
like a seethrough I don't know if it's
wet or seethrough or both
[Music]
um which I think is a genius idea
actually I might still use that
prop you guys like that idea
huh
mhm
mhm speed one will make it more
interesting I feel like some things are
certainly speedrunnable but not
everything
I don't know I I don't have time for it
like I legit don't have time for it if
if it ends tomorrow I don't have time
for
it I would have liked to participate but
the circumstances are
[Music]
Musashi yeah I don't I don't I don't
know I mean I hope that there's no
rewards that I really would have liked
to
earn hope not missing out on something
super super
[Music]
cool quick somebody find her some bugs
there's like bugs coming out of my
sewage I guess in the bathroom every now
and then with tiny flies I mean the tiny
[Music]
flies yeah yeah they did say that it
wasn't as crazy but it might still be
pretty nice um I don't
know I don't
know but all I really wanted was the
money the budget to do something cool
and that doesn't seem to be a thing this
time so it's
[Music]
okay they made you busy on
purpose no they didn't but it's still
bad time for me anyway let's read super
chats I
guess do I have a I should have a fro
candy let
me
[Music]
going okay
okay a 9k
bed they haven't written to me I should
write them an email about the
mattress okay no
don't most of Ian haven't been able to
do the Bingle except a few of
Justice except a few entr M right Super
Chat um sorry I'm sure somebody already
told me but can you tell me again what I
have been
[Music]
missing Super Chat
reading
[Music]
time uh start from W again
what uh the from the latest dedicated
Super Chat reading stream ahuh
interesting there Super Chat reading
stream when did I last do a super chat
reading
[Music]
stream
no
h j don't give up on
me don't give up on
me where did you
go where'd you go you were just here but
now you gone
she spammed it earlier well why why have
you guys not picked it up
then
huh maybe toilet
[Music]
ah you sent a Super
Chat don't tell me probably because I
kept on missing you thank you wait what
where is the Super Chat readings when
did I do a super chat
[Music]
reading when the hell did I Ah Ah that's
just the the one that I skipped so
that's why it's so far in the back huh
[Music]
so found
it thank you
[Music]
Tas sorry that I haven't been like able
to stay on top of
everything well you know how it
is Jacob 47 D pain D happy Bel birthday
oh I'm so
late happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you happy birthday dear pain
pickle happy birthday to
you green Wilder thank you for the red
of chat I'm quite late but Happy
Birthday wa oh to me oh thank you you
you're quite late don't worry I'm late
you're still amazing and cute even if
you're exclusively streaming after my
bedtime while you're in Japan am
I well not now right not actually a big
deal I always wait but wait that was a
separate Japan trip and yeah I was
streaming at a weird time then um uh
well actually today I guess as well but
um this currently in this trip I'm
trying to do more like na prime time
streams yesterday was really
early not actually a big deal I always
watch the vs W on demands anyway anyway
you're awesome and I love you keep up
the great work thank you are you here
now probably not because it's past your
bedtime and well then have fun with the
w and the man
I hope I hope you still catch me
sometimes maybe you caught me yesterday
thank you so much for the support and
the happy birthday wishes thank you
soon much love back to
you not L thanks for the pinky happy
belated birthday boss thank you another
late one huh teacher lee d j d mle tanks
T and thanks for the pinky happy very
late birthday
W I'm sorry I have dipped quite a bit in
stream attendance
recently it's not my choice life is
beating me up a lot but you're so my
Koshi forever and thank you for always
giving me a reason to smile thank
you I'm glad you're still around don't
worry I don't really feel like you like
I mean it didn't like stand out to me
that you you've been hear less so you
still hear
plenty of course every stream would be B
best but that's difficult also with time
zones so don't worry too much about it
thank you so much for your support I
still see you around so I think all is
well as long as you're still here
sometimes I'm
happy Adonai
an he who eats
faces oh thank
you spata dun I give thanks for the
pinky I missed the limited cuz of work
but I will still get the merch because
it's divine happy late birthday to my
Kam oi and to many many more I also left
my bucket a few days before too which
also meant uh it was my cat's birthday a
your cat's birthday I wish I knew my
cat's real birthday
because I think the one that they gave
me when I adopted the cats was just a
vague uh
guesstimate of it
I wish I knew properly then I would
probably like celebrate it more
seriously but since I don't know the
real date I don't feel
like appropriate like I don't want to
celebrate it cuz I don't know when it
really
was which you might be surprised that I
don't right I seem like the kind of
person who celebrates their Cat's
birthday I don't but just because I
don't know the
date can celebrate the adoption date
instead H I guess so but I don't
know just doesn't feel right to
[Music]
me but yeah that would make sense too if
I did that from the beginning now I
don't remember the adoption day
[Music]
either every day can be birthday yeah I
guess so but I wanted to know the real
day well thank you so much
hi I'm glad you got your meriz I've been
seeing people receiving their froggy waa
plushies by the way I don't think that's
the one
that oh wait never
mind no yeah yeah that's a different one
yeah yeah the froggy wild one was a
different one but yeah people are
getting it can you guys check you guys
have do somebody who has their fogy
waas
anybody can you guys check so far in the
pictures it looks like she has no
eyebrows I don't remember did did I cuz
I remember in the production of it that
stood out to me and I was like why does
she have no eyebrows and I'm not sure if
I actually like ended up getting proper
eyebrows for her or if it's just like
stayed like that but can you lift her if
you if you get her or if you have her
can you lift her bangs and tell me if
she has
eyebrows let me know I'm curious would
be weird without eyebrows because the
thing above her eyes that's just ey
[Music]
Lids yeah lift her bangs but you can
also just lift her in general give her
aies she does have eyebrows really I
guess they're just really up
high looks
weird I I thought that already when I
saw like the
sample
abies but even if she doesn't have
eyebrows please give her love
highbrows yeah
literally
pu
[Music]
cute
um Anthony W thanks in the pinky K it's
nice to see how much you've accomplished
as well as how you've grown happy
belated birthday to our beloved T thank
you it's already been a while since my
birthday actually my my anniversary is
kind of closer now than my birthday
oopsy
thank you very much
doll appreciate it ex bread dog who
loves bread and Hungry Jacks thank you
for the pinky from Australia random is
it normal for feral born kittens to
trust and hang around with me been
taking care of them for months because
their mama attacked them away no the
point they're competing over climbing up
and sleeping on my lap or am I just
really lucky
Pebble
Pebble thought you were bread dog
[Music]
I think it's normal very normal it's
actually kind of a flex I'm jealous no
when my when my cats were kittens they
were also more clingy and were climbing
up on me too um and even sleeping on my
lap
occasionally I wish that was still a
thing I really wish so I'm jealous you
should cherish it I don't know if your
kittens are still like around you or if
you gave them
away please please update
me bunny D Gary Garza thanks for the red
chat happy late birthday wa sorry I'm
late my credit card got stolen what but
now that I have this new info I want to
say I'm proud of you my Kam oi son my
Kami oi
son are you just saying I'm proud of you
son like like a meme like a
[Music]
joke okay thank you Dad
thank you so much I'm sure you're even
more proud now that I performed on stage
in New
York thank youah
Mah sorry for the late reply and I'm
glad that you're you have a new credit
card now I
[Music]
guess does that make them out grandp
PA no no cuz you guys are
adopted I'm
adopted pyro than for the pinky wait
Gary Gara did you get a kiss Gary Gara
pyro than for the pinky four years of V
birthday memories I think I'll not do
one request this month anyway uh looking
forward to rest of the what do you mean
you not do one you mean you do more than
one can't wait to wear happy way too
much I think I'll wear my fun happy to
more today if not too
[Music]
hot well I'm glad you have the fun hppy
it's really
gorgeous did you go to the concert
[Music]
pyro are you here
now did you go to the concert the fun
hoppies were hot really they're supposed
to be like Airy and
fin I mean I never at my time M's back
in the day I don't think copies in the
like hello project fandom were not
really a thing so I don't really have
experience with them maybe they are
supposed to be on the thicker side
actually and they just look really
thin I wore two at once why would you do
that mine felt
fine a much thicker Fabric or maybe they
just wanted it to like not feel flimsy
they just wanted it to feel like good
quality but the result of that is that
it's
hotter but you know what that means that
like in winter time if there's a concert
you can also like ah especially for
world tour concert H you could wear it
maybe over a sweater and feel pretty
warm it's still official on fof fic I'm
not
[Music]
sure at what point you guys would call
it
thick so I don't
know yeah Mak some sturdy it's good I
was hot in the concert from jumping a
lot in a t-shirt yeah see uh anything
will make you
hot if you are jumping
[Music]
around can't wait for the official happy
I'll wear it next anime NYC let's
go also like I mean if you guys are is
anybody planning to go to like the next
Fest assuming it's around the same time
frame again anybody who wants to go this
time
[Music]
again I think it's still pretty chill
during that time in Japan so it's good
if the happy is on the warmer
side h
you wish no I love to
go I want to then do it don't let your
dreams be
dreams I wish I
could wish I could I like to go
[Music]
again ni but tickets are probably
impossible who says that last year a lot
of you guys got a get and there was like
this or this year there was this uh like
Foreigner Lottery
[Music]
too I think it became easier than before
for
foreigners have to go to Japan for
another concert later huh which
[Music]
one Japan vacation would be nice yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah you guys need to
combine it with a Japanese Japanese
Japan uh vacation everybody needs to do
that once in their
life Eden
[Music]
Exile Eden Mr Eden Mr
Eden want to go
bowling
Eden you're good at bowling right
[Music]
right that was you
right so funny that you guys went
bowling
cousin my
[Music]
cousin cousin it's so funny that you
guys went
bowling it's so funny to
me I mean it's a common thing to do with
groups of people but I'm assuming you
you guys did it because of GTA as a joke
right who came up with
that so
genius it's a default dude thing e no
you did it because of GTA
right you just did it because it was
fun you weren't thinking of
GTA you so you guys are not as funny and
smart as I thought you were
huh I am disappointed also thank you
D wait what the
hell I see I I've seen you guys like in
the normal chat window that you guys can
like kind of reply to Super chats now
but I didn't know that if you click on
the Super Chat that it opens another
window and then it opens kind of like
its own chat box where you can see the
replies to that very super
chat that that's funny and unnecessary
but thank you
[Music]
YouTube it has its own chat
box
yo yeah I guess it probably doesn't work
on hyper
chat okay continuing with the super
chats that I'm so far behind
[Music]
on uh
than pinky this is a pretty nostalgic
time to watch youo you know Irish
recently solved some go I she was having
apparently there was an update oh always
happy to hear when you meet up with the
other stay sa so I already know about
the ghost update or like yeah basically
I know it's like working again this is
very out of date very old
unfortunately but at the same time now I
even have have a new mixer
so even the roadcast will be replaced so
I guess I I guess I'm not going back to
the GL salar for
now yeah the M mixer yeah let's call it
the MTO
mixer oh but you sent me on on Twitter
in the hashtag what was probably you I'm
just assuming it was you again didn't
you show me like a cool new thing from a
media a new capture card that's like
kind of like a dog at at the same time
that's pretty
dope wait the person that was kind of
doing a Kimo noi cosplay posted on the
kfp
hashtag they posted a picture of the
cosplay I was like who the how the hell
did people get such a clear screenshot
from my stream showing this person but
no they put up a screenshot look here so
that was on purpose
amazing wait now I noticed the wings in
the back they're kind of like probably
supposed to recreate um The Fluffy apron
that I
[Music]
have yeah okay I was trying to find that
tweet
again where is
[Music]
it I can't find
it but that's okay look at this WWA by
the way look at
this cute anime I am so
anime
wow those freaking Bones on my hip
fish cute isn't that Cape
cute Cape cute right keep cute keep cute
keep cute keep cute keep cute keep cute
[Music]
shut up about the
Hat teal coloring on your hair looks off
you look you look off but nothing looks
off
here looks perfect
although they were
so like generally like I think
they they're really careful that
everything looks
according to the default design the
proper design but I'm just noticing now
the yeah the back of my hair there
should be way more turquoise
there or like green turquoise blue color
yeah okay now and now I did notice that
yeah is that in all of the
scenes
No ah yeah partially
they have
it uh it looks like they thought about
it in this
[Music]
one because see that looks like a lot of
it is there but it seems like again they
did not think of it in this one because
here it looks like only orange
again but it's okay I didn't even notice
until now
still cute still
cute okay back to Super
chats h s thanks for the red super chat
with no comment okay thank you though
thank you for the support you seem like
a
lurker cuz you have a armored C icon but
I don't really see you around and you're
not even talking to me in the super chat
but okay thank
you thank you for the
chat missed the birthday K get you to
work so I'll give the super chat now
said happy birthday thank you wow it's
still my birthday even
today the celebration goes on and on
maybe this is why I avoided reading
super chats because I just wanted it to
be my birthday every
day thank you cion
[Music]
bener okay and this one I have to
translate cuz I cannot read
[Music]
this Chan bingu thank you very much
dun I'm finished with these YooHoo
what's the next have I skipped anything
else or can we kind of go back to the
more recent ones
GD do you have the info the
Deets
she I skipped that
too you can go in order until e no
way oh
okay a that reminds me I did have like
uh a really cool idea for a hand cam
stream that combines hand cam with
3D I don't know if I told you about
it I really wanted to do it in this trip
because I already thought about it in
the last trip and then I was thinking oh
no worries I have no time in this trip
but I surely will have time in the next
trip because I'm there for a long time
turns out I have no time
but I guess I'll just do it
again next time or not again but I'll
I'll do the idea when I'm in Japan next
time my pleasure will arrive Wednesday
let's go you mean you mean the fogy
waa yay frogy
Wawa okay then uh
shii Shi so cute she want me you know
like I want to tell you like the D
dynamics of cuz I'm sure you're
interested the Dynamics of
our what do you normally call it
backstage
room she w
we like she had she was playing on her
switch a lot of the time and was sitting
on like on the side alone most of the
time but like she would still join
conversations like uh here and there
didn't seem like she was
like like she chose to isolate herself a
little bit by being on the side but I
just feel like that's kind of you know
she w we
[Music]
style she was playing games I don't know
which game anymore but like the whole
time she was playing
game kind of introverted yeah but still
always ready to bring herself back into
the conversation
[Music]
yeah uh for they were of course staying
together and then they would like always
be um open to joining fun things like
the the slapjack game that they
[Music]
played are we lagging again
no I feel like mostly everybody was like
kind of
social but certain people sticked
together
and yeah she will we was kind of like on
on the side and then I for me
I I I went to the like manager room a
lot cuz I don't
know the the girls room was a bit
overwhelming for me sometimes and I just
wanted to kind of
like chat with like jenma and so on
sometimes so and I ate like my food
sometimes over there
too I kept on going
[Music]
there yeah then I was I was signing my
Polaroids for a while over there because
the girls got like so loud and then
we're hitting the table in the in our
room where I was signing the polars I
was like I'm out of here I took my
polars and went into the staff room and
signed my polar wordss there for a while
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah so I spent some time
there but besides
that honestly I guess everybody was
like hanging out
there having fun talking playing that
weird horny dating
game but as I told you me and Nissa like
stayed away from that we were like ah if
it was a girl maybe but hm like this no
[Music]
oh actually the
crony crony
like like so she like gave someone a
massage and I heard that I was like oh I
want a massage too and then I was
looking for her and I find her like in
the changing room
sleeping and she slept so deeply she
kept on disappearing for
naps any time she could find she was she
disappeared for a nap and then
eventually Amit found out about it and
also joined her for a nap so I ended up
finding I I think it was both of them
was someone else it was biu too at some
point I think I found no okay wait it
was B and
crony um with their faces in opposite
directions sleeping on the couch in the
changing room
like people just eventually joined
crony and then on a separate occasion
yeah it was not the time do were napping
together I don't think so on a separate
occasion I found am napping on the couch
like damn these girls are
[Laughter]
sleepy the couch wasn't that
big they seem pretty like cuddled up
together was a popular couch yeah
definitely and I was wondering how the
hell can they sleep
there cuz like I
think I don't know if it yeah no crony
was at one point
sleeping while the girls were all
screaming about the horny dating game
like they were legit so
loud I'm like how the hell can this girl
sleep is she really
asleep how does she man manage to sleep
[Music]
because it's like literally the same
room it was just like separated by a
curtain
[Music]
amazing must have been really tired
yeah n we wait we were there like for
hours like so long so understandable
honestly I was surprised like you know
not tired and was able to get like good
amount of sleep every
day so you
know let's rate the Shi super CH j7 n j
Monkey py D feel Legacy D left s d uh
Tom dang oh here I think I see
some uncommon names again
[Music]
uh DCH thanks for the pinky finally
caught you okay the name is a family
name from Celtic ah
dor do dor means hurt unlucky cursed the
original DCH was my ancestor W and the
bad luck was to meet him in
battle what Granddad got into G genology
in his
retirement well you kind of raised more
questions than answer
right now
man what can you give me like this is if
this is a tldr can you give me the long
version of this
tangent maybe on
Twitter I need to know more it's not
like it's not like you were cut off by
the Super Chat like limit right that's
still pretty short why did you not tell
me more please explain please expand
[Music]
yeah
more deep lore about
D
ping and duck attack oh wait it
continues there's two pinkies as for the
duck attack that's a totally different
thing Avan martial arts Technique No Way
nah you're just you're just [\h__\h] with
me you shout out a tribal battlecry then
headbutt bites bite and wings slap your
target I learned this after giving birth
BR to some ducks in the
park then the swan
Wars dot dot dot
what this is [\h__\h] you just came up
with that because I pronounce it like
Duck
attack even though it's written
differently so you just came up with all
of that I don't believe
[Music]
you what explain the swan
Wars there doesn't seem to be any more
Super Chat after that from you so I'm
confused thank you for the two pinkies
[Music]
though you thought it was duck attack
yeah because I say it like that but no
it's not it's d a c h a r t a c
[Music]
h
t remember when using an OG board Ouija
board always tell the Spirits by and to
leave and go back to their homes causing
harm to none I'm serious waah
wa I didn't because I want to see the
world
burn dratic Arrow d zly d py d thank you
very much all of
you finish this one can't believe I
skipped all of these and didn't go back
to them oh my God cuz I went backwards
huh cuz I was like oh I don't know where
to start so that's why I went backwards
well that makes perfect sense takanasi
kiar that makes perfect
sense thank you
Tak that's why oh that's why mint was
able to appear right makes
sense okay take a 47 extinction
extinction human extinction human
extinction thank you for the birthday
[Music]
wishes you moved let's
go to where to a different city to a
different country or just
like different apartment or so kechen
entrance La law school you got into law
school
sick amazing I hope that's going well
for you I am imagining that's like
really difficult so much to learn but I
wish you all the best that sounds really
cool another lawyer
awesome you just got out of class
oh all R graduated huh just
kidding our legal team is growing yeah
soon soon we can
take up any kind of
lawsuit with
[Music]
ease
nice py D Che Monkey D unkknown thank
you for the pinky I just got my freee
membership batch for the second time
let's go
oh wait cuz that's your like sub account
but did it become your main account did
you lose your first account
or do you have just two main accounts
more or
less oh man but at least like Honestly
YouTube used to be way more
sussy you're still here a there we go
okay like remember there were many times
where you guys had to make sub accounts
because like he would instantly get
banned for some
reason so you know we got to acknowledge
when YouTube is doing things
right or maybe not because this should
be the
default we should not
necessarily I mean we can acknowledge it
but should we be praising it maybe
[Music]
not that should just be
normal HP V also thank you for the red
super chat first Super Chat ever
yesterday the 13th was my birthday so I
want to give thanks to the gift that
keeps on giving after nearly 4 years
Also let's go sports surely someone will
win hey thank you someone won for sure
it was not us wait we weren't even in
this
one well thank you very much Don and
happy belated birthday to you was that a
good PR w
[Music]
W man it's it's almost as if
I'm spe spec spean H
spean cuz I don't know which one this is
Spanish or
Mexican
or something along the
lines I can't tell it AP part like I
think names are s
similar
from that kind of you
know Mexican sounds cool though yeah and
they speak Spanish in Mexico so it's
like how could I
[Music]
know oh thank you
Hispanic oh there we go I forgot about
that word you Puerto
Rican
nice
hot
spicy that sounds cool Puerto Rico I
want to go to Puerto Rico what's Puerto
Rico what's the
[Music]
capital oh it's a Caribbean Island San
Hanan ooh but Caribbean islands I think
they're so [\h__\h] far
from uh Austria like really hard to
reach well that's beautiful though those
colorful houses what the
hell oh my God I've seen a lot of like
colorful tropical places but this is
like crazy w why are these houses so
cute
[Music]
po iron
Mouse cute it's
gorgeous I wonder how clean the water is
cuz like in pictures like oceans always
look beautiful but then you go there and
IRL is like [\h__\h] ugly but oh my God
there's I found some like Instagram
picture there's so many oh people are
taking so many instagrammy pictures in
these like colorful house alleys
Alleyways that's so
[Music]
cute seems to be well known for
that wow cute
[Music]
wow closer than Brazil
huh but there might not be as many good
easy
flights because of his location
[Music]
the Ocean looks amazing in these
pictures I feel like it might actually
be
[Music]
clean thanks for the membership gift the
azor's island oh no I've heard of
those but aren't they also wait
Portugal oh
wow what is this
beauty even if it's Portugal it might
still be really far yeah pretty far but
but those kind of places again seem to
be hard to reach like there might not be
as many
flights lots of hik
though holy [\h__\h] that's
[Music]
gorgeous what nice gift okay I'm going
to continue not getting too distracted
shall we H chocolate Insomniac
D Jose if I forgot kiss here is kiss R
than pinky greetings tantel love
now let's see if ghost M's prediction on
who wins comes through what did Ghost
guess was it
correct I'm not sure the number surely
wasn't correct but the country
maybe spanking face with the red super
chat woo I finally get to see the match
see a match with the wers cats are
sleeping but they'll be awake
shortly I
um you know we were observing the uh
message
board
um and
then um one of the girls pointed out ha
funny how someone look someone literally
just like put their cat on the message
board and then me and Kelly are like Ah
that's spank that's
[Music]
spanking that yeah that's that's our uh
fan yeah that's spanking time like we
didn't even have to look at
it okay I I looked at it before so I
knew what it was about but Cali didn't
even look at it in that moment oh but
maybe she also saw it before but we
knew I recognized the cat we're like oh
yeah that's that's spanking I'm that's
our
[Music]
fan and they're like wait why do you
know how do you know how do you
recognize a cat and we're like well you
know SP time always chose and talks
about his
cats
yeah what do you mean do you only
recognize Us by our cats of course not
because not all of you have
cats no but like you guys got to admit
like spankenheimer
[Music]
without my cats I would be like [\h__\h]
melted puddle of
nothingness I miss my
cats thank you spanking
[Music]
hik
you I'm in tank Nikolai D thank you good
luck with your military service
100 days left so I mean by now it's
probably like like 50 days left Jor
junor in this
economy
s
spank oh yeah everybody used to use team
speak some nostalgic naan cotton thanks
for the pinky hi attal good to see you
enjoying yourself on stream again well
honestly this is ages ago but could be a
Super Chat that was sent
today could be
today I've been having a conflicting
week some good things but one big bad
thing and it's just left me emotionally
exhausted
no so it's nice to just relax and enjoy
my favorite streamer are you okay have
things like cleared up and
improved I hope so
Nathan are you around are you here
Nathan
H let me hug
you I wish you the best you don't
deserve anything bad none of us do but
you
[Music]
know feel better
more that totally did it right
py D Sky
D
yeah not here right now okay but I hope
you will hear this eventually
p
g Gary g z z Tuesday d h Steven Rose D
black
[Music]
danielia and
space Yi that's already
free what do you mean he's
here I mean Nathan where's
Nathan that's already free streams now
behind do let's go
[Music]
yippee he answered
oh I am
blind I am blinded by your beauty
Nathan you are too
beautiful stop being so
beautiful
okay another
one yum yum yum
[Music]
this little game you know I really
enjoyed it but I I do realize it's maybe
not a good streaming
game unless I mean okay
maybe it depends how you see it I
generally
think
N I guess even Sims is better as a
streaming game I say even Sims but like
Sims used to do really well on my
channel
[Music]
so it was never a bad one but
buckbuster I just I'm just happy you
know that this game now has a spiritual
successor and it's really
cute
yeah did you see ah new Korean seems
yeah I think I saw that but there's I
don't know now now that my brain is
trying to remember it I
I can't because there's been many like
games in the past one year or so that
I've seen that try to recreate Sims in a
way um enoy yeah that rings a bell but
let's see let
me in oops intoo
intoo ah
[Music]
ah oh my God the trailer gave me a heart
attack you didn't even hear it but the
sound cuz I didn't see the video yet I
was like where did the video why is it
not opening like it opened as like a
minimized video
thingy my
heart ah
surround sound of my headphones too
[Music]
good I don't know like I feel
like no matter who in what way tries to
recreate a Sims game it will never be
better than Sims because Sims always has
this charm and this one yeah it has a
very like too realistic look to it I
agre the inside of like houses on what
from more I see that's like fine and it
gives me Sims Vibes but
yeah some of the city gives me GTA Vibes
for some
[Music]
reason yeah it's it's I mean people say
like people criticize Sims for being too
cartoony but then at the same time I
feel like that's what makes it good I
don't want to play a hyper realistic
Sims um
I will say
that in terms of like art Direction so
to say Sims one and two versus like
three and
four or especially four there's a
difference there that I understand if
you don't like it
uh but it's it's still like good I think
I still like it generally and it's not
like it doesn't have to be like hyper
realistic it shouldn't
[Music]
be oh that reminds me I in the in the
Nintendo Direct I saw this like Sims
like cute like Animal Crossing Style
game uh
being uh ported to Nintendo switch I
guess it was on something else
before M that looked cute if pushed
directly it could would have an animal
crossing kind of hype or so within whole
life I feel like there's potential
there there is potential there I think
maybe even only within I and ID I don't
know I I might try to get people into
[Music]
it I see it as a completely different
game from Sims honestly so I see it more
as an animal crossing kind of thing and
for that I think it's
[Music]
fine yeah you tell us soon let's go I'm
so
excited okay Jacob for7 space for now we
have a rainbow from valian did I not
read this yet
wow kiaha paying my rainbow taxs and
making use of the space to explain my
schedule a bit since you looked confused
the last time I do have indeed most of
my weekends when I'm at the base wait my
ear what the
[Music]
[\h__\h]
sorry weird pressure in my
ear that was weird uh I do have indeed
most of my weekends when I'm at the base
thing is I'm actually very rarely at the
base oh we do a lot of training Fields
shooting Rangers specialization courses
VII pirate French cfp should all know
about this one as well as outside
deployments and these usually mean 24/7
work for example earlier this year I was
on the warship in the Mediterranean Sea
in the mountains in Norway and at
a s of last year
oh October of last year I was deployed
in Lebanon it sadly doesn't leave me so
much time uh to watch my favorite silly
orange woman but I still try to catch
your streams whenever I see one and buy
your merch when I can that rubber
chicken is going to look great inside
the
tank no what if somebody like shoots it
and it dies keep an eye out I guess then
it can no that never mind keep an eye
out for me if you watch the Olympics as
I'll be part of security detail oh yeah
right you said that I feel like I read
that what the hell that sounds familiar
to
[Music]
me what if it stops the bullet and saves
his life a it will it
will chicken got
drafted
cute my precise role in the Army is tank
Gunner and anti-tank guided missile
operator enough about me time for more
chicken thank you that's cool to read
all that information thank you for
sharing it with
us I was just like so surprised like
even if you have free time I did not
expect you to be at a freaking
convention I did not expect you to have
time to go to a
convention I did not expect you to like
be there and like in the middle of the
crowd and
like it was just so crazy that out of
all the people who are there like you
were the one that I chose to out of the
crowd to answer a question in our
panel I was like weird
[Music]
coincidence and yeah I think like you
didn't even tell me the name yet and I
already like kind of felt like this aura
from you I was like this this could be
[Music]
fan see like I'm so crazy how do I know
these
things some of you guys even if I don't
know your face like you you just have
this like
Vibe oh this this could be that person I
had that before with a different person
I think where I didn't know their face
or so but I just assumed like this is
probably that person because so and so
their
[Music]
Vibes
yeah and I mean okay a certain amount of
like logical conclusion because for
example in this case it was France so it
would be somebody who's somebody who's
like somebody wants to somebody who's
dressed up in a good amount of merch
seems very
very infatuated with me right um I
didn't expect you to have that much
merch
but it did give me the vibe that you
must like me very much so it must be a
um a hardcore
kfp and what's more hardcore than
someone watching me inside of the
tank so hardcore kfp in France hm
there's not that many that I'm aware of
and then also uh male
okay well okay
not there there's just not that many
that are very active in the
chat so logical conclusion I
guess the best place to watch W inside
of tank yeah it's safe really safe
environment in there
honestly do you have a blanket in there
a imagine imagine him like
the word cozying himself up in the
blanket inside of the tank from outside
it looks so so cool and so hardcore and
manly and then I wonder if his like
mates
know what it looks
inside him freaking snuggled up in that
animal
blanket and a cute chicken d duck
sitting in there and other like cute waa
merchandise hope he doesn't get
bullied but maybe there's like other a
couple of other like like-minded people
maybe not necessarily whole life fans
but like just
Anime uh enjoyers in
general tanks have multiple
people I thought he might have his own
tank like solo tank see valdian you need
to answer another question I hope you
even though the Super Chat is super
freaking old I hope you will find that I
have answered your Super Chat finally uh
here I hope you will be made aware of
[Music]
it imagine you're in the tank you start
streaming spanks
SP Sparks
[Music]
H
um maldi and thanks for the
wibo hope you don't get spanked in the
Army for watching anime
girl
spring no not quite not quite but I'll
take it
specs cuz
spanks um
guide the
way
turn the
butt all
red M
day don't stop don't
stop just spank me some
[Music]
more um
[Laughter]
Y
what I'm going to move on come on
come a don't learn this English from me
Monkey
nction D un CH D alud than for the red
super chat can you get my good side oh
was I taking pictures what is this
stream oh cuz I was making movies Al L
starring in my movie my Blockbuster
thank you for free right for
free I was losing so much money you have
to work for free for me you would do it
for me right you guys are already doing
it you all are working for free for me
it's a given now I'm sure thank you
Saluda hope you enjoyed my
movies just spank me your way ha I'm
sure narissa would like that version of
the song pudding cat dangun positive
Android dangun candy stamps danash idle
business regulation director Dan thanks
for the red super chat H our records
show that you have not corrected your
violations before the deadline we regret
to inform you that a warrant for arrest
has been issued and the great yellow
Oster stre tanaki Shakari has been
select to manage kfp as a new
CEO too bad she's dead killed
her she's no
more she will not save you from
anything kfp is mine and it will always
belong to
me you cannot take it away from me I'm
too
[Music]
powerful give
up bow to your one and only true
Overlord Tanki I have a tank
[Music]
okay the
is oh not sure if I saw that there's a
phoenix unit what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] than you
oh it's still called Council R you know
what at this point it's kind of
nostalgic I want to keep it that
way Tanaka d d Rodan D Devin d valian d
d Bob d g
d d Jim Tracy D zip D
and today I watch your stream until the
end for the first time a long time I
haven't watched the stream Until the End
these days it was nice to be able to
watch it until the end today thank you
for the stream for the fun stream come
Sita well today also should be good time
for you I wonder are you
[Music]
here are you here nip nip
cool H maybe not already
sleeping well good night to you I need
to
learn Korean again I am such a lost
cause but I feel like all I need to do
is just get back on to dual
lingo this one this one Korean bro his
name name is Kim
a changed your name literally for me
didn't
[Music]
you guys
I know I wrote all about it on
Twitter
but okay no I've said my part on Twitter
I will not bring it up now
I will not bring it
up no no no I've said all that needs to
be said on
Twitter about the Korean documentary
[Music]
yeah but I was a bit sad with how few
people knew what I was talking about I
mean it was just the usual people
again the usual couple of people who
understand what I'm talking about when I
talk
[Music]
you just started watching it let's
go let me know when you're at the part
that's quite shocking where even I
thought I'm not going to support this
group because this feels kind of [\h__\h]
up but now I I do think like after that
one part where you feel like wow this
[Music]
is like traumatizing after this that it
really seems
to like calm down again and there's like
no more drama really after that
mostly it seems to be
chilling so that's why I kind of I guess
forgot about that the fact that I didn't
want to support
them yeah but the craziest thing okay
whatever I'm not going to bring it up
but let me just say I'm going to bring
up I guess like imagine you sign up
for a like audition thingy where you'll
be trained and everything to maybe
eventually be chosen by judges only
judges uh from the companies that are
working together to be put into an idol
group and you get trained for months
actually and then like suddenly suddenly
they tell you it's a [\h__\h] Survival
show which at first I thought oh well I
mean don't make such a big drama about
it it's not like that much of a
difference is it but turns out it
actually was because you can tell in the
documentary the moment they make it into
a um Survival show um I was actually so
confused about this at at the time when
when videos
from that show were put up on YouTube
but their Survival show was kind of kind
of weird compared to others they didn't
have like the whole process up because
they were making the documentary and
keeping all the process that behind the
scenes for the documentary to be
released way later and at the time all
they put up on YouTube for people to
judge whether or not they like these
girls and who they're going to vote for
was the performances so you would know
nothing about the girls's personality
really I mean okay they would post I
guess they would post up uh end up
posting like Tik toks and
stuff um but most people I guess just
judged it from the performances which is
fine too that's that's the most
important part in a way um but you could
notice that it was like they had no idea
what was going on behind the scenes the
fans at the time you could tell from the
rankings and like originally they had a
ranking in terms of like skill made by
all the the teachers the dance teachers
the teachers and so on and after that
the like the pyramid got
completely scrambled and messed up
because of the like popularity votes
coming in and so people with a way lower
skill set for suddenly in the top five
or
so because people were just voting based
on looks like that's definitely a thing
that where I would think
okay I would be pissed if I was in a
survival show
suddenly when now people are getting
into this group just based on their
looks cuz they're all skilled in the end
they're all
great but it doesn't matter anymore if
you're number one in dancing the girl
who was like for forever number one in
dancing didn't make it into the
group at all like she was one of the
least popular girls there were like a
bunch of American girls but also like
all over the world girls like someone
from the Philippines and someone from uh
Switzerland and this and that and you
noticed that like for example
Philippines the girl from the
Philippines got insane amount of support
from the people in her country um and
became like top number one constantly
thanks to the Philippines votes cuz she
was also the only one from the
Philippines and then the Americans they
were stal Americans so all the American
votes were kind of split between them
but at the same time the American ones
like the American votes just didn't care
so much about voting for the sake of
just someone being from the same country
while the Philippines people would just
like only vote for Philippines you know
they wouldn't care about any other
contestant they would just vote for her
because she's from the Philippines you
know what I'm trying to say like there's
certain
countries uh like certain girls from
certain countries who had an advantage
just because their country was like
extra patriotic I guess
and then the American girls were totally
[\h__\h] nobody cared about
them yeah so people like once the
survival uh show and like online voting
aspect was added the ranking changed so
abruptly from first being skill-based
and now suddenly it was the cute girls
at the top and the girls with the most
like like
excited motivated country fan base would
be at the top so I would be pissed
too if I wasn't positively affected by
[Music]
that
yeah and there was this drama about this
one girl she's really cute you know and
she is talented but she's like from
Switzerland right and she joins the
whole thing later uh she hasn't been
trained as long as the others and then I
guess like I understand like she must
have felt really overwhelmed by the
amount of work and the amount of
discipline necessary they had like hours
and hours of practice every [\h__\h] day
it was really
intense um and she just wouldn't show up
to practice quite often and so the other
trainees were kind of
like upset with her and weren't having
it and you know
um they were just pissed because they
were working their butts off and she
just wouldn't come to practice but it
got worse and this is you know I think
like if you look at it from like a
psychology POV it's really just in
understandable so when the survival
aspect was
introduced people were like before this
girl she wouldn't come to practice and
her skill set was so low so she was like
one of the last five contestants in
terms of skill but uh on the on the on
the pyramid but then the survival thing
comes in people vote for her just
because she's cute suddenly she's in the
top five for doing nothing she was still
not showing up for practices so the
other girls were so pissed and were like
that's like what everybody's like making
a drama about now because the other
girls were pissed and then people are
trying to make it out as they were
bullying her they were really not most
people who are saying that didn't even
watch the documentary properly and or
fully I think
um but I do I I don't think there was
any bullying it didn't look like there
was any bullying but I do understand the
resentment very much and in a stressful
situation like that where like suddenly
you're in a [\h__\h] Survival show and
you realize that all your hard work may
be [\h__\h] useless now because it
doesn't
matter because your
votes the votes are coming in for
different reasons now of course you're
going to be stressed out of course
you're going to be salty and like pissed
at it you you didn't sign up for this
you didn't [\h__\h] sign up for
this and then this girl who's not
showing up for practice is getting all
the [\h__\h] votes what the [\h__\h] I would
be so pissed I understand anybody who
who would be pissed but I also think
that girl was cute and I understand why
she wouldn't go to practice because she
was overwhelmed and different culture
like you know not the same kind of
like mindset and all that and she had to
learn that and she ended up learning it
but I understand both very well how you
know you just feel like I don't want to
go
because well I don't want to I'm scared
I'm anxious I can't do this I feel
overwhelmed at least a2k didn't have
voting system wait wait I'm getting
confused at2k was the one with vicha
right so
vicha God nobody like except for two
people in this chat will understand what
I'm talking about but yeah I I I so what
I what I think is like while the
documentary was kind of like showing
messed up parts of it they definitely
did like so much of a better job in
putting together a group that is managed
by K-pop companies but aimed at the
Western Market because in vich like what
the [\h__\h] having a [\h__\h] what
13-year-old girl in the group and the
overall image like that was it's just so
childish and the song they debuted with
and everything how are you going to
Market that to the like you can Market
that to other countries but that's not
what's going to be popular as a like
look look at the cup groups that are
popular globally like black pink mature
as [\h__\h] girl crush don't make a freaking
like cut group when you want to promote
it in the western world and like you
need you need more older members like
I'm sorry but like
bro yeah and like the music they were
cre I like it you know but also I didn't
like the final lineup I really think
they made a mistake with the final
lineup I don't think that much about uh
the group they created with the other
program that I just told you about they
actually did
great at making a group that would
appeal to the Western
Market
honestly there's still like maybe one
member I would have added
but they did really well and their debut
song I mean they they have several I
guess but the one that they're promoting
the most now the touch touch touch touch
okay it's not really like a cool ass
song but I do think it's a song that
could do well in the charts and at least
it's better than
the what was it only only only only one
only only only only
one how did that song go
Al that wasn't that their second
song first song was more lame I don't
remember ah girls girls of the Year
actually I like that song wasn't that
the second
song
[Music]
wait
yeah
yeah h
[Music]
yeah their like first song was this y o
univ visual is kind of
lame oh
yeah I mean I still kind of like
it although the chorus is lame sorry I'm
rewatching it right
now and nobody understands this so maybe
I should just
go nobody understands what I'm talking
[Music]
about will you apply for your origion
again
no honestly
like it's probably already too late
again for
Austria even if I wanted to
and I don't know like
I'm too busy anyway and then I don't
know how much confidence I have in my
life performance and it's just too
complicated they probably don't know how
to do it like they don't think they can
do it like in terms of like rules like
your revision rules they probably think
it's too complicated um I think that's
probably the
reason why they turned me down
previously uh and I think it's possible
it can be made possible but they
probably just think it's too complicated
they don't want to bother with
it
but also like the last one was kind of a
[\h__\h] show in terms of politics so and it
seems to be like that almost every year
recently so um I'm just not going
to
yeah it would be even M then it would be
a
great
promotion I don't
[Music]
know if they if Austria were to approach
me I would probably consider
it but
yeah
promotion I need a massage
I'm going to get one tomorrow I
think I feel strain in my shoulder
blades like between my spine and my
shoulder
[Music]
blades applying for your version game
was Chima honestly yeah it did I don't
think I would have gone with Chima uh
under normal
[Laughter]
circumstances uh
yeah because like I just went with like
because I was you know we were in time
pressure I was like hey girls what kind
of demo tapes do we have right now that
I can choose from like already written
songs
basically U and then I was like H out of
these I don't know if any of these are
perfect for your vision but if anything
it would be this I said and then we
speedran the production I probably
wouldn't have gone for this if it wasn't
for the stress and the pressure the time
pressure
but it turns out it was a good choice
people really like ca press
[Music]
four so guys I'm going to go now we read
all of these too I think I think I just
finished
it
um yeah I did so four streams
phito y Yi even anami liked it yeah
animi listens to
it no please don't go oh my God don't
panic I'm still like here where do
Webers go when they end stream into the
void into the [\h__\h] void no no I'm
real I don't go into the void I will go
into
bed I will literally walk into
bed I will stand in
bed I am ghost I cannot lie in bed I
walk in bed
yeah let's go to
bed and thank you for watching today
hope you had fun all blue
[Music]
protocol I will be on official channel
on side and it will be I think 11:00
a.m. jsd I don't know what time that is
for you guys it's on my schedule though
uh
hold is it did I put a
time I
know 400
a.m. well okay yeah Europe is a bit
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah the reservation is up so if
you want to check the time for
sure uh check out the reservation on the
Channel yeah it's
F and Ena IIs and me I
think so it will be
fine let's
go in German we say Al in good night my
throat hurt a little bit I go now
tomorrow I dance and then dance dance
dance with my hands hands hands
oh oh happy birthday star
Platinum
congrats
yippee
yippee thank you for
watching thank you
wowow
bye-bye
bye-bye bye-bye
[Music]
oh I got to watch load of the Rings you
SE I don't think I meant I think I won't
watch it until I'm back in Austria I
think did they release all episodes at
once or is it one by
[Music]
one I think I might just watch it in
Austra cuz I want to watch it on my big
[Music]
TV oh so that's where I'm logged into my
Amazon
so three
episodes now and then we ah okay well
then I can't watch it at all uh at once
anyway so I'll wait so don't spoil
me and yeah and then I need to watch
Umbrella
Academy not on the flight home Nah if
anything I'll watch umbr Academy but I
realized I'm it's it's less than like 2
weeks now I'm I'm I can finally like
look at the calendar positively and not
feel like existential
crisis the end is near and my last
quests are to be completed in terms of
work my recording is near my
fredd Solo solo well not really solo but
yeah my 3D life
is to be recorded soon the end is near
in the most positive
way my cats I I I can I can smell
him yeah so for my sanity's sake and for
your guys' sanity's sake because you
just miss me streaming regularly I
guess it's it's
coming I see it on the horizon
[Music]
I need the cat cud I need them
now but I have to wait a few more
days it's more than a week
but it's soon
bye-bye
[Music]