[Music]
foreign
hello are you surprised to see me hey
guess what me too
ah
this was arranged so suddenly
but you know
[Music]
fun fact I woke up like 30 minutes ago
anyway
so guess what
doing a uh Among Us
and a hollow live collaboration
and look at it look at this we get
stickers
why pretty sure this is automatic why is
this not going
what the heck
dude oh there we go so look
Isn't that cool I can't see anything
yeah so oh my God this is so
my life in shambles anyway
so getting you can get a standy from
Amelia Watson and guard girl and
hoshinova Muna
yeah and not only that you get a
keychain and a sticker featuring
everyone oh look at that
is it not beautiful
I'm going to cry like Fountains of tears
all over my face and it's gonna be great
and the order is available until
November 28th uh 23.59 jsd kind of like
uh when my essays are due and or only uh
10 days left so
go go get it right now if you don't have
it
and then it's an in-game collaboration
too and there are items and Designs
covering 68 talents
and yeah like we said there's a diorama
stand
featuring 10 and gain talents and
Hollow crew made plushie site which is
also cool
and then the emergency meeting keychains
like this from above
like this look at that it's cool I I cut
it out because you know it's getting in
the way but see that's the whole thing
isn't it cool it's very cute
[Music]
and then
um sorry
I did not even drink water uh a
collaboration stickers and uh yeah
it's cool it's great
so what are you waiting for
go get him right now and the Cosmic Cube
thing it's available until December 20th
uh Pacific and 21st for uh Japan time
and
yeah you can you can download it and
stuff
and there's also like inner sloth made
merch so you can go check that out too
can you tell us an EST it's like three
hours
at at three more hours to Pacific by my
brain can't do simple math right now so
yeah but I think well did I just speed
run everything I don't know how to live
my life now
[Music]
and uh
oh man
[Music]
I think I think I may have
done something yeah you know what I'll
fix it later yeah it's all good so you
can go check it out I will be up
updating it in the description so be
sure to check it out
it'll be awesome
oh or something I don't know
I guess it'll be good and then
what else
yeah
and also yeah did I tell you that hollow
life made merch regarding this
collaboration but you know inner sloth
also did it too
so you know go go check it out right now
oh man you know what I'm just gonna
update it right now I'm gonna update it
right now give me one second I'm going
to show a piece of my mind in this
description
[Music]
oh now I see the problem
what the heck
angled brackets aren't allowed why
[Music]
so yeah we're gonna be playing with like
some of the some of the IDS some of the
en is going to be fun
[Music]
this is this is great it's everything
that I could have ever wanted I don't
even know what I'm saying anymore
um
[Music]
but I like Among Us Among Us Among Us
gave us some really great memes I
honestly did not think the memes would
last this long did I say that I can
probably say that right
because I'm saying a good thing
oh
wait
[Music]
okay I'm gonna I'm gonna do it I'm gonna
do it
I'm gonna do it
I'm gonna do it for realsies
oh
shy I I
[Music]
I'm gonna do it watch watch right now
like watch I'm going to change it
nobody will ever know
[Music]
done
yeah do you see it do you see it yeah so
you can go check it out in the
description right now it's like nothing
ever happened don't worry about it
yeah so go check it out diorama stance
keychains stickers plushies The World is
Yours Seize the Day carpe diem
whoa
you can go check it out on the hollow
live website for the merch and then and
then the inner sloth store for the merch
like oh man the world is your oyster
go go go go get him because it's it's
limited edition
[Music]
because like I said
recover made merge it's gonna be
available until November 28th 23 59.
and then for the end game collab The
Cosmic Cube it's going to be available
until December 21st I just got kicked
out of the room
[Music]
uh
man
foreign
[Music]
part of the deal no it's it's really
nice
but I did get kicked out
we need to make a room again
who's gonna make the room
[Music]
ah
oh wait are we
[Music]
hey you know and you know the inactivity
like the room being closed due to
inactivity it's been lasting longer it's
it's awesome it's great
foreign
[Music]
all right okay remote works
[Applause]
oh hello there we go hello
hi hello
hi hi
hello hello
everyone tired
hello
everyone like a morning voice do we want
to do like a you know a classic
introduction of everyone yeah it can
also be a soundtrack maybe yeah a sound
check let's start by the top
hello everyone hello Tanya melfisa from
polarvin second generation how's my
voice
it's amazing
thank you
next what was um
the rat I'm gonna Channel my sleepiness
to being the best sauce rat that I can
um
[Music]
oh no you silly you silly
in the room yet I don't sit here in the
room no I'm not isn't it
I made a new one
okay
we are hiding what are you hiding
coconut I'm shy do you want to hide with
me yeah
she's naked
oh no
exhibitionism
why are you not wearing anything
oh
[Music]
naked compared to everyone else
is is you're just beautiful you don't
need yeah
you are born naked the natural beauty
why was that done an echo
I'll join you've convinced me
returning to nature
clothes I don't have any clothes
oh my God oh my God
[Music]
hello it's me Oro crony from Hollow live
English Council and I'm going to kill
everyone if I can that is
laughs
the sound effect is sending me
they say crony is low but I have her on
Max I can't do anything else
is this your voice do you want me to
just talk louder or something
enunciate speak from the stomach crony
speak higher yeah
you're too low
yeah
well I think that needed a buttons but
then nothing happens I'm sorry
oh my god oh say again crony this is
this loud enough now
yeah I think you sound better okay yeah
yeah
me
too
crazy already
amazing
thank you for bringing the energy that
we need yeah we need that caffeine here
by your energy I felt that in my
eyeballs I know how did I whoa how do
you feel it in your eyeballs
in your eyeballs who's pants
[Music]
foreign
Indonesia generation
[Applause]
[Music]
you didn't register to me that you're
saying oh hi I thought you were saying
Ohio but then you just cut it halfway
because you couldn't be bothered to save
it
I am saving time here come on
okay
[Music]
oh no I'm the uh
oh that was like some good like
okay let's see
where are my fake tasks I'm gonna go to
electrical
and then I'm gonna go to the reactor
just in case and then I'm gonna do the
wires gonna do the wires
laughs
foreign
I'm going to fix it
so that I seem like okay and everyone's
doing good right and I'm gonna close it
there
or I'd be like oh my god what the heck
I'm gonna go to Med Bay
because why not
oh okay
and then I'm gonna check the samples
and I'm gonna wait
and then oh I was at Bed Bay
close this
did I close that I did I'm such a silly
little goose
close the security I guess delay the
inevitable
foreign
hi I'm hi I'm Stu hello I missed you
guys hello hello hello hello
[Music]
two buddies yeah there's yeah oh yeah
where was everyone at
um
I just arrived on the shield
in case you're trying to speak your
music
oh sorry
um
the body I need to look at the map okay
and I actually saw a member go in that
direction right before I discovered the
body
oh
Bernie would you like to explain why you
were there right before I discovered the
body
wait but like I've been traveling like
everywhere else like I've been traveling
the right side of the section so I
didn't really notice anything like I was
checking samples so that's why three
seconds before that I when I found the
body why did you not report body if you
were there
I'm so tired
there was something there I didn't even
go to the right side the whole time
are you sure
we've already lost two crew members
yeah we were on the right side
yeah okay I should kill Bay first
foreign
oh
my God
because you just killed
I didn't see it did you all see it I
didn't know it was like it was like yeah
in front of my eyes oh okay I we were
all there together so cronies kind of
sauce yeah yeah obvious
um
me and Anya were together though
well goodbye Connie wait can I enter
mine well you know okay fine I'm just
gonna like yes I am the Imposter but
guess what
um
who's the other one
I'm gonna give this the Innocence the
win so
um
it's actually not
yeah
no I'm sorry for the team kill I'm so
sorry
[Laughter]
because I already said Anya instead of
so they're gonna be suspicious you know
foreign
The Imposter said that the next imposter
is someone don't believe it
which means that they're gonna be
innocent the only two people remaining
were Kiara and moon so I had to choose
between the two
yeah
we both did so much work for us to win
that round right yes
[Laughter]
yeah but thank you for not voting me out
appreciate it is missing in the room
hello
thank you
Ollie like when I was about to walk over
and Anya was there and I was like crony
you just got me in so much trouble
it worked out though I'm also sorry to
everyone in advance but hey that's the
game
man I was like when when you guys were
in the discussion and Courtney was like
no it was like people were there and
then everyone else seemed not convinced
and I'm like she
come here guys
that was so funny yeah
I couldn't see it because I was doing
like tasks
and then like I was like okay it must be
yeah
and like I was like I was hoping I was
hoping that Zeta would say something so
that I didn't see I didn't see it but I
was like don't ask yeah I was just very
lucky that ran the funny thing is that I
was like I was about to go out from that
room so if only you had waited for like
a few more seconds I probably wouldn't
have thought that
yeah okay
learned her lesson for next round right
yeah
faster twice
I can't believe
that
I'm so [\h__\h] sick of this
okay where am I okay it's this way
and the go do the Pew peop
oh wait that's not the pew pew that's
this
the thing going
okay I'm gonna do this
electrical okay
[Music]
okay why is nobody like fixing
okay dudes seriously
stacked though oh
wait that was too early oh no
give me a break
it's very dangerous
people
because paws are two times in a row
right yeah and I was trying my best
trying to turn it on but people kept
turning it off
thank you
he stopped and watched and I was like
okay when's this gonna be done
I was at there at the scene too but if
you wouldn't have just admitted
immediately that it was you then I
wouldn't have known because there was so
much going on
[Music]
I was I was in there I was in there
because electrical was out and everyone
else was there yeah yeah yeah how can we
know we know it was her we don't know if
it was her I mean you can try
the animation of Corona killing it okay
yeah so I don't know because like
the way I saw a movie but like I don't
know I'm not I just arrived no no it's
not Mommy I saw granny in front of my
eyes killing it really whatever
unfortunate but like I actually did see
movie
what Luna said chroni just incriminated
herself right I mean you can try
thank you
tell us the other one you it's you who
exactly who knows
okay
[Music]
I just wanted to be an innocent oh wait
that was too early whoopsie
man I should have done the stack kill
earlier on when everybody was occupied
test test
but while he'll live and learn
all right who else was the Imposter I
forgot it
oh what are you doing
don't hesitate Be not Afraid go kill
to your heart's content
all right
let's do O2 this time
[Music]
oh
go get some water while you're at it
for a split second it would have been
really good for a stack kill
but that was way too quick uh if only I
was like a few seconds faster my Shields
are working that's great our visual
tasks on or off
all right
let's block someone in here
[Music]
all right
foreign
[Music]
second and then she went out immediately
oh I was just checking to see what's
inside
why won't you check who's inside why
can't I check who's inside I can be like
oh someone's there why won't I don't
know man that was dinosaurs yeah yeah if
you don't have any tasks like and inside
the electrical then why won't you go
inside because I just want to see who's
inside and see if I could stick to
anyone
I mean Ollie and me were like going out
of the room why why couldn't you like go
with us instead where is I'm sorry where
is this
going out
but like you you like you you were like
going inside for like one second and
then you came out immediately
yeah because if you suck I don't want to
get like find someone then why didn't
you go with us
well because I don't want to get killed
there
last time last time we were all in
electrical we got somebody got killed
but
I don't know um
okay somebody stick with me then oh no
okay
cool people for that
all right dudes
thank you
I think it's being narrowed down to Zeta
but I'm I mean this might be a win for
the civilians
how else do you call the innocence by
the way
like I know they're like imposters right
[Music]
crewmates right
ain't nothing but a heart
don't change that
don't do it don't do it don't do it Bae
Let It Go
don't go there
nobody go there okay I have to keep
following Zeta
oh Zeta I know you're scared but
sometimes
you have to take risks
that's what the game is all about
but then again yeah they're all going in
groups so I can see how hard that can be
but look how well that turned out for
you well the beginning of the game yeah
it turned out pretty good but like the
second one I did I did the stack kill a
little too early
where people would be done
what up what up hello I was watching the
admin thing when we were all in the
admin room and then I saw someone
teleporting from
storage to the to the main lobby
isn't the three of us who were in the
admin room and it wasn't yeah it wasn't
me phone and Kiana you know what's
what's interesting is that Zeta came off
the Dead
yeah I came from yeah but I wasn't I was
like going walking I was walking I don't
know I don't see anyone teleporting
though but Zetta Zeta was like yeah I
said I came to admin
because I saw you guys
I was in security we were doing stuff
interesting so that's interesting I'm
I'm suspicious interesting
so can you describe
to arrive at your destination
but I'm just gonna say I vanished my
task s
the wiring okay so so it could be a task
one yeah let's let's pick up for those
who
finishes
who haven't who haven't finished the
task
[Music]
no I hope you like space oxygenzetta
laughs
run faster
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
I didn't teleport by the way
I can't get up in the pain
can I just mention that in the
just was not getting
it
crazy I thought you were just ignoring
me on purpose I have no idea how that
song goes I didn't even know that was a
song until later on oh my God
[Laughter]
like I'm standing there and you might
jump
guys
you want to try a different map or stay
in the same map girls maybe
maybe I'll try it
I sure hope I don't get imposter because
I don't know these
yeah okay
might be fun okay
oh there you go
thank you thank you
thank you I'll see nothing one second
one second step on me
excuse that they don't know the map well
so they didn't know where to go no women
exactly but I'm wrong I never know where
to go
um yeah
okay bye everyone
[Music]
I don't know why that's so funny oh man
[Laughter]
so the key is like you have to remain
consistent while you're
like an imposter
and an innocent so that people would die
have a harder time finding a difference
because they could be like
okay well it looks like I'm not getting
that opportunity today but like you know
it's best to let them know how you're
how you're like
the crony again well she's not the
impossible wait what do you mean tell me
again
oh office office
um
didn't you report
oh
yeah
I think
no I was from the office and then it was
on the left room right left from other
office I think so I was in the office
and then I go after you I know you're in
the right room Anya yeah
and then you saw it it was like it was
dark so like I should kill Anya next
I was right behind you you seemed a bit
sus
I was right behind her oh she was like
acting a bit sus in that hallway right
before she entered the right office so
in front of me it's Anya yeah but I was
behind you
so I was yeah
was actually on the left left side of
the office I saw her I was in the office
I was in the office and then I saw
something going away
yeah I think mommy is near
Communications or something yeah yeah
Senpai was like around there but I don't
know how do we know
self report I didn't see it first yeah
they and Anya are kind of teaming up
against Muna
I don't know I don't know if there's
enough information or anything
um
said nothing in this meeting
did say something
how cute
ah sucks
don't kill anyone while I'm doing this
task I'm actually going to kill you
now you can kill
it's pretty relaxing
me like
uh
sorry
[Music]
it's kind of peaceful I like be like
don't kill don't kill
okay now I'm done
hello everyone
I am done with my tasks
not that you can see
just wanted to say oh no but just saying
okay
foreign
oh yeah
forgot Muno was an imposter let's see
yeah move now you can't kill anyone yet
maybe if one of them
head out then you can start plotting
what is this weird standoff
okay they all left
IO
someone die in storage nope
oh actually maybe
no this comes
huh
oh hey
welcome back
foreign
on the way to the Bay was suspicious of
Muna and I didn't see her the whole
round no I was with Mommy before but I
go with Mommy before yeah I didn't see
nothing but I know I was in The Boiler
Room I'm still doing my thoughts
[Music]
um
I was in the in the with Walnut exactly
before fauna only and Zeta we made right
and we're just like standing there yeah
in the emergency room yeah
yeah
oh yeah the office and then final went
to the specimen room and then we met up
with Anya and then we went to the
laboratory I was mostly on the right
side of the map the whole time yeah me
too so I can be on the left side of the
map
um where are you I thought I saw you oh
yeah I guess I just wait you said right
side right
yeah wait never mind never mind I guess
that is
nice but we don't have any imposters
voted out yet right that's kind of bad
yeah yeah this is kind of bad I mean
there's two people left right I don't
know how long it is
[Music]
and and I mean if you die you can do
your task faster so it's a win-win
boxes I'm already done with my castle
I'll just follow people around I'm only
I have like one more I have one more I
have like one more
okay
uh
foreign
[Music]
I was thinking wait or can we not kill
again do I have to report before we can
kill again
excuse me
yeah it's a new mode haven't you heard
it's there to explain yeah why did you
miss it you should have prepared and you
wouldn't have you wouldn't have missed
it uh-huh oh yeah right gaslighting is
the victim's fault okay
oh
yeah
that's just a new feature results
I'm missing one person
oh who gave up put it who is it
uh get in here
I'm sorry oh that's okay I'm learning
the game
two rounds then wait this one is
the next one okay
kind of want to just troll actually
but I shouldn't I'm gonna be the better
person here
oh no it's dark which means I'm gonna go
do my tasks
this is a very good spot to die Did You
Know
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh wait mummy don't do that it was very
scary
what are you doing
I'm gonna hide
laughs
why
oh man
uh that was that was pretty funny though
okay ah come on
it's not crony guys it's not coronary
twice guys
why did you not record it then no I was
on the security cameras I saw it what
and who was it what what
could you what was it
your body
well I saw it on the security cameras it
was mermaid standing over crony's dead
body and also walking away
earlier to creep her house
when she died why didn't you report her
what wait wait what was her natural
state
I didn't see her body
oh
my God give me the lights out
first part of the game
I believe I don't know I have no idea um
because she was running she was like
there and then she went the opposite
direction so I don't know if she really
didn't see it or she said I don't know
another double M I think it's a double M
imposter no I didn't see crony died so I
I think they honestly but okay I mean
she did walk over my body
um oh
thank you goodbye
oh wait we turned off the Imposter check
oh okay
oh you know
the lava reminds me of ramen now I want
Ramen
foreign
okay I'm dying
well she'll see she'll probably see
well you know also
figures
but you did walk over my body
I saw
it was nice
I felt less lonely and this cold world
an opportunity
to watch
what
when was I a snitch
why am I a snitch
oh a snitcher a snitcher me
I can't
oh thank you I know
you too
yo it sounds like Ramen boiling
foreign
[Laughter]
good job
again wow
I didn't kill anybody
you did walk over my body
after moving uh get out everything's
like this is so hard to kill everyone
yeah everyone was together yeah everyone
is just like going together
and I was like bro this can't be real
your character your colors
me yeah oh yeah oh yeah
the colors
um
why are you looking at a camera babe
that's creepy
I was like a boy
but but you guys instead not in like one
step but have like a different style so
I just like oh this is hard even though
I do it
it is hard I think everybody should be
off on their own and isolated at all
times honestly
for real
do one more round and in case someone
gets imposter who already got impossible
before we restart or just yeah
I'm going to kill all of you
again
okay yeah if someone gets it like
um
already got it okay
oh yeah oh yeah
do you want to play one more round it
doesn't matter who imposter is if I get
it again I'm gonna throw it let's do
that well like if we get imposter again
either Muno or me we could just do the
emergency meeting and cast okay yeah I
found an imposter I'll be throwing it oh
[\h__\h]
well
do I just report myself where do I
report
nutty no wait are we oh
what I I saw someone but I don't know
who it was because I wasn't looking at
the screen but there was someone running
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
I have a spider Rockets right oh yeah
yeah by the Rockets
I I was stalking fauna and then it got
dark and I lost sight of her but then I
saw crony come from the opposite
direction
and I started stalking her wait where's
the body again oh thank you yes
there was the rocket oh it's nearby the
laboratory
weapons all I'm saying is that like on
the left side of the map it's fun did
whoever was did they cross paths with
you or did you see them to the left
interesting left
from the right to the left interesting
oh I did see crony run however I don't
know I I don't know I just wanted to
keep it sunny and then she might have
um
so I wasn't sure if we were playing or
not this round so okay I will fess up
I I did get it again what but like
should you cast me out now
[Applause]
I don't know what happened
someone else give me give me the head of
imposter and we'll just continue like
that
oh an imaginary kill people I will just
act as if I did it
so like if I'm imposter again should I
just out myself and just everyone kill
yourself people doing like it narrows it
down too much so I'm not sure we can
really do that I mean we could just keep
crony around
I'll just not kill anyone I'll just do
sabotage
[Applause]
oh oh that was close oh oh close
at least she's honest she's very honest
at least
you're very honest
yeah
okay I'm gonna I'm gonna sabotage then
yay
and then I'm gonna
do uh
I'm not gonna help with that
okay
because why not
oh I'm sorry did you have to go there
this is not working out well why are you
following me that's suspicious honestly
can I can I follow you
is that allowed oh I'm gonna stalk I'm
gonna stalk movie
foreign
[Music]
she's in like the middle left okay in a
hallway wait who was with someone was
with me at stabilizer so they're also
safe
um
I I was walking up with you but then I
went to the left and I met Corona and
she was coming from that area but I
guess she didn't she didn't touch it
yeah why would I touch it
I won't lie
it's okay
yeah anything can happen it must be the
other imposter
Fisher friends not food God I I have no
idea you go skipping
I kind of remember anyone have any
leaves
[Music]
honestly I choose fauna at this point
what
are you ready
she said that and amuted herself
immediately
[Music]
well like if you guys don't have anyone
else to choose why don't you just kill
me off I mean that would work out pretty
well
oh no it's blocked off oh no how am I
gonna live now
hmm
let's see where should I where should I
block things off
follow people around and just trap him
that'll be fun let's do that
do this again
all right all right
can't follow Fey around too much
oh wait I want to go
can I
oh hello
foreign
all right
let's see
maybe I should kill
to help
uh
I have a theory like Romeo and Juliet oh
what romantic
I have I have a very big Theory so I was
assessing uh Zeta
ume and fauna at the very start because
they were Daenerys people after I saw
Muna senpai
and since Connie came out I felt like oh
oh it has to be someone that then came
out after meeting Anya
um and isn't the type that would be
um going on herself doing duties just to
get in anyone's trust if she's an
imposter so it couldn't be heard it
couldn't be me so it's either KR Senpai
or bae
but that's just another theory
I
could have killed you right
or maybe your cool down was not done yet
I don't know I feel like I I really
because we're kind of dwindling to the
final people so if you waste a if you
waste the thing we're gonna gonna lose
by the way the body yeah
um beside the weapons is that weapons
like you better choose someone properly
weapons
why is cardi still here
left
you out first company that's cool
okay I mean I don't know why I'm still
here to be honest you
the jester
appetizing but like really big props to
like the other imposter doing a very
nice job let's stay together and
finished us I'm done by the way yeah
I know why they kept me around to be
honest
but like all I did was just sabotaging a
diligently
and not doing
crewmate tests
are they all in here
[Music]
I'm sorry
in the Back Bay you stopped me where in
the back
they was on a killing spree
I felt it in my spine when you did it
respect to the ones who stayed alive and
finished the tasks yeah yeah oh honestly
I was dead and had to finish the tasks I
think it was me himself when I did it
okay
if that's possible since it was hard for
the other imposter
red but I wasn't looking at my screen I
was like were they someone red but I
said no
oh yeah but is it possible to do one
more since like that that one round it
was just pretty much one imposter
um
and the killing time is like 10 like the
lowest 10 seconds and pretty much they
have to try and kill every everyone
before they finish the talk you know who
the do you know who the Seeker is yeah
yeah so you have to you have to say that
you're the Imposter when you get it and
you've set the the running speed to the
fastest whoever's making the room and
then yeah you count to ten if you're the
Imposter and then yeah okay I have the
player speed on Max oh my God that is so
fast
no report okay
do we have okay we have to do tasks yeah
yeah yeah yeah so the point is to finish
all the tasks before you get killed okay
[Music]
the task was too little yeah
so wait how many should I do
another
do you want to do the normal one for now
let's go
lower imposter Vision as well oh we're
not gonna mean ourselves by the way
right yeah until you're dead
Okay I'm gonna do each other's screaming
[Applause]
yay screaming
[Music]
oh God I'm like meant to die
are you faster
uh it's impossible I'm meant to die in
this I have no idea that scared me
oh God
like the moment when I get this task it
means
um
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
go grab a coffee
and who died
I don't think so we can haunt her home
[Applause]
repent for your sins
I was gonna click the use button I guess
everyone can just skip yeah
so close oh no it's actually harder than
I thought
I think it's good I think it's well
balanced but it's a challenge
fine hide again four three
two oh my God
okay one more time
all right
let's go
possible
[Music]
wow wow amazing
um
should I change something any
Improvement advice was actually okay
if I hadn't messed up I would have won
so it's because I think okay you have to
play well if you want to win
I don't actually don't I don't actually
want to be it so please know please wait
we should restart
well we could just do an emergency yeah
can kick her out okay
all right goodbye
goodbye
why don't we just you know doing the
marketing
don't forget
tomorrow and the merchandise
just do it
do it
do it do it
is incredible
it just fault me me
all right will it be fun again
[Music]
okay wait what
you guys
you guys are confusing me I didn't do
anything
it's not good
oh man
I have no idea what should I do but
nothing
is broken
well this is peaceful
I'm definitely not in the cafeteria
right now you don't need to go looking
for me okay I
can't do the card
look at me
oh no
um
you're so small
not in the cafeteria at all
um
one more time and boom finally
it's my fault
oh it gets hard when
there's only a few people left yeah
I already mentally gave up
thank you
you are scary
besides me never get imposter I've been
I never I never got one only an onion me
we are first
yeah
it's not fair oh that's cute
I'm going to sue someone I don't know
probably Susie
or hello
so this actually means milk in Indonesia
give me
[Music]
it depends that you can at least give uh
you can always just say cool too uh
something
like you just added
[Music]
mama
I will marry you or something like that
sorry
anyway guys
don't purchase it right now it's gonna
end soon
yeah in like 12 hours I think so maybe I
can grab the March guys
acrylic stand yeah
t-shirts
really nice
thank you for playing so spontaneously
yes
thank you
so much
fun for you guys too thank you yeah it
was really fun thank you
thank you everyone
foreign
[Music]