[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
pap
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
e
n
[Music]
[Applause]
pap
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
to
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
he
[Music]
n
[Applause]
a
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
a
oh
KY I'm having so many issues today what
the
hell okay well first the PS5 oops first
the PS5 wasn't
working and I fixed
that then game capture was being weird
as [\h__\h] again I fixed that then the
sound was not working I fixed
that
uh now our app I don't move interesting
let me restart that again but that's
also already been kind of weird since
this morning when
I was doing
the the bang Bangkok
uh event thing
I noticed like sometimes my face just
stopped moving on the desktop
app not so nice yeah I think there may
have been some update and they just
didn't send us the new software
yet uh yeah during the convention yeah
but I'm at those times I just like
always restart restart
restart how did it go anyway you so
fast give it a moment
moment until I have time to
tangent okay I think there we go I'm
moving for
now moving for now then the
chat okay now everything is fixed yeah
no time like the
present no no no be patient my
chickens so we got this figured out does
the shirt always move this much it's
stuck to my
boobies I
suppose I have new hacked accessory from
blue but I'm keeping the shirt for now
the old
shirt because it separate the arm is
separate and that makes it
easier
oh that moves
more I'll just leave it here okay isn't
this
cute
okay very cute yada one year let's
go oh love being here W is amazing thank
[Music]
you yeah yeah yeah yeah okay okay okay
Toyama thank you I already get it I
already was
told yeah um due to bad audio and
Foreign
Accents them discussing my Ty
Curry sounded to me like they thought my
tyer looked
disgusting misunderstanding corner I was
like
disgusting and then I don't know it was
little bit difficult to communicate
because the audio was a little bit like
w and
then I I didn't hear so well what they
were saying overthinker no because the
thing is I wasn't overthinking because
um so the panel was in Thailand Okay H
in Bangkok in Thailand and
[Music]
and uh they uh like you know okay there
was a convention in Texas right where me
and Cali were uh like just doing a
panel and
I I thought it might be cute if I
prepare some pictures that we can look
at from the area to give a feeling of us
touring the city cuz I think for locals
it's always very exciting if people like
us like you know show interest in the
place that they're in well we're not
there in person so the best I can do is
take some pictures and do like a little
digital tour so to say so I did that and
people really liked it and staff also
liked it so this time they were like
okay let's do this for Bankok too but
this time they prepared the pictures
last time I prepared the pictures this
time they prepared them and I didn't
even look at them really beforehand
uh also C was controlling the OBS so I
didn't really need to look at
it so it was just like pictures of
Bankok and Thailand in general we had a
lot of pictures we only got to use like
seven out of like 20 pictures in the end
cuz it was too much uh too little time
and then I was told beforehand by the
staff that a picture of my Ty Curry is
in there as a joke because
apparently uh my Curry was like like uh
a meme and the thae H Life Community or
something my my my Curry from like two
years ago hi chunky wonky hi two years
ago it wasn't even a hella fresh recipe
I think in this case so I can't even
blame it on them um but it was just a
little freestyle Tha Curry okay with the
bases of uh yellow Tha Curry uh paste
okay with coconut uh uh milk and veggies
and chicken and rice and all that and
apparently that's not how you serve
Curry over there so that's that's why
they were I didn't know until like
afterwards when people told me in the
Twitter
replies normally I guess you serve the
the curry soup cuz normally apparently
more
soupy uh and the rice
separately and yeah I served it together
but I feel like you should still
recognize it and apparently my thing is
more like a
masala but that's still a curry
no rather than like normal Thai curry so
they were like what is this I'm like
it's it's just Thai curry like I mean
yeah it might not have all the typical
ingredients but and normally they have
more like red and green curry but I made
yellow curry cuz it's like the least
spicy you know it it similar to Japanese
no only only this the the plating was
similar to Japanese style like half half
you know in one in one
plate half Bowl plate
M uh I half half with like the the rice
taking up half of the the bowl
yeah this is what happened to me with
the tacle I heard recently something
happened with her in a tacle and
be uh saying something or I don't know
what was like um I was like oh is this a
like hard shell and soft shell like we
talked about
previously she made a very bad
tackle why what what's the problem like
this is the this is one thing I don't
quite understand like when people get a
little bit she made a taco for milky
people got triggered I don't really
understand
like when when you take dishes like this
where there's so much potential for
making whatever you want out of it not
even talking about the thae curry now
but just that like the taco or so like
let's say a burrito or a pizza or
whatever like you can make whatever you
want out of it it looked really sad okay
but like let people let people try to
cook and let people try experiment and
let people make things according to
their own taste ah Cy Callie I defending
you right
now Kelly I don't know if you just rid
it and you're not listening but let me
just say I'm defending your taco right
now for justice for Callie's
tackle okay like let people just like Cy
I didn't even see the tle but people I
was just talking about my tai Curry and
then we went to the Cali taco and I'm
just saying like let people just you
know like make the the food the way they
want to do it okay maybe it's not 100%
accurate to what it's supposed to be but
like yeah make your own thing be
creative the cooking is about being
creative too and if you want to
put these ingredients that you like so
much in there put some put some I don't
know brussel sprouts put some
strawberries in your tuaco I don't give
a [\h__\h] we should have more freedom in
our food creation process if it tastes
good for you yeah that's fine I mean I
really don't know how bad this Taco was
but I I think if Cali liked it if it
tasted good to her if if that's you know
what she was trying to achieve then then
it's her Taco it was very American I
have to check it
out my friend liked it there you go so
it tasted good so that's that's the the
end goal of food to make it taste
good yeah you know like I said with like
pizza like okay some people get really
creative with pizza and then maybe some
Italians get a little bit angry but like
um you know
people just uh just don't see it as
something else see it as a different
dish
then but like you can't create a food
like a pizza and not expect people to go
nuts about it because there's so much
creative stuff you could do with a pizza
like oh my God you can do so much with a
pizza I mean I don't really I'm not
really one for like Nutella Pizza um
although I did have a sweet pizza before
that was pretty good but like you see it
can turn out really good
so yeah it's a canvas of food right
pizza is literally like a canvas for
food Nutella
Don well that's something else right
that's something I made up no
yeah Nutella Pizza is delicious yeah I
mean I guess it can be good yeah yeah
for sure I had some sweet
pizza but I heard there's this famous um
uh frozen pizza brand that we have in uh
Austria Germany and so on
resturante Dr utka and they make all
kinds of pizzas frozen pizzas I eat
their pizzas all the time but they made
a Nutella pizza before that I haven't
eaten but people say it's
m yeah not not the best thing they
made not the best thing they came up
with we have it here in Norway as well m
yeah I think it's like all over Europe
at
least yeah dessert pizza with like
something like Nutella it's off
officially probably not Nutella just
some chocolate
spread it was a taco it just wasn't a
traditional authentic Latin American
Taco which is fine exactly that's fine
Taco same thing like man there's so much
you could do with that yeah okay why am
I yapping so much about this
anyway I've over
yapped I have over
yapped
okay I had that was
disgusting but there's certainly ways
especially if you make it yourself with
proper pizza dough and proper pizza oven
and all that oh you can make a great
dessert pizza I'm sure but then I guess
I wouldn't really call it a pizza
anymore at that point doesn't really
feel like a pizza anymore but still the
base the base is a pizza H and now fense
on the taco we fought K's friend bought
it from a food truck okay I have to go
see this Taco
now P
Taco people learned about K's white
woman Taco that she made for her friend
should I watch this
one oh cilantro yes cilantro yes I don't
have the Jean lucky oh do you I yeah I
want to know what good cilantro tastes
like but it always tastes like butt I
like skip this I would listen to Cali
she makes great tacos shut your mouth
you make great tacos why you say shut up
is there a picture that's the joke the
joke is that I okay let me tell you a
story a friend of mine named milky Queen
I was on a vacation with her and I just
I thought nothing of it I just made a
stupid homemade just American Taco like
the taco that you get I made the taco
and I was like yeah whatever that's
sweet it's like an American for taco
they have the taco shells at the
supermarket you just buy it and you make
your friend a freaking Taco yeah that's
it you know there's nothing really to it
they didn't like it they saw the picture
milky took a picture of it she's like my
friend made me a taco they me that made
it where what's your problem guys they
didn't know that it was me that made it
they later found out they found out
about it all right I wouldt let know how
they felt about it real quick like fresh
tomatoes and salads go it's uh people
are very particular it's just tortilla
and meat oh no viu they're going to want
to be me you wait can I ask what you put
in I thought it was so much worse basic
like uh tomato lettuce um cheese meat
yeah some seasoning you know it was
basic what wrong what's wrong with this
it was a basic
to yeah there was a lot of so I love
that that looks delicious to me cie
probably not listening anymore but Cy
that looks delicious to
me looks really
refreshing looks good I love it I would
eat that I would make that because
you're
aan I think she's gone let me let me
tell
her okay I just watch the clip and saw
the pick I think that looks delish I
would make that I would eat that I love
it it's
perfect looks
healthy two I'll make you one she says
she says thanks man bigups I'll make you
one it was really good I believe you
[Laughter]
100% I got you man yeah let's
call
Taco no I love these kind of things with
like lettuce and tomatoes you don't you
think that doesn't belong in
there it belongs there if the cook says
it belongs there let's
go yeah it may not be in like the OG
like ingredients but if it's good it's
good yeah okay and discussion ended oh
that's it let her
cook in the end cooking is all about
love cooking for your friend what's like
a bigger sign of love than that H H yeah
okay here we go like a dragon infinite
wealth I think we're aren't we still no
we're not in the casino the casino Arc
is over and we didn't get to gamble
scam
absolute
scam unbelievable actually make a huge
ass flashy
Casino show it off to us with cute way
more or less cute wa interested and and
you just you just don't let me
get what's wrong with you what's what
happened it's just Yakuza is just not
the same anymore it just changed too
much so guys welcome to the stream we're
going straight into a boss fight
enjoy I think we're ready right like are
we mentally ready that's a different
kind of question but let's
go no blackj poker all right here we
go
oh
oh y i hanging with
the they look a little bit
older sorry sorry
sorry wait
what that's his that's his
type what was it what's in
demand they I think they're a little bit
over
4050 plus is in
demand I mean they they're
cute the smile of the left lady Crips me
out
but
[Music]
smile 50 is a new 30 let's
go we like to spread Positive
Vibes but I got a lot of
bite what I want to make sure you don't
forget it I'm Army on my back sound
sadistic he's also sadistic by the
way
oh oh [\h__\h] okay y let's
go oh oh he's just chilling he's fing oh
he's just
like oh
you once again didn't we we already
fought him last
time we're really just going to treat
him as our Pokemon Rival
huh okay here we go guys let's start
with a little
buff I don't know how difficult this
fight is going to be but like can you
move a little
closer y you're not getting the buff no
matter how close you stand for me
sorry that was sick yeah the cut scenes
are so sick
uhoh
oh sorry sorry why is he dancing like
that look at
[Music]
him I'm trying What the freaking
timing all right what's your is it water
yeah water there there
but let's do a while you're still so
close together maybe an
AOE wait all
yeah yeah I don't know if it's worth it
but it get free
people that one just always comes in so
slowly I just never get it
right yo I blocked that what are you
talking
about I totally blocked
[Music]
that I finish him probably don't need a
skill
right
yeah yummy yumy yumy
yummy oh nice Miss Nice
[Music]
Miss
yeah we have warmed
up still little monkey
F invisible wall why must you do this to
me if only we still had fire actually no
cuz he uh doesn't like
water we can do this because then Tommy
can help us unless you move that way
okay you know
what some
hits
[Music]
missed
no imagine if you didn't perfect God for
real holy
[\h__\h] that's not fair
500 there's he can't do that like
endlessly
right they healed him all the way back
to the to the to the
max okay good
hyper
potion hopefully only
once
I wait what are
[Music]
you maybe I don't
know something strong
strong yeah 47
77 we're back we're back we're so
[Music]
back do I want to do an AOE he's kind of
close to the other guy but
no I'm just going
to actually
yeah ah wait he's weak to this then I
guess I'll do this maybe over kill I
don't even need to heal right
now oh wow wow
wow wow wow my PC lagged I
think we love
tuna especially tuna Pizza w w w w w w w
w I
love how wao
oh damn the back of my knee he hooked
himself into
[Music]
that okay let's let's try to
get him ah wait he he's got a
guard ah
[\h__\h] didn't think of the
well we can break him
with okay yamay is left I wonder if he
brings in extra extra
minions K skills have been silenced no
maybe we take this opportunity to heal
him cuz he's the one who has really low
[Music]
HP
movie in the
distance oh what should I do
maybe maybe just this one is that too
little it's pretty
[Music]
good why why does he have so many fire
things is it it's just because of his
weapon right I wish he had some
stuff well I'll do
[Music]
this yeah that's decent and I get some
HP
so yeah he's Fire
based okay at least one ooh ooh
ooh [\h__\h] this why you guys should be
terrified of Ena
crowbar is no joke that's what I've
learned from this game so
[Music]
far I personally
am don't heal him again
girl no hey what the [\h__\h] m not a heal
maybe above or just nothing at
all I feel that bottle was
[Music]
empty oh oh oh [\h__\h] he's
insane let me attack please
hey hey no oh hey come on five what is
can I take them down please those ladies
get into the battle so I can take you
down that's not
fair 500 again you know how long that
takes me but at least now the minions
are gone so I can focus on him I
guess I can't use
[Music]
skills I feel like I want to cuz yeah
my's turn is not up just yet
so I feel like I I want to not heal
myself yet maybe I'll use an attack
item water right maybe ice damage here
wait
150 oh [\h__\h] I don't have the strong one
anymore and let's throw this one at
him 15 would be pretty low hey
paralyzed
um how close is everyone oh I can reach
everybody buffing everybody and with uh
the lighting I'm going to heal everyone
don't worry guys don't
worry [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] okay healing time I hope
everybody's close
yeah uh coconut
shower beautiful okay his turn don't get
so close okay he can't move yay paraly
is paying off and we're no longer
poison it's still silenced
though
[Music]
H should we call
someone might be fun increase space
[Music]
no are they even worth it heals high50
base damage in a straight line for free
turns sometimes causing
stun that's not even that
[Music]
much
okay here we
go
[Music]
mhi very very
Happ
[Music]
hold
delivery
delivery all right attack please go
to okay okay
okay
delivery Soul
Capture oh yeah oh
yeah please stay paralyzed please do us
a
favor uh-oh he's
back
[\h__\h]
who nice
ass what twice on other what what
no
there maybe that's more worth if there's
more than one enemy on the
[Music]
beld hot do I
guess okay as long as it's not the the
alcohol
oh we now one
silenced
okay we need the we need the Big
Tuna oh nice nice good
collaboration oh halfway through oh wo
he's ice skating oh [\h__\h] I was kind of
late gy
gy look at her
dancing she's such a Vibe yeah well he's
still on the ground yeah oh no he stood
up for that what the
hell what should I
do still Paralyzed by the way
okay
maybe maybe
a pretty much done well I'll give
everybody a
heal uhoh oh
[\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
M yeah
yeah feels
good but still her HP
got yeah it's a lot less M
strong you do be
strong
hey I saved her yeah she might have died
otherwise
y we got to do it we need more more
TOA yummy T are so
[Music]
big you know from Dave the diver I kind
of
already oh goodbye already kind of
oh uhoh what is this AOE no okay kind of
already learned this and then I saw
another video where I really realized oh
wow uh oh counter St Tunas Tunas have to
move all the time otherwise they die
they always have to be
swiming swim swim
swim that's why fresh tuna is a little
bit difficult actually
sharks too
yeah like sharks
yeah okay H oopsie uh we're going to oh
I have I have no MP for
[Music]
that I'll just give
her although I wonder if everybody
attacks although he has the counter
stands otherwise I would say if
everybody attacks we might get him to
die this
round
but this is a bit complicated
[Music]
okay this one's
fine he can't count the range
ah well she didn't really have MP for
anything good
anyway
um nothing shuts him up like a shot of
Adam's Apple a shot to the Adam's apple
damages an enemy and applies your
weapons after this should just go for
one of our Strongest
Ones I'm
try
[\h__\h] I missed oh but look look at the
look at this ice spe I I got half of it
down
again
easy this one's pretty strong
too could be the final hit is the final
hit
yay yeah again didn't need to
heal Yakuza training gear
oo level
up she got a new skill butterfly
something
true
[Music]
go yeah perfect LS are pretty
good
what
for
[\h__\h]
tomye
[Music]
Tommy you got the guts or
not you got what it takes or someone's
going to stop him from doing it
yeah just do
it oh maybe K comes out of nowhere now
oh
no
okay
oh
[\h__\h] we got to make it more more
dramatic we got to put a knife to his
throat and say give me you or he's
dead
hi oh oh they got they they let us see
him
okay they're treating him wait that's
actually amazing cuz he wasn't able to
go to the
hospital you're liting
him that's
[Music]
nice um maybe because yam might hit him
in the head with the crowbar
M maybe shouldn't have done
[Music]
that only first aid
damn
[Music]
he's so cool though but [\h__\h] him he's
a
[Music]
so he's just a loot
Goblin he doesn't even know why he's
looking for
[Music]
her
well yeah
[Music]
true she doesn't like
it
soft
belly oh I think she was on the toilet
that's why she
[Music]
foree
are we really not going to see each
other ever
again
[Music]
really
I'm surprised you say that
[Music]
m
H that's what he's dreaming right
now is that a second
child was the
same is he just collecting little
girls
it's all the same
girl
[Music]
foree that's
the that's the girl we're looking
for
besides our
mommy wow nice Cut to you
[Music]
wow it's like a different
game I just
likeo
true
damn nice good morning
kid good morning
[Music]
sunshine
foree
foreign
[Music]
truee
fore
[Music]
don't let him
Die Why did I give him
cancer that's so
[Music]
hard is he actually going to
go
[Music]
man he just wants to
help
har who the [\h__\h] is that I don't
know it's his surp child
[Music]
surprise
spee
foreign
[Music]
fore
a so we're losing him
immediately is going to
go I let you stay
[Music]
in good that I didn't invest into
number
[Music]
for do you guys hear the
static noise that I'm
[Music]
hearing oh I fixed
it
[Music]
for so I wonder if in a future
game
K is like he comes back
being uh healed from cancer or he's just
like this is how the producers are
phasing him out and he's just going to
[Music]
die what do you think guys you think
he'll make a comeback or is he GNA
die it might be their way of
like oh oh is it is something going to
happen like within this game
already oh okay
k your son s good head as for you you've
been through a lot today yeah all the
rest yourself
yeah if only there was a second
bath
yo rested Safe
House ah there
is second oh mush
mhi Pat I will be giving away gifts if
you interested you can find me at wo
burger what does that
entail is this only because I called her
in the last
fight or would that have come
anyway you think he
dies
see that's that's realistic and that's a
a a way
to get rid of Kido and move on to
ichan without people continuously asking
for K to come back because he's
gone pretty [\h__\h] brutal to kill a
character off like this making us suffer
with him making us follow his journey so
we're like more emotionally attached to
this whole story especially people who
played the previous all the previous ke
games
Bros bros for
life
[Music]
damn can't we just have him retire like
for real for real like make him have a
and be like I'm out of here like I would
accept
that why is it got to be like
this 20
years didn't work
out that's
unrealistic with a with a with a face
and a body and a personality like that
how can he not find happiness with a
family how can he not find a wife that's
like so happy to have him like he's like
a perfect man there's no like look at
how many women are like oh my God
k um so many people would love to have
him as their husband and he would be a
great husband this is okay this is kind
of unrealistic that he was not able to
like find a a great wife and have a
great family that's just not
[Applause]
realistic would you marry him yeah I
would but
like I would I would let other
women take
priority uh like a
certain obsessed lady out there there
you go yeah see well
yeah what
who the world ripped the happiness away
from him
well well yeah that's are you are we
talking about like Haruka what what
about like just getting a wife you
know another a new one maybe I don't
know just
I don't
know majima would totally marry
[Laughter]
K hello
[\h__\h] oh
well it's
difficult bye-bye
[Music]
n
kind of sad that he's the one who has to
leave but we didn't use him anyway so I
guess it's
good he blew them
off
Baka K
you k
you he's going to
die
foree
fore
oh
video
[Music]
knowing his identity now I'm not sure if
I want to go
back it's better to not know
he'll know that we
know oh
no oh
no K and Namba left the
party
yeah
I uh
wonder if I
should take a quick look at the
vocational school or if I should do that
off screen because maybe it takes too
long where is it Anyway can't see
it
I never
used
STS don't take too long
Southwest huh
where Southwest would be like
here is it is it a green icon or
oh wait Wes is here never mind sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry
confused
um sh sh
[Music]
sh yes
no
um what am I looking
for what kind of
sign found
it closest
taxi
let's do a little quiz quiz time
baby you
know it's so warm I was feeling really
hot before the stream cuz I was like
cooking and stuff oh I can go this way
really was you not here
before it's getting so hot I want air
conditioning give me air
conditioning
but during the panel they told me how
hot it is in Bangkok right now and it's
just April and they said it was like um
like uh what was it like around
40 and I'm like okay um I'm not going to
complain anymore more I
guess um what the [\h__\h] what what what
the actual [\h__\h] how is it so hot already
um
what how's that
work I I mean Celsius by the
way and then it's even humid you know I
assume why are we seeing this again we
see this
before that's a yikes from me
dog same yeah he does look
familiar what does he he reminds the guy
from the previous
[Music]
game
I never mind he's supposed to be maybe
the guy from the school from the
previous
game yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
yeah excuse me what goober am I the
goober is he the goober is iar the
goober
iari ah there he is in his real
attire what's up what's up hey yo what's
up that you know that's this is such a
simple thing but but you know we we got
some we got some fans from Bankok in the
audience to like come to the middle and
speak into the microphone and like do
Q&A and whatever like we did little game
and and like a lot of them had like okay
English but definitely like an an accent
okay and then this one guy he comes up
and the first thing he says into the
microphone is a really nice English
fluent sounding hey yo what's up and
everybody was like whoa I don't know
that was so cool somehow everybody was
like whoa what's whoa whoa he's got like
some
swag hey yo what's up Cali was like
taken back by the swag yeah Kelly
Kelly's been real quiet ever since you
said hey yo what's up and then yeah okay
here's the thing we did a little game is
uh two troops one lie and they had to
guess okay but they got it uh the the
the the dude he got it wrong okay so we
made him do a Batu and cie suggested to
have him rap do a freestyle rap and I'm
like that's that's like a
pretty pretty like for someone who let's
let's assume normal most normal people
out there that you meet randomly they
they can't suddenly do a good freestyle
rap so that's quite the prompt that's a
big ask yeah that's asking for a
lot especially in front of like so many
people and then yeah we we were putting
him on the spot and I was like worried
but maybe cie just from the first time
he said hey yo what's up she already
recognized that this guy had some swag
in himself like he had potential she
maybe like sensed something and then he
said Okay I uh I can wrap something in
IND in in Thai language
so he he lets he wants music but we
can't really provide music so everybody
starts clapping in the Rhythm and he
starts rapping In tha like whoa like he
was fired he was going off he was
popping off he was like really feeling
it and he was really good at it it was
like it was like it might have you know
he might have been doing this like every
once in a while on the little stage out
there like maybe maybe he sometimes
makes music like definitely you get that
vibe from him so everybody was like whoa
holy
[\h__\h] yeah he was he was ready he came
prepared we had to stop him the MC had
to stop him because he was on
stoppable yeah again Call's been real
quiet ever since he was spitting those
[Laughter]
bars rapper sens is tingling that was
that was crazy I want to see the clip
well there was a live stream of this
apparently for um taii viewers like you
needed a VPN if you wanted to watch it
from outside I don't know if anybody
recorded it because seems like most
people were unaware there was a stream I
feel like I knew and then I forgot about
it that's why I didn't tell you
guys I forgot yeah there was a live
stream of it and once I found that out I
was like really embarrassed no VOD oh
then you you would have had to you would
have had to be recording
that but maybe it's better you nobody
was recording because
uh yeah some some something better
stay within within
there did you need to buy a ticket ah
yeah I guess for the streaming too I
guess
so lost media anyway can't F him for
commitment last I heard he'd earned over
100 certifications but the job market
still let him
down
obnoxious stream ticket antip
makes sense I mean why would it be for
free if
it's
we
forey cover
rainbow never heard of
it sounds like an idol
song
oh nice of them I
guess 200
now 100
certifications
what happened
what I don't remember that at
all he's like the way he's saying that
he's like kind of roasting him and
making fun of him but you should not be
the one talking you're not the
position we should
[Music]
tell
your you two you guys you should like
go take some different kind of
certifications how to talk to
girls oh
makes
sense
w
let me in let me
join
yes
okay true
true
ich starts from
ich now that's what I came here
for up
come
on oh come
on this is actually really fitting cuz
uh after Bangkok panel thingy time is
money money is power I went to sleep
right and I Had a Little Dream part of
the dream I was I I went even though I
am old Phoenix now so for some reason I
went back to
school to finish school I
guess and
and in the dream I was like I went into
the school and all that on my first day
and I went to my classroom and most of
the people already had their seats and
then I was like there were free rows and
I had to choose where I would want to
sit and it was really important because
I was thinking like if I sit in the
front I I'll feel too pressured I I've
there was a time before in school where
I sit in the I sat in the front row and
it was it felt like too much pressure
generally and then the back row I also
had some year where I was sitting in the
back row and there I must say was chill
but a little bit too chill like you kind
of like just you do be chilling all the
time and like you you kind of like log
out of the classroom in your mind and
you're not really there a lot of the
time so I guess middle row I guess I was
thinking
and I was thinking about that and and
and then I was like getting emotional
and I started crying while looking at
the seats and people were like looking
at me like why are you crying even
though they're all also like kind of
like late to the party in terms of
finishing school but I was like starting
to cry because it was like kind of like
PTSD to be back in school it was scaring
me and freaking me out
and kind of traumatic so
eventually I sat down I found a seat and
then it my dream just kind of skipped
and I was like at the end of the year or
so and apparently I I just ended up not
going to school much again and I failed
and the projects that I did have like
there was apparently some project with
like
plants uh that you had to grow and mine
were all moldy
and died um in
mold and yeah I just failed again and
then I was thinking to myself why did I
do this like I would have felt better
not going at all now I did go and I the
only feeling I get from it is failure
again
so doesn't feel good doesn't feel
good you get those dreams too really I
never I never got a dream like this
before I think but
yeah maybe it's because you guys were
roasting me about like how education has
failed
[Music]
me
okay
[Music]
what is wrong with
you um you need to
stop your reaction meeting
[Music]
me
for my
[Music]
God poor
lady having to deal with that but she's
just trying to be professional
shut the [\h__\h] up get out of
[Music]
here oh my God
help he said shut the [\h__\h] up and go get
lost that's literally what you said
wrong translation
[Music]
hi the owner by vocation is a private
Institute which enhances personalities
by passing an exam acquire a
cerification
[Music]
here
wow
shut the [\h__\h] up oh my
[Music]
God you're going to lose students like
this I've come this far might as well
see M on the B my for yep um can I
choose what's
that passion and Charisma
okay let's see cuz like in in previous
times I needed your help
sometimes but the first one okay uh uh
The White Flower sh what's his name uh
habiscus
but that doesn't look like no no it
doesn't look like a hibiscus plaria
maybe yeah doesn't look like a
hibiscus for playing what does its name
mean uh no idea
uh maybe flowing hair no free jumping
how do you guys know how do you know
which of the following images is of aay
a decorative known to have
many uh
this ah
ah I know this from
Pokemon
[Music]
Mas Masada two four two four Mas two or
four two
two yeah Pokemon
Moon which of the following
volcano is named le le lion Diamond Head
I don't know
uh
uh uh uh four
what but that also sounds pretty
Hawaiian I'll say diamond head cuz what
if why would it be
called do I have to have everything
correct like that that was the only
English thing I
passed five five is okay okay how much
did I get nice one woohoo will I tell
me I want to
know plaria okay I got it uh um I I I
was like about to press high biscus but
then I
realized
ah yeah we got that thanks to you I I
had it on my own Mada yeah I I was
between two and four and yeah okay you
guys were I don't know if you guys were
still on the previous question when you
guys were writing four but everybody was
writing four and I was like I mean that
makes no sense like it's a famous
tourist spot that is named Le AI in
Hawaiian but the other things sound
already Hawaiian so it kind of got to be
Diamond Head and I heard that thing
before I heard of Diamond Head before
y you thought you were on the Chima MV
press four press
four okay nice let's do another
one okay you're just scared of
me
[Music]
for what stat should I be looking
for
I don't know what I just do
everything
okay let's do this you guys got to help
me it sounds kind of difficult to get
everything up
there take an
exam uh oh I passed the second one but
what about this first one is that
less tier one sounds like it's less
difficult but I guess it's more
difficult style kind wa wait wait can I
see
it uh what I already have in terms of
stats uh
personality okay okay we don't need to
do passion we definitely need to do
intellect wait does this count for
everybody right
or yeah the stats are for everybody in
my group basically like if I can get all
of them to five I can get all jobs for
everybody okay so we need uh confidence
Charisma kindness style intellect
confidence Charisma Just One More
Level intellect quite a
bit no more passion confidence friends
let's
do yeah let's do this one marine
life down mus uh which one is a clown
fish oh this one I
think well I'm a snork so which lives at
the lowest point below SE
levels um not the ofin
maybe the lowest point uh maybe in clam
or the foot
[Music]
bfish maybe the clam or the foot you
know what that even
is since Dolphins don't have they must
how stay sleep in order to avoid ah ah
ah I think I
know
H they sleep from they sleep uppr I
think
maybe maybe they sleep
uh they alternate which have is this
wait is this not the same as of sharks
and and the other thing we talked about
P are famous for being flightless birds
and exceptional swimmers which of the
following species is largest in size oh
King B no Emperor emperor penguin I
think yeah okay okay okay
okay why the Turles appear and shed to
shed tears from their eyes when they lay
eggs because they're pressing it out too
hard I don't know we're going elevator
symptoms of dry eye because they sad
well I mean probably salt concentration
sounds pretty sounds scientific
okay
nice salt salt sounds
[Music]
logical some of these questions are
really difficult but really
interesting so what about these uh
sharks and tuna is that a different
thing that we were talking about then
from the the the
Dolphins can cfish yeah
oh oh doas are capable of un uni
hemispheric sleep with in which they
closed one eye one one half of their
sleep brains and the other half what
that's kind of like
insane that was not the clams than
[Music]
God involuntary resp what does that even
mean I guess that is I I was like trying
to read really fast so I didn't read it
properly I thought it was like a tuna
shark thing different friend right but
what a
[Music]
skill they cannot breathe without
thinking
ah oh
so I guess we're still thinking about
breathing even if we're sleeping cuz we
no we're we're not thinking about it
because we can't do involuntary
respiration as human humans is that what
we're
saying they cannot do that so okay what
evolution [\h__\h] you over
Dolphins Emperor nice okay everything
correct
[Music]
yeah the
Sega
confidence
Charisma wait let me check my stats
again did I level up
anything no okay we need a little bit
more confidence everything else
[Music]
okay let's do map because it gives me a
lot of intellect and I need that the
most [\h__\h]
a
one
maybe uh I would say probably one two a
I haven't looked at dice is that much
di uh 1 + 2 * 3 wait do you do 2 * 3
first uh 2 * 6 1 yeah that's yeah uh six
no wait nine wait three three * free 9 +
4 uh help
me 1 plus threee 6 uh 10 15
uh uh 21 uh uh 28 uh uh uh 30 uh [\h__\h]
help me help me help me help me no there
more than
35 it's a minus 10 at the end oh
okay
[Music]
maybe what I need a calculator for
this four not 14
really
um 6 I I should be able to do this uh 20
20 20 20 20 no uh
[Laughter]
okay I'm so
slow
[Music]
[Applause]
going
two
I only did it because of
you okay I didn't no this I didn't know
this I think I was too
slow what would I do without
you how about Sega proficiency test tier
two you may
begin SE released what is rightly
recognized as the first 3 fighting game
which later became it own serious The
Following on is the very first game in
the series oh give me at least titles
like what are these give me a
title or Virtual Fighter I've heard of
that
one SE catcher you is a crane game which
in which players which of the following
is the first
you
they I mean this and this is the same
picture almost almost I oh maybe this
one looks pretty
old one looks pretty
old yeah this one looks old I don't know
they look so similar in Sega Sonic the
Hedgehog series uh which of the
following items do players typically
collect during game playay Rings right I
never really played Sonic games but
Rings this full body motorcycle racing
game has been an operation since 1985
and features a bike shaped cabinet that
players would ride on leaning left and
right to turn what's its
name uh drift
on
[\h__\h] what hang on which of the following
video games consoles is dream uh wait
this one maybe I never had it but maybe
this
one
[Music]
looks like a mix between a PlayStation
uh one or so and the in the
GameCube
pass okay do we have to watch this every
time thank you thank you thank you thank
you let me down this is scary to me I'm
scared of
heights okay five in
confidence correct correct I I just
guessed that like because they all look
pretty similar but that one
was kind of funky looking y yeah okay I
want I got this one from you and this
one I guessed as well SE sat Genesis
Mega Drive Sega Mark free what are these
others what are these other are they
newer than the
Dreamcast were they any
what was it we don't need confidence
anymore or we can do oh we can do this
one this one we need trivia King tier
two they were older oh Saturn was the
last one okay uh which of the following
was originally used to remove pencil
marks before the RoR was ined oh maybe I
would say I don't know is this in Japan
if we're talking Japan and maybe
Moi but okay bread really does bread
work interesting oh what is the name of
the classic neapolitan pizza that's made
with tomato sauce and white with right
on top oh I I know
Margarita
Margarita who is the almighty god of the
sky and thunder and ah uh
toys toys no maybe
Apollo uh Toys okay okay okay uh which
of the following foods known for's
unique texture is made from casaba root
vegetable that grows mainly in the trop
never heard of
that uh which one stop making fun of my
German pronunciation it's better than
yours which of the following vegetables
will float in fresh water
ah potato
potato maybe Lotus Ro cuz it's less
heavy
oh no
H oh dear oh dear we're not so sure
about this one AR we
interestingly but it's probably less
heavy oh we pass
okay wait doesn't matter only I guess
okay oh curious about this one where's
my
kindness style intellect okay no more
confidence no more passion
okay it was pumpkin cuz it's Holo
inside
wao
H
interesting thank
you really cool stuff can we
do can we do this one
again it's exactly what I
need clothing stains caused by oil from
food like pizza can be difficult to wash
out what type of powder is often used in
the kitchen as effective at removing
this kind baking uh uh soda baking
powder baking soda I always hear this
from
Americans like oh my God you can do this
at home videos pigeons have been used as
a messenger messenger bird their ability
to fly over extremely long distance and
the night homing abilities what does a
pigeon use in order to find his way home
magnetic
field magnetic field yeah in an
orchestra wind instruments are divided
into woodwind instruments and brass
instruments which of the following is a
brass
instrument
uh uh
saxophone trumpet yeah same thing credit
card sizes are determined by an
international standard for easy about
how many sheets for high quality copy
paper does it take to match the
thickness of a credit
card excuse me I don't know doesn't
matter 15
20 15
maybe sh Holmes is a series of famous
detective novels written by Sir arur con
and Doyle what was Holmes Partners John
Watson's previous occupation before they
no idea never like read it or watched it
or doctor hold
oh Amelia
Watson we
found how many times my hype gang man my
hype
gang oh let's go let's go pretty good
pretty good
uh baking soda uh-huh only this one was
wrong
okay okay I only really knew this these
[Music]
two yeah I didn't know the
others now need more
style can do this one I oh
no
well uh I'll need your help with this
one alcohol
expert it I don't drink alcohol cont the
may serve Whiskey on the rocks by simply
adding a large feere of eyes which of
the following statements about ice spars
is false compared to regular ice
cubes uh Falls it probably doesn't melt
more
slowly or it's not it's not easy easier
to prepare but yeah maybe melt yeah
melts the same way the plant shown here
is used in beer for its bittering
aromatic
pops right when mixing a cocktail what
should be added to the device shown
here
ice
maybe wait wait wait wait maybe I got it
wrong I don't know which up the find
cocktails sh here has ha in the
name um probably something with a
pineapple I don't see a maybe maybe this
or
this okay okay yeah yeah yeah yeah I can
I think I yeah I think I know what that
is a blue Hawai sugar cane was once
grown in extensively in Hawaii the sugar
from these plants is even used to make
certain ah
wait uh
ra Randy no ra yeah yeah yeah yeah I was
I was going towards that I learned that
before in in hotel
school I may not like alcohol but I
learned some stuff about
alcohol in hotel
[Music]
School
congratulations
[Music]
conat
nice am I actually a t side I knew quite
a few
things y okay now I need I need a bit
more of everything except confidence and
passion oh I was thinking about it is
easier to pray might be Falls because it
prepare it doesn't seem like something
that's easier to prepare so it does melt
more slowly
interesting I I was kind of going
towards that no the rest I got this one
right I learned that in school that just
makes
sense this one you help me a
bit all the rest is ahuh screwdriver
martini
spon and BR nice not too bad not too
[Music]
bad how
about kindness and
style perfect for those looking to grow
fruits and vegetables in their home
guard
that's me in the future so let's
go uh
basil uh support in order to grow
Vines oh that I don't really is it on
the picture there
oh that probably I
know Morning
Glory which of the following flowers is
famous for their forns well a rose I
suppose the others don't have forns four
leaf clover is a rare variation of a
regular Clover and the symbol of good
luck how many leaves does a normal
clo the sunflower often symbolizes
summer and blooms during July and into
Autumn which period is the most
appropriate time to sew sunflower
seeds July to
September April to
June wait wait wait a second J jul oh
blooms okay yeah never mind if it blooms
then then something
else okay you better be right with this
one
guys I don't think I don't know if I
agree with that but
okay and maybe I feel like I heard that
before though I I feel like I heard the
the real the AL start to Happ for
sometimes
congratulations okay all right
yeah yeah wow wow wow wow thank you for
the
upes okay okay we got style and kindness
up with that okay oh yay hey most of
those I got
right I didn't know Morning Glory I
wasn't sure about this one either okay
nice nice well these are pretty easy
though actually it's pretty
basic it's just not necessarily
gardening it's also cooking
okay what do I need
uh gem proficiency beu
proficiency let's do beu proficiency
here we go what is a ring called when
it's offered to a significant other
during engagement
ring oh is it though yeah which of the
following genes is pyro electric meaning
it generates voltage when heated up or
under pressure
[\h__\h] a
topaz
or teraline oh maybe okay in Oscar wild
fairy tale the happy prince the statue
of a prince asks a swallow to take Jews
and gold leaf adoring his body and
deliver them to the pool which jeel
served as
a well blue maybe Z wait wait they're
all kind of blue oh [\h__\h] uh
Sapphire damn why you guys know the
story though most gems may be formed
from a type of mineral not all are which
of the following gemstones is formed
from heart and Tre ah uh emper no a got
a got amber amber amber amber amber ring
sizes follow an international standard
and are assigned a number of or symbol
based on their International internal
psych conference Japan uses numbers such
as one and two what does United the
kingdom
us
runes
um well probably Roman numerals then it
the Greek
alphabet
no I will not do what you say this
time I'm sorry if if you wer actually
right let's
see let's see if I actually um I'm doing
the right thing by going against
you or maybe L I don't know but not what
you said not what you
[Music]
said okay sty is level five we need
internet kindness and Charisma ah okay H
we were both wrong most of you said free
for some reason or were you still on
looking at Amber huh well that's enough
Okay so it's like the words written out
huh what did I say I
needed intellect kindness Charisma
intellect kindness Charisma intellect
kindness Charisma in kindness
Charisma intellect kindness
[Music]
Charisma inter
kindness ah
that's exactly what I need trivia King
oh it's the
oh extra difficult one guys are you
ready for
this which of the following snails is
false they can safely ter a razor blade
their mucus can s
metal I
think they don't have 10,000
teeth but also this one I false they see
they both seem S no way but I might be
like oh I'm so small but I have so many
teeth kind of thing why was natural
indle used to Die the first
jeans react C easier to see you just
because it was there no I don't
know color retains heat
well because of the way it reacts of
course I think
so h
M ah a helicopter generates both lift
and propulsion from spinning rotors to
fly helicopter can be broken down into
which two root
words I would say hel and
copter but that's just a syllables I
don't
know the Japanese eel's body is
transparent in the early stages of its
life cycle but gains color as it matures
what is the reason for its
change
not the first
one two H I was thinking that two
[Music]
but no because birds have big and of
teeth how do they break down food to aid
in
digestion uh I should know this right
they swap no they
don't what what you guys are
crazy that's not bad that's not good for
your stomach they don't they swallow
Stones how does
that how does I do they poop out the
[Music]
stones
two what how come I never heard that
does every bird do
that intellect
kindness oh see I was like yeah that's
just syllables it doesn't seem right
helico and P what Helo is derived from
the Greek word Helix meaning spiral and
P is the WRA from the Greek word pon
meaning Wing h
yeah I can see
that huh I was considering that one
[Music]
too
H the same process causes human skin to
T yeah yeah makes sense no quite intense
though in this case quite intense for
them when if they were once
transparent damn Birds possesses Birds
an organ known as G as a
gizard like a lizard which is commonly
referred to as a and te the the
swallowed rocks and Pebbles remain in
the gizard as it contracts to break down
well for how long for forever do you
just swallow them once and you don't
need to swallow them again until like
maybe 5 years or later or so
[Music]
what
like a grinder yeah yeah but like do
they sticking out your G for the
gizard what the [\h__\h] what what did you
just
[Music]
say chicken gizzard taste that's a thing
that people
eat I guess it's just one of the in
inner things that people eat cuz you eat
in in insides
[Music]
H
what
what Santa you know how many
certifications have required you're
doing wonderfully
mhm it's really expensive
girl funny how I used to hate studying
when I was in school turns out I don't
need to be scared anymore cuz I have
thousands of people helping me in the
chat doesn't mean I'm cheating not at
all don't get me wrong I agree
completely kasak kasan I think you're a
perfect example of why our school exists
yeah M I'll be right by your side to
support okay no I don't need you I don't
need your support I have my
chat go she likes me too much
already don't walk out I want to do more
uh-oh uh-oh oh yeah that's what I
thought he's a Jelly Little Beach what
do you
want the way were talking to luran just
now it almost seemed a bit
flirtatious you better not have been
arranging some sort of
r o calm down she was just
congratulating me for working hard
lately sure and that's why you walked
all way looking so smitten like a kitten
don't insult my intelligence I've gotten
certifications by the score and lower
chance never once gratulate
congratulated me this isn't right it's
discrimination exclusion I sh I followed
all the rules keep your voice down do
you ever think it might be because you
keep causing SC like this and you're
embarrassing as [\h__\h] I don't know what I
should do please give me
advice H man I don't have advice my love
life has been far from Rosie okay
believe
me think of the depths I'm being forced
to S what you mean asking me I the
death sheesh just be honest with her
about your feelings that's always the
best is it not no no not necessarily
Ichibon maybe yes may be all right very
good I'm going now to confess my love to
her in this day and age the heart is too
often Fred by compliant and hostile
Behavior but I say love conquers all
only I don't exactly feel ready at this
exact moment maybe with a little bit
more time slowly influencing her
thinking you mean manipulating her boy
this
guy yeah just propos on the first
sh um
so I keep on forgetting okay we just
need a little bit of intellect a little
bit of
kindness thank you
[Music]
Lan these are just a lot but let's do
them I guess outer space
exam sounds fun help me guys The Crab
Nebula part of the constellation Towers
also has this designation M1 one
similar also what does the m stand for
uh
Mass
no you okay mass m you which of the
following is responsible for the rise
and fall of the tides Moon the Moon the
Moon the Moon right I hope so what if
the following has a gravitational pool
so strong that nothing not even light
can escape it a black
hole
is the four for this question or for a
different one like okay uh Saturn the
six planet in the solar system is the
most famous for its ring system what are
these Rings compared ooh gas
gas I
think
no
ice rock
ice okay but they have a lot of gas on
the planet right if you could walk from
Earth to the Moon approximately how many
[Music]
walking none of this seems realistic to
me four maybe 40 years
then yeah the planet is scas
yeah I mean surprisingly low
numbers
D
what well you can't so why would I know
something we can't do
anyway okay we
pass congratulations you think 40 seems
like too
much maybe it does maybe maybe it this
was huh I don't
know oh it was wrong 10 only 10 years
the distance from Earth to the Moon is
about 380,000 km if you walk in a speed
of 4 km per hour the trip would take
approximately oh we can make it just
need somebody to build a road I
guess
nice I didn't do so
badly I knew one or two
questions uh then uh this one I think I
wanted to
take world history
H I like I like history but uh which of
the following began in south from Peru
then United civilizations across the
unland eventually including mon no
[\h__\h] idea oh wait
what aaya no a a in Ina oh [\h__\h] Inca Ina
wait wait they all sounded familiar to
me okay
sorry uh or this no a these
wait one of those
two oh okay the other one who's who drew
that one that's that one's famous
too which of the following phrases was
coined by French philosopher Renee DES
gardes in the 17th century no [\h__\h]
idea I think I like that
one I've heard that one before the other
ones I have not heard before okay we go
with the one that the only one I heard
before Galileo galile was an Italian
physicist who is often called the father
of modern science what other field is he
known as the father
ofo
astronomy
Y which of the following portraits
depicts George Washington was often
consider
a no that's Lincoln right Abraham
Lincoln him maybe one or four one okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah number two
looked familiar to me
too but not as
Washington but you guys should know you
guys should know we did give off
Washington Vibes very
strongly
congratul well I am indeed not
American I'm certified American
now wa I want to do more tests yo let's
go all correct I want to do more I want
to do more do I only need five in all my
stats what does it help me to do more to
level up
more what does that do for
me muscular science is this a muscle
science
wait okay
uh
details uh
aha
oh Heroes encouragement but I want
details on that what does that mean what
is Heroes encouragement is that like a
side
skill like a buff thingy that he
has her's guts fear resistance her's
guts blind resistance here is
blessing it's his uh
yeah here is wisdom sound I don't know
doesn't really sound so worth it let's
see if I can get those jobs that I want
to have even though these quizzes are
fun but they also cost a lot of money I
feel like this might be the end of it
unless we have a [\h__\h] ton of money at
the
end
[Music]
yeah got go
here so much for infinite wealth yeah
for now for
now nice Jake thank you for
acknowledging me from that
distance new jobs guys it's time for
cool cutcenes
oh wait I have to take test the the the
the
things it's time for
uny um I can do everything now I think
we can do the
yoga uh we can do what is this what the
[\h__\h] do you get from this you mean
shopping water gun fitting cuz it's
San and they use water guns to shoot
each other and make each other wet well
there's not much left
anyway pirate sailing this is amazing
guys this is just amazing do you have
enough money not maybe not for
everything uh right away but
um yeah I did paragliding before but
Paras sailing is is paragliding paring I
think Paras selling is a little bit
different isn't
uh isn't there something pulling you
yeah there's a string there isn't there
a boat uh yeah a boat is like that's
that's
awesome pretty cheap
too let's go par
sailing I I need to do this but it's
probably really expensive and you only
really get to do it in like
uh vacation stuff ah [\h__\h]
parrot wants to kill
me
oh nice landing wow oh no no not the
Coconuts it never
ends
oh oh that's not what I expected that
you would learn from
[Music]
this
okay woo action
star Bruce Lee
now wow okay I don't know if it's a good
class I don't know if we're going to use
it
but it was a cheap one at least okay
yogar let's do some
yogar
hi got some Fick
F yeah I can do this I've done this
before
oh oh
no
yeah she's rocking
it I think she regularly does
it you [\h__\h]
idiots
[Music]
amazing whoa okay I can't do it that
pretty oh my
God yeah moody
[Music]
moody a for
incredible she won up
there
wow does she learn Kuni from
this yo let's
go oh
wow
nice I want to give her that job because
we have the Little
Weapon Mortal
Combat
oh I see you really Tak you to the
activities you've been offering I do
hope you find them
enjoyable getting to run around and
explore a huge island almost makes me
feel like a kid again really ni good to
hear I wonder if there's a good one for
an his eyes so pure and radiant with
life and such a child at heart wouldn't
you agree
aloh hi
sure terrifying what's going
on maybe there's a secret job that you
can get after you get all the other
courses done what good around
[Music]
here
this
H um water
gun not don't know what these ones do
1,600 1,600 that's a lot of money I
don't want to learn maybe we can keep
one or two for next time probably T J is
amazing okay there we go thank you then
we shall do this one and then we call it
the day for
now you think I'll earn it back
[Music]
fast he's not even in the video is
he he wasn't the yoga
[Music]
one
n what
what what Sun beach
party what oh come on what what
you what's wrong with you
[Music]
ichan what's wrong with you
ichan
really
really that's the kind of connection you
make come
on
do okay so that one for I can see I can
see how that would work quite well he
seems like a strong class
with
yeah oh the yokahama outfit a well no we
need a crazy outfit so it's either black
or silver
black now she shall be
a it's time to
change
yellow
yellow and we change him to
[Music]
something I don't know about this one
Tommy doesn't look so good on
[Music]
you maybe in a different color like is
it even is it even good for
him keep ire dancer to unlock Skillet
Buffs attack to
Max
okay action start isn't good for Tomy m
got the water gun job for
Tommy and switch eachon to action
star is that a good
idea action star
for
oh yeah those other patterns look better
on him
it's just
okay wait right now he's uh an aquan
not freelancer is good for him
too that's just a BC
One I didn't have a good time with
aquanut let's just try it non to every
class that that does just blun skills is
nothing is ever weak to
it
oh maybe leave him until 18 okay that's
really
close
okay ah so what about the skill
inheritance
thing I take one skill with me right uh
from ah I can only take one with
me
maybe what does she even get with the
other class what should we get here
probably healing if she doesn't have a
healing skill in the other one then
yeah
okay H he's still the same oh for him he
doesn't get anything yet okay okay
okay then we need to look at weapons and
gear I have just the right thing for
you or so I thought this is the one that
we did pick
up or she just automatically equipped
it I think
so okay oh she's not wearing anything
here what the
[\h__\h] n uh
I want another good oh wait we can give
something from
kidu I suppose
this okay for him do we have something
oh I guess that's just something I had
lying
around more agility for
Cheeto is that isn't that uh no that's a
uh
willpower I think I have something yeah
this
one aamba is gone anyway yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh okay she has double then double
agility
okay we take a break
tired her
skills
what
oh
oh all of
them B all all of
them doely healing I guess I can do all
of them for
now oh
damage on the grand
line here's
wisdom boost
defense ha increases with higher
style
even enemies mhm
AOE
chance of a critical hit can I take one
of these too or are they not
worth oh wait I'm I'm done why is this
one
rainbow now what's the rainbow SL
oh super skill keep skill
okay okay let's see what we can do
here do I want to craft something new or
just upgrade what I
have we got this one now which I thought
is pretty strong it is a four star
knife we were quite excited when we got
that see what you can CFT okay so this
has like base
84 okay the one I can make is pretty
low
oh cuz I'm missing the bases of the
other
ones so maybe I just upgrade what I have
for now
it's okay I think this is fine damage
wise shopping more
yeah that's fine that's
fine
M and then the other one was for him the
samurai combat sword wait let's look if
we can craft one for him
though oh it's like the same
stuff no cannot
do
just let's just give Max I'm running out
of things oh no oh I can't why can I not
use these
things oh I can barely do [\h__\h] I need to
pick up more
trash I don't really I thought I had
some oh
[Music]
man wait how about can we at least brand
it no no man we
can't need more trash need more trash no
don't talk to me need more trash where
do I get more trash is there like a a
treasure grow of trash
somewhere stamina XX is amazing but
that's not what I'm looking
for
stimulant mod ver that's not what I
need this is my fast tring is bed okay
okay you know I love running around
anyway we'll run around a little bit
more then yeah where do we need to go
really far
okay oh
yeah okay let's go on a little a little
trip we'll be
walking just want to pick up literally
everything I see everything I spy with
my little
eye hi
Dogg calling
tea so I want to go to Ocean
Beach not screw
you well I am Austrian let me y they
don't know I'm
Austrian interesting critical
information
leave me alone leave me
alone no it's getting that bomb up let's
go can you even
y something like
that oh ha level 25 oh a good opponent
give me
your he resists he probably resists
everything no no no he doesn't
okay let's see let's look at her skills
flicker of light damages an enemy with
blade strikes nearly too fast for the
human
eye okay here we
go yes
try wow 400
plus nice
already very strong Kun is so busted you
think so it just
busted more agility buff you have on it
amazing amazing good that we have some
agility items
then wait unnecessary why am I wasting a
te
I did level it to like eight
yeah leave me alone leave me alone I
just want the trash no okay but it's not
trash it's just
banana
[Music]
okay I really like the idea of s
Festival right now I didn't even know
about the existence of that if it wasn't
for oh it's raining
if it wasn't for the
event so you know what that is it's like
um you know cuz it's really hot in
Thailand right now it's already summer
basically so what they do I don't know I
don't really know much but they they um
there's this thing like they play with
the water they have like water guns and
they shoot each other I guess maybe
there's more like water related
games you'll regret that I don't really
know what else they do but it's overall
looks really nice and
fun you get metal pieces easily from
helping out
people I don't have time for
that but also I
noticed they like to wear Hawaii
shirts during
San so a lot of people were wearing
Hawaii shirts and I was like oh why is
everybody wearing Hawaii shirts that's
so cute I feel this is giving me um
right now it's giving me Yakuza Vibes
cuz I also wear Hawaii shirt when I play
this game wait I'm going the wrong
way free magazine a fancy
one yeah and then they wear like Thai
pants and I've worn those before at like
Thai massage places sometimes they make
me wear those TI pants and I never know
how to properly wear them
CU they're like really wide on the hip
cuz you you wrap it around your
head and then you tie
it it looks really comfortable it is
really
comfortable
[Music]
people from the FR system who need help
how do I see
them they don't stand out to
me where are
they you looking
at so anyway I felt like everybody was
pretty stylish with their Hawai shirts
and the the tie
pants and then when they told me how hot
it is there 40 I was
like how are you guys wearing two
shirts in this
weather because they pretty much all of
them had a shirt
under going to C under the my shirt so
that's two layers
you do
it
C thank you thank
you for the M
[Music]
message not
interesting maybe to absorb sweat no I
don't think it has a purpose they're
just like built
differently hi
Bes
realistic I just stay in the room of AC
on 24/7 when I'm in Thailand I I if I
lived there I would probably do the
same but if I go there I I would feel
like oh my God I got to go out I'm I'm
oh
no
[Music]
no what I never saw it coming I never I
I never would have thought that my
neighbor was a murderer I never saw that
coming we're always so nice when my
cable is I think too short let me get
the longer
cable not even a prior warning yeah what
the
[\h__\h]
might
kitty sleepy kitty
[Music]
little I I found smovie on the
way she's off I gave her some KY
patties She's So Soft she was
like when she saw me she was
like when you trying to say
movie what are you trying to
say hi birdie bird how's it going I
haven't seen you in a
[Music]
while oh yeah right you don't agree you
don't you don't care about that do I
have bird food
yeah we're not Bes they seem happy guess
I made the right choice there's
something in their mouth egg oh yeah
these eggs are great 300
HP
thanks who's a good chicken who's a good
chicken it
no no I'm not interested in fighting you
I want to pick up the item quickness
lemon okay oh my intellect goes up with
that oh yeah can I just Flex so
okay I you know we're having an arc
right now at kfp where everybody's
terrified of me for how easy it is for
me to recognize
you so so for people who don't know
recently in the member stream I hey was
watching the VA for the concert
recently
and and they were like panning the
camera behind the audience and I saw a
dark
silhouette of a person stand it's just
stood out to me you saw hundreds of
people but there was one silhouette that
stood out to me and I was like I know
this is this fan this particular
fan I knew the name and I mean I didn't
see a face I didn't see like like not
even real color because it was a dark
silhouette and I still got it right and
that's really [\h__\h] fascinating it's
freak freaky but it's fascinating right
that I from a simple silhouette among
hundreds I was like this is this kfp
member yeah what do you mean distinctive
hair the thing is that you didn't see
the
hair was because of the of the of of the
accessories let's just say that okay and
then so you guys are terrified of me
because of that but uh then so let's
continue this Arc shall
we she's out
up
a don't watch Qui new vog okay I'll
watch it it's been getting recommended
to
me on YouTube
a
lot
nice okay I'll take that as an
invitation it's in the job
description nowadays yeah after many
complaints so wait I have something in
my
[Music]
eye today was the event in b
and in terms of Thai fans there's a few
a few Thai fans that I can think of you
know that are like very prominent and in
terms of cosplayers I know I know
there's this cute girl called tatan and
I knew she was planning to come but then
uh two days ago or so a tweet of hers
was in my in my timeline on Twitter
where she was saying like she was so sad
because she was planning on going but
now some like job thing keeps her from
going oh no
unfortunately she can't go to the event
even though she already had a VIP ticket
and everything and she was really
devastated about it I was kind of sad
too oh like oh too bad like that she
can't
come so I was like in my mind okay tan
will not be
coming and then during the
panel there were a few cosplayers okay
and a few a few cute girls okay not
saying there were not cute girls but
there was just not too many girls in
general there were some some girls you
know you saw her at Expo yeah she was
there
too and uh then I see I see some girls
in the audience I'm like hm I see I see
one
you know she was sitting uh somewhere
you know not in the first row in the
second row like somewhere there in the
middle and I only saw like the top of
her head on on the zoom camera like like
they were using two different cameras to
show us the audience and I saw like the
top of her head I saw there was like a
kiata cosplayer okay and it wasn't very
close either like it was pretty far
pretty small but I was like the camera
looks like Talan but like it gives me
Talan Vibes but but I thought she wasn't
here but then again like that kind of
looks like her so I called her out and
it was confirmed it was her I was like
yeah I I could trust my feeling my
gut okay that was I was feeling pretty
good about my guts and then uh in the in
the beginning we we were doing a little
pre-show um we were watching people come
in take a seat and we were just saying
hi and I accidentally I thought we
weren't live yet and I was like testing
out my audio and then it turned out we
were live and people were saying oh we
can hear you and your music and I'm like
oh [\h__\h] that's really embarrassing [\h__\h]
why didn't you tell me that we were like
live at this very moment and
audible but anyway I was like observing
people coming
in and
I see in the first row I see a
kfp with a really friendly
face KP I can say because they were
wearing like a orange uh orangee Hawaii
shirt there were a lot of kfps I would
say that were wearing orange Hawai
shirts on purpose for the purpose of
being
orange
and and then uh he had had like the new
the beach bag and the backpack all those
T turquoise things and I think maybe
even a chicken plushy or something like
that I don't know maybe that was someone
else but he had a lot of merch with
him proudly representing
and the one thing that nobody else was
doing but this person was doing is he
was wearing a frog cap a cute frog cap
besides all the other
stuff
yeah and so I was thinking okay because
at this point I I only saw the visuals I
didn't hear a voice I didn't hear a name
I didn't hear anything I only saw this
like pretty passionate looking
kfp from Thailand I was like could this
be it's such a random thought because
like I have I never saw blank before
never saw what he looks like I just know
you know black who always like was like
gifting memberships and
stuff I just knew that's one of my one
of the Tha kfp that uh jumps into my
mind when I think of Tai kfp I was like
maybe it's blank like I I see blank as a
very passionate kfp and this this guy
kind of gives me that aura even though
blank also never really wrote much in
chat or in
like the super chats or
whatever so I really didn't have much to
go off
of nothing I had actually nothing to go
off of
nothing
yeah and
then uh after the event like this was in
my mind the whole time like ah could
this be blank could this be not blank
hold up and after after the event was
over I was like going for Twitter
and uh blank tweeted a
picture of his hand holding some merch
up and you could see he was sitting in
the front
row and I was like front row by any
chance front C I didn't want to I didn't
want to like just assume and like
Clearly say it because if it was someone
else was wearing the Frog cap then it
would be kind of embarrassing that I
just assume you know that's why I'm like
I try to still be careful but I was like
pretty certain you
know so
um I was carefully like oh FR question
mark
and he said yes frog cap and sent a
picture of the Frog cap I was right this
was purely based on the aura and The
Vibes and the couple of Tai kfp that
show up in my chat SLS super chats uh by
name every so often it was just based on
Vibes I was just
assuming is this not
amazing am I not
amazing I just have this
intuition
[Music]
whoopsie
I'm pretty proud and I think if you're
that fan whoever I recognized I feel
like you should be like
damn she she reads me like an open book
she knows me
y even if she never saw my face before
she knows who I am how the [\h__\h] does she
do
it I think I think it should be
generally
flattering and the
chicken here's some
biry I might not ever see you again cuz
this place is kind of random but
enjoy
oh oh yeah I pulled out I finally pulled
out the the the cat hair out of my
eyes
this really
nice
no I get it Tomy feels weird to me
too all right sorry I was like what is
this
lemonade
wow you want me to buy
$1 I'll buy them all I'll buy them all
you're welcome oh I'm so glad yeah go
make some more lemonade also oh my God
he's got like lemon lemon tarts lemon uh
cheesecakes and stuff oh my God give me
some of
that oh yeah we got to support local
children's business ah another
one
I'm actually going to go to the place
where I'm supposed to go
now no we're not taking a
break the walking was the
[Music]
break clearly Japanese developers don't
know how expensive Hawaii is
I feel like a child
might uh be selling it relatively cheap
is this one of
those that you were
mentioning okay I'll do
it go cry
give me that iron
junk level 16 all
right he's guarding Dam but he's
paralyzed y' having having uh fun
electricity on that is
pretty strong I think you think I'm
stupid stupid go ahead take
all wearing theay helps get more ah
right for items I don't think anybody's
wearing it right
[Music]
now I
went okay we got to move on I've been
like running around with no goal in mind
it
seems oh oh that's one a we're here Pana
the
cult oh K is wearing it ahh k k
yeah is there no one here did
they no one
home
for
oh he's baiting us there he kid his
bait
hi hi hi
hi and so the enl Nae in all her wism
cast greedy into the Ping
fires oh this is kind of terrifying with
the fire above
him just like modern Game of Thrones or
I don't
know
wow uh okay poor
kid see he knows that I
know I knew that he would know that I
know
they're scaring me Father Pryce fear not
my child no ever can can withand the
hakal of
spirits what we should do now is pray
and let us beseech Madame nee to envelop
them swiftly and
painlessly why not get a native
speaker
yeah use the
D what
baracudas
yep yep
yep speak
clear speak
clearly
yeah exactly thank youan it wasn't just
me Oh I thought he was leading them into
the fire Heretics be gone is a [\h__\h]
tails off game I'll bury you sorry but
that was really fantasy RPG like
[Music]
28 oh big
area be
good bring the
be hit that one really strongly I see I
see I can crash him not the be
uh oh weak the fire
weak okay let's do it on
him
see come on good enough I keep on
forgetting that I just need to press
square a lot with that
[Music]
one lier to the
Leer what that dude's really
strong
what that dude's really
yes
[Music]
ow ow ow ow
ow they are mini B
huh the po po
Zealot okay okay okay okay
okay ichan already pretty low uh on HP
kind of
concerning ooh okay what do we have
Shadow
[Music]
slash wow those deep phrases here
freedom is to live as though already
diseased no not of surpassing others
merely surpass
ones calmed mind is a tranqu lake able
to reflect the Brilliance of the Moon
plunge recklessly toward death and
awaken from
dreams wow
[Music]
inspiring do your work
H foreign
spee got I use
this cuz of the guards needed a grapple
yeah BJ I'm pretty sick
hey okay how about we just
uh kill this
one one down your
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah oh we like that line we
like to see that
line yeah finally I have we missed on
that one okay uh okay for the first time
in a while I finally get that button
ProMed
right and I
still magic raised attack is
raised
[Music]
just this one right now is
okay wow sick looks really
cool what was
that at those little punches
is okay oh my God ichan don't die if you
die the game is
[Music]
over
who that's
so
700 did you see that damage that
probably wasn't AE but it did AOE H did
I see something wrong or was that just
collateral that's just
insane oh it's kind of crazy wow I mean
yeah they were weak to it but wow that
was great it was AOE damn nice H I
didn't
realize
uh
[Music]
think I can get
everybody good that we brought the heel
for
sure got so many attacks
guys I don't know if I really even want
to bring so many attacks with me I
always got to scroll down and think do I
want to use
[Music]
this yeah we can do
that
finally I got it right oh first time I
think we got too many options for my
[Music]
taste wait let's just
uh
finish mercele is a good guard break
move for each and does have the chance
to lower enemy attack defense both did I
did I bring this want a
long did I take that
one ow
ow should take out the the smaller one
first
[Music]
huh
yo didn't that one have full
HP look at her dooming around oh no
don't why did you get close to the enemy
uh-oh cleansing flash
uh-oh
yeah that sounded like an
[Music]
AOE they resist
fire
[Music]
but I use dreaming Arrow right or was it
burning error I it was burning error
what I was using was it cuz these one
say one enemy one
enemy
burning
okay well on let's shoot him towards for
me I didn't help shot by the
[Music]
way
huh wasn't it supposed to hit the one
behind as
well yeah you suck by the way yeah you
suck
I think it's because Tommy moved a
little bit before yeah before he did the
that's a scam that I I planned it all
out you can't do this to
[Music]
me this one's next but this one I might
be able to
kill
yeah have to end
him
woohoo all right he's got no chance at
all it's over my
friends Mr
ha it's so over
[Music]
eat this tuna that I got from Dave the
diver
yum get fished you stiny you should get
out of here now and take a shower cuz
you stin you
stin well time to take a
[Music]
break final
hit from our resident
Kun
nice we got some level 18 r up that were
waiting
for so Mr Bryce what do you think of
this oh look
[Music]
behind friend or fo I feel like they'll
be
friendly Dana those are good
people
brainwashed
we can reason with
[Music]
them
for it's a cold
lady wanket from the
bed
no not
like no no
no it's so
nice
well they only saw like the end of
it could be lying about what
went
[Music]
what's
becoming
enlightened enough to go to the
island
for well
no
right not that difficult to change your
voice is
[Music]
it
for
spee for
foree
for thank you
Trevor
[Music]
wow he's deep in the
cult too
deep my nose running a little bit
[Music]
for
oh
okay
guys fill in the
gaps
[Music]
I know your brain can do it I know human
brains can do
that just learn Japanese
easy but we are chickens oh yeah right
sorry move to the middle no no I moved a
little bit more to the side ah ah ah
I still feel like sneezing
more it's ticklish in my
[Music]
nose oh five memberships thank you oh K
you wait are we in a new
is
that no it's an airplane wait it sounds
like an airplane but it looks like
[Music]
a must have been a must have been a
plane looks more like a train from the
inside
wait how long does it take from like
Tokyo
to
Hawaii how long is the
[Music]
flight very mixed answers I guess I got
to do it myself
look it up Hawaii to Tokyo well where in
Hawaii is the question I don't care hu 8
Hour 40 a different place could be 11
hours yeah so 9 to 11
hours with non-stop flights are like 9
hours onstop flights are like 11
hours to kaaa to Hulu there's a lot of
non-stop flights they're really cheap
too but 9 hours that's a that's a long
long distance flight that's what I'm
saying is as a very experienced
flyer that I
am that type of airplane is not what
they would use for a 9-hour
flight just
saying there was only two like you know
there was one aisle in the middle
there must be you know it should be like
a a free 4 free it looks like they're an
economy it should usually be like a free
for free or maybe a sometimes maybe a
two for two but
n it's too small
for it's too small for such a flight no
no no look there was only one one no no
no no don't
skip can we get another
scene of
everything do we get to watch that no
they didn't show it
anymore
I was starting for my air travel
locational test oh they do show
us
[Music]
yeah
for
Fore
so you think he's toughing it out but
he's also trying to go to death as fast
as can or is saying because he's
toughing it out he's overexerting
himself and thus it seems like he's like
rushing to
death maybe that's what he means cuz
otherwise it seemed
contradictory thank you for the
membership
somewhat
cozy
true
[Music]
fore
what do you mean found nothing found
cancer
[Music]
right
oh goodbye
moos more
Wheels another nice
see
he looks good with
glass oh he's
listening oh oh it's
her Korean battle chick
right woo
[Music]
son
fore uh
Al
RTX
not
quite not
[Music]
quite
tell him oh she
pretty
for
[Music]
duck no what what is
it don't think too deeply about
it
Korean I just read the
bottle
[Music]
foree
wow
[Music]
not really
but apparently you
are that's why we've been saying for
ages for
weeks lay the [\h__\h] down go to
[Music]
hospital
no no no
no going to a cat
cafe should go to a cat
cafe are you for
real
wait are we going to play it like a mini
game it's kind of
interesting building this little
group on the Japanese side I feel like
they're going to add one more person and
then we will end
up fighting with K
again and this the rest of the
group I see a big picture where there's
like yeah like more of the
older people
characters
oh and we're still kind of looking for
uh what's her name again the other
girl
not ah son joined the party what do we
need a party for if we're not going to
fight anything huh yeah
sat
sat yeah yeah
yeah
H why do we have this party we going to
be splitting parties like we're
splitting hairs now
huh I want to go to
[Music]
Hawaii what the [\h__\h] do you want
h
oh yeah that is
true yeah let's
[Music]
f we all know how this is going to turn
out
but he's he's in the
fight what's the
point oh he's confused cuz he's seeing
the things the people the way that
ichiban's seeing
them you've become a
hero I don't know how how is this
happening to you is it
the maybe cuz you're drunk
[Music]
what one was all that talk for if he's
going to end up fighting
anyway
big p
moment
o can we give them over here also those
Hawaii jobs or probably not right I'm
fine with it but you
know she uses a [\h__\h] crossbow oh we
can
oh wait they're strong what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] ah the good old pigeon raid and the
good old pyro belt and
[\h__\h] good
stuff H it's not very
far hm
oh
[Music]
well nice C I was even looking at the
chat maybe I should always look at the
chat there actually he won't be there
long because none of the weap sell
ah yeah makes a lot of
sense no that's good that they don't
sell it cuz what if you like into nambas
so you want to keep him in your team and
you put all all you get him all this
equipment and stuff and then he leaves
right away You' be like what the
[Music]
[\h__\h]
shees
there's a reason why chat was pushing
fori I just thought it was because he's
stronger but okay
[Music]
nice my controller is so
hot he's so
[Music]
hot
yeah
charging
ow I mean it probably wouldn't even need
to be charged anymore
but why not keep it
[Music]
connected ah
guys do you have for next month cuz I
got to put in my order you guys have
like a
suggestion what do you want to see in
the member's
wallpaper like a theme cuz I'm running
out of themes and may is like what even
happens in May Rocky is not not really
doesn't make sense to move do it
now like a
[Music]
cherry blossoms cherry blossoms season
is kind of now may kind
of I don't really necessarily want to
always have it season related there's no
need to do that all the time I've been
doing that for 2 years now or so maybe
just some like really specific
theme like yeah like a made for spring
cleaning interesting but is this made
like more end of the spring already
middle
end a h talk set ar oh
[Music]
interesting
CCL strawberry ping I want to do
strawberry picking cuz that's the season
of
strawberries I do want to go strawberry
picking that could be
cute that will
okay gets me hyped
up but like not in one of those Halls it
should be outside in a field out the
open with a nice
[Music]
Basket in a cute
Dr cute dress
hair chicken's
helping he chickens with smaller baskets
or chickens holding the big baskets over
their
heads with the strawberies many
straberries
that's
cute this sounds like a great idea yeah
I picked a seasonal food I don't know I
just had
a a light bulb turned on over my
head a Flash of
Genius oh K on there's this garage
nearby called a romance Workshop we used
to get our Rons oh okay
okay uh
we'll go check it out it's like isn't it
like right here this thing no no they
want me to go
to is it this
one no that's not what he me what did he
just say romance romance
[Music]
something
no
this oh this place is so big oh what the
[\h__\h]
H I was
[Music]
at oh
oh
guys I'm suffering from hallucinations
okay go easy on
me oh
no level
[Music]
30 no what the [\h__\h] oh this might be
your
B
H what should I
[Music]
use
yeah laying him like a fiddle oh
[Music]
no wait I should choose him
though
[Music]
but this should work too will it will it
work yeah no it only works on two people
all right that's okay I
[Music]
tried at least he's getting some rest
now while
standing charm no they're using a lot of
debuffs
[Music]
okay I think oh this might be perfect
they're pretty weak to it too you guys
just got to get a little bit closer but
I think it
works yeah Free People
oo good damage
oh wow wait I thought K was sleeping now
he's Charmed I thought the lady was
Charmed
nice
nice wow W strong they're all kind of
low on
HP let's
[Music]
next can I get some
AOE
again oh interesting will this work n
cuz he moved out of the
way
[Music]
but
still I'm satisfied if somebody loses
their
life okay guys what there anything I
should be talking
about
anything
can't think of
anything oh we finally need to heal but
y how's the toe the toe is
okay toe is feeling pretty good
y to is okay to is actually pretty
healed up oh yeah y y
[Music]
yeah I should have
healed I should have definitely
healed good to hear
yeah the toing get amput no that that's
why my toe is fine because it's gone
that's why I feel
good um
so I think a priority is on healing K
up how about the
egg where's the
egg jumbo
egg it's time to use the egg we're a
little bit in a pin oh no
[Music]
maybe okay you can have the
egg
[Music]
I know maybe
yeah I can't block that can
I [\h__\h]
sleep I've been trying to block it but I
don't think we can to grow back so it's
okay what are you speaking from personal
experience otherwise I don't believe
you holy [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
um dude this fight is a little bit
crazy
um I guess
[Music]
I'll what a waste only two
people if I revived Namba then he would
probably die a Kitt would probably die
or she would die one of them would die
too
so okay
we finish the other
[Music]
one we'll finish him
now at least we get some AOE oh no he
doesn't
die what's with your [\h__\h] powders oh
he missed thank
God running away is not true I didn't
even really oh see it as an
option oh my God I have to heal him
again
come
on I don't want to run
away I'm not a
coward perfect guard really important
right
now a winning
this what is here weep swords
[Music]
anyway kill him
uh yeah I could use pound
[Music]
M
delivery maybe this one maybe cuz this
one heals also but is that all he does
Blast Away bad guys for free turns doing
h b damage for each and healing upward T
HP of the
party I
[Music]
mean should i
r a
[Music]
turn
do I just bleed forever or does it go
away ever
uhoh ow ow ow ow ow I would have died if
I didn't
he we were supposed to protect Kido and
now I'm just like using him as a
punching bag more or less ah she's out
of MP
[Music]
no n this is so
dumb I can't can I leave I can't leave
now can oh wait I I
can whatever I'm leaving
I
couldn't is are they going to
uh-oh oh my
god well that's the end of kio's story I
hope Ichiban will not be too
sad oh my money oh my God that's so much
[Applause]
money oh no it's fine I actually have
quite a bit of
money but
man it's kind of
unfortunate they were pretty high level
and I lost number cuz I was yeah not I
should have healed in that one
round then we would have been
fine
ooh pretty little
thing
[Music]
one whole week one whole
week
oh there's the Aly
thing Japanese Curry okay I was actually
I was hoping to go this way but the
enemies were scaring
me I'm scared to fight now but it seems
like I need to level
up anyway oh wait it's not this way it's
that
way
WAOW modified rocket launcher 600
damage
y I got to grind those are special
enemies earlier H I guess okay the one
dude was really special for
sure the rance's workship shut down you
really didn't know what of course I
didn't know I don't understand did she
go out of business with us no apparently
she word of her got around so far that
some head hunter from America got her a
cushy Sil Valley job if it's any
consolation I hear she's only in it to
hone her skill set she wants to come
back someday and make her Workshop
better than ever well how about
now well good for her of course she
couldn't just leave the garage full of
heavy duty Machinery sitting unattended
so she found people to rent it the
people running it now are competent I
occasionally come here myself however
the LI share went to some place in
Hawaii H so I guess if we need our
equipment maintained this is still where
we go Hawaii you said do you think it
could be hm small world well let's see
what they have to
offer okay she's gone a fantasy Star
online soundtrack she's gone but we can
still use the place
what did I invest so much money into
this
for okay do we want to craft a new
weapon can we even no I
cannot I do have what I need for this in
terms of base weapon but I have no Lava
geod for the
others
I I can
make a
cane what I don't know it's weaker than
what he
has don't know about
that you can exchange GE at the dungeon
oh should I do
that let me out let me out let me
out the D
what is the
dungeon
dungon I can't do it now
oh maybe just like
some small upgrades for
now
but I use the same stuff as it's in same
inventory I guess I don't have much they
but the story is making me go here I
don't have much
I'm off to work
about I just don't want to upgrade is
that okay
too it's okay
right rainbow fragments oh there's a lot
of stuff
here we're not
microwave nitrogen Z Chun we're not
microwave damn to much [\h__\h]
trash
[Music]
will okay maybe we have to fight we
should
fight Bring It
On will be
weaker yeah 28 that's much
better oh [\h__\h] she has no
MP
[Music]
M no
problem no need for
M
yeah Revenge what just
happened I need take some lives to feel
better what really Namba that's kind of
weak he was already weak to your element
and you still couldn't take him
down
OMG
[Music]
pretty
epic yo I like this music this seems
like a theme I haven't heard before but
maybe maybe I'm very
wrong
is this
new it is new okay all right next up we
go ooh so
far but I I think I'll walk so we can
pick up items and find some people on
the way oh hello a you're just making me
wor about the Aloha jobs okay okay okay
okay
should I change shops then should I
keep
drops for the FKS
[Music]
here just somehow looks the funniest to
me on
him
this looks like a cowboy to
me
ooh oh mate maybe that's what the ankor
is
for I don't know man I don't know what
to do without clear instructions I'm not
sure what's the best thing to
do
let me another cotton angler AO let
me make a route at least and let me
check my gear because he's also
missing an item we can have
this
again
ooh ah forgot about this ooh Max HP
decreases we don't want that for him MP
also no nullifies nullifies nullifies
boring we could take one of these until
we switch
again now give him the magic
thing no
gear so I'm guessing agility is good for
her as
well might be wrong but I feel like her
job that kind of Suits her
just go for the main story you can
figure it out later
yeah just some random modified grenades
lying around
here in Tokyo no biggie nothing weird
about that nothing concerning about
that everything's normal
ah
[Music]
I do not feel safe in this
environment oh my God look at look at
all these skills she
has Gatling bow gun let's try this in a
line got I use got to go for this one
maybe the one that thir well but they
moved out of the way those suckers
man yeah I brought the lemonade with me
it's still good it ages like Japanese
Curry no it doesn't
[Music]
but
I
[Music]
miss what do you want to do n huh's we o
h wait can we get
both uh maybe from this
[Music]
angle y
fire oh yeah speaking of fire makes me
think of Sparks but you know what I sang
at the event I sang do you and Chapple
and Kima and then we sang Fire and Ice
so I sang free solos Callie also sang
free solos and then we sang Fire and Ice
together that's seven songs quite a lot
of songs and it wasn't as short as the
usual panel because we you know it was
our event so first day we're like okay
guys you can do like a 50 minute set if
you want but you can also do a longer
one I'm like oh we should do a longer
one because you know all these
people we're having like a special event
just for them so I feel like it would be
nice
wow especially cuz there's no meat and
greets Namba don't die
again if there's no meat and greets it
would be nice if you know we can give
them a lot of Great
Value m
make the most out of it yeah and then
and then we were even late as well late
as in uh we were
over uh what's the word we were just
using up too much
[Music]
time yeah all
time
nice I think in total our panel was like
1 hour 3040 or so I'm not sure but it
was really
long and I was getting pretty pretty uh
like weird like DIY or just feeling not
so good because I woke up at like
450 or so
455 and then I just had a
yogurt and and I I I was I was pretty
awake for it though even though I didn't
get much
sleep that was fine but yeah I think
they got good value for
it we did uh just the introduction then
we looked through the pictures of
Thailand then we uh played the true or
false game a few
rounds I I Bamboozled people by like uh
putting a statement like so tell me tell
me if this is wrong or right
Tak used to eat 54 chicken nuggets per
day or I used to claim that I do
that wrong or
right right
true that's what they fought to F
because it was
fre a lot of nugget
yeah I've I've been Boozled them a lot
with numbers like that was also uh
another another false one was that I had
30 Holo talk episodes
no it was
29 but they all they got it all wrong I
was like um because the staff told us to
do this actually and I think it makes
sense for the questions like when it
came to my questions chose a dead beat
so that it's not too easy we asked like
okay who here would consider themselves
a dead beat rather than a kfb and those
people whoever said they want to do
it they came to the front and they were
like
answering
accordingly to the best of their
knowledge and for Callie's
questions we were looking for kfps to
answer the question the true or false
thing it's not really
question what do you mean I'm not the
most reliable source of lore
yeah that's quite
reliable like kfp were also getting uh
the Cali uh true or false statements
wrong even though a lot of them were
Kiana
related I think I think no one got
anything right so
the staff originally planned that we
would be doing Bas like if the if the
guest uh gets it right that means we
lost our side Takami side so then we
would do aatu but they always got it
wrong so I was like okay let's let's let
the guests do a Batu then and they were
all pretty up for it that's why the one
dude was rapping and then another one we
asked I asked him to do a vol more cute
oh God there pink and he was
so he was so dangerous he was so
motivated he was so into it he did the
whole pose and he was like really Ganky
he was
like no he he even
said and everybody's like
wo I think it was a a really nice
atmosphere everybody was having fun
everybody was having a good
time yeah they had good
energy sorry I'm not really they're not
this interesting these
conversations sorry
NBO it was B
yeah and the Q&A they told us that Thai
fans really like Q&A so we added a
little Q Q and
A and they they they came to the front
to ask a
question one question was
like can you tell us what do you like
about each other and then the other
question was um what
uh if you if you were to go to
Thailand with some member Ian no whole
life me besides your uh besides the
other like right next to you AKA for me
cie who would it be and cie said she
wanted to take the dogs but then I was
like oh you should be taking beu though
you're so close with beu and she speaks
Tai why is that not your first fought
and she says like ah well because I
wanted the dogs to play in the water
because of
sunron and I was like but you should
take beu doesn't that make so much sense
so she was like I'll take all of them
and then I said okay for me H you know I
could say Nissa but I already took her
on a trip before so maybe someone else
and then in myth I kind of like the idea
of traveling with you know the myth
girls besides Cali but they they I don't
know they're like you know they a little
bit um shy and all that so maybe I was
thinking how about ID I'd love to go
with the myth girls too but then I was
thinking yo going with ID is always so
much fun like I haven't really traveled
with them but just from the time I've
spent with them I knew they were going
to be like so much fun so I just said
anybody anybody from
ID would make me really happy to go on a
trip with
yeah doesn't even have to be waya
because
like who what did I just do I pressed
the button it [\h__\h] everything up I
don't see what you guys are
seeing when I have to think I have to
open close and open the
thing anyone but
Ana yeah anyone but Ana cuz I hate
Anya I love way is I can't be
unbiased well see I was thinking of
saying way it too but again I've been on
trips with waya so I was like I should
choose someone else so just anybody from
ID maybe
Ollie
[Music]
MAA anybody B of course
B yeah I just love hanging out with them
they're so
fun h all happy jobs please yep yep
thank you thank you
MH interesting F rally I no
no no no no no no we're not doing
that Co would be fun for real
yeah yeah yeah
yeah so should we change
jobs no
well we got sidetracked a b but we
should be able to reach a batting side
now are we actually going to go batting
or is it like when we said we're going
to a casino and we didn't
gamble I cannot trust this game anymore
I have trust
issues they're all lying to
me kind of want to see what else they
were up to at the event besides our
panel because I I only know they
prepared like some games and stuff I
think s Clan
themed
games and there were our beautiful
sandies and our beautiful merchandise
but besides that I don't really I
haven't really seen pictures of what
else there was to be done I yeah and we
had like little little screens where you
could take a picture with us cuz we to
collect some videos again
uh so you can stand next to us and we're
moving it's like a pre-recorded
video besides that the outfits on art is
so good
right so good what do you mean Battle
Royale for the cardboard CS what does
that
mean what is what are you talking about
is there like a situation where somebody
gets to take home the cardboard cut outs
and people battle over it or
what
it's so good I have to buy it right I
really love it
too new jobs yeah but do I want
them that would be fun you want to
battle other fans for the cardboard
cutout last chicken
standing yeah those acrylics I want I
want my acrylic
stand
ah yeah the flowers D were so pretty
thank you for organizing those my dear
[Music]
tyin you know I love seeing
those from my days in
[Music]
Japan what do you
got watermelon
wait what does it do 10
HP six what do you mean 6 out of
500 I'll just buy
him oh yeah for the fruit salad salad
salad fruit salad fruit
salad fruit
salad
[Music]
salad I know I'm at the batting Center
but you know
me oh sports equipment oopsie
a yeah we not doing that job anymore but
maybe I don't know maybe Kido could be
doing it no no Kido stays what he is
right never
mind a pink
boss
no
do we have like something nice no
they're
all all 15
MP and yet they have different
prices this one looks like oh the
cheapest these
two Ando for another 10 levels
mhm
not thinking of going in wait wait I'm
not supposed to go
here supposed to go over
here hey I'd like to use the Batting
Center I've never been in the Batting
Center
P oh my God they got Puna P the but it's
a little
bit
unusual
usually usually
um
usually don't worry I don't think I've
told you this part about the P up before
so let's let's imagine okay um I think
we need
pain I think we need we need
Paint this is
important
okay
okay sorry sorry so
sorry so with you know you see um you
see when you walk into a place that has
puura you will see many boobs next to
each other they're pretty big and
they're like these cubes okay and
usually on one side there will be like a
little screen and a place to put in your
money and Al uh also like okay it
depends like sometimes the money
entering plac is on that side and then
the other thing is on the other side and
this but um so sometimes they're
combined and you can like in the
beginning screen you can choose like
what do you want to do and this and that
sometimes however that is inside
sometimes to go inside and then
um inside okay when you're inside the
the the shooting location it will look
like this this is
like um how do I do this lights lights
uh uh
camera a screen maybe where you can see
yourself and um a place to put your bag
and a little hook a little hook and then
behind you is the green screen and you
stand here sometimes sometimes usually
you do like a like a full body picture
and then some close-ups but what are you
talking about actual huh uh but
sometimes there's even like puy curas
that focus on only like waist UPS or so
whoo so they don't even take full body
so the green screen isn't even from
bottom to the top but H let's just say
it is like a more classic one that takes
a full body and some closeup and so on
so you go maybe maybe you go in maybe
outside you just threw in the money but
sometimes you know you have to throw in
the money here and it will be like 400
Yen sometimes it's more expensive though
and uh and then you choose there's some
choices you can make like the pattern
you can choose maybe you want four
close-ups and two full bodies or you
want four full bodies and two
closeups uh it depends what you're
feeling and then sometimes in the
beginning you can already
uh choose like how crazy big you want
your eyes to be how natural Etc
sometimes you can do this afterwards
sometimes before but yeah it will tell
you what to do but in any case what I'm
saying is that unlike in what You' just
seen in the game usually there's several
several sides to it so you see maybe you
see like a curtain here usually there's
like big cute faces like you just saw on
top and I see oh okay that's where I
enter cuz I see a little green screen
below so you go in here you take the
photos and then you come
out on the other side and then you go
maybe to this side or to that side let's
say we go to this side and there's
another curtain and you go in and it's
like really cramped in here why why
because well let me show
you let me show you let me get rid of
this
here
and I want to start a completely new
document oh this actually pretty
annoying I should have Maybe started a
new document so after you're done taking
the
pictures they the they tell you please
walk out and turn around and go to the
next next part okay and then you go
through the next curtain which is on the
other side perhaps and what do you see
it's it's really cramped it looks M how
do I draw this this is the
curtain and then there's like
a it looks like
this he's listening he's listening and
so we stand you stand like here it's
really cramped so that if you're wearing
a backpack or so it will like make the
curtain go like this yeah you know what
I I mean so you're standing
here and uh you hang your there's not
even a place to put all your bags no you
there's a little bit of a a Nook here
that you can uh hang your bag onto your
shopping bag maybe but then there's the
screen so you both s cuz normally you
take P CA with two people sometimes with
more people but everything is made for
like uh taking care of the editing and
so on with two people so then you start
doing all the stickers and stuff and the
you add like some writings and stuff on
the py to make it look cute like you add
all kinds of like comments and some
Doodles some scribbles and and then also
there's always like some kind of music
playing here so you can switch to music
while you're editing it and if there's
somebody in here like in the same
particular machine already taking more
pictures like uh they're they're coming
up to your editing area soon then it
will have a countdown that's really
stressful and sometimes there's really
barely any time for you to put like
stickers and stuff and cat ears and so
on on on every picture cuz you take like
six or eight pictures and so on it's
barely anytime and it really stresses
you out but then sometimes it's
nothing's happening so you have like
forever time and it keeps on extending
the time and and then and then you
choose a layout because it can it can
look like like
[Music]
this or it can look completely different
okay and they usually come out like this
and then you cut there's usually some
table with scissors there yeah but you
see you see how crowded how how little
space there is so this is the second SE
well well first first of course there's
the outside section where you also get
your picture uh in like a it comes out
of this hole oh and then there will be a
screen let's say you paid inside and you
chose all the beginning beginner
settings inside then outside there will
be a screen where you put in your email
address and and some sometimes you
choose the layout out here sometimes you
choose it here oh my God it's always
different okay but so let's say you
chose you chose the the email address
and how you want to send it to you and
this and that you chose it there and
then you wait a little bit and then it
gets printed and then whoops it comes it
comes out of here like like fresh bread
like my pen doesn't seem to work
anymore no I broke it why is it not
working
anymore a there we go okay
and then you take you stand here oh it's
not working
again you stand here with your
friend and you take the piga and you go
and so there's threee Parts at least
minimum three parts and you got to think
that this first shooting area usually
takes up like this whole half of the
cubicle and then yeah it's like honestly
I don't I I don't even this is a mystery
it's like a a little maze like a magical
maze where are they putting all this
stuff I don't even
know like it could be like this like
here is the editing area and here the
shooting area but the shooting area
really really feels so much bigger than
the other stuff I don't know how they
squeeze it all in there it makes no
sense it's magical we have to we have to
get a detective to fix figure out how
they're squeezing this all in in this
little small
cubicle wow impressive engineering it's
crazy what's happening is there like a
like a second dimension that you're
entering when you walk into the curtain
to take the pictures is there like maybe
it's like a secret room you think you're
in the cubicle but in reality you're in
like a different room or a different
dimension all
together like
niia
but so yeah do you understand what I'm
trying to
say why did I move my setup so much holy
[\h__\h] CU here you can see
clearly just they got it all wrong I
mean maybe just because it's a really
old machine but I I've seen all and I
haven't seen one side puty like this in
a long time
it's so one-sided there's only like
this W it's like a like a not even like
pyura it's just like a normal photo
machine
H it's like normal photo but there are
no normal photo boobs in Japan no there
are but but then why I put these
pictures that look so pretty like on top
of it like it they are normal photo
boobs but they're not this cute and pink
you
know this is for entertainment you know
but anyway but anyway
anyway I'm done I'm done I'm done don't
worry I'm done oh wait where am I
supposed to
go yeah disappointing
P one out of
one out of 10 I'm not satisfied I'm not
pleased I've tested many many P booths
in my past uh time so far on Earth
and I must say as a pretty
conosur this has not what I desire in a
puura machine thank you for the
memberships though I appreciate it is I
am the puura expert yeah how many boobs
have you used oh I have used I have used
so many I even worked for pyura company
before and I told you this before
right I worked for one of the top three
biggest PR companies in Japan
before I worked for them so I even
tested their
machines uh at in the
company
pretty good at tear list they they
really push out so many machines
throughout the year um I would have to
live in Japan to make a tier
list cuz uh yeah like every I feel like
every
season they bring out like all the
companies bring out new machines there's
always new machines and there's always
different ones that are the most popular
among the girls among the teenage high
school girls and all that but yeah swing
bats
okay this is like fishing but it's not I
see
uh
yes PR you going have a few shorts but
the is
ah what the
hell that you can't see my not supposed
ah when am I supposed to
hit way earlier I
guess I've never played this before and
we're life nether
okay what
unbelievable oh
hey what am I supposed to
know what are you kidding me this so
mean make me feel like
[\h__\h] yo finally home
run yo even a home run not just like the
other
ones I another
one I
another oh I'm getting it what the
[\h__\h] oh cut whatever that is single what
does that mean at least it's not a
strike
yeah wow okay I needed a few tries it
was the first time in my life but hey
what the [\h__\h] rank
D now you got me what do I get out of
this do I get any money from this no I
just lose money right yeah
oh [\h__\h] our
BS our first stop what are we doing next
taking
oh my God baseball is healing his
cancer I'm always up for kind of
[Music]
there's a point from my mini
game okay that's all you had to say
ever you had
[Music]
me
ending that's so depressing don't like
if you make your bucket list early in
life then okay cuz then you're not
expecting to die anytime soon but making
a bucket list when you're like you have
cancer and you're about to die like
isn't that so depressing bro don't don't
tell him to maybe think of doing that
you're just saying oh you're going to
die thanks
man oh my
God
[Music]
yeah
they
[Music]
calling that's even more
depressing
[Music]
for
BR
[Music]
to he definitely trying his best to take
care of
I
[Music]
love he liked it for once he's taking a
suggestion
[Music]
wait this is so depressing so is that
like what we're going to be up to on
this side like when we're not in haai
we're just going to be checking off K's
pocket list
for the rest of the second half of the
game
huh I don't know if I want to do that
that's just depressing what the
[\h__\h]
quietly
staring
[Music]
awkward
for
don't
laugh you think you're better or what
sure you want to eat those sweets
too
[Applause]
why why Club can we not just go to
sweets
Paradise all you can eat sweet in
Japan I don't I don't think the young
people who want to eat nice sweets that
are popular right now go to a cabaret
Club n are you okay you just want to go
to the Cabaret Club that's that's just
what you want to
do if you want to go where the young
people or go to Sweet
Paradise
oh
oh awaken kio's Soul Tech and Body by
checking of items on his bucket list as
he regains more of his former self the
dragon of do fighting style as well as
his resistance to status a and Elemental
types become
stronger
okay stronger moves
okay
oh ading K's unfinished business while
there's still
time will help restore his will to fight
but we didn't want him to fight Oh you
mean like fight the cancer or fight in
fights check these tasks by revealing
unfinished business in The Bucket List
oh come
on
man
ah
huh huh how could she be here if she's
in Hawaii
wait huh sometimes nostalgic sites can
reignite memories of the past the more
kid you happens to see remember the thir
that he awakens well well why are we
treating him like a patient of uh
Amnesia what's up just seeing the sign
gets me a little no
stag it does have that look does it
place is bable let me take you to my
favorite spot trust me you won't regret
it oh it's like all sub
stories you canot take
[Music]
taxis
oh a cabaret
Club among all the cities I visited each
and every Cabaret clubs oh he's just
like me with the
Pua just as glamorous as the last really
oh you can enjoy some quality no they're
really reminiscing this is like
screenshots from old games he's really
dying
Shin M the customer can only have a good
time because of all the Blood Sweat and
Tears that go on behind the scenes
having dabbled in management side of
things myself I've seen firsthand how
much effort it
takes I'm thinking back on it I'm
actually starting to miss that c of work
now about to join me sometime even
though he'll make me promise not to
drink oh
man can't be for real oh there's another
one right over
there
land soap land looks close right now
seeing one reminds me of that
conversation I had with Haruka all those
years ago when she asked me what a soul
plan was I had no idea how to answer but
that cheky little girl probably knew it
would get me flustered and asked anyway
she definitely had me on the ropes there
I wonder how she'd react if had to asked
her the same
question that should be as flustered as
I
was
[Music]
wait where's by where does it lead
to I don't need to go there where am I
where am I going to go
next
here
man don't want to fight with them but
these ones we can fight with
you the essence of
dying
[Music]
defeated
[Applause]
oh hostile hope
worth doing this I mean I'll
[Music]
fine I should have killed
him oh he's got my
[Music]
heal thanks for the
M thank
you
a nice insight into his past yeah it's
it's sweet but it's also just so
[Music]
depressing they're rubbing his death
into our
B
back me
too I want to go to
my
yeah I'm so
jealous oh
man I would
I would let K give me a massage I will
never turn down any any person offering
me a
massage okay maybe if it's a complete
stranger okay then I would most likely
turn it down don't worry
guys death boom box W for Breakers
oh what a
you want to eat
h
where am I
going nice
toughness can I give you a massage
K maybe
not
on y we're getting so much number
Bingo chicken WIS have no R yeah you
guys guys
calling wouldn't do such a good job but
at least it's
free I'm thinking about
it can I get a massage from you yeah
when I prepare you
for
tomorrow's chicken
she
here wa it was this easy to get to
her
does she know the Korean
lady does right we work they fought
together
right
yeah so that we have a four people party
I can't believe she's joining us this
easily
I guess as long as ich is another
around don't let
ich don't tell him
cat
fight and they not
to
welcome back to the
[Music]
party when we update ichan about like
how K is doing I was just going to
completely let not
mention
H
fore fore
[Music]
spee
that's
fine
she's got the hearts for
him
Dam she asked about him so she
cares
yeah she cares she
cares she
does
[Music]
fore
foree
fishing finally what the [\h__\h] how is
this our first Bingo we're just like
speedr running it of
number
yo I won't lie this river is filthy mhm
like the river and S Buon maybe things
have changed by now but it was also
pretty dirty back then
so then buy entertainment capital of the
West and Kam's biggest rival the rzy
ambience is really similar to Kam but it
still has its own lure it also happened
to be the Battleground between the
jingan mafia and Omi Alliance there I
met ruji Goa and K for the first time
guess you could say it was a pretty
special place to me plus the food's
great nothing beats authentic
also wait I I I played the game that
they're referencing here
no too wait I don't play a I played zero
but I was there
too it's a great City yeah but it won't
ever top
[Music]
Kam so many
items I want that memory over there
there and if I have to fight for it I
[Music]
win was yeah was alsoo
right I
missed take
there
[Music]
nice Sledge
haror
wow I do want to change her job it's
kind of boring to
me
lock the
dynamite this Des is one of eo's many
symbols a h of different bars and pubs
it looks really
cool this reminds me I used to hit up
one of the bars in oi pretty often
everyone there was irregular so it was
hard getting to know them turns out they
were all good with' raise the glass and
chat over good drinks together I'll
always be so thankful for the bar for
providing me with a comfortable
Space six
I someone's almost dying here maybe I'll
just oh I can't Auto
recover
[Music]
I oh I guess I could have eaten here
damn
it let's fight I'm
motivated
is oh [\h__\h] no
MP
oh thanks K nice follow
[Music]
up we have healed up three of survive
yeah I
[Music]
guess he's weak to
this pigeon
G eat this
human Feast on him take
revenge for how people are treating you
like trash
bird you are better than those human
trash
pigeons must take
revenge Jus must be
served we chickens stand by the pigeon
fraction in
support when they march to war we March
alongside
[Music]
them our
bre we suffer with
them and we succeed with
them
die in the name of the
birds
Superior Justice
for
yeah that's right PE was it's never an
option yeah you
got you got the
[Music]
spirit I like
P except when they poop on
me that is not very
nice no wait wrong place kind of
okay should we
tell the lady she's not here
right where is
[Music]
she oh
survive the
name it works so well
what I
guess
no no they know each
other
what is
[Music]
this what was he
doing
I don't think I
remember but I also remember him from
the first like a dragon
game my
brain it's mixing
everything want to service the whole
place for
us or do you just know there's no one
else coming because no one ever comes
besides
[Music]
do
fore
speee
[Music]
you're not even
listening you got to
listen wait is he actually feeling a
little bit like what am I singing
[Music]
for
you're getting the honor of
[Music]
being oh is just tur again yeah he's
just singing
[Music]
his
again
[Music]
make me
sad
fore
[Music]
great our Liv hero
did we have a sign of this
before
for tell
us
for
foree they're
being
for
Mama
that's why my island is filled with
trash I thought he was going to be in
Witch The Witcher four not in
Godzilla
fore fore
fore
[Music]
for
than
[Music]
damn A lot happened tonight I should
head back to kasuga's apartment wasn't
there a place to crash in here
too whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
okay chill
out oh
no what is
it it's time oh all do hosan how's it
going you know each other uh do we C got
used to pitch in for him
huh what
this what was this about is are you all
right yeah now oh thank
you sorry about that let me introduce
myself name's
hio hero president of part-time hero Inc
we'll get you a hero or my name's not
hero Suzuki I haven't heard the part of
parttime hero before well it's a service
that this bad is hero is across the city
to anyone who might be need our heroes
of course are parttime as we believe in
what we do time was uh we dealt with
practically everything from bodyguarding
to hurting cats ah we've been a bit uh
short staff lately because ichan left us
so we've pivoted our Focus to our
part-time rescue division
for there's an epidemic out there of
normal folks being
flr extorted and harassed we aim to
provide them with protection any hero
who successfully resolves such a
situation earns rewards from us the more
you help the more you compensated hey Su
would you like to register with us like
I said we could definitely use more
musle kasan was able to do how does he
know that we know
kasan part time work that helps people
in danger huh it's a noble way to make
money I suppose all right if it was good
enough oh
really how does he know that we are with
kaso okay
[Music]
byebye guys don't give me good
explanations
just say say it's
sus don't be so reasonable
no I was trying to stay away from
you
this is
[Music]
perfect
amazing you
love what do we have champagne shower
that sounds fun
uh only if you guys go in line do I
choose the one that's in front of
me
wait wait now you move
this yay time I got
wa oh she was a little bit angry there
at the end she let out her anger issues
very good she was thinking ichib Bon
when she threw that in his
[Music]
face po ich
B maybe you should put on a
shirt no now I callau a
coal him kill
him
I like how we're having a
50/50 lady and Men ratio in our party
this is very well
balanced girl power
strong she goes to us for too long it
really
hurts what was I going to do
nothing I forgot so it's
nothing in the yellow there's two
memories over there
submarine is this what I think it is
hustle Boutique looks like some kind of
secondhand clothing shop yeah we used
this before I've got some pretty
fashionable clothes in stock too reminds
me of when I picked out me's clo what's
with all these kids thinking back on it
now he looked real sharp guess I do have
a good sense of fashion after all there
such a thing as reincarnation maybe I'll
work in the fashion industry in my next
life another one of his children
okay but there some there's one
inside
what oh
here oh a clothing store that I just
reminisced about here's some more ever
since I joined the fashion I've adhere
to the address code every single day M
looking
sharp the usual outfit I used to wear
the gray shirt and the red shirt with
the popped colar I guess you could say
that's more my style now I'm starting to
realize I can't wear whatever I want
anymore oh you
could you look pretty much the same just
with gray hair which makes you look even
cooler
so
me
well there's a hero job over
there gu I'll
help I'll get 50,000 all
right should be
easy most what each like fine wine
yeah I
hate but I like this
one
a great opener I think a little bit too
small damage for my taste but at least
it's big
[Music]
AO
why yeah I don't
[Music]
know I can live without
it
he looks like a
host
[Music]
what if anything I think he looked like
that more
before when he was
[Music]
younger
yeah he's like a k boy band member now I
can't
talk that one's hard to
tell why is it so freaking cold in Tokyo
we keep on catching colds we should go
to Hawaii
man
[Music]
somehow I thought I could kill him
oh oh man he helps her out so much I
think he loves
[Music]
her I ship them
you guys want to see the soup that I
cooked before the
[Music]
stream is really
yummy I added a bit like about 200 more
milliliter of water than
the
like make you add I thought this is like
nothing it was barely a soup I mean I
think it said it was more like a stew
anyway but I thought this needs more
liquid and then to to balance out the
possible flavor that it might possibly
be losing by me adding more water I
added some other spices that weren't
supposed to go in there what's K in
English
criminal what's that in
English really good for Soups and for
bread ask
human yes yes yes oh let me show
you I took a picture just for you
[Music]
guys it was so good I think I made this
before a while ago but I think this time
I made it even
better
oh
[Music]
HD it has um uh carrots potatoes and uh
uh sweet potatoes and the bacon and Lea
and uh
sausages and a lot of fresh cut um
what's it called
again
what's it called ches yeah I love
CH was nice cutting them with my new
knives the ches it's so
good that's way more than a yeah no I
like it this
way nice it's so good but I ate it for
lunch basically before stream now I
don't know if
I if I should eat it for lunch tomorrow
again or for dinner like the second time
today I think I'll just make like some
toast so I have some
variety ham and cheese toast
for
dinner and then tomorrow for lunch I'll
eat the soup
again dip some bread in it oh it's fine
without bread I think I would have for
soup I'd like it to be even more soupy
generally
but it had a a good balance I think it
was good that I added
one so
much
sh
why is this fight dragging out so much I
don't want to use so many
skills looks good right I mean pretty
simple and also I've been
trying we got a lava geld I've been
trying to oh that's why it was so long
cuz it was a rescue and I've been trying
to to cut stuff with my fingers tucked
in today or tried
I'm going to try to get get good at
it my God it's so
[Music]
far yeah no let's let's let's for this
one let's uh take a taxi a cab yo so far
oh I got to go
here yeah I've been walking so much in
the
Stream if you cut a you just send it to
coron
you think she'd be happy about that
really it's not just anybody's UB it's
my yub I think she' be concerned for
me all time at home to some of the
tastes takak in town looks like business
is good o Every Time I Think of octopus
the first thing that comes to mind is on
by pure chance I somehow ended up
helping out the local of spirit SP
really I want to learn that too I W up
having to fight sharks and other huge SE
what sound like something out of a dream
but I swear it did Happ really probably
last time I go spear fishing at least
for a
while did this really happen
guys sounds like he hallucinated
it oh
mother but we're going to go rest anyway
right nobody's going to attack us there
right except for
them
um let's go this way but I I can't climb
over quick quick quick quick quick quick
oh okay safe
safe we're
safe we reading super chats today I
think so I mean I'm kind of tired but so
I I think I'll read them
yeah maybe maybe half more hour or
whenever chapter ends I don't know there
will be an ending of a chapter
soon all right K if you're going to meet
know we need to take a taxi we had to to
C Clan's branch office I can show you
the
way uh oh okay I guess we'll take a
[Music]
taxi you think now would be good
stop
no
really but I only played 5
hours play a little bit
more and where are we
going
this
only the diving fing reminded me there's
a good Slice of Life anime called Grand
about a group of divers who is there any
cute
girls sounds
interesting
damn
spee
[Music]
fore won't they recognize him is that
okay that's what I'm
saying
true
maybe it's more drinking anime
oh I wanted Dave the diver
anime that would actually be so
good
wow
[Music]
you
suck let him
in
right
who whoa
where did you come from the door didn't
[Music]
open
okay oh what
an he crawled
under
fore
foree [\h__\h]
noobs
[Music]
fore
for what do they just always stand
[Music]
there was like I mean we just arrived
like they couldn't have done this just
now coming here usually ends
badly
[Music]
for
foreign
[Music]
foree
the one with the
[Music]
wrong excuse
me
rude
for oh well thans
oh
oh okay they bow to us this is like the
Chima scene at the end where I walk and
everybody's going on their
knees so we going to talk about the dirt
bag in the
shades oh yeah think his name's not aaki
Coy guys like him come with the
territory don't let it get to you easy
for you to say I was ready to go to
war glad you've got my
back so this is this told to clown the
headquarters was I mean it looks
nice they treated it
well first time for me too crazy I'm
actually
here you know this almost reminds me of
the inside of the diet building I went
there on a field trip back in grade
school you're saying a Yakuza
headquarter and the Japanese government
look similar bold comparison hey I
wasn't trying to make a point I'm just
saying what I felt they're both official
feeling well whatever they are just
remember this isn't a field
trip sorry got swept up in the
excitement every now's probably waiting
for us in the meeting room it's
upstairs hey it's your neck of the woods
what but I'll meet lead
way um they didn't warn me when I went
here that it would be like super
dangerous and are you sure you want to
go in so I
hope we're not going to have a million
battles
now you guys also didn't warn
me
m h seems Seems like they take good care
of them these slows are pretty expensive
too how can you tell
we have little displays like this back
at the club still there's no way we
could ever spend this
much didn't know you like flowers kid
your son kind of surprised
honestly oh well I thought i''d make a
good cover if they start
sh so much for being surprised always
thinking one step ahead impressive as
ever
no battles in
too you used to be a chairman for the
too Clan right just for a short while I
quit pretty soon after shortterm in
office huh any reason I mean if we're
talking yaka chairman of the too Clan is
like the de of promotions right oh
actually yeah I've wondered about
that oh sure I guess when I was younger
I did dream of a rual of life but then
well I found something much more
important than
that as to whether or not I made the
right choice that's hard to
say you think you regret it don't
know you know even even if the past is
weighing you down you've always got to
dat just have to tell yourself that the
choices you made along the way were the
right ones even if it's a lie
n besides there's no guarantee what's
happening now is the result of all of
that seriously and hey if you have need
any ear arm here all right I even helped
set up 's first date which was
absolutely [\h__\h]
terrible wouldn't that prove the
opposite thanks when the time comes I'll
keep that in
mind she's right there
number she can say how much of a shitty
job you
did this way what's about what what what
here hi chunky
wony hi hi
baby did you
hear she's so cute what's up with this
book s who's to say maybe they'll try to
look
smart well if that's the case shouldn't
I get rid of
that I'm not done streaming she's
sitting down there looking at me with
expectations I think the cbles are
running
low
agreed okay I guess I'll go into the
fake
door you just want
attention you don't want my heart baby
wait
I huh you know last time we spoke I
thought maybe we could actually trust
him situation called for it just don't
let your guard down
right
um
y
y they're not warning me so so it's
probably
fine
why I went pretty much straight
here
she
flopped
fore
speech
chill also came
over another
fanboy
looking
comfy
she became fluffy
bow behind
monitor
[Music]
for
business part say the
name say
it
but they were directly
involved
motion
mention
for that's where they're sending all
those was
it care trash or
what
they don't have to send many people if
they get all
those to do the job for
them oh
okay so holy why put so much trash
there
for
[Music]
drama
he doesn't
knowe
spee
proof
believe us trust me
real okay
I
guess
so B WS for
junk
for okay we didn't
fight
h
it seemed rather
genuine
but of course they might be just
lying thinky knows yeah there was
something sus about it but they were
pretty genuine but
sus
fore
[Music]
oh
understand
[Music]
fore
foree
[Music]
fore so many things to
do but it's 11:00 p.m.
now said maybe I'll end it at 11:00
p.m. H maybe I
will Victory lab yeah feels like it kind
of many many flashbacks the game is
doing this on purpose they're really
letting him die they're just showing
everything off again
it
hurts now I'm getting really hungry
too how come I ate directly before the
stream it's only been 5 and 1 half
hours is it normal to be hungry so
soon maybe it is
nor
um can I save here I I don't
understand just save
here depends on how much I ate I think a
pretty good portion for my
standards I did not eat
rocks I do not need to consume rocks in
order
to uh yeah work through that meal thank
God
[Music]
close
game I don't have a
gizard that just sounds really weird to
me salt or itty bitty rocks H
true but when rocks are that small I
don't think you can call them rocks
anymore
okay guys we're going to go and read
some super chats I'm lazy though we're
going to stay in the screen I'm hungry
and I don't want to upset chunky wony
she seems to be enjoying lying under and
behind my
monitor her butt is sticking out and
touching the keyboard she's so cute
she's so
fluffy yeah PlayStation menu
bgm ah where did we stop last
time I'm sure
somebody has the
memo yeah let her stay let's not let's
not push her away oh good night thank
you for
watching frog
detective sounds good sorry guys I said
we can like go really long and then I no
I didn't
really it's just a lot of Yap Yap it
makes me tired Maybe
[Music]
oh good had a fun stream thank you no
need to pself thank you no it's 5 hours
No 5 hours 40 she's doing a
stretch she's puring but you can't hear
it
okay
rock very enjoyable stream thank you it
was kind of chill I didn't have too many
uh too many tangents I do want to say
thank you everybody for streaming
Chimera so far Kima is actually how I
say it and don't forget to listen to it
on Spotify Etc as well if you can
Yol enjoyed the pretty good
attent I'm surprised I didn't think of
telling you all those details in my
previous PR tangent I was
really like leaving out some really
important information I'm so sorry
guys I'm so
sorry that was
vital for
the pry
tangent there was some overlap e
really
I've been listening on Spotify thank you
very much share Chima with everyone you
see maybe we could make it hit 300K
today well not today for me but maybe
tomorrow when tomorrow should be
possible it's been growing pretty nicely
thank you YouTube for for once not
effing me over I appreciate it
YouTube and I think it's not just the
algorithm being
nice it's not so much even that I think
it's just genuinely people were curious
about it and people on Twitter and so on
making a big fuss about my
butt
yeah so keep on watching it because now
now is where the algorithm really gets
important the first two days people were
curious and actually wanted to watch it
now everybody has seen it so this is
where it gets important this is where we
need to push the algorithm anybody who
hasn't commented it on the video yet on
the MV feel free to leave a
comment leave a thumbs up as well maybe
add it to a playlist even make yourself
a little
playlist endurance Kar of Kima I don't
think I'll do that because like the
timing is like why would I do it I could
have done it as a thing for the
release but also by judging by how my
schedule is looking so far I think I
don't really have time to do
that
yeah maybe when it reaches 1 million
views oh could do could definitely do
that me
babbe yeah listen to it every once in a
while at least once per day open up the
MV maybe twice maybe once in the morning
maybe once in the
evening what's
this is it intentional for it not to be
purchas purchasable purchas purchas
purchasable download on Amazon I think
this is the first song that is like this
really I don't know is it normal for my
songs to not be able to be purchased the
I could purchase it on Amazon oh I
bought it oh there you go some other
people bought it so maybe it's a you
problem
already added it to the heck playlist oh
you have a heck
playlist what the first one I can't buy
maybe something's wrong with your
account I also bought it on Amazon see H
thank you guys for buying it by the
way only works for us as Amazon what
that's
weird is it like
what
[Music]
what maybe I'll consider buying CA
please
do please do wa the favor you should
it's a really good song okay super let's
read super chat before I fall asleep
check 47 Studio
Rob thank you for the being super chat
for froggy waa I'll take that one
e thank you
than as she would say or so I've
heard
ar ar again mp15 GX thank you for the
red chat this Delights me froggy waa is
my
favorite what about me
what about me it's not listed on ah I
didn't put it into my originals playlist
yet that's okay it's not a big deal I'll
add it
eventually it's the automatically
playing video on my Channel at least
that's pretty
important
oh I love K more that's
exactly what somebody would be saying
who's trying to hide their love for
froggy wa right now
do you think it'll get combined soon no
idea I mean I saw what you were writing
I think it was you was it or was it
someone else maybe it was someone else
um oh yeah yeah we already changed it to
music
category I don't know it's just the the
the whim whim the whims the whim of
YouTube they just do what they want to
do on YouTube I don't know I don't
understand how it works but it doesn't
really seem to be affecting the video
negatively at the moment so I'm not
stressed out about
it uh so yeah thank you np15 fre
G I hope you will come
around and understand that froggy waa is
no
more and you can only support me # # Yol
can you stamps
thank
youan frog and oh na I just
autocorrected your name in my
brain blade ball Pro Dan Lou Moonlight
than for the red super chat I think we
just found out why the pandas are an
endangered species they must all be
fighting for the fortune of that Prince
cousin we all
have m
what is this was there a Panda in this
game I don't remember or is this about
kung kung Fu
Panda I recently I see more and more
Kung Fu Panda related things in the kfb
hashtag which is I think cuz they
brought out a new
movie it's so annoying get out of my
hashtag get out of
here this is kfp
hashtag
stupid movie even before that every once
in the Blue Moon they would write
something in my hashtag just random
people but really really rare and now
now it's quite a bit get out of here
it's
ours
attack you block everything related to
the
movie yeah it's got no place
here yeah I don't know how you can think
of K FP for Kung Fu Ponda it just I just
it just doesn't make sense in my
brain thank you do Moonlight frog and D
the car Channel D you have more for the
pinky I saw for your plan for you
manipulated K and most of kfp to take
your brainwashing
hoodie and supervision plusy but not me
the Phoenix will rise again in the end
of the week my security team will have
defeated you back in your jaw jaw
J J you wrote JW with j a w Wait now
you're confusing me what's the
word jar yeah oh my God I was like wait
what what how do you wait it sounds like
that but it's
not got me really confused here thank
you I like the idea of it being a
brainwashing hoodie and a supervision
plushy I do like the idea maybe that is
what it is you guys got to check the the
plusy for cameras and microphones okay
and the hoodie you got to check for some
like notes or something be careful I'm
just taking the money I'm not like it's
not my not my my fault you know I'm not
I don't have responsibility over any of
that I just I just get the
paycheck h
make sure to check your merch when you
receive
it before you put it on
M the plush is going on the lock down
you're taking no risks good choice best
choice belly wrap belly wrap stayle
can't believe she's still here she
really wants those belly wrap
she's
desperate um frog
G I am a t be than frog UL frog than
Foria K Jones wow we put two two frog
puns in there than space frog pond than
Cruise
than thank you for the red super chat
frogy waa I offer you a warm welcome I
hope that you can get along with K and
not murder
her she's a great bird and she could be
a great friend to you she works so hard
and she means you no harm we at KY have
room in our hearts for you too wow
you're reasoning you try to reason with
for you Wawa and you're being so sweet
but I wonder if you're actually
genuinely trying to be sweet or if
you're trying to manipulate
her which one is it is this just like
just like some genius plan
to get froggy Wawa to soften up and then
you then you catch her and then you yeah
when she lowers her guard you catch her
and put her in the glass
jar surely that's what your plan was I
mean I believe I believe you're on my
side but
yeah in her mind she already had me
murdered in her mind I was dead but I
was just in a coma surprise
speach thank you D or should I say
Ducker Tech that's who you are
right thank you so much for the red
super chat and Cy stamps than thank
you that's all for this one let me go to
speed Bean frog oh this one this Bean
frog a good
one a good
time honestly spin frog death So
based and the MV H MV the thumnail is so
cute
right man I was getting so much cute
froggy waha fan
art too bad I can't use it now cuz it
Doesn't doesn't really work but the ones
with the um with the Poncho with the
cape those I think I'll get some use out
of those cuz I like wearing it yeah that
one is fine cuz that's
me yeah it was so cute I think I used
most of the ones I wanted to use
anyway and the ones I couldn't use I'll
just use for next next froggy Wawa week
which will never happen of course cuz
our security measures have been
increased
check 47 Dan studio Rob Dan for na pinky
[Music]
for thank you py may believe for the
pinky frogy so smart encouraging whole
life fan games so she can get her own
official froggy waa game one day smart
business frog that would be so a awesome
maybe like a Frogger Style game with
froggy Wawa would be so
awesome
a or froggy waa cameo in I don't know
Holo cure or Holo
break I would love to see
it put her Legacy in the
game that would be nice one day one day
froggy has to to become stronger and
more
welln guys did you all buy merch by the
way the froggy wa merch did y'all
purchase
it got to sell the frogy AWA
merch yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes I would mind thank you the minute it
drop thank you they want buyer thank you
full set thank you give me a week no
problem take your time but not too much
time
I forgot I will do now you
forgot you mean you
forgot how can you forget it's in my
intro screen my loading screen every day
sorry while ran into financial problem
don't worry don't worry about it I don't
want to like pressure you guys if you
can't then you
can't you do have one month time
although by now I don't know half a
month oh I should push them to give me
pictures oh but I guess I was weakend
maybe they'll say s me something on
Monday maybe they'll make some progress
cuz they're still working on on the
sample for the hoodie U I think the
plushy
is uh yeah I think the plushy was pretty
much no no did I even see a sample of
the plushy I think I might still be
waiting on
those waiting for my next payment the
next one normally you should have most
people received a payment a few days ago
a week
ago I start a new job
tomorrow f i I hope you I hope you have
a great time there good luck there I
wish you the very
best might not make it in time until
they give you a salary
though I guess some people get paid
every two
weeks
I get my payment this
Wednesday Wednesday let's
[Music]
go
exciting and until April 30 oh thank you
for telling me that I didn't know the
exact
date April 30 it
is okay that's five sneezes in this
stream are we are we hitting moko's
record anytime
[Music]
soon you guys are still saying it in
German even though I don't even say it
you guys are saying it on your own so
sweet thank
you I'm okay by by the way it's just so
sometimes uh I'm not sick or anything I
I don't think when you sneeze I don't
mean it I don't think it means uh that
you're getting sick can just be a little
bit of dust in the air or you're just
feeling a little bit ticklish in your
nose for some
reason you were taught to say gonon
birth in German or you mean just bless
you
fluffy cat yeah fluffy cat hair in the
air someone's talking about me oh yeah I
guess that that was the thing with
sneezing oh someone's talking about
me pepper in the
air it's common in some Rel regions
really very what it's is a thing that
you guys say well that's kind of crazy
what the
hell
what gun tight the way you wrote that it
sounds like some sciencey
thing oh my
God what wait why did I never know that
you guys say this relatively commonly in
America feel like you guys were all like
acting like oh my God what a complicated
difficult word I don't think I can ever
remember this what a crazy word oh
German language
[Music]
crazy yeah I mean I I guess there's a
lot of Germans you who
spread the
beautiful word of
gizon yes Health to all of
you easy to say to spell easy
gunite well if you say it correctly and
it's
gunite how do you guys say it do you
just probably say
gun gun I do you say it properly
huh there's an AG
there yeah it sounds like gun
height don't forget the
H some tie
no no he don't fight
no you say proper you think so I will
need a voice recording of that to check
over your
pronunciation if it's really
correct you may think so but I don't
know about
that we say a t instead of an H see
that's wrong
already it's gun
height
nonous people say that over bless you oh
really well yeah I guess it has
definitely less religious connotation to
it than bless
you oh God bless you anyway uh so yeah
thank you Maple Leaf smart business Rog
y thank you you so much I hope I get
into a h Life game and roggy Wawa at
some
point I would play the [\h__\h] out of that
ghet D ulti frog D del d loan gaming D
Moonlight thanks to the pinky let
somebody say red coins hello there
little green waa I hope you're having
amazing spins and turns and circles and
all the round stuff thank you D for the
red super chat it was a lot of fun we
had really good spins really nice SP
really nice
turns was a good time I really enjoyed
it for just being such a simple game we
had a good time with it
really CH theja thanks for the pinky I
love this frog so damn much born too
late to explore the world too early to
explore the Stars just in time to
experience the Wawa but do you mean
yourself or froggy waa you were B born
too late to explore the world too early
to explore the stars but life is good
yeah thank you
Jesus that is very
poetic but it
does it does speak the
truth surprisingly every little rage
that game yeah I also thought I would be
more like yummy panicky or raging no no
no
no I gave up pretty fast more or less
though at that one point but we already
played it for a good amount of time so I
was like I think we good
frog R frog G Don na coton thanks for
the
pinky after another long day of work uh
setting up for the holiday I finally
made it home to see my favorite comedian
but the amphibian is here
instead
aian sorry Nathan I'm really sorry I
wish I could have been there but I was
in the in the
coma I wish I I wish I could have been
there for you but that little [\h__\h] she
took
over now everything's back to normal
you're safe here
Nathan she will not come back to haunt
us anymore except for Halloween and then
for froggy while one
week thank you naan Egger Santiago
Martin thanks for R chat for I love you
I'm a big fan glad to see you also I'm
glad wa not here she was making me work
huh a lot only for a few coins don't
tell her please I'm on a little vacation
now would you like to take a vacation
into the usual room Santiago Martin I am
I'm gladly sending you there how about
uh so you can really rest and relax and
recharge and refresh cuz I think you
really deserve it how about a full month
eh yeah go treat yourself go take a full
month off in the usual room yeah it's
okay don't need to feel bad about it I
wish you the best there you deserve it
treat
yourself see you in a month hopefully
you'll feel so refreshed you'll be a
different person when you come out
again you'll be perhaps a little
brainwashed perhaps a little
manipulated never doubt the Wawa
again have a nice vacation I heard it's
nice there froggy fellow D valian oh
thank you for the red super chat they
say frog legs taste like chicken no
particular reason for me to say this did
you try it before because we know I'm
sorry but we know valdian is
French
and you making this
statement makes me
wonder have you tried it then I
genuinely want to hear
about your
experience would be
[Music]
interesting French Bros is not beating
the
allegations they eat frog lights in
America too ew but come on how common is
that
can't be so
common it legitimately does
though do you take off the
skin does it not only taste like like
when people say it tastes like chicken
is it like mostly the
texture I would hope you take off the
skin because like ew I can't imagine the
skin looking
[Music]
very
tasty frog porridge ew disgusting at
least make it crispy I don't
know why why we such a mushy thing
together e it's like eating chicken
lollipop I've never had a chicken
lollipop how am I supposed to imagine
this yeah you would probably fry them
right oh oh thanks for the raid welcome
welcome welcome we're like pretty much
at the end of the stream though thank
you
though I keep on auto correcting I'm too
used to your name like reading it out
mob7
frog
G thank you ordering the merch I am a be
pyro and uh
Spartan Dan and one more time frog G for
apparently a sneeze
[Music]
Dan
okay I'm done with
that okay I'll read one
more one more more one more one more
even chunky wonky is still chilling
here can't believe it this is the one
where I broke my
toe un un
un Anor Anor
Anor frog known amazing name amazing
variation thank you with a pinky day
four of disguised as a frog these
chickens are all brainwashed I remain #
woke # yolk for now but frogy wa's
cuteness is getting to me she's almost
as cute as the real WWA she's too
dangerous must resist Kwa please save us
I understand she do be cute but it's all
a
facade facade I don't
know she's just she's deceiving you
she's playing her tricks on you but you
stood strong I'm so proud love you I'm
so proud I know it must have been a
really terrifying scary time for you
it's okay it's okay come here come here
wait here I'm holding you can you see
you're under my
shirt it's okay little
chicken it's okay I give you a hug it's
going to be okay it's already okay
Cruz D frogy fellow 47
you cute Lulu thanks for the red super
chat frogy my beloved Lulu my beloved
wait never mind I won't say that cuz you
said that to froggy waa not to
Me
Lulu
sad
you your real beloved is Tak right not
froggy
wa
right please tell me Lulu I need
reassurance thank you for the Super Chat
temp to talk thanks for the pinky fral I
already pre-ordered the plush you don't
need to remind me again thank you good
job yes order the
merchandise yeah give me that money that
F you how was supposed to get it feels
so good feels so wrong and that makes it
feel so good spank and hi thank you for
the uh red Super Chat no Frog We forever
oh yeah this was uh kind of the last one
besides the VR
stream yeah who knows maybe she'll maybe
I'll let her out if she behaves well but
not anytime soon she is in in Glass
Prison
now but I'm glad you had a good time on
I guess no I'm really glad though I'm
glad you guys enjoyed frog
[Music]
week yeah I do have a good time with
frog week usually I can play some cute
little oneoff games and usually they're
indie games and they deserve love
too I think they're also Charming it's
always fun to be froggy waah cuz I can
show you my little
hands yeah it's nice cuz because the
Expressions they always look a little
bit more different than like here with
me or even my 3D model they
just they're less stiff the expressions
are less stiff on froggy waa yeah even
though it was like really simple basic
rigging love the little hands I miss the
little
[Music]
hands yeah thank you spanking Heim Mah
mod arade frogging for the Frog
satisfy
egg frog K
Jones
FR shiny Toto di thank you for the uh
pinky you sound new to me time to build
my w thanks for the great tips oh thank
you for the pink Super Chat thanks for
the support Studio Rob also thanks for
the pinky k
and there's a lot of flush chats I'm
going to skip them this time and then I
come back with a broken throw oh thanks
for the membership welcome to the
membership guys enjoy your
freebie FAA thank you for the red super
chat I need to buy one more fogy plushy
you want more you should get more yes
yes they're going to be so
cute when you get them feel free to put
them in a
prison you can be creative with
that put them put it behind bars at any
cost don't risk
anything
sneeze
[Music]
no I think we're good it's it's going
back
inside thank you FAA
there FR picture of a
telephone it doesn't want to come
out Tiara
Asel even though I feel like ticklish
moonfrog D thank you General froggy d
space frog dun James Seer dang thank
you wow a fan since debut and this is
your first Super Chat thank you so much
Nathan coton thanks for the pinky I have
hatched a plan I order to rescue my
beloved
heno from the clutches of this F ow and
fyan O you're you're you're becoming a
rival to Trevor G I will purchase the
froggy while merge and use the hoodie to
huh nope it it's it's there and use the
hoodie to infiltrate frog Society
although I do think I look good in
green you're welcome to go won that
mission but once it's over you cannot
wear the hoodie
[Music]
anymore orange all the way orange is our
dress
code
yes and oh yeah donut country was fun
back in the day certainly D thank you
the books
M the show while not bad makes many
changes to where it becomes a different
story after season one and the original
story is amazing
yeah I always want to listen to the
audio books of things but I don't get to
it and then I thought I had a
subscription but turns out it it just
ran out and I I don't know I don't want
to activate it
again so H at some point me listening to
the audiobooks is way
more likely than me reading uh the books
I did
uh ask because I saw uh n narissa was
telling me that she was listening to the
audiobooks for load of the Rings and I'm
like why are you doing that did you
girls like decide after the movies
you're going to do a book club or
something like that cuz I was I you I
mean if you were going to do that I used
to want to do that so maybe I would like
to do that with you and she was like no
no I'm just reading uh or like listening
to it just for fun you know um um she
trashed Game of Thrones after leading
reading all wow okay wow she really
likes it I'm
glad she did it beforehand so she could
sound
smart
amazing um but yeah so she she was like
no no I'm not reading it for that I'm
just reading it cuz I want to and I was
like okay maybe maybe if you girls are
really all into Lo of the ring so much
maybe maybe I could do my book club
thing maybe we can do the The Hobbit and
I was going to ask you
guys
um how fast can you read The
Hobbit how how fast could you read it
probably in one day right but like how
many
hours two or 3
days three days the page is very
short
H cuz I I feel like uh if we read it
like it's if it's that short then I feel
like we can really only make one stream
out of
it so we would discuss the whole book in
one go normally I would say like let's
split it in chapters and all that in
several chapters if it was a longer book
and then get back together and all that
isn't it kind of weird if it's that
short I don't know maybe it's good but
feels like there might be a lot to talk
about if if we do it in one
go no idea how they turn it into a
Trilogy that's right I know the story so
it does seem longer but
[Music]
H and then I also don't really know how
we're going to really like just going to
talk about the whole
story I would tell them to like take
notes of think that they would want to
talk about while they're reading it so
they don't forget about it anything that
came to mind when they were reading
it what do you even do in a book club
I've never been in a book
club you just talk about it right is
there anything else you
do in what way do you talk about it I
guess you you would if if you don't if
you're not finished with the book you
might even like like discuss how it goes
on from there but if we read the whole
book then we have no need to discuss how
it might end and so on yeah predictions
and all
that we could discuss the characters
yeah and yeah yeah I have some coffee
some
tea so you guys think it would work well
if we read the book the whole book
beforehand and the one stream on it
won't that be too much do you think it
will be too much to talk about in one
stream with several
people it may be short as a book but
like maybe it's a lot to talk about
though it's doable in a 2hour
stream I just feels like rushed though
but then splitting it when it's this
short also feels kind of weird
read a and discuss it on stream show
pictures yeah that was the plan we're
not going to read on
stream quietly reading with K I kind of
love that idea too just turning on a
stream everybody's quiet everybody's
just reading their
book but that's that's
crazy I have so much legum in my
mouth ever since I first
sneezed okay I spit it
out okay so both would be okay I guess
splitting it or doing it in one stream
it might just be a little bit much maybe
but I think I might do it in
one one
stream and then we can do a watch long
of the movies after we read the
book well I saw it before but I would I
would think they would want to watch the
movie
afterwards I got to stop them before do
you guys know if they have any plans
those Lord of the Rings watching girls
do they have any plans to watch The
Hobbit too because I got to stop them
before they do that
again o I liked
it it didn't say
anything she was going to read The
Hobbit okay I got to stop her oh my God
girl
[Music]
chill where is where is
here
don't read The Hobbit
yet I want to do a book club thing with
you girls
soon it's a short one
so it' be better if it was more recent
in your memory okay she said she has
good do not I repeat do
not
nice
I've secured her
participation yeah gooda read it
before I guess I'll ask her if she wants
to be part of it anyway maybe she can
refresh Her Mind by reading it
again anyway what was I
uh a yeah I read the nae and cotton
Super Chat thank you for the pinky El ho
oh no I was already here at certainly D
pimble winter D the artist d teras
Kazi no I don't know that actually and
Michael H thank you for two super chats
and random collusion thanks for the
pinky subsidizing The Chew The Chew that
I gave to Nathan or so I think by
accident so much
FL e e e e ew
why is there so much
FL but it's it's really really
liquid
disgusting thank you random collusion so
does that mean I have to give you a chew
as well look maybe half a
chew no no m w ah for
you just
[Music]
a what are these
that's it that's it with frog song
that's it we're done so tomorrow I have
a day off I have some a lot of stuff to
do I
think
um and then I'm
planning I'm
planning a a little oneoff game on
Tuesday a members on
Wednesday uh WEA Holo break on Thursday
Friday probably Dragon Dogma Saturday
Sunday
Yakuza Pretty Simple and
Clean uh schedule I would
say Simple and
Clean tonight it's hard to let it
go
who whoa whoa what's what did AI
write why are you guys all replying to
her I can't find
it hold
me I can't I'm not allowed to sing
that I can't chunky wony is still
here can I bring the mic
closer
say
something she's purring but it's too far
her head is
like she's giving me her whole belly
she's like shaped like a
banana She's So Soft she's so soft
help me guys she's too
soft should I I'm going to pull her out
and make her face the
microphone wait
wait
sorry come
here
come hi
yeah she's a baby you're a
baby
so much love
oh
okay we're going to end the stream now
yeah and then we can go to bed and get
some real
cuddles I'll let her go say
[Music]
goodbye
oh okay goodbye I love you I love you or
do you want to no
okay goodbye junkers thank you for
saying
hello so many hairs on my hands and in
my
mouth I'm going to wash my hands in my
mouth
now okay I stopped moving
anyway
so in German we
[Music]
say bye bye see you on Tuesday stream
Kim sorry I got a bit tired at the end
trying to keep up with the energy but
too
tired bye-bye bye-bye thank you for
watching see you again soon soon soon
soon
kimim have a nice day off thank you you
too full reminder yeah I don't know if
I'll get to it tomorrow I was thinking
about it too though it's somewhere on my
mind feel free to remind me again uh
during the coming week
yeah my
[Music]
bye
y
[Music]