[Music]
for
oh oh hello everyone we're back hello hi
hi back um we are playing another game
for the last uh the last game of the
relay the last collab of the relay today
yay y
yay chat can you guys hear everything
okay does the volume sound
good one twoo check Che SS good okay uh
yeah I saw a lot of people saying oh
we're playing Minecraft maybe we're
playing
jackbox but
actually we're playing a really cool
game yeah
G fun game G for
good where are you
girls I'm uh I'm here can you see me
only can we right now what do I look
like I don't know what I look like
somebody's coming for us and you look
like an old guy we also have yes joining
us so we opened it up to anybody in Ian
and ID to join so we do have some people
that are going to play with us yeah ah
yay who will be join
us I wonder I wonder they might show up
yeah oh I'm a skeleton who no I'm not a
skeleton someone else is a
skeleton okay so this the hello would
you become a skeleton what the heck you
have a gun do you know how to pick up a
gun no there's guns yeah there's guns on
the floor um you you got you got to walk
over them and they'll pick up
automatically
oh
oh whoa I just heard a
gunshot oh I
see
okay oh my God they're so big I know
chat Chad is so excited cuz Gary's Mod
is really fun oh my
God we have some
guests
hug hello hello hey I'm unarmed okay I'm
unarmed hello
hello hi they're here hello I like
seeing the PE and chees PE like so
gigantic you guys taking over the
stream all right so much blood on the
snow we're playing Gary's Mod today and
it might be a new game for some of you
guys so if you have any questions you
know it's okay you can you can open
doors with e pick up guns scroll Mouse
click to switch to your gun
Cat hello hello thank you for joining hi
oh welcome oh another one another
one so cute let's listen to Auntie amama
uh have her explain everything okay
everybody listen to Amma oh yeah so this
game mode people compare it to like
Among Us it's kind of like Among Us with
guns so everybody has a gun and uh
there's some traitors there's one
detective and the detective can check
bodies to see if that person was a tra
or not whoever is dead so mhm mhm pretty
much the goal is just like Among Us you
know the Traders have to win uh whoever
they
are uhhuh and and yeah and then we're
going to switch to a few different game
modes but this is a good one to start
out with so you guys can learn how to
shoot and pick up guns and ammo and
stuff okay cool one thing that I would
like to know is how do I change uh my uh
model my avatar oh right so if you check
the messages I I put in the instructions
there's one that's called bind player
bind a key to player model select you
just have to paste that into the console
all right got it thank you yeah this I'm
just going to stay old guy there's only
one rule uh if you die no chatting so
that you don't give away like you know
who killed you okay that's all okay like
Among Us yeah but I think the round
might end here soon cuz uh we'll just
get everybody in and then we'll play
okay
yeah uh wait and does everybody
understand like when you want to switch
weapons you have to scroll on your mouse
and then click left Mouse button to
actually like fix fixate what you what
you want to use yeah scroll and then
left Mouse button that was loud oh yeah
the gun's real loud mhm yeah this I like
every time this game launches like the
audio is super loud so you should turn
it down if
yeah oh sh are we just shooting people
what no the round's about to end are we
shooting now I'm
dead
bye I'm trying to change my avatar stop
win
hey we're dead together that was for
taking my
bed oh my goodness we're uh
very friendly here on the floor hey
anybody want to meet up where are you
guys oh I your fight going on
here are we playing seriously now or uh
I'm just trying to end the the round I
guess
yeah the chat there is only you started
it
first it's fine it's fine how do you end
the round anyway do we have to destroy
each other Must Die oh my God there's so
many dead bodies
here yeah that's that that was me that
was my
faulty just coming in to destroy
M congratulations it's thank
you I was a Traer done now
ah innocence win okay now the round
starts again mhm now we're serious okay
for real play okay for real for
real and um my dear kohai remember the
Senpai attacks and the respect yeah
right right don't shoot the in the face
okay I'll try not to yeah what is the
Senpai T yeah I don't know what that is
um you guys just tell your
traitor oh that's you guys right got it
oh hello kitty cat I got
AOW how do you get weapons oh so you
just over cross
it I'm trying run weapons uh shift hold
shift I
think doing anything P am hello wait how
do you have a gun let me pick one
up I have a GL where are you oh my God
just a big baby
hello probably wait why do you shooting
people I mean that's what you're
supposed to do
right then you're not really supposed to
be shooting people oh unless they give
you reason you're wounded you're also
kind of uh scary looking see Callie for
for reason we have to use the a normal
looking model none of none of our stuff
even though I put them in I wish we
could use them I know that yeah it's
okay it's okay no one saw anything no
one
saw B
baby you we're together in oh hi man
excuse me we must be right I trust
youo going on okay's a
detective wait why did you kill the
penguin where are they who is
this I think are you safe I think you
just
shot
I'm I hope we shot the right person you
randomly bleeding big baby who's
innocent who is Not Innocent is there
another
traitor wait how do I how do I really
know tra I I think you have to be a
detective don't you a detective
detective yeah I the bodies
baby isud
detective did we killed the wrong people
or or oh let's leave the baby detective
to it if they say innocent does that
mean they're innocent yeah yeah it would
tell you if they're a traitor ah I see
okay sorry Callie oh oh
Callie oh there's some look over there
don't look over there somebody screw
something who did that wait if this is
people and this is and this is f then
who's left am is dead or who is dead
wait who's it was someone who showed up
and threw a bomb who is the penglin I
think they were wearing a white coat or
something penguin is
me okay okay I'm
[Music]
scared we're strong yeah how many um
terrorists are usually in a match
usually it's like uh you know if there's
a lot of people there's going to be like
two or three depending on how many
people are in the yeah I see Hello what
the why are you shooting at me why
did you shoot at
me that's what you get what's going on
think it's
that
wait stop shooting at me dud dude why
what the okay no I don't trust this not
because you're Ball but I just don't
trust
this how do you reload do you reload in
this game you do but you might need to
pick up ammo we can we can talk about it
we can talk about it talk it out there
will be no
talking who who threw that who threw
that grenade we must find
out oh that person it was that model I'm
pretty sure you yeah yeah oh
yes it wases me nice try nice try you
sounded very convincing
good first people was first to kill too
it was yeah yeah we'll play like one
more round of this and we can switch to
prop hunt how about that okay all right
I'm a chicken man now much how to
restart round uh it'll restart on its
own right now
okay
give be this I don't know is it it's
okay the TF2 ones are okay the
T let's find stuff
shorty okay oh you're following me the
cat who's that little penguin yeah cat
team you guys getting enough I don't
know
oh a gun I have a gun what I'm just I'm
just switching through my weapons seeing
what I have oh my God the gun above your
head yeah using the force oh Traders
have been
selected we got to stick together hey
can I only get one gunun one type of gun
hello one of these oh okay oh wait I
have I need to find one
too there's many guns in the snow
there's a there's like a shotgun
here I need to go look around oh
nice is it
good I'm so lost in here hello is that
is that
for hey hey I'm innocent protect me I
will I don't have a we protective Ena
Don't Shoot Me I'm Actually innocent
this in how do I look at people I'm
literally I'm literally innocent this
time oh like if they're dead
I swear see I haven't s a single shot of
you are
you I G you don't I think someone else
did wor you innocent nobody's dead yet
there is somebody over there aha no
one's dead yet very quiet killer hasn't
begun their job just yet there's guns
snaky oh you know I'll be your bodyguard
I'll protect you okay okay this Baby's
looking suspicious
she has who gave a
baby come on that doesn't seem
right so
dead all right detective penguin it's so
cute I can't find someone running over
there are you guys in the we're outside
in the snow right now now I see you hi
hello hello no dead bodies yet wow okay
no one's dead who's not here G is not
there cuz I can't I can't find any I ran
into the W outside
outside's a chicken now oh my God SC are
you outing yourself as as a
kfp oh who's that wus badly wounded what
happened what happened sh me hiara did
that it was a misunderstanding filled me
with before I even said hone she scared
me I just press everything scares me but
that's another story right no one is
being sus yet yeah some people are being
sus
watch watch I we just going to do like a
with the hovering gun over their head
I'm
detective of course with the baby with a
gun it's a very mobile baby yeah very
fast very SL
sorry I shot by accident all right who's
who there's not much
time oh the time is running out
oh is bad for the killer you wouldn't
you wouldn't you're nice you're nice you
would even know killer I wouldn't shoot
you how many how many killers can there
be I think there's two to three traitors
so probably two there's two Among Us
Among
Us Chicken Man
Traders yeah you
like why is going to lose cuz we're
sticking together that me shooting by
the way if you don't know if you're a
traitor it's a it says in the bottom
left corner if you're the
traitor what happen action is there a
body shot
uson W over here finish the job we're
coming to test there's a
grenade the
job sheor threw grenade he was dead you
killed a baby on site kill on
site no baby dead all right time to
check the body I got the
bodyo body oh no he's got an accomp
there's the body of bo
boo not the the
verdict what what does it say um I I
think I'm not sure innocent she's
innocent was innocent oh check up here
all right all right all right I don't
trust you an identified body she was in
she only threw a grenade she threw a
grenade was a firefight Kara was a
traitor so there's one more left to find
out what
happened wait ky
ky out she inoc she was innocent okay
che check check call dead body this why
you don't start shooting she's innoc
what that means it's one Traer
wait who's left
wait when you shoot you know you can
shoot me if you want I'll stand right
here
wa oh
nice all right we're going to if you
guys can type this in the chat
exclamation point RTV you can type by uh
typing uh press y
okay but one question was I as a traitor
I was looking for a sign was I able to
see who else is a
traitor it was us yeah but was I was I
supposed to be see sign of oh no it's
it's like if someone shoots at you that
means that they might be a traitor cuz
they're trying to kill you and like get
you to be you know okay but there was no
way for me to really like know by a sign
that I had a partner in there okay okay
oh you didn't thr the grenade did you no
no I didn't have one that was
us I you good all right so the next game
mode we're playing uh this is not the
right one hold on sorry the server might
reset really quick sorry about that no
problem just give me a
[Music]
second it's wild thank you guys us
VI second I got
yeah I don't think we're doing very good
job
again why are y'all so aggressive oh my
God all right the server is going to
restart so you guys just have to join it
again one second sorry sorry okay okay
easy green
Violet okay it's starting up now
so you guys can join with that uh you
know really easily by just going to your
favorites if you added it mhm okay
mhm yeah it should work now okay it's
working it's working entering are we
doing Prop Hunt now yeah we're going to
play Prop Hunt let
go okay fck I hear bubbles what's these
what's with these bubbles oh I'm not
sure why it does that you guys uh we can
make it even so if you see a spot open
on props or Hunters it's okay if props
has more than
Hunters oh I didn't shoot anything oh oh
Sam you might press uh F1 you can change
team
oh
okay they want it even
okay now it might not be third person
mode yeah so if you want to become a
prop so the whole point of this game
mode is to hide and plain sight uh and
make people believe that you are a
prop I can't move though I'm stuck you
might are you stuck yeah I've always
wanted to it's just black right now
right are you are you a prop Kiara yes
all right one
second uh try try holding control and
jumping and moving around like that
jumping oh oh
I yeah I feel like I'm I'm I'm I'm
spectating
now oh try joining joining uh F1 um I'll
join different I joined a team but I'm
still spectating it might be because
we're in a round right
now okay okay I can end uh I'll just
I'll I'll be in plain side if you guys
can find me okay nice find her find
her where
is as they like to
say
Oh I thought I heard a
door it's a bit
[Music]
spooky what killer
spot that was not so when you find a
prop do you shoot him with a gun yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah you can there's a
bunch of different guns and if you use
the SMG and right click you have a
grenade you only have one though so you
have to be
careful colder colder
colder
warmer no warmer warmer
warmer something that looks
suspicious I should have started
running yeah yeah now we switch
sides have SW okay oh okay are we in the
prep right now or yeah so screen is
blank that means you're the Seeker
pretty much so you're closing your eyes
okay how do we become the prop again e e
yeah there's there's some props you
can't turn into like bigger items but
usually smaller ones you can oh thank
you okay all right
I died in the oh
no you know I'll let you guys go for now
okay oh no wait how do I get out of this
room oh press e on the door there might
be hidden doors like in
bookcases hello hello open door it's not
letting
me free be free be free okay just
destroy all the furniture destroy
everything suspicious if you smack stuff
uh you can smack stuff but if you if you
hit Furniture you'll notice your HP goes
lower because you can't just hit
everything ah okay okay oh I see there's
a lot of rooms in this
Mansion guess we can't just go go wild
huh H too many chairs
here sorry I just realized myit stream
is really low I'm just going to restart
it really quick keep playing sorry chat
one second I forgot I change something
not yeah if you fall down and take a lot
of fall damage I guess also I think oh
yeah if you fall from to wait I just saw
someone sorry I saw what you doing over
here chair and then I di did you kill it
was bleeding what the I don't know kill
someone though I don't know why your
name shows up I don't know if it's
supposed to show up like this huh hey
girl are you a penguin
too run while you can run while you can
run oh is this a dead
where people running confuser hey guys
there's a chair over here you guys want
to see this really cool chair I found
chair run run where is it where' she go
wait actually where' she go barricade
the door why you let her get away
I found a secret basement she
she's you guys see her how you how about
you like with free people not able to
get
sh oh she nice you dead yeah I think she
dead there's one there wait a
second guys oh there's NS there no one
here W you're so
good
I'm I'm
[Applause]
trying for you you didn't even change so
much you're too
py all right wasn't
working I'll switch te really it doesn't
work on every object only like some like
chairs and and maybe like bags are you
we
survived are you Chang yeah I was
pressing I don't know if you can change
right now but you guys are fine how as
is I think this is good there's a lot of
props mhm yeah wait how do you
change oh how do you change e press e uh
with the with the bigger items you can't
so you should go there's a hallway
behind you good you can go in there
there's a green you see that green thing
it won't let I am coming to for you go
in the H go in the hall just keep going
if I can get out of this room I'm so bad
at opening can somebody open this
door
guys hey
guys you me
never open the door you remember in a
way out oh yeah climb up the walls it's
just
like be fine yeah it's they don't
they're not even close I
mean find is here
[Music]
worries where is
Ladi where is I think they'll eventually
do you I feel like everyone's
[Music]
together what no no
uhuh if you shoot at the wrong thing it
also makes you lose Health just in case
somebody didn't
know where are you
I'm
I'm nothing doesn't help nothing looks
suspicious are you guys
stuck yeah there's a painting in here
that looks like
yo where
you room oh there's you guys there's a
ladder oh you can
[Music]
climb nowhere nowh that was not at home
nope I have to get up there again a here
stairs they're asserting dominance over
you
guys oh can anybody can everyone hear
the noise if I make noise like that I
think so yeah oh okay I won't make noise
if I give the the hunters uh a little
bit of a hint there's some secret
passages you could uh check out
maybe
you I found all of you I found three
bodies you'll never catch me alive
you'll never catch me alive
[Music]
how do I safely go down
that what did you see
anyone'll
[Music]
never guys are stuck again hey how many
shots can you
take how many head shot can you possibly
the run the clock
run is that a
ladder the ladder Oh Oh The Blood
splatters oh my God she went up no and
she went down okay all right run at the
clock it sayy did that but don't believe
it most of that was me yeah right
sure it's so get out of here
[Music]
okay no suspicious props change into
props like minute why do you st so
obviously was tanking oh my God the
perfect you were I don't know I wasn't
turning into a prop so I don't know what
going on this is
impressive very impressive don't even
breathe where are
they hiding in plain
sight this is oh you can press e yeah
nice what the
m we don't have much time left
no I don't think will ever get only is
it only you and me really good did you
find something no I thought the bananas
were weird but oh yeah they are they
arein are still alive is Callie
still no I I take the
damage she's right
there the
open
drops win nice oh my God where were they
definitely thanks to our laundry shoot
uh
strategy switch okay we got to hide well
I was blending in with the floor and the
walls and the tables you guys have 10
seconds until they're
released release the
tackle 5 Seconds yeah oh uh 5 seconds
until the h are released three two oh
God oh God let's
goair the
chair go for the chair or the
suitcase I'm so scared I'm so
scared I'm so scared there's a suitcase
oh that's
you it won't make me into a problem
me spaming e if you can oh turn turn
left you you can are you stuck left
no it just won't put me into a prop even
if I press e you got you got to try on
the suit you see the suitcase there it
it should work yeah like a chair or a
suitcase like smaller items yeah yeah
yeah you can choose what items okay now
just set up set up thank you nice nice
where are you by the way if you do pick
smaller props you have less you have
less HP oh oh that's why we were so
tanky yeah yeah so bigger the more oh
cuz you stayed human
oh
interesting where are
[Music]
you three minutes we have to survive fre
minutes who who here is a prop except
me
who oh boy girl too good at this G
didn't even need a gun she just used the
Crowbar red health bar oh okay okay yeah
sometimes with like some of the props
you can see uh like some
HP
oo oh
oh who else is a prop
now okay and
me bananas look
Sasa what ban I don't like cars either
call
[Music]
bananas Banas
look okay maybe not maybe not not the
bananas maybe
not are you seeing names
still sorry I I oh sorry I didn't me
sorry oh
sorry oh if you are the prop move your
Mouse that's when they see somebody you
guys have the button to lock your prop
position and look around I I forgot what
butt there's a there's a button for it
yeah like e or e
oh well I'm dead my head exploded oh
I'll I'll just stay calm as as calm as I
can maybe
shi shi maybe that will
work right hard to
I don't want to risk it right now a
confirmation so click fig it
out I don't
know does it give me a sign when I'm
lost run there's a bottle there's a
botle on the loose it's always locked oh
oh oh where'd she
go where'd you go find them rattle them
well I'll just stay calm there used to
be a bottle here
so
small Run Fly Away where sh don't give
up we have 1 minute
left car you got to hold out hold out
yeah I'm holding out very well you can't
see oh my
eyes no one
sus no one suspect the WWA he's gaming
30 seconds left you good where is the
W where
is
f i don't think you even
noticed does that mean they're
here who's still alive from the props
besides me uhi running around with the
juice I believe Yos oh we're done we're
so
done pretty quick Kelly Kelly you were
in the room where I was hiding and you
shot a chair and I was actually hiding
in the dark as a suitcase we'll we'll
play one more round and then um I think
we'll switch to murder which is kind of
similar to the previous game mode but a
little different okay but I'm you know
that in in 10 minutes you know look at
the time oh uh actually it's at the 20
Mark of the next hour okay yeah yeah
okay perfect
perfect murder oh wait I'm am I propag
again oh looks like hun I'm a Hunter
again this must be propaganda because
I'm
propaganda I think I'm hi hiding in
a is there something to turn into
here oh I saw something you saw nothing
I saw something sorry okay okay I saw a
health
bar someone
hiding someone's hiding some
help hello
hello where are
you hell hell my view is confusing me I
don't know the the looks so weird I
don't know which prop I am there's
something around I saw a health bar you
guys are props again I guess cuz you if
you win you stay
props that's fine I like being a prop
what do you do wait car press press e no
e yeah never mind don't worry don't
worry oh is that the Locking position no
no no you were just hold no what what
was I what was
I no
no you can still make
no no no
no back here why are you
me sorry I might have given away your
position you were holding an item up hey
I thought I was the prop was I still a
human no you were you were
box also floating but that's so weird
I'm so
confused oh
well nice last time I carried now you
got to carry your
[Music]
Senai
okay I think F must be in a really good
place are they are
they shoting
shooting she can do it feel like Shing
will choose like a
small
human
again you guys are super
taky yeah it's a it might be a strat
honestly yeah
yeah I here V let
me it's a
baby it's a
baby survive
survive
survive you are the Baby K the
baby nice
okay I'm going to restart
the it's okay that was good that was
good that was
VI all right we're going to play a new
game mode again the the server is
probably going to change really quick
sorry all good
all right you guys should be able to
join like 30 seconds it's restarting
okay
okay I like this why have we waited so
long to play Gary's mom it's a little
difficult to set up but it is fun
classic
yeah thank you Amit for setting it
on fun with us thank you always in
anniversary by the
wayy oh I heard happy
birthday thank you happy birthday to you
too happy birthday in your shoe happy
birthday
birthday happy it's our birthday okay in
some way we were born 3 years of
birthday yeah 3 years
old Jesus what the fck that was a loud
scream there's a scream so what's the
purpose of this a murder where that
murder has happened oh oh yeah kobo's
going to join us also so coobo will be
here soon oh I wonder if we have to
actually I wonder we have to move to the
other server I guess she could talk to
us in
game oh yeah wait there's I think I
joined too late cuz I'm just
spectating me too I'm also just
spectating okay we might have to wait
but just press F1 to make sure you did
join the team but then when the round
restarts you'll probably all
join hello F1 okay nothing happens when
I press F1 what's that it's Shing what's
this oh if you this the green items you
get a gun if you pick up enough oh so
there's in this game mode there's one
person who spawns with a gun and there's
one person who spawns with a knife and
the one person who spawns with a knife
has to try to kill everyone else
that's cool gun person a lot of pressure
what does the gun person do yeah try to
kill the one with the knife or I guess
you can kill whoever you
want the power and if you are a murderer
you just have to scroll and click to to
get your weapon out just in case
mhm okay knife person wants to kill gun
person but knife person can also pick up
gun should I no we okay should we hide
our weapon that's not very fair
weapon
weap we just asking for the
first a knife can also be a
weapon I have my hand yeah I had are a
weapon right yeah yeah maybe some guns
or something huh not
enough yeah it's can you
see
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
R you did that thing where when you you
you point your finger at someone's shirt
and then they look down and then you
like you
know you did that with a knife done this
is so how do I know what what what I
have how do I know what I have uh uh it
it'll tell you if you're the murderer or
not like in the bottom
corner hello so only people get like um
self-defense items everyone else is
just
out murder's happening oh I forgot what
the green thing does I can't see
anything oh my god oh
somebody the light I turned it back on
oh cool where's the light Swit wait why
you turning it off turn it off is that
what that
is sa what wait what is this what
I that's my little my little baby so
where protect hey don't kill me I'm not
bad
guy too late I already pulled the Trier
what
happened I will remember
this you're welcome oh so if you shoot
an innocent person you can't use the gun
for a while what why is it down oh oh
you got a punishment for a little bit oh
I a gun
anyway happy of you I'm not sugar happy
you got the gun a dead baby I have
nothing I'll try this oh it doesn't
work oh your name is NI in this game
there's somebody else what are you doing
with that axe hey what you Romeo I'm
just going to
ask
bottles I'm just going to C bio's body
this is what you turn me
into oh my God who killed the bystander
what it's
okay dead the baby is dead you can leave
you're cool right I can't leave me the
doored save yourself it's okay I'll just
I'll just be behind this door then I
actually what's going
onire Fury
I'm just a penguin penguin the penguin
is I'm just an innocent penguin don't
trust the pengin doesn't sound right it
sound
quiet who has a gun by the I'm going to
collect a
gun only trust the birds who are in
horal to not this penguin not this
one not so bad I'm just a
penguin trying to
in this in this world who is
Papa Papa Papa Papa we all have code
names huh yeah we all have code names
oh M what do you say about that body H
oh that's you K yeah that's me oh my God
is M
sen there's Romeo does anyone have a gun
yet colleting stuff Romeo's dead I don't
know I didn't kill
them I have nothing I have no weapons I
don't know I have no oh
I just I just I just saw am what
everyone's
dead it's always did you witness that
you know you're still alive just now you
witnessed it so you must be downstairs
right you didn't know about the light
you yeah I turned him off on purpose
what did she knows everything about this
game yeah it's a little
unfair I forgot what do the green things
do again so if you collect I think five
of them you also get a gun
oh yeah so as the game goes on if you if
you get more and more uh you'll get a
gun yeah where's Ena
hiding no little
paina don't give
up you can sneak up on her this end when
you kill me we have to kill each
other I don't have a That's Not Fair
start collecting better start
collecting I don't have a
weapon meet me in the lobby we can talk
about this
friendship you can defeat me with the
power of friendship yeah
right got to take revenge for all her
Uno wins yeah
she che where did you
go maybe you must be upstairs
[Music]
then wait was that you with the kill and
blow oh my God that was
scary nice job Ena you did it yeah
amazing
nice that was
clutch great that was very
clutch be yeah I'm I'm scared of you
what oh yeah I will remember this wait
till I get a weapon no I remember that
okay we just got to we just just got to
get something for self-defense why why
do I not even even have a knife I'm
[Music]
confused green things I hate you D too
bad what just happened dang no someone
died
already died I came out of the wall and
someone died I'm I found I found a gun
someone's dead
already that there's somebody who's very
scary who has the gun Whoever has the
gun is innocent we got to stick with the
gun I have a gun I have a gun okay okay
where are you okay I have a gun
now a gun I had a gun oh oh you picked
up the gun oh I didn't know how to pick
it up Ena protect us protect us Ena
in has anyone seen someone come out of
this room uh wait why did did someone
there the murderer the dead body is in
that room dead oh no are they oh no
there green things in the attic I wonder
yeah there should be hello I see I don't
see any green things maybe it's just not
meant to be I found two green
things just taken all of
them oh I found my third green thing I
found a baby it was green a green baby
oh I think you can pick it up then maybe
okay yeah I picked it up you like three
of them you should see like a number on
the bottom left oh so it's different for
everyone
okay like it shows how many green things
you picked oh there's a there's a green
thing and I have four now um I think the
murderer lost their knife
murderer murderer lost their knife uh
you can throw the knife just in case the
murderer wants to know with right click
uh the murderer did not lose their oh
okay okay I'm scared there's a baby
following me God there's a
baby I was so close to F A baby is it
the
baby
baby baby with oh man baby oh so close
so there's always only one murderer yeah
okay we can we can also play pro on the
other map we were on oh o could be fun
yeah is
it is it a time yet question mark uh I
think we still have 16 minutes until we
have to do an announcement and then yeah
oh okay okay
hello
hello hello baby hello you want
something from me baby I just have hands
this time me too sure me
too you what are you hiding in your
diapers diapers
pinky I don't think you want to look in
there what is someone
die
is that the D I thought that was just
the sound of collecting things
oh who did
that over I just want to turn off the
light the do not do
not do not oh by the way there's a
flashlight guys if you just in case
you're uh caught in the dark you can
press F
A the
F yeah
F penguin so small he's getting in the
way Callie actually a little sus I'm
looking for green items uhhuh um green
you're going to feel bad if you let me
down and I'm not the murderer y are you
chasing me no you were in the way cuz
you're so big I am not big I am cute
that's true that's true you're you're
not big you're cat
oh hey I have this oh you can go
underground what are you doing why do
you have a flashlight you turn off the
light turn off the light you have a
flash
it KN the penguin is knif I'm stuck does
anyone have a
gun have a gun dead she's
dead it's a penguin
underground one of the Penguins is sauce
wait wait it's hard finding stuff yeah
okay two things everybody's looking for
green stuff so it always gets picked up
get out of my I'm going to the bathroom
Okay I'm going to watch someone get
something wait who's the other penguin
hey there's the pink penguin is safe but
the the other penguin is not safe from
Penguins yeah is this a pig penguin is
this a pig penguin a safe penguin wait
wait wait wait that's a dangerous pengin
I back
here no has a there's a penguin
your penguin come back here is this safe
to go now run just
[Applause]
broke getting
blasted who just Di
let's cuddle you guys are you your are
we cuddling together I like how I see
when your hands it's not penguin penguin
oh yeah the penguin is really I was
wondering why my body suddenly moved
even though I was dead let's watch a
movie together what do you want to watch
Titanic oh I've never watched Titanic
what what that's a
crime inal the one where go on a fishing
trip oh yeah it's just a nice it's a
nice plus movie yeah mhm very family
friendly that's the perfect no blood
Feelgood movie you will love it you will
love it no you will really genuinely
love it is it scary I'm a suspicious
now it's a horror movie about fishing
you know is that you with the
knife no definitely
not I can't I can't go in here I have
never met someone before who didn't
watch Titanic before this is like crazy
you can have your first like reaction to
Titanic in a movie watch along in your
stream maybe we haven't seen a lot of
classic stuff so I don't really know
anything about movies too
much only anime mean you get to watch
them even Marvel movies it's like I know
their name we haven't seen Lord Of The
Wings
no we started I out of my way to go to
lot of rings musical in London you have
to watch the movie we're not allowed to
not allow not we have to read the books
m is that a lot of books though I will
give you permission to watch
Hobbit
hob just just just believe me just watch
watch the movies cuz like when are you
going to read the book whoever is
pink ah it will be so worth shito what
about we do like watch along or
something for it you could yeah and then
you can play that um that spin-off game
I forgot what his name is but no don't
play the Golem game don't play the Golem
game Golem game don't play the Golem
game
G I don't want to play the G game did
you try it that good it's not yes it's
not worth brain Str who's alive is a
timer run out I think there is a time
there might be a timer but I think the
murderer might win automatically so you
have to like try to get a Gun there's
one in the lobby it's not
safe oh there's yeah other games maybe
Shadows of mortar would be good sorry I
should I shouldn't give you information
since I'm dead yeah I was thinking that
I'm bad hey man it's my first time
playing I get yeah yeah still learning
I'm
spectating wait so the knife person has
the knife person is the innocent one
right uh
no yes the is the murderer oh okay
then I am spectating the
murderer oh how do you do that I'm stuck
on my body oh you just m one left click
left click or space where are
you I don't know innocent
murderer ah
very she would be so easy to find like
she's running around happy oh no with
her
knife just chilling yeah it can you can
shoot me anytime somebody needs to stop
her like how to stop her when you have
no gun oh you got to get
one missed it's so hard to get a gun
so the murderer can also pick up items
right so are they picking up each like
the items away from the
others what what what
what dam nice
play that's such a long time who was
that who was that I had the gun it was
just spinning the do you guys want to
play one more round do you want to move
on to next game mode cuz there's one
it's called Death Run you have to run
through obstacles
o if you guys can type exclamation put
RTV okay mhm R
TV thank you wait don't don't press
anything yet uh yeah okay one it is
number one yeah if you guys want to for
that R
TV I new Tye what oh uh why why why
why
why why why death run
extended uh death run Stone
extended which one is it which button do
I
press I'll leave it up to you guys what
are we doing now ah so this is death run
um so there's a few people that are in
control of pressing buttons on the other
side of the wall and they get to watch
as people go through like a big obstacle
course and they get to trigger
traps oh I used to watch this in the
video okay I since here oh my God press
this button when they try to cross and
then you you have to try to kill them
yeah so you just press e on this button
over
here I
see you guys have to learn the hard way
wait who's
zooming let's go go climb
climb penguins have smaller hit boxes
the first and easiest trap got me oh my
god do feel like to press on it I'm not
close enough okay let me in I'm going
I'm
goa's ging today press e
press it is the
ening
her
fast hey got
that's pretty tough
oh where's G what G Going oh she has a
trail why do you have a trail where'd
you get that I don't know I don't know
what to
is oh kobo's
here is it okay if we switch the other
server yeah yeah switch the other one go
over there
okay
oh
KO
hi hello wait you guys want oh okay
nice oh they still not everybody's still
in the oh they're not in this I forgot
they haven't been
added oh then we should do the the the
other one the Japanese one oh okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
Bo Boco she's waking us up yeah wait
time for me it's 4 a.m. let's go let's
go how do I get over this without
falling down cute somebody go
first
yeah you got you know how this game
works guys let's go in Paris I'll bait
them come and get me they control traps
Co there some of them some of the girls
control traps behind the scenes oh it's
like you got to be careful okay when you
run is it safe did they already trigger
them my leg oh my head I sacrificed my
body we died oh we died
yeah you were hit by by a
trap rat
ohes I'm the rat oh there's like random
things that say they kill you uh myy was
a big buff
rat yeah oh that's they got to carry
us wait I'm okay I'm safe I'm alive I'm
alive I made
it what is this is this gas bad I don't
know you try
it okay it's fine we're good
oh alive good luck alive oh
she what part is the Trap oh okay I'm
alive got a
platform there you
go natural causes of natural causes this
is the way I want to die so that's
okay
best yeah so
aggressive what is that what is that is
that that's what gave me the
tra I wonder what it what does it
actually do okay you got this one I'll
go to the next
one not
again yeah because we we didn't get for
the obstacle course none of us did we
try again it's really different
yeah we can do it I
believe let's go oh kidding kill her
now what's this
this oh oh no
get
what the Patriot hear them I'm following
you people to go
okay oh she survived that wow what watch
out you supposed to press
Callie are you dead no I'm alive oh okay
you're not pressing buttons yep I got it
oh okay so means you're like one of the
death pup cuz you're some but yeah yeah
like that
that suck into the void inappropriate
yelling I feel so bad for the
baby this this trap where The Dumping
happens is difficult is
difficult all right wait uh really quick
uh uh myth we have to do a quick
announcement super fast you guys can
keep playing and then we're going to
what would you guys rather do for a one
more game mode prop hunt or TT or
murder Prop Hunt was really fun yeah
okay when when we come back if you guys
can wait a little bit we'll play prop
hunt on uh that office map we on
okay okay okay we'll be right back if
you guys you guys can keep playing time
okay thank you if you guys want to go to
the back to the original voice chat and
then we can do our
announcement just go one down oh oh yeah
whatever down whatever works
[Music]
yeah hello hello
wow where's Callie wow announcement
announc Kell there she is there she is
she's sleepy head there she is okay I
actually have no idea like what order
we're supposed to be doing this it
doesn't matter it doesn't matter any
anyone you I have no idea does anyone
have like a thing to
read ladies and
gentlemen three years of myth yes hey
guys thanks for hanging out with us for
three
years thank you here we are uh I'm Mory
Kip no need for introductions you know
are yeah we have some special stuff that
we are going to be putting on up the
Holo Pro and I Think Geek Jack also
stores for you guys to
[Music]
buy we had solo merch but this is this
is something else extra I forgot nice
little something 3 years um and now you
get some cool stuff from us shall we
begin with flush some image M the Holo
live English starter
merch
yeah starter merch from what I know
these starter merch is going to be
available all the time right oh it will
be yeah I think the St one that's
available all the time you know that's
nice so it comes
badges mm a random one
okay ke this is not random just good but
um hold on you could also get
tapestry a card
case really
nice okay so you can get this of all of
us at any time this not one month
limited uh ordering time or anything
like that and then gacha buttons Guys
these are random oh is it gacha the
buttons are yeah oh the buttons are Goa
okay cool I like the key get a bunch of
them yeah so these are going to be on
sale I think starting today right 14th
yeah it should be today
okay if you want to support us with that
that is one option thank you and then
specifically for the anniversary we also
have special merch uh for this year
so
Tada Yahoo yay
yay rerun of the plushies and Keyes yeah
plus the same ones right the same ones
if you missed out on them that the time
these keychains are the key chains y
really are so so nice of them I wonder
if it's in the middle are they sefr or
they think it's right yeah I think it's
like like see through empty cuz it says
resine I think resine is usually see oh
it might be goodz with the Trident looks
super cool too yeah yeah
good your Trident can bend like that is
that
normal wow and then of course plushies
rerun Plushies are back yeah the
plushies been waiting for so
long get cute cuz I have everybody
especially for the new fans go get him
go get them so soft and so thick and
chunky so nice soft so if you didn't get
a chance to grab yours you have time
again they're running
again it'll be on the page yeah it'll be
on the page all right do we have
something else oh and then uh also on my
if you guys want to you know pick up
something extra you can get a Bubbe
chain added to your order
chain
cute merch right oh yeah this is the
solo merch pretty much my God so cute oh
my God thank thank you all right so we
can get back to playing the games I hope
you guys continue to support us thank
you for supporting us for 3
years years you 3 years there's one more
thing that we will not really say oh
should we do that or I say it's coming
should I post one of the images or no
yeah yeah I'll pick one one second get
excited for this last thing there has
been some delay but it's coming it's
going to be cool are we going to
announce the song too like I mean sorry
the
I well we just did so the title is on
the graphic then I guess that's fine it
is it is we have yeah a song coming
reun reunion myths I guess technically
fourth original song by Hol myth yay
fourth original song by us I think this
one is uh quite different from what we
did until now I think this one is
more yeah the look
[Music]
for we're working on it right now a lot
a lot of stuff yet coming out this merch
and song and stuff so thank you thank
you thank you thank you they look so
nice in those outfits excited for it I
love the idle outf so good yeah all
right so if you guys are cool with
playing Another Round we'll do uh
another round of Prop Hunt if you guys
are up for it yeah all right let's move
back into the server I do have to
restart the server really quick but I'll
tell them really quick before I do it
okay let's go see everybody okay let
go
[Music]
hello we're back thank you wait thank
you guys for waiting sorry we're going
to I'm going to restart the server
really quick so we get to the the new
map that's okay got it okay all right
one second oh by the way
Advent and K I hope you're aware that
you you you read the the small font in
the contract that by joining this collab
you have to buy our merchandise right I
was like what hold on what I was
like I was scared for a second don't
worry I'm not talking about that kind of
contract oh damn we die give me a
fright so byy the mer am die
thank you forever all right the server's
going to restart really quick you guys
are going to have to rejoin uh it's
going off I'll let you do the
SL all right orange
clown thanks again for S up the server
and
event problem it's fine it's fun thank
you guys for joining us short
notice can I already go into server uh
it should be up now I
think okay
on my way yeah it's up you guys can
rejoin okay it's the sandai Tex exactly
exactly pun time this is so
fun can we make it even again choose
choose
team H it makes me choose again why yeah
everyone loses how do
youit why am I spectating now sorry oh
the the round will probably restart uh
if
somebody wait I there's a way to like
kill like kill yourself I guess in game
if you type kill in the
console oh how do you exclamation mark
and kill
yeah that might work we starting it uh
the server's up now you should be able
to join but uh if you guys are in round
then if you die the round will restart
with
everybody oh uh how do I we just die
destroy myself uh in the console you
could type kill and press enter and then
you'll
die oh
okay I don't think we're dying
yeah there's so much
blood okay there there are some props
you guys can try to find the props a
certain uh Kia pumori hiding right now
sorry I'm trying to get
out I'm trying
to just reconnect all right there we
go
Arrow ising oh oh did you install
Counterstrike
spectating
sorry you install counter Source should
work what is that again oh another game
on Steam yeah it uses the same textures
cuz they're made by like the same
company uh
sorry
uh but that think time to do that now
it's just really
small it is it's really cheap like yeah
like two bucks three bucks but yeah oh
yeah cuz steam we have the same
anniversary as Steam so right now all
the stuff is on sale but um
iary steam we love you steam if you guys
don't mind waiting I could change the
map if that's okay that way coobo
can okay all right you guys can play for
now but hold on I'll just change so coob
don't buy C Strike Source okay don't
don't don't we're changing we'll change
it so you can take part without buying
Counter Strike Source now to buy no no
no wait keep though wait wait don't
don't buy don't buy it has 90%
[Music]
discount that is a good argument but it
takes some time you can buy it for later
for another time okay but we're still
changing the map yeah
are you guys okay I think the only other
map is uh clue which is the one we were
just playing on is that okay
yeah okay Kobo is going to use all her
pocket money that she got from me for
you guys TV in the chat yes thank you
okay uh we're going for clue Prop Hunt
so you can vote for PR four mhm here we
go okay go well hopefully you should be
able to join this one I'm pretty sure
cuz I think you this one also before
M H has joined the game m is missing too
no no no we're still changing it takes a
minute to change oh oh okay okay okay
it'll
change don't be so loud Mama Mia
Mama it's 430 in the morning can you
stop shooting
guns no perfect time to shoot guns is
400 a.m. all right well if you join now
it'll be the the other
map okay I'm joining how am I still
awake all right so we have a a round
going with some
people but uh begin it's
[Music]
okay
uh what oh
boy my camera is a little higher up
please let
me it's perfect yeah you see that I see
this how do you see that be a I'm
spectating why are you
spectating I don't
know it might be because of the
round will not see me are
you I don't even
know where are you guys
oh oh Kobo you know how to play the game
yeah I know are you proper Hunter which
one I'm a prop okay you know you have to
press E when you want to become a a
thing press e okay and only small
objects mon normally looks like volume
is low oh I did turn Up's volume but I
can turn I there before oh yeah I can't
it I can't I can't be a prop let you go
let' he
go no what is she where I'm just a dude
I'm in a zigzag they'll never catch me
if run a
zigzag I hear
sh never catch me run a
zigzag get her get her he'll never he'll
never get me he'll
never did get her yeah yeah I don't know
why got her can't be a prop it's
fun and that's exactly where I hid
two it's a good hiding spot right in the
[Music]
shadow you're still
alive see a lot of blood up here in the
Attic
[Music]
blood
scared of
me she's running around the
Crowbar no one will find
me what a pretty
lamp run
yeah it was such a pretty lamp yeah it
was actually nice that was awesome
combo's still alive somewhere maybe in
the sewers or something waa is also
still alive somewhere a no I'm not I'm
not playing in this round oh okay are
you a spectator yes then maybe I'm the
last one yeah in the the true challenge
no one will find me she's probably one
of the
rooms I'm chameleon oh hello hello
besides a mini lamp huh
lamp not
suspicious I don't know I'm just I'm
just tasting I'm just testing the t
[Music]
uh no hello no no I don't know what you
think you're seeing I don't know what
she's a baby she's on the top floor
she's making
[Music]
where' she go
wa nice okay now everyone can play
Yay the name be able to see my
name yeah usually if you get really
close to a prop you can tell for some
reason I don't know why God it's kind of
M step all right they better show me the
names yeah yeah I it's like I saw when I
was looking down at the bottom like at
your feet for some
reason all right we're going to get him
yeah crop gang oh for sure now we're the
spec now now we're the the hunters let's
get him the
hunter
must what happened to a must has the
game started already the game started oh
no oh no oh
no in the baby's in the Attic baby's in
the Attic baby in the
at please please this is bad
uhoh oh babies where is
everybody hiding
oh I'm going to throw a b hi baby I see
nothing down here oh look are you in
here still sure hello oh yeah this was
that thing oh I thought you had less
Health as a baby what are you made of
who ising us who ising us tanky
baby how to open a door how to open a
door press
press okay die nice
people PO on which side are you I Hunter
oh there's fall damage okay there
isage oh just somebody died a fall
damage yeah a baby like eight
times the
baby
yes the big baby the tiny baby the sh
baby oh yeah they have I think has 8
hp E I had one when I was
the
got nice
people give me some
kills who's still left how do I do that
I think there's one if you wingus no no
no I'm dead I'm dead no
ia's really good at
hiding he's a good
Hider oh
h 2 minutes
[Music]
left
no no it's time to use those shots
up I think my graphics driver crashed oh
no the game you're still in the game
you're still in the game you're okay
hiding spot is yeah
still still pretty good yeah
yeah she hesitated she doesn't sound
[Music]
good what could it be the Giant now all
right well I'm out wait how'd you die I
guess too many
times oh yeah if you hit too many things
yeah yeah you'll
die you died over here in the
corner no you died what she shooting
barrels I mean I had to I had to rule
out the barrels Kell you were you were
so close not the barrels am I supposed
to not talk when I'm sorry oh yeah me
[Music]
too I can't find
anything
hi where Doo where are you you know in
the
house yes but where m just took fall
damage
yesh hi only 47
seconds
hi I'm a I'm at soup oh oh kitchen
kitchen I hear weird sounds what the
hell what is
soup it it's it's a it's a we 20
seconds 20 seconds 20 seconds
[Laughter]
no shoot
everything what what is I don't know
what to
shoot
h
no
soose you so really close she was in the
basement like in the
cellar you literally shot right beside
me like a
pixel are you guys both playing one one
more round one more round yeah one more
okay last round last round okay yay
let's
go I pressed e but I didn't turn into
any prop oh it has to be like one of the
smaller ones it's tough you're prop now
right coobo I'm a prop okay if if you're
if you're a small prop you have less HP
so if you're if you stay big you'll also
be tanky
oh okay okay okay okay
the
started
blood oh
no I am committing to my
position oh somebody's Wasting Bullets
and
I put it
on I'm so
sorry where is the light oh there it is
good night everybody time to sleep okay
what that looks suspicious down
there it's not oh the light is back on
it's not really
[Music]
yeah oh supicious
thing y
[Music]
yum maybe they're in the
sewers
hiding nothing
St Dead
Silence guys let's this do you find
anything to S uh I haven't seen anything
in the
sewers nothing looks touched in the
kitchen either oh no that was yeah M
suspicious over
there I mean you HS could also just give
up so that I can go eat my dinner and
then
sleep hey hey we got two minutes okay
you have no
chance oh oh
last y little wait now you can eat
dinner
props where are
you I I'm dead died I don't think I
because this is a flesh wound shoot
me you might still be alive nice go is
that did I you did good spping out props
it's your first Blood first round my
first round being prop and you killed
me
thanks
didn't I saw I saw bibu but then she
disappeared I
did no it was dark it looked like it was
uh over here oh there an axxe oh an
axe you'll never find
me I'm too slippery I'm watching the
stairs that was
a I was an Axe and every time someone
came around the boxes I'd slide under
them to go to the
other smart the strats
what wait who's left fall
[Music]
damage for a
bit but then she disappear
be slippery maybe she could be a bab we
know what people look
no no no I'm stuck that's just you stuck
oh there we go I am the best steal rock
you will not find it's Weir but there's
no baby here H let's go to the
basement yeah I'm going to check in the
sewers no surprise that a rock is good
at
being oh never mind I thought I thought
I thought it was people but it was just
me holding a circus
oh 98
s she'll come out of
hiding
she was a suitcase wait what was
her it was her
wasn't good
job I was in that closet behind that
suit other suitcase that you were
shooting at I was Lally behind that one
but you you thought I was the other one
so you didn't see my
guys you really had to holda
fear yeah GG though
G it was fun yeah we'd keep playing but
we have been streaming for a while today
a lot of excitement with the
anniversary going to sleep for a million
years thank you so much
everyone to play together yeah holy
forever
also it started with just all of us myth
and now we have so many friends and
Ian we come a good long way in there 3
years I'm happy should we say some
cheesy goodbyes I just said mine yeah
that sounded like one I just said hers
okay oh we're going to make the co has
listen to our cheesy oh sorry this yeah
oh you can
leave listen if you like cheese you can
stay I like cheese I like cheese too
cheese okay well then who wants to go
next with cheesy
goodbye no cheese just looking forward
to
the always looking forward to what's
next I hope we can play more games
together it was really fun thank you
guys yeah yeah yeah yeah I I'm always
open to if you guys ever want to play
Garry's Mod again to set you know
something up or yeah do something that
be so much fun do it I want to say big
thank you to myth for holding strong to
ever for such a long time you girls we
are we are so strong you know those
three years three years sound maybe
short to some people but I think it was
a long time and every day was so full
with like insane memories every day
every day we try our best to make every
day the best you know so let's continue
doing that and I'm so happy that I can
share this experience with you girls and
I want to continue sharing every day
together as long as we can I love you my
I'm so happy that we became myth
together I'm so proud of us we are
strong thank you again to our for
joining I'm so
happy happy
year you
everyone keep having fun into the fourth
one let's
go out all the fans thank you for
watching thank you guys rock all right
okay I'm fading us out now goodbye
[Music]
okay
n