]
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
Te me
[Applause]
why once
[Music]
please are ready
for
much you guys are
practicing you guys are
ready Are you guys
ready We good
We're going to do it What is what is
your team name What is your team
[Music]
name
come and  next team The Dead P team
here Dead team
It's not to L Okay I list all right so
how are you uh How is your
preparation for this for today event we
are preparing so much right oh so
much Oh are you guys are positive
that you  guys can uh Win today so
positive no  idea Oh yeah we're so
positive yeah yeah
and uh What is your team name do you
guys have team name k What do you
think no hope team no hope Why so good
You say we need to do the rer psychology
Oh I wish you good  luck everybody Oh
thank you so
mucham come back for to thank you
over here over here please a little bit
away from everyone because it's very
loud yeah
hello
hello Attention please
attention attention Ricky attention
attentionicky we are a very nice synergy
between the two So what is  team name
[Music]
didn't even have to think of one because
we were prob Nash all along We Were A
Team for years
now
we will
be the winners anyway because we are the
ones who love each other the most
[Music]
here
yeah okay
Good
evening J
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [
Music]
gamb Can you introduce your team name
[Music]
er that our team name team not H
JP
are J okay
okay Inside bracket not  and then h j ok
ok not the not is really important a
really important part of our team name I
see yes Yeah I hope you enjoy today and
Um There will be a Treasure Hunt game
So your team
tested
tested teamwork don't H Your
[  Pat  hands]
teamk so I
[Music]
guess hello
hello Kobo have you eaten Have you eaten
yet Kobo eat first Kobo eh S I've eaten I've
eaten this, Jeta also gave me herbs
earlier ah great cool cool cool cool
cool Yes
spirit spirit Yes I yes  I'm right, Hi,
if there's something that
might be troublesome because you have to
carry it yourself for a
while, cheer up, ma'am, it's
like we're looking at Kobo, don't you know?
P
okay eat
this
Yes so that's it
[Music]
Min you why I'm
all
oh oh three of them are
tigtig okay
Okay chairman
Guys okay Guys E this is because maybe we're
one less but that's okay e
first of all we're going to Treasure Hunt  So
the first game will be Treasure hunts
they There will be around Spot of
Treasure it can be in CH it can be in a
Dr it can be in
anywh
so your mission is to find
it has around three
emeralds that you can use for the
later  there is a hint around the area that
you can check
[Music]
okay so before we start Let's sleep
first
[Music]
again Okay is there enough beds I know
Survival for
the it
my
B
[Music]
than one more one more
everybody  the time the time for hunting
The Treasure will
be 10 minutes so after 10 minutes We
gather here again we will we will ask
you to gather Here by
chat wait where is The
Treasure on the first floor it's on the
very first floor with the many many
[Music]
grass on  the ler with
and GR don't anything Don't you don't
need my RPG sens are
tingling is everybody
[Music]
ready I'm going to count the timer So
Are you guys ready ready
[Music]
everyone stand
by Yes I  'm it
in one go find
treure don't know what the sear is near
here there
l later later later
[Laughs]
later Oh I
think okay ma'am I don't understand Wait a minute
I'm still like I'm trying to read k
I can man I don't  play this game
enough What does look
like things he can step
on most
Stone that button by the Oh that's it
guys because the
kinya k
because it hasn't come yet So Come on viewer
help me I cash in my opinion yeah something
like this usually has to be two
people so you look for a shelker  Just a box, there's a
green shelker box or a
gray one. De Ay
can Oh you found
it How do go back
up
est How does this game Work Sensei I'm
sorry I only show up you
Canal and not classes Oh thank
you I  really only show show up to the
Sports festival and not classes I'm so
sorry it's I found I found you guys did
it that was one of the trickier
[Music]
ones we did
it I didn't know No they would have
reacted they would have reacted if they
found it  I have no idea only I'm looking
here for like five minutes now and I have
you already checked the book Yeah
it says like among the Flowers Vi and
BRI The Great chest HID from side
so maybe they did find it I don't know
among the
flowersers I'm trying  I'm also trying
like I tried
hard Did you find something No I see
buttons though we have to press at the
same time we don't have to break
anything
right How far would it be from the chest
should we break it from I'  m going to
Desty public property No I don't think
we're supposed to break it right I don't
know I'm going to the next
one uh you guys can like keep on
pressing stuffs and whatever or just look
for them
ni  I don't know if someone is destroying the flowers or not  Did you
destroy the flowers? Don't know Oh,
Popy's number is in the
coy. Behind it, he said it was urinated on by Mrs.
Coy,
what's wrong with that? Eh, where can you get the flowers?
If that's the case, we're going to pie
[Music]
inia
goes down soruhuh
oh there's nothing coy underneath Coy
him  it's not going
to be destroyed, it's
going to be destroyed, it's not going to be destroyed
[Laughs] it's not going to
be taken, it's not going
to be taken
Gosh
B okay
[Music]
poor thing Hi yeah you know we
Made Nobody found
[Music]
this
is this is the Hardest
one not really The Hardest
but how does
senp know or not actually does senp see
or does senp look in
that direction Heeh there Actually there II forgot
e take it Oh yes
H means you put four huh  Ah, I've
found it, it's okay, it's free.
Rao, it's okay. Hint for children who are
playing alone. It's okay,
good children. Thank you for working hard.
[Music] I'm
happy if I don't make a mistake near the
stairs  Is it also there
or has it been moved
[Music]
yeah oh I also forgot where we hid it
even I forgot where we hit all
of
them she May have we waste waste it no
we spent our time last night just hiding
all of these HS anders and making
theseaps it was
I'll pick you up first
[Music]
where is there
Yes I think She is here Kana
deh kan De Hai k
currently ex's already
broken
a
ko ah k dah koco
[Music]
You should be able to get
en
[Music]
friend love love gotemp
Emerald I got F Emerald
found What I want to check her po after
this Yeah I don't even know so you guys
did you guys find any No I don't know
what to  search for no no did you guys
know that there's actually one really
close by yeah probably right here ah
what the
hell that's what it's supposed to look
like
Said There and chest and
hoppers I would recognize
[Music]
that everyone comes here everyone
[  Music]
everyone Who  got Emerald Who's got the
Emerald
We
did Um in total nine
there treasures tre How many emeralds
you
got That's
[Music]
awesome but I don't know
the puzzle That's
[Music]
nice I gu it's
F How many
you got
[Music]
budet
other everyone
[Music]
everyoo ha Attention
please ok thank you thank you for the
attention since we've already done The
Treasure Hun so we have to go back and
the bu to  continue the Simon say the
next game so shall we
go
Sep let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
What if we share a b Together in
Minecraft the game we are so
[Music]
romantic
C Everyone pleases go let's go I love love
love oh oh  I'm catching up I'm catching
up no you're not no you're not catching
up I'm
catching I'm catching up
Run It's okay you get
Run It's okay pretty well
with yeah that's
true are you talking to me  I have  I have
a feeling that I'm the one Who's going
to
m It's okay we probably mess up before
we get to five or
[Music]
so
W I'm going to the top I'm going to the
top What Simon
says why does it matter to  us say
Hello everybody are you guys
[Music]
here L just 10 anyway until they
can keep going L yaere bisut
s
ready I think B on discord just
like that Jadiora
[Music]
we have like
demonstration because it is at the top so it
goes
[Music]
first are
you my Knees Are Broken but
[Music] [
Music] [
Music]
[Laughing]
ak level
to the
end if it's wrong then it's over
[Music]
I'm right, we'll make a group for them
I've already made it for the participants
[Applause]
[Music]
is
Iton
[Music]
ha tu yo H OK
l
a
throw away three two
one Hey throw away Yes, how come throw away throw away Oh yes
k throw away I think it's like that, no,
not throw away, not throw away, Ris throw
throw throw, throw it wrong, repeat it,
OK, bro
Oh
yes, okay
throw it Hi,
throw it, don't give
it a bonus, committee bonus bonus  I said wrongly,
bonus, it's better to just do it again, yes, yes,
it's okay. Later, there will be two, we'll repeat it
, we'll repeat it, okay? It's okay, just
two, four,
throw, squat, three two
one
ramp  jkak
okay facet
facet facet throw throw
squat
jump three two one lat
J lompah
[Music]
lompah three
emeralds Emal facet facet throw throw throw
squat lar Jengkok jump jump jkok
forward
twice okay okay okay okay three
throw lemp squat squat
jump forward two forward two
I
wow  throw
squat
jump forward
twice facing left left Oh okay okay okay
three two one
throw
dongkok  jump jump forward
two left left
uh
cuyyukiiuki
Yes sengwa throw throw squat jkok
jump forward
twice face left left face right right okay okay okay
okay okay three two one demp
squat
J jump forward jump two
left
right eh eh sorry I see Antoni
Antoni Antoni
we left pretending left right okay okay okay okay okay okay yes
yes yes where is Yopi's mother
eh I I I saw it looks like
Yopi  It's wrong, right, right,
right, right, right, right, right, but
Yopi turned around, heh, that's what I said,
Yopi should have faced Muna when he was
facing his right.
]
okay Gok
Gok
ye this is the emerald yeah
okay okay thank
[Music]
you
pleases Oh okay Nice
H hai
[Music]
guys  here The rule y i think I think
it's better to stand in the red for the
beginning stand Thank you face Muna
there where I'm here Hello oh Hello I'm
here I'm here
in
BL I'm blind apparently Ok so The rule
is like explained during the practice so
you guys will be given
progressive
eh Commands
Commands and the more you can do it the
more get yes and if one of
you yes do we do it at the same time or
do Yes at the same time  Ok at the same
because There will be 3  two one okay okay
okay Are you ready now
okay okay start from the first one the
First
ready yes
throw three two one let's go How do you
throw in this game
this
okay there's no sound it's there So this is
okay Or not
Okay sorry can't see it from the pv  ak
Okay I think you should be in my place de
so it looks Okay
Okay you can you can take your item back
Okay okay my bread Okay
next next because you guys are right so next
one is
throw
jkok three two
one
okay
[Applause]
okay okay okay we're going we're going
fast we're going fast
throw squat jump th two
one getting getting hot next is throw
squat jump forward twice
Okay three three two
[Music]
one
What You
forgot
forg  What you JP so you throw and then
you J and then jump but you throw and
then J
Sorry She's A
Hp so I'm sorry Brain That's what you mean
guys uh pass three rounds Okay give
you three
[Music]
Emerald Thank you  Thank you
stud You should have stud you
shouldud I just forgot the order It's
not like I forgot the
meaning uh guys
can now Thank you wait on oh Hello Hello
welcome it's I for everything now please
speak slowly
Ma Okay I will
be everyone stand by in  the red
hit JK Jump
left right
okay stand on
the on the red area please i on the
R are stand in the red
area are are yeah okay It will be super
easy speak slowly
Okay R ready kar ready yeah Okay I will
give you the  my first one  guys PR for
us
throw three two one go
[Music]
You're starting off a difficult one
because Sounds like So that's like th
stuff or is it just and stu just one ST
okay okay okay okay
ah Okay okay I'm telling
me so next is  l
jok th two one have a question have a
question okay no question Just do it
wait okay
May
okay okay okay okay And if you want to stay jok
That's also fine don't worry you got it
you got it ah Okay but you know e  yeah
gitah OK  next next is getting
Harder
throw
squat
jump
fold One OK throw squat
jump let's go let go go go go OK next
next next
throw
squat jump forward twice okay okay
three two one throw squat jump forward
two
De ah
next next next emald OK OK OK  next
throw
squat
jump forward twice facing
left
three one
eh
jump forward twice
hood Ki Hi
see How's this OSIS president continued
already five continued OK next OK next eh
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left Ki face
right face right three two one
[Music]
l
eh and right and here and here and then
after that one I forg one I forgot and
then If I Turn and then If I Turn Right
do I  Turn 45 De
right oh well I
mean As Long As righted
no As long as you turn right I think so I
guess That's correct okay yeah you can
we hear the Ding Ding Ding no what who
was wrong me right what did I do wrong
No You  should you should end it with
fing means that i'ming the other
way so yeah first you fing to re and
then faing to
Mey but I what I faced right that you
don't see how many Degrees
yeah no No that's 90 De Yeah you  didn't
say How many
Degrees Well I think it's just like well
it's a misunderanding oh well it's H
up H up means only like of like we
facing here and then because this is k
and then had right is like to the right
of this  position so you have to face
here
yeah so that means four emeralds five
was it five right five five five
emeralds five
emeralds
y there you go Okay thank you thank you
Actually did great Don't
Worry yeah still the highest so far no
no I think  he got but anyways yeah still
the
same
over not It's Not Over Hello are you
ready yes wa we had a question yes oh So
if you say like kitty
uh KITT go forward do that means I Turn first
and then I go forward Yep Yep Okay and
then the other question was if you say l
do we just Run Anywhere or we are going to
run in a specific Direction uh Run at
the front side You're facing at the
moment
okay okay okay okay So if facing right I just
Run like
this
okay  if you're facing right, face right then
just
front just face right
Run Wor not
as you can stand on the red dots here
red block
[Laughs]
stop Are you ready for the first
one yeah
okay the first one I'm going to tell you
is
throw three two
one Setak ngadap front dong Zeta ngadap
there zetaun ngadap
muna ngadap muna but that
was right
kaking the right way don't Wor Take Back
item
moving on moving on the second one is
throwing
squat th two one
Okay I'm really sorry take  take back your
item fine That's
so nervous in my life
before relax relax the third one
throw
squat
jump three two
one right
fast
ye getting hotter here next is throw
squat jump forward twice three two
one
okay you can get back to your
position wow oh next strong okay okay
thank going strong next
throw
squat jump forward twice facing left
three two
one
okay okay you can get back to your position
get back to your  position going strong
next one
is
throw
squat jump forward twice face left
face right three two
one Oh hm
OK wow wow
wow guys to get this far
[Music]
ye going strong going even stronger next
one
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left face
right back five times three two one
Wow the
Oh my God even Harder even Harder even
hard next one let's
go I'll start again
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left face
right back five times three o'clock  times
three two one
crazy chat that was crazy
okay Are you guys ready for the next one
another one Oh my
God wait go go go Before I Forget Okay
okay
next next get into position okay eh red
block please zetta okay thank you  okay okay
next one
throw
squat jump forward twice face left
face right back five times hit three
times jump four times three 3 two
[Music]
one the last round last one last one
you made damn ooh let's go
Are you ready here we go
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left face right
back five times three times
jump four times run to the
red block three
two
[Music]
one all crou by
accident so
[Music]
apparently forgot
to go back five times
it's
only just like three That's
F got far yeah the high so far
Oh thank
you so on the back on the
back that's emeralds it would have been
10 right if we got it got it yeah PR
That's one less yeah yeah
yeah oh thank you thank  you thank
you so where isylaj
OK OK OK OK I have Fa in you
guys where we face
Muna Thank you You a face Muna
Mun Where is
Muna the entrance entrance up
entrance I'm
here
crononon we're Running On the time  here
Hello where is she here I'm here in the
green Thank you ok ok are you ready Can
I just the and now yes okay so every every
time the command finishes you guys get
back to the red block alri and pick up
any item you've thrown  okay okay okay the
first
one
throw three two one
[Music]
that was easy moving on moving on next l
squat three two one
Okay next one
uh throw squat jump three two
one I have Fa in you
next throw
squat jump forward twice  three two
one
okay okay okay
next
throw
squat jump forward twice facing left
three two
one we have to be patient okay okay get back okay okay
you made it you made it don't worry
believe in yourself
yeah next one next One Okay here we go
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left face
right three two one
[Music]
apparently don't know i bot
yes yes face left face right face left
face right yes face left face right
not face left turn right okay  facing
left is left and facing is Yeah but Oh
I was I was like stopping here a bit and
then should I should I do that uh Okay
Okay Okay but that's okay you guys
that's fine you guys are great
[Music]
fon Kyla
five hold on  does that mean that and
Canada is the last y did
you pick it up
thank you okay thank you thank
you should be should be the last coy and
ye
OK Hello ho hello Hi yeah yeah yeah yeah hai hai
[Music]
haii Z
First
throw three two one go
throw throw
[Music]
throw throwado
throw t t throw
t throw throw
[Music]
emp l
Okay take the item again ma'am
okay
Jan
throw
jkok th two one go ah
yes take it again Hnya ma'am OK we
suiii
throw
squat
jump three  two one
go uh
wow cii
okay squat throw
jump forward twice three two one go
[Music]
okay
that's
throw
squat
jump forward twice  face left three
two one
go k k k
Don't die
yet I'm sorry I just couldn't
hear it
Okay
throw
squat jump forward twice face left
face right
three two one
go Oh with
them
[Music]
k face
right face left face left face right
Hidari Migi
m No no no  didn't you just turn
right instead of
facing right
J turn
right turn back
[Music]
very
triyob Emerald
wait
is my faak both of you
Sal
finish let's go  to the let's exit this
grp
Let's Now I am so ready to be a
disappointment
[Music]
This is going to be
fun
akak bisaudah
k
[Music]
here we have to
R yeah to prevent people from
cheating  Nice So People Don't
scream but like well you will probably
explain this anyway but like does that
mean That everybody gets the same amount
of time yeah everybody gets one minute
each long as we get it it doesn't matter
if we get it 10  seconds  Minut yeah
because we wait for one minute
[Music]
anyways you just Open it right
Click I think we have to decide on one
guess we can't WR
[Music]
several you can't That's quite different
From Yesterday though like  yesterday Oh,
so whoever gets it quickly No,
so that no one cheats, so that
we can replace all of this, that's how we
have to replace it. Is it necessary to replace it or not, for
example, just one, it's okay Oh, it's okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay?
You can't hear it
What's up OK voice GR voice GR
[Music]
so everybody has one minute each and we
will be starting at the same
time
y How do say in
Japanese
[Music]
t apa
H
[Music]
OK so for  the builders you guys will go
to the corner over
here and you guys will see the for
your Made
these are homework any from
cheating so when you know the answer do
notam it out
not please
PR like right there go go ahead Can I
try and I  guess when we built  it's
best
Right Round one this one
yeah maybe the gu Shouldn't look at
[Music]
chat Bu or
I got did
you
us replaced turns out to be the same both look at
[Music]
I
can
Bu This all of the  builders for the
nonbilders please stay in your Lan yeah
[Music]
pleases yeah
yeahke ul
[Music]
i
haveimah Jing is wrong right damn I'm really tired
[Music]
just come in okay
there  is everybody
[Music]
ready GR chat to have a voice group chat
so we can
[Music]
ka group chat
the team for the book
Ok time to count on
[Music]
it's
okay tired yes
tired it's okay you already you
already done great  anyway Okay let's
count It okay
count it one
minute one
minute
Okay game start
in
three two
one go go go go
go Gou
Anju go go
go anu
Aju
[Music]
IP ajimaru
ajaru
ohy nice
I I heard a voice  Is that not
okay? We know that if they
don't don't tell each other, how
come they don't tell each other? Right, they're on their
respective VCs, ah,
never mind, never mind,
whatever it's called. What's it called? Eh, I'm still
checking, I'm still Yao.
Sorry, I'm emotional.
guys, it's not professional, it's just how
tired it is, guys
[Music]
sexy mo
OK Guys,
the committee, how do you
make two mistakes?
Oh, no need for us to announce it,
where did the sound go?  everyone
Well yeah I'm also confused they're all
Sonya in their respective vc groups next Just run
eh the
winner
round
one
no not yet we haven't yet
Ask to be a [ __ ] I'm sorry Kan Sis ad
who is this
okay J asmos
no m book
m
m Okay yeah
[Music]
yeah  It's not a
turtle OK next
miggi kck OK miggi kck only right cck Kan deh Kan
[Music]
De only only right cck oh no
can
[Music]
Okay thank you thank
youar cheers I will
confiscateers
what s thank
you what wait can we are allowed to
have sheers now
[Music]
oh beer
next round are we ready should I check
the book I didn't check it yeah Please
check the book Oh OK I checked it
ok No I  'm assuming everybody already
check it yes
in one three two
one one minute one
minute pretty hard it's pretty
H come
n
kengeng yet l
this looks like a
Bu another Temp it seems Wow and this
one is the
attempted drawing and this one w
[Musik  ]
[Music]
okay okay wow wow
wow there is
some yeah We should Put Temple ya
see Canada is the closest
one reallyu
[Applause]
[Music]
okay okay
okay
[Music]
Nice why
is the writing so small Muna so
the writing is
big okay
[Music  ]
okay G tough them
plus 1000 Aur
awesome R you're so cool Thank
[Music]
you
This is
one two years
[Music]
F Thank you What is
that cheers Oh
okay everybody ready
Okay game  ST
in three two one
go they'll have to make a
circle people who can make circles or a
ball would be great
it also looks like an egg
[Music]
please the out in back turn
ah hi ha ha ha that's it
Eh how is it
[Music]
Ye
to okay
answer please
[Music]
oh eh
What yeah
okay
okay Al next round
[Music]
is Oh yeah after this one we tell
them to switch next time to do it
[Music]
guys
ready everybody
[Music]
ready yeah
Lady
let
Mar AD
[Music]
Oh I can see that
everybody's t
[Music]
t
interesting ah
[Music]
oh
eh okay  please put it
this picture is right
[Laughs]
[Music]
ah It's
okay
[Music]
goodak
Good good know
[Music]
okay
Nar ouch
[Music]
[Music] it
can be taken, it can be
taken, my nationality,
my nation and my
land
[Music]
my water, Come on, let's
play Indonesia,
go wait,
hah,
W
halah halah
[Music]
okay, that's okay, that's okay, okay, never mind,
let us not  give it extra time
that's
fine this one is practically kind of
like
Impossible I guess pretty much
Impossible
give it
Another we'll give it more time
here, Ken,
more seconds Actually  I don't know
how many minutes or seconds have passed.
inconsequential Cel where is it from per t Mayan
[Music]
lol
Om
where how do you do olii yeah It shouldn't be this,
right
Hah It should be  Isn't there really
another word? Wait. As far as I know, there isn't,
that's it e
[Music]
k Oh
myusnyaak, how come there's no sound,
Kamer
eh no Kamer no no
Kamer okay
[Music]
turns out I've been muting because
I'm scared  suddenly
ngelatah gangkai M
M one more round
okay easy easy easy
easy ah Easy easy easy easy easy easy
easy
easy easy easy easy easy easy
Yes it's
easy eh who's taking the book
etay Wi who's taking the book saha
hey hey open Who's taking Beka
[Music]
Okay W piro next okay
okay
bluetooth
z z take it again
Z
again what donon do you
donon Oh that's
it you guys ready
eh  later copyright won't sing the
song on
nambawan Oh five Oh th F
oh go
on What kind of [ __ ] will I be ah
Ih  I just realized
that my eyebrows are really thick
[Laughs]
eh Kiara's ones are cool too
uh
it looks like snail yeah looks like looks
like
snail
Mar I can actually kind of see it oh
this is nice oh oh oh Kole nice oh koa
watino
ohak what's cheating  This is hilarious, his name is
ah, that's an obvious
name, you know, but he can read,
no, that's all, right? Ben,
he understands it, actually he
can, because I  I don't understand it myself.
Once you look at it, you
can read it, how come you can't?
Oh camel why are there so many camels w
w
w w
Kang, that's
great, I've been told what that means
Oh, litally, that's why I'm writing
an answer. I mean, write down his name,
his name is just Anjay, then he's a
tubakya,
don't do that.  I'll laugh later I'll cough Yes, sorry,
I didn't
laugh. Okay,
I have to go to the toilet again, it turns out he can
read, he can read, I don't want to
destroy it. This is really cool.
Isn't that cool? That does
n't
mean I can go to the toilet.  Wait a minute or
not, Li, go to the toilet, go to the toilet, go to the toilet now, I'm going to the toilet first, I'm drinking a lot of horses, the people have it here, eh, ak, good job, eh, y'k, cast, get Emal, really lucky. Very cute, like a child [Music] at school, pleasinin okay OK, everyone, Deven, mute, mute, don't Deven
OK
it's nice to join V Okay gr gr
voice
also is
mute supposed to be mute ah mute okay
Okay everyone thank you so much uh for
playing this game we move to the next
game yay it's a wrong wol so we have
three minutes to play with the team and
each round gets five emeralds There will be
like three rounds So let's go to
the wrong W together Shall We Come on
Come here Come here follow us
let's let's
go I Think first you guys need
to you know  Click the bed just in
case so You won't spaw in outside anymore
[Music] [
Music]
we're not going to do this
yet come
on come on up
here every
Ik come on
[Music]
this committee will  There is  how many rounds three
will there be three there will be three rounds so I Can
we expain
Okay There will be rounds in total round
Har and There will be no switching there
will be no switch switch so switching
[Music]
Nas ro It's A Battle Royale
we're not going  by groups we're not Solo
Everybody's going at the and
for the wool cutters You are
Um You are to press F1 when you want to
play the
game and for the
forem You cannot crouch
well if if hating is allowed then is
eating also allowed  or  like what if you
die and don't fall i guess also hting is
only for like you know make people fall
don't don't kill you're not allowed to
kill you can hit but you don't
kill but what if like you'  ve Been hit so
many times You're about to die from just
not eating I think there is food there
There is food outside in the upper there
in the middle you can in here too there
in
here going to
[Music]
please join I have  another event
I will change place for this
I will  take my now Thank you Thank
you byee
cheers The Purple
box
cheers okay
[Music]
for all the for can I can I see what
your color
okay
isink Where's
other What color is not tak There is no
orange You Take Two
or only  Brown Pink Green
yellow blue and red because that is the
obvious color yeah it's so as you guys
requested you guys don't want to like
colors that even We won't even like using
one fully I think
so What color should I
[Music]
take  for deform
for  we're
going should we have Green If It's not
taken
for the for Who has taken their colors
Please go Upstairs because ITL be easier
for us to
monitor I'm Brown Okay is not
[Music]
okay right here so Green Pink and yellow
is  out Green pink yellow and red Okay
let's go with orange I have Brown orange
There is no orange has
[Music]
brown
yellow green and pink is already out so
the left one is brown in Brown Ok Ina
Brown I blue Okay now go up please wa
How many stacks Can we take  Sorry two
please two Oh only two should be enough
two or Three is okay I brought a lot
I'll be
down but I think
every I'm going to say it again
Okay uh is everyone here one two year wait
where are just going to use  all vc or
putting my
ST on the VC VC
we going to stop Using the all
vc proximity proximity Yes Ok
[Music]
okity
in just Brown Yeah Don't forget to F1
for the level good luck
[Music]
proxity pleases let
me I think like  Even if I fall down you
can still
Okay
okay focus on not falling
down we Cut
F1 can we play peacefully guys up
here no Pushing
are the
[Music]
holes
yeah out I I
[Music]
I forgot they could
is
it if if everybody dies then the last
one standing doesn't matter if
you but if everybody  survives then we
[Musik]
everybody I stoping only two people I
Believe In
You there's Ait
[Musik]
right Minut
just being careful It's Okay I'll Be
More careful next time
on
[Musik]
it's you need to take more blocks
Um Where  do I put the Blocks I
got to perspective color How many Emal
is
this could be like 10
[Music]
who's maama back
How
much time pressure Can we  try
can try a bit fast
wawa
wawa GM pleases GM every already
in
[Music]
I think we have to speed up the time
they say they have to leave in a minute
so 1 and a half minutes okay Half a
minute okay
[Music]
Oh I check DMS I have replied
okay oh my  god oh my god oh my
god oh my god Oh my God wa What color
Brown One more minute
[Music]
I think
I If I If I don't go too Close To The ah
[ __ ] toally didn't drop
up you
the became a  really
[Music]
nice lot of
Brown everyone stop in right now stop
doing
I counted pink yes I counted first
[Music]
two Green is 24
13 14 15
16 C
BR is not there
yeah
blue only EMP 35 367 38 39 4 42
4 44 46 so many yellows
[Music]
one more
round here, that's what
Emerald took earlier,
but when it
falls
[Music]
I there
team two rounds and then the fin I
think Come here Come here
[Music]
good stay in that
corner
the okay  we
start to the
cast Oh F oNe Oops Oh yeah F1
please F1
Please I'm sorry but if we F1
F
then it's already on the timer, right?
[Music]
no need to be
so one minute
[Music]
it's
[Applause]
okayry nice nicece
[Music]
green Green wa you can't
anymore f f th
[Music]
Two The Survivors
[Applause]
are e the pink one I'm red
[Music]
yeah
ut different
[Music]
let It's Okay It's
okay I really tried and I think I was I
think I stayed pretty long
[Music]
It's time to comb all your
emeral wait you can take my emeralds
right to
buy stuff Put sword [Laughs] a please
[Music] well Stone
what
else?
Anywhere, one bow and 10 arrows please okay
[Music]
Have you got it yet shnyaak
Okay again, dongrow again, dong tig
okay,
that's it, what's left, okay,
Stone
Okay, a  thank
you is that all
already
[Music]
Hello What would you
like um We would like
aing We would like uh Okay Where is my
list okay so we would like one Stone
sword one Stone sword
uh one Bow shoing
Hello Um one Shield  one shield and 30
arrows 30 arrows Okay That Should Be 27
I
think okay so money
Please
uh thank you
here are your
stuffs
oh nice nice did you get How many oh
wait I got a lot of arrows like oh three
arrows
right yeah  that's 30 isn't it 10 arrows
for three
emeralds I already have arrows so
30 I must have had I must have already
had arrows Okay is that all I'll I'll
give you some of the arrows so I don't
accidentally oh
Oops
uh here I'll give this
back I think Oh
No I'll make a group V Okay thank you that
should be it oh there's six more
thank you thank you Ah whatever uh thank
you
Do you have
money Yes what would you
like  hi hi What would you guys like uh
I'll do the stone sword First
mhm I just uh send the emeralds over now
like oh Just Give me the whole order
Okay uh Stone sword Stone AX Stone AX
shield and potion I think we have enough
for  all of that I did the math Wow you
guys
are Rich wait don't you need Bow Uh I
mean
arrows for the navigator you mean Yeah
you guys have a Bow but no arrows oh oh
I mean hit anything it's hard I mean the
arrows  is
we like the emeralds that we have is
just enough to buy potion Stone AX Stone
Sword and shield Oh okay unless you
don't want to get potion we
could forg
potion No I think hold on if the navigator
dies The Fighter can still fight  yeah
ah then just get the potion okay so here you
go okay yeah okay oh thank you money
Please
Okay wait we're missing the shield Oh
right You wanted a Shield money Please
OK Cuz the thing is waiting Sorry I'll drop it
all at once  Thank You Hold  on I
think I
think this is sorry what if What if the
sorry what if the we switch it with
[Music]
a The Fighter can
a Yeah I think we have
[Music]
OK
guysanj Guys
[Music] the
shield is for the navigator  or
Fighter fter for vigator can also be
done hi
[Music]
Go okay
Hello What would you like to
buy
one yeah Okay It's S right and then
one Shield first one shield and then  B
crony or another
Shield um like I don't know what the
durability for The Shield is I think you
would Know Better you play Minecraft
longer I know I don't really use the sheld
anyway
Um
[Music]
Um justord
yeah Just go with sword  then Okay one
sword that's all no
stonex no we want both so Stone AX
shield and sword yeah sword Stone sword
yeah is that all that's all y that's all
money Please two three It's How much is
it
12 19 19 is it  19
Oh Okay Okay is that all Yep there you
go don't want to give more of your money
no are you sure no thank you this is the
last round you don't need to keep the
emeralds By the way No it's it's only
two  we we cannot buy
anything How about this I'll give you
guys a
bargain since you guys are the last one
and since you guys waited patiently for
two emeralds I'll give you guys
arrows what
yeah we G yeah we G to take that  yeah
yeah okay  it's it's a discounted arrow I
'll give you guys Okay sure eight yeah
thank you so much Yes that's Wow thank
you for mone thank you so much y Thank
you that's great amazing fantastic
would like to sell your soul
Maybe I don't have a  soulon sell your
soul I don't have a
soul Let's Go I think we need to watch
them let's go let's go Thank you
bye make GR
[Music]
Hello Chad Would you guys like to buy
anything Everything's pretty much very
cheap we got arrows we got bows we got
Shields we got Potions If you're thirsty
that sword two times even
an AX two of them two
types a beautiful
smile Okay That would cost your entire
bank
account
please
okay your soul  is mine
I'm stressed stressed all
to are they going to do it soon
[Music]
how many minutes is this? By the way
ah Where did you fall
to Where's zomie I don't know I I didn't
see it
[Music]
that That's
rainy and is
there in The
Rat In The Rat in KY
please She's waiting for
me Yeah I got out I got out You got out
Okay sorry it's okay I hope you're fine
Sorry I didn't know I didn't know where
you were I wanted to guide you but it
like that's cool we're good
okay pleases
Now sa
Okay good thank
you
ha
rainy  ry trying to get
in trying to find a
place are they are they
they they want
it they are the ones who come
he can really
press the piston and then jump towards it yes
kanatanya falls eh Kanata
kanade kanade falls down Yes hang on
[Music]
Hi shoot
the arrow ah
OK anyanya in
out Oh anyanya that's the fighter yes
yes
oh now
re re and  Oh, he's using a
good jump, he's using a
piston, slime, so he can easily go
anywhere, Auntie is looking for victims,
that's scary, that's
all.  like a shark, don't you know,
with the sound of help, he's like there,
right there, right there,
yeah, but I'm actually waiting,
waiting for Iovi to get hit by the piston,
actually, or any member, like that,
get hit by the piston, why do you
miss it, it's just fun to see, oh  that
means because Anya lost, Anya will play
in the final, yes, no? Oh
[Music]
okay, out, okay,
hah, vote out, never mind, vote out, that's it, that's
it, that's it, that's all.
already three teams Oh that's three teams
just now three teams heah Okay
OK
next round
two te
OK Seta
Ame
Seta k
kade y
same too
hai
[Music]
hai oh wait no
oh you can go to the yellow Temp
u ru accompany this yeah
sorry  sorry we can go I'll leave the
group chat for now okay
there's
pink pink there's no red eh oh
pink sorry sorry
red I forgot
GL I haven't had any water I've finished I haven't
taken it yet so I'll bear it later
we'll finish
the streaming eh ah why not I ca
n't come out
Okay ready
[Music]
coincidentally there's Anya
too yeah
oh the committee just don't let it be fair okay fine
thank you
[Music]
ok ready ready Ready okay
game one
go go go go go go  I'm curious about Risu
Kanade Oh Risu is the fighter for
Risu Kanade and Kanade is the
[Music]
sniper yeah
Oh yeah and they are staying safe in the
crazy Al
zone
yeah Kyla and crony are also staying
safe in their zone oh But Kyla is
finally moving She's getting Close To
The reone
yeah wait what's the other
team is in in any zone yellow Oh
yeah She is She's In The Middle
oh r Down to the bottom
sitot and
So now
but not bad either  yes Mr Stone that's sir
Oh
[Music]
P okay
Kani
[Music]
k I I missed ame keegprek ame
Earlier he said keegprek I missed it
oh what a shame the viewers tu tu tu tuh
he really wanted to
see it  that's it, that's it, that's it, they've been
staring at each other, you
have to be careful because of the
sniping, right? Oh ohing each other
think oh r falling there R falling there
but it's there, there's this, I don't know why he's
still Staying there, even though he's staying
[Music]
up  are
you I think all
over go
yeah
sure Oh A closeup
Battle that's why I'm
scared okay
[Music]
looking at them from Up close
One is really funny if m-mul
kegepk Come on, keegepek  dong I want to
see the chipmunk
eh
uh but
it's useless for you
[Music]
hiding but the tools are still there
[Laughs]
the tools are that Fun to be Invisible
actually You have to get Rid of your
weapon
[Laughs]
yeah It is it
is yes yes  yeah it
was k Tom and Jerry
right wow
this looks like the power of the committee
[Music] this
is a
dog game wait I'll break this first okay
[Music]
here here Here There you
go This is so  dangerous I'm sorry I keep
Falling It's fine So can we How do I go
outside we can just go from here Okay
thank you I'm very bad with
Directions you will be my navigator I
don't have a bow and arrow Oh that's
okay then I'll just tell you where
Everyone Is at ya How does navigate
you so he's like telling
and then he's like telling you don't come
here because there's something like that and then
like if we can't see too
far like that so yeah I don't either  didn't
get there  the place is really far away
you know Oh okay I me the room By the
way I think it's just like that g like
Who around and then was acely aiming at
me And then She was like she you be
careful okay
then uh am make the group first
okay, lots of substitutes
today, grandma, are
we playing?
Ne, it's okay. Is
the enderman gone, is he still there? It's
already lower
[Music]
Temple Rene oli green Green Temp k Oh,
from each other, this is the committee versus
Buset committee
okay okay so Norm if in Z area
are
are Okay so I'll stay away from those
Okay who's the fighter for this
team Eh
this issue is just the two of us, actually
Anjir when I'm up against the committee that's
really [ __ ] Man when I'm fighting  the committee can
do it, how can it do this by one right by
one by one Do you know if their Navy
has they have a bow and arrow So I
think it's better If you play, the
furthest is half Oh
by Okay where is he at
most?  can see where I am Kam
half of the middle one Oh coming
from the careful
[Music]
She's just waiting at this
point I I want to I want I want her to
be like Where the arrow Can't reach
me okay now she's you guys are  close to
each other just separated by Walls I
think She's trying to bait You Into the
like the middle I'm not I'm not going to be
baited I Think You won't get hit by
the arrows as long as you stay behind
like  the circle Walls  in the middle
it's
Yeah but She's a really good Shooter wa
How many arrows does she have Why is she
not running out I think they bought a
lot I think they have like 40 Oh
crap I'm Lost I'm like legit Lost Oh
then  Don't worry she's coming for you by the
way I think it's going to be your
chance uh getting close Okay you guys
are separated by one wall there
you
great
Kara
ohord Oh I also got
discord me tooakapaingop
[Music]
Thank you Thank you, let's
get together first, OK, Man, let's get together first
in the
same place, oh
[Music]
one, thank you so much for joining  the
for this
year I Really appreciate it that you you
SP your time to play with us to try
the
games and also Thank you for the ID
for helping me to build finishing The
B
m anj
m
and after this after this for the there
another  another stream
[Musik]
I and for the
participant Anji awas awasan
for
the in
here thank you so much and enjoy enjoy the
game enjoy the Food enjoy
everything Please Don't forget
to play the medle song that just arrived
for a couple of years ago  thank you so much
where
yaar ajaak's Go
[Music]
Nik
already Oh my
God sleep sleep sleep
[Music]
Okay Where are they?
in front of the front bed
okay
a Batam can't see it from
where Okay you can see it looks OK okay
ah y Yi Okay OK this is okay th two
one yeah
[Music]
yeah eh hang on
guys hang on  guys, wait a minute, guys,
it's not good, it's
not good, it's not really good, wait a minute, oh, take a photo
so you know, why is BEC
Flying B on the break? Oh, more or less worse, I
think it's worse, I think
[Laughs]
yeah, that's
really funny, hang on, hang on, hang on,
BB Thank you, thank you
thank Patience Patience guys
OK th two one Gok
[Applause]
[Music]