[Music]
this is
thank you
[Music]
assistant
thank you
[Music]
thanks
foreign
[Music]
questions
three
two one go
sh
[Laughter]
you're amazing
welcome welcome welcome
everyone
and welcome to the first I would say
full collaboration but now we have
Council so it's the first almost full
collaboration
yeah
[Applause]
Discord comes out the Discord vital
Discord is actually probably watching
sports
did you guys see the tweets from Discord
yesterday with all the screens on Mario
so we are glad to have the Discord
support today and hopefully also the
viewers support today because uh today
will be a very very passionate and
dangerous and fun and exciting events
it's race day baby
it sounds like burning rubber exactly
and bad drivers bad drivers no not here
I may be a bad driver but I'll drive you
guys nuts oh wow
[Laughter]
I think we shall start with some
introductions of each member uh now
let's start with
um Indonesia
[Music]
hello thank you for having me this is
in generation thank you everyone oh I
can't wait what's your what's your
ikigoni yes
um to not be um the last last place at
least
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
okay what about
um bye
oh oh hello oh officers
generation one so my motivation tonight
is
um to show you my practice I guess
that's all oh show me what you got yeah
[Applause]
next up how about rainy
hi attention please I'm popular Rainey
from whole life ID generation 2. my goal
today is to be number one in your heart
and also not that last night
huh yeah yeah I thought you were good
you and Iris have heard good good good
news about you
good practice yesterday right right
bye
[Music]
hello my name is
Indonesia generation one nice to meet
you
what's the motivation for today oh well
I I want to be at least not on the last
okay but in the middle it's okay
[Music]
not glass oh okay we will see we will
see we have some competition time become
the last in my heart
the last in someone's heart is that such
a good thing
doesn't sound like a good thing yeah
okay next up
[Music]
hello hello everyone I am Theresa from
Whole Life Indonesia and thank you so
much for inviting me to this collab I'm
so happy though I'm so excited thank you
for today
[Music]
my motivation for today is that I would
like to have fun though although yes I'm
not really confident but let's have fun
as long as we all have fun that's all
that matters
and Ollie Ollie
yay
zombie crazy
second generation hi guys hey
um
for my motivation I plan on ranking pop
so that you guys become my bottoms that
is my motivation for today
I don't know what else I expected from
your motivation only
[Laughter]
you won't be dominated that easily
yeah nothing wait did I get that all the
introductions from ID I think I did
yeah I think it is okay
[Music]
let's
start with Iris
oh yeah hiris it's Iris whole alive
English project hope V singer here
um my goal today is to get first place
Victorious
full of participating and looking
forward to your driving skills
yeah thank you so much for having me
here so I heard that you waited for yeah
I waited you were literally the last
Edition that I needed because before you
it was like we were elf elf that's what
that was German we were 11 people
yeah
thank you thank you next up how about
um
today I'm gonna win okay okay
this is the I own I heard you only
played Mario Kart so far in the members
only stream but that's about it
yeah I won in that one too oh oh okay oh
really confident
I see then you might be the hidden
winning choice that the window into the
Dark Horse
a wild card player that's amazing
thank you thank you next time
English
um
um I'll do my best I think we have a we
have a future competition to be not last
and to be first so I'll do my best
you know I was also taking this very
seriously in her practice round so I'm a
bit scared of Ina um I don't know
I'm still falling off Maps oh yeah it
happens oh Kelly joined yes nice thanks
Kelly
thank you I'm here now nice then let's
start let's continue with the
introduction from
me
hello everyone my name is callipi my
parents are still asleep and probably
can't watch the news this morning Maury
nice to meet you I'm gonna be talking
about that low because it's a bit early
uh so excuse me for that guys but I'm
very excited just to be here I really
didn't think this was gonna work but
it's what it is
thank you Kelly for joining even though
it's such an early time and to kind of a
Troublesome with some setups and all
that I'm glad you're still here and you
know what you being so whispering and
calm might be a good thing for driving
because that way you might be able to
focus more
introduction please
and I'm kind of sick today and if you're
watching on my side I just need to say
this now I've had some technical
difficulties very suddenly so I am made
of cardboard I'm sorry please well it
was not my fault it's out of my control
right now so anyway I'm PNG tuber Doma
PNG tuber Let's Race today baby I'm the
wild card today
hi dust well you know on the screen
there's there's gonna be a lot of things
happening so your viewers should be
looking at the game and not you anyway
so I think it's fun I'm curious of
course they want to look at me right
welcome everyone I wanted to do this
tournament for a long long time uh I I
think my viewers have heard me talk
about it since months ago and finally
it's happening uh and I'm very glad to
have all these lovely girls here
together it's the first time we're doing
a tournament like this so I I don't
think anyone has to feel bad about you
know not being so good it's all fine
maybe we'll do it some more often in the
future so please don't stress yourself
out let's just have fun today yes yes
[Music]
but but before that let me say thank you
is the hats and the cards are sponsored
by ninoma inanis yes so
cute all right let's everyone switch to
the rules image please thank you
all right okay tournament rules easy
there's not many rules basically uh all
characters all courses are allowed
however if you choose uh please do not
choose random courses please choose a
certain course that you want to actually
erase but if that course has been used
before like if it has actually been
chosen before please do not choose the
same course again alrighty understand
though yes
number two items are allowed number
three we are racing in 150 cc with no
assist everyone please check if you have
turned off your assist I think you can
check by pressing why
[Music]
if you press Y and select your character
at the point where you select the card
you can press on a plus the plus button
and then when you see the the three
options on the right side if you press l
uh if if there is a if there's a sign
that says no
then it's uh Auto steering off that's
how it's supposed to be okay okay
yeah it's supposed to be crossed out
exactly the other one you can ignore
yeah okay okay all right okay okay
well then I also want to quickly let you
guys know that um I'm on I'm gonna be on
like Auto mute this whole time so unless
I have something to say I'm gonna be
muted don't worry if I'm a little quiet
I'm still here with you guys in spirit
okay
and next row uh oh yeah there's no more
rules there's basically it's just a
system we're doing the first cup all
versus all big mixer four races each and
then we get we will mute each other by
the way during the race and just to
focus everyone on what we're driving and
then we get back together Discord talk a
little bit then we go to the second cup
which is en versus ID six versus six yes
yes that's when we will separate each
other in uh The Voice channels by team
this one in this one we will actually
talk with one another if you wanna and
then we uh give some comments together
again when we get all back together in
the same channel and we do the third cup
with random randomly thrown together
teams no Ian versus ID but like all
mixed together naturally beautiful yes
random random random we will just like
I'll count down and and then everyone
joins Eva voice chat room zero or voice
chat room one
of them
everybody wants to be you won well done
we're gonna have to do it again and
again and again
okay sounds foolproof perfect and by the
way just so you know the the those like
team cups will basically be
um like the same
thing as all versus all the difference
is just basically like if you throw
items like red shells or whatever and
there is a teammate in front of you it
will not go to the teammate obviously it
will go directly to the closest opponent
driver that's around around you so yeah
that's how that team system works I
think yes
is everyone ready to get started we need
to fix who is that right
okay
nine ten eleven twelve is it Olly
then everyone who's ready mute yourself
on Discord if someone's not ready then I
will ask you why you're not ready
bye-bye okay okay wait guys how do you
wait guys uh how do you go forward in
the game
thank you thanks guys love you
too okay okay they're all muted so let's
let's set this up guys uh okay
okay I'm gonna be probably very quiet
because I'm taking it actually quite
seriously
normal items right frantic yeah no we're
doing normal items and no CPU uh CPU
vehicle own Vehicles yeah that doesn't
matter and racist forests these settings
are fine right I think they're fun all
right
start race this will let us select the
thing right right right right right
right audit
oh yeah okay no teams no is this is this
how you do it is this how you do it it's
the first time I'm doing this this is
this when are we going to select it
there we are okay okay I actually
have one like specific one that I feel
like
this is the one I'm like super super
good at
oh God my hands are already sweating I
just don't want the rainbow world to be
chosen that's all I want any of those
rainbow roads man
um
one that I am decent at
I really thought I don't know
um
anything is fine
I don't care no no we're not doing
random we're not doing random
because I need control over like so that
the roads don't get chosen
um like a second time you know what I
mean I mean okay in the first time it
would have been fun to do random but
anyway I just chose something no oh okay
I I'm okay with that one I've I've
practiced that one a bunch of times it's
quite difficult but it's but it's fine
it's fine
okay
okay I will be quiet now I will actually
be [\h__\h] quiet
I'm taking this seriously also nice
viewer number 69 let's go
oh my God
I practice a lot that was a slow start
[Music]
I never know if I should go for those
but okay I guess I did
okay
[Music]
Iris in front of me
and you took that two items away from
you even though I didn't even need it
I'm gonna leave that banana
I got someone without a family I'm
second
is that gouda or I don't know
but I'm probably not going to
[Music]
I don't care about not winning oh my god
oh
uh
I was just vibing yo
oh oh that ghost saved me from the
explosion
oh again ghost
nice
who is the [\h__\h] player what the hell
[Music]
what the hell who are you
what's happening
come on come on come on
oh yeah okay
yeah baby
[Music]
I'm good
come on
come on go oh close good a close one
who's number one who is number one are
lisu
no wait are not decent
that's later later holy [\h__\h] man
holy [\h__\h] wait that was Elena and who
else
okay next up
[Music]
they they I was like falling behind
around the end but
uh still kind of was able to catch up a
little bit there okay so we're not doing
uh what was that one
what what was Mario Kart Stadium right
no wait which one did we just race
which one was that
was not Mario Kart Stadium
doesn't matter it was okay uh I'll I'll
go with chief chief Peach I guess I
don't care
no no you're supposed to choose Mario
Kart Stadium again
someone chose Mario Kart Stadium again
it didn't look like that though what the
hell
wait is there two Mario Kart stadiums no
no okay
okay
we can do this I mean I don't I don't
need to win like I don't care about that
but I'm just proud that I'm driving
decently
okay I'm sweating
go
Dorito
okay
that's okay I probably won't even
[\h__\h]
what am I doing I was like huh which
item should I go for
um I'm not sure
laughs
okay come on Focus we can still catch up
we're gonna catch up
oh finally
[Music]
oh yeah holy [\h__\h]
bamboozled
oh my God
need items
I didn't
[Music]
okay
okay catching up
nice
[Music]
okay
oh man what the [\h__\h] am I so good what
happened what's going on oh yeah nice
nice
coming for you Iris oh she didn't get an
item I think
oh [\h__\h] no
[Music]
no Focus
Focus
I need an item to protect myself right
now oh no no no
ah okay food is okay
I want I wanted to get someone [\h__\h] okay
it's okay it's okay okay okay
[Music]
well let me tell you tell them
okay and please everyone do not use
cheap cheap beach or uh Mario Kart
Stadium anymore for your race selection
thank you
I'm gonna try and remember that but I
don't know
yeah yeah nothing that looks like a
beach and nothing that looks like a
fancy night life Place race all right
but isn't there multiple Beach uh yeah
but this is cheap beach the one that we
just did from the DS version not anymore
yeah okay okay okay okay are we doing
team wait what are we doing teams
uh we still have two races to go for oh
okay
um
she's muted okay
oh sorry okay
drink water to
get rid of that
okay
uh-huh okay
let's go
what was that one called something
horrible Toad Harbor
attached a shortcut over there can I use
that one already I never used it before
I think I could but like I don't know
let's let's use it no I can't
okay never should do that
I've never said two things that you have
no idea what you're doing okay it's okay
[Music]
you see me like styling here see me
styling they see me rolling
what the [\h__\h] man
[Music]
no no no no
pocket item
[Music]
should have taken I know everyone always
takes that one [\h__\h]
didn't have much to us there
we'll get there we'll get there okay FB
hey
one item
I used to name player
it's like a stare at me
the name player
what happened there okay
[Music]
oh hey hey hey hey I was in the middle
of Dorito
[Music]
oh driver
why why is that's so far away y'all
[Music]
what's happening
oh hey
you're supposed to go for number one not
for me
you know what this means guys this means
that you know I was winning against some
of you this means that you guys even
though you're supposed to be so so so so
good the ones I raced against are worse
than some of these girls who are winning
against me
oh my God
oh man
okay that was the what was it uh toad
toad
told something was that one totaba yeah
and we didn't do electrodome yet right
oh my God Ina really wants the freaking
Rainbow Road I guess because she like
practiced so much with it right
[Laughter]
she practiced so much with that one I
think
laughs
I don't want oh
isn't this the second time mine got
chosen rigged yo okay I am in control
Kiana is in control
I'm not even particularly good in this
one I think but I did race on it a few
times
I at least know how it works I think
I don't want any shortcuts though
[Music]
but does anyone know any shortcuts at
all some of these girls do
that's one thing I should have looked
into
um
we can do this
I kind of want those
I hate the bombs I don't I I'm like so
bad at using the bombs
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
hope you like the water
nice Tony still gura
hey hey I love the music and The Vibes
in this stage
[Music]
star is useless
oh don't go for me oh nine
yeah
you know he's like a million miles away
oh my God Blue Shield
coming through
okay go go go go go
guys I got disconnected oh no
I can't unmute right now sorry busy
disconnected what are we doing okay so I
didn't really think about that
what did what did I do in Japan
tournaments uh some van Halo tournaments
when someone gets disconnected
what do they usually do does anyone know
she just get like
um restart
but like it's automatically sets to four
braces so graduate do I just add another
one
because this one not mad disqualified
restart
they don't
oh yeah
[Music]
you can help start again
would I have
um at last place for this one it's like
kind of sad I'm like a little bit like
educio
[Music]
dosio
okay about the disconnection I'm yeah
I'm not sure like normally it seems like
in in the whole of Japan tournaments
they automatically give the one like
well the like this qualification like
last spot if you uh oh if you are oh wow
uh congratulations oh everyone cannot
mute themselves now oh yeah yeah okay oh
yeah
he's very impressed
but she still what a fourth or what so
yeah I think that's just how we're gonna
take it it is what it is
so uh let me let me just uh Ina was
number one right Inna number one
congratulations
[Music]
I saw you kept on selecting Rainbow Road
why do you want to kill them
I wanna I wanna uh make the suffering to
them uh you know
everyone you know
what yeah yeah she practiced on that one
a lot I think that's what she was going
through
well maybe I guess they'll be ready
oh okay someone has to uh yeah wait uh
wait who was number two
okay no problem who was number two
though
how did you how did you manage to get
number two today
I I did bad on the first race so that
really pulled me back but yeah Ina
Senpai was very quick ah yeah but I did
my best I did my best
are we tied for the food
is on the third yeah
good job good job wait wait are we
complete in the lobby right now one two
three four five six
okay
okay well then shall we uh continue uh
what Muna Senpai is currently
unavailable
my battery is 100 but it's a low battery
so I didn't know which one is low
battery oh
um
do you think you were fine to go or you
need some time I I think I think it
should be fine okay okay so we're making
coffee right now
everyone who needs coffee go get
yourself a cup of coffee
I want the caffeine shakes already so
I'm banned from coffee I was actually
really surprised about ama's driving too
like I thought you know because she
didn't like we didn't see her practicing
we didn't see her play the game and to
begin with a lot so third place and most
of the races until the end when I got
[\h__\h] over yeah
Watson it was pretty good good gaming
tag as planned right it's all part of
the plan yeah
whatever yeah no it would have been a
waste if you would have shoutcasted how
you uh suggested uh I mean because
you're such a good driver we need you we
need you
all right then let's uh okay only okay
okay Ollie is going to an idol we're
picking teams are we picking teams like
dodgeball no
that gives me really bad flashbacks I
don't like that
again because that means someone now I'm
gonna pick last and I don't want that
I'm gonna go up my full power now
because now I'm fighting for the en
ladies yeah
this is where we put our all in it yep
yeah
of our teams
now let's just warm up now
this is good because
Ian wait me too no
[Laughter]
I got this in the bag hey hey
that I can I'm I'm okay at not getting
last place so that's good news
Morrison is a good asset to have I want
her in our team oh yeah
guys
will have to carry uh Indonesia's uh
back yeah it's okay I will support
Rainey
no I can as long as we don't get
disconnected again yeah oh yeah gosh
[Music]
oh I hope you don't get disconnected
the disconnection but I didn't everyone
and please split into teams by I think
let's just um Ian go to Voice channel oh
one thank you okay
Adam
oh no no Elena can stay in zero okay
wait wait a second
okay okay okay okay uh just Cali is
missing did Kelly get the memo
okay
well ladies I'm back
strategy for winning against Eddie don't
listen
but like um you know for items do they
automatically um not hit our teammates
yes it only hits like yes oh okay that's
really helpful nice yes but I've never
parted teams yet I'll see how we can
select that I think we will um like
every every a participant will have a
choice to which which team they can join
I think that's how it works let's see no
more items no CPU all vehicles race four
races let's go
all right
I'm the one doing this okay uh player
was Ollie right yeah no wait no no no no
no no no no no no no
no no how do I how do I cancel this no
uh
I might have to like you might have to
ah oh wait I can go no problem okay it
looks fine okay Communications
it's okay you know what to do girls
okay I mean
I'm creating the room right now
sorry girls I did a little mistake
because like I thought uh oh yeah you
know
uh oh but I just opened the room again
you can join the room
okay okay
now you can you can join in again it's
open again I think it closed once you
can join again now okay yeah thank you
hurry
you guys ready to drift
very much
drift as much as you can that's that's
how this works
yes but not overdrift you know oh there
they are oh God the bald one is back
wait there's two headphones now
losing her full power with the baldness
that is
okay okay
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven twelve okay I think
we're complete teacher's doing a head
count everybody stands still inside life
I think we are okay
no CPU all vehicles for races
like who's the other ball
yeah at least a little Baldy
just so you guys know my mom is watching
she's not gonna say anything bye
are you sure you don't want to say
anything
this is how you do it
who is that Anya okay okay now it's even
let's go there's actually a random
button there so for later we can I can
just do the random button we don't have
to do the voice chat thingy
wait with James now yes we're here
I think that's using math yeah uh please
choose again a new map a new map which
one do we want to use which one do we
all have confidence
yeah which rainbow yeah um I want to do
Wario's Stadium
you don't have to where's work they're
using a tactic oh you guys are all for
loading the probability
just teams come on
no they're definitely teams
[Music]
because Kiara picked it I picked it for
us
oh nice we're blue blue
for the random teams
okay how cute we have the little Flags
when do we push the gold button on the
two on the two yeah right now
baby
come on
[Music]
it's my shell I'm so sorry in uh
does it work with like the same people
oopsy it's really I don't know Chad told
me that it doesn't hit uh your own
people unless I don't know it was it a
green shell
is red
oh also red okay I don't know well then
you just gotta be careful
damn what the hell
[Music]
I see someone right in front of me
kissing I think we're laughing
on this road
hate
it
[Music]
yeah
okay we got it we got it
[Music]
that was my red shell
okay no we did okay
wow wow we're opening on the red team no
that one is yes the a is
on okay one map guys come on
Castle Bowser Castle Bowser Castle which
Bowser do you Bowser cat no no no the
crown cup whatever it's called I like
Mount Wario or like the animal crossing
map is easy like easy as in it's like
cheese
we have crowns
okay okay
no I don't like cheese one no
girls
I don't know what it is
[Music]
I have practice in that one
isn't it
yeah just has a lot of traps and a lot
of obstacles
okay everybody don't suck obvious people
laughing yeah
let's go
yeah let's go
I was number one for one second I love
that one that was a good second
I am I like this music it's hype
let's go
what is that stop it
oh
hello I'm still number one
I'm not useless
oh my God
yeah
stable
oh okay okay who's in front of us
me that's me and Kiara yeah okay so
everyone's Ian then okay yeah that's
good that's good
okay
I won't use the shell
thank you
wait that wasn't me protect yourself
it seems like the Blazer does attack
until
okay good I have a bomb I don't like the
bomb don't use it don't use them right
behind you
these Corners are tricky
oh
no
no no no you're gonna play by ID oh no
oh no yeah
okay
okay we're good we're good yes there's a
little yeah bye no we got bites
monkey mode Let's go lucky yes
oh I'm not bad at this map
[Music]
it's hit me like a wrecking ball
ball
whose song
Miley Cyrus ah
is
[Music]
in front of
the Red Shell right now with Eno so that
I can be number one no
what what's happening
really bad timing
oh I hate it when the lightning hits
when you're about to jump and you're
just like I'm dead alrighty let's
freaking go
okay we're good we're good
oh no oh no
ah oh no what oh no
what a play
Oh rain there moving up the Rings she's
taking it seriously I feel like they uh
I feel like they're definitely getting
tactical on us here you guys
we're good but we shouldn't jinx it all
right guys
no rainbow road is going to be ready
rainbow road on the crown yeah Rainbow
on the crown what that's rainbow run on
the ground okay what does that mean
let's hit him with uh
Kiara yeah one job
one way it's a nice one it's a good one
but how high are the chances that it's
gonna be that one don't worry it's going
to be Rainbow Road and I hate it
um I feel like it's gonna be cheese yeah
it's too much cheese here
oh oh
um
okay why do they like that one so much
is probably really good at that one
that's why I chose that oh probably
trying to get the points back we can't
let them all right we'll get them we'll
get him we have a good Head Start yeah
hell yeah
just kidding
no item
I didn't even know that was a shortcut
they know the shortcuts were in trouble
they do they do
it's okay I'm still I'm still doing okay
we're still good we're still good
okay
I thought I sent it went to someone else
in front of you which will be number 12
I guess what the hell
it's gonna be a long road for that one
right shell okay I read somebody play a
light character I shouldn't have
listened
oh
okay so she knows the shortcut I see how
it is I thought I just saw it I was like
oh yeah there was a shortcut here
at the very end
[Music]
oh
okay the player nice blue shell
nice blue shell nice nice nice nice oh
wait I like that
no no no oh
no I'm going off track what the [\h__\h]
noise
okay only only iris is ahead of me
that's good yep yep oh Raina came look
at the shortcut
I didn't have a boyfriend to use that
shortcut okay she's first now okay
give me something good oh no not a
banana
I'm gonna kick your butt
throat so much
come on guys come on don't lose it now
oh God okay
guys together
foreign
[Music]
that's the last one
by the way Indian
rainbows
I think it'll bite Us in the ass but we
have Ina so okay
but the shortcuts just go down in space
to Sana
I know the shortcuts for that
no oh we're getting right oh
we can do it
just don't fall off the edges
yep
[Music]
okay here we go
oh thank God this is so easy
oh thank God okay easy easy shortcut oh
my god oh please please don't don't this
is so slippery
scares me I was watching Ice Cream yeah
[Music]
okay we are at one two three right now
yeah it's all of us okay okay
[Music]
okay that's fine
all right that was not me that was not
me that was not me either that's why
it's fine oh
yeah
don't get too close we have a retail on
my back okay that's fine
I'm just gonna follow you
oh
horrible timing
why'd they always get me when I'm in the
tunnel
I know
oh yeah
okay that's fine that's fine
I saw that
oh no always only went in front of me
okay okay I still have one more lap we
still have one more time
no
no oh no blue shell coming
no it was so nice
oh my God
no there she is
okay there she is let's have it damn it
okay no no no
it's okay we'll get her we'll get it
oh
[Music]
yeah I see I see Ollie no
me Bullet Bill come on
[Laughter]
[Music]
Hong Kong
nice
easy easy okay let's go
oh it's so scary there
you know I'm in me I think
I had that I was like third fourth place
the entire time at the until the end
of the race let's go
yeah
still not last still not last
[Music]
oh yes
[Applause]
yes guys
[Music]
uh what was their reasoning behind
choosing uh the cheese one and the baby
Road
I like cheese because
I was the one who told them cheese road
because I like like cheese yes
it's gotta be a road where Elena knows
the shortcuts and stuff yeah I am
do we have uh some uh comments from the
winner Ina it was number one I think
ah yes uh I would like to thank my chair
mates
um
for this opportunity Because of You Yago
I was about to be like yeah go let's go
okay okay
thank you
okay so uh we're doing random teams next
there's four more races so please
everyone be careful to not choose any
roads that have been chosen previously
that I would appreciate that
[Music]
um
what did we choose
even if you accidentally choose one that
has been uh chosen before don't worry it
will probably not be selected so let's
just let's just try to not choose the
ones that we have uh raced before then I
will do the random teams now actually
there is uh we don't have to do the
voice chat thing because there is
actually a way to do it here
and then once the teams are selected oh
there it is okay so uh invoice chat zero
zero zero one we want uh gura
um
all right all right team what is in the
back uh
Warriors
what's up
[Music]
um
oh they're going for the airport
[Music]
let's fly to the Bahamas come on are you
guys choosing
the Moon
okay okay
baby
I think that's actually good all right
let's go
yes let's go do our best
[Music]
I don't know if the shortcuts here are
worth it um I don't know I don't know it
is kind of risky yeah it's very risky
right it's very high versus the way
that's on the other two
[Music]
um
let's hey
the hell
what happened
um I got uh yeah we eat it oh my God
heated he didn't eat
yeah is very risky I don't know if I yes
yeah
oh no okay we're doing fine or no I'm
doing fine for now yep
no one saw that
Ollie's over there
I misdifted
they always informed me that means I
have someone to Target
I hate these curves I hate these yeah
[Music]
good man
we're on the same team
wait what did I hit you yeah you in Hong
Kong that's fine that's fine
I'm sorry
it's fine
[Music]
oh wait sorry
[Laughter]
who was that
oh
[Music]
as always the question who the hell hit
me this time who missed yeah
who must oh
me and my life all this speed
fast
too fast
that was a decent safe
okay
who was responsible for that who is one
two three
I'm sorry sorry I got Blue Shield right
in front of the Finish Line
okay we still we're still pretty much at
the tops yeah
she's on my tail
this is the most adrenaline I've had in
a very long time hey my heart is like
[Music]
so much fun
yeah it is it is I'm like surprised like
I didn't think it would be this much fun
to like have a full tournament with
everyone I'm having a blast man
every every half year we should do
something like this
what are we picking where
oh no problem we didn't have that one
yeah
no that's the womp womp womp womp again
yeah baby
this is the right choice
blessed by the RNG
I'm not I'm nothing aren't I oh
[Music]
okay I'm just kind of like wondering why
I might need mute sorry sorry
who was that I don't even know if that
was wrong
come on yeah
it's just chat things you know yeah
oh
the humanity
okay
oh Callie what happened
God this is not looking good
who are these
yeah nice
uh
-huh
okay this part I usually choke but okay
I can do this
we can do it
what the hell
blue
y'all be careful
okay I got the mushroom for the last
part
oh my gosh
wait I didn't
I didn't oh God oh God oh God I didn't
know I heard it worked that way
so friendly fire
no it doesn't like it sometimes it hits
like people by accident I think but
generally it goes for others oh God this
is bad
I don't know because um I accidentally
hit oh I didn't know that's not part of
the card
okay okay
so close I was like
during this race
[Music]
is scary
she's right behind he's running behind
me
yeah
we've got a little bit of leeway yeah
good job everyone good job
[Applause]
now what do we do
watch the clock get picked
up is this the final no we have one more
like two minutes okay I see
okay since day one airport so much let's
direct them in there yeah yes
or do we have one more ah we have two
more yeah
three out of four
[Music]
open right now
Irish
iris is so scary
oh my god oh everybody
[Music]
this is mine
that was horrible chat hope you guys
enjoyed that in the chat
just got screwed over like you would not
believe
what happened I'm gonna come back me too
me too because I'm behind you
yeah
we're brighten up there we are don't
worry I got you
Man I Feel Red okay let's go oh God oh
God oh God oh God oh
The Blue Team coming back in I'm at
night let's go let's have a blue team is
behind me why
let's go
this is Ollie
curses Ollie I oh yeah oh it was good
okay all right and Iris okay that's the
slime
oh
I keep not getting items this is not
looking good cool yeah okay just gonna
believe in the RNG
[Music]
with the RNG that's Mario Kart I gotta
come to the house
Callie I'm so proud basically I gotcha
it's not here right now but I'm so proud
of Cali
I don't know how to use the how do you
use the paraglider
uh if you press down you fly higher oh
then I can't hear
oh she blocked it okay
oh my gosh
I keep getting screwed over in like the
worst oh my God everyone in front of me
is is Bluetooth not not
again
hello something a miracle happens I
don't know I'm not feeling this one yeah
this is bad this is really bad this is
bad I have never gotten the mushroom
before I couldn't use any of these I
can't come back from this me neither
this is unfortunate unless we get out
it's okay it's okay
[Music]
you couldn't come back
[Applause]
next one gotta be serious mode
this is the last one yeah this is the
last one okay which what do you want
okay
drop down
okay wait listen the Warriors
I don't know if she can join in time
wait some someone please don't join
don't choose a race yet if you can
because that is
joining again okay
[Music]
um
I think this is uh
shogunai I'll just choose the clockwise
for no reason oh no
here we go let's go last round let's do
everything we can
come back we can do this
I'll do my best but not good here you go
good luck yeah this one's a little rough
we can we can do our best but I don't
think I've ever played this one let's
have fun
I'm just gonna start playing Mario Kart
because yeah
it is really to prepare for the next
tournament
[Music]
casually right because I I casually not
really no
oh really just for streams and until now
it was really exciting yeah I don't
stream either
Ollie's really good at this map
oh man
oh maybe that's why they're Tuesday
it's risky
yeah oh is it the one with the bouncy
stuff yeah yeah
I I don't know how to use it I don't
want to risk it because oh I fell
no I saw you disappeared before
I'm coming in with the same here it
comes
okay I was just gonna kill me
oh sorry if I hit someone
[Music]
yeah okay I came I guess today I learned
that you know even though it's too
friendly fire is somehow yeah there was
no setting for that though unfortunately
it's fine
let me on the ground get me on the
ground Captain let's go
home
yeah okay one more one more one more
let's go let's go let's go
blue shelon coming
that's garbage oh no
oh no
oh I couldn't get her sorry oh my gosh
I'm just very
trishelle I threw that don't get hit
okay
[Music]
adjust my drifting skills
I do see the Red Shell going around I
deserve that one so like it doesn't
immediately go to the closest one it
goes it tries to go to an enemy
like a button I need more ah no I lost
that I could have that we should only
come in is this it
me oh because it only finished oh you
finished
[Music]
only finished the course that's what the
blue shell came to me
it's okay as long as we got the pop
spots
oh no
okay I sent sarcasm unlucky
we got it anyway I think
this is our favorite course
again
no
[Music]
yeah I got disconnected like right
before the last lap oh no that was me
and my Shark friends after the Wi-Fi
cables
but that probably means that you know
the last round if if Lisa you know got
disconnected and the points got deleted
that means that the last round uh final
result is not really accurate
um but that's okay but let's just say
the last round was an extra Encore for
fun and yeah and yeah and I would like
to give out some golden juggles
right so okay they're not showing up on
your stream they're online but I'd like
I would like to give one a golden juggle
to Ina for winning almost everything
[Applause]
good job congratulations
congratulations
[Music]
and I would like to give uh another uh
golden Yago
um as uh to Iris for also being
absolutely amazing holy [\h__\h] so fast
[Music]
for being I guess the strongest in the
ID team holy moly
the biggest
goes to gura for being absolutely the
speediest shark I've ever seen yay
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
yo honey
[Music]
another golden juggle goes to Muna for
being amazing
I didn't see you that much on the race
but I think you were still shining
brightly as as the moon always does
the darkest time
goes to ollie for being also
surprisingly damn good you were gone at
the end yeah good job
speed squirrel let's go
[Music]
another golden yellow goes to EOP
movies
and another golden Jago goes to Cali for
actually really you know I don't you
surprised me you surprised me Cali I was
I was looking at you driving there and I
was like damn well what the hell man she
didn't even do practice Arc since she's
so good
Kelly I didn't I didn't get last place
even once guys that was my goal
thank you for cheering for me everyone
thank you I still love you moving don't
mind me uh chat I'm not gonna be able to
fix that now I think one two three four
five six seven eight nine ten eleven
wait who did I not give up
my dear I know you were you were
surprising me too sometimes I have I had
an eye on you thank you congratulations
goes to me
[Applause]
thank you very much everyone
um thank you
um can we get like a uh last comment
from everyone let's start with Anya
oh me okay
um that was so much fun but I have to
practice more if there's gonna be a next
time I don't know maybe
maybe there will definitely be a next
time yeah
there's always room for improvement
number one thank you so much everyone
for the fun time thank you
Kelly what's your closing comment
uh let's see my closing comment is Kiara
thank you for everything you made an
amazing tournament you worked so hard on
this you had a logo commissioned you
made all of this stuff in as well for
helping with the assets but like oh my
goodness you organized the whole thing
and it was a blast and I just wanted to
have fun with my friends and I was able
to do that because you organized this
amazing thing just thank you so much for
for working so hard on it because it was
a blast you I'm so glad you enjoyed it
thank you yeah
Mom and Dad yeah thanks for everything
it was fun to organize
good uh closing comment please
oh thank you I want to say thank you
also to Ina and Kiara for all the hard
work you guys put into this tournament
thank you and I'm very I'm proud of
myself for not doing nearly as bad as I
thought I would and I would like to uh
say that it was probably because I fixed
my switch legs so I didn't have any lag
let's go Gamers let's go
oh excuse him so I watched and I won
though I can use that excuse
[Music]
in a long time I think yeah no practice
baby let's go raw challenge let's go rob
Challenge
from last place closing time
ah yes so I'm just uh thank you for
organizing this I know we have uh
mishaps and some troubles uh Beyond but
yes thank you for this golden yellow I
will cherish it and talk to you every
night thank you so much thank
okay I've completely disappeared I'm
sorry guys uh okay Iris closing comment
please
thank you so much for inviting me to
this wonderful tournament Kiara and
thank you so much Ina for the very very
cute assets and yes I will practice more
so that we can I can go against Ina
my goal is Nina yeah I'm excited to do
this again hopefully one day yeah yeah
[Music]
thank you I hope yeah one day I want to
win against Ina too that's a big vehicle
that would be a big accomplishment it's
not that big of a goal
[Laughter]
s anymore Iris I'm so glad I'm so glad
you joined Holo Ian because that's what
made this uh tournament possible yeah
I'm really glad to be able to join this
wonderful Tournament being part of the
cool kids yeah
all right Ollie closing comments
okay I'd like to say a very very big
thank you to Kiara Senpai for organizing
this I've organized it once and it was
really hectic so I can't really imagine
the links that you go to will for like
the logos and stuff and even the
thumbnails those must have been hard and
also they were innocent by far making
all of those assets so quickly like you
guys really um how do I say it I really
appreciate it a lot and I'm sure all of
us do so thank you so much for your hard
work it was really fun playing with
everyone and um I may have not popped
everyone but one way or another you guys
will all be my bottom
I forgot about that goal yeah
you'll get them someday only you'll get
them
closing comments please
um first of all um thank you for you
Kiara for organizing and thank you guys
can stop thanking me stop
I mean I I don't think without without
you organizing we will don't be like
this I mean it's it's rare to gather all
the whole life Indonesia together that's
true yeah so I'm so thankful for that
and also
um big thanks to Ina 2 for making the
assets it's really great thank you so
much and I hope in the future we can be
like this again yes yeah yeah yes yes
yes yes I hope so too definitely I was
thinking like maybe on on uh like around
Christmas or New Year's Eve we should do
something like this again
closing comments please
yeah I'd like to say a big thank you to
uh Cara for organizing it of course I
know like organizing collabs and
everyone in different time zones and
like schedules it's really really
difficult but you really put a lot of
effort into organizing it commissioning
like the logo and everything really
thankful
um and everyone feel free to use your
hats and cards like in your Mario Kart
streams in the future too definitely
holidays
yeah thank you everyone for joining us
today like it was so much fun like
playing with everyone and I hope we can
do it again
yeah
operation this was a great collaboration
between uh kfb and Taco Taco Bell taco
eats definitely
we always just work so well together you
know
our fast food franchises are meant to be
together yeah we're speed yeah fast food
comments please
okay I know you said stuff but thank you
and also in a senpai uh thank you so
much and I had a lot of fun uh there was
a little mishap there there was a little
disconnection issue but overall I had a
lot of fun and I would love to have this
kind of tournament again in the future
you were so Good by then yeah yeah no
thank you
training so I'll get better yeah good
morning everybody next time
[Laughter]
[Music]
comments please
okay so it doesn't end there I would
like to say thank you thank you
to everyone here also especially uh
Kiara and Ina like these are amazing and
also okay uh I'm really happy because I
could actually uh gather and play with
all of you guys here because yes like
well uh I'd appreciate it more more more
collabs like this so if you guys are
planning to do so
I I'd love to I'd be I would be happy to
participate oh yes thank you so much I
love you guys
[Music]
okay
closing comments ah well first uh I'd
like to apologize
if I was salty I'll see if I curse that
you guys no yeah
[Music]
uh and uh yeah thank you Kiara and and
Inna you guys worked really hard thank
you guys and thank you everybody for
participating it was really fun I know
it's hard to organize these types of
collabs everybody's so busy and
different schedules thank you and I had
a lot of fun thank you thank you um
you know now that we have um now that we
have whole Council we can like we don't
have to rely on these exact 12 members
anymore so next time if you want you can
do shout casting
thank you thank you everyone for
participating today
um I hope I hope everyone had a great
time even if you know maybe you were not
number one number two number three
that's fine I think today was really
just about getting together putting um
two communities two fan communities of
hello Ian and hello ID together and just
feeling Unite liked it definitely and I
I'm always glad to do stuff like this
again so I would gladly invite you guys
again whenever you have time for it and
want to join and I'm sorry that you know
because since it's such an international
collaboration
um it's not gonna be an ideal time for
everyone so I'm so sorry for the girls
who had to wake up at like six seven a.m
or something like that I'm so sorry I
know it's tough I I apologize it's no
problem it was fun it's okay I just wish
my parents could watch the news but I'll
be I'll be happy
that's okay I hope your mom enjoyed the
tournament
I think she did I think that she did it
as well
hey girl
well well then with that I would like to
officially close to hollow Ian Holo ID
Mario Kart tournament everyone be take
care of your golden yagos polish him
every day he wants to be shiny and
sparkly and yeah I'll see you guys soon
bye
[Music]
yo I want to give another credit though
a last shout out to Spirit snare for
making this beautiful logo and helping
uh with some other small details as well
thank you so much so much there is there
also members only stream in a few hours
I'll put up the reservation uh ASAP yo
yo thank you everyone
[Music]