[Music]
foreign
do
[Music]
foreign
do
[Music]
okay
hello everyone welcome to oh
among us whole life english versus
hololive
japan
[Applause]
[Music]
we have come here together to play among
us and
we have lots of members today so maybe
we'll start with some self introductions
i'll i'll start with myself
i am not suspicious let me tell you that
but i am often the mobbed one
i hope today everyone will be fair and
square to me
hey
i'll also help out translating a little
bit in between so
if there's anything uh i can help please
let me know my dear
colleagues
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
good
what is your what is your goal for today
or your
motivational stage uh
yes
[Music]
ian's a number one detective today
i will perform my duty as a law abiding
justice seeking detective hi
uh
[Music]
[Applause]
bye
yes
[Music]
i will do my best not to load
today
[Music]
kelly
hello everyone um my name is
and um i'm going to kill lots of people
today
it's
[Music]
bye
why can't they hear me what do you mean
you can't hear me
nobody can hear you huh
oh my my chat's canceled
no so bad
[Music]
yes i know i'm still in standby guys
because you can't see the code
the code new code please do code
[Music]
but we still have to explain the rules
okay
can everyone put on the image from the
rules
[Music]
is