[Music]
do
my
[Music]
cake
hi
good morning good morning um a stream
at this time is very very rare for me
uh right
i usually don't stream at this time of
day because i usually still sleep
at this time of day it's 12 o'clock
in japan originally i could have even
streamed earlier i was awake earlier
than that for me it's very rare but
tomorrow i'll be streaming even earlier
than
than right now why am i doing this i'm
doing this
for you my dear friends from
around america canada and that area
always complain that my streams are at a
bad time
and i always wanted to mix it up a
little bit
so here we are and yeah it's actually
perfect because
yesterday i went to bed
and now wait for it
wait for it before midnight
what what what what what
what
is
this is amazing because in the past
seven
months or eight months i haven't been
able to sleep
before like three or four o'clock
sometimes five sometimes six o'clock in
the morning
i would my usual time to sleep is
it was uh five or six am for the past
seven months
yes but yesterday i was able to sleep so
early
thank you for the super chats what the
hell what's going on
thank you yeah
i mean it's not like uh i don't sleep
enough like once i sleep i sleep a lot
usually uh but yesterday wow
yesterday i fixed it i guess so tomorrow
should also not be a problem but then
again
i have a late night uh movie watching
stream on sunday so that would ruin
everything again
yay i'll be awake until
five or six at least uh when we watch
the movie
yeah but for now okay two days having a
healthy lifestyle yay
welcome everyone to the stream uh
so i guess right now there should be
some people who usually don't watch my
streams live
is that right because you usually can't
catch it did i
am i imagining it right
yeah okay that's good
thank you because i was thinking my fire
and blame streams need more
appreciation wait i don't have bgm
and they need more appreciation you know
felt a little bit lonely these past days
so
here we are here's some
here's some btm do you hear this oh wait
i don't wait
but you are do you hear this yeah
is it too quiet
it's kind of it's kind of quiet
generally but yeah the gym is fine okie
dokie tell me if it gets too loud at
some point
uh we left uh last time we left it off
at
right after doing a battle but
apparently i can do
another one right away so thank you for
the super chats what's going on thank
you
thank you thank you what's happening
why what's going on why are you so
excited everyone
a bit louder okey-dokey
glad that i'm streaming earlier yay me
too but this will be
all ruined again once we watch the movie
with members only
starting at midnight uh watching
extended version of the two towers
a lot of the rings yeah that's gonna
take a while
i might even fall asleep let's see
thank you guys thank you oh what's
happening what's happening
yeah i almost have 400 almost
anyway uh so i guess we're gonna do this
one huh empire
uh territory uh battle in the empire but
isn't that exactly the one we did last
time but i needed to level anyway right
so this is the one i can do without like
getting uh uh
without using the points uh
then why would i do this one
[Music]
on my streamlabs that must have been a
youtube thing
because usually if f is and it's my
fault then my streamlabs fs2
but it didn't so it's youtube's fault
not mine thank you for becoming memphis
i see you want to watch god of the rings
huh
[Music]
oh
excuse me get some type also maybe my
voice is still a bit cracked cranky
because i just uh i didn't just wake up
but
i woke up like an hour ago
thank you so much here we say it in
germany
[Music]
thank you for the super chats thank you
for the sneeze chats steve's chat sneeze
jets
so this one was actually real i didn't
fake it okay i didn't fake it
thank you
oh what what did i just read it's a good
time for you
mr mr yellow super jack that makes me
happy oh wait
i don't know this map yet oh
wait but this is not the main quest
map right
oh okay let's see what units do i have
casper no thank you
wait why does he have uh why is he
differently
um marked than bernie even though both
are not in the team
[Music]
it's a grinding map okay
what at
your tent what does that even mean
what does that mean
[Music]
he's supporting another unit how can i
change that
he's not how can he support when he's
not even
in the in the group he's paired up with
woofoo
[Music]
with why what ah
oh thank you okay well i guess
we'll do the same team as last time
bernie you can take a break again
i'll bring you back soon don't worry
about it
okay then map oops
map please let's see what we got oh
this is a pretty map oh but kind of
annoying because the
the the roads are so narrow
though not not that right and
the path says on that route oh wow
that's okay
uh can you like switch switch with him
yep thank you
[Music]
can you switch with her
can you come here no ah you can only
switch
okay yeah that's okay
okay save
because everyone's going to kill me if i
don't save i got it i got it
i have saved my friends should i save
again
make bernie uh how do i do that
no how do i do it
but why doesn't do anything i click one
doesn't do anything
on somebody else oh who should it be
should it be someone uh a close distance
[Music]
okay ah oh it can only
be done with um units that are not in
the group anyway okay
interesting okay that that that looks
good
let's fight begin the battle
route the enemy all right no problem
i will kill them all
gotta press them here we go
my boys you think you have a chance i
probably need more weapons ooh
one hit you guys have one hit wonders
[Music]
nice
you may kill someone too if you would
like to
if you can no he cannot and that's
actually
that's all right i'll finish him off
with my xiaomi
[Music]
rifle
thank you
hot but she's not really my type
although i must say if she
would push me against a wall i
probably would suddenly be very quiet
i'm a bit too big or
[Music]
big to tall
am i too small now but you don't see the
menu otherwise
too small oh wow i also don't see it
that's the thing
bottom left
[Music]
okay
oh thank you thank you for the super
chat something about petra
i will read the super chat after the
stream
one hp left oh come on but if it's a
quit maybe he dies
i just finished him off of someone else
so let's go for now
[Music]
oh i can move again
i can move again i don't want to move
again
i would attack again yeah but not moving
uh he can't attack in here okay oh wow
[Music]
[Applause]
broken heart she rejected me
[Music]
i was i was so slow
like restarting the game and starting
off as a male character again
i was so close guys if i had more time
if i wasn't so busy these past days i
would have done that
until today's stream i would have i was
ready for it i was seriously
considering it like so seriously
[Music]
but i i also don't like playing as a
male character
between a female and the male character
i would whoo she's what
i would never choose the male character
so yeah
i don't really like them oh are they
coming from my passion
she's hitting out those criticals like
it's not a big deal
oh you challenge my furnace
[Music]
one miss you got no chance my friend no
chance
try again and another one
attacking from afar still got no chance
oh man okay maybe he's
he needs a healing now
ooh player bags
let's see can we
attack yes wait
uh what
[Music]
i i know i can see the enemies range but
i don't really care about the enemies
range
[Music]
isaac heal him need
it one of our strongest warriors
we gotta treat him well he's the only
one on the horse too
doing god's work
[Music]
let's move forward with edelgard the
pubs are so narrow here anyway
so it's kind of hard to stay together
anyway
[Music]
so vane can kill him i guess if
he can no i guess he can okay that's all
right
[Music]
i should also finish them off with
sylvain he's only level 11.
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
something like that probably i think it
was good
[Music]
cali is releasing a new song this week
that's why she's so busy
wait i wanna do something with her i
guess we gotta bring her
[Music]
are you hot aren't you hot for the new
song i'm really hyped it's probably
gonna
like i i don't know i have no idea i
haven't heard anything
but i'm just gonna guess it's gonna be
something halloweenish something spooky
maybe
maybe maybe maybe
because she's releasing it on me
[Music]
i also want to hype you up guys i also
want to hype you
up wait why can't it wait is she whoa
why can't she attack does she have to be
like this close yeah wow okay
luna what does that do
[Music]
i also want to tell you something that
could hype you up i have a lot of things
that could help you
in planning a lot of things actually
like
oh in in i can tell you november will be
uh very hype for me i can tell you that
no crit but that's okay
i've got so many things planned for uh
oh you can move again
no no no i mean actually yeah let's move
actually yeah
although he will be attacked by everyone
maybe not let's go here um
yep
uh i i i shall give you a hint guys
i may or may have not but may or may not
have planned something for thanksgiving
may or maybe not i don't know maybe
maybe maybe maybe
[Music]
to to get your um
to get your attention off of
thanksgiving and thinking about eating
meat i maybe have planned something for
thanksgiving
maybe oh they're not gonna attack petra
even if she goes there interesting okay
[Music]
and also the talk show i've been talking
about
damn it the talk show i've been talking
about will also happen in november
first one ah
oh what
yeah let's just send the bully on to the
combine bye-bye
and i got at least
three collabs with japanese empires
planned in november at least but you
know it's gonna be more
and i got more i got more i got more
uh there will be some videos released
in november too videos
videos not streams videos of
uh different types you know
interesting videos can i please
i gotta move back okay
oh you can attack with who's who is
there why can't you attack
ah because of the sword of the creator
no no no we don't need that
you took this to the last hit thank you
aren't you guys interested november is
gonna be
fun november is gonna be lots of fun
he's almost dead what the hell who did
we kill him with
[Music]
i can't wait for october to end oh the
time is passing so fast and i don't know
if i like it or not
i don't know if i like what you're doing
thank you thanks for the super chat
what do you think uh what do you guys
think i'm planning for
for thanksgiving what do you think it is
guys
yes oh i keep on forgetting he's trying
to move again
stop attacking ferdinand
okay um interesting thoughts i will not
say anything
to your thoughts because they're wrong
you're all wrong but okay
there's nothing here huh okay we're
almost done with this map
talk show happens before thanksgiving
the first one it will happen before
[Music]
can you please heal ferdinand again he's
kind of
weak at the moment but
there we go
[Music]
um
ass boy
mvp petra
okay yeah keep on showing me her face
game thank you
keep on showing it to me i enjoy it
i'm so excited for november so excited
i'm so excited and i just can't hide it
i know i know i know i know i want to
i want to
oh birthday
i'm not gonna talk to you directly but
you can have some flowers whatever
just taking my she's taking my petrol
away from me
oh you're welcome
quest complete it is the end of the
month which means we will
have some story progress nice nice
timing
uh i guess oh we have to go straight for
the mission oh here we go
are we ready for this let's go
the monastery is shocked to learn that
sethuff's younger sister flynn has gone
missing
after an exhaustive search for clues you
finally come upon a lead oh yeah
for everyone who wasn't there in the
last stream
flame the little cute girl
with the green hair she got missing she
apparently got
um abducted kidnapped
so we will find her again certainly but
i didn't really have a draw
oh i guess i did okay certifications
now i'm in the way again
bottom right
almost how it's supposed to be and what
do i do
do i do all of them what what
she's a mercenary now do we
no wait ah oh yeah right that was our
problem we don't have seals
i cannot buy sales right now where are
they again
uh
we are at a stack of intermediate seals
because um yep
unfortunately unfortunately
where's my gold bullions sell that gold
selling gold for gold oops
yes thank you i have more
i got this one and i could sell all
those torches who needs those torches
what oh what about how do i use those
i don't use those anyway
[Music]
don't sell those yeah i'm not selling
those stunks
and okay i wanna um
do we maybe need some more uh
armor okay wait so she has enough
she could use
ask maybe what do you guys think
take samia seal off of her eh what does
it do
interference ah when we take it
oh wait so hey why does she have that
on her anyway okay wait how do i do this
how do i take it off of her how do i get
to her
how do i do that
without selling it menu
oh
okay
[Music]
okay and now we can
do the certification for one person who
do we want to do it for
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
but isn't she already an intermediate
something
isn't she um the second thing in the
second world
[Music]
yeah the edelgard oh yeah that's the
edelgard she's
she's still in the beginner thingy okay
armored knight
or brigand why is her cold
thing still the same does it not change
like the others
how you say it even
okay let's do this
[Music]
okay well that's all i can do
she has enough right
oh wait can we
can we um repair right now
blacksmith but we do forging not
repairing
right guys geez that's how we do
forge this boy
nice smart smart kiara
and
the steel lens but with what i can't see
this thing okay
interesting okay okay okay
um i would have to buy a steel axe first
right
for him i steal lance i would have to
buy first to be able to forge it
together
right is that it
no it
i thought you smoking stuff
do i have to buy sniffing stones now
where do i buy this mipping stone
shop
ah from missions request okay so i guess
wait it's fine
now we'll survive anyway
[Music]
let's go the underground chamber
special merchants ah safe i'm saving
guys i'm saving
promote sylvain yeah boy i need some
seals
chill i don't have any seals
okay i have beginner seals
wrong options
[Music]
but i can't imagine like any of those
characters
that we're like in the monastery being
bad characters that's
such a to me it's unexpected
emergency
like like like this dude who bet they
look
evil but they're probably just good
peeps no
uh hmm
[Music]
okay are we gonna fight him
again oh wait again i guess we didn't
we didn't really fight him last time did
we but we i think we did try to hit him
with bernie or so and it didn't really
go well
uh yeah sure um
[Music]
oops oh yeah whatever okay so we go here
we kill those
the roots we go here we kill those roots
then we go
here we kill that dude and probably this
will come from the side and then we go
for here
and we kill those dudes and then we go
down and we put those twos and then we
go through here and we kill those
no wait there's something here
wait wait wait wait wait wait because
there's a chest
wait why did i just see here's the chest
oh do i have to send someone for the
chest again
oh wait wait wait so that would be like
here here here
how do i get there is there i'm not
seeing
do i want this it looks like a lot of
effort to get there
teleporter ah
is that like looks like it's gonna take
a lot of time
two chests it's worth it
wait what what are what are the teleport
tiles
are those some teleport types no race is
death ooh
is that a teleport tile uh if i
activate it ah
um
it's a long mission
so probably eventually i would end up
here and teleport back here and then
move so we would we would need to send a
unit
that we don't need
but i i
think i need all of them
maybe maybe sylvain but do
would i want to send more than one why
the hell is edelgard unavailable
okay she's busy oh come on this is
important
someone get here
i don't know seems fine to me
if one person is spamming up what the
hell
don't confuse me saying i already saved
but okay
i think we can start fighting
that's fine begin the battle
defeat the death knight or root all
other enemies okay so we don't really
have to defend
[Music]
oh wait does that that one bring me over
here oh
and that and that one bro
probably brings me here oh that's not so
far
good luck wait what you can't
you can't go here but you can't go here
come on
that's annoying don't do it you have no
really okay
i don't need those things maybe
attack iron sword kill him
[Music]
as well nice
see
yeah it'll go like that i don't have
many spiders
i have a lot of lungs
[Music]
not many clothes come on
spiders
[Music]
is
nice kisokuni
receive dorky oh okay
stupid
don't confuse me please only write
f if if the stream is dead or something
ah what do i do how about
first hit with her
but i want to do something specific
nice and then i want to finish him off
ah wait how close does he have to go
ah damn it i wanna
[Music]
oh okay wait we move pilot first we move
bala wait
and then we'll finish him off
that works right
yes
[Music]
cannot leave anyone behind
what oh wait that's a special leg
damn it probably shouldn't have used the
special lens should i use the special
lens
yeah i think we're all quite equal
except for balof and ital guides
but other than that we're pretty equal
[Music]
use it try to save it okay
in this round i think
wait i killed all the enemies here right
what's with her hp why why are you her
hp
so that oh that's not her hp right
[Music]
really sorry i haven't really been doing
much with you these days
[Music]
foreign
um
what's gonna happen
oh you go here
oh wait i can see what's happening
what's gonna happen
that racist of evil has no effect on
flyers
wait isn't that a good thing
it raises my chance to avoid damage
right
no it's not a good thing
[Music]
yeah okay
because he was like oh be careful seems
like a good thing
oh guys by the way tomorrow i'm starting
a new game
thanks for joining the membership if you
saw my schedule
you know we're starting super mario
sunshine tomorrow
uh and people were like oh she thinks
it's gonna be easier but it's not but i
think
um it's going to be easier
because i played super mario sunshine
before i didn't finish it ever
i played it every now and then
it doesn't really do anything if i move
it on any ah actually it does
[Music]
avoidance and uh it's
one thing that is definitely easier to
get my sunshine is the camera and the
controls
and that's one thing why is she
attacking with that sort
it's not some special color
yeah and those are the things that
bothered me the most about super mario
64.
the controls in the camera they
[Music]
they made me so angry they triggered me
so hard like
and yeah and also i have more experience
with
super mario sunshine anyway
i think i played a little bit
baby when i was a child maybe
but i don't even remember it's been
so many years i mean i remember my my
brother playing it
but other than that yeah
[Music]
let's go for this one
i just love super mario sunshine because
the music
and the whole theme and the whole
atmosphere
i love it so much and it's like it has
so many
memories for me
and i'm a boomer i guess
i'll have a phoenix i've lived for
millions of years
why would you expect
it's moving moving forward nicely
you should probably change
[Music]
don't worry chad i gotcha
i got don't worry don't worry i know
what to do i know i need to heal my
petra
if she dies then we'll [\h__\h] oh let's
attack bernie
she's so strong holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay let's go here
oh yeah
should i always attack with the javelin
or should i attack with these
four ones like this
there we go
[Music]
okay let's go forward
and that's it you're dead oh
i guess not and wait how does this work
i have to open the door with him i guess
door oops ah i can't keep up
nice
is he going to attack pregnant then we
might as well go
in first or not
or not i'm a big
because he has already some damage
attack with balance
[Music]
yeah essentially the convoy i guess ash
yeah
oh yeah sure we're not gonna pick up
that chest anymore
it's too far anyway i guess
casper is like a cheerleader pretty much
yeah
3.99 damn
santoku
[Music]
okay
we're getting there my friends we're
getting there
unarchived karaoke stream we're getting
closer
which is i think what i decided to do
for the anniversary for the celebration
[Music]
again oh wait do i need
can i go for those doors
i need another door key who has the
other dorky does someone know
uh bad luck you're gonna go gotta go
here for a second
kinda annoying that i have to move them
dory oh and the opposite side is also
open
where does that thing go i wonder
she also has a key oh well
[Music]
assistant
thank you
[Music]
attack those beaches
ah
[Music]
oh wow
ouch i actually know i did no damage wow
you're weak let's finish them with
[Music]
bernie
i believe in your belly
uh wait sorry she's not doing anything
why did i bring life sophia when she's
not doing anything
i also feel like it's a waste to give
her any kills because she
will she's not a member of my team
this is how you broke my heart was a
critical hit man
it
let's kill him breakspeed
[Music]
let's get him down to nine
wow
and then let's finish him with
she can't
but she's stealing my wife my not
wife so
i don't like her anymore
[Music]
um
25 turns turn limits should be fine
i think
this turn is kind of boring nothing's
happening
just moving everyone wish i could move
them as a group
[Applause]
probably also because petra is on one of
those tiles i think
let's get these boys out of the way
these losers
he said i need to level
me go to cheers
i want to bring him closer but it's so
cramped
there's no space so so this is
distancing impossible on this map
how can i social distance like
there's no space
[Music]
okay what is her
green bar for anyway i still don't
understand
because if you would just listen to
yourself away from that
i need distance she hurts me so deeply i
mean citizens
[Music]
[Applause]
ah because she's not one of my own okay
but why is it uh
why is it not full because she should uh
it it wasn't full
from the beginning did she not have you
guys said it's not hp
i mean yeah she doesn't have full hp but
she did have a unfull
incomplete hp bar from the beginning
in that case you guys said it's not hp
i'm confused
too easily finally sylvain is
closer so let's do something with
sylvain
oh no that's a bruce
but i can repair it right it's possible
to repair
[Music]
should we go for it or
let's let's mix it up
and then finish him away
[Music]
uh
the convoy can be used by anyone right
here is so far away can you heal him
from here
all envelope oh okay so i gotta open it
with balance all right no problem
[Music]
no problem
i'm moving i'm moving
petra oh so she still has a key
okay sounds good to me
right
[Music]
let me tell you a story from my
childhood in birth school
uh you know how in sports class uh
what's it called physics
what what's it called
what's it called what's sports class
called
p.e physical education
when i was like really young uh
pe was like the scariest thing to me
because uh
we did like a lot of like uh
like parkour kind of stuff
like in the in the hall
and
and i just my whole life i still can't
do it
i cannot [\h__\h] do it at all
and every other child in my class was
able to do it
can you hear me what do you mean you
can't hear me over the game
what are you talking about
yes parkour
what
suddenly it's louder than me okay
yeah we did we did parkour in the hall
like in in the like in indoor parkour
like we just
did some small things there
what what
okay maybe not parkour in the way that
you're thinking of it's just like uh
like jumping over something and then
rolling
and then uh going left right left right
and stuff like that you know
shoot obstacle run yeah something like
that that's
pokorman that's pecor
anyway so we did that like pretty often
i hated it so much because
oh because
often they would ask us to do a back
side
back back side roll like back backwards
roll
so from your head backwards
understand what i'm talking about and
yeah i just
still up up until this point i cannot do
it i don't know how to do it
it scares me the thought of doing it
scares me so much
a barrier barrel roll not a back flip
back roll
no not a back flip no not jumping
why are we having these communication
issues
i never look back
no not the cartwheel you know a
summerslam
yeah it's just when you when you when
you running when you when you when you
um
you go down and then you
roll backwards
inverted car no not a car why
are you guys misunderstanding me on
purpose
i don't even know anymore anyway i just
wanted to talk about
me not being able to do that and then
um me being scared to go to
a physical education class
every time when i was a child
it was the most horrifying thing for me
and like every other child in in my
class was able to do it
except me i was so scared do it i was so
scared
and i was also scared to fail so i was
all i was sometimes trying to like
run over the obstacle without doing the
the flip uh
not a flip the bat back row without
having people notice it
[\h__\h] you can't do the door i can't guess
pressure has to do the door
ah this is stupid this is stupid
how many of your classmates are 400k
features now i wonder i wonder
okay wait am i
is this dude strong he looks kind of
strong this is probably a weak ass
piece of [\h__\h]
that's
[Music]
language
let's kill him with him i hope that
makes sense
constantly but i i do still think that
this has to do something with
the fact that i uh did the
the luck plus two uh cooking thing
because it was i got so many crits last
time as well
when i did it the month before
wait was bernie able to attack someone
oh no
the whole group is like lagging behind
even though i'm moving them closely
always
physical education class man i hated it
but you know as a girl there's there's
one thing you can always do
you can cheat you can say ah
i got my period i don't feel so well i
will rest
in today's oh yes every girl does it at
least
one two or three times every girl does
this
one more thing sometimes um especially
especially in summer time uh
our teachers and students would think it
would be
fun to go uh have
um instead of the physical education to
go swimming
no cure and i was and still
am a bad swimmer and
so pretty much every physical education
class
where we had to go swimming i
had my period
oh what a coincidence oh what a
coincidence
she's gonna do what
why is she gonna die if she does that
yeah but every girl does it i swear to
you every girl does it
even the even if the girls can't swim i
was just the best swim i was just really
scared of being like
being exposed in front of everyone
because i was already the unpopular girl
in the class
i was really unpopular at school
maybe not later on but in
in like uh what's the thing called
nah i guess yeah junior or high school i
was unpopular i was so
unpopular in january he's almost dead
um i need to focus though
why is he gonna die oh let's do this one
wait that doesn't even do much
nevermind stay there stay there
let's bring out petra
oh you can't detect though
how about now okay
[Music]
attack first oh yeah right if she
doesn't miss
okay okay we say
end of map end of game
wait what was i talking about i was the
unpopular one but where was i going with
that
[Music]
you're running away again
just face me now face me now
i'm ready man i'm here and came all the
way for this stupid [\h__\h] maze and you
run away again like a little [\h__\h]
man
[Music]
um language kia yes nvp
balance that's what i would say
yay
nice nice the month is over
okay not bad
[Music]
my
um
i know she was busy but that's sas
well we still don't know if it was
jaritza or do we
[Music]
show me the face maybe
i'm just happy
um
foreign
[Music]
hmm
can i fight with her
[Music]
oh yeah would be my pleasure
oh
dedicated healer dancer
hi mama
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
thank you
um
is
[Music]
are you like watching two windows
thank you for watching my stream too
[Music]
foreign
i i was so busy talking to the chat i'm
not sure what exactly happened but my
papa is leaving
why you leave me and he hid something in
the room
in his room
[Music]
just watching me oh thank you
only me thank you
so much
they be chilling what a beautiful piece
of art
okay we have finished another month
it's just cute wait what is is that from
this just monica thing but just monika
where did that come from is that a game
i've i heard it before
[Music]
uh
ah okay okay i i thought it was a doki
doki literature
clip because there's like this monika
chick that's really crazy right i didn't
play it but i know she's crazy
i know she's kind of insane
caspar would like to speak with me is he
gonna confront me about
not taking him on any missions
she's like me
what do you mean
come on you must be joking
casper wants to quit well we'll talk
with
him
i'm sorry casper
oh
[Music]
suspicion isn't enough to go on
uh-huh
yeah he's doing tasks he's just doing
tasks
you need to come down oh the path is
working leads to
[Music]
yoga
wow okay what do you think he's gonna do
with them
he's probably just a good guy
yes why did you not listen to me
wow he's very um
[Music]
you gotta feel it
foreign
[Music]
i will take responsibility
yo
[Music]
bye bye casper it was nice knowing you
oh he likes me
well there's a lot of events on sunday
what's what's happening now
bernadetta oh yeah let's go see
[Music]
bernadetta
yes stay inside
stay inside everyone it's better inside
for many reasons
you can take responsibility for me any
time
what what
who tied you to your chair who
[Music]
who
wow
[Music]
[\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
in a bag
no one hates you
[Music]
oh
don't apologize
b b
i can marry bernie now b
support level b support level b
be
she's straight
okay
[Music]
uh
didn't we already do that
okay that was a small version oh okay
okay
[Music]
foreign
what was wrong about that what was wrong
about that
[Music]
anyway let's go fishing
i saved all my baits for this day
let's explore
[Music]
up
when can i make a move on you surface i
want to make a move on you
okay oops how do i do the map again
okay okay but uh
wow we need to talk it's the beginning
of the month we need to talk to everyone
here
everyone
fish
[Music]
anything here no
hello hello come to brazil i love when
people tell me to come to brazil but
i've already visited brazil before
[Music]
you didn't think of that huh
didn't think of that dude didn't think i
came to brazil before
it was amazing i went two times actually
but i've been to brazil two times
[Music]
i ate trudeau
and what's it called that what's uh in
sao paulo
in sao paulo there's a
huge shopping mall
and there's this uh i don't know
japanese
kind of um
area
okay let's go fishing
fishing fishing fishing
yes
okay i got a bunch of them okay okay
let's go fishing i forgot how to fish
but let's do it
no
yes
oh wait i should what i need to accept
the request oh
god damn it hey i thought i was already
participating okay
[Music]
okay this is like animal crossing
okay now i do fishing no or do i do it
on my own
nah do it again right
okay let's go again fishing fishing
fishing
no wait for it
yes
[Laughter]
next
wait can i already win with that i
wonder
uh no thank you
no thank you
wrong bait
oh tournament bit boy
okay
no yes
hey hey hey
hey hey
[Music]
huge fallen carb
am i already winning with that is there
like a specific fish that i will win
with
do i do more can i use them after this
tournament too
wait for gold okay need gold okay
no no
no
no next stop
goddammit
[Music]
damn this one is so fast
that was fast wait
toy tattoo spike nice
but not what i wanted gentlemen
ah
next one
oh wait but i need to i need to wait for
golden anyway right so it doesn't even
make sense
but i can probably use the fish
afterwards too right can i use the fish
after the tournament for cooking or
whatever
or like selling them
i can stop already but didn't you tell
me i need a
golden one talk around the pond first
really do i need that i got it
i got it already
it's like a rhythm game
i need to talk to them i got the five
star gatcha fish
okay what about you
[Music]
oh
give me something give me your heart
iron sword man
okay i'll
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] i should have maybe still asked
him oh well i think i'm or did i already
talk to everyone
anyway
oh my god okay
good
[Music]
that's all right i'll keep the rest of
the bait for oh hello i guess you
existed
but no okay
[Music]
hello greenhouse i would like to do some
gardening
i would like to do some harvesting
and i would like to do some planting
[Music]
we have so many seeds but so little
space
how can i how can i plant more than that
is that not possible
scatter bone meal okay
sure we got the money spread your seeds
oh i'm trying i'm trying
[Music]
i'm sticking your surface yeah
i think sophist is the one
it's already over i already won my
friends i already won
okay who else wants to talk to me
[Music]
you're willing to serve as a fishing
guide thank you
ingrid is so cute yeah should we invite
her to tea
should we
[Music]
not able to make it nanda
why can't i do it with ingrid i really
like ingrid
why are you all like distancing yourself
from me
[Music]
that's so depressing everyone rejects me
why does everyone reject me
shut up petra by the way guys
ever since last stream i was like really
really sad okay i was so sad
and then um
the voice the english voice actress from
[Music]
i didn't even i didn't write to her but
she replied to my tweet where i was like
sad about not being able to marry petra
yeah that was very surprising anyway but
i don't i don't really want anything
from you thanks though
uh hello hello let's have some oops
sorry let's have some food
[Music]
yep
she told me that petra loves me anyway
and if the voice actions from petra
tells me so i think it's
it's true
as a friend no no no no no that's not
what she meant
that's not right
i'm gonna do this every month now i'm
gonna cook um
the luck lucky thing
the blessed jelly this is the reason why
i get so many crits i'm sure of it
actually no i didn't even hear that
english voices
love you as a friend no no no no no no
no
no no no no
no it's not yeah it's not the reason why
i get the crits
i think it is do
wait is no one here
everyone is at the fishing tournament
huh
[Music]
i don't need lands do i
who wants to talk to me you oh hi
hi
i rarely see uh people with orange eyes
ever
nice eye color but nothing
nothing
nothing can beat these beautiful
purple eyes that look
like the universe
right my chat stopped i don't know if
you guys are all asleep or
if it stopped but it stopped
[Music]
for when my chat is dead
oh i think it moved again yay
[Music]
look i'm looking at you don't do
anything stupid
i'm looking at you
okay back to normal
i'm moving so many things where am i
where am i
here i am hello
too close what do you mean too close
are you embarrassed because i got too
close to you
don't be shy anyway
[Music]
i don't know what are we talking about
don't worry about it
does anything belong to you oh what's
the first item
nice actually yeah let's ask the others
too there's
like so many on on the fishing punch
field
i was just randomly i'm gonna ask her
for all those items again
[Music]
useless
wow quality content right there
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
i know what you i well petra
you know why i got it first try because
i went for your belongings before
when you went in your room oh my god i
went through it
ah
thanks for your help ashley i ask you
yet
do i have something from you
is there a possibility the possibility
that i have something from him
by the way what can you teach me lance
axe heavy armor horse should i
learn something from him
this is the quality content i'm hearing
for right
horse is pretty good no no oh yeah
okay
[Music]
thank you for taking that off of me my i
have some pretty heavy
luggage with me i need to get rid of
some of that
[Music]
is this how everyone does it i always
wonder
okay next stop actually bernie do i have
something
from you can i do i always have to talk
to you for the door
can you at least open the door cemented
[Music]
no
welcome to the membership
okay what do we do
now oh there's some people oh wait how
do i get there
[Music]
item i
saw that from the corner of my eye i
have the eyes of the hulk
but i am a phoenix some of you might
think i'm a chicken
but i'm a phoenix yup
since yesterday people are hatching
everyone who was a member from the first
day
is hatching yay congratulations on
hatching
[Music]
foreign
means a lost item or something you
dropped somewhere
something dropped and mono is something
like an object or
yeah so it's a dropped object
[Music]
you are welcome go flex your japanese
skills with someone else
by any chance do i have a otosimo from
you
welcome to the membership
thank you for joining everyone thank you
i'm gonna teach you german too
uh for members only eventually
and then tell me did
[Music]
what what am i saying
to me to me to me
to me for me
[Music]
i thought that the perfume would at
least be yours but okay if you don't
want it i'll use it
okay if you would imagine
the holy yen girls uh
a person per
personified as a perfume
what do you think the
smell would be thank you for the red
super chat
teaching japanese y'all might be in
might be a possible stream in the future
yeah
yeah gravy shut up give me something
more beautiful
and shiny as i am
hi i would say
you know how there's like a like ocean
ocean smelling
uh she won't smell like the ocean but
like not like
a real ocean but there's like uh
air refresheners
that i like call like ocean something
ocean breeze oh yeah glad would be ocean
breeze
what would ena smell like what would be
an inner perfume
you know you know you know you know
lavender lavender lavender because
yeah first of all she's purple second of
all she calms us all down that's so
perfect
in a perfume lavender but that's not
that's actually more like a air
a room room perfume more than like a
body perfume right
anyway that's perfect
well first of all me should be orange
orange i would say orange okay
should be a refreshing orange
that gives you energy so for ame
orange is taking so something like yeah
citrus citrus or or
coffee because she's so like crazy and
energetic
so coffee would be fitting but
um citrus may be better
right okay and cali should be roses
oh yes
scent of romans exactly
wait there's some people uh over there
wait what how do i get there not like
that
cali is easy
oh thank you for the early celebrations
of the chad
oh training ground oh yeah bye hello
do you have something from you what
motivation also increased very well you
shall fight for me hubert
fight for me
cute
[Music]
evaluating
reminds me of a new character from
a certain game
yeah she's no petra yeah anyway
got some items
that's a new item where
[Music]
now
does she automatically join the house
that you play in
no no she's not playable what
okay sad
i wonder what class she is what's going
on here
uh what house is her sword tournament
sword
my strongest sword
[Music]
fighter is wait ill guard does she not
i thought she fights with the axe right
oh yeah petra she's strong as [\h__\h]
true let's go petra make me proud
hi tall
[Music]
gumball
making myself a bit smaller hey
hey
[Music]
it's almost dead wait
the flag
bye-bye marianne it was nice
having you in this tournament you guys
are weak as
i will love you forever just how i love
my baby kelly oh wait
wait oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
i should have healed but even then she
was so weak
[Music]
can i do it can i do it again
oh i can i'm going in again
oh i don't care about those points
i will not take this and defeat
i refuse to accept it
i will fight to dimitri i will hear
myself next time
i don't care about those activity points
it's all right
yeah okay
okay we store
yes now here we go let's see if we still
lose please no huh
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah
we start but can we that was close can
we win against clock
especially because probably
[Music]
okay ah
against claude but he's still
level me
i'll be able to be happy but we are the
first hit
and there we go
oh another one can i heal again
no no more healing [\h__\h]
[Music]
mojito
is that the last one wait 11 31
ex wait wait wait wait what level 31
what
mandato
okay let's go i have no choice
if i would have been healed this i would
have won
was it worth it i don't know was that
worth it
[Music]
okay what's next
there's something there
[Music]
there's something here
who wants to talk to me there
oh marianne let's check out marianne
see you oh yeah
of course i'm always praying so that
petra
ends up being into
[Music]
give a moment to chat
she's very chatty
oh let me teach you
oh another sad story coming no no reason
i hatched mom kara welcome to the world
write it down in your calendar
[Music]
they're hiding in the shadows japan bros
hiding in the shadows not coming
it is what it is
oh
thank you oh an item
nice let's see
[Music]
where do we go let's go that way and
then that way there's a lot of people
who want to talk to me over there
um
how do you feel after i smashed you to
the ground
oh i didn't but how does it feel how
does it feel being smashed by petra tell
me tell me tell me i want to know i want
to know i want to know i want to know
[Music]
there's nothing i want to know more in
this world than that
[Music]
ah
i see a spider on my window
but i will ignore it because it's small
[Music]
oh i guess my business is done here
yep my business is done let's go to
the cathedral
smalls buddha
kill it with fire it will only create
more spiders it will multiply into
thousands of spiders
oh yeah we should ask someone for
assistance
who should we ask for assistance this
month someone useful
maybe we should be asked
[Music]
okay i guess not let me see this
i feel like we didn't we have her before
no problem it's not like i wanted you in
my team anyway
it's not it's not like i wanted you
let's sing now i need to be on the right
side again
i don't see anything
[Music]
let's use these
in the middle it seems kind of weird to
be in the middle because then i would be
covering up
the speech bubbles
[Music]
maybe
foreign i'll stay here then
okay this is weird
excellent this is how things are
supposed to be
pond liver called aldo becky
uh this is a bit confusing though also i
cannot see the map
right now let's go here
actually this is this may be this is
probably the best spot because then i
cover up the calendar who no one cares
about
which no one cares about
it isn't there something here
there's a mark on the map
maybe not
[Music]
top left
wait being what was it again top
top top
top for yourself being being innocent
right being pure and the right was being
uh smart
letter to who
what what who
who do you want me to bring a letter to
you
nothing going on here
japanese bro asking me if i if i'm a bat
because i'm hanging from the top no i'm
a phoenix
[Music]
somebody once told me we should watch
shrek together who is up for watching
shrek together
oh yeah let's watch let's watch it
[Music]
i think i'm done in the church uh
there's something happening here
wait i still don't know how to ask for
this mom's assistance
who yo gatekeeper what up banish the
balance no problem my friend
leave it to me
hilda but does it even make sense
because i can never recruit her anyway
okay what do we want to do here
[Music]
um
anything else
[Music]
people who come into the stream now i
wonder what they're thinking
[Music]
do i want anything i think i still have
a [\h__\h] ton of
tea and actually a lot of smoking stuff
you
m
[Music]
seeds oh i have way too many seeds and
gifts oh yeah but i still
i think i have still a lot of gifts
because i bought so many last time
i think that's all i need right
wait there should be a thing here
some kind of dialogue oh it's
you sure talk to me
what
[Music]
are you jealous
top left
who wants me to come down and who wants
me to
[Music]
step
oh
[Music]
what is the problem with him i'm not
worried
what is it like trying to start a fight
foreign
oh that increased our friendship it
seemed very
uh awkward to me
where's thomas got it
[Music]
okay
anti-gravity
[Music]
be
[Laughter]
he got so excited hey fellaini let me
give something to you
um wait what is at the top
[Music]
actually i don't know what you like
i here take this
bye bye final nand have a nice day
understandable have a nice day
okay wait who did i not talk to yet
oops what okay felix
oh i didn't talk to any of those
he likes tea leaves
[Music]
i have a letter for you guys
oh they don't want it to be delivered
yet okay what about this
i have so many things with her name i
don't know who they belong to
deep connection emotional attachment
what if it's the same person or a
different person
cyril what
you get down from there no i don't wanna
come down
[Music]
you cannot force me to come down
although all the blood that is getting
to my head makes me feel a bit dizzy
my young lady get down here this instant
no i don't wanna go down
[Music]
you're not my mom
[Laughter]
it's not a face mom i'm just like this
it's not a face
maybe this
i know
yeah okay good
and she likes me
ding dong
[Music]
what
everyone wants to talk to me i'm so
popular
papa don't leave me
[Music]
uh
revenge how dare he hurt such a
beautiful woman
how dare he oh here oh wait look
here someone is here
[Music]
wait where is that speech bubble
supposed to be
[Music]
actually i just tried to not cover up
anything important on the screen and i
have to i had to keep
on switching between left bottom left
and bottom right so i decided to just go
to the top because here i don't cover up
anything important
oh we're halfway there
[Music]
[Laughter]
nice
okay it looks
what a banger
maybe i'm in brazil right now
because usually i'm in japan
[Music]
but the other side of the world is
brazil
wait where's jorita oh thank you for the
super chat
i read it i read that whole message
later on
why do you guys say australia in my
logic it's gotta be brazil
hello
oh that was quick that's all i want
okay uh did we talk to everyone now
400 don't no maybe someone unsubscribes
now don't
wait it has to be a bit more than 400k
before i celebrate
because maybe someone unsubscribes and
then it's not and then that's
embarrassing
no no no that's embarrassing if someone
leaves now
we're still at a sensitive point
[Music]
who can we not talk to i think we talk
to everyone
oh thank you for the super chat ah wait
[Music]
okay thank you guys
thank you
well last one two reach 400k
again yay
thank you guys thank you thank you
it's a it's a big number
where are they thank you for the super
chats
thank you where are they
[Music]
yes we're top we're top left today for a
little while
your hair should be falling down i can't
do that but i can't let my
my my hats drop
[Laughter]
[Music]
i don't know um i already planned out
the whole week so for the celebration
stream i'm not sure if i should push it
in
uh somewhere this week or
[Music]
or if i do it next week
i'll check my schedule and we'll figure
something out
[Music]
gorilla celebration
thank you thank you thank you thank you
i think i'm done with exploring no wait
no i think i'm done
okay ah thank you thank you
thank you for the super chat thank you
thank you for the congratulations
[Music]
all people who woke up and finally came
to the stream welcome
maybe i should turn around again
actually i enjoy being up here but
i guess i'll turn around
hi
yep
you for the congratulations i'm bottom
i'm bottom right i'll be bottom right
no i don't want to go back to bottom
left no
thank you thank you
[Music]
i think we're done
because of copyright reasons
it's difficult to figure out the time
when i should do it
like i've been streaming uh
like during japanese prime time a lot
and i know usually that is a difficult
time for
but i think i i established a viewership
during that time zone
by now so maybe it's the right time
there will always be people who can't
watch it and especially with unarchived
streams
that's kind of sad
you all gotta wake up
[Music]
okay i'll try to do it on the weekend
then although my weekend is already kind
of busy
thank you for the super chats again wait
400 damn
thank you siren
i keep on forgetting the words
[Music]
that is so
this word i've asked you guys so many
times
[Music]
otherwise one day when i reach one
million you will have to donate 1 000.
that's not good we don't want that day
to come
thank you
challenge accepted
what oh man there's so many
[Music]
that's more than enough anyway more way
more than enough
doing way way way too much
i'll get the college fund no no no no no
no no
no need for that
[Music]
to doing the super chat reading after
dance
foreign
[Music]
thank you guys where did you all
suddenly come from the viewership
suddenly went
up from below six thousand
to eight thousands
[Music]
wait she ended right when i got 400.
thank you for the super day
[Music]
the have arrived
oh
[Music]
i'm doing my best to make my papa proud
don't aim for it you might get something
else you might get the opposition
[Music]
and we keep on listening to those
support
chats
those who are interesting
sounds like a win-win
[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
he said something completely different
in japanese
[Music]
foreign
thank you for the congratulations all of
you thank you so much
[Music]
okay wait are they gonna marry each
other if i don't stop them
[Music]
are they gonna marry each other if i get
them too high
oh [\h__\h] i don't want that to happen i
mean i'm not going to marry edelgard but
yes no i don't want that to happen
freddie who do you want to talk to with
dorothea okay go ahead
[Music]
yes i love flowers too
it's been a while since i last received
flowers
[Music]
do i have a favorite flower not really
not really
[Music]
i like all
i didn't know that was a thing
[Music]
beautiful very beautiful thank you chad
thank you
[Music]
i would ship those two i wouldn't mind
it
i'll allow it as long as dorothea
doesn't marry petra
you cape are you okay bernie
next sylvain talk to
dorothea
[Music]
um
uh
[Music]
foreign
you don't know what love is let me tell
you what love is
love is when
[Music]
love is novice
oh [\h__\h] no no don't make them
[Music]
is
okay
[Music]
no
what do you mean
[Music]
accept it accept and know
thank you for the super chat
no i will never let them speak to each
other
ever again and on the battlefield they
shall be far apart from each other too
it's unacceptable
still so many what the hell
okay let's go
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
yeah what the hell man
i'm hungry i'm so hungry
let's snack
[Music]
oh my my stomach said something
he said
it's eat chocolate
[Music]
hmm what
you are not
[Music]
foreign
um
thank you for the super chat oh i want
to do super chat reading ah
can i do you mind if i do the rest of
these off stream
maybe go into super chat reading already
and then continue
until something in the story happens off
stream
yeah i should probably do the rest of
stream it takes so much time
you guys are probably bored bored by all
of this
[Music]
hello owl i like owls you too cute and
fluffy
okay in that case
let's uh go read all your super sweet
super chats
wow
wow wow wow okay everyone are you ready
to change
the screen are you ready
[Music]
uh wait how do i save
save one second
save and yep
hello oh oh yeah wait i need to show you
i need to show you some sweets that's
not the one that's
the one from last time
i need to show you sweets
what do you need to say guys you need to
need to ask me trick or treat
that's right that's right let me
show you oh
how about how about this one
hi take it
to the puzzle another part of our
trick-or-treat halloween piece thingy
screenshotted it do you have it i can
also
try to show it on a black screen if that
helps there you go
yep by the way let's get uh rid of this
beautiful art
from yoona best art
are you done okay
okay
next door was it this one yep
super chat reading
hi er where did i stop last time i think
i did read it until the end
from last stream pretty sure yep
so i will just read the ones from this
stream
and let's get some bgm going
bgmo
yay
[Music]
i'll keep this one up here
and make myself a bit bigger where am i
there i am
like this
you're here to be jam maybe a bit louder
[Music]
now let me scroll i have to scroll
this is gonna looks like it's going to
be a wholesome
super chat reading better not make me
cry
with your words guys
[Music]
thank you for your number four eleven
duncan
bernie is not best girl she's one of the
bestest girls for sure
jacqueline duncan vegan referee eleven
duncashin
secret super boss of the best girls yeah
ferdinand von eger
generally the heart may be crushed the
soul
smashed but the will to carry on and the
fight is as sharp
as a plate fresh from the forge for love
and glory we shall never stop
we are kfp viva
i agree strongly thank you general
picolin
gustavo romero five zero
nine thank you robot duncan
i need to work on uh
on uh soundproofing in my house by the
way because i hear
when someone's like outside in front of
my house i hear their voices so i guess
they probably hear me too right now
but i was checking for amazon what to
buy and it's like
more expensive than i thought and then
it's a bit confusing because some things
are like
soundproofing but it's more like
acoustic material apparently
and and they say it doesn't really work
for soundproofing so i'm a bit confused
i saw also by the way i saw there's like
even sound proofing curtains but that's
[\h__\h] right that doesn't work right
does that work like maybe a little bit
it works kind of but not really it helps
[Music]
hmm
every bit helps i was thinking like um
the walls my house is like the one that
i
live in now that i moved into recently
the walls are
uh so um they like
if you touch them the it kind of like
crumbles off so i don't think i can put
any
soundproofing stuff on it
now it's not it's not really paper thin
i mean like that the wallpaper itself
is like crumbling off
yeah um it's a really old house a really
old house
so i can't really like put anything on
that like
it won't it won't stick you know sounds
dangerous
but i think i can put it on the windows
at least and i think the windows might
be the biggest problem anyway
so if i put a soundproofing foam
on top of like all of the windows and
then
over that soundproofing curtains
maybe that's gonna help because i i do
feel like most of the sound
goes through the the windows
doesn't sound safe and it's just the
wallpaper not the wall itself
the the thing that's crumbling i thought
it's a very cheap house yes otherwise i
wouldn't be able to
to rent a house so it's kind of like um
a special deal because i only stay for
another five months
just like in between rent you know
now i'm moving out again in what how
long is it
probably like five months or so but it's
almost november
so that's oh no not not even only
december january february
only three months what the hell wait no
no no no four months four months four
months
november december january february yeah
i will not say a price but it's very
cheap
i wouldn't be able to afford a house
right now at all
a normal house
i'm abandoned
400k congratulations thank you thick
curtains installed on each wall around
the room
that's difficult then i have to like
install like like like
curtain things everywhere i don't know
how to do that
a haunted house it feels like it
sometimes yeah
it does feel like it sometimes it feels
a bit lonely too
yeah my computer is facing the wall yeah
was thinking of like um
these things that the soundproofing
things that you put around the
microphone
but then i realized wait then i don't
see the screen anymore
because it's gonna be like a huge thing
i'll figure something out i hope
callie is busy stop stop telling me to
like
do something with cali she's busy
she's busy making a song for halloween
man
anyway where was i sanji shawn duncan
dreamy robot thank you
wait did i read though did you scroll
too much
gustavo romero thank you and save
thank you for your great content you
produced so far and for the great
community
keep it up we are going to top right or
bottom left
can't be together we might yay thank you
yellow yellow thank you shane i'm very
happy i can make your stream live for
once it's 8 00 p.m for me here
oh nicely i love seeing your streams a
lot your personality is so infectious
thank you for being you
mwah thank you so much i'm so glad you
could come to my stream that is what i
was trying to do by choosing this time
slot
yeah account name thank you
thank you for the lunch time stream you
mentioned every strangle
struggles on views but sending
appreciation for rifle chess yeah thank
you so much
actually if i compared
it to my fire emblem streams previously
actually it didn't have any effect now
that i think about it
the different time slots didn't have any
effect
huh i
guess so it doesn't matter when i stream
does it just not matter fire emblem will
will never be popular with you guys
would it never be good enough for you
guys
oh
well everyone who's here now i'm glad
you appreciate it
i don't know
i don't know man i don't know
oh well
thanks for joining the membership
i'll be here regardless of what time i
stream thank you
rico
[Music]
super glad you're streaming earlier so i
can watch live i actually went out and
bought the game after watching you play
oh
thank you so much thank you thank you
calvin thank you
multiculturalism
no thank you thank you for the
preemptive congratulations
i absolutely love the fire emblem series
been playing since game boy advances oh
this is one of the reasons why you're my
favorite i hope you keep enjoying the
game
thank you oh i'm glad some people enjoy
it thank you so much
keep on spamming the younger dangerous
chat keep on keep it going
[Music]
election
usually happen just as i wake up for
rick which is awesome while work spins
up the tonight work froze me
on the night shift so when i wake up to
you every stream okay
good morning
cage dennis thank you oh
happy birthday yesterday
happy birthday
thank you for watching my stream
jacqueline
black knight thank you michael milner
fluttering asmr i wanted to thank you
for streaming i struggle frequently with
self-harm oh
and your streams have stopped me from
doing it many times because of you
i haven't self-harmed in over a month oh
wow that's a
oh
i'm glad i can help please don't harm
yourself
please don't time yourself
then keep on watching kiara i'll do my
best to stream 24 hours a day
[Music]
uh you are representing kfp on
a good ass and longest stream welcome
back
joe saw him down shame about what
happened last room with petra i had this
i had the same experience as male 1
of claude oh here's to helping the rest
of the playful girls better from here
yes hopefully no more broken hearts
please no more
thank you thank you thank you for the
red super chat
how do you pronounce the h after an l
in portuguese how do you say it
leo okay
bernie is great yes yes yes lunchbox
thank you lunchbox
[Music]
yeah i mean i enjoy playing fire and
blime a lot but
i would also enjoy just playing it off
stream
it's just a bit a bit sad to see
that huge gap to when i play
fire emblem compared to when i play like
whatever minecraft
it's uh it's sad to see that gap
but i'll keep it going until the end
i'll keep it going
[Music]
foreign to celebrate your hatching yay
happy hatching day
after gap let's finish this yeah
everyone who's here please stay with me
until the end of fire emblem at least
you guys gotta stay with me
please thank you
can you teach us japanese maybe in the
future i will do a
japanese teaching stream if that's
something you guys are interested in
maybe maybe pedro fernando dan question
imagined
shin tempura danger
[Music]
a name i cannot read because it's
russian
i just want to say that i have the
impression of you as a kind and
responsive girl
be healthy and happy and i am happy to
support you
thank you so much
from the best thank you very much
good morning i got up at 3 30 am just to
catch the stream but i'll have to go to
work now oh
congrats in front okay thank you devon
thank you
thank you mtk
new york
[Music]
m
i had a night shift until now and i'm
happy that i can see you until i go to
sleep
you are the first youtuber where i
became a member and want to spend some
money
thank you so much thank you i'm glad for
your support
thank you for everything and keep who
you are missed you your yesterday missed
you yesterday
thank you thank you shane thank you for
your support
thank you rolo thank
oh here comes the here the the the 400k
congratulations super chats start here
i just want to say that i'm really happy
for my best youtuber the source of my
everyday
motivation oh hope you can really grows
more sore hi kiara thank you
thank you
[Music]
i think that's a red super chat i think
if i get the currency right
eden exiled on kashin dance dan kashin
rico
danke
[Music]
russian name i cannot read uh danger
warlock warlords thank you lord pimple
thank you
scooby doo you saved my marriage
my wife thought i was crazy when i
started watching her life but i made her
watch one of your streams and now she
understands
yes i'm good with with the wives i'm
good with the mothers
of course she understands hello wifey
how you doing please forgive your man
however
if he watches the streams more than he
watches you then
bonk him bunk
give him a good book thank you
[Music]
congratulations stancho 400k it's just a
number what you're doing for everyone is
much more meaningful we don't have a
we have we don't have to celebrate right
away yeah i'll try to
check my schedule and see if we can find
a good day for it
thank you chase master dan kishan
thank you what a simp kfb navy admiral
dankeshen to be
thank you thank you queen
thank you
soon thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
video
congrats on free 400k i can't think of
anyone who deserves it more
you've come incredibly far since your
debut but your adventure is still just
starting
here's celebrating the smile song and
many many more to come
thank you thank you
thank you for your kindness always
signboard thank you crispy dankeshen
kfb employee ashley thank you
thank you catherine van gogh thank you
so much
thank you for following me and
supporting me thank you
manchester lord kfc duncan the elemental
thank you shane antique stun cushion
looking for the top thank you
hello i noticed a lot of your audience
are girls
you sure about that now that you went
from unpopular
to 400k subs youtuber in record time
what would your advice to all unpopular
girls in your audience be
shout outs to all on puppy you mean
because of this stuff i talked about
uh being unpopular in school
issues
advice i don't think there's many girls
watching my streams to be honest but
um huh
being um the unpopular one in school
i know it's tough and now it feels like
[\h__\h]
i know but you'll get through it and
eventually you'll end up being super
popular like me and i don't know you
know
children are just sometimes just
such idiots like they bully you for no
good [\h__\h] reason it's ridiculous
you're smarter than them the reason that
you're the unpopular one is because
usually it's because you're the smarter
one
and we all know it's true
so one day you'll rise above them
and you'll you can look down at them the
way they that they look down
at you at that point and then you can
say well [\h__\h]
look at where i am now
[Laughter]
yep
however most likely you'll not have
contact with anyone from school
ever again just like me
once those four or eight years or
whatever are over you'll probably never
see them again
so just i know it's hard to try to get
through it
you'll get through it eventually just
focus on school focus on making it
through to school try to focus on that
there's nothing bad about being smart
there's nothing bad about doing your
homework
focus
and thanks thank you thank you for the
huge super job
ah congratulations on for your pay
attention
thank you for your streams they always
make my day keep being awesome
really i make someone's day
i try my best thank you thank you
thank you
wait i like what what i'm back to 3.99
someone wrote it in the chat
see this is what i didn't want to happen
maybe i was trolled was i trolled
yeah it's on my screen too
uh
i know four hundred thousand
sixty-five
could uh instantly change if 65 people
decide to unsubscribe and
want to make me cry
oh no it's uh four hundred thousand
eighty two now
okay it's a growing not not
uh not
the opposite okay stay there stay there
no no no
don't tell me guys
max 8413
don't say again don't say again
no
[Music]
thank you cut out thank you
you're the morning sun that shines so
bright and also burns me
but just cannot have enough of you
please keep doing the great work
you do and just be yourself no matter
what thank you
thank you thanks jenkins thank you
fire holder one time thank you for the
red super chat
thank you fluviophile thank you sharon
thank you
[Music]
red super chat from papa
thank you
[Music]
here's my first red super chat you have
done such an amazing job and i will
continue to support you
you've really helped me in such tough
times and i cannot thank you enough
keep on rising higher and higher
attention thank you so much for your
support always
also i love your your icon it's one of
my favorite fan arts that i've received
one of my top 5 favorite fan arts that i
ever received
[Music]
so i like seeing your face
thank you so much for being my source of
motivation you're amazing
enthusiastic funny and so lovable don't
doubt yourself and be confident i'm sure
everyone would love your wholesome
personality continue being the mood
booster
thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you
thank you for your support
hydration check
them
um that was not much my bottle is empty
okay i'm almost at the end
ah
hello
what was that word again uh
[Music]
uh when someone is um
like irreplaceable and only that like
who's
like i
can't think of the word
[Music]
but irreplaceable yeah no not precious
unique unique yes thank you guys thank
you you guys are so great
you're so good at guessing words
unique
okay
thank you and the rest of the gang for
these dreams and for bringing joy in
these travel times your successive
friendship
are inspiring to see best of luck for
your futures
thank you thank you for your support
thank you dds
[Music]
i'm at work so i can't watch but i'm
listening it's gone so fast
already at 400k i'm happy but i'm
worried that the more popular you get
the fainter our individual presence will
be you should try
valkyra chronicles it's one of favorites
yeah maybe in the future
and uh there's already a bunch of you
that i remember
very well so i don't think i'll forget
about you guys
so don't do anything stupid
keep on spamming the duncan's chat no
slacking off why do i have to keep on
reminding you anyway
thank you thank you call galleon dan
kashin mario albera dan kashin i love
refrigerators thank you
thank you mario olvera many times thank
you
your translations have been a blessing
but you're worth so much more than that
to us
thank you your personality shines so
bright in all of your streams
have been such a joy to watch
congratulations on finite k
thank you i want to hug you
thank you this sugar girl
thank you congratulations on founder k
love you so much i would like to know do
you recommend me buying fire emblem free
houses of course i do
if you like rpgs go for it
[Music]
okay i need to refresh because i reached
the end
wow youtube thank you
what your self-certification ratings are
so accurate
so you get faster monetizations
decisions oh thank you youtube
thank you youtube youtube is
congratulating me for being a good girl
oh some more super chats thank you
stonks
has youtube seen mario kart my mario
kart stream
no no don't mention it don't i don't
know what you're talking about
no no no no
no no
[Music]
that candy is candy don't know what you
mean
mike ranger thank you
very much
foreign
oh you're gonna make a really great
whole life senpai one day
oh i wonder
but if possible for a little while i
would like to not have any
uh underlings just yet
just yet i would like it to stay the way
it is for a while
symphsia
[Music]
your power has been out for two nights
from a snowstorm where the hell do you
live
snowstorm he's donating an american us
dollars
i have to sit in the car to stay warm
and keep the phone charged
wow wow i love snow but that's a bit
rough
where in in america do they have
snowstorms
alaska
are you watching from alaska damn
damn
thank you
wow the dominion's just a team
thank you and timing is everything do
what you want to do don't worry about
the rest have patience with yourself oh
wow deep words those words being around
will stay
you'll get better if you take time to
learn anything and don't worry about
screwing up
have fun for yourself wow so these are
some really
really wise words thank you very much
this is what i would like to hear
in those red super chats where you guys
keep on writing nothing
this is what i want to hear
alaska is easy life blizzard's damn
andre mast thank you thanks for
continuing to do fire emblem i've been a
fan since
game boy advance and i'm happy to see
someone giving it love it deserves yes
thank you thank you soon
there's still so much more fun to have
with fire emblem i can't wait to see you
complete it even if i can always be here
live you're always great to watch don't
be too hard on yourself
if it can't be your life please watch
the archive don't forget to watch the
archive thank you shane
matt m thank you for your first super
chat
kelly oh dan kashan thank you for also
your first super chat thank you
thank you thank you i will write you a
fair letter soon oh
thank you i'm looking forward to that
galaxy
thank you
hmm that is true that is true it is a
big number
for brewing sanction darwin
here's the official congratulations for
getting 400k subs here to celebrating
the growth of the mighty phoenix here's
the more subs viva lakia
thank you
this is late but you are the first
feature to convince me to spend money
and you're the reason
i now watch so many streams and have so
many memberships of course i'm gonna say
congrats on 400k
thank you so just one weird comment that
made me go
what the hell king go ten dan kishan
alvido lancashien ko galion dan kishan
garduri dan kashan samaritan pakkashin
oh the white guy
rice salma danger
please continue with your good work your
number one but be more original and play
more games
what isn't that what i'm doing
huh you are number one
but be more original and play more games
huh okay
thank you i think the games i choose are
quite original
i mean look at the fire emblem stream
and tomorrow super mario sunshine will
start on my channel
tomorrow super mario sunshine
last refreshing again refreshing
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you second try
congratulations my second try
ah because uh okay congratulations on
for the cake
you've come so far when hawaiian started
you were my least favorite
i like hearing that but now i'm happy to
skip all the streams to watch yours
thank you
your energetic personality is always a
joy to stand here
the comments doing rpgs are healers
thank you
it's okay it's funny it's okay
thank you i'm glad to have you on my
streams
i'm glad i i could change your mind
about someone else
about something about me about me i'm
glad i could change your mind and
get you to be one of the kfp
crew members
dankeshen and anthony salazar
also thanks for joining the membership
that's it guys
i've reached the end
[Music]
thank you everyone for the support thank
you everyone
for subscribing thank you everyone for
joining the membership
thank you everyone for everything oh one
more
that finger thank you 400k subscribers
congratulations for the milestone it is
amazing how much you evolved
with all the collabs and the streams you
are incredible and you've kind of been
my daily show oh
hey i'm happy to hear that thank you so
much for everything you've done
and thanks to the community you've
created
thank you thank you thank you thank you
for your kind words and akibaki
packaging
so will you all be there
tomorrow for the super mario sunshine
stream i hope so
thank you for the membership
i will probably never continue
super mario 64. unless maybe in a year
or something
maybe in a year when i'm a pro gamer
and i have recovered from the traumatic
experience
that was playing super mario 64. but for
now we are moving on to super mario
sunshine
thanks for joining the membership
yoona i do feel like kfb is the best
community
yes i strongly must agree with you
yuna
okay guys i guess that's
it i will do some stuff and i'll see you
oh thank you for the super chat
[Music]
can't wait for all that juice all that
juice
all that juice
and i want food
hey i played sunshine before it's not i
feel
super mario 64 was much harder to me at
least
all right thank you everyone
again for congratulating me i'm so glad
to have you guys i'm so glad that you
guys are
here for me
[Music]
i'll do a special stream for the 400k
sometime soon
uh but it will be unarchived so oh
it will be very special you should all
be there you should be there don't miss
it
all right then and in german we say
auf wiedersehen
[Music]
cheers
love you
[Music]
so
you