[Music]
so
how we doing hello
guys guys guys guys one question
am i supposed to play this game with a
keyboard or with a controller
because right now i have it open but no
no controller connected
what's better
controller oh [\h__\h]
oh
okay
okay i hope it will
oh so
hope it will automatically recognize
what i'm doing
control would be easier keyboard
oh most people say controller okay
all right i trust you i believe in you
keyboard mouse and keyboard for shooting
controller for driving oh can i can you
switch in between
[Music]
secret chip
okay
controller connected
suddenly i can't
hear music anymore wait now i can
okay controller already works
and keyboard still too
okay so i will switch
is that a smart idea i will switch to
um
to the controller whenever
i drive
switching is better
damn
that's
so busy
i'm gonna be a busy woman
such busy women
oh [\h__\h]
um
now one more thing is there anything in
this game like i know i know i know i
know about you know like
um there's some yeah bye
i'll buy sequences here and there where
i need to censor perhaps if possible
um
but what about also i'm turning v-sync
off is that okay
i also know about dmca blah blah blah
but is there anything else i'm not
supposed to show
turn off discord overlay
uh-huh
what the discord discord
where's that display
where would that
be
is that not just a discord thing
i don't see a discord overlay thing here
turn off this we don't need that to
happen again uh-huh interesting
cap the frame rate
let's see
cap the frame rate is that advanced
i don't i don't see where that is
refresh rate is auto
racing on
yo you better be right with that
okay
i know
um
where is that
the radio setting
[Music]
where's the radio setting that says
return don't turn it audi automatically
on
when you go into the car we think off oh
my god
always the discussion with v-sync
unbelievable
uh
on audio i don't see that
there's a self radio mode
but that's not the thing i think
they sync on motion blur off
nah you can't keep on telling me what to
do now you're just trying to control me
like a puppet
you're playing with me
okay i'll turn this card off even though
then i'm worried as
i'm worried that i don't know what's
going on
[Music]
oh wonderful okay eh how do i turn
discord off this is the first time in a
million years i'm turning this cord off
quit discord
oh my god oh no i did it
oh no
you're calling me a puppet i'm gonna pop
it
okay i think whatever we'll get let's
get started
everything is fine
whenever i hear dmca music i'm just
gonna turn the music droop down
with my
button over here
yeah i don't see the discord overlay but
i turned off this skirt so all is good
i
think i think we're fine
okay what is this oh cute car
okay story mode right now i'll start
with keyboard this is confusing
entering story mode the window on my
screen is tiny
so small it doesn't even take up 50 of
the screen
[Laughter]
oh well
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
wait how fast is there going to be a
need for censoring
open the door they'll get worse than her
which one am i
like slightly to the left that's so
weird
come on eh censor now wait what what
for a while not for a while okay
sir we're giving you everything you want
i don't even think about it
sounds like me sit tight i'll handle the
plastic what's going on are we robbing a
bank what is this place
em get these [\h__\h] in the closet aim
how do i
aim oh [\h__\h] that's not it okay like this
sorry i almost had you but um i'm doing
you're lucky i didn't get you i can't
move why can't i not move inside the
closet get them in there come on oh god
come
[Music]
i don't want to shoot you
i almost killed him almost it's not
not quite there press up to bring up the
phone
detonate highlighted press
i'm gonna call it is that a bomb oh
already yeah chill the [\h__\h] out
oh it was lagging
fps trap
bobcat what did we blow up
locations on march
where which way are we going
this way open
this way yeah yeah okay wait it's
there's some fps drops sometimes can i
do something about this
um maybe i should turn the sync on
controller is lagging the pc no way
turn on subtitles oh yeah that would be
good uh
subtitles here
subtitles
oh on
yeah resolution is [\h__\h] tiny on my
screen
[Laughter]
and okay that's okay
and then you know what i'm gonna
i don't care about the
i don't care if i drive like [\h__\h]
i'm just i'm just doing keyboard now
um
oh interesting
wait
output monitor oh can we do um because
i'm already on to would that help if i
actually do it where it's supposed to be
wonderful okay
i don't know let's let's just go check
again
why are you so slow
when it's so
urgent how do i run
oh there we go jump in and run what
no
oh over here
shift
collect cash cash
how do i take it uh
how do i this is not telling me how to
take it
okay
auto sequence that's fine
whoa over
one hundred thousand shoes okay
i saw your face i'll remember you oh
thanks every day how about you make sure
this is one i'm full screen hello
okay
i can try
normally i don't play in full screen but
because i feel like that actually makes
everything heavier
watching
oh god it's even in the menu it's
especially laggy
you know what i will turn v-sync on if
it's if if there's like a problem you
normally fix it by switching it on and
off
oh [\h__\h] hell
no what pause game on what
what this [\h__\h] manual
what
no
i can't switch it now
why
it won't let me do [\h__\h]
finally okay
apply
get out of here does that work
it's so laggy i can't even press it
oh wait that's better i think that's
right pal am i supposed to shoot crazy
oh boy
you want to lift tell me you want to
lift twitch
i can switch character l out
make them up
what
while holding l i'll use to select a
character
okay
and then
release uh-huh
uh-huh i think i did it all day oh
[Music]
it's real kind of weird though yeah
oh oh okay
i can be anyone who i want to be
the freedom okay take cover take cover
okay i take a piano
you're on a timer so break this why do i
take cover there's nothing there i'll
bump another bomb
overkill dude
holy [\h__\h] dude [\h__\h] you hear that
siren moving away from cover okay hit
the shutter switch
wow what a difficult uh it ain't
supposed to go down
they answered
[Music]
i was born like this
do i have hp
get out of here
[Music]
i mean this point of view this angle is
kind of weird but
well i guess i can get used to it
[Music]
oh he's dead
oh
nice i'm so good
get to the car i'm i'm at the car yeah
yeah
oh oh oh oh reloading
[Music]
oh the snow makes you so much slower how
realistic
[Music]
what
unless it triggers you guys
[Music]
triggers you guys like in minecraft
no i never i never um like shot people
before in this game i played like an
older version of this game i think
and was just driving around in cars
[Music]
you have to uh accelerate is what sorry
what does it say we move quick we can
beat this i don't know what it says hold
s to break and reverse and i believe in
this bird
okay s to break that's a that's that
stupidly positioned
oh i stay on the right lane okay i say
there's a jump
[\h__\h] okay
there's a chopper driving is not my
specialty
and here no oh [\h__\h] i went too early
sorry ah sorry
i'm better at shooting than a driving um
good that i have
no driving license yet
[\h__\h] out get back on the track
[Music]
the world is my trick buddy
was vaccinating and still driving i
don't know how that was possible stick
to the plan what plan
did he lose his eye now
what plan
he didn't tell me to plan
where the [\h__\h] the chopper where the
[\h__\h] is the chopper chopped up
i'm gonna check around
the [\h__\h] badge someone must have
[\h__\h] talked
all right yes brad's going to put the
word [\h__\h] into every sentence just like
me they speak my language
you suck how did you get yourself legit
i'm gonna leave you my cake go
gotta look down
all of you
[Applause]
i was suddenly a different person
she's she's oh are we taking a geyser
in german it's called the geyser
mr tubber she doesn't know any chambers
[Music]
first of all let's let's hug each other
get the chopper
chopper is a helicopter right it was
like
michael
was not always a good house is that are
we going to the cleaner well of my dead
friends
he did not die a hero's death
but he was a man he was a man
at least
that
what an accomplishment
he was like anybody else are you really
saying that we do not know your infinite
mysteries
but we know so rude
that you will show mercy to our friends
have mercy
begging you for mercy yeah
won't yeah
believe me yeah
yeah yeah i'm begging you for mercy
i want you i faked my
i picked my death
what
was my
he's a good kid
how old is this game the graphics look
bad in my in my point of view
no
he sits on his ass all day
smoking dope and jerking off while he
plays that [\h__\h] 13. if that's our
standard for goodness no wonder this
country's screwed
and what about you
what about me
i guess that's decent
i don't have the advantages that kid has
by the time i was his age i'd already
been in prison twice damn son i robbed
banks wow you're so badass
these were the opportunities i had so at
least i took therapists and where did
these opportunities get you michael
they got me right
[\h__\h] here
the end of the road it's beautiful here
with a big house and a useless kid
stuck talking to you because no one else
gives you [\h__\h] oh i'm living the dream
baby and that dream is [\h__\h] it is
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] yeah [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] let it
all out let it out
i think i just did
oh
well i
think that's all we have time for oh
the same time next week
it's just like the script i guess that's
the therapist script he's sticking to
the script okay so unoriginal [\h__\h] is
working for me
now a sense of overriding futility is a
vital part of the process uh-huh
embrace it we should kill him whatever
you say he talks [\h__\h]
oh is that is that copyrighted
it sounds cooled up first part was just
game music
stream isn't um monetized anyway
nice car
oh wait can you get um
there it looks like where is a place
where you could get elotes
[Music]
sick
oh oh bodybuilders
oh they do be lifting
oh dagger
girl
should i
put some sunscreen on your back
i think you need some help
i'll get burnt
[Music]
i know just how you feel
man [\h__\h] gotta be around here somewhere
russia they buried it under the sand
what are you looking for brilliant lamar
davis production [\h__\h] you hey excuse me
can you tell me where berto beach house
is
no homie i cannot man would you come on
we need a [\h__\h] counter right there with
the yellow stairs
yeah really good looking at home
appreciate it man get your stupid ass on
damn why don't you ask if he knows the
[\h__\h] owner or better yet do some
skywriting that reads there's a couple
[\h__\h] here about to boost some cars in
case somebody didn't realize see what
you don't realize that we ain't boosting
this [\h__\h] is legit what is that mean
boosting oh yeah i forgot huh 401ks tax
returns and all that's the chance i'm
doing that
i'm getting my money in the hood i'm
straight food i'm cool you cool stealing
boosting means stealing gang signs yeah
right whatever homie
cacti this the spin knot right here
beautiful
[\h__\h]
get your ass in there
oh they're so tented
oh i'm playing him now
what i have so many personalities
i can't hello cat
oh [\h__\h] sorry no i wanted to go down
where the [\h__\h]
god
[Music]
[\h__\h]
i pushed the cat away where is where's
the cat no
it's got i killed it i killed the
[\h__\h] cat
god damn
yeah i think the white one
she was one of the cars he hit this one
still remember press f to get in right
oh we take both hard with the drop top
oh [\h__\h]
no eraser corridor
hit me on the speakerphone okay okay oh
it's like that
okay safe driving everybody buckle your
seatbelts
oh
oh sorry oh sorry oh sorry oh sorry oh
sorry
i hope i don't have to pay for the
repairs
why is this this radio is this dmca
here's something
wait [\h__\h]
wait for me
go away go
move
you're in my way where did she go
nice sick turns
what the [\h__\h] was that did someone
miss you failed at last
can i do it again
oh
sorry i need to get used to this you
know
all right all right i'm taking i'm
taking this car now who cares this [\h__\h]
must got the baby dick
like that bobby big dick on a [\h__\h] huh
[\h__\h] for real homie
what
this [\h__\h] got robo roofing
everything [\h__\h] he should have paid the
nizzo
man you got a grind to keep that [\h__\h]
now it's back on us hell yeah i want to
see what it do hey hit me on the speaker
phone
oh it's like that show homie what's your
homie
i i don't think cool should ever play
this game
[Music]
kind of stopped myself at least
buddy hold
me
let's go
i i didn't lose him yet
and then losing me i see him i see him i
see i see i see
[Laughter]
[Music]
very smooth driving
wait
i'm on a mission some important [\h__\h] to
do
whoa whoa this is a movie set what are
they filming
the next blockbuster oh hello hello
back
i mean in this game you're supposed to
break your cars right that's that's part
of the
fun
get into a nice car break it get into
the next nice car break it oops
[Music]
how the [\h__\h] can you like
uh
destroy those lamps so fast so easily
that's
oh my god
yeah i got the gameplay down
i know what we're here for i know what
we came here for uh
some time over nickels and dimes i stick
to repos dawg
oh [\h__\h] what suddenly you have to tell
me
bro you have to tell me when you
suddenly change
lanes like that
warn me
okay okay
oh
only macaroni where the [\h__\h] are we even
going
just give me the address i'll put it
into my gps man
oh never mind we're here
i think
oh he's still not there huh
this feels like a roller coaster it's
really bad for roller coasters oh oh oh
we made it
that's right
move over so the traffic can flow
through whatever [\h__\h] i'll let
something flow through your ass oh right
to shoot us you can change the radio
station
thank you oh [\h__\h] one time be cool fool
we got the paperwork
whatever you explain that [\h__\h] i see you
at the dealership explain this
oh no where am i going go i don't see
him on my on my screen anymore
[Music]
oh here there you go radio oh my god
[Applause]
[Music]
this guy costs like a million more than
a million five million ten million i
don't know what the realistic price
point is
in the [\h__\h] way
just lose them okay
oh just 200k
oh [\h__\h] okay this is oh oh now we're
[\h__\h] oh now we [\h__\h] now we're really
[\h__\h]
now we're really [\h__\h]
uh can i restart
[Music]
my covers
oh this is a train lane you're not
supposed to drive on the train lane dude
did i lose
them you don't lose them
i know the the stars are uh showing me
how much i'm wanted right
it's still two stars i have to go down
to one star or zero stars
[Applause]
nice nice starch but still bonked
oh oh i'm uh in german we say
geistaffara
ghost drivers
are on the wrong lane oh my god i'm so
sorry i'm sorry please
i'm not doing this on purpose
[Applause]
but oh oh oh we're on the right lane now
baby
oh by the walk in the park
how about a walk in the park oh [\h__\h]
what
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
what what what
ll
what what uh what can i not just let me
land
what
slow motion it
it's fine let me land
[Music]
stunt jump failed what 50 stunt jumps
remaining what do you mean
was i supposed to do a stunt
is this a trick show
well this is a nice area to drive away
from the police perfect no one can get
in my way
out what the [\h__\h] where did you come
from
i thought no one knew i was here
oh oh oh
[Music]
never mind turning around
i guess that's a dead end
how about
can i get back up here
[Music]
that would be helpful now like a
speedboat kind of thing
i'm really bad at escaping is this
normal
wow
nice
[Music]
okay back on the road i guess
look for a place to hide
[Music]
okay
like get out of the car
[Music]
pop show on the mini map
oh wait it's telling me to go take the
car back why did i do they know how much
i broke it and they want the money
they want
they want the money
oh no
oh wait i'm not wanted anymore
oh
nothing suspicious about um someone in a
car like this
wow yeah that's what i say every time
that's what your mama says every time
she sees me in the morning
i tried
yo mama
what this is simon's card friendly
you are a racist and i don't like you
and i will not sell you this card you're
talking i will not you make my skin
crawl you neo-nazi you're all the same
you're
disgusting this racist insulted me hey
what's up bro what are you calling a
nick no no i'm not calling nobody a
[\h__\h] wait what the [\h__\h] i i mean
are you german that's not cool man i
don't say that you [\h__\h] right and you
better keep it right cause this man
right here he's an international
businessman a multiculturalist that i
could not have said because we broke his
beautiful car but seriously maybe he's
not a racist but i don't think that he
is man enough for a car like this
wait wait a second
it's a normal car
you know
get him a hybrid that's a real man's car
give him the rent
you get a tax rebate i understand money
is an issue eh money isn't an issue this
is the best part watch this when he
really mean he gonna get all his full
money what's this look man i gotta go
hey samia
i'm out
i holler at you homie it's the best part
can i take a different one right i can
take the white one right because we're
the different characters now we can take
a different car
no
listen to the quality of the stuff
pre-processed uh-huh wait uh how about
this one
it's playable characters their own
unique vehicle oh
yeah wait then not the red one right
on the mini map
don't tell me it's this shitty red car
or ah wait this one i'm driving oh i
thought we were taking separate cars
okay franklin's house
[Music]
oh cute
it's a chump change how i'm gonna knock
a bad crony sexy [\h__\h] fighting got a
fat pisa who you trying to impress yo i
see the knees with all that ass [\h__\h]
she got ass
she grown yeah
she grown into a [\h__\h] idiot no she's
actually sexy
she more like obsessed with sex [\h__\h] oh
man for the penis that's exactly how i
like my women
[Music]
they're really good buddies huh um
they get along so well
i'm jealous okay let's lay that the it's
green it's great [\h__\h] [\h__\h] love
it's
green idiots
nice oh look at that beautiful driving
style
what's up
hi girl
oh this place looks familiar
this is the place from mikko's clips
wait i'm not
the back of the car i thought it was
i've arrived oh no quiet i guess over
there
[Music]
[\h__\h] it's good to be home
school's a careful oh no no damage run
let's go
this is my it's my place
what's up can a lot come up in your crib
man [\h__\h] you i see you at work oh [\h__\h]
don't hate me cause i'm beautiful [\h__\h]
maybe you got rid of that old ass
haircut you guys get some [\h__\h] on
your dick oh better yet maybe tanisha
call your dog ass if she ever stop
[\h__\h] with that brain surgeon the
lawyer she [\h__\h] with
[\h__\h]
what
okay no she's watching
[Music]
i
still live with my mommy
really
oh how old am i look at that huge bottle
of pepsi
oh that's my aunt okay
still
change clothes at the wardrobe okay
what the [\h__\h]
can you not
how do i
i'm gonna change clothes at the wardrobe
expand
what oh continue
fine
press e
oh
we're playing sims now
that's cute
and
i don't care
[Music]
man man's fashion is not really my thing
you know
yeah that's fine
maybe a hat i don't know
huh oh yeah sick huh
yeah i want that
huh
does it work and then and then maybe
some glasses
huh wait i don't have them
and they look [\h__\h] no no glasses we're
fine
what about some sick shoes
oh
i like the green ones yeah
i can get more later oh we can get
clothing shopping
yeah
is is that music that i hear is that
dmca music that i hear i'm turning it
off as much as i can
what now
oh a gentleman
what's his name if i may ask huh
maybe i should check him out before you
do and see if he's good enough for you
um
interaction menu holding m button
interaction
hell no my cooking is [\h__\h]
what why is it turning like this i'm not
doing anything
uh interaction menu what what
record yourself playing brief
select the place your waypoint
shut up the blimp has now been unlocked
call the blimp contact on your cell
phone to arrange for a blimp what's a
blimp to be delivered to the nearest
available drop-off location what's the
blimp
no i'm turned off though i i i i
unplugged the
oh i can drink water
i unplugged the
controller
eh what was that press e to do something
ah
can i take
i'm going to take he doesn't [\h__\h]
work
huh eat the drink there we go
wait does that actually get me drunk and
wobbly and [\h__\h] when i drive
i have a full health okay
ah disgusting
hate beer
where's my next mission auntie
cooking for you or what oh these doors
are cool
those are some cool doors
if you drink enough yeah
okay we don't want that i'm already
driving wobbly enough we don't need any
more difficulty
okay
oh incoming call uh-huh
simon what's going down home the market
my boy liquidity is a [\h__\h] get over
here so i can give you the new repo list
all right dog i'll be around when i get
a chance
ah wait so is the thing in this game
that you pick up cars and places and
bring them to the car dealership
some nice cars for him to sell
whether the contract to get a mission
from simon
for now
oh
there's a lot to do okay
nice car
[Music]
all right
we're going to the s
oh they're not showing me like oh sorry
sorry sorry sorry
they're not showing me the easy route
now
what the [\h__\h]
you want to fight
wait how do you fist fight dancing
where's my god [\h__\h] i'm useless like
this
no [\h__\h]
we need to learn how to fist fight
though soon
lock on
what what what button
click what put just click right click
okay
we made it safely yeah it's already
there that was close
oh sorry sorry i was looking at the
i was looking at the buildings they
looked interesting
[Music]
sorry you should have moved honestly
not my fault hello
oh the floor is so shiny damn
what's so similar did you have someone
lick the floor nice to see you so good
hold me
which is why
i am very honored to announce to you
bonus bonus that you yeah our employee
of the month wow anyway
it wasn't easy picking a winner
yeah me lamar your nephew sacha with the
twitch look man it's been a real honor
homie but i got to move forward in my
life it seemed like all i do is let
people tell me what to do when i do it
and nothing changes i tell you what my
boy you tell me exactly what you want i
will very carefully explain to you why
it cannot be wow today is repossessing
vehicles so inspiring purchased at
exorbitant interest rates no
together
i never had a black son
but if i did i want him to be just like
you no no
[Laughter]
[Music]
franklin here has been awarded employee
of the month ah
good for him
you [\h__\h] with me right
man we both being [\h__\h] with dawg
oh man for real after all the
[\h__\h] work i put in man man [\h__\h]
this employee of the monster i'm sitting
up here trying to shoot you mean [\h__\h]
this employee the mother [\h__\h] man when
there's some [\h__\h] to be one god damn it
i want it
yeah you can have it i'm talking about i
take no prisoners i go hard doing this
[\h__\h] big dog all he wants when james is
on the [\h__\h] board i want to see
my name
who wanted to be the employee of the
month
maybe next month next time next month
what about today yeah the man to retrial
just the bike hasn't made the payment at
all taking it so seriously his name is
esteban jimenez esteban jimenez
curiously enough i did not inquire when
he bought the bike
we got work to do uh
employee of the month
[\h__\h] you in combat y'all proof myself
today
ass [\h__\h]
let's go to best beauty best booty
that's bootsy beach
can we see some hot ladies in their
swimsuits
type [\h__\h] but now it's all starting to
make sense
you driving oh i'm counting on you to
cover me when someone tries to shoot me
all right who took the bike that s.a
vargo's dude with the tattoo on his face
and [\h__\h] yeah that was him [\h__\h] homie i
don't want no unnecessary [\h__\h] here
all right whoa
[\h__\h] it's a reason simeon pays a couple
of mean looking [\h__\h] to come
repo this [\h__\h] we ain't girl scouts
in your case i ain't so sure about this
he just put a dub down on this bike 20
g's with a 3g note whoa
dawg man this whole setup designed to
take out [\h__\h] sorry um whole setup
designed to take drugs money all right
man look we going quiet in and out no
[\h__\h] drama
that sounds like a flag there will be
drama [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] and you love me for it
[\h__\h]
that's right most people questioning is
she honestly standing at a red light yes
yes i [\h__\h] asked jacking for all this
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] you talking about but
that's a long red light damn that's how
[\h__\h] work ain't it you do some jobs for
food
uneasy relationships
this way we make the police love me okay
they'll love me they won't ever say
anything against me how about the boy
with the eye from around the way marcus
or something you were slanging for him
and then he got what was coming right
that was good that's a sick card
i don't want to clap my boy terry and
either i like homie it's just smacks of
the inevitable look dog this time we
legit homie this honest work they talk
so much
you down straight that's trill partner
but it's a shame i don't believe it you
want to drive it takes about one week
if you drive according to traffic rules
one week to the one reservation casinos
only that kicked your ass off that's
really interesting though
you and all your little racial
stereotypes and [\h__\h] i find them
offensive i'm very sensitive to your
intolerance my [\h__\h]
this is like you know
heart mode
imposing what are you doing
posing some rules on yourself to make it
hard mode
never gotten to hear the full
conversation
there you go i'm just delivering you
guys the full story you guys just go for
life too fast you're not enjoying it you
know
you need to
slowly take a sip and
take it all in yeah the bike should be
in one of the lockups down here should
be is the story of your life [\h__\h]
so rude be nice
i drove you here [\h__\h]
[Music]
his limbs are all over the place oh
hello car oh sick music yeah that's
right
keep it moving [\h__\h]
everybody needs to mind their own
business
where's the bike
hey look let's keep it smooth homie
let's move your ass movie let's move up
in this [\h__\h] man what exactly did i do
in the past like to deserve
[Music]
you should know a block makes a
difference hey hey hold up
you guys somebody said press b to pet is
that really so
search the garages
uh garage which one there's a couple
come on man let's get it before these
fools get back
well like this one
i'll guess all of them yeah yeah they're
marked on the map
uh no or but what is that
i i picked something up but it didn't
tell me what it was
open
this one
that will kill it oh no oh come on okay
that's not it either that was a
deduction it's telling me it's right
there yeah that makes a lot of sense
bees attack oh man ain't this boxing i'm
more um
[Music]
why would you show up so soon
oh wait did i not take tap to bring up
the weapon wheel there we go
head shot
[Music]
and you're on my side right
oh that wasn't it the first one wasn't
the headshot
i'm trying to save ammo you know
shut his [\h__\h] arm
faster
[Music]
his gun goes
everything is legal
huh
what are you shooting um
[Music]
let's ground to your right
easy easy easy club
i don't see anyone
ah
there
no that one's already dead
who are we shooting
where's the bike i thought we could just
talk it out but man
now they're all dead they can't even
tell me where the oh there's the bike
i got it before you drove away
[Laughter]
very fast reaction this snap
easy
nice
speed run that's it right don't i have
to pick it up
oh i'm on the bike now
go to the car once oh waking up the car
wash
at the car wash
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh that that hurts sick
wait for me
wait for me dude oh please
i i it doesn't matter if i lose him this
time right because i already
i know where to go
oh i like riding a bike
yeah stick them map don't worry
i would say that was a sick shot that i
did
the dude on the bike
that deserves some respect
sick
sick instincts
right yeah
i'm a natural at this
i know that you can like put on your own
music into the radio i might do that
next time
oh oh
put in like do you in sparks
and
my most famous song
wow
nice
yeah i can also put a
kelly's music would be sick maybe
some rap music would be pretty fitting
for the vibes
okay that was not good
that uh felt like uh
my accident when i was skiing with cali
in hokkaido
that was pretty much it but with a
little bit more momentum actually
and i my body went even further than
that
like about double double the distance my
body traveled when i
was released from my skis
that was a good visual explanation
psychopath you don't finally [\h__\h]
lost it
oh yeah
ptsd
honestly it's a miracle that i didn't
break anything like seriously
and we ain't going to neither [\h__\h] i'm
gonna keep this [\h__\h] for myself
tell simeon we couldn't recover oh yeah
i don't want to keep it you [\h__\h] tell
them you [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
ah we're back to the employee of the mom
is this some this was the employee of
the month right
he got a gunshot wound right on his like
heart what the [\h__\h]
mission accomplished though
he'll bring it to my house eh
where the [\h__\h] did he take it i'll i'll
have to take it back
oh wait what now strangers and freaks
can be found for san andreas at question
mark am i supposed to go there
strangers and freaks you want me to go
to the strangers and freaks on purpose
all right this is my home right
there's some strangers and freaks right
at my home
those are optional okay
am i supposed to like knock them out
let's go check out some strangers and
freaks don't you come over here let me
take care of that lonely ass ah let's
ain't nothing wrong with me [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
well your ass don't look too good where
the [\h__\h] is jb smoking and what about
you
i mean you know i quit
those shoes with the rainbows what are
those jb look jb gonna lose everything
he gonna lose the house you know what
i'm saying the business everything and
you his cousin [\h__\h] you said you was
gonna he helped my cousin whatever if
that's how you feel what the [\h__\h] do i
know about torn cars look it's easy if
jb can do it you can do it for [\h__\h]
sake come on imma show you come on [\h__\h]
all right dude what are we talking about
everything
hey look let's make this quick i got
[\h__\h] to do
you need to slow it down tanisha was
right
go to the tow truck
what's the blue dot
all right is this what
my my wheels
you want me to go get my wheels
i thought she was making bank yeah i
thought she was making me well girl
i'm trying to keep my car safe because
you were dangerous girl
you were a dangerous woman i forgot
which one was my house
trucks at the davis sheriff impound my
chill a second
you asked for my car i'm gonna go get it
i know you've always been sweet on me
steal a car
i don't have a car right now your ass
must be high or something oh i drove it
to the to the dealership huh see the car
but that's illegal
but i'm doing good boo your eyes don't
laugh is she gonna get in fast as well
that looks like a [\h__\h] car
i'm scared to steal a car i've never
done that before
what are they gonna give me wait wait
wait wait so how do i do this how do we
do this oh my goodness oh [\h__\h] i don't
know how to do this get out get out of
the car i want to go in i want to let me
and let me in
girl you get in too yeah yeah you know
how we're doing this girl girl
faster
move your slow ass
oh wait music
wait i forgot uh
oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
okay okay well they're not following me
they're not gonna call the police or
anything
interesting easy
you learn lessons for life here
so this is how you do it
this is how you do the thing
if you do it too much and yeah oh
or maybe if it's like suddenly i steal a
ship or a helicopter maybe that makes me
a bigger target huh
gotta do that all right i have a ride
let's go bring the cha-ching
nothing
well where are we bringing this big
thing i don't know if i have a truck
license but
i don't have a helicopter license either
and we're also going to drive a
helicopter eventually
ah [\h__\h] music
yeah go pick it up
and my boy franklin we filling in for jb
uh oh
we have like a walkie-talkie here
for days 10-7 i'm gone a bucket
this one should be easy not easy enough
that reminds me apparently
i think this may have been in the state
of play
but someone tweeted this at me there's
like this new game coming up i forgot
the name but it's like portal
and um stanley's parable
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] maybe you guys remember
the name
it looks really good i want to play it
it's coming out this year still i think
it looks really good it has like exactly
the same vibes
right here in the settings
you don't know
doesn't ring a bell
you didn't watch it
yes the entropy center that's the one
that's the one
how do i just turn down the music volume
radius i'll never mind radio station
radio off
[Music]
[Laughter]
it was already on radio up
self radio mode ah
radio sequential
random
radio
i'm confused
sell it to radio okay
oh [\h__\h] wait why
okay
okay let's see if that helps when i get
into a car
whoa sick your car your car is as flat
as xena's chest just kidding
okay i've seen jb do this a hundred
times back up close
make sure the hook is down trying to be
cool slide right in slide blind
oh into that car
thank you hi baby
back it up nice and steep
okay i got it
i lined the tow truck so it's
back um it's like cars
yeah
isn't that
this is not correct yet
i thought i was doing it
control and shift
what how can i attach it gabe you didn't
tell me that
i'm playing along with the hook
hmm okay we
for a long time okay
oh fine
this was not how i saw my day going
i have to be careful though there's some
long [\h__\h] on my back
dangling around
so i ain't seeing you around the hood
much i've been trying to branch out
can't stand shamelessly well an employee
of the month doesn't just get to become
an employee of the mom that easily
worthy
[\h__\h] changes you the one all turfed up
jb smoking but he ain't smoking homies
we out here grinding
for yeah
cause i could have sworn it was me out
here touring cars
and looking damn fine doing it too baby
oh does that make a dangle less
oh sh
[Music]
justin bieber they're talking about
destiny but no way
no freaking way
justin bieber is not cool enough for you
okay we make the drop where they got the
area's mark
wait my other car is gone
[Music]
how
on the hook
can't just
out are you going
where get
it's okay
girl you're making me go crazy yeah
i'll see you on the block okay and you
need
you holla at me okay what do we do about
the truck can i keep it
i mean it's kind of slow
okay
make some pass what do i get for that
though do i get anything
i'm gonna go get a different car
oh so now you want to pick up i got
franklin
for you
franklin clinton she on the phone again
i got respect when it is what about
money what about money i don't care
about respect
let me in let me
sit right
[Music]
beautiful
i still hear music
stretch is getting out homies street
jazz
his bit's almost done we're going holla
at you dog
stress is that like a friend of us
a a new text message breaking up the
phone with up
and i saw that should i call him okay
oh i'm calling him
it's not picking ld long dip holler
he doesn't want to have a conversation
with me all right all right yeah i got a
sick new ride uh which one is my house
you're that one
huh
what's that car doing there
can i keep this car
i'm gonna keep it
stretches my senpai
should i just mute the music
i was thinking so too but i wonder if i
mute anything else with that oh no no no
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
what is it
stop playing that music
okay
well now
game tell me what to do
like important [\h__\h] not side stuff
should i go to that s
was green
a main quest no right though or is that
i don't know
f or s go to s okay
[Music]
okay
well i'll take this car again
i don't think this one is so pretty so
elegant and sleek
beautiful i'm gonna put on my e on
that girl
uh it's making some weird noises though
i don't think that's normal i don't know
much about cars but it doesn't sound
normal to me
eyes on the road
oh it's right there
as normal really
it sounds like it's sick
it's an oil change or something
wow
that was a short ride oh we're at this
place
again ah
[Music]
um please don't take the car that i just
got
i'm so proud of this one please don't
take it away from me
where
above
[Music]
what if i leave it there are they gonna
take it
what if i if i like park it
it'll disappear no
please don't disappear also how do i
what
let me in
you're not gonna open it up i'm an
employee of the month
servicing
front door okay
go to sleep oh you can go to sleep in
this game
oh oh is it like too late now can i not
get in normally oh wait never mind
there's uh this spot here
premium deluxe motorsports
now it's daytime thank me because you
think that i am an arab what no what are
you talking about excuse me
boy
i am his men ah he's having that kind of
discussion again what do you mean a
mental don't worry about that
okay so what you got from james de santa
kid he is already late on his payments
and i have this bad feeling that he will
do more damage to the car than we can
get back from him in the exorbitant
interest rate payment exorbitant
interest rate payments yes
[Music]
hamstead of eclipse it's an suv
some rockford hills daddy's boy nonsense
don't worry about it try to bring the
car back in good condition huh i got you
don't worry about it easy to see you my
boy hey good luck in
law school high school so
mr kellet where are we at
financing yeah listen to that
conversation it's like a shitty deal
ah because of the color of my skin you
think i am a scammer
no no skin color's got nothing to do
with it
oh
that's awkward now
he he's got no response anymore he's out
of responses because that's his only
response huh
okay oh sh
wait is my car still there
you waited for me i'm so happy so proud
of you
no
all right
all right let's go let's freaking go
you know i really don't know much about
cars if i don't even like have
a car that i i want to get once i ever
get a car but
i don't have any preferences oh [\h__\h]
that was
that was bad
but
even though for my whole life i was like
telling myself i don't want to drive
because it's scary i don't want a
driving license ever
if i ever need to you know get to places
hopefully i will
one day
live with someone who has a car you know
but
i don't know
the past
oh
i better pick up again
oh [\h__\h] no
sorry i mean i wasn't in the car so you
can't believe it on me it didn't happen
when i was in the car
uh
wasn't me
definitely wasn't me
let's take this kind of cute car that's
so cute i love it oh my god oh my god
it's so cute
see that i like too but that like
there's no space in there right
um
but it's so cute it's so compact oh my
god
what was i saying
oh no
the cops are following me against [\h__\h]
okay now that's our priority all right
no problem i have a really
swooshy dynamic car
there was no one in the car man how how
can you automatically assume that i
stole it huh
was literally no one in there
yes i may have broken
the window but that's just because um
i need to get it replaced it was already
broken
i just made it even more broken because
what's the difference at that point you
know
it's gonna be the same cost to repair it
anyway
did i lose them there's still one star
there but it doesn't feel like they're
following me oh sick car
and now i lost that beautiful car oh i
also lost to the police
all right one last thing
oh yeah yeah yeah recently the past one
or two years or so i had to rely on
people so much for like their cars
oh guys
and i was like [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] i don't
want to rely so much on people anymore
and also
it's just nice to have a car at your
disposal at any time i guess
so my plan is to get a license maybe in
like
two years or so
sorry
license and a car but i don't know what
car i would want
and also
i think
i wouldn't even really use it much until
maybe when i live on the countryside oh
sake why does everybody have such sick
cars
yo
what the [\h__\h]
you know what that means friend
i'm gonna take your car
[\h__\h]
was that french
all right no no
she did you guys see that guys i have it
all on record i have it all on camera
caught in [\h__\h] 4k or
1080p or actually 720p but
never mind
we're at it i'm letting you go just this
once
out of kindness
based on my needs
hmm
yeah well
sick
this game can give me like all kinds of
like inspiration
whoa what is this place
what you must let me in no oh who's
living here
whoever lives here
is rich as [\h__\h]
damn
i'm not jealous
find a way into the house
i mean
i mean how about we just knock
no no no knock on my door ooh knock
knock knock knock on my door
really
i pressed space i thought you could
climb that come on i know you could do
it what about the heads the heads won't
hurt no
no no
okay oh should we just go in from like
from here
this is slow enough come on or just go
through honestly you could probably just
uh squeeze for real
oh
nice pool
what
but honestly like living in the middle
of a
busy city area like dad with a house
like that i feel like a lot of people
are gonna attempt
to break in lctrl to enter stealth mode
lctrl
i don't see a difference in this
that's not much of a difference
that's your stealth mode weak
absolutely weak are we breaking into the
house
to reach the open window climb into the
car
and then onto the roof
by pressing
space
what this this this thing
what i don't know what the hell they
went
what can you repeat that
i'm going on top of the card i have a
massive gaper [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] homo you're dead
dad he said i had a massive
jimmy called me a [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh so mean
come here out of the window jump into my
arms and i'll rescue you princess
what now
what now what
you get in there
this is so
dangerous to knock your [\h__\h]
no one creeps on the j dog my [\h__\h]
avoid alerting your residents um
i don't know what exactly my retrieve
the car
that one and why did we go inside the
car is not inside
the one in the
cut your dick off garage you call the
administrator oh my god i am the
administrator
i still love him though
sort of
well the other day i walked in on him
and he was jerking off over pictures of
my friends
oh my god unbelievable
thank you what a sick bastard
you uh
where's the [\h__\h] garage
you're a real pro mrs
a real pro can't find [\h__\h] in this house
great student now just loosen up those
hips
okay like this
yeah
loosen them up there you go
and follow through when the [\h__\h] is the
garage
[Laughter]
oh
i see what you're doing
[Music]
[Laughter]
easy did they know this not yet
oh same card
that's kind of a lame card that they
have though all right man that's a
boring
look at my millimeter semi-automatic
pushed against your skull don't look
around
take me where you're going hey come on
man this was a repo job [\h__\h]
you told me a little bit too [\h__\h]
late [\h__\h] no unlikely considering my
son just got the car and looking at the
way you're going about this
my guess is
that's beautiful
[Music]
appreciate a kid purple follows orders
without taking responsibility yeah maybe
one day girl
and i'll explain how the world really
works respect who gives you the slip a
card sorry i got distracted
so this businessman he looked legit to
you look man it's just between him and
your [\h__\h] son
don't worry
me and mr yatarian we'll work this out
okay please don't shoot me
i've got a whole life ahead of me as the
employer of the month okay
got so many places to go
so many things to achieve my dreams are
big you know big
oh i'll get you there safely
don't worry
i'll get myself there safely
you're such a good driver yo if you if
you just like you know you make way less
accidents if you don't actually drive
like a [\h__\h] insane
sicko
yeah have some control over yourself and
then see your car will survive a lot
longer
yeah
[Laughter]
all right man it's jess up here okay
stop the car
pull up okay
here
i know not there
ah over there oh that's very exact man
holy [\h__\h]
hey is that the place
right through the [\h__\h] window
and fast no i'll put two rounds in the
back of your skull and do it myself okay
man you can't be for real i look like a
[\h__\h] joke to you
do i look like a [\h__\h] joke to you
[Music]
all right um oh wait but they got them
the big orange floppy man
i don't want to hurt the flappy man
that's so cute
all right merry christmas
shitty situations dog
that's not exactly how it looks
i always trump big for a job well done
get out of here kid
thank you
[\h__\h]
okay world changed
me
in your face oh two fairy coming tonight
but yeah yeah
not gonna leave a single tooth nah
gonna need your grandma's teeth next
this car
does it look like it's worth five grand
a month
i'll tell you something this thing's
gonna need some serious body work for
it's worth five grand a month
[Laughter]
he agreed to financing i have his
signature yeah did he agree to have some
punk break into my [\h__\h] house
that kid might be a [\h__\h] idiot
but you are a fraudulent scumbag piece
of [\h__\h]
the way you fell down
don't make me have to come back here
[Music]
wow so much confidence
oh
we need to ask him how to get so much
confidence how did he
where did he learn to have so much
confidence huh
anyway are we going into one of the blue
blue spots
and i i can surely take a car right
maybe i can take this one because it's
mine anyway right
yeah
fine
oh can we go to therapy again
switch to frank
who is frank anyway
oh oh can i go to the app should i go to
the f
l i'll switch to l i'll switch to
are you frank
is he frank
oh
whoa we're on the beach
whoa
sick
i couldn't go for a swim
thank god that's over for another day
this is the vip
oh
[Music]
what what city is this playing in this
is it a real city in america
yeah
i've seen this
street art [\h__\h] around the city dude is
real man them some
authentic ass line based off of l.a ah
[Music]
see i've been to la and the beaches
didn't look that nice and the people on
the beaches also didn't look that nice
so
that's unrealistic man
oh the water
no way this didn't look like this
ah
can i swim swim
swim
switch to michael eh
i switched to michael now
he just oh there we go
[Music]
your swinging poster is kind of weird
is that how you guys live is this the
correct way of swimming excuse me
oh they kissed
[Music]
me
i'm gonna go eat you up
down now shark's coming
why is there only women in this water
they didn't react to me hello
yeah yeah swim away [\h__\h] oh nice bud
oh shiny nice butt oh shiny shiny
oh
nice view
sorry um
going to the end
or
i said to switch to him
how far is he
michael
what did we get well
why did we go to him
if we go back to michael anyway
why did you guys somebody told me to go
to michael
both characters are gonna go to the same
place it's on me
ah
okay
yeah okay
no
that's by accident
no i took the car back not he i took the
car back in my car so uh i just go
toward the episode
hot dogs or something like that
did you guys see on twitter yesterday i
i posted some
of the foods that i made recently
and uh the
the second one is what i made yesterday
so i'm gonna eat the leftovers today
go to f
looks good it it did not only look good
it also tasted really good
but the thing is for both of those i
wrote that i had to make the sauces
myself right
now
it said in the recipe you know sometimes
they
if you're not careful
and they automatically pick recipes for
you in hello fresh you get assigned
recipes that need some tools that you
don't even have like for example for
these two i needed a progress dab
no don't know what that's called again
[Music]
um
i can't go to f
oh that's why it's i need to go to the
blue one to where m is ah
sorry oh that's another lady
uh yeah no not a blender
like a isn't the blender just um like
like it's like um
a thing on the stick
and then you mash stuff with it
you know pure puree
stick blender yeah it needed something
like that but i didn't have it so
for both i just i tried using my
smoothie mixer
it didn't blend everything perfectly but
it worked out
it worked rather well for the
curry sauce
the sausage sauce
but for the
the pestle the tomat tomato pesto
it didn't work so well for that but
you gotta
improvise it provides overcome adapt no
improvise adapt overcome
adapt and provides overcome which one is
it
it's moving
this movie is a mixer now
this movie has many talents yeah yeah
improvised adapt overcome
there you go
oh
yeah so that was pretty good but then
when i i did everything according to the
recipe okay i used all the ingredients
that they sent me
the right amount and all that because i
mean you can only use the right amount
because that's exactly what they sent to
you
but then
when i tasted it it tasted kind of lame
so thank god i had some actual
tomato
pesto sauce
like some already finished sauce so i
just i didn't put everything and i just
put in a little bit for a better taste
because before that it barely tasted
like tomato even though i was supposedly
making tomato pesto by myself
but i ended up just mixing in a little
bit of finished sauce
[Laughter]
i'm once again improvising
but i still made the sauce it just
didn't taste so good and that's that's
not my fault that's the fault of
why am i going back there
oh
that's the fault of them
my car
thought of the recipe not my phone
where's my home
oh beautiful it's my safe house oh
[Music]
damn he's rich as hell
nice improvising
indeed oh sick
[Music]
nice
one day
i want
a changing room like that
oh nice kitchen whoa
holy [\h__\h] how did you get so rich
i don't know
damn
crime oh
all right yeah yeah and we robbed the
bank and got like 179 000.
why the [\h__\h] not he is not oh my god she
has a [\h__\h] stamp
she has a [\h__\h] [\h__\h] stamp
that's what you call it right
yes he's just like me we both still use
wired headphones but at that time he
probably didn't have much choice
music
what's up
wait
you
are you doing
what do you want okay i come by for that
drink you offered that's all
i wasn't really serious
what if you're not serious about it then
don't [\h__\h] offer it in the first
place
man i never robbed you that was just a
repossession okay
whatever you want to call it i really
don't care
what can i do for you [\h__\h] i just came
by to see if there's something i can
help you with uh i see you doing well
for yourself
what would you think he would need help
with staying at a [\h__\h] sunset
you know i've been in this game for a
lot of years
and i got out alive uh-huh
that makes me the right age
you look like a good kid
but if you want my advice
give this [\h__\h] up
you work hard screw over everybody that
you love
hurt what do you mean give this [\h__\h] up
if we compare these two people here if
you're
what he's doing is actually innocent
he's just doing what his boss is telling
him to do and repossessioning the cars
it's not necessarily illegal is it
so what i saw the other day was like
when a corpse briefly reanimates itself
and terrorizes everyone right what you
saw the other day
was a guy dealing with pests i guess i
never saw myself as just before that's
illegal today's lesson's all about sound
illegal
tomorrow we'll try a training month it's
just a way cleaning what uh it's just a
i was just looking just how you make
things look you know yeah i can see you
spend a lot of time there as much as i
can so that's why you're here in
vinewood then right gotta be good at it
because i'm just turning things around
twisting them
thinks that imported palm trees are a
good substitute for not really knowing
what the [\h__\h] you're doing on this earth
jesus man
you a good time you know that
i tell you what
least i can do is buy you that beer huh
there's a little bar i like oh that's
not too far from here
let's go all right me i'm fine isn't it
a bit early for a beer
we're taking my wife's car oh
didn't me how do i pick up the phone
again i'm going for a drink dad [\h__\h] i
mean our boat going down the western
highway no it's it's been stolen my butt
what
the yacht's been stolen
trying to sell it i know you didn't want
it sold but i need money if they don't
want to buy it they just want to take it
in the head you're insane
all right i'm coming for my boat
unbelievable all righty then whoever
that jimmy is he's losing his head he's
in trouble
he's darling bully
get in amanda's car
well can i check those amanda is um
is she the one who flirt who was
flirting with the tennis instructor or
[Music]
is she here
just wanna make sure
there's nothing going on here in my
house
oh what's this cute
cute
oh the door opens both ways
sick
okay no one here actually it sounds like
no one's here my son's in trouble that's
my son
okay where's the car
uh
oh wait
is it the blue dot
this one
[Music]
you're getting in you wanna help me i'm
gonna teach you how we do it
i'm gonna show you how it's done lesson
number one
don't ever have kids hey man look if i
had kids i don't think no parenting
issues would arise over who had both
privileges and who don't [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] would be lucky to sit in
the bathtub [\h__\h] things that desperate
huh oh but you know [\h__\h] i was making a
point
mythologizing self-deprecation i know it
well yeah man but [\h__\h] where the boat is
little shit's been hiding there's
somewhere on the western highway man
ain't you worried about my boat
yeah i am hell yeah i always buy another
boat yeah tell my account oh you gonna
get something you're gonna always get
credit for one right are you all right
no thank you
all right
i ain't your homie i'm someone you want
to impress real man i thought you was
retired why the [\h__\h] do i want to
impress some slip away [\h__\h]
because i can still teach you a thing or
two maybe help you open the door to all
the joys that boat-related parenting
issues entails so i'm gonna help you get
this boat back right there you are my
friend
this dude is winning
michael was his name he's winning
well this this scenery looks familiar i
feel like
me and my friend we drove
um when we were driving to the beach we
drove by in like an
area like this yeah it was also like a
circle like this
yeah yeah yeah yeah oh my god it looks
exactly like this
oh there there there it is that's my
fault i don't see it
i only saw a truck that's a trap we'll
catch them
what boats
what i just arrived [\h__\h]
oh my heart
oh it's on the track i thought it was
normally a boat should be on the water
oh that's a bug there it is that's my
fault you're both in a [\h__\h] hurry man
yeah we'll catch em
that body is the recipe on water
they give
oh my god oh my god oh my god
[Music]
[Applause]
an immediate effect
[Laughter]
frankly
oh there there there it is and that's my
boat
in a [\h__\h] hurry man yeah well we'll
catch em i'm coming for you
okay focus focus
focus focus focus
so i'm guessing we should get him on the
side or is it right at the back good too
but that's like so scary how how can i
not crash go go jump on it go jump on it
you [\h__\h] idiot
i gave you the right moment
the back
okay
he's taking his sweet time down
there there it is
i'm giving him everything i got a
[\h__\h] house
get into the [\h__\h] boat
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] hello [\h__\h] israel
oh that was that was uh
hopefully not jimmy
switch to him get to jump on him
no i can't sounds really difficult too
to play him right now
you want me to shoot your [\h__\h] hands
off of him
oh
[Music]
i really did that didn't i
all right now look for my son
holy [\h__\h]
yeah
[Music]
oh
wait wait wait do i get it i get it i
get it okay
[Music]
who's driving now
who is who's driving
nice safe that was really close
oh yeah okay you too
and on the ride
that everyone
all right time to get the boat back
it's just a thing at least you still got
a son
hey it's a chop shop back there dawg if
you drive us there you can get the ride
fit okay
really man
this song's my boat
we should have set priorities straight
both first and then please stop doing
that listen
i [\h__\h] up okay
i'm not going to lie that was a really
bad judgment call yeah [\h__\h] dad i nearly
died and all you give a [\h__\h] about is
his [\h__\h] body wait i'm just like a
dad
all we do is scream at each other no
wonder i can't get a job it's all your
[\h__\h] fault or it's not but it's
partly your fault [\h__\h] traffic jam i
just want to impress you
by selling my boat to some gang bangers
i know it sounds dumb when you put it
like that but
all you do is daydream or get angry look
i love you jimmy but you're an [\h__\h]
oh and right now with my boat
disappearing over the horizon that's all
i can see my boat franklin did you do me
a bear give this kid a ride home after
they fix this thing i want to head but
the road in peace
oh great leave me with the home invader
and thank you
no problem damn enough all right
oh we're already becoming best buddies
you call me a cab
franklin and michael love forever t.t
hey
i need a cab as soon as you can send one
los santos customs by the airport
all right thanks
customs hey so you uh do much yachting
not anymore no i don't before i mean man
no not really
this little [\h__\h] stays in this room all
day and i don't have any other people to
go with you know
i like looking at it looking yeah yeah i
come down to the marina sit on the dock
pour myself a drink nine and look at her
look at who jacqueline huh did it clear
my head you're not gonna name me a boat
jacqueline huh
well maybe you need to do some other
[\h__\h] to fear your time dream other
dreams man yeah sure whatever
yes
don't let your dreams be dreams just do
it
i am michael
i didn't
i didn't think i would um relate so much
to him but i guess
hey this is the place up here i know
this dude man his name how he gonna look
after me all right take what's in my
pocket a couple thousand bucks that'll
cover it right yeah it should be cool
good
all right we have we have arrived safely
yeah i got this all right everyone
relates to michael you know
it's all good though man you're gonna
get your hair right all right all right
listen thanks for today i appreciate it
that went really well though i would say
you see fit pretty well sorry we're
gonna get your boat man
come on man let's trick this whip we'll
get the boat eventually
you can't just steal a boat
you can't just do that i won't forget
about it
one does not simply steal a boat
one does not simply walk into model
yet amanda's car repaired all right yes
click here let's do it bro mama wants a
sport what she wants in here
how oh there okay oh can we
back up
you can do it i believe in you we're
going backwards we have to learn this
from my driver's license in the future
oh [\h__\h] i'm so good
i have a real talent for this
oh
come in
if you don't open the door how am i
supposed to do it oh it only reacts to
the front of my car i think
franklin see if you drive especially
okay okay okay
well yeah take your time dawg
this looks
like ride oh so nostalgic can we pick my
ride oh i remember empty me pimp my
rides good old sons little times
sometimes they would put [\h__\h]
jacuzzis into the back of the car or all
this [\h__\h] that's really sick
like i said bro trick it
drink it
pimp it
every exhibit
exhibit
uh oh so what how do we repair this
do i bunk bunk bunk huh
no wait what i don't know how to do this
are you trying to think of like the
sickest ride that's even conceivable
um repair vehicles it is new oh wow
my mama's car had almost as much work as
my mom
this wagon gonna be sick carbon hood
oh
but honestly like is it worth it because
like
i mean this is my car so do i is there
no way of like losing my own car
completely
we're not gonna buy now but maybe in the
future you know
yeah mom's down will win with some sick
rgb lights
wait i don't see the neon where's the
neon
oh well
don't come through
it's not mike oh yeah it's amanda's car
but it's family
it stays in the family you know
all right man i'm taking you home
it's franklin right yeah frank all the
credit for our guy the home invader you
know what call me what you like man
yeah i i no i i mean when he's so nice
frankie so nice or james
jimmy
or just like
jesus putting up with jimmy's
so uh what's the deal man huh the
babysitter
i see you at the dealership and someone
steals my whip and pop is all like he's
been down there to talk to you guys your
props did more than talk what'd he do
look man if he ain't kidding i ain't
gonna tell but i lost my [\h__\h] job and
i thought maybe he could help me find a
new dude my dad is retired like fully
like his only marketable skills are
watching tv and daytime drinking man
look i don't know homie he seems okay to
me
[\h__\h] he saved your ass
you saved my ass
well well maybe we could indeed teamwork
okay
if it keeps him out of the house
sorry that's cool by me
yeah well we'll see look i'm sorry my
dad lost to your job it's hard out there
tough i mean
i didn't get a job i've never had a job
wow
for life
she's just kind of disappeared hey you
play rachel slaughter uh he's a gamer my
sister first couple okay
you guys said everyone relates to
michael but i'm sure there's some people
who relate to uh jimmy
what
well i love them you know this is really
obnoxious people
who make these boom boom boom boom boom
sounds
to annoy other people
be like a certain dominance
we all hate jimmy
wanna have all this to me does the game
tell you
all right
you'll move
hi yo oh go cat
yeah
that's what i'm saying
dang
nice car
oh i can blow my horn
how do you blow your horn
jimmy's like 20.
dude
jamie i'm so disappointed
gee gee
was that no that was not my horn that
was someone else's one
it was not it was not g
h are the lights oh good to know
f
oh [\h__\h] you
oh yeah
guys i thought you guys know how to play
this game
you know nothing about this game don't
ya
[Music]
so like since we're both unemployed like
we run together you know right yeah i
think about it home run to where or we
could just like choppy you know what
does that mean get our drink on
strip clubs oh god dude i get real crazy
yeah i got your numbers you get real
crazy huh hey you know what may go easy
on your pops dawg all right all right
church
church exactly man church my brother
from another mother i mean
i hope so cause my mom was kind of a
skank back in the day
yeah whatever homie peach
funny i like the
interactions that everybody has this is
very funny
so far i'm enjoying it
more than i thought i would all right um
what are we doing next
do i switch to
my boy
no i don't think i can
oh sick car but i'm taking this one
again oh
i've had to life invader accept my
request and we can hang hit me up
anytime bro nah
nah
no i wanna
switch to michael oh
all right
oh
just fine right here thanks oh
we're done
where are we going next michael
is it far i don't know how far that m is
should i get in the car
this one i want this one
i want the ice cream truck or whatever
that
is nice car please
map
and how do i look into the big map
m m is just
escape
ah
oh that's relatively far yeah okay i'm
gonna go grab a car
feel so bad about stealing though
[Music]
you guys automatically know what these
cards are just by looking at them
because i definitely don't
grand theft auto oh you're right it's in
the title
sorry that is a is that a maserati
most of them some of them
no idea about car standing just like me
a lot of them are fictional oh but i'm
sure they took inspiration from certain
models cool
oh cool
i'm just like car shopping here i'm i'm
window shopping for cars
you got lucky buddy
yeah
hi somebody's so lucky
[Music]
yeah mixed together oh really
where's that
wait am i going i'm going to the m right
isn't that my home again
[Music]
oh
oh um
oh scene
oh man franklin are you are you in there
in the car where i left you
[Laughter]
so many cars here what the [\h__\h]
who whose cars are those
who aren't
someone in my home is it a tennis
instructor
again
construction cowboy
uh-oh
this mission oh oh do i have to censor
something
are they are they doing yeah buy stuff
are they
having an affair
tracy
yo
tracy don't disappoint me
no sensor okay
too many cars in the in front of the
house
yeah yeah yeah yeah i know exactly the
cars already gave it away they don't
have to look at those
amanda
you better not be that in my house
michael go away
150 bucks an hour to [\h__\h] my wife in my
own bed michael go away oh i'm sorry bro
she said you hadn't you and i are gonna
have an arrangement oh read your [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] personal story so lame i promise
you
you're talking about this session or
something else huh i'll die
bastard i'm gonna [\h__\h] kill him hey
you stop it what's up man is she not
happy with what michael has been
offering her that was a misunderstanding
villa [\h__\h] beautiful cars a
beautiful pool [\h__\h] it i'm in let's roll
let's get this [\h__\h] yeah yeah
yeah yeah oh yes we will kill him
the way she shuts the door like that's
like a [\h__\h] teenager all right let's
go
hey we ain't gonna get that dude at this
rate [\h__\h] yeah we ain't gonna get him we
ain't gonna get him what's the [\h__\h] he's
lost his eggs
in the canyon we'll find him oh oh
okay
what the [\h__\h] is
[Music]
if i gotta go to a motel she's gotta go
to her no let her get crabs for a change
you got crabs what no man cause i like
those oh crap
this guy is really bad at driving it's
not me strong
oh oh that's okay something else
i thought it was the
pokey things in the bed
oh oh my gosh
oh oh i'm not paying for that no no no
no no no
[Music]
but they are in an open relationship
really that makes no sense that he would
get mad then
okay this is the turn
beautiful landscape though
oh nice
you're telling me oh that is accessible
that's pretty sick
little pricks up there look oh [\h__\h]
coat's doing all right for yourself what
where oh up there
[Music]
let's go kill him
you're not coming oh back in the truck
hi hi hi hi hi
there's a winch i'm too [\h__\h] out of
the truck
supports up there
he's gonna pull his deck down looks like
a house made in [\h__\h] rust man you
really gonna be this [\h__\h] dramatic
yeah whatever terrible terrible failed
fishing bud well there were a lot of
freaking sessions bud i'm thinking you
were working on that jester backhand i'm
gonna hang him down come a long way bro
but sometimes it's got to get worse to
get better yeah well maybe i should come
up there and practice my backhand yeah
on your face
energy is seriously bringing me down oh
i hope it is
[Music]
seriously how
you got the wrong idea pal whoa you know
yeah an eye for an eye
okay we're doing it this way all right
[Applause]
that's not
call this realistic good revenge wow
[\h__\h] a let's see how he liked that
whoa man
[\h__\h] him yeah [\h__\h] his neck hey homer i
think you put a little more than that
yeah that's a foolish man who builds his
house on sand
hey man i don't think my boy matthew was
thinking trucks when he wrote that [\h__\h]
okay bye-bye
ah
[\h__\h]
does he have like a black princess or so
because that was a very dramatic way of
taking revenge
[\h__\h]
oh bro i couldn't afford a place like
that i'm a tennis coach i hit balls for
a living
just [\h__\h] terrified sorry i'm so i'm
so sorry green light excuse me
this car sucks [\h__\h] yo
whoa
oh
martin
martin madrasso my dress what you said
damn dude's a king
man you better hope i ain't hoping
anything
chick was a stir
chill out
hey man wait what are the wrenches right
behind you wait i lost you where i need
to go all right help me deal with this
what why are they after me
[Music]
oh that makes no difference
oh no
[\h__\h] man these [\h__\h] are me
[Music]
oh god oh oh i'm supposed to shoot them
you're gonna use that gun you'll have to
keep the car
what's the pedal man we gotta move
come on kid
shoot that gun kid
can you see them
[Music]
hey let's go let's leave them boys
[Applause]
wow
[\h__\h]
you did good what what sorry what what i
mean your aim's all over the place but
you were a hell no
thanks my aim was on point hey don't get
defensive
go to a shooting race work on your end
you'll do fine nice aim thank you
good
got a few knocks you okay
you did good kid man i'm cool man i mean
mentally oh man i'm [\h__\h] x my heart
ain't [\h__\h] like that in years oh
yes
[\h__\h] hey bubba
you sound kind of manly you just been
greenlit by the way he needs to go to
therapy again trust me is that what we
want for me wherever the [\h__\h] martin
madrazo is
i've known worse
we just handled a few low ranking clans
we sit on it we see what happens
kid there's no use second-guessing
felt good man
do something for a change hello are you
martina
oh no oh no our waste is sitting by that
[\h__\h] fool man you're right
i need to do something scotch and
sunshine is sitting on my ass
[\h__\h] that i'm better than that i think i
need to have a talk with my
dying wife you don't pass that [\h__\h] on
it's gone homie i bet you know some [\h__\h]
we know all kinds of [\h__\h] hey thanks for
the help out there today thanks i had no
idea was going to get that hot hell yeah
pulling up it's crazy
went a little bit too far yeah well i
thought i was through with all that [\h__\h]
we should have just killed him instead
of killing the house
oh [\h__\h] i think we're about to find out
oh oh
oh hello
um you know who i am no you don't know
who i am no idea do you daddy no
i think so good
i know who you are i know where you live
who are you i know where your house
lives
license license plans
will check make sure it's the right
franklin no
franklin
maybe
help mr de santa here who am i no idea i
think martin madrazzo i guess
if we connect the dots i guess a little
off the background
and mr madrazzo he's really mad
mr madrazo is a legitimate businessman
just wrongfully accused of running a
mexican-american gang and a narcotic
ring right charges
because of the witnesses came up really
missing smart kid
no
michael
got a question for you oh yes i can
answer everything
did you pull an architecturally
significant
wonder home you're done
i thought the owner was banging
literally taken out of breath strange
house for a tennis coach ah i always
think it's straight
you need to build it on piccolo's level
really well if it's that easy to take
down it was just crap near the hotel
while you finance the rebuild won't [\h__\h]
sure no
location here
they're ripping
yeah somewhere in the 2.5 million range
of course
great
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
he's a funny guy
come on man he's such a funny guy damn
you
i
never better
so what now
looks like i'm gonna have to postpone my
retirement
[\h__\h]
let's rob some more bands stuff to my
eyeballs
look i only know one way to make money
um i'm gonna have to give an old friend
a call um
lester
i think he's in town somewhere
i'm gonna have to track him down
just give me a little alone time all
right
all right though
oh
it's so sweet
[Music]
wow back in business
marriage counseling
ah
that there was no talking involved i
feel like counseling normally involves
talking
hello
is this still the number for lester
crest who's asking who's asking who's
asking you're awful cagey
[Music]
even for a dead man what the [\h__\h]
michael dustin you don't sound good
buddy
tactful and charming even in death hey
come see me old friend i'm living in los
santos just like you marietta heights
whoa whoa wait hey how do you hello yeah
you [\h__\h] what why
okay
let's grab a car
um the l is it the l
[Music]
oh no
no yes
wait
don't go yet
i need to borrow
any
any way you could like fall out of the
car anymore dramatically
doc hey
oh i'm looking through my appointment
book and i don't see your name oh yeah
well i'm more of a walk-in guy
walk-ins are more expensive but i'm
always happy to accommodate
you'll accommodate me as long as i got
money in my pocket right hey i'm in a
bad way is that the end that's frank
doesn't stand for the doctor
michael can now see dr friedlander at
uh the thinking bubble
can we ride the zeppelin
up there oh sorry sorry i see some bad
drivers but you
[Music]
yeah
oh my god
amanda
not getting another coach anytime soon
someone
needs someone to play with my group are
you [\h__\h] kidding me is she honestly
breaking up
oh my god
can't believe this girl
[Music]
tennis
tennis and like golf and all that
if you send
your wife to do that kind of sport
with a teacher
you know those sports the way they teach
those sports very very very
intimate sensitive
be careful
oh wrong lane huh
goddammit
uh
[Music]
quick gps
ah lester
huh
hmm
where the [\h__\h] am i
that's a therapist
i am
i don't see myself
is this me no that's me oh we're pretty
close
crazy
never mind we're pretty close thank you
boo
mo
wait you don't see me driving
hey
okay maybe that one
oh fire people
fire people my friends
oh
oh do i have to go up
double click ah
i'm like there
i'm right there
and then
waypoint
[Music]
aha
nice
okay that helps
on it can i get out of here here
a pitch with
shut the [\h__\h] up
they speak so much like valley girls
[Music]
sorry i know you're just doing your job
respect that
hi
i have arrived should be here
and i come here for again alex is like
my old buddy right
uh
i just walk into the house
which one this one
mushy mushy
you gonna let me in or what give me a
minute
ah before andrey take down doug
okay hello what what the [\h__\h] mess
i was wondering when you'd show up damn
boy you live like this praise be
i guess you weren't very dead oh my god
you oh need my help
how do you know
cause you came here why else would you
i haven't been a good friend for you
lester i know
and you're gonna make it up to me by
doing whatever i ask
or rather i mean
i need something done you need to know
something so why not help each other
i gotta make some dough
so you're back in the game
i guess
look lester about what happened before
i know you never mentioned my name i
know i'm not on any lists anywhere
i know you never betrayed me
as for you you got to figure that i
never told anyone oh are you the one
that makes like the bombs for us
and you're angrily decomposing in los
santos with a shrink
and a wife who don't love you no more
yeah yeah well
since you put it like that shut up a
minute i'm getting an ifind alert i find
that little college boy sack of [\h__\h]
phony [\h__\h]
who
jay norris yes that [\h__\h] is a lying
bastard i've read his [\h__\h] emails
he's a [\h__\h] cheat
i heard him say that he saved america
what by outsourcing all the jobs
by selling us little bits of plastic
restricted access [\h__\h] well now it's
payback time you lying
turd the hell are you talking about you
are about to get that white collar gig
that you always dreamed of mikey here
take this uh
fashionably retro weird for a 45 year
old man but i cannot let go of the 1980s
bag
and dress yourself up like a billionaire
math genius with low-level asperger's
uh-huh you better be ready for the minor
glitch of your repulsive
pseudo-messianic life okay lester get
out of here
get out call me when you're ready
we are about to put the darwinism back
in social darwinism
and brother it is gonna be fun you
[\h__\h] kidding me i'm a bank robber not
a web designer so we'll go robbing soon
i'll find something just like the old
days
okay can i have a sip of that
can i have
please
okay
go to the suburban store in vinewood
well we're buying a suit
with the i guess there's cash in the bag
this is the car i was taking
sensor on this mission okay well to be
honest like um
i probably won't
unless you guys tell me very far ahead
like at least
you know there's some delay as well
i have a feeling like i won't be
successful at really censoring [\h__\h]
sensor when you get on the computer okay
the computer you say
okay
alrighty
wow well see this car moves so much
better than the [\h__\h] truck we had on
the previous mission
like you really expect me
to
like
successfully escape
in an escape mission
with that shitty truck really
it's a sports guy yeah nice what's that
what is that
pretend
whoa
no i don't have a driving license no but
i like safe driving
i enjoy safe driving
no reckless driving please
like um actually
i think uh once in my life i was in a
car
uh
that had an accident that was on the on
the passenger seat
once in my life it was not a big
accident and um
no no big problemo
but
the friend
who was driving the car
generally drive was a bit reckless often
oh damn i'm driving in a circle
yeah but it was
like um i had to explain this it was a
normal road not a highway like this
outside
uh let me try to explain let's imagine
this is a normal road a side road and
then in front of me this is a main road
right going from left to right okay
and
like we were driving out of the side
road and then i think someone bumped
into us
but i'm not sure anymore whose fault it
was already a long time ago but i think
it was kind of our fault like i didn't
do [\h__\h] though
i didn't do [\h__\h]
obviously
oh wait uh that way ah that way
cool
that's where i was supposed to go here
ah
yeah i did nothing wrong
but i know
the driver was not paying attention very
well
that was shocking
but thankfully that was i think the only
time in my life
did you guys ever get into an accident
before
yeah nothing really bad happened i
didn't get hurt or anything
yeah yeah oh so many of you oh
did someone bump into you or did you
bump into someone was it your fault or
the other person's fault
safe driving guys
oh yeah i know my car's hunt
he hit us i got sandwiched yes
unfortunately me bumping oh no
i bumped the deer oh no
well that's i mean you know
tears they do
whatever
better than you know
having an accident with like
humans now that's an interesting car
they talk about my car
yeah yes but it's kind of [\h__\h] up
hello
ah
excuse me
what kind of clothes are we looking for
tech company i'm thinking i need
something i don't know techy geeky
youthful you've lost your job and the
world's moved on huh
that's too bad i didn't lose my job
of course he was retired okay got
outside it's his choice thing happened
to my dad
now you gotta fit in with a different
generation
what about a vest and some cargo shorts
cargo shorts all right
i guess i said um i'm having trouble
recalling what car this is not cargo
shorts we're wearing right now a cargo
shorts the long ones with like a like a
fold in the front
what do you call cargo shorts
how do i where do i
is this
is this where i get the cargo shorts oh
yeah oh no those are cargo shorts
this this i mean we're supposed to look
geeky yeah
geeky geeky i don't know
uh yeah whatever [\h__\h]
shorts really shorts
we're going for shorts
but
yeah it should be one of those oh yeah
oh
oh yeah
that's so cute
[Laughter]
no but maybe
maybe that one
yeah selecting that one
did i buy it dignity aside i think that
might just work thank you i know but i
already have you i already have pants
like that do i really need to get new
ones is that
important can i maybe
um
i mean he still looks like
too old
wait what about oh
i can't buy those
[Music]
oh jackets
sick
oh those jackets
whoa
[Music]
i can go now is this boomer enough
i look like
i look like i have a midlife crisis
uh this is really what we're going for
is that how we earn the respect of
something yeah baby zoomers
i mean the car the car might impress you
know
i can't dress to impress what i can
drive to impress happy feet
you get like
a hippie feet big massage or what
hi michael i'm all dressed up now you
want to run me through this thing the
prototype is somewhere in the life
invader office find it and fit it with
the device in your bag they just gonna
let me in why wouldn't they if you look
the part let's hang around to someone
act entitled fine abs entitled all right
let's become a karen
whoa
i'm getting really good at driving while
looking at the gps though without
crashing into things compared to how i
was driving in the beginning of the
stream
i must say quite improvement
right
oh yeah sensor for the computer okay
okay i'll probably just turn off the
screen i don't know
[Music]
that's probably the safest option
oh [\h__\h]
uh what
what where oh there
oh
[Music]
go to the rear entrance okay
i drive better than ama
really
let me get like an
image
[Music]
perfect
how big
and where where exactly is this is this
good
i honestly really don't even know what
would happen to me if i
um
if i accidentally show some nudity on
stream i don't know
um
if you get immediately
like banned or so
what what exactly happens i never
happened to me before
life invader
it's not nude
oh okay
what
hey it's quite suggestive oh okay
pm's pushing for more functionality
it's already on monetization so i think
features especially if we plan on
releasing a fully priced update a year
later
oh my you know yeah well you know you're
gonna get you were already chit chatting
i mean we're talking data in q4 maybe q3
look milestones are one thing but when
design is changing its mind right right
right right right i mean we're talking
so much so it's strange what you can do
about it
my union allocated smoke brick spout up
so don't think a minute do i know each
other this guy is able to keep secrets i
think so
i i t temp right oh totally i look like
an attempt to you okay do something for
me
you gotta put it in a ticket ah no
i'd like to keep this one out of the
database if you know what i mean
okay
what that was easy
[Music]
to sweat lots of sauna becoming a tech
evangelist when the big boys fast maybe
not even tech i'll evangelize anything
yeah bye okay uh what uh up there okay
froggy mama
where's my mouse where's my mouse i'm
gonna focus my mouse
what
i don't see my mouse
huh
where's my mouse
not yet but i don't even find my mouse
when i'm on the desktop what oh it's at
the bottom i can't get out of the screen
i know i can there we go
again
hi
oh hi
chill out on the bean bag marcus will be
right out
oh um i'm going to take you
i have a terrible bag home company yeah
the brief was for a relaxed creative
individual the kind the preferred i like
it oh you're so it's a cool place to
work at hey guys really they're not big
enough
we're taking a good look at it huh
okay what's up
here you go if you guys let me use the
os i requested this wouldn't be a
problem
oh you've been added on this pc
uh
got any antivirus software i think so
behind this junk on the left clicked in
nsfw link bro bit me on the ass yeah not
safe for work huh you know my son's
computer runs into the same kind of
problems i close the pop-ups
shark tanks
start them early bro you write your best
stuff in your tweens after that it's
just a hack job
well i'm supposed to click away
everything why i get all these migraines
really interesting with the middle
they gotta send me on another one of
those seminars
another one popped up
oh it's like a game might be faster than
the pop-ups
yeah give me a second will ya oh
[Music]
oh
military girl it's actually kind of
stressful too ain't it something else
out here i don't have the manual on me
okay we got some
is it okay to show now i wonder oh [\h__\h]
face i'll try to boot up this anti-virus
no
not yet yes
[Laughter]
cause my hands are free
there it goes
[Laughter]
you want to take a break for some air
guitar give me the wink bro exterminate
my son probably wrote this a little [\h__\h]
bag
and that's very effective why don't you
try and keep things strictly safe for
work from now
[Music]
when norris announces it at the keynote
minds
[Music]
this is the future of american economy
jay thinks being a quirky douche boosts
creativity
he's this close to installing a ball pit
he's become such a [\h__\h]
if we don't keep smiling the cameras
will pick it up and we'll be outsourced
to mali
[Music]
it's a good thing we got rid of that
morality clause yeah oh my god [\h__\h] that
morality [\h__\h] morale welcome bienvenue
bienvenidos enjoy because we're all
about to be outsourced
nice to meet you man for a social
network i feel like we
i don't belong here
i don't fit in
how does the song go
again what i'm just uh
i can just exit now making history dude
leaving mine back there without the
little guys
bye welcome
welcome or so yeah he left the bag what
what
really
you know i thought that
fast
don't worry about it oh don't find come
on you're going to learn the foot bag if
you want to get a job oh we called it
hacky sack in german
i think if that's a guitar oh oh
no sorry follow me okay you suck at the
air guitar you need more passion
believe in yourself
oh okay they didn't they didn't call it
a hacker sack though maybe it wasn't the
hacker there was a totally non-passive
aggressive note on it
if i drown in mucus
it's your fault your illiterate effing
sees they're like trying to pretend she
doesn't exist she's not there
what if i suddenly start a fight can i
do that can i like punch these people in
their face
[Music]
send a cat picture to my fellow
employees
every day is candy day you can send cat
pictures to your employees
oh i want to work here i want to receive
cat pictures i want to send cat pictures
of my cats
boast my kitty cats
all right um
wait a second where are we
going oh let me get that card out that
car is beautiful gorgeous
hey michael hold on hold on
don't i don't ya lester
the thing's in the prototype i'm going
home to watch the keynote teabag time my
friend lester did you hear me oh yes no
one is not dead yeah yeah sorry the
phone is rigged what's your problem you
don't like shooters they're all the same
yeah besides you know me i'm a movie guy
classic monkey colors channels
i don't really know it's just
superheroes
and remakes none of which interest me
hey
i believe this country can still make
interesting movies there's no better way
to define american life and a two-hour
plot in which the hero looks good and
defeats evil oh my god now whatever you
say enjoy yesterday
anyway just call the device after he's
unveiled it and then we'll talk
michael love of my life
let's go
although i would prefer him without the
all the crime
just like me for real for real hello
oh my god you guys are so lame oh no
i'm watching fame
[Music]
fantastic
how long does this go thank you
thank you oh god thank you so much it's
great to be back thank you
fame or shame completely original
television something you've never seen
we've got desperados performing change
has been oh yeah yeah we've got an
analogy
what if i don't wanna and everything
together we are down to the top acts
it's the finals
have you guys never just continued
watching they were
i know i can change the channel but i
don't wanna
phew let's save the venom for the axe
they're not even out yet
you have a stylist
what's he dressed you as what they call
this look wow morg chic mooring chic
rose dead
wow
come on you those he just got bullied on
this show
guy
or gay
deep in the closet his friends call him
okay wow so funny gentlemen please
welcome
to the stage
wait for dinner to pull out the
prototype phone and then give him a call
hey
uh-huh
this company has wait how do i call him
a long way since we started it in my
parents pool house in east carraway
today you're about to witness a new
phase
full on weapons grade red alert world
domination
combination
private data whatever he says don't
really listen every penny we could be a
zombie of the society
we have one of the youngest workforces
in the world downward button average age
of only
14.4 years that's not just impressive
it's revolutionary let's just press both
today
right here we're about to make the next
step
prepare to witness
the future
[Applause]
dude you won't believe it i'm in the
future now mobile device
yes we have invented something no one
else has ever thought of
a small
hold on a second
i think someone's trying to talk with me
uh-huh
hello
jesus whoa
whoa what the
holy [\h__\h]
um
oh okay why did we do this though
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
that that was an easy kill huh
damn what
what
last
that was heavy you watching the news i
don't have to i'm watching the markets
i'll be trading pure alpha till close
all right
hey about that other thing oh we don't
care about the same yeah yeah absolutely
let's do it put on a suit look somewhat
professional and meet me at my warehouse
off the ls freeway oh and i'm about to
email you a link for the exchange you
can put in some trades of your own i'm
trying to stay off the day trading
maybe i'll take a look
okay now go for a swim
nice
why is it so [\h__\h] loud here
can't relax even for a second
so noisy
stocks
okay
damn that's uh some heavy [\h__\h] michael
my money where is it you do not want me
to visit you again next time it'll be so
much worse
um i don't have so much money yet can
you
wait a bit longer i'm on it though i'm
i'm out of my retirement i'm
i'm working on it
[Music]
oh it's probably um
me another timeline someone's good
someone's uh
on the run
just like me
for real for real
okay we are going to
l
right wait let me let me figure out
uh
how do we do this
again wait what
what is it again
i thought it was a double click there we
go
i know
okay
oh wait have to grab a suit here oh wait
there's a store right there apparently
over there is that
maybe a fitting store
this one
perhaps that looks fancy
oh we're getting out on the other side
whoopsie
was it the same place that we went to
before no
oh they have suits definitely
come in look around
okay
press e to breast oh
he looks like he's from the mafia but
look at that
look at those prices
oh
oh not bad i mean lanky some suits
this way he looks like
he looks like
i know how to describe it he looks very
rich with that
oh but ah
we should go for the cheapest one that
one's cheap
okay
my money
that makes sense
imported no
oh but they told me
to buy a suit
make sure you mommy the students at home
are not the same
this one's cool
she got a [\h__\h] poodle
how do i get into the car oh [\h__\h]
can't get into that car anymore
all right i'm going to get into this car
seriously at home
um
[Music]
sorry
oh what is this funny looking car
whoops uh
[Music]
how do i turn them off
oh it's oh it was the other car maybe it
was the other car
nice
goes away after a while okay good good
good
oh stick
clean
might be a good time to start making
some moves in stock market
really um i don't know i don't believe
your [\h__\h]
nah
i don't trust you buddy
should i is that really is it good in
the game
is it actually a smart choice
bye bye bye
[Music]
well how do i
how do i do that do i have to can i do
it on my phone
maybe for the text let's just send wait
where's the lester text
ah
stock training
and i choose that
oh there you go
how do i buy my cash 3 800.
sorry
ah
what's the right thing to buy
buy high or something with a with a
green or something with a red arrow
i'm in the news
mommy i've made it i'm in the news live
invader
that's kind of ironic
okay
what now do i go like this
how much
go all in
really
don't
i'll spy whatever confirm continue
okay
not that
it will drop in oh i didn't go all in
i don't understand
should i sell
now we wait we just hope for hope for an
improvement
what else maybe a burger shot
i i don't know i don't i don't know how
to read this kind of [\h__\h]
uh
vanilla unicorn
can i buy elena
let's team
this is cheap
okay here
is that good
let's just see maybe let me let me out
of here
okay now
more important things to do than that
i've invested
[Music]
some good money hopefully you get a lot
of money back from them um
so that
this dude
not gonna kill us
when he gets too angry until impatient
we don't want that oh
yeah who's this i don't know this number
from life invader oh i know you're the
bro who deactivated jay bro no i don't
know what you're talking about what
you're talking about
what you do is your business bro anyway
jay really got a big head once people
started calling him a god guess you
proved he wasn't one they reintegrated
my team in burundi after the design got
signed off and now
my shares ain't worth dick sorry about
that i need work and i thought and still
i invested in the company i mean i'm
smart enough to track you in the company
where i just killed the head of the
company hey
right
[Music]
smart investment well
maybe it's smart because
if i killed that dude would i really
invest in this company you know later if
they investigate the crime they'll be
like it couldn't be him he just put like
half of his money into the company right
after he was killed
no one
with a sane
mind and
a part of a negative no with no one with
an insane mind and a negative
stance towards jay
would do that
so charlie
show me he's a good guy
anyway what should i go through the the
car doorway um
what was that wait why did i even go
here
isn't this where i need to go
a vehicle to use
okay i go inside then with the car
uh and to the l oh i don't know why i
came here
my brain just automatically decided to
go here
why did i when did i go here to the l
oh i marked the wrong place
i just marched the wrong place
ella's right there
okay that happens
[Music]
okay
don't be such a [\h__\h]
[Music]
the hell is this place garment factory
i needed a job that didn't require me to
do anything apart from uh paying taxes
uh huh
okay listen
what do you got
no i won some prize union depository and
they say it cannot be hit
has it been yet
look
i just owe some mexican hood a couple
million bucks because i wrecked his
girlfriend's house we'll need to go
crazy here which mexican martina thrazzo
he's not supposed to be very nice uh-huh
when i met him he was charming no room
was pretty nice accepting
um patience but now and that's a bank
and a stick so we do a store which do
you like
well a backpack store's usually easier
but i got to make a big take yeah well
gems it is then let's go to vangelico
buy ourselves an engagement ring we're
going to need a crew i can round up some
of the old guys there are no old guys
moses ironically he found jesus
irish crazies they mostly just
disappeared it's fine i got some you
guys got franklin and jimmy the eastern
european guy making moves
yeah he went quiet
all right well we're gonna need a crew
you got any contacts in ls or not
i've been working with someone but
they're too unpredictable i'll have to
reach out to me why not jimmy let's take
jimmy
ooh
all right see i knew
is that my car
i knew that
we would go into a different car that's
why i just jumped out of the other one
chihuahua is always a few steps ahead
your fib buddies they uh know you're
back in business fib buddies what are
you talking about i checked out the wpp
thing doesn't look like any whitsect
program i'm aware of for starters
they don't put witnesses up in
multi-million dollar mansions in
rockford hills well maybe they thought
this would be the best cover and most
witnesses don't transfer five figure
sums into a particular fib
excuse me
i'm trying to listen uh of course the
money gets moved around and washed
through a number of fronts but the trail
is there deposits and withdraws the same
sum every month agent
the shooting of a notorious stick-up man
michael town yeah yeah yeah yeah all
right
lester i'm very impressed
look uh we can talk about this another
time but take these glasses awesome my
eyesight's fine they're fitted with a
camera and a radio relay
technology you're in the store getting
what we need
nice we're well prepared huh
this is really chill i like this game
it's fun it's chill the driving is like
really chill
and the gameplay is not so difficult so
far
it's funny too got some funny dialogue
okay i'm here
jesus watch it
i'm here for some sweet diamonds
hey okay okay okay you want me to drive
a few uh
[Music]
a few more meters
towards the front okay
hi mom
things are great here okay let's get
this done i love it i'm to become a
superstar here in l.a
[Music]
this is my time
when are we taking what does he want us
to take photos off that's my proposal
and where exactly are we entering honey
phenomenal hey
frankly i think you'll be blown away oh
this is walking i get really cheap yeah
see the mini map
why don't we stop our car there
mm-hmm
[Music]
in here
what
what did he say hey cameras
all right camera
the doctor outside stop don't see one
thanks for opening the door i here sure
thank you
the alarm keypad is on the left when you
come in on the wall by the side door
glasses are live shoot away
the alarm the vents and the cameras come
on
okay that's their alarm
uh
i see a camera
great you got the security camera
ventilation in that shot
good work now speak to the assistant and
see if there's anything else we need to
know oh wait what about the vent okay
oh nice picture it's beautiful oh
jewelry so much fancy
what
oh come on i mean that's not really what
i want to do
you're kidding me
what
that's just
why
what the [\h__\h]
ventilation
what the cameras
hi i was just thinking about you sure
someone needs to say that
is on the left when you come in on the
wall by the side door
glasses are live shoot away
okay that's their alarm can you get me
an air vent in one of the cameras oh
okay i i guess i had both things in one
piece
the camera and the ventilation in that
shot
now i cracked the hair back to the
assistant
[Music]
outside of the counter
i need to pick up a little something for
the woman in my life
well one of them
i'm sure we can help you tell me about
her what's her taste
uh
tennis player you're talking about
she's really into tennis players i don't
want to spend time
maybe
ten grand our rings start at eight our
pendants start at 12.
all right
so these things built to last or am i
just paying for the evangelical logo
here
we use perfect clarity jewels
18 karat gold 950 platinum nothing but
the best
all right i think he just made a sale
i'm gonna take a look around oh that was
easy come back to you baby don't go
anywhere i understand okay i understand
i agree but i also don't understand come
back to me
she's like secretly thinking don't call
me baby
don't you dare call me baby
i understand so don't call me baby
i need to get eyes on the roof of the
building i understand but i've shown the
train
okay what that's in the building what a
photo from outside or what
what if you take any longer you're
risking blowing this whole thing
is that what you wanted
no i wasn't quite listening
go to the car okay okay okay oh hi
you're so impatient
drive us around the block we got to find
a way up to the roof
i think
that is easy
how about here
do i need to find like a
like a ladder look there some
construction oh they're gutting the
place i might be able to get to the roof
okay
go to the rooftop
all right now we're getting like
some
difficult complicated intricate missions
are you going through this so you keep
up with the old crew now after your
death slash disappearance
i saw a ladder climb up it and see if
you can get to the roof
yeah where'd he go north south east west
wherever there were liquor stores to
turn over and hitchhikers to disappear
oh come here not as far as i know he's
probably a john doe then right what do
you think od shootout maybe just a car
crash right anonymous charred remains on
the highway
they only knew what a sick puppy they
had on their hands
come on oh my shoes i sewed i need to
know where the air coming out of those
vents and vangelico originates there
should be a unit above the store
this thing
am i am i too close get on the high
ground all right all right all right
high ground
can i get that helmet
no
um
high ground
hi grant how are you doing i am pointing
out this oh event i have to high ground
no more venting
for you
it looks like the highest point is on
the northwest side
hey i see the vents yes
can you get any higher
uh
yeah a little bit
you're just the highest point
what now you want a photo
no no the air conditioning roof unit
we need to know where those vents come
out
it's like a big box on the roof
don't you mean all of these
can we get much what are you guys
memeing
vantage point what's the vantage point
that thing over there
maybe up here
which box yeah which what about what
about this
all right i've got a shot of some small
vents they're vents but they're not the
vents we need come on
maybe
up on here
um
i can see a burp sitting there
cute
[Music]
i can't do anything with this can you
get
up can you get
higher uh i mean i could ride a
helicopter i could quickly go steal a
helicopter
maybe
what do you want from me
well just kill me if i touch that
um
[Music]
oh the yellow point oh
that one
i'm running around around and rattle
right
no
slippery
can you get much higher
i can't get much higher place to take
the photo of the system now
we've got our shot
oh i have a feeling someone will spot me
it's like building up to it isn't it
where's the action
should i just jump down
i don't know does that do a lot of
damage or do we go back to where we came
from cause that's my plan right now
yeah jinx it
on
[Music]
there's no such thing as jinxing
things happen the way they're supposed
to happen let's speed this up we don't
want to draw attention okay okay okay
this game does does have fall damage
right definitely
okay
oh
ow [\h__\h] um that's just uh paint that was
not my bloods definitely not
hey
what's up
here take your glasses back praise me
let's go back to the garment pack crazy
we're doing so well setting up the
information
garment factory okay okay let's go let's
go
so what did you see
nothing that will cause undue
complications oh yeah it looked like a
simple setup
i was
[Music]
anything else well
more valuable
than the cabinets in the center of the
store by the register so i'd start there
that's what i'm thinking about
bulletproof means you can smash them
easy enough but the stones
we melt down the gold re-cut the rocks
that's an okay score
yeah shame we can't go in after hours
man
those fence looks wrong trousers
trousers i'm listening wait till we get
back
about the crew yeah there's this kid
who's been helping me
maybe we could cut him in i don't work
with amateurs he's made for it or if he
is he's a gifted amateur hell yeah
it's a good kid
you know what they say it's your funeral
one of them at least
i'm not going down
not yet
wait i'm stupid
nice
all right
is that a boomer movie or something you
don't know it i mean i guess it's a
boomer movie oh yeah workers have their
uses it's old okay
but it's supposed to be for children
nice to see the methods haven't changed
well you have to figure out what we're
doing somehow yeah
all the crews the rolls prep work
going to leave evidence behind in a hard
drive
so yeah the
methods don't change right not for a pro
well mapping out the options
i'm showing you all the angles that's my
area of professional expertise it is a
classic yeah decisions
that
is your domain my friend uh-huh
here
there's two ways i see of doing this we
go in smart or we go in loud and dumb
remember the best fine if we're going to
be maybe not in the pump a little bit
more dash through the air system and hit
the cabinets while everyone's out you'll
have to source the gas of course but
crowd control won't slow you down and
that might improve the take the cover is
pest control so no one will look twice
when you're wearing gas masks that means
getting a pest control van though you go
in dumb and you'll need your uh famous
way with people and four carbine rifles
we can't buy them and risk them getting
traced no no we've got to find some in
circulation it's awkward it's uh
real awkward but this is the gun favored
by lspd tactical teams so one of their
vans is probably a good place to look
a hacker can disable the cameras the
length of time depends on their ability
the alarm will be operating on the same
window
the exit strategy is more or less the
same for both options the driver you
pick will of course source some bikes
you come out of the store and make your
way through the new subway tunnel
they're digging off the del perro
freeway
all right i want my guy franklin on to
get away he can handle a bike all right
if you vouch for him i'll take the risk
so how do you want to do this run into
the front door or try to play it smart
you have to decide
can i decide spontaneously however
things go
because if smart fails i'll have to
switch to loud anyway
[Music]
um
smart
yeah okay
ah you've grown wise and cautious in
your old age okay
select personnel with that in mind as
ever the better they are the bigger the
cut now the driver they'll source the
bikes lead you out through the tunnels
okay well i'm choosing uh um
i thought i was choosing franklin
i only have two choices
he wants eight percent of the cut
this dude's better in many ways though
yeah let's go for it for eddie eddie toe
now you can count on him to get you out
of a spot guns now we're hoping to keep
so this guy shouldn't make much
difference
scary oh he he's [\h__\h]
let's go for the best people das moda
he's a pro not much else to say
hacker back office but this is the
person who will determine how long you
get inside
oh my god a girl
christian felt this guy ricky i met him
at the life invader office uh-huh may
not be that good but he's enthusiastic
uh
but look at those scales though eh what
do you think
do we still go for ricky
i oh how why do i all wreck it
nah i owe him nothing
local okay
this is how you want to do it i'll get
moving
well guys did you write down how we do
the smart approach
did you guys write everything down i
hope so
oh they will improve mmm nice okay
decisions decisions hmm
what
i'm not i'm fine with him
great uh i'll do some research on the
pest control van and the knockout gas
and i'll be in touch oh yes switch the
corner don't take the damn i'll call you
when everything's ready you'll need to
pitch up to the guys
my rep don't count for nothing no more
i should have chosen a cheaper one
michael
okay feel good
oh well
um
you know what
after we're done we just kill the gunner
so he won't take a cut it's that easy
it's the easiest thing you guys are new
in this world
newcomers amateurs
just kill everybody in the end besides
yourself
accept yourself
oh the gunner carries the money
well he won't carry it for long
is that what the joker does i never
watched the that movie
so i don't know
frankly no i would never do anything to
franklin
franklin is my best buddy he understands
me he gets me
he respects me
[Applause]
[Music]
michael what's going on listen um
i gotta get hold of the money for that
house we pulled down so
well i'm getting a crew together for uh
you can guess the pay will be awful and
the risk will be high but you might
learn something if you're interested man
that's not exactly a great seller
i guess i got to start somewhere thank
you
maybe one day you could put together
your own deals your own
jobs wow what a dream life there's so
much desiration i gotta do sit tight for
a while my buddy lester will get in
touch with the details
okay
[Music]
so we switch to him
see what he's up
to i'm eating potato chips
hmm
it ain't moving
what are you doing
and we're gonna go to the oh we're right
at the app we didn't go very far huh
is that where i need to go
[Music]
why
if he needs to go here then why did he
uh drive away from it
that's just his home
yeah i know but i still don't understand
sometimes when it doesn't show me where
i need to go
where
oh sorry but you know what it's getting
to be a bit much i have no idea how you
code because i go i'm a woman and that's
the truth
but girl they're getting that workout i
could do go get it but you know how boys
wait a minute
one girl uh-uh
hey how much further
we ain't even going five yards yet
i know i'm just asking is it for real
spirit walking exercise even i can go
further than that it's all the rage we
are women and we are free free
we are winning
why didn't he hide anyway yeah thank god
i missed her crazy what's up she's
spirit walking this [\h__\h] now man that's
just her attempts hey don't be talking
[\h__\h] about yourself damn that dog
i mean she cool as a [\h__\h] man
come on come where
we got to go pick up some [\h__\h] from
around the corner
at the same time my [\h__\h] why the [\h__\h]
we can't drive around the block with
chop
you need to walk with your fat ass
yeah okay you tall linky son of a [\h__\h]
huh it's a doggone job i mean taking him
for her walk come on homie we ain't got
all day let's go
task at hand homie come on
[Music]
what you got up
kidnapping fool that clown d that og
fool from ball
dawg i told you no more gang banging
retro vengeance [\h__\h] i'm trying to
make some [\h__\h] paper too gonna make
some paper glow and ain't nobody out
here gang banging it just look like that
you got to know the difference man [\h__\h]
man great mom would be very happy homie
she wants me dead anyway so she can get
the [\h__\h] house
business
where we're taking the dogs
i don't remember signing up for uber as
a driver
me and chop got a lot in common your
annoying ad man i'm carrying both of
y'all asses homie look what i said
man [\h__\h] this man you seen tanisha she's
straight it's me and you that ain't
straight though homie oh i know homie
look i meant this contact this white
dude real serious dude man this
[\h__\h] know the streets homie i
know he'll be a good hooker for us we
don't need no hook-up fool i know these
streets you know these streets
are still
boosting gas tankers on a different
street i know i know
the commodity trade or something fool
that [\h__\h] went up man look homie i don't
mind dying you feel me but i just want
to die with something that matters homie
that's what foreign gases should really
be about and i know this much the
[\h__\h] og's ain't even giving a
[\h__\h] about us though
you know what i'm saying this ain't no
[\h__\h] pyramid scheme
wait hold on listen to your boy one time
listen your boy you want some paper my
[\h__\h] this is what it's about check it
out i'm talking about 40 000. no problem
in hand two days time no killing nothing
no just starting another beef with the
[\h__\h] ballers [\h__\h] that's class ain't
feeling easy money we gonna keep our
disguise home ain't nobody gotta know it
was us
yeah whatever homie sorry
i'm so sorry don't go don't be scared
i'ma protect you [\h__\h]
he down his alley up here oh
man
ah
dropping in and training [\h__\h]
[Music]
well [\h__\h] how about put one these little
x pills up your ass crack next thing you
know you're gonna be begging for it
that's disgusting what's happening now d
man ain't no fun if the gangsters can't
have none man [\h__\h] you mark i ain't
sharing no ass to cgs ain't nobody
sharing nothing man shut the hell up
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] man [\h__\h] y'all i ain't
there a law against you marquez
insignia man's wearing [\h__\h] oh
so what's up now [\h__\h] listening to
something new [\h__\h] ass [\h__\h] [\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] i'm out of here
[Music]
come on let's go
in the van we gotta go
i don't know if the van can keep up okay
man we ain't gonna catch it
oh gangster we got this
let's go get bumpy chop
oh geez get in the way
[Music]
do that special driving thing you do
hey
you're gonna be able to trace this [\h__\h]
if he goes to the ground i know your
answer should talk to you in buffalo
man i ain't gonna perform for you like
some indian in the wild west show what's
your special
[Music]
ass bites
the motion for shooting trying to signal
[Applause]
ghetto birds all over the place
surveillance my [\h__\h]
i need a freaking sports car
oh where the [\h__\h] is he
he stopped
that's not good
do i shoot for the store
i slow-mo for turning corners okay
alley
all right so ah he's already over there
now okay okay i'll kill good guy i
thought he stopped
oh [\h__\h] damn
[Music]
why did i do it right when we stopped it
anyway
yeah
really
we're letting the the dog go go after
him
all right
jesus
hey i don't wanna watch i'm getting
eaten by this canine punk
[Music]
oh wait that's the wrong guy [\h__\h] sorry
i'm sorry okay
[Laughter]
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
where's my dog
i hear him in the distance though
got him got him got him
i got him i got him
i caught up with him
don't i have a gun
wait uh what's the
[\h__\h]
no [\h__\h] wazes [\h__\h] no moon come on
boy find that fur
find him
then
okay we follow the joker don't leave me
to him
wait i can beat a dog
no wait
you saw something in the train
oh please don't please don't let me be
um
smashed by a train
[Music]
where is he
where the [\h__\h] is he sniff him out
damn
dog a mean [\h__\h] man so i have to
wait for the dog to find him
tonight
can i find him first
okay i'll go
come on smell that stinky [\h__\h]
yeah
life is in there
give it up get down
get out of there bastard [\h__\h]
hello nope
no one in here
there's probably no one in here either
but okay just just for
the sake of
being
as detailed as possible
man [\h__\h] okay
how's it going dougal
you found something now
oh you're gonna get demoted if you don't
find me the dude
not no more snuggles for you no more
throwing balls and [\h__\h]
no no i'm not gonna play ball with you
you're gonna find oh hey where you going
boy suddenly
chop no
did you find him
oh you find himself a dog don't smell
the [\h__\h] no no no no no no no no
no
filthy [\h__\h]
i mean we don't we really don't want to
see that but can you stop stop going now
i keep on calling him but he won't come
ah
choppy
this ain't time for humping tom come on
man
we gotta dump her come on dump the beach
ah can be improved oh his behavior can
be improved
bad guy
we in this together chop let's go
come on
he's not doing anything
i could easily do that without the dog
stop running dawg
you scared of dogs [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] you and your stupid dog why don't i
just use my gun
i'll be faster no okay
finally you bit me man shut the [\h__\h] up
over here oh [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] man i
ain't got no beat with the cgf maybe we
doing our own thing what the [\h__\h]
who's a good dog
good kidnap good good you don't train
chop you're gonna be a lost cause like
you dog mm-hmm we're gonna stash this
dude in my spot
okay
i prefer that anyway
we're going back to your crib i've been
there when you was indicted
my
friends i knew it was true
really well i guess that means we're
gonna have to shoot your ass when we
pick up our phony stacks
sorry you ain't gonna pick up [\h__\h] fans
gonna be on you before you can either
get so be quiet angry in the middle of
the conversation look where the [\h__\h]
you're going
i was driving so well
you calling them on a cell phone you
dumb [\h__\h] trying i'm trying
we want 40 000 just pay me or pay the
funeral director [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
you just gave him our location now we
gotta let this [\h__\h] out of here
get the [\h__\h] out of here
[\h__\h] give me that damn phone what the
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] y'all i'll be seeing y'all
soon the only reason you've been seeing
[\h__\h] cause we went easy on your ass
remember that dog
oh you owe me a fight
yeah this some [\h__\h] take me down the
cut
we let him go how why did we kidnap him
if we just let him go like that
me no understand though man what the
[\h__\h] is wrong with you [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] is wrong with you [\h__\h] i
was getting this pain what the [\h__\h] is
wrong with you [\h__\h] that was a good
phone a good phone
capture's all over [\h__\h]
all right [\h__\h] you're the
[\h__\h] you better watch out for
them if they gonna be on you man
he got tracked
franklin is a good guy
i passed chop chop
i want to do my
my mission though my
my
my jewels mission
um
i thought if we switched to franklin now
we can do it too but i guess not
franklin's trying his best yeah
hmm
money heist
no time my dick might fall off
why what you do
oh i thought we were waiting for
something
okay
where is we going trying to locate that
equipment it's going to take some time
before we're ready to go drinking so
spend your last few moments of
retirement with your family
i don't know if michael really wants to
be with us with his family at the moment
they kind of suck
all of them
but okay let's check it out maybe we get
some story yeah
two birds with one stone
sometimes
you just gotta show him who's the boss
[Music]
a michael
am i going the right way i wonder
[Music]
whose boss i killed
nope totally didn't get lucky buddy
probably wasn't man what you talking
about no no not me not me
ow
okay so the trees you can't take down
the big steel straight lamps you can but
not the wooden trees alright
i've learned my lesson
okay but i'm here
true in real life
gta logic
really
it seems difficult to take down a tree
like that
because at least the tree has roots in
the ground street lamps don't have roots
in the ground
i think i don't know
could be wrong
ah i love you
don't like me
stop with the emotions just like me for
real for real
for real
going to teach him a lesson jimmy jimmy
god
stop being so toxic do it
nothing really because i keep hearing
them
go away what go watch your lining
answers game or dog porn just go away
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] i can't believe you did that
that's my tv you don't talk to me like
that i can't believe you
mom was right about you yeah you don't
know any better and you can't help it
but you're an [\h__\h] yeah well why
don't you talk to you
besides just you got all of this luxury
just because of your dad you want to be
hit by your son yeah
no
i want you to do something besides
sit there eating yeah great thanks for
the you were eating too dad
wait
i'm just trying to help you oh
um nothing says i love you yeah like
[\h__\h] tv need some anger management
i'm sorry i mean now it's still a
demoral day i just wish we could do
things together yeah what things i don't
know
play baseball play ball oh i have bad
plans
bike ride then
bike ride you want to go on a [\h__\h]
bike ride okay [\h__\h] nine let's go on a
[\h__\h] bike ride
okay
fine
a bike ride along vespucci beach
okay dad i got just the thing to show
you hmm
bike rental
this day was going so well do i look
like someone who rents [\h__\h]
all right
i guess we're driving yo you're lucky to
even be allowed out of the house after
that boat stunt what's the big deal
if i'm hanging with you i'm listening to
my music
[\h__\h] yeah yeah you'll think there's no
consequences in life for taking your
daddy's boat that's funny you can just
fake your death
you were hiding in the head crying
kidnapped they just took receipt of your
property with payment pending if it was
anything other than what you told me
then that's on you all right they
[\h__\h] stole it and who knows what they
would have done
but i didn't expect or want them to get
killed
maybe i should kill you
you're driving like a psychopath yeah
are you so hot you're making me drive
like a psychopath but you think this is
normal
[Laughter]
i think we'll both be happier if we can
spend as little time in this vehicle as
possible god do you think i've got
learning difficulties huh take a good
long look in the mirror pal i'm not the
one who doesn't respect my fellow human
beings no not unless they're a spit or a
jew boy or an ass munching homo oh there
was me thinking there's a difference
between witty beasts
you gotta complain
against the competition
[Music]
hey i never said you had learning
difficulties jim well i do
and you never cared oh i just said that
dr freelander thought that maybe you had
problems relating to people
relate to my [\h__\h] old man
wow
sound me and relate to my [\h__\h]
[Music]
is that my dream car no it's just the
same color look at that it looks kind of
fun though you're saying vapor vape wave
away vibes
i like it
please don't shoot the bike rental guy
out of like force a habit
you
you my boy i'm getting real cocky
bless you don't pay me no mine
hey
two bites take your pick
um okay
i go for the yellow one i like the
yellow one stands out nicely
if i beat you to the end of the pier
buying me a new tv
um
nah not feeling it but wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait
wait it doesn't that's not going back
fine but if you lose you're gonna do
something with your life front brake
rear brake
who needs brakes
let's go why am i so slow
why am i so slow
oh my general stamina will be improved
nice
mash mash what
where's the w button or what wait i'm
losing guys i'm losing because of you
i could buy my timmy you better buy him
the tv guys
i should double your button
i'm mashing it
nothing's happening
i'm so slow
shift
oh [\h__\h] hell
this is okay okay i'm just gonna buy him
a tv
i'm i'm just gonna buy him a [\h__\h] tv
what's the right way to do this i can't
get speedy yeah
i'm gonna choose the wrong bike or
[\h__\h] sticky key is man
caps lock uh
thank you [\h__\h] girl could have told
me that sooner
ah
where's that car
anyway
well i'm not winning this anymore
i demand a refund
oh doing it again maybe i can do a
shortcut
ah
i could if i would have been a little
bit faster
ryan's already there like oh
[\h__\h] ah
[\h__\h] help
wait
wait i think we can go up the stairs
yeah yeah yeah
[\h__\h] mountain bike
man this could be so easy
see even even with that big of an
advantage she didn't get there that
early is that my boat
better not be my boat
what the [\h__\h] joke
what a [\h__\h] joke can i restart the
mission
oh
ah reply mission
i'm available while on the mission
once you have passed the current mission
okay i will buy them
number one
i mean it was a bit of an overreaction i
never agreed to that
you know this is real nice dad
if you consider that i lost my boat
because of him then it wasn't accurate
right
you would have no fun if it sat on your
face ah come on i mean why do i have to
hold your hand through this whole
midlife crisis [\h__\h] she really don't
have a midnight breakfast from tracy's
butt sometimes because tracy doesn't buy
cars she can't afford so the thugs break
in our house tracy doesn't get kidnapped
or destroy my yacht well that's just
because she's too busy getting [\h__\h] by
dudes to get on tv you don't talk about
your sister that way well i'm sorry but
it's true i mean according to her life
invader page she's hanging out with
producers and porno guys this afternoon
what are you talking about
actually it's all happening right out
there oh what that boat that makes yours
look like a refugee raft
you [\h__\h] kidding me what kind of boat
the one that makes it she's cheating on
me with a different boat drop her pants
and spread her legs
this is the reason you brought me he's
already ready to swim over
i'm taking this boat
[\h__\h]
run towards the edge of the pier and
press
space okay
why didn't we just zap like that
run run run run yeah
damn no [\h__\h] way that
that's
not ellie
um
[Music]
yeah i'm trying to i'm trying to
what
what what
no how do
[Music]
what
[\h__\h]
dad
i'm going
what
do i i'd like glum
left shift
god damn it
go up
oh they're like inverted
whoa
what a swimmer doll
good swimmer
that's pretty far away
no way there's no sharks in the water
oh wait
i mean we already saw some crazy [\h__\h]
but there's no way that there is a shark
there's no way that there's sharks here
but i saw i saw the ladder
oh they got speedboat
steak
i i ran out of stamina
it caused me to lose health okay no i'm
like we're literally there chill
okay
what is that oh it's a cute floaty
oh nice
can i just join the party
this is perfect for my midlove crisis
i'm a dancer yeah
wait this is dmca music yeah
[Applause]
music michael just like me for real for
real
yeah you're embarrassing her dude
we're shooting porno here they shoot
porno all over town mom rented our house
to them last summer
yeah man you got a killer pad it's been
awesome let's go those walls
you're such a jerk and that's pretty
aggressive again dumbass these guys are
serious yeah it was so much
are you going to shoot me while i'm on
the speedboat god damn it now go
whatcha gonna do
[Music]
um
oh
[\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] they're popping off they are
performance shark turn a b cold space
and a d
we'll use them down here
who the [\h__\h] are these people oh you
know
teeny people collabs serious talking
why do we just go behind them
is that not a good strategy oh [\h__\h]
that's dead
i could i just shoot them
did i bring my gun with me
it doesn't look like he's carrying a gun
he's practically naked
[\h__\h] they're coming after us
oh my god [\h__\h] they're shooting at us
one of your asses how come i'm not
hitting them
lose them
are you saying shooting is gone
if we keep going this way
okay [\h__\h] are these people oh you know
teeny people celebs serious drug dealers
since we're the tv people and drug
dealers start hanging out oh come on
get away from them
try and get the one you want to kill
[Music]
oh
my hand
[Music]
i bumped into something
nice
okay this is going to be a tough one
if you say so trace
we should just switch and go into a car
oh [\h__\h] they're popping off at us
who the [\h__\h] are these people oh you
know
teeny people celebs serious drug dealers
well since when the tv people and drug
dealers start hanging out come on
slow santos
no it's fascinating
go away
run okay my dad's gone crazy
oh sh oh ah that's bad
okay
oh where the hell is he oh he's so far
maybe we go at him from behind
oh i could rupture an implant
let's stop chasing us and help lake
can't you see he's a psycho go away
oh he's sweet but a psycho
i'm gonna show that i'm gonna shoot him
okay my dad's going crazy
oh come on turn around
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
you're [\h__\h] kidding me
shut up
okay sometimes you just have to stop
moving
i know my song says don't stop don't
stop go your own way but in this case
just chill for a second
what now
i'm an accessory to murder
wait i was basically murdered just now
give me a second
that was that would have been um a
little bit sad if i would die right
there after already killing them
you did blow yeah i did some blow and
that might like make my testimony
inadmissible what you're not admissing
anything there won't be a trial unless
you're on a trial for doing bloom after
you ruined my where exactly are we going
though
hey stole my friend [\h__\h] cat them and
i'm the one on trial they started it
and i'm looking the right way if you
hadn't hung out with some creepy ass
porno people had done
so this should be like an increase in
trust and honesty okay and porno dudes
are like the best dudes i could be with
oh dear she's got it all wrong yeah they
actually respect women and treat us
right it's los santos dad what do you
expect when he moved here enough
this conversation is
over his children are so shitty
[Music]
[Applause]
wait i thought i was supposed to get on
the beach
was it just like a few meters away it's
not oh come on come on don't be so exact
about it whoa whoa chill out babe oh man
what did you say
wait wrong way pleasure i bet it was a
pleasure you're only pleased when you're
being shot at no i meant you don't have
to whoa
you
don't have to thank me and there's so
much water saving your life from those
maniacs you didn't say that you ruined
it
[Music]
they really have some problems they he
shouldn't only be going to therapy alone
they should go as a family
they got some real issues there with
this family
they are not functioning
so
they want me to go
right over there
nowhere else
[Music]
wait don't don't land now
okay here here here here here here here
here this
jimmy you
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
he he's the [\h__\h] [\h__\h] okay he
smashed my tv and he took me to the
beach the beach with my sister for
taking you to the base my day where's my
dad
get you i just told him where you were
you know he got that crazy look in his
eyes you know like you get sometimes and
he just went this is me and my brother
when we were
like 12.
i guess
but no my brother was always like
so chill
while i was being so dramatic and
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah he was a good brother
now we get along much much much much
much much better
thankfully
he's so sweet
he turned in such a sweet boy into such
a sweet
boy hey buddy we're still running
tomorrow right
but i feel like i kind of want to end it
here for today
[Music]
has it been saved or do i need to go
home
to
pest control have some vans at their
warehouse in the port of los santos okay
not today though
a good place to stop
oh i'm sorry about that all the save
should be on
save on the phone
thanks for the notice
[Music]
quick save there you go
save are you sure you want to save your
current game progress and then you're
like hell yeah why would i not want to
do that did i do it
i mean let me check
me you're right if i can see it yeah
there you go
eight point five percent in the game
that's how far i got today you know what
that's not so bad considering the game
is pretty big
pretty long
this has been fun it has been fun yeah
i enjoyed this so much it's like you
know not like the typical kind of game
that i play you know cute rpgs and all
that
but
very very very much fun
hope you guys enjoyed it too
i i'll definitely play more i don't know
if i'll finish it apparently
all the other young girls who played
this did not finish it i guess maybe
it's seen more as a
um play every once in a while and have
some fun game but
i wouldn't mind playing it like weekly
for now
because we don't have anything else
until until pokemon
um
i wouldn't mind so far honestly it
wasn't really difficult either
i mean the game kind of trolls me a
little bit when uh
i
i don't get out exactly where it wants
me to get out
but besides that
it's a great stream game yeah so far i
think you know it's very entertaining i
don't have to talk too much because
there's a lot of dialogue so that's good
for my throat
thankfully
i can play multiplayer with the girls
is there like a like any kind of goal
when you do that or do you just [\h__\h]
around
because uh that sounds like fun too
though
how's your froze um i think it's all
right but
yeah
you can do bad guys oh
there are missions you can do together
really
fun
why why have the girls not done that yet
before you get the flat tag let's go
really oh
[Music]
four four players maximum
amiko senpai did it
really
oh they did it before
no private service
how does it work do you not just like
connect with your friends
perfect isn't that perfect
that's perfect i'll talk about it if i'm
it
i think i'll enjoy that more than like
uh as much as i enjoyed playing
overwatch and paladins with her i think
this will be more enjoyable
i'm sure she knows her way around town
too
flair and mika was perfect today collab
oh that sounds like fun
fun okay okay thanks for telling me that
is that like when i started the game it
gave me the option between gta 5 and gta
online would i choose gta online then
is it still in the gta 5 world
but do you like make your own character
oh i see i see csc
sick
ps4 recommended but i'm so used to
controls now on the keyboard
did not need the controller i think the
driving driving is not so bad with
keyboard i mean it might be even better
with controller but it's not so bad
also
i think someone told me about auto aim
which i don't think i had on
but
my aim wasn't so bad
at the end there while driving the the
boats i don't know what the [\h__\h] was
going on there i was supposed to kill
them way earlier
my aim was decent
only the controller has all the aim aha
i see i see
oh for flying oh
seamlessly switch that's that's good i
mean if i ever have some travels
troubles
flying or so maybe i'll try it but so
far
i was pretty fun
what went pretty well well
try playing with mikko senpai oh i don't
mind that's made me uh
an interesting collab idea
hmm like we could do ame and mikko
because i'm sure miko senpai wants to
play with ahmed but
communication doko
i would be the third wheel though
oh no honestly no no no no no from my
point of view mikko senpai is the first
wheel from mikko senpai's point of view
um i'm the third wheel
and from ama's point of view she doesn't
she probably doesn't even realize what's
going on
[Laughter]
two ladies
and we got two ladies around her arms
imagine imagine i'm i need a fan art
where ame has like her arms spread over
the shoulders of on one side me and on
one side miko senpai
and having a really smug look on her
face
i and her [\h__\h]
let's go
[Music]
all right guys
i'm not feeling
super chat right now
uh
if that's okay i would like just leave
it at this and then tomorrow we either
play rust or we do another super chat
rating to get um
[\h__\h] done i'm not sure i think i'll
decide after i wake up hmm
is that okay
thank you guys i had a lot of fun though
damn
[Music]
thank you for the stream thank you for
watching and for giving me some tips and
some advice on how to play the game but
but it was relatively easy to figure out
everything
gotta see your eye of sirens
i already saw it i already saw it yeah i
need to
um i wonder what mummy
thinks of it she didn't see it yet i'm
sure but we need to let her know and
impress her when she logs in and sees
what's her home now
i wonder what she will think
oh thanks for the memberships thank you
i'm great at taking advice wonderful
yeah and so she likes having a good
overview over everything surely as a
bird
you like to
be at the very top of things
oh congratulations for the memberships
whoever got them
my roommate is sauron nice moment
i'm not sovereign
no
but the tower the the stairs like i saw
i saw it already like
um and then pick what i said by a stream
but it's like
it needs quite some jump and run you
need to jump over some
spaces but but it looks really properly
built
it's very wide
yeah who's scariest sauron or mummy
oh that's a difficult question
it depends how well you know mumei i
guess
you can build an elevator yeah
i can try um like i have the recipe
maybe on the other side of the
mountain i can experiment with some
um elevator at some time at some point
of time
time off point point of time yeah
yeah mummy you guys say mummy is scary
than sauron
i think gandalf
says otherwise
yeah you can reach the top mm-hmm
yeah yeah yeah she built it all the way
to the top azuki sample and piccolo
senpai together
well i'll show you guys
when we log into rust again
[Laughter]
true again
hmm
rusty kuzan
what day is it tomorrow friday
is spare girl
no that doesn't fit her no
thank you remember me said thank you
no
column is so eew
oh yeah id 3d that's true that's
tomorrow the day after tomorrow the day
the day day the day after after after
tomorrow um so my streams will continue
to start like later like today because i
can't overlap and uh you know
so if i stream then i will stream after
the streams from the id members
they have some showcases
yeah i think tomorrow is munna senpai
i think oh no maybe not no i think it
was like that muna senpai
and then liso and then you feel but
maybe maybe
exciting ah they're in japan right now
uh
ina
must be nice actually right now it's
also a tokyo game show i wonder if they
have time to visit probably not because
their debuts are like exactly on the
same days but who knows maybe they have
some private time to go to tokyo game
show i wish i could go
lucky
tokyo
[Music]
inaudible
they're very busy yeah yeah i already
got like a [\h__\h] ton of clips recommended
about how muna sent by smells
by fook senpai
so many clips about that thanks
algorithm
and they seem to be very busy i also saw
a clip where moona was talking about
wanting to meet cali
my whole my whole timeline is full with
that those clips
[Music]
well well well
i'm stalling again
i'm stalling
it
you got one of at least breaking into
eof taking what
but you know those three they already
met several many many times before right
so they already
have like a good friendship and all that
established
like in like in real life they've missed
out they've met so many times so
uh
i feel like you know
they're yeah they're so close
like myth only met one time
up until now
that one time so
when we when we meet again in japan
sometime and have like an airbnb or
something like that together like id
i don't i don't think there will be any
breaking into
bathtubs
of another girl
i don't see that happening
i feel like we
we want our privacy um when we take a
bath
all of us
yep please don't i mean i wouldn't take
a bath anymore i would take a shower but
um
i i would like to have some privacy
please
baptized
no please no no
god no actually i was watching um
i was watching the office yesterday and
today and i i got to the point i i i was
at the episode again where he goes like
god no please no
the meme the meme
and then the next episode was everybody
stay calm
oh all the memes in the world
all the memes
so good
michael michael
all these michaels with their midlife
crisis
what's up with that
the michael and gta 5 the michael scott
in the office they all there are all in
the midlife crisis it's hobbies poor
toby yeah i feel so sorry for telephony
who doesn't feel sorry for toby
no
my book club we're deciding we're like
figuring out what book to read
um
please watch a different show no [\h__\h] no
i keep on watching different shows i
actually just finished one
becoming elizabeth i just finished that
one
it was quite shocking
had only one season because it's
relatively new i think it came out this
year
you know i always watch like something
new and something old at the same time
like some some
like the office and so on i just watch
like when i
when i want to fall asleep and i don't
care about falling asleep while the show
is still running because i already
watched everything before so i don't
miss out on anything
um
and then when i'm actually awake and
want some
some interesting stuff i watch something
i haven't watched it yes i finished cleo
i
i have to recommend cleo it's on netflix
it's a german show
it was
really
uh a good show
with k
clear with k
um parks and rec i've watched it already
a lot of times too that's one of my
uh watch and repeat shows
um
clue yeah
[Music]
dark i don't know
stop spamming that
cobra kai that wasn't my recommendations
too
yeah
sounds interesting you should watch it
but i wonder you should watch it in the
in the original german voicing with
english subtitles if possible
always watch an
voicing tad lasso i want to watch that
isn't that the show that you can only
watch like on the apple
ah
i want to watch it
ted lasso i always was thinking i want
to watch that
yeah yeah yeah english sub all the way
yeah in that case you should
since the original the original
language that last was amazing how many
seasons does it have
i'm interested i don't have like apple
tv
[Music]
oh yeah i need to continue violet
evergarden as well maybe i will today
maybe i will
spanx family too i guess
but i kind of want to do um violet
evergarden first
i think
it's so beautiful it's so gorgeous
finnish handman's sale
yeah apparently the new season of
handmaid's tale started but
you know
it's a really really good show
but i can't get myself to get back into
it because it's so
terrifying
ah
maybe i will just wait until the season
is done
so then i'll binge watch it once
it's done
then i'll binge watch it in one day or
two days in one go
yeah
although then i don't get like a mental
break like a mental breather break in
between but that's okay
it is quite addicting like the previous
seasons were really addicting too
but it's also so terrifying to go back
into it after a long time of not
watching it
um
whatever makes you happy thank you
stop on the last episode forever no no
i have to finish it apparently uh the
season they're doing after that is the
last final season
it's good to know that an end is
near
more or less i guess within 2023
because
that means i don't have to
be so mind-broken anymore afterwards
um
no i did not watch our wby ruby ruby
right ruby
miss most of jj yeah custom vlog you
should you should
it was a lot of fun and now i'm just
just
chit-chatting
so there was a final before no no i just
mean there's a man there's gonna be a
final season
after the the current one
they announced it
i know of course i know it's by my papa
i know
he's working on it
okay
i think i shouldn't be stalling so much
i really have
sometimes i have some issues like
starting and ending my stream
like in between all cool all chill
sometimes i don't know how to start or
end my stream
[Laughter]
[Music]
hope for your happiness that's so sweet
i hope for your happiness too thank you
yeah yeah well well i will eat the
leftovers from my
weird pasta that i made yesterday the
pesto pasta
pesto pasta pasta
mmm cooking do not know like i like i
always get like to be honest it feels
like even though i get recipes for two
servings
it's mostly it feels like like free
[Music]
so
i could eat for three days when i cook
something like that i'll i don't know
when when they give you a recipe with
meat
the meat portions are usually tiny as
hell
but the rest is like overkill so
much
kind of sad
like sometimes you get like a piece of
pork fillet
and it's so tiny even for me i eat tiny
portions
but even for me it's really tiny
pistachio pesto never had that before
interesting pistachio
meat lover
i'm not sure if i'm a meat lover
one of my recipes for this this week is
like a
a burger but there doesn't seem to be
any meat it seems to be uh like a
cheeseburger literally because there's
like fried
oh i think it was camembert
whatever it was called
uh
fried as the patty or so
with like
um lingonberry diamond that's how we eat
that kind of cheese here it's really
yummy
fried
camember kind of bird cheese
it's really yummy i do eat that
sometimes
but without the burger just fried
camembert cheese out of the oven with
some lingenberry jam
so yummy
i don't know how to say that is that how
you say it in english
come on bert
it's it's yummy it is
yeah mozzarella sticks as well fried
mozzarella sticks
yes yes baked brie
fried brie fried baked brie also with
lingamer jam we eat all of that with
lingenberry jam here
i don't know how you guys would eat it
but all of these fried baked cheeses are
so good with lingonberry jam
10 out of 10 would recommend
chunky wonky
with that smoothie i don't see you a
high smoothie
she knows i'm ending the stream she's
like stop stalling mommy
oi
i love you baby girl
she's such a sweetie
ah
want food
oh yeah they got lingam mary jam at ikea
[Music]
there were some ikea people at my place
today actually
here's my last tangent for you guys
i had some ikea people uh cause um
i i ordered something with uh
what's the word again montages is
putting together something [\h__\h]
uh assembly yeah
i always forget that word because
like the word that i use in that we use
in german already is a borrowed word
it's not actually a german word montage
i guess it probably maybe comes from
french i don't know
um so i i always think of that one
because it already sounds foreign
anyway so yeah they yeah they assembled
me something um that was i was so
excited about
a big big big big shelf basically and i
was filling it up before the stream and
my cats were really interested in it too
once the shelf was done
they like
um explored everything and jumped up on
the shelf and
sat down and chilled and
i put there was like some shelves uh in
the shelf what some like um drawers and
my
i put something in there and i i thought
you know it was close but then i noticed
john cruz was like
um reaching her paw through it
several times trying to get it out and
she actually managed to get it out and
i'm like chunky monkey what are you
doing so i put the stuff back in there
and close it again and it seems like
really safe like
i'm like surely she's not gonna reach it
now i don't know how she did it before
maybe something was like falling out of
it but now she surely can't do it again
and then like two minutes later she's
doing it again she's like trying to take
out everything that's in the drawer it's
so cute she was actually managing to
take out everything
she's like [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] [\h__\h] that [\h__\h]
you did that [\h__\h] get out of there i
don't want i want this destroyer it must
be empty
so cute
so cute no bad chunky bad chunky so put
everything back in again
i put it to the very very very very back
of the drawer so that she can't reach it
so cute
um
so now i'm really happy with my shelf
but uh it was very expensive
and
took quite a long time and i didn't know
when they would finish
but they finished in time for the stream
thankfully um
yeah yeah yeah really happy with it but
then i noticed i forgot
one important thing
i should have worn my ikea socks
i have some ikea socks blue socks dark
blue the ikea blue with an ikea logo on
them that i bought before when i was in
japan because they had like a sock store
that had all kind of funny socks and
some of them had like brand and company
logos and names on it and i bought ikea
socks they're really comfy i really like
them i should have worn them to like
belong
a cert dominance be like i'm one of you
guys
i love ikea i got some ikea socks
shame life doesn't have a mission replay
true
they are comfy yeah it has the ikea logo
they look really good
i love them
i love my ikea socks
[Music]
but then the whole time while they were
building it i was watching the office
because i didn't know what else is it's
kind of awkward i don't know maybe you
guys know the situation but when you
have like
um
like like strangers over to assemble or
do something in your place for several
hours
i'm like oh this is awkward
i guess i'll just watch tv
i tried to like clean my apartment a
little bit and i tried to do something
on my pc but yeah i didn't want them
like when they had questions they would
try and look for me and i didn't want
them to go into my office where they see
my whole
gamer setup
and my my whole life merchandise and all
that
so i tried to get my work done quickly
and leave the
office and then
go back to my bed and then watch more of
the office
with the kitty cats
it is awkward yeah but not because they
made me feel like i should be helping no
just because um
like i just don't know like
i'm sure they feel awkward if i'm like
watching them straight for five hours
i'm sure these kind of
workers don't want to be watched by the
person who lives there
so just try to mind my own business
while also while also being available as
available as possible when they have
questions
um
because i did have some questions here
and there
yeah it took quite a long time
i mean maybe not five hours maybe more
like four hours
yeah but they were nice they were nice
they did a good job very clean got rid
of all the trash afterwards
million pieces of cardboard
yeah very clean but that's included in
their job so that's supposed to be
normal
oh but
you know um
um
at some point while i was watching the
office
um
i i uh my mom called so i pick up the
phone
and we start having a long conversation
you know and my tv i didn't set this up
but um
i didn't set this up myself but um
uh somehow
my tv it's like a smart tv i think
uh
when i don't do anything with it for a
while it goes into like an afk mode you
know
and
um
i was on the phone so i didn't notice
i mean i noticed very fast and i reacted
fast but you know there was one of the
one of the builders was in the room at
the moment and then the
yeah the screensaver shows up
and
let's just say it's a little bit of a
spicy picture
and i'm like oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] and i
quickly turned off the the tv but i'm
not sure if the
worker saw it or not because
in theory he was looking in that
direction in the moment
but yes i was hoping he didn't see
oh yeah i turned off the tv as fast as
possible
yeah wait it takes no no it takes like
pictures i think from my
my my my google drive
um
i mean
stop
yeah i i will not go into detail
what kind of spicy picture it was
but
uh it was a bit spicy
[Laughter]
not not too spicy you know
um
but a little bit spicy
um anyway
uh-huh yeah
um i was really fast though so it should
be fine
[Music]
clothesless cuda
no i don't have a clothesline scooter on
my tea drive
mama and oni
that one is very spicy and neat
that picture
that's a good spicy
anyway
um
i'll leave it at that
thank you guys for watching today
uh i wish you a lovely evening i'll see
you guys tomorrow i probably won't put
up a reservation until tomorrow
i'll just see what i feel like tomorrow
what i feel like doing tomorrow okay
um
[Music]
bye
thank you soon for watching thank you
guys
see you soon
[Music]
do
you