[Music]
for
hi
guys is the music on is the music on
M okay okay the case of who slap the
tatang no no no no no guys let me
explain to you what's going on today
okay
really making use of the Patti pus
music nice
yeah guys so we
are today this stream is a little bit
different
because we have to do the bingo so
unfortunately I have to leak my real
life job okay
guys
M so actually guys
guys when I say no not when is sketch
when I say pea business actually my job
is an investigator guys I'm an
investigator
in uh
in marang
corporation and right
now I've been Ted to handle a very very
very
give a difficult
task
culprit so guys as you all know well
maybe you guys don't know but now you
will know because I will explain it to
you yeah what is
happening this is I have also prepared
upstairs up herey so guys basically in
our very very peaceful neighborhood
a
thief has successfully stolen A
mysterious
treasure and by the way I'm at a cafe
not because I work at the cafe full-time
but because my Superior is giving me
permission to work at rain cetron Cafe I
totally have nothing to do with
me yeah it's another me but not me yes a
mysterious treasure the thing is they've
been keeping it so secret that I don't
even know we're not even allowed to know
what was
stolen cross promotion to save money
shush so basically because I have no
leads I am
forced I am forced
to you know use my artistic
ability to sketch what the culprit looks
like hopefully y i get it
correct but yeah because we don't have
anything else and I did not see the
incident
unfold I will have to rely on
everybody I will have to rely on
possible
witnesses witnesses of the
cre so they can call me
and help me sketch the
culprit and then if we have a complete
sketch we will be able to identify
hopefully what the culprit looks like
look for them and hopefully catch
them really no le no no no no that's why
it's a very tough case and I'm forced to
open the the window of this stream and
then we can send this thief to
prison
but that is if we get enough
information because we don't know how
many witnesses are going to be there to
call at some point I might even need to
create Flyers to distribute to people so
this can go so many ways guys the stream
can go so many ways
if there are some
witnesses who are going to call and we
have enough people to call we will catch
the copper but what if we
don't well you will see hopefully we
don't get to see it but
[Music]
yeah is there a time constraint my
Superior my Superior is giving
me uh let me
count a little bit m
one 2
hours for me to
get for me to get the lead so you know
let's just try our
best hopefully enough Witnesses are you
know brave enough or at least have heard
of this Station's phone number because
if
not yeah but anyways the phone sat down
anybody can call I mean not anybody you
know it's open to like some some people
in this area but not everyone I think I
ran out of my mouth oh I did
not the culprit will probably come as
like a witness as a witness without
anyone knowing that's like that's that
that reminds me of a game but this is
not a game guys but anyways guys it's
very close to
lunchtime so well we wait for hopefully
any
calls we will be having some
lunch yes I bought this lunch at the
supermarket near the
station and this is I don't know if this
is good or not because normally I only
get
Jelly you know because sometimes our
budget gets tight you know so we only
get so we only get to eat jelly but the
today is special and I think because I
need all the brain power possible you
know to do
this oh
shoot hold on hold on hold
on where uh what
[Music]
um hold on
okay well it seems
that it seems that we have we have a we
have a witness that wants to call so
fast I hope this doesn't you know this
isn't just early luck I hope we get more
eventually and it's not going to be the
only today but okay excuse me I I'll
just pick
up what
the
hello mosy MOSI hello this is the Pavia
Police Department not really Police
Department that's just me making [\h__\h] up
um who am I speaking
to you're making it up I thought was
if I was legit well I have a serious
crime to report not the crime I have a
person to report oh so were you a
witness in this mysterious treasure
stealing shenanigan
thingies indeed I have witnessed very
good at my job own eyes yes I've seen it
all well see you know Miss we um we're
just looking for the culprit right now
it would be very very helpful if um you
could probably give us like one or two
descriptions about
what the culprit looks like yeah yeah
okay so hm let me think let me remember
uh it all happened so fast you know it
was like really scary and I do you know
what
wasen um The Mysterious treasure that
was stolen I'm not sure what it is I was
focusing on the
person I think I saw like a a pretty
tall T pretty tall
yeah and this woman
woman had long hair dark long hair long
hair and dark I see yeah okay you know
it happened in nighttime so the dark
hair I'm not sure what exact color it
was if it was black or dark blue or so
but it certainly looks very dark to me
it could be black but I'll leave it up
to the other
people yeah okay okay so is that all you
could tell us it's very helpful thank
you so much yeah um if you need more
information um call
me uh I don't know your number well you
know what that that's okay anyways you
can always call me yes thank you thank
you Miss for your cooperation have a
good day yeah you're welcome good luck
please solve the crime because like oh
my God we're all so scared what's your
name what's your
name
uh tanakak caria Tanaka Kia all right
let's go okay thank you so much um I'll
let you know okay please save us okay
have a good
day insane wait hold on I need to get
out I need to get get out first because
um I think a witness is calling in from
a special special line a special line we
don't want the calls
toaru to
kaburu okay that's cool well we we'll
we'll just hello police oh hello it's
Pavia Pavia police station here PPS I'm
I'm really scared I just I just watched
the robbery I just watched the robbery
take place right in front of me and I
don't know what to do it's really really
scary I don't know how to c this where
this is where I get therapy I was told
that I could call here I could get free
therapy and they would offer me no no
Cal calm down calm down um you know um
our officers have jelly for lunch so
that's not really our thing but no
therapy I back to my childhood no no no
no listen listen no no no no we we we
can work something out okay so you said
you said you saw you saw the the the
robbery take place right right I I saw
it I saw it was really
scary okay um okay let me let me take
note of your name first what is your
[Music]
name
uh my name
is go golly G
uh cookie snaps golly G cookie snaps I
understand um that's my full name name
that's your full name I yes I understand
so um what what can you tell me about
this uh C do do you have did you see
what the culprit looked like I saw I saw
it I I saw her take the thing yes yes
she was she was tall tall I agree yes
yes it was tall and I do agree that she
had long hair
um she she had like a side ponytail
almost on the side of her head and and
her eyes were so striking and I don't
know what color they are perhaps blue
blue a blue
blue turquoise kind of like a dark a
dark
blue blue
turquo kind kind of can you can you
spell turquoise for me please I'm sorry
spelling is not really my strong suit
t u
r q u o i s c sorry you're the police I
wasn't I didn't know I was being
interrogated here I didn't do anything I
oh now you're
interrogating I literally have one
witness I I know I know I know please
please calm down we'll talk about the
therapy after this okay we'll talk about
the therapy after this okay okay okay
blue turquoise eyes is that what you're
saying oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
thank you very much for your cooperation
um do you have any idea what might be
stolen because we have kind of like
lowkey no information on that so if you
could if you don't that's
fine I would tell you but it's a
secret will you tell me if I sign you up
for
therapy a family
heirloom was stolen not mine though but
a family's heirloom a family hairloom it
was it was taken okay what shape you
don't
know quite quite large if you saw
someone walking outside with it you
would think it was strange okay okay
okay suspicious okay thank you so much
um you I will forward you um I will
right now move the line to my uh my
coworker and you can talk about therapy
there is that okay thank you Miss thank
you all have a good
day
bye I hung
up
[Laughter]
anyway oh my goodness we're running out
of rooms so I think we have to do this
another way I didn't think that we
needed to take notes of the
description
so well we can I guess we can I don't
know I guess we can take notes first and
then draw later yeah but
anyways can I jump in
oh wait h
[Music]
hi can I police oh
hello hello I I'll I'll make it quick
because I'm also on the Run myself what
uh uh uh okay we'll talk about that
later uh okay so um is this a call about
the mysterious family heirloom
stealing
incident yeah um I've also seen this
culprit somewhere around uh uh where the
where the thing took
place so for I saw the culprit brought
like an umbrella umbrella yeah an
umbrella yes yeah an
umbrella and
I don't know like it they just felt like
I don't know they just felt suspicious
to me they had like a really smug face
on smug face yeah really smug face and I
was like H that's not a face I see
around very often so so they're not like
a local no they're not a local I don't
know where they're from okay okay I see
I see and they look to be really quick
in their actions I feel like they're
running from something quick fast or
someone yeah quick
fast okay
mhm yeah that's all that I saw okay your
information is very very um useful for
us what is your name if I might ask oh
I'm um You can call
[Music]
me uh hello oh hello yeah sorry sorry is
the connection fine yeah I I I I think
so you're kind of breaking up hello
what's your name yeah yeah I was sorry
it was reconnecting
[Music]
um the phone okay I don't
know
hello
hello oh I well we didn't get we didn't
get her name but well she gave us quite
a lot of information
yeah so
um all right then turns out she said she
was on the run I
will oh hello oh the hotline's hot today
hello
ooh
hello oh hello hello yes this is the
Pavia police station
how may I help you and uh
uh it kind of smells like cookies in
here I don't know why cookies yeah
cookie snaps cookie snaps yeah at your
house or no no no the police station oh
the police station oh wait is this a
phone call yes it's a phone call I
didn't know oh I guess our boss
installed a little bit of um you know
yeah maybe there's
a yeah but anyways scent coming through
the phone wow that's very weird I know
you can't have them but um you can tell
us about um you know are you here for
the robbery case suspicious person I saw
you know it was very weird
because I saw that they had three hats
on Three Hats on not one not two but
Three Hats Three Hats on
okay Three Hats
on that's it anything else and uh they
were wearing some very tall platform
shoes tall platform shoes okay that I
think checks out with our other oh my
God I can't spell form
shoes okay thank you so much so um can I
get your name
please uh my name
[Music]
is okay yeah I got it
I got it yes you got it yes I did how do
you spell
[Music]
it and
then right can also call me oh yeah uh
um uh you can also call me uh
uh I don't know what what do you want to
call
me
I yes any yes thank you so much for your
information if you have anything else
please do not hesitate to call again and
the hotline will be open for
approximately 2 hours and then it it
will be time for me to piece stuff
together hopefully I don't get fired but
yeah I hope you have a good day oh
okay
okay okay okay take take take take care
um I I hope you have a wonderful day do
you need
something no I just want to know how you
are doing today nice Wonder oh it's just
it's been a slow day I was about to eat
lunch um I had a Bento basically so at
work we had this funny Bingo where we
had to like eat Bento so you know it's a
special day yeah have you
eaten um no yes no no no no kind of well
yeah you know what well maybe if you
want to come over to the police station
we do have some cookies and maybe you
can just take some don't don't tell
anyone I told you that but you know you
sound hungry so you know just just doing
what's right yeah but anyway ma'am um I
don't think yeah we uh I think I don't
think we should use this line to talk
about cookies but if there's anything
you want to talk about regarding the
case feel free to call back okay thank
you so much have a good
day we have grasshoppers by the
[Music]
way what's with the witnesses and them
hanging
[Music]
up oh my
God I'm dealing with you know well I
guess that's
fine that's
fine but I kind of need to
um make the field
wider because change it change canvas
size I think
make change canvas size
because because
because
yeah
oh hello Pavia police station
[Music]
here I I have valuable information you
have some valuable information for me
hey hey you sound you sound are you
okay I I
actually I I I I fought the robber the
the I I I I saw the culprit last night
you saw the culprit last night can I
have your name
please that's not important what's
important now is in information oh yes
that's true that's true yeah that's fine
too that's fine too um so what can you
tell me about the um the culprit the
prince of the
culprit well it happened so late at
night it was so dark yes and the lights
weren't on I think they sabotaged it but
I had a flight and they fell on to me
they they had something very soft
somewhere around their chest area soft
around chest area wait sorry sorry let
me take notes chest area okay so um what
happened after they fell on top of
you they smell good they SM uh okay and
anything else I I think when when they
crashed I felt something glasses like I
don't know glasses I think I felt like
glasses just near barely dangling on my
body it's well yeah so something with
like big breasted glasses I don't know
what like actual glasses yeah yeah I
think they were wearing
glasses okay I I see thank you so
[Music]
much
oh the witness just hung
up okay
um okay well that's new
information what happened to I don't
know I would call back but I don't think
we're supposed to use the line to call
back because but well she got the
station's number and I guess if she
wants to call then she will call but so
we got quite um some information you
know um blue turquoise eyes tall long
dark hair side ponytail smug face
umbrella and platform
shoes soft around the chest
area smells
good and glasses I yes well anyways um
while we wait for the other callers I
just want to open the Bento that I
wanted to
open well you know it's not it's not
every day we get to eat
um it's not every day that we get to eat
Bento usually we just get to eat I don't
know jelly or whatever but no I thought
to you know treat myself for once you
know
[Music]
oh sorry my co-workers just um they
handed me
something I'll get to them later
okay let me show you guys the Bento I'm
having let me see let me see let me see
it's pretty silly too cuz like we're
doing this bingo in the office I'm so
close to finishing it but I don't know I
might have eaten another Bento but I
guess today I'm having Bento again so it
doesn't really matter you
know did you take a photo of the Bento
yeah this is this is um I'm trying I'm
trying to send you guys not send you
guys put it on here I
[Music]
guess
huh
okay this is the
B let me see
[Music]
it's really hard because my notebook is
right on top of my keyboard so it's a
little bit difficult to
um save I
guess okay there we
go I will show you
guys oh my God I think a witness is
going to call
like let me eat my B to in peace just
kidding everybody can call whenever they
want
[Music]
Bento Bento Bento Bento where is it
h where is the Bento where is my
[Music]
Bento this is the
food this is the food I'm having right
now
[Music]
yes this is the Bento I'm having you
know well there's no set break time
because I'm accepting all
calls but
yes but for now I will eat as long as
there's no call I am going to
eat so yes so far we've got a lot of
information I'm really positive about
the end result of all this but yes let
me just take my lunch
break everybody can call if they want to
if the phone rings I'll pick up and put
my food down I
guess are they Greens in there yeah
behind the chicken
[Music]
I didn't get everybody's
names
M very
nice is it spicy no it's
[Music]
not
m m
[Music]
can we actually get
something mine is the height
[Music]
though soft around the chest area that
means they have BBA
yeah boing
boing smell good we can't really do
anything about it well long
hair I wonder if the hair is long or
straight I mean sorry uh curly or
straight or wavy I don't know
know but there's also a side
ponytail how long is the side
[Music]
ponytail smug
face blue turquoise eyes with three
[Music]
hats I don't know
family heirloom black hair
though oh for but
glasses okay so right now we kind of
unless so right now it maybe looks like
this a little bit but we'll sketch
later seems very
[Music]
fashionable m
M nice
food this is a good buffer
time
[Music]
M what if one of the callers just the
cul trying to feed you false info
hey that's why we get all the calls
[Music]
first and then we filter the information
but unfortunately in this
case we're kind of on a time crunch
here one of the witnesses for um they
said platform
shoes so yeah she could actually not be
tall and just looks tall because it's a
platform shoes
[Music]
and the hats might make her look
tall yes yes
[Music]
yes m
like that I have new information on the
message
board somebody's asking me
something I have to answer them
[Music]
okay soft around the
chest yeah it's very interesting so from
what we know we can update the
information
actually so the mysterious treasure is
apparently a family
[Music]
heirloom I'm I'm going to have to
probably ask some more specific
questions for the next Witnesses because
I think we've got some key defining
features but the thing is it's really
hard to
[Music]
um it's really hard to ask them what um
the culprit was wearing because it was
dark but maybe I can even
[Music]
try and the umbrella yeah
my food is so
[Music]
good
M how is it possible for the culprit to
get away with those tall platform
shoes I'm not
sure
okay we'll see
to vacuuming the food no I'm not done
eating but for now I
[Music]
am just arrest everyone in the city and
call it a day no one can complain if
they are in jail the thing is we don't
have enough capacity this is just a
small
[Music]
station and
now as much as I want to do it first we
don't have enough space and second if
they if I get found out I'll get in
trouble so I don't want to do
it but
anyway M very
[Music]
nice but it's finally nice I think we're
having a little bit of um space earlier
we had a lot of call callers callers yes
for information
but now we haven't really heard well but
I think it's good I finally get to have
a break to eat let me just reply to my
coworkers for a second um
[Music]
okay yes
hi I wonder if some are in collar are in
cahoots with the culprit
okay we still don't have any information
about what type of hat she wears okay
wait this is actually really good so
hold on oh where's my pen I lost
it so have no least of the treasure
itself but even if we don't if we have a
hint about the
culprit um Okay so things to
ask things to
ask next
Witnesses okay it will
[Music]
be what type of hat what type of
hats okay
and then
straight or
curly
Etc hair and how
[Music]
long bangs
Etc an umbrella I would assume is a
regular umbrella because if it was a
small umbrella she would say that it's a
small umbrella but she didn't say
anything about like oh it's a small
parasol or whatever she just TR up to
say
umbrella really makes me curious though
because the woman who said umbrella she
did say she was on the Run herself so I
wouldn't
know what did their voice sound like
that's kind of I don't know I don't know
if they they even
[Music]
spoke okay quick fast Hasty anything
else you guys think I should ask the
next caller
[Music]
yeah
earrings time name
location if the culprit mother is
[Music]
single hello hello hello hello oh hello
this is Pavia police station how am I
help you I saw the covert but but um I
don't know I don't know if
there's uh I don't know how how does it
looks like oh well um okay any
information would be useful um but just
in case um if you did not saw them see
them very clearly um I could ask you
some questions is that okay okay um so
another tip uh from another witness said
that this culprit is they're wearing
Three Hats all at once are you familiar
with
that Tre
hats so what type of gu so yeah yeah
yeah it just yeah I remember it just
this those tree hats not
exactly uh all in her hair so oh okay
yeah so one is one is in her hair okay
one is around her um what does
it take your time take your time take
your time take your
[Music]
time oh uh in shoulder yeah shoulder
yeah one is in is shoulder yeah and and
then and
then and one the others is in his hand
hand and all of them have a different uh
different kind of hat different design
yeah oh but you don't remember
what but I all I remember from uh the
one in his hat is like a kind of like
like a dog type of hat like having in
kind of like a gear
hat and a little fluffy hat fluffy hat
fluffy hat yeah all of them is Fluffy
hat yeah yeah oh okay I understand uh
that's a very valuable information for
us if you have any other information
please do not hesitate to call us by the
way may I have your
name uh my name my name is anong anong
thank
you
an okay okay thank you so much anong uh
please don't hesitate to call back if
you have anything else you want to tell
us okay thank you so much I hope you
have a good day thanks yeah
yeah
yeah okay that's actually big info we
got what type of hats cleared up next up
we need to ask somebody what hair or oh
hold on is
single the heck oh what
clothes they wear in
[Music]
yes yes yes yes oh my
goodness I'm running out of not
space
Oh okay let me just make this smaller I
let me just make this smaller so I can
maybe fit more
stuff okay this looks good
what clothes they're wearing and then
what so
many
yes Sor India bro oh my god really oh my
good yeah I'm not understand Indonesia
you you you do not understand understand
India okay okay okay I'm all right yeah
oh okay okay I used to you then um okay
yes yes yes yes yes yes before before I
forgot yes yes yes I remember the hair I
remember the hair oh yeah your the hair
remember hair is as
day straight or curly or how long it's
curly but not really that Curly into a
dead loss it's like you got a perm that
Curly curly oh like digital F yeah like
yeah
[Music]
C why I remember cuz I feel jealous God
Dam the hair is so so wavy am so perfect
yeah yeah so perfect like a K-pop Idol
yeah and then another tip said is long
this so um how long how long how long I
think I think it's almost reach her G
her but okay reach
her uh G can you spell Gat for me please
uh g y i a t t m okay uh I see and then
and she
um the pony
how don't know do not have P like a bang
bang curtain curtain Cur curtain
is yeah okay oh yeah like that like that
remember okay okay
okay
anyways I will be jealous also I think
if I see the culprit right right I would
be jealous too I really want to say like
hey where where where what Salon do you
go to but he he already left so damn it
okay do you do you actually know what
was being stolen yeah uh no but I mean I
I think uh they have a bag probably
inside the bag oh bag bag yeah okay bag
okay uh may I have your name
please oh it's it's e i not
l e
[Music]
Fe it's it's e with I not with L so it's
not Loi but it's
e okay okay e thank you so much if you
have any other information please don't
hesitate to call the station and we will
definitely assist you thank you so much
I you have a good day have a good day
stay safe
[Music]
bye
[Laughter]
you fake name I don't
know Loi Gat what is
gat I have no idea I need to look it up
what does Gap
mean what
does Gap what does Gap mean yeah some
new hire in our police station you know
really likes to say stuff like ski
toilet SK ski toilet but I don't
understand you
know soing like oh my God so Demir so
ski so stigma but I don't think a lot of
us understand but I think it would be
useful if we would look at this yes the
aura is busing oh oh hello Pavia police
station here how may I help you hello I
am a little shaken up from my experience
you are shaken up from the exper is that
your name or sorry having no no sorry my
name is Oro crony oro oro crony okay I
see yes um are you calling here uh about
the information you know with the you
know the family heirloom Thief that's
been you know and on the loose yeah um
they just looked so oddly intimidating
that I'm currently getting therapy at
the moment oh okay
where uh where yeah your
therapy oh where is my therapy or
yeah well it's under NDA at the moment
so oh I understand yeah it's yeah I got
I get it I get it um but okay let's
let's focus on the matter in hand so I
need to know if um the cprit's mother is
single no no no this what clothes were
they wearing um do you know they were
wearing a tropical t-shirt like Hawaii
tropical t-shirt and um were they
wearing a skirt or shorts
or they
were they were wearing
stockings stock just stockings just just
stockings just
stockings mhm okay um this is very
valuable information thank you so much
um Oro crony is there um anything else
you could tell us if not that's okay
too um I'm not exactly sure it was a bit
dark but was this person a guy or a girl
um from on our other witness's testimony
was a
woman was a woman it was a tall woman
with long dark
hair
okay then I think um
it was a skin tight no it was a skin
tight skin tight stockings but it wasn't
transparent SK it wasn't seethrough it
was opaque you can't see okay just just
making oh they weren't going around
around flashing people just to clarify
they they weren't down to that level oh
okay okay I see I see skin tight just
stalking op but opaque so like black I
guess yeah black stockings just just no
it was like red oh okay red
stockings I see I I see very valuable
information you're giving us thank you
so much or cron if you have anything
else to tell us any you remember any new
information please do not hesitate to
call us again and we will you know just
take notes I guess and yes um I hope you
have a good day um good luck with
therapy thank you I hope you have uh the
best of luck with catching the culprit
mhm yes thank you so much yeah she's
crazy I I guess could could be she's
very crazy okay thank you okay she's
very crazy what what' she
do
she I mean the way she's dressed up I
mean like that's already kind of telling
don't you think so well we are here are
thought not to judge but you know it I I
I can see what you mean by that all
right
okay okay have a good day thank you
thank
[Music]
you
[Laughter]
hello um okay so we got a big big info
here now we finally know what the
culprit is
wearing a tropical Hawaiian
t-shirt and no pants no skirt no nothing
thin just stockings skin tight stockings
but it's important to clarify that they
were opaque but they're they they're
actually red and not black okay I
understand opaque red
stockings I think we can draw this you
know I think we have enough information
we have enough information
but I'm eat yo accessory
okay so now the only thing we need is
probably
accessories accessories yeah well
they're already wearing a lot of hats
but okay the next thing to ask is
probably accessories what kind of
accessories were the culprit
wearing what kind of bag oh yeah
what kind of bag what kind of
accessory I I can I can erase this what
kind of bag what kind of
[Music]
accessory what kind of bag carrying the
heirloom the
big family
[Music]
heirloom and what's what's the other
one accessories
[Music]
I don't know why do I feel like why do I
feel like the culprit is too
fashionable accessories
jewelry yeah all
right I think we're getting close I
think we're getting close to um
the of the
investig so so let me try to slowly
sketch let me try to slowly
sketch
[Music]
um
okay so
first so they're tall they're wearing
platform shoes right
[Music]
let's just assume they wearing platform
shoes are they tall we don't know
that the culprit is definitely not from
Earth I mean I don't know the
description look normal and
[Music]
stuff so maybe what's what's like a slay
pose I could use for
the you know what's a what's a slay pose
because I think the culprits kind of
slay so I think some character in um the
sketch would help
out oh yeah I
[Music]
know I know like like the super
Slay Slay
pose like um oh my
God like them being like Oh my gosh it's
the leg
okay yeah
something like
[Music]
that yes okay
so yes girl they may be a model as a day
job yeah I don't know anything is
possible
guys and well let's try the hair first
what about the hair
uh the hair they said it was long and
dark no bangs
so no bangs would be like this
[Music]
probably that's like this
and okay then delete this one the hair
reach her Gap yes yes yes I remember
that the hair reach her
gat the hair reach her Gap so like
around here
yeah and her hair is like Curly but like
so like this I would
[Music]
imagine like this I would imagine
H the hair if the hair reach the
Gat yeah so maybe it could be something
like
[Music]
this okay
ah because most criminals they try super
hard to look good because less attention
catching as much as possible
[Music]
really
okay okay so I think for now I think the
hair would be like
this blue turquoise eyes well and then
smug face
smug face maybe later Hawaiian shirt
though what the
hell is the culprit single we don't know
yet I don't think we can know from the
witness
statements easier to describe okay
Hawaiian
shirt a very loud
one okay
like probably something like this oh and
she got the boas yeah needs soft you
know with how our witness describe how
soft her whatever
is I
think something like
this
mhm something like this
maybe how how do you draw like a
Hawaiian
shirt how do you draw a Hawaiian shirt
not sure
yes the culprit is too
confident what color is the tropical
shirt I don't know I don't I don't think
it
matters maybe like flowers yeah like
this flower
[Music]
mhm something like this I
think yeah and then they
wear they wear like three hats they said
it was a fluffy
hat
um it was a fluffy
hat uh hair shoulder and hand but
they're
fluffy I kind of didn't get what the
culprit said about the
hats
[Music]
but maybe this is what they mean with
fluffy
[Music]
hat and on the
hand so one of them on the hand I'm not
really sure
[Music]
which hand not sure I mean it doesn't
really matter I don't
think fluffy
hat so like this maybe h
the hand would be I think maybe here
maybe this
one it's like a hat it's wearing a hat
or like holding a hat I'm not really
sure
either what about the umbrella oh
yeah um okay I think hold
on let me just oops sorry
the umbrella
huh oh
oops the
[Music]
umbrella oh oops umbrella would be she's
carrying an umbrella it could be like
[Music]
H and the bag okay okay I
see
H the
[Music]
bag the bag what kind of bag but we
still don't know what kind of
[Music]
bag we still don't know what kind of
bag like this yeah still don't know what
kind of
bag and maybe the umbrella
[Music]
the umbrella could be just like
this yes another half break of luck
thank you so much we hope we can catch
the culprit as soon as
possible yes maybe this is the
umbrella
[Music]
mhm and she is wearing all um opaque red
stocking
uh I
guess opaque red
stocking it's going to do it this
way
okay last witness was kind of focused on
her legs I guess so well and then she
wearing platform shoes but maybe I I I
could just I don't have to draw a full
body I could just like okay this
description
here where the Gat the Gat is why do you
why do you want to see the Gat it's a
police sketch kind
of smug face quick fast
Hasty
interesting skin tight side pony oh we
forgot about the side
[Music]
ponytail H there we
go this is the side ponytail
[Music]
okay family arloom smug face quick blue
turquoise eyes soft round
chest oh and
glasses
glasses okay
interesting
glasses like
this kind of glasses I'm not
sure softer on chest area that doesn't
matter side ponytail what kind of bag
that's the info we need for the bag well
if you don't get our uh any other tip
that's fine too but right now we're just
okay smug face now we finally have to
draw the smug face
[Music]
I have to draw this
smug the
[Music]
smug
smug this
is the best way I can
I can um draw a smuga
[Music]
face it's smug
face how do
you how do you draw a smug face well
this is enough I
guess
okay well I
guess this is a lot of
information we only needed info about
the accessories but even now we can
already start piecing together what the
culprit looks like and glasses glasses
is in
here or maybe we could do this too
it's up to it's up to um we'll we'll
provide an alternate
sketch you'll provide an alternate
sketch well that's not big enough youo
what hello excuse
me excuse
[Music]
well well well this is um the only
way I can piece together the witness's
[Music]
information the Hawaiian trip bows out
and conceals the buba size that's why
the witness only knew them by feeling
exactly it's what I'm thinking also
[Music]
it's what I'm
thinking
[Music]
okay
okay I'm really curious still about the
jewelry like what kind jewelry is she
wearing or if she's wearing any because
so far the descriptions from the
witnesses uh makes it seem like um this
person might be someone a little bit at
least they want to present themselves to
be to look um like
fashionable especially from our tip from
y not y it but Yi
yeah or like if if she's wearing any
like earrings or something like that it
probably wouldn't
be uh it probably doesn't seem too
useful at first you know but any any
kind of information would be important
you
know any kind of information would be
important
because because I don't know who knows
the next time she is here but with a
different get up you know but maybe
she's um
maybe she's clumsy enough to maybe wear
the same accessories or she does that
because she uh thinks oh well they're
not going to find out because I have you
know different looks you know something
like
[Music]
that
or yeah if we find the earring maybe it
fell and we you know we get it as
evidence it would be very nice and
useful
yes yes yes yes that sounds more like it
she does seem overconfident almost as if
this is not her first crime you know
maybe she's done it before maybe under
different disguises who knows I have a
feeling that because of how confident
this person is I have a feeling that she
might
be not your average Thief you know
[Music]
okay Hawaiian
shirt this is the
Gat the hair like the hair reaches the
Gap like Yi
said CCTV
yeah it wasn't clear so we don't know we
have to rely on Witnesses this is a very
special case
[Music]
guys this is a very very special
case so we only need to know about the
bag and about the any
[Music]
okay and one more hat on her hand which
we which we are not
[Music]
seeing
okay so something like this this is by
the way
and do
this let's do this
first so it doesn't
look
weird the culprit looks like adult yod
oh my God is it you it from the future I
don't
know well well
well looks
like like we're doing this this is the
only thing that we can get maybe all
right oh no she's she's still a
criminal unless we get new information
about the bag let's just pretend it's
this kind of big
[Music]
bag
yes something like this
[Music]
I think so far this fits the information
that we
[Music]
got
this this girl seems too
confident to be just like a
random
[Music]
criminal this is what we have it's
either this or
[Music]
this or
this yes
okay
[Music]
no okay
okay and let's see about the color
[Music]
we have to find out if she's single guys
she's a criminal
why okay by the way okay the stockings
yeah the
[Music]
stockings the stockings
opaque red stockings I don't know what
kind of red our witness is talking
about but I think right now it's um like
this
yeah the criminal single I don't know I
don't think that's what we're here for
we're here to catch the
culprit yes
[Music]
okay was she stealing alone well um all
the descriptions never mentioned any
like accomplices or anything so it could
be highly possible she was doing this
[Music]
alone you know
yeah but I don't know could be
anything
red and then a Hawaiian shirt you know
what I'll I'll choose some a nice
color I'll choose a nice color
[Music]
the
best the best
[Music]
blue or maybe in a
maybe now maybe okay oh
[Music]
shoot matches AR rise well maybe we
should change the blue a little
bit maybe you should change it a little
bit
[Music]
okay see this is is
better it's a little bit better they did
say blue eyes right I'm not sure what
kind of blue but I'm going to like fill
it in like this for
now blue oh turquoise oh like turquoise
closer to
turquoise so like like
this yeah
[Music]
always imagine Hawaiian shirts as red
well I'm not sure let me check out the
bunch of
[Music]
colors see they're like red blue or even
yellow not really sure we can try
yellow can try Yellow
base orang orang base is not bad
[Music]
honestly and we could always be like
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
it could be also be this kind of
Hawaiian like not the flowers but the
[Music]
trees
yeah I saw this kind of pattern when I
was looking um common Hawaiian shirt
pattern
so maybe it could be something like this
[Music]
too
um we could also
[Music]
like something like this
like a sunset kind of Hawaiian you
know
[Music]
yes okay
so maybe a little bit like
[Music]
this
mhm how did she smell I don't know I
don't think it matters guys I don't
think it matters how she smells
please calm
[Music]
down
okay
okay okay what's next what did the
witnesses say
[Music]
what did they say um hat is okay
umbrella smug face tall form long hair
dark probably like black
hair I'm going to like test with brown
for
[Music]
now I'm going to test with this color
kind of looks like black
anyways because you know they're saying
it's
black because it was dark so
[Music]
maybe could be
anything could be
[Music]
any s
okay well maybe I'll color all of this
first
[Music]
okay and I don't forget the hair reaches
the
Gat that's what yir said so we're going
to draw it this
[Music]
way maybe let's see if what if we make
it another color
oh like
[Music]
this and maybe what
if what if we make
[Music]
it what if we make this another
color what if we make the Hawaiian shirt
another color maybe it'll
[Music]
be h
H just just testing yeah because this is
not nothing is set in stone this is just
a
[Music]
sketch this also pretty cool
well we could always change it to our
[Music]
liking and then I'm not
sure
mhm still not sure about jewelry but at
this point I don't think we're getting
any information regarding that so I
think it's
[Music]
okay
H
she she doesn't look intimidating well
if anybody comes up to me in the middle
of the night wearing like uh wearing
like a Hawaiian shirt and Skin Tight red
stockings you
know maybe we're sketching her in broad
daylight or like in a safe space maybe
that's why she doesn't seem intimidated
intimidating
enough intimidating is like a Vibe not
necessarily a look our witness our past
witness said that she um she had a smug
face so I think think it's best to
follow that because um Oro crony did say
that she was intimidating and she um Oro
crony was intimidated she had to go to
therapy but she never really said
anything about the you know the face
being
scary fluffy
hat okay
I mean we could always like make this
another
[Music]
color
okay something like this
[Music]
maybe fluffy hat as I know has
said this like Pokemon Pokemon gym
leader oh my
god oh oops same layer I drew I drew the
Hat the same layer as the in so I can't
change the color well I can
but I
can I can but I'm lazy
oh you know what no no no no we could
always like reset
this no
okay it's way less painful to color the
[Music]
skin this this kind of
awful this is kind of
awful
ah
okay okay okay okay better better better
better little bit okay it's
[Music]
fine oops
maybe okay maybe something like
[Music]
this T I'm not sure I'm just doing
whatever
color oh maybe this maybe it matches
just the overall colors is
[Music]
better and then maybe the color of the
oh
[Music]
yes I'm having you
know okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay
okay yes so know the lipstick color well
maybe it's something regular if nobody's
mentioning
it if nobody mentions it I would think
it's something pretty
[Music]
regular okay
so we can
[Music]
we can kind of
um see how the hair
[Music]
is something like this maybe not sure
mhm
but
[Music]
darker something like this I
think
yeah my only cry my client did was SL
play
[Music]
in okay
H opaque
stocking yeah the bag what kind of bag
because we never really got uh enough
information about the
bag we just don't know what do you think
kind of bag is
[Music]
it m
yes the umbrella we didn't know what the
color of the umbrella was but I think um
we should just assume it's a regular
umbrella yeah we should assume it's a
regular one I think that would be safe
like a plain one because I think
otherwise the would have said something
about
[Music]
it
yes
[Music]
okay man what are we doing this is the
job I have to deal with
[Music]
red and white
umbrella
[Music]
yes okay low key I don't think it's a
good color but you know this is not
about whether a color looks good or not
this is about this is like a w this is a
witness sketch and it's something it's
very
important
okay it's very important it's not about
whether it looks good or
not I kind of want to change this red to
make it look better I don't
know
shoot oh yeah okay let's look
better like more
polite
[Music]
okay
okay okay cool
I don't want the boas to be too
big that's like Mahi witness testimony
but I don't
[Music]
care okay there we
go the witness may have been seeing what
they wanted to
see Oh that's oh um I guess so well
sometimes we got to like you know be uh
give
a witness testimony might be 100% not
accurate might not be 100% accurate and
sometimes it might be up to us to you
know just like compare Witnesses
uh you know info and we just you know
deal with it I
[Music]
guess I
guess yeah okay
[Music]
okay
yeah
okay okay that's
good Hawaiian okay what's the B color
what's the generate color for a bag so
it's not too misleading if we get it
wrong but it also you know
[Music]
Works dark brown
okay checkered brown black wo wo wo wo
try try Brown first
okay try Brown
first what the [\h__\h]
okay let's try Brown
[Music]
okay do something like
this
[Music]
okay maybe change the color a little bit
something like
[Music]
this yes yes yes yes yes
yes my goodness
[Music]
this is
tough this is
tough where is
the yeah okay
[Music]
wait wrong wrong
one this is this
[Music]
maybe
yeah okay a very specific
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
okay oh
oops oh the bag is below the hair there
we
go oops
[Music]
sh
okay imagine if the witness is yeah
imagine if they accuse the wrong lady
[Music]
no okay well um this looks this looks
okay is I
think
[Music]
yeah
mhm there we
go because of the profile I think um
yeah okay
[Music]
what color is the glasses well I winess
couldn't see
[Music]
sadly oh oh this
looks why why why why this lowkey eight
hold
on wait where's
the where's the sketch
[Music]
where's the sketch I don't even
know why this Loki at yo let's go um
let's make the shades red or something I
don't
[Music]
know yo
why the criminal to
[Music]
slay why the criminal to slay what the
hell okay
why how
[Music]
come how come the
heck okaya
[Music]
so okay this is probably what the
criminal looks
like based on our witness
[Music]
testimonies the skin tone doesn't match
the
shading but we'll fix that soon
we'll fix that
[Music]
soon uh hold
on wait where's the skin shading
[Music]
color oh
there we
go
okay yeah cuz like the the shade I chose
is different from the shade of the base
skin it's kind of like when you pick
warm and then the shading is cold it
doesn't
match oh 10 are not oh my my
God yes yes that's a very good idea hold
on let
me let me let me let me let me make two
[Music]
versions hold on hold
on uh hold on let me just
yes so this might be like
post
oh so it's kind of like it could be
anything it could be
[Music]
anything can you you see 10 while dark
yeah that's the point that's why we are
making
multiple versions of the
sketch
because it could either be like this or
like this well maybe it can also not be
accurate you know there's there's so
much you know we can only do so much
when it comes to limited
[Music]
information she keeps getting hotter and
hotter come
on we have the witness call back to
confirm the sketch no I don't I don't
not have any way to reach them
[Music]
why why why why this why this girl low
key
[Music]
yo oh there we
go hey are we done do we have it do we
have the
sketch of
the of the possible culprit
the witnesses have created the ultimate
life
form and yes oh my
God what the
[Music]
heck thank you to all the
witnesses who have helped me
find the ne you know who helped me
sketch I guess not fine we haven't
really found anything
yet
yes I'm so so so
happy where's the I'm I'm really
confused like where's the where's the
lines is it this one oh
yes just to clean stuff up you
[Music]
know okay
okay
wow have this opaque red Super Chat as
thanks for this incredibly fun stream
commenting your investigative skills
your drawing skills look brilliant and
with the likeness of the criminal we can
track her down ask her if she's sing oh
how is she committed to the T no we're
going to we're going to bring her to the
station we're not going to not going to
ask her if she's single or
not you know we have you know we we we
can't cuz it would be um against
protocol I think so at
least it wasn't against protocol though
I don't
know okay
well we must get her she won't be
getting away well you know the thing is
this is an initial lead you know she
might not have done it she might have
done it you know so as soon as we post
this
wanted
postera we
could uh hopefully get more
leads and it's like not probably some
people have seen this person somewhere
and then if she's actually very very
sussy then like
yeah she's wanted all
right if evil why hot when she changes
her clothes she's gone forever though
that's why we have no time to lose
we have no time to lose
of wanted for the theft of the family
heirloom
okay well I'm going to finish my Bento
after this I'm going to
post I'm going to post uh the you know
we have two versions We have this
version and this version
no I don't know
maybe oh no this is
fine okay
yes this looks better I think maybe you
know we can imagine it it's not
necessarily true or not maybe we can
imagine she goes around the world to
look to steal family heirlooms or
something like that but anyways thanks
guys for
coming I have a report to right and
thanks to the witnesses I'm not losing
my job hell
yeah
okay thank you I'll post this thank you
guys for your attention officer Pavia
wayy I'm going to eat and then do some
obviously investigatory policy stuff I H
see you never again I guess salamia
what wow
[Music]