[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
my
ah
um
[Music]
hello
oh
[Music]
that was a good sandwich
sorry for the weight
i didn't think i needed more food but
then i was like this might be a long
stream because of the super chat so
and i decided to quickly have a sandwich
sorry because if i eat the sandwich
after the stream
then what about my dinner because i
still have some leftover from yesterday
yesterday i actually cooked let's go
[Music]
i cooked did you see on twitter guys
thank you
dad thank you blessed better nuggets mmm
nuggets
[Music]
i'm drinking iced tea
but it's almost gone
[Music]
i stuffed bell peppers
actually
i stuffed them with lentils because well
the recipe says lentils and to be honest
i have no problem with lentils
but
uh
my mom used to make stuffed bell peppers
by stuffing them with like
rice and or
uh
minced meat
and i used to really not like stuffed
bell peppers but as an adult now i i
totally understand why you make your
kids eat stuffed bell peppers
because it's
pretty easy to make
but it's it's also not bad like it's not
it's not bad it's actually good but i
don't know
as a child i didn't like it much
hmm
lentils probably never that much but
there was there was one point
um
i don't ever ever told the story before
but there was one point where
uh i was living alone after
coming back from japan when i was still
young
and i i
i was
i started my
training
at a school while working
and
i was living alone and
i didn't have much money because fool
paying for the apartment on my own when
the
when the pay in the first year was
really really bad
like it was really bad holy [\h__\h] maybe
maybe 600
oh let me look it up
it's actually a little bit more but that
might have changed because back then i
don't think it was that much they they
make it higher every year
yeah it's around 700
now at least
700 old yeah but i lived on a little bit
less than that
and i was living alone and i was really
um
uh uh uh brooke and so i
i think i told this before i
took
um
bread and leftover bread and um
linens
from work
bed
linens
from work to use at home yeah
uh
[Laughter]
yeah just you know wherever i could save
uh some money you know that's when you
have to save some money
[Laughter]
at some point
my um
brother moved in with me for a short
amount of time
and
um
he was he was sleeping on my couch but
the good thing was while he was living
there he was also used to the broken
life and at that point back then he
cooked way more than i do now
already
uh he's just one year older but he cooks
a lot or he used to cook a lot i'm not
sure
but he's used to cooking with cheap
ingredients
so
he made like um
lentil
a bunch of like fruits with lentils and
all that because lentils are cheap as
[\h__\h] and that made me actually like
lentils because he actually cooked
pretty well
so he lived for free in my apartment for
a while but he cooked for me and made me
like
lentils
yeah yeah yeah yeah good stuff
not
yeah well bad sheets
it was one it was one bed sheet okay
like actually not bed sheet but like
uh the
blanket cover
[Music]
yeah man thinking back to that time holy
[\h__\h] i don't know how i did that
it will be like that being adult and
not earning money
um
yeah he's a good cook yeah
you sure
he always because he lived with my mom
for a long time so he would always help
her cooking
which made him learn much more from her
than i did because i [\h__\h] off to
another country very early on while he
was still living with her so so
we are back to
cult of the lamb
yeah
second episode
so we will continue this yeah
oh
i hope that'll give you more money
good luck min
okay kuza
uh day 14
eight followers
playtime three hours 32 minutes yeah and
we defeated one of those
so hopefully today we'll get to defeat
one more
let's see
oh the eye where count of the phoenix
[Music]
okay
ah god
do i remember what to do in this game
let's see
the hunger is pretty full
what exactly is the
the top left the the one with the
praying hands supposed to tell me
you guys know you guys remember
i'll collect this
oops
oh that's not x and none of this x on it
[Music]
faith okay then that looks good too and
i want to collect divine inspiration
okay um
huh
but i have one i can buy one i wanted to
collect the ones that go like
okay let's buy something
oh
we
bought
some things
oh yeah the last two things that we
bought are these two things thinking
that
should help quite well
let me see
i want to
get
an outhouse or a janitor station soon so
in order to do that i'm gonna get
shelters
yeah
there you go
oh basic decorations no one needs that
no decorations
see okay now i can receive it okay
thank you oh whoa whoa whoa what's
happening why is that so
why is that so glowy is it just telling
me we have something new to build
we can build shelters now but hmm
the sleeping bags still work
but will they be happier if i built them
the proper shelters
do you like materials back when i
get rid of something
let me move this around a little bit
less maintenance oh yeah yeah the the
the beds the current beds they break a
lot
shelters last longer
yeah yeah i guess it's worth it
for your
okay
i can upgrade okay wait i could upgrade
from like where it lo how it is now
resign
and how do i upgrade
uh i edit buildings probably
move remove oh
is there really like a direct upgrade um
option
upgrades
no just buy the thing
click on build it'll automatically place
him over
okay
ah
oh you have to build is it so that you
have to build the the this kind of bed
first anyway as a base
ah
it seems that because i can't put it
anywhere else
okay let's replace a few
uh
one more that's all i can do for now
hope you're happy
they look happy
any poop to clean up before we go to an
adventure
or anything else we should be doing ah
perfect timing
okay uh what about the berries is
someone working on those or not
you pause it let me do pause those i
guess
uh chameleons can you even eat camellias
hi what's wrong perfect shots
how did i come up with this name again
perfect shot
perfect
whoa glorious leader the bass is an eye
so hi we
we need beauty to celebrate your glory
let us build decorations yeah okay okay
okay okay we i just said i wouldn't do
it but okay if you're asking for it
i accept it but it might take a while
um eyes for medicine
oh
[Music]
oh wait how do you build this again do i
also have to go to the building station
yeah
okay i'm building a few more because
these ones
i can
i can build plenty
this quest is a time limit oh [\h__\h] well
i don't know if i can get it that fast
oh it really does
i do have anything that's that counts as
a decoration right now oh i do
okay
hmm
oh i do have a lot of community files
okay let's let's do this
okay now
i didn't think i would be doing stuff
like this so properly but you got me
oh oh it won't properly fit there but
[\h__\h] it
ah that's all i can afford anyway
okay well i built way more than three
decorations now
everybody you should go to sleep
go go to sleep
i guess i'll be building something alone
i can move the temple yeah when i when i
can build more of those decorations i
guess i will
i'm not a building
i have to build along i chose to build
so late okay
okay
um you only put down the deck oh i i
should yeah yeah yeah yeah oh spider how
do you catch them again like
ah
[Music]
yo
i cornered it
it just stopped running there i thought
i lost it when i ran inside the building
nice
it's got my top
oh well i'm not afraid
looks quite nice
you know what i saw
i understand now this whole twitch
integration thing you can play this like
on twitch um and have
the followers be
twitch play uh twitch viewers if only i
was a twitch streamer huh
if only
but can you like actually run around
um thank you
if you're one of those followers
another building
i would like to talk to
perfect shot
but i already forgot what he looks like
you also have ah
i know you could do it really divine
divine exquisite
oh
i'm completing fingers now
i've seen it before but
oh you guys gonna water this stuff or do
i have to do it
i know it was for the quest completion
but
real
credits
ah new commandment
okay will they really water it let me
i'll i will stay here
will they also plant it yeah he's
planting okay okay okay
okay okay i'll trust in you guys i'm
just like worried that they won't do
what i need them to do
oh poop
i should have someone yeah a son to the
farm
okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
let's do um the daily stuff
uh a sermon
listen
[Music]
oh
what the [\h__\h]
12 out of 15
huh
it's not enough
i need more
what the [\h__\h]
is there something i can do here
no
inspiring as ever apparently not
inspiring enough
maybe i need more people
yeah you guys need to be more devoted
okay
uh so wait well yeah i can make
something new here right okay okay um
instructed
where's jordan no death is not the end
have them profit both labor and love
teach them the true meaning of obedience
preached on the valley of earthly goods
i would say work in worship or after
life hmm
[Music]
afterlife is useful
what was that scary sound
i shall devote my firstborn child so you
you wouldn't be the first one to do that
ah they're not dying yet
uh-huh labor labor i'm going for this
one or am i i don't know whatever it
doesn't matter i'm going for this one
oh
playful trade all cult members will gain
the faithful trait
generate devotion 15 faster oh we were
just talking about the fact i need more
devotion but not really actually in the
game
all cult members will gain the
industrious trade increase rather speed
by
you know what i want this right now i
feel like they're working too slow
work faster
yeah you guys are used to working hard
carefully
this trait will be applied to all
members of the cult and will change how
your faith is affected by events
okay not a hotel and do we do a ritual
too
no okay
okay you guys are dismissed
leave
go back to work as i just told you
and i think i need to go to the pilgrims
passage
so i shall do that
um
after perhaps making some food
go
[Music]
there you go
travel right here
sounds retired me no
i mean
that would be nice but
would have been nice but no no i'm fine
actually i'm fine
i think i sound the way i always sound
what is this cute place
oh fisher guy
well look what a toy dragon
i'm not one of your mindless acrolytes
oh can i fish
oh no
fishing in games like this oh
let's see oh that went really far
oh okay i see it's like that
oh pretty good pretty good first try
those are useful after all at useless
you should perhaps we could help one
another i happen to have caught some
extremely valuable treasures in my time
things are a fish like me uh i mean
official fishing bad like me has no use
for but to you well you look like you
like valuable things
those waves love some of the hardest to
catch beasts that ever lived and i've
been trying to for years
if you could stop them these treasures
are yours
touch me crab
lobster
octopus and a squid oh so many
i should wake up
mm-hmm okay
oh
enemies have a chance to drop a fish
neptune's curse ah it's another option
that we can get now
only by interacting with npcs
thank you tucker tank
oh
oh thank you
[Music]
oh we'll talk about that oh thanks cat's
biggs yeah i also thought about tales of
a rice for a moment
fishing fishing fishing
i don't know if i'll be doing that much
but i guess they don't dislike fish
recipes huh and i can use those
right for
oh cute your animal form your followers
can take oh what oh cute
wait is it just a head
or do they get a body
what what are those huge fish what the
[\h__\h]
let's try oh they're coming for it ah a
small one out of all the ones i could
get but it could be like a crabber so
who knows oh [\h__\h]
ah oh i did get them a couple of small
ones
but now i'm hooked
funny because i'm gonna get the fish on
the hook
where did you get come from
oh [\h__\h] it's really hard actually to
keep it
because you don't know where it's gonna
go either and oh my god
when you hold it it goes like all the
way up ah there we go
ah is that something we needed no
wonderful
oh [\h__\h] why did i go so far that looks
like a tacoma chicken
the
the the the thingy
look looks like a tacoma chicken to me
maybe i'm seeing dakoma chickens
everywhere they don't care
right oh thank you you agree oh oh big
fish
oh
don't
just ah
ah
yo
it's so difficult
oh is it is that a squid well let me see
oh i can give some yeah yeah okay it was
something you needed one of those
and
oh
good thing there is no timer yeah good
thing they don't don't just completely
[Music]
disappear
and then i have one of those the other
one i'll keep you know
the loose of squid you take this card
maybe 50 years ago no use to me
what is that what am i gonna get from
this
what could that turn into um
maybe
i don't know
no i don't know
oh it's getting dark
could it be the big fish i don't know
whatever
guess we're going for the small one
maybe it's a crab
what
gold bars that's fine too
give me the big one
oh yeah even though the [\h__\h] the big one
is really tough why did i why did i
decide to go for that one
oh it's something new
but that's not something he wants tuna
for my kitty cats
good evening hello there
i wonder if depending on the time you
can get different things i'm guessing
not
wait why am i so hooked on this
yeah
oh
but nothing i need lobsters and crabs
yeah
what else is there here peering to the
darkness
oh
hello
oh my god
a little oh
a little
a little lamb all alone careful
you never know what lurks
and yet i smell no fear on you
how curious
oh i see
you wear the red crown
i know your predecessor he was a weak
and cowering thing
not like you i should think
little lamb you've made a deal before
how about another
fear not i won't ask for anything as
valuable as your eternal servitude
i'm hungry starving
raven
ravenous
i want a fish
a big fish and i will give you something
in return do you accept
oh i thought he was gonna ask i don't
know something else
but like ask me to join a different cult
he just wants a fish
well that's fine but he probably wants a
really big one
give him gouda these are not big or was
any of their shadows big
maybe
oh how about the squids
clever creature
take this and look away won't you i'm
afraid i'm a bit of a messy eater
you will not see me here again but our
paths will cross elsewhere in moments of
chance in the cover of night
oh does he only appear in oh wait
it's never one of those pieces i thought
i got all four from the dude for all the
four fishes
i can only meet him at night
a new day
interesting
what's going on here
it's just that the lighthouse is getting
there no matter how hard we use it and
the ships keep sinking on the rocks also
means no new [\h__\h]
[Music]
no we have no choice but to pray until
the lighthouse is lit once more ohio
[Music]
cute white wood so
oops i'll get a few oh that's the quest
oh wait wait that's why there's trees
outside let me try that
oh yeah i've noticed those trees here
15 they need thanks for the pinky
i have six now
oh i chopped a tree uh still another
tree
what is that thing here
buy follower form
unlock follower forms
i don't really need that because i'm
going for pigs i guess as long as you
guys don't have chickens
do i get 15 now
how many it didn't show me this time
okay let's check if it's
enough i did it
bring of light is the chief one i got
i'll pray is happening
thank you i'll bring one for sending
this lamp to save us now the pilgrims
and we're turning to our choice we're
staring in light we pledge ourselves to
you oh
all all of you
all seven
of you
[Music]
we will pray to you and your great light
on this drawing please pay by now
adoration okay no they're just giving me
the
ah
35 more have no wait what
no i wait when i know they're not coming
to my
camp right will they just continue
praying for me in there and i can keep
on picking it up
wow
okay
we pledge ourselves but you don't laugh
but no they also they don't place them
to place themselves to me but
oh
but they stay here i think yeah yeah
yeah so i can use this place as a
little camp of extra stuff
nice
oh
oh greatly darling what do you know
about parrot cards i cannot use them
myself but i find them often when
walking by the sea
even though they're half drowned or
buried and
some say the cards reveal fate i say the
cards are 25 gold coins each interested
i have like no money right now
another time what is this
[Music]
i had a love of ones who went to the sea
never came back they used to lay flowers
by the door
flowers suit the young and beautiful
best they have no place with me
these decorational items ah
yeah yeah yeah flag
flooring and more flooring i like the
middle one but uh
yeah
i'm gonna
uh
maybe sometime if i'm rich as [\h__\h]
which i currently am not
i want one more
of those thingies
do i get it from completing the quest
come on
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
please be the other thing i need no
okay but i get i give you hereby a a
crab
yeah massively lucky really are they
rare they feel rare
oh oh the last piece i needed have about
even completing the quest
oh baby baby
we have found all four pieces of the
holy talisman
talismans are mystical relics that the
red crown can use to unlock new fleeces
oh
i'm not going to quit places from your
altar in your temple
oh was i not able to do that before
[Music]
l3
yeah
what
but i have to do it and in my temple
right here yeah no fish can i never fish
ever again what oh am i just done for
today i guess so
cool
let's go to the cult of the phoenix
we're gonna fight soon
new facial facebook
i thought someone was shooting me
too much rust
okay
okay okay okay
are you working or what you're just
standing around
are you just standing around
what what's the matter with you
give command
ten
go tend
you don't harvest oh man okay
but you didn't water properly
after i ever saw this myself oh my god
can i have a right hand you know like
the king
in game of thrones
thank you guys for the greenies um
that's the bones
thank you
oh more birds
those aren't fully uh
i saw that one had a sign i thought it
was just because i uh put some poop on
it they look fully grown
are they not
i have to upgrade the phone
shouldn't you be working
i would love some
uh some of the flowers from the dark
wood dungeon uh
okay
i used them all up for the decorations i
guess
the spices
okay okay okay okay okay where's the
poop
show me the poop
here's one
it's nighttime again
time passes fast in this game
fetch quest uh oh but the the poopy
thing that was also a quest
oh ah
ah i got it
oh i'm getting good at this
i don't see another poop
almost there i don't see another poop
this is really there do i have to wait
there i passed one
ah there ah
thank you it's kind of dark right now
it's hard to see
okay
collect reward from broke really
so many quests now
today guys i had oh oh spider is it
gonna bite me cuz it came right at me
i got it again oh my god i'm so good at
this
today
i had a little bit of a karen moment
and i feel a little bit bad about about
it but at the same time it's the other
person that made me turn into a karen
okay
what can i do
like normally i i don't ever
do that
oh it's gonna turn into level two or
three
yay oh to find inspiration
[Music]
before we go up i'm still gonna go to
this one because you guys said i should
get this one
[Music]
too much detail i guess but
um
oh collect loyalty reward oh
nice oh another one
[Music]
but like
there was a
uh a person
a stranger
some kind of worker
who
oh [\h__\h]
like
said something to me and then i said uh
i did that because i wanted to help
because other people
recommended me to do so
other people that have the same job as
you
and then he was like yeah but i don't
need this
this is this is more confusing to me and
i said well you made a team you got it
to work anyway didn't you and other
people failed at their tasks so i did
this because of that so that's why i did
it and he keeps on
like repeating himself saying oh but
i don't need this this is you don't need
to do this and i said i did it because
i
you're confused
[Laughter]
he didn't yell at me but i also didn't
yell but he annoyed me and it was such a
long back and forth i i was like why why
are we doing this
do i do we really have to have a
discussion about this
and then he was like you know no we
don't have to and then i said okay and
with that i say goodbye and thank you
have a nice day and i i
smashed the door
um
because she really [\h__\h] annoyed me
like
why do you have to be so [\h__\h]
complicated
uh
damn was good taster yeah pretty much
like that
[Laughter]
was a bit annoying
[Music]
no the language was definitely clean i
didn't insult him or anything
but in the end i raised my tone a little
bit which was surprising to myself too
because normally i
normally i'm not really able to do that
normally um
i'm like pretty
i have to say civil oh [\h__\h] i think i
failed oh no i didn't fail it
i'm pretty civil normally
i want to go fight but there's so much
stuff to do here always so much
yeah it didn't get worse i just shut the
door really loudly and then bye-bye
oh that was fast what the [\h__\h]
oh
what why is he trying to make this is
this new
um oh no this is that menu okay wants me
to choose
uh
well we have this one already right
chris with the hood for new curses will
appear on your crusade
i don't know should we go one should we
focus on the one path or should we
balance them all out
the curse
oh there is only one choice oh oh i have
to fill them all up okay okay okay
before i can go even higher
ah there we go okay
[Music]
hey
wonderful
anything else here
oh yeah yeah
here you i can uh
i can get
can i get more of those
uh
what did he call them talismans no
i can give them
okay but there's no [\h__\h] orange
there's no chickens in this game there's
no orange what the hell
i guess the golden fleece will suffice
but wait is it really worth it using
that yeah yeah yeah it doesn't it's not
usable for anything else right
wait wait there's a wait there's a wait
wait there's a there's a there's a
attribute i thought it was just looks
i just saw when i was activating it
wait that was still increases after each
kill but resets when the hit take double
damage
oh
what the coolest
deal double damage
and cost half the reverb but merely dead
whip whatever oh [\h__\h]
should i even use this
damage death increases after each kill
but resets when hit
that itself sounds good
but i always take double damage from
them
just don't get hit we can try it and see
how much i fail with it
i thought it was something i could make
them wear
oh
okay
okay marshall
let's collect something camellias
magic armor i mean i look pretty cool in
it
i guess
i'm gonna go now guys are you guys ready
to be left alone i'm a bit worried
okay
you like that sort of play style
it's not quite my thing but
yeah
okay
anubra
what the [\h__\h] is happening
thanks guys you can leave now
yeah new area it seems like i can still
go back to the old one if i wanted to to
practice my meat or grind
but we're gonna go here
kill everything
yeah okay
[Music]
we start with the choice of
a perfect dagger chance to heal the
wielder ah
wait isn't that sick in combination with
the golden coat
because
i get healed by the dagger every time i
kill someone
and for every hit i do it might get
reset after i kill someone but for every
hit i do i get stronger so so actually
it's a sick combo holy [\h__\h]
oh that was um totally on purpose all
according to keikaku i knew i knew that
this was yeah
okay how do i
use this stuff again what is this
read the lands of the bishop heckett
those who do not follow the ways of the
old faith will be destroyed
yeah
no no well i take double damage but
every time i get hit
wait what was it sorry what the [\h__\h] i
forgot every time i get hit i get healed
no every time i kill someone
uh yeah yeah i think it's a good balance
okay um
uh [\h__\h] i don't i don't remember i don't
remember i don't remember i i don't
remember the fight i'm not there
wait ah wait
i hear this spot this button
i was looking for the red button [\h__\h] i
already got kids twice
okay but did i get healed now
ah holy [\h__\h]
oh oh hold on hold on
is there a focus button no
no right i was asking for that last time
too but
did i get help at you
or is it only sometimes on it
was it a slight chance
well i got a little bit health back here
sometimes okay i think i saw the healing
in effect
like one time
okay no it's just fine
it's fine it's good it's good
it works
damage plus 40 is [\h__\h] sick
oh you're just gonna talk to me and
disappear right
oh yeah yeah
well you know what i'm gonna give him a
cute voice
[Music]
we are the guardians of the jewelry and
we shall not tolerate that blasphemy
[Music]
where am i lisa
oh he's gonna be fine right there's food
at home maybe
it's gonna be it's gonna be fine
question mark
he only pleaded half of his hunger
he's fine
what happened
oh my god
i love them
so i'm trying to get rid of the stones
with the
miata it's quite useful
they don't even attack me what the hell
oh there you go
nice push which
push did we get everything
let's just try to get home as soon as
possible to feed my boy
right right or up um
right
yeah
right joyce hey
what's up
how are you doing
uh received
ah both are good but this is this works
with my combination of taking a lot of
damage and getting healing back
yeah
poison is good but
we don't need it right now
did i take the right one
the menu the animation confuses me
is it here
oh yeah i took the right one okay it
kind of looks like i took the other one
the way he talks reminds me of the maybe
the orcs and lord of the rings
me to the fireplace
oh you're right
i forgot
you have to
destroy everything
and these frogs are [\h__\h] weak i love
them they're so cute can i just have
them as pets
they don't even seem to want to hurt me
they're not enemies they're supposed to
be kept as pets
cute frog
cute
i want frog
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] i got hit too often why did i do
that
oh yeah right it gives me the option to
sacrifice someone
or
ah
should i
then i can continue fighting
is it worth it i'm not sure
return okay
i
[Music]
even with those frogs
yeah i'll rise again thanks dude
it matters not how many times you're
struck down the culture will continue to
grow
it's strong indeed
should i change my fleece
and i want to try one more time
but let me feed the people
don't fight guys
oh dear
can i um
[Music]
i'm sorry i want to help you chomp
one or two more yeah i was just thinking
that
so did i not bring the items
back home or did i do like a part of it
hunger meter rising yeah yeah yeah it's
fine it's fine it's fine give me a
second
just getting some berries i bring back
some okay
that's what i thought
okay let me see what i can draw
yeah oh [\h__\h]
you keep on tending
let's make some food yeah cooking time
have some stuffed bell peppers with
lentils
i mean i have some leftovers thankfully
to
my
hellofresh box being
for two people always because choosing
one person is not possible why they're
discriminating people who live
alone
oh they became friends
[Music]
they only offer their services to
families and couples isn't that
discrimination
for real man
we alone livers need some help to
single discrimination man
i mean i'm not really mad but actually
they should offer an option for single
people what the [\h__\h]
but it is even for like
for two people
even for two people the
um
oh i can only do one
the portions of ingredients are so tiny
for some ingredients that i can
understand that it's hard to make them
even tinier to fit what
you know you're cooking
oh
they are really small now
and i guess you know i can always eat
the rest on the second day
so it's fine it's fine
can't do another sermon
oh i can
my cats can't eat the food i cook
[Music]
oh oh what can we do curse of the
occultists three new curses will appear
in your crusades or
increase the total amount of
you can hold allowing you to cast an
additional curse
wait what
can't wait what is furvor again
i can go to this one too
ah i'm going for this one
[Music]
especially if you continue carrying the
golden coat
mana ah
ah
happy
oh upgraded
damn he's so enlightened
sasuka whoa look at his eyes he's so
blessed
oh my god another divine inspiration
unlocked
holy [\h__\h] it's going fast guys i think i
i'm a natural at this
i was born for this
oh my god okay
[Music]
is this
a place for us who are not worshipping
to pray throughout the day and deposit
devotion
i think every cult leader thinks they
are born for this
yeah that is no purpose
we don't have any naughty followers we
don't need it
um
i can't go higher yet so what's the
missionary senior and the holocaust
together ah
i need a prism
okay
i don't want them
use your own room okay
ah there we go
10 out of 10 refinery
oh
interesting okay let's find another time
a prison disney i really need more gold
so let's go out and kill some
uh enemies show me
and we
finish that quest
let's go
the quest
oh whatever oh wait but if it fails then
uh
[Music]
wait i wonder if i can get chameleous
faster if i go into this one the dark oh
yeah it is not i says dark wood maybe
the caminos are only in the dark okay
okay okay okay i didn't realize i
couldn't uh hi
are you surprised i'm back here
wouldn't you change blue oh
[Music]
before it started mobile motionless
centuries grew for host
now let she have fallen in here upon the
inhabitants of this land begin to fight
on you to pursue whom
ye so don't fight them so easily
dispatched against
oh [\h__\h] okay
[\h__\h] is gauntlets an iron fist from
which none can escape
that sounds
exciting and new
a death sweep
they're sending mimi attack that can be
charged for increased power
what two new weapons that i don't think
i've heard of before
wow wait this is like out of a tilt of
uh viseria
let's go
wow it's a cool weapon it's relatively
fast
so i can work with this
ah [\h__\h] i shouldn't
be so careless
oh oh that's how that works okay hmm
right in front of me
okay
i'm gonna go down this time
yes
i'm always right
oh shiny when attacked 20 percent chance
of negating damage just receive double
ah well since this is shiny i'm going
with a shiny
i have two out of ten and i have half
half time
half of the time
20 20 is good yeah
hey the decoration
tells me the room
these two
things here or even you mean that thing
over there
oh
okay there's a lot of enemies gotta be
careful
okay
bye
oh my god
[Applause]
okay the golden coat is nothing for me
[\h__\h]
look at me why do i look like that
because i died too often
oh man
am am i ashamed
oh
i don't want to hear his criticism at
least i didn't
get rid of any of the flowers
[\h__\h]
no
i'm sorry at least everybody's
sleeping they think i'm weak but they're
sleeping
[Music]
oh why is that there
uh
where was it
yeah
maybe maybe if i get really good at the
game again
then i can use the golden code
oh man ah [\h__\h] this is embarrassing
[\h__\h] i have no time i can't talk to you
what do you want wait what did you say
old h
oh we can sacrifice him soon huh
okay okay okay i can still make it i can
still make it
i can still make it
just gotta
oh it's this weapon again
and a fireball flaming shot
hold and release to make an explosive
okay
ah
i mean the enemies here are stronger
than before so
it's not like they're as weak as
they were in the beginning and i'm
losing against that
oh sure
okay
three out of ten and some money this is
good
let's go let's go let's go
oh
oh oh oh oh
[Music]
again
[Laughter]
these are really strong wait it's not
just me right
all right i'm gonna i'm gonna get you
oh wow that's really strong
oh
one temple very high it's half a heart
plain easy no
no
yeah
[Music]
wait someone's old anyway i kind of
sacrificed a guy who's old
oh my god
it's really [\h__\h] tough man
this is the old one
was it perfect shot no elmo it was elmo
old age
i mean what's gonna happen to old age
people anyway
[Music]
um
like
is there any meaning in keeping the old
ones
he just dies anyway
elmo
what are they also
it's a cult right there's nothing wrong
with sacrificing people right
especially for my own health for my own
survival
well those will give you faith
the old ones still give you faith during
sermons yeah
um
for the greater good
ah but i can maybe revive them too at
some point if i wanted to
it's it's a it's a common thing in this
game right
we're doing it
elmo
loves
i'm so sorry elmo i need to finish this
[\h__\h] quest please help me with it how
much health do i get back though
i'm gonna just die again
and he will have died in vain
oh god
oh [\h__\h] i'm wasting it
i wanted to shoot him but you can't
catch him when he's on the ground
oh [\h__\h] those spikes come over here
okay i can do it i can do it i can do it
yo he's so strong
what's up with that
oh my god
only half a heart back i'm just gonna
die again
hey the rooms are so [\h__\h] packed
oh my
god it is
i'm scared
oh god
ah that's fireballs again
[Music]
okay so i'm doing okay so far
you still need it to warm up you know
here or here it's better now
need to also understand how
serious this is serious business how
much time do i have left enough okay a
card please
a good one ah
nothing really health related but
what do you think
poison damage to get those strong
enemies down faster mm-hmm
oh three more three more
hope i get enough in this one run
oh
oh nice
oh that actually looks pretty i mean
more or less
and we get some healing
a little bit of healing
let's go
oh it's such a long path
uh
we just sacrificed someone maybe we
should go get a follower
[Laughter]
should we
i think so
i'll save you
tactical hit and run
strategy
oh there's more
also i'm poisoning them so hit and run
is even smarter
in this case
[Music]
sucker
hold down here
oh there's more
okay okay okay okay good just this one
okay
welcome to the cold ah
you have quite the beautiful headdress
my friend
let me gather what's around here for a
second
we're running out of time but we need
two more camellia flowers if i fail this
quest i swear to god
okay quick quick
risky rescue rescue breaststroke pass
the best pass pass
bye-bye see you later
i'll talk to you when you're in my camp
ah
it doesn't matter it's both the same huh
but what comes after is different uh
hearts
does this heal me i think so
i guess i need that before the boss
left has more gold
yeah but i need healing
otherwise i would go for the gold
oh
oh yeah oh yeah right wait no flowers
ah
no flowers
i need two more
if i get out of this without the right
amount of flowers man
can i buy them somewhere i wonder
is that a house i can enter
no
it's just for show
oh i stuck who the [\h__\h]
oh god hello oh yeah ah still devotion
there's flowers here
okay okay did the time stop for now yeah
because i can give it back any time
right i can uh i can
redeem the reward anytime
thank god
[Music]
travel
loose red heart gain deceased hearts
what
why can i travel here
can i go
home instead of going to the bus
don't use it okay
i can fight the boss again
i i guess we will yeah with so little i
thought i was gonna get more
more health back oh that goes to the big
bus oh oh the teleporter goes to the big
bus
oh my god
okay okay okay
almost cleaned up perfectly
why can't i clean so well in this game
but not in reality huh
yeah his aim is terrible
okay so was that the last room
no
oh god not the spikes not so close to
each other i hate it
okay
hallelujah
love the soundtrack man but
it's making me also kind of
i don't know nervous
all right left okay let's see if i can
see which one is
[Music]
are it is one of them the parrot card
which one
right
what gives it away
see the star in the moon oh
[Music]
ah
i know
thanks for telling me
yeah
oh good to know
that was just everything on the screen
one hit oh yeah increase this chance to
spawn better chest and go for the chest
let's go
let's finish this map
okay
yeah
oh did you guys see um did you guys
watch leina's run stream because i was
actually playing quite long with her
maybe for an hour or so
teaching her
how to start off
yeah i saw her on the day before i saw
her stream reservation
and i was like you know my that's my day
off and like it's at a good time for me
so i might as well you know show up and
then
on the actual day she
oh hello what the [\h__\h]
sacrifice health
no for deceased hearts
should i eh the seized hearts what do
those do again
are those the ones that um
damage everything i don't think so oh
you can watch it elena's most recent uh
rest stream
deal damage when you take damage
i don't think i want it
eel can i have destroyed it oh [\h__\h]
oh wait uh i thought i was fighting
something
[Music]
what's this
an old god may still reside in depths
tentacles will strike out why is it both
tentacles
hmm
okay i'll take it
yeah i thought she strained it again
today but this time it was a bit too
early and yeah i don't wanna always
uh
have to say
hijacker stream
yeah but yeah on the day when she was uh
gonna stream it like a few hours before
so she wrote
in our shared discord um yo i'm playing
grass for the first time if anybody
wants to help
uh
because it's my first time please join
feel free to join
and then a few people
said they would but i was in the end the
only one except for anya but i didn't
realize i saw later on that anya
had it like
kind of planned to help reina but then
why did reina
ask
the others too i don't know so i felt a
bit bad because i didn't know it was her
whole intention of of anya's stream to
have reina as well
but then anya was doing something else
anyway if i understand correctly
and i've i i thought in that moment
since i didn't know what that was her
intention that the best thing to do with
reyna right now is building her base
anyway so we should just continue with
that oh
yeah i want to write a message to anya
to apologize
cause i feel like
i'm feeling i don't know
if oh [\h__\h] if i had known man
ah
i'm sorry anya
i mean you know
she wanted to um
go for that
and like have a fight for that thing
that
um crate and i mean that sounds fun but
i was thinking reina just started the
game
let's do that another time
another time maybe
you're shh
wow that looks strong
ah that's and sells attentive i didn't
even use maestro
oh well
uh okay let's see ah it's this way this
way i can see it now
yeah yeah aina needs to learn first
but she's learning fast
i did my best i think i was a really
good teacher
i was thinking
what would i have liked to know right
away what was helpful for me in the very
beginning and i still had a good memory
on it because it was very recent
it's all
ah
you know now my health is not so bad and
we're almost done maybe i'll go for the
fish
i might come for the fish
[Music]
yeah i think i did a good job
it was nice it was um
nice to hang out with lena a little bit
i'll get some fish
[Laughter]
i feel like normally i would never
choose this card but
oh
well
thanks
so about rust
i know
i i'm aware
of how
not all of you
are like really big fans of the game
ow and that's fine
but
not not all of you but some of you are
or or maybe really less than one handful
really only a small amount of people
are like being
um
really read about it
i i'm gonna tell you right now if you're
being an [\h__\h] to me on twitter like
that trying to control my content
i'm muting your account okay
so i did that
so i can't even see it anymore but
the thing is like
i can never make everyone happy you have
to keep that in mind and it was
definitely a
a majority of people that was saying
they want me to play the game
and
even though it's not like visually the
most appealing game to me
in theory it's kind of similar to
minecraft and i can currently everyone's
playing it so i can if i play it i can
you know
try to at least hang out with some
people even though it doesn't seem to
work out the whole live english
because they'll play at different times
and i keep on missing it but i have to
take this chance right now because i
feel kind of
isolated um recently so please
understand and and even if you don't
like it let's let's have an open mind
okay
um
you know if you watch the what i did
with reyna i think you will understand
that
it's a it's a good thing
[Music]
but i'm i'm not really
like
did that is that where i came from
i think like most of you were even the
ones who didn't like the game
were nice about it anyway
so thank you for that
i'm gonna destroy you is he stronger too
i wonder
it's so nice because he shows you the
arrow oh
oh my god no
don't spam little mobs
oh no but he disappears he [\h__\h] off
that's nice i can focus on them at least
he's just i'm gonna take a coffee break
okay here we are again
so for us
um honestly i don't see as much content
in it as like minecraft for example
because it doesn't have like
all these sick cool
enemies like
the ender dragon and all that
the map is [\h__\h] tiny
so it will not be like an like a forever
game like minecraft
but you guys can see it everybody's
playing it now so
[Music]
if i don't play it i'm gonna be forever
alone man
i'm like i
i've been feeling that very strongly
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] oh god
oh god oh god oh god
oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god not
these [\h__\h]
zombie catboy
oh
i thought he waited
[Music]
okay okay okay two with one fly what
[Laughter]
okay then we have two more huh
a new follower form gets offered to us
but we don't really need it
we always do pinks anyway
should i go for the gold nuggets can i
turn the nuggets into actual gold coins
oh i don't want to ask some
um a id member at some point to show me
the minecraft server yeah yeah i've had
that in my mind but
should i take this one later but not now
okay okay at some point with the
refinery okay okay okay
what would you guys go for i think i
have enough food right now so i'll go
for the gold
oh yeah oh
finally money again
okay repeating this place we really only
did that because of the
oh [\h__\h] someone's starving right i
should go back home fast i really only
did that because of of of the stupid
quest man
it wasn't planned
um
ollie oh maybe only yeah hmm
indeed because i was gonna originally
ask dana but now we already had you know
the rest collab kind of i don't want to
spam too much
when i ask like different people too i
was thinking kobo but kobo just joined
she wouldn't know that much maybe maybe
ollie
wanted to hang out more with ollie
anyway
now you have to defeat the bishop of
this area may continue on wide
isn't this old information
hmm
what
can i go home now
onwards oh they really mean onwards
no i'm going home what the [\h__\h]
yeah
oh you
i'm not gonna carry her shopping bags
though
uh man that was uh quite something
[Music]
please respect me again
you see me here in chains reduced to
nothing but it has not always been this
i was bound to this rich place by the
bishops of the old faith they betrayed
me and left me to rot
each of the four chains and find me a
guard by one of the bishops
destroy the bishop and you break the
chain break all four and i will be freed
i gave you a life a new vessel and now
you must repay the debt you know what
must be done
to defeat the bishops you will need to
become stronger sacrifice a follower to
absorb more power this will aid you in
your
you want me to do that right now
i
teaching me now sacrifice a follower to
grow your strength and unlock new
abilities and weapons
higher level followers will be more
valuable
i just sacrificed someone but like in a
different way
interesting thanks for teaching me
okay okay hello hello hello are you
angry oh [\h__\h]
hey
bro cooley no
my face is shaking i can see for your
lies you're a fraud and i must say no
oh
followers begun dissenting against you
this happens when it comes no
the traitor is spreading false it's
about you other follows my house will
understand no
yeah the prison it's time for the prison
okay so we have to stop him fast
gonna build a [\h__\h] prison
it's not like i wanted to
but you're forcing my hand wait wait
didn't we learn how to make a prison
they're cool ah this one
oh no
we have an empty corner here next to the
poop
okay i'm putting it here
for now one is hopefully enough uh
how do i put how did i bring him there
wait should we complete this quest
finally
patty's old too now
oh
wait which one is broken
where the [\h__\h] is out here
how do i bring him to
oh there we go
[Music]
wait i'm just re-educating him i'm not
putting him into prison
but she still looks angry though
[Music]
it's already been very educated okay
that so that's not enough okay tonight i
feel it oh okay okay
oh good job good job good job guys i'll
help
build the usual room
use your room go go go go go go
so hungry yes i go oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] wait wait make some
bye
bye i've been away for too long i know i
didn't want to be gone for so long
eat
except for the
dissenter
prison
um
shall we let him eat first
i'm so kind
you know you don't want your prisoners
to starve to death you want them to
continue suffering i
he refuses to eat
oh my faith is fine again though
it's looking good again
make them suffer longer what this [\h__\h]
what is he doing
okay okay so i i was gonna i was gonna
keep you out there longer so you can at
least eat but [\h__\h] you
and poison this
[Music]
oh my god no we're re-educating him
don't kill him
patty oh look she has a stick now
she's so cute
wait are they are they
talking [\h__\h] about me
all right
see the thoughts
the center they finally knocked the
heretic away yeah he agrees with it
lock up the hernicks shoulders
oh he's a good guy remember his name
what's your name who the [\h__\h] are you
okay okay who the [\h__\h] are you
you
you are one of the good ones
you will not be led astray that's
beautiful
yeah that's what they were talking about
they weren't talking [\h__\h] about me they
were talking [\h__\h] about berkeley
okay
that's a different story then hey bert
stop eating my berries
no mercy
remember his name who the [\h__\h] are you
it's easy to remember no because you're
like you look at him and you just go
like wait who the [\h__\h] are you
i don't know your name and then
that's it
that's it yo
problems are broken
wait what do you want oh dude what the
[\h__\h] what happened
ah
do they actually disappear after you
like like completely drained the
what you can get from it that makes
sense wait i see this one's bigger than
this one
oh i'm gonna finish it but okay i'm
gonna keep an eye out on
oh is it bigger
maybe that's that's an optical illusion
i think it's an optical illusion
scarecrow yeah we need one
but not that urgently
[Music]
the sketches and heredits have made
their way to occult cruising our
uh cursing our way of life but they want
to join should we welcome them
recruit dissenting
[Music]
followers someone who's already
dissenting
you want you want me to
take them in
ah
yeah i'll need another prison
i guess i'll do it because you want me
to do it yeah i have to indoctrinate
someone else anyway
welcome cute
[Music]
you become
wait i want to look what the fish looks
like
ah they do have a body
that looks so weird though a fish hat
and a body it's like gouda just kidding
that one looks fancy
i mean it is good
um
wait what color was he before
ah like a brown maybe
i have so many bronze you know what you
will be purple because i think your
original form was kind of purple i don't
know
not your skeptic oh [\h__\h] called
prophylactic
intense faith when falling out
you blaming me when you fall ill
wow
yeah
purple pink
and you shall
[Music]
i don't know
there's worship for now i guess and
welcome to this party too you're also
purple
so
this is a non-believer
we will have to deal with him
appropriately
he will be in prison for life probably
i'm making my light purple now
oh wait we can also make him fluffy here
there you go
silence ignore the centers when they
preach oh that's actually good no
no
but he's at the center will he ignore
himself
you will have to ignore your yourself
man
and the farm for now what oh maybe that
it wasn't him it was him
wait are we getting too
[Music]
[\h__\h]
wait wait dude
oh my fave is yeah bye
ah
um
okay uh
sheesh what should we get
make the prison first okay
they were saying yeah i was gonna do it
there's so much to do
i just
uh anything to get more faith
maybe this
grace for the elderly soon that's true
too
is this a grave it's a body pit
um
not quite the grave i hope we'll cover
it up
uh
[Music]
okay okay okay building another prison
unbelievable
they shouldn't be close to each other
right not too close so that they can't
talk with each other but i don't want
them to be too scattered either because
of space reasons okay well if anybody
sees them talking to one another you
know what to do
wait but was that one really the the
center or is it this one
wait don't sleep i need to hold the
sermon
talk listen to me
shabbat
[Music]
yeah okay that helps quite a bit
uh
can we do something here
industrial straight
wait we did that one right
yeah just had to look at it
and rituals
we could do the the fast again
but uh
it lowers the faith
this one makes the faith higher we
should do that one
and let's do a rachel
eh sacrifice a prisoner
oh
wait we can do that one too right
uh-huh
okay faith looking better
sacrifice oh
wait
eh what is it what is the game trying to
show me here ah
ah this one oh yeah uh
law and order maybe will that help of
the dissenters actually
the old don't contribute what
wait for faith to go up before
sacrificing yeah after life
okay yeah because if we sacrifice then
we want to assure them
yeah okay i believe inside ah
all club members will gain the belief in
sacrifice trade
plus 25 when another club limit is
sacrificed
all couples will believe in the
afterlife trade
only lose minus five faith when the
follower dies and said why would i
why would i go for this one
because it only
it doesn't help me does it
why would i
where would i go for that one
after afterlife is good i thought it was
great sacrifice sounds way better yeah
it sounds better
because you lose 75 less
ah for all
deaths ah not just sacrificing so if
someone dies of age or whatever
oh
no i'm going for this one then i guess
i guess i don't i don't know
yeah just sacrifice them before they die
yeah
that's the way to go
kaboom
beautiful
okay oh yeah
uh okay bye-bye
i'll show you already
i don't want to sacrifice patty though
no
but i have don't we still have time
[Music]
oh she looks so happy
oh no
[Music]
if i revive her does she get back to the
same
um
level and uh does she start from age one
again or
doing her favor
patty was my first follower
i think
[Music]
ah revive the same age oh
hi
i'm so sorry but i know you're happy
about it but okay i have to no oh my god
oh it's terrifying
oh god they all
they all
celebrated
i i have to too i am the
leader amazing
for the cult of the phoenix
gonna help my
my stray lambs and piglets and chickens
oh my
god i'm so happy i'm not crying that's
sweat it's hot totally i'm not crying
it's not painful
[Music]
okay
maybe this one
yeah whatever i don't care
[Music]
yeah yay for stuff yay
what a beautiful day hallelujah
okay you may go
oh i woke everyone my sleep in their
sleep that's a problem for you guys oh
my god
minus 15 faith for waking them in their
sleep unbelievable
ah
i still didn't put the second person in
the
uh
prison because they don't seem to be
disentered actually
they're not shouting around
kill kiwa or anything like that but let
me see maybe this one oh this one has i
haven't in bed sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry
i'll build it don't worry i'm gonna
build it myself
uh what it
wait
they could just sleep in one of those
we do currently have enough and why did
i stop moving
wait a second
that's weird
each one is clean oh can you come now
yeah they're coming now
why did i stop moving is it updating
ah okay i restarted day
23 uh how are you doing [\h__\h]
he's looking sad
are you suffering
what
you can apologize but it's not gonna
help never forget
pretty oh thank you
reeducate him again i'm okay
a second
building the prison to make more people
suffer
us
read minds
[Music]
broccoli's dissenting against your faith
and spreading falsehoods [\h__\h] you
you have to learn
[Music]
oh my god
how dare you just send me
a cute cat
interesting markings on his forehead
though
what do we call him
[Music]
help me
oh it's just now that you say it it does
look like a smiley
garfield
okay but he won't be a cat for long
he's now
garfield's the pink
does anything seem wrong with that
no garfield was always a pig
generates devotion 15 faster
okay
so are you into the center
[Music]
come here
because oh yeah he is
you guys have pigs because
there's no chickens in the game
this one
okay it wasn't the other one we should
rename non-believer he's fine
garfield
what's your problem is it because we
don't serve lasagna at kfp
we serve lasagna and italian kfp at
least
let me tell you about italian kfp you
could work there you could start a new
job in italy today
there's a lazada burger wait
should i try that
lasagna burger
did anyone ever make that before
lasagna burger oh
ah
it exists kind of
[Laughter]
oh
oh my god it's kind of a thing oh my god
it has lasagna sheets in between the
beef patties which makes sense because
like lasagna inside is just beef but
minced minced meat
or not it's not always beef sometimes
it's pork or mixed but i guess it makes
sense
wait like kind of
interesting we're gonna want to try that
lasagna
oh my god mom's lasagna burger there's a
youtube tutorial or so about it
it looks good but does that really have
the the sheets in between i only see the
cheese and the sauce
oh my god
don't let your dreams be dreams
i don't like burgers with too many
patties though because i can't eat that
much and they're so big they fall apart
when you try to bite into them
with one with one patty i might want to
try it
what a genius idea
lasagna burger
let me make some food just in case what
is this oh grassy grill no
we're not gonna make that
uh
can i get rid of that
no i made it for accident okay whatever
um we can make some berry bubbles
what is this
deadly ditch a truly vile concoction
75 chance of the follower dying
instantly
100 chance of dropping valuable
resources oh
what
that's like sacrificing someone quietly
very quiet wait minced follow
me follow our meat
a dish made of the flesh of phil just
every day at kfp
oh my god
fellow cult members 75 chance of causing
illness 20
chance of increasing follow loyalty 40
chance of stooping a follower from
descent stopping
falling from dissenting
do they know what they're eating
yeah bye
why do i have the meat for that is it
patty oh god it's a belly patty
no
every time i sacrifice someone i get
their meat
i guess why not someone might get ill
but
let's try it out
it has good effects too so
we'll see who who will get the
cult follower
meal
who's getting sick that's how we know
who ate it oh i see oh i see someone got
sick is you
yeah
are you sick
can i see did someone just smooch me
saw poop nah he made me just have been
feeling sick because of the poop he saw
what it
i'm not sure okay we have a quest
cute my faith in you was
justified yes yes yes yes so it is so
easy to be like that
ah
so much love
oh it's down thank you
oh
wait it's still there isn't it it's that
one nobody ate it
oh yeah yeah
let me try to upgrade
one of them
[Music]
it's just still still on the honey
eating it
[Laughter]
how's it going here i can re-educate you
again i think no not today okay
oh lots of poop oh god
daniel do they know
hmm i wonder if there's also one thing
where you can make them believe in
eating
the other cult members so that it
doesn't give you
a minus
oh it doesn't
although i guess it wouldn't change
anything about
them getting sick but maybe we can build
an immunity
it does
help the loyalty already so it's not a
bad thing for them
you can make them cannibals oh my god
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's how it is
thanks for listening guys i'm gonna go
out and fight now
okay
bye-bye
i think i did everything i needed to do
here i left some food too they're
looking good and faithful
let's go finally to this world
onyo um do we have to take care of that
right now
well he will stay there right he's
already a pig
he's one of us
but he'll he'll stay there right
i wanna go fight now
oh [\h__\h] i rolled into it
yeah someone can't smell tasty crinkles
in here um
there's enough for you and enough for me
don't let your photos wander away you
never know who might be nearby and
hungry
tiny prophetic creatures but so tasty ah
i can save them but i have like
absolutely no money for it
wait is he he's not one of mine anyway
it's not like he's still one of my
followers
he's fine it's it's fine he sells food
for sacrifice
eh
is that so because i have to buy him
back or like buy him in the first place
it's like a merchant it's [\h__\h]
expensive pascal
or he gives me
spider meat in exchange
oh
it's the tesla viseria velvet gauntlet
but with poison oh my god let's go
amazing oh i love it that might be like
my favorite weapon just because it
reminds me of tales of vasuria
i want to play tales of berseria but i i
completely
cleared it before oh frogs
last time they killed me once but not
going to happen again
what
oh where is the stars and the moons
hold up none of them had it
yo yo yo
you can run but you can't hide
now time to enjoy some real gameplay but
what
you just finished the game but how was
how was you playing it not
not the
gameplay huh
there's so much stuff to destroy here
yeah i killed the snail
i got the shell from it i wonder if you
can make food or decorations from that
yeah
bird place the true way
now i've played tesla face area before
i don't want to
play a game like
if it was something really old that i
played so long ago that i don't really
remember then fine but tesla face areas
you know
i was
i wasn't that young when i played that
oh my god
where's the poison
there we go
yo the reach of the this weapon is
pretty good out
hmm
[Music]
how much do i really remember
yeah
enough
[Laughter]
yeah i don't
i don't think i before i play
a tales of game again
i would rather play an old one for the
first time
that i haven't played before
i'm not so good at those hands really i
think they're so easy to fight with
shiny oh that's a good one getting a
temporary heart oh
let's go i already have poison so i
don't need the other one
isn't
immanucado
that was fast
just two frogs
yeah i wanted to play symphonia but when
i mentioned it last time a lot of people
were like oh no not symphonia too
yeah i don't know why not this is really
bad i can't imagine
it's a tale's off game man how can it be
bad
and i just even even just for like
completion sake since i played sales of
symphonia one as my first ever jrpg my
first ever tails off game and the reason
the reason kiwala is the kibabo that she
is today
you know
even just for the sake of that
i'm down for motels of kino oh there you
go it's a
heart that i was promised
oh yeah i already do play what i like
hmm
i mean i'll be honest for for rust
i wasn't that motivated in the beginning
but uh
after getting a little bit into it
i'm a bit more motivated about it
building has been
it has been fun
i need a horse stove
i never shiny divine curse plus
50 percent less favor
wow
lucky
so lucky oh this one's so short what the
[\h__\h]
um
definitely not a follower we got enough
recently
[Music]
would or
shop with materials but i have no money
anyway i would have to buy it right
why don't we have money
what let's go for wood yeah
oh i don't need any wood farm what [\h__\h]
i need to rebuild those i forgot
oh there's a lot there's so much
wow
oh well it's around 20 or so that we got
it's not that much
no
huh
okay
any wise games wait what what a wise
games
what's a wise game for example
why is that the developer
ah are those games no
okay no i think i know what you're
talking about but no i didn't play them
no no
okay yeah
careless
[Music]
some of them are pretty fun some only
some of them
ah after we're done we've called up the
lamp though now we're also done with
tunic and i'm still waiting and it could
again take ages for the english
permissions of catherine
um
damn
we could start enough with zelda not
that i wanted to play in our zelda so
early on but uh
it's almost as if they're forcing my
hand
let me get that snail
so tiny
[Music]
i'm not feeling another yakuza right now
they're even longer than
oh they're even longer than um
i'm gonna go for this one
even longer than
zelda games
look at me hollow knight
dragon quest
maybe oh yeah i did i did mention gta 5
[Music]
well i'm probably gonna
think about this a bit more uh when
we're close to the end of cult of the
lamp
i mean there's always something
always something we can play right
gta 5 would be funny and it would be
style wise very different
from my usual
choices i guess
it it has a proper story right it's not
just [\h__\h] around all day right
did you just kill your buddy or was that
me
oh yeah
a 30 hour long proper story wow
good for collabs too
it's a special one
is it not good
there must be a reason why it's so
popular right this is just because it's
fun to [\h__\h] around
probably maybe that's why
maybe that's all there is
it's edgy
i can imagine
yakuza 8 is on the way wait is there a
release date
when is it
which one should i go for
i think i'll go for this one
it just showed screenshots
oh yeah i think that's all i i've seen
goosey on
a
it froze eggs
oh i can i can kill them before they ah
[Music]
before they grow out of it
ah that did that
hit or did it go for the smaller one
oh [\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
you're so cute
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i'm so busy with those
frogs
[Music]
are there actually fluffy frogs
is that a thing i can't imagine
there's no variation of a frog that
grows fur right
oh look at him
no i felt so sad
i feel like they could look funny
frogs are hairless oh man bald for life
oh don't cry
i'm just gonna destroy the skulls of
your babies you don't mind it right
because it's monster babies
cute
wait were there frogs as a choice
blueprint
follow a form
nuggets ah i kind of want to go for the
blueprint but maybe it's just decoration
again
it's probably just decoration right
they're off rock filaments but they're
locked initially
no okay
usually decoration then i'll go for the
gold again
yeah we don't need it we have other
decoration
if we really want to decorate
gonna make money first
next yeah wait one
oh wait that's it that was it
that's it that's it
i'm returning i can only go back there
when i uh clear the whole thing again
huh
yeah
honey
wait i'm confused
someone's sick
what oh yeah right they must have eaten
the
the pig stew
oops
let's help them
[Music]
vessel do you not worship me do you not
give offerings in hopes of gaining my
favor
when you return to your cult you shall
find a new offering chest there you can
provide offerings that i in my
generosity shall turn to called all
so that you might strengthen the cold
but i am not easily satisfied the same
gift offered too frequently will cause
the price to be lowered yet fear not
over time it will grow in value once
more
give me proper tribute and you shall be
rewarded
oh i thought i wouldn't get anything out
of it but getting gold out of it is
actually really good
sounds good good deal what a deal
[Music]
what was i gonna build oh yeah i was
gonna build um
new
new farms no no not those farms these
these ones the stone mine
and
oh [\h__\h] i can't build the other one well
at least we got some
some wood out of it out of wherever we
just went
um
[Music]
can we upgrade one of those
oh yeah
[Music]
nice
wait
let me go like this and then see who's
sick
faith is low again oh it's you oh no ah
don't run away from me what the [\h__\h] are
you gonna throw up somewhere is that why
you're running
oh
it's okay oh he looks so embarrassed are
you oh no you have to
bed rest bedrest go sleep my pretty baby
surprise
okay how's it going
still dissenting looks better though one
more re-education and then he's truly
fine
ah
he's being brainwashed ah check
did he just get
verified on green twitter
it's an eco twitter
stop dissenting finally broccoli finally
get out of here don't do that ever again
[Music]
maybe this one too
yeah okay okay wonderful
heart change on repeat always helps
garfield
you won't change your mind right
good good
oh god there's so much poop
okay they're
building go for price i wish i could
carry you to your bed
oh
at least you have someone to take care
of you oh
oy to take care of you while you're sick
i
i usually have no one
oh that's new i can build mushrooms
oh yeah ah
two gold coins for
on my way
10 for gold boys um that makes no sense
right
bless me bless the cold leader
[Music]
oh you have a question tomorrow i'm
thinking what's what i should maybe some
flowers
and uh oh the squid i don't need to
squirt that's quite a lot of money wow
follow on me maybe two i don't need that
what okay okay i get it
what's the question did you give up
didn't he have a quest for me
does he give up after a while
oh no
divine inspiration
i guess we should get a scarecrow
what does uh come after that harvest
totem
trap scarecrow devotion harvest toten
a refinery
where is that
this one oh okay maybe that's more
important right now okay
and then we get the scarecrow
wow
cool
look at it eventually
it's not such a high priority right
frog
the fluffy frog the flop frog
cat
let me look at the where is the frog
form
i know i can use it ah but there it is
ah that would be so cute actually
oh well
oh you can get you can get the form out
of anura
so
i'll get it eventually or do i have to
buy it
because i unlocked his form
so i think i'll i'll get him too at some
point
oh i will get it nice
make him fluffy
there you go
materialistic when building better
sleeping quality oh don't worry about it
i'm working on that
rocks basically tastes like chicken
oh
that's true i guess i mean nothing i
ever tried but
that's interesting
[Music]
because then
uh-huh
we can make everyone frogs and just act
as if they're chickens it's the closest
if the if the meat is really so similar
then it's the closest we can possibly
get
reptiles in
general oh
i've heard so i've heard
um
shall we do this one or
this one
necromantic weapons they're gonna have a
chance to summon dangerous ghosts from
dead enemies that attack nearby foes
they will appear in your crusades
we already have a bunch of cool weapons
though i don't know
[Music]
they're both gone what is this christmas
turner
i'll go for this one i guess
[Music]
oh
what's next should we invest more into
the top three or at least get one of the
little ones too
maybe law and order
afterlife or resurrection
[Music]
law order yeah i don't know at least one
should be good
punish sin or celebrate virtue murder
follower unlocks the murder follower
action a simple solution to many
problems but some followers may find
it's upsetting if they're awake to
witness
them in their sleep i see
a send follower ritual performer virtual
at your temple in which you can send a
follower's spirit to a higher plane of
existence
all followers gain loyalty
interesting
a sent their spirit to a higher plane
what does that mean oh that's is that a
nice way of saying killing them
i was like
what does that mean it's very very
cryptic
[Music]
murdered him in the temple so it's
another sacrificing ritual don't know
isn't that kind of the same thing again
[Music]
but in a nicer way
similar to sacrifice but nicer words
yeah then why should i get it maybe i
should just continue with the other
paths then
[Music]
ascend is happy
but then let's say i need to get rid of
someone why why would i
not go for sacrificing like
then i have two choices i can ascend or
sacrifice them where is the difference
loyalty the other one is faith
that was it right uh sacrificing gives
me faith
ascending is my loyalty
no no not talking about this one talking
about what we had before
ascent gives you loyalty oh
give us more bonus
hey can i i'm already locked in here i
want to check what the other one could
give me oh wow
okay
declare
one maybe in cooldown
true
okay
yeah
okay okay
whoa
there it is
back to work
i need to build
the bed i think
oh do i always have to build this first
i guess
i'll place it here
because i think yeah
10 out of 10 right okay
okay
i shall build helping
i should help building
oh you're getting better for fries i'm
gonna make you some chicken soup
i'm gonna make you some chicken soup
right now
[Music]
totally chicken soup
okay
let's make a feast
provided to you and sponsored by
hellofresh
healing bait to heal them oh there's
such a thing oh
like a hospital basically
oh
poop right next to the food i'm so sorry
ew i have to clean that up too
you you you can we bring food to my my
sweet surprise
is he getting food properly
someone taking care of him properly
please
oh can i build ah
yeah [\h__\h]
amount of money
i need more money i need to let's see if
i can get some money um
one of those one of those
[Music]
okay
no need for the squid at the moment okay
now we can build it
okay
yeah
go fishing for my money hell yeah
fishing
if you get those squids and all that
they're really valuable wow
[Music]
can't believe they aren't sponsoring me
yet yeah it's really weird why wouldn't
they work
why wouldn't they want to sponsor me huh
right i would want to sponsor myself
which i guess i do because i am
paying for my apartment and stuff i got
a poop
i saw that
i know i know it says the same gifts
will decrease in value but i think you
know i had quite a variety in it so
no problem you wait wait wait
uh
let me clean that up in a second don't
believe her
i was oh
not another one like you
a bowl of poop
okay
uh i can make one for you yeah yeah
oh [\h__\h]
here
ah now it's nighttime he's not gonna eat
it right away
oops good night everybody
while you're sleeping i'm gonna get some
berries
will they ever get over
that they're gonna get sick from it why
would you do that ew
did you get your valkyrie connected
no i didn't i asked about it and it just
takes so long man but
it's it's gonna come eventually
i'm hoping
soon
because i'm sick and tired of
pooping toilet what
scooping poop from the cat
why am i mixing up so many words today
but pooping and scooping sounds very
similar
speeda
you good
um yeah we'll get it eventually
i'm sure about it um last time i asked
like
maybe
um
a month ago or so they said they were
like you know working on it
processing it or whatever
but they also have to send it first to
um
to japan again to the
office and then they send it to me
because we don't want him to send it
directly to me for
privacy reasons you know
a bear has collapsed oh my god not again
okay is the right person going to eat
this i forgot who asked me who the [\h__\h]
are you right
oh no no believer was the one eat it
isn't it you
you have to force him
make demands
find a meal and eat okay it's out there
so uh do it
yeah austrian customs i hope they don't
charge me for receiving my gift because
the possibility is high when like a
a new looking
item comes from asia
like
especially what comes out of asia is
they like to
ah [\h__\h]
charge extra for that
oh
i'm just trying to get some wood to
repair it is i need one more
hey do you guys have some wood here
oh thank god
okay
is it time to go for another battle i
want to go
you honor me greatly that we're terrible
we're grateful
well that gave him a lot of
faith and also a loyalty also he didn't
get sick
not bad okay then but the thing is if he
doesn't get sick he probably didn't
learn his lesson
that's disgusting what is that
ah
holy [\h__\h] so much poop
any plans in the memory stream
i don't know either
playing um
uh what was it
[Music]
a cityscaping game
or
watch a [\h__\h] ton of animes together
first episode of 10 animes
i think i might do the anime one
city skyline yeah maybe i'll make a poll
which one
you guys wanted to do the anime one for
a while and
i figured
we can talk about
um the anime on stream if like you know
we'll have a new topic if i do that
yeah
oh you guys really want that one huh
i can't keep up with one more time
because we're gonna watch the first
episodes of ten animes to decide which
one
i will probably continue watching
which one speaks to me
you know
what if what if all of them speak to me
that now
i'll have a problem i'll be like [\h__\h]
there's so much to watch and so little
time
yeah
okay i'm gonna go
now i think they're fine
i'm gonna go fight
they have a different one now
is this like like an auction
when when you see a pretty follower that
you really want then you might want to
purchase him but they're going to be
expensive
but oh man
cute but
[Music]
if they speak to you just don't respond
aha
necromantic dagger there you go the
necromancy
when showing a foe chance to summon the
ghost that will attack nearby enemies
nice a helper
that's good
but not when i fight against like grass
right it has to be a foe
yeah
we can't see it now
okay
it's right here kiana makes me feel
things oh
cool
collab with cobble i don't know maybe
kobo play rust
she didn't start yet did she i don't
know i didn't hear anything about her
base being somewhere
wait
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
there's so many stones here oh my god
nice movie my beautiful summer child
wow
[Music]
we cuddle so much
you know these days um
she sleeps a lot like right next to me
on the height of my arms so we can
cuddle a lot without me changing
positions weirdly and then sleeping with
my head where my feet usually are
because remember i told you smoothie
always likes to sleep around my feet
she's changed her habits recently maybe
it's because i've been
um like on on on trips so much [\h__\h]
hell
oh thank god
maybe it's because i've been on trip so
much but um she's more clingy
it's so cute
fertilizer
she's over my feet yeah
now she wants something else
she doesn't like my feet anymore
with chunkers it's just more and more
tsundere it's interesting actually they
changed roles
this movie used to be the tsundere one
now chonkris is the tsundere one
overall weapon damage increased by 1.2
let's go
what
find more of his beloved manta science
mushrooms
he carries only for mushrooms he's
madness gross
oh
he's so cute
i want a voice act for this game like
for real and just be like
well that must be so fun to voice
actresses
when we arrived we realized we don't
know how to find mental side mushrooms
and now we are afraid to return
empty-handed
[Music]
if you were to bring him inside
mushrooms he would certainly reward you
you'll find him at the spoke window ah
mushrooms i think i do have a couple wow
that looks cool
oh
um
doesn't seem like i can hit them
oh god i'm sorry i'm sorry i didn't want
to oh they run away they don't attack me
back okay
sorry
i'm just trying to get some materials
here you know
romantic oh man
are we all but players in this game of
chance interesting
i'm gonna draw a card to the monster
you have something good in store today
how's the gator rates uh
death's door when hit down to half a
heart all enemies will be dealt two
damage oh i would hope i don't get that
though
go for the chest
yeah you missed a mushroom valley girl
i was kind of going for that
thanks do i really have to destroy all
this do these things these stones ever
drop anything
don don donkey let's reach old age no
i don't want to lose my oldest followers
so i've been for so
[Music]
can i much make them eternal
or like give them uh a drink to be
forever young
a drink of the youth a cocktail of youth
you know wouldn't that be nice
because
i i get emotionally attached to them you
know
yeah even if i make them immortal the
thing is they don't work right
oh [\h__\h] what's gonna happen
what is this
why is nothing
happening just scary music
do i have to stand in the middle
or get rid of all the
candles
[Music]
what
nothing's happening but i can't go to
the other room so i guess i have to
stand in the middle
i don't wanna
okay ah okay
hello we're gonna find a lot no you
wanna talk to me
five points to a pentagram 5 14 of doom
five siblings stood oppressed five gods
and one tomb
chabura
where he had failed before
[Music]
five becomes four becomes three becomes
two becomes one becomes nothing
shabu i
oh
[Music]
what will happen if i do any of these
options obviously i should refuse
but
um
yeah we bought no one except for myself
when i see myself in the mirror
right refuse obviously right
that was stupid that was so unnecessary
you guys really think
i'm gonna bow
but what what would have happened if i
did that though game over instant game
over money
cash money
what is that sign
what is that
i fight and i get two half hearts or
what hmm
bo is losing faith ah
and then no boss fight in the end or
what because how would that help me
they talk trashing and run away
deal and receive double damage
oh
and this one is
money but danger
besides that they're all just fighting
[Music]
which one should i go for
maybe just the money in danger one
money but enemies drop poison pool
okay i'll go for that one sounds
interesting
danger if i die then that will be a sad
day
okay history
oh my mushroom spores oh
i just had mushroom sport i have to grow
it
myself
okay good stuff
guys you want to talk about something
i'm gonna get something off of your mind
talk to your leader chihuahua
and i will enlighten you and help you
find the right choice for life
sit down and talk to me
talk to me anything you can talk to me
about anything
trust me
i've been thinking about how kiana is
cute recently that is very true
no problem with that
i need plexi minari plus cafe yeah
i saw the two today they put up like
some careful decorations
not the sole one different ones very
cute
how though you hit me
uh have you had any nutella recently no
i haven't in a while
i've been actually going to the bakery
like almost every morning recently
morning you know
noon
and i always get like a chocolate
croissant though
but they don't have
that much chocolate in it i sometimes
wish they put more in there
oh i'll go for the faint gauntlet i like
that one
yeah i recently enjoy fresh pastries
i don't know i feel that more than
making my own nutella something recently
i should start doing like making french
toast and pancakes and all that in the
morning and again i did that for a while
but then i kind of stopped
i should do it again
oh rainbow
oh
i've never had that before wait what
shiny and rainbow holy [\h__\h]
okay now that we have 75 percent lesbian
then we need to really
shoot
blast
anyway i started blasting
what
oh
i don't want to waste them on these tiny
boys though
thanks guys yeah i feel very sneezy
today very ticklish
she pushing my nose
nutella tastes like frosting to me
almost what
a stoneman it's cool
oh
no
thanks for the blueprint
the blueprints that i was looking at
with reyna at the fireplace were nicer
[Music]
i mean you can still go here if you want
to but you guys think i'm strong enough
for this danger zone i don't have much
health left
[Music]
hotel is a little expensive to consume
every day actually recently i've been
buying a knockoff of nutella that's a
bit more healthy because it doesn't use
that specific kind of oil i guess that
nutella uses that's that's uh i can i
don't know bad for the environment and
unhealthy or whatever i don't know
um
so it also it has better ingredients and
it tastes a little bit
tiny bit less sweet yeah the palm oil
something what was wrong with palm oil
i'm not sure
i just know it's uh bad but
yeah nutella has that
going in for it whatever
don't be scared chihuahua
i'm strong
especially with the rainbow parrot card
it's not environment running okay that
was it
dabble gold enemies drop poison okay
that's not so much of a problem
holy [\h__\h] i'm so
oh strong
does it taste as good as yeah it does my
friends actually um
told me about this one specifically and
we're like oh this one's really good you
should try this one blah
i mean
honestly
i feel like i've tried several nutella
knockoffs
in europe
pretty much all of them are good i would
say
i had one
in japan before a knockoff
like a chocolate spread but they are not
even trying to knock off nutella i think
they just made some some kind of
chocolate spread and i have to say that
one was not so good oh my god
did i hit anything
oh god kill frog fast
[Music]
i need hearts i only have heartbreak
left
oh god
the one from milka
i'm not sure if i liked that one oh look
at the hearts
oh blessed be the fruit
[Music]
i'll go for that one
thank you
tricky enemy hmm yeah the one with the
fireballs yeah
don't like that one no just one enemy
that's lucky
lucky because of my current state
i wonder how much gold we have earned so
far
um
what is this place
not just a normal map
easy
are there chocolate coverings for bread
where i live where do you live what do
you have
also should i go back
maybe the other one's a dead end
let me check
yeah that one was a dead end good that i
went back
there's always one path to follow and
the other one is usually a dead end
always good to go back
chocolate spread from bell gym wow
more hazelnuts
i don't i don't want it to taste too
much like hazelnuts
has to be a good balance you know
what is that oh point of corruption five
for none are undeserving of punishment
or of empirical nah like
eh no wait should i go for this one mine
is currently giving poison chance to
heal the wheeler using the
lighter voice of his life
i guess i'll give i'll take it
yo i'm so into this gauntlet
there's a hershey spread ew
ew
is that good you say it's too dry is it
good like any good though
oh it's vampire yeah true
all hershey's does is
kept on interrupting him trying to
attack
ah
[Music]
which is the way uh
that was that's good
oh ow ow
but wait good it hit my my deceased
heart
yeah yeah yeah if i passed didn't i
write about this on twitter like
somewhat recently that uh
american chocolate
uh
it's like they have something in there
that's like the same as in vomit or so
but americans grew up with that taste so
they got used to it so i was wasn't it
like a choice of like cost
made it cheaper that way
that's why american chocolate tastes so
different
yeah
oh nice hints
oh
that one's golden
got it
oh bump
whoa it's so that it doesn't melt as
easily oh
everyone else has to make their smell
like what
what
i don't like hershey's but acknowledge
that i am
which i'm pulling disgusting
the corner
no it's okay to like it like seriously
like you just if you used to that flavor
since uh like because you're forced to
eat it as a child
because you don't get any other good
chocolate you know that's
just you can't do anything about it and
that tastes good to you because that's
normal for you it's totally fine
nice it's really fun
just a matter of perspective mm-hmm
yeah yeah yeah i'm sure that unlike some
people don't like european chocolate but
that's just because of what they're used
to
and i don't really like japanese
chocolate but that's just because of
what i'm used to
or is it really like can you even
consider anything to taste objectively
bad
it's or is it it's just always yeah i
guess so if you [\h__\h] up like a
a meal because you don't put any flavor
in it like no pepper no salt and then
you i don't know put some
soy sauce into something where there
shouldn't be any soy sauce and then you
definitely can [\h__\h] up something that's
objectively bad
so streaming ah there's people who like
it for some whatever reason
ah isn't what i have right now better
than this
no that's five i have four but mine goes
in four directions
this is a blast maybe
maybe i'll go for this one it's easier
to hit everyone
maybe
bad milk
but that's that's that's actually like
something that went bad
that's not supposed to taste good
nobody chooses to drink bad milk
i can spam my attack so much
[\h__\h] i got hit by these little [\h__\h]
flies
i was doing so well
[Music]
way to go he glitched into the world
for real though what the [\h__\h] how dare
you go there that shouldn't be okay
oh that was dangerous
oh my god
yo tough
not the [\h__\h] fly
no do we have someone old no i don't
have anyone old
[Music]
that one had a lot of health
no my cards were so good but even if i
killed someone i'm just gonna revive
with like one heart or whatever
oh don't you don't don't oh yeah right
don't know done what's old oh that's
where is he
what
[Music]
their level
or age
determines how much i get back
i think i can finish the fight with
this amount of hearts
maybe i'll name someone after him
and then his name will be
donkey one more done
so the song will be
it doesn't even sound wrong it sounds
natural just add added one more done
i have another old person
oh yeah
for a prize
isn't he still sick i can't oh no
her price
oh
okay surprise
it's you
i'll miss you
i will miss you all
this makes me so sad okay fight fight
fight fight fourth justice
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
damn oh you look funny
it has like a little like a little bow
on its head it's cute
oh my god my heart
big gift
it's
it looks like it's just a stone
and pumpkins and lumber
what what is the big is it worth it i
feel like i'm being uh
scammed
if i take the gift
yeah we'll get a new one and call him
for a price too um a fair price of
double r
it could be anything
gifts give loyalty
i give that to my followers all
but in the end with
building loyalty is not worth it because
you i just
can't just grow old and eventually have
to kill him anyway
probably starving oh
i'll
go for the gift i guess it's interesting
i'll give to raise a loyalty of apollo
okay
yo i don't even notice when someone's
starving like that thanks for noticing
heretics defeated
wow we got 100 coins 100 gold coins one
and four
i'll sacrifice his wife i don't have no
regret
you say that but
non-believer actually did turn into a
non-believer
wait a second i have the perfect place
for you
non-believer
like they're all kind of unhappy right
now but he's the unhappiest
in prison
living up to his name
okay
um we can already
re-educate you
you shouldn't be marrying you're a pig
oh [\h__\h] maybe food first i don't know
how about this much is that good enough
for you guys
oh [\h__\h] oh i didn't [\h__\h] it up good
hi
hi oh no
you happy now
i would hope so
he's doing the i'm keeping him
he's we need we need to really
re-educate him because he doesn't seem
to know what um
are you good
what uh
what he should be saying who just
what's going on
don't
hey look at the poop throw up
chill i'm getting rid of it now
okay okay quick quick a sermon emergency
sermon
some
some quick brainwashing
dangerously low yeah
don't doubt it
ah it makes a lot of sense thank you so
much kiwawa
and uh
uh
oh
oh yeah i can buy a new
thingy
docio
maybe work in worship
does that help with the faith
[Music]
acid
all right it's also in parmesan cheese
oh interesting
afterlife why do you guys always want
that one possession possessions yeah we
haven't had one of those what is that
what do we have there
extort type steps
unlocks all the extort types follow
action and collect money from a follower
once a day from every follower once or
just one follower
brian follow unlocks the brightpearl
funnel action
bribe a follower with three times the
money to increase the loyalty
[Music]
is money the root of all evil is the
true evil withholding it from me
yeah it's taxation i would say extorting
me me
right works better than long run it does
increase the loyalty
wait what is bad about that nothing
i have a follower three times
oh wait no this makes me use money this
makes me get money
hmm
i prefer extortion okay i'll go with
that
they're buff
good i guess
they should be bribing me
for my love
okay uh can we do a ritual
cool down cool down
we could ascend one of my old ones
but it only gives me loyalty no no faith
but i guess better than nothing
should we do one
donkey
[Music]
oh
he doesn't look that old in that picture
he's all dry
thank you
okay wow yeah
type me i never heard of that word
before
wait he ain't old
it's in his 50s isn't that considered
old and it said he's older he walked
with a stick
it just didn't look old in the preview
oh my god
oh the music
oh
okay faith restored apparently
oh i woke them up in i sleep again oh
[\h__\h]
stop doing that
um
you will be
uh
since you're furry you will be for
prize too
so we will remember for price and then
the next one will be don don donkey
[Music]
once we um sacrifice that one the next
one will be done
[Music]
hmm
sad day
he's fifty percent faster on sick and in
bed rest ooh ignores the scent wrong
this this is a good one
this one is a good one
foreign
[Music]
wow
okay
what do we want and when do we want it
confession propaganda speakers
outhouse healing day janitor station
missionary
scarecrow fertilizer cello
outhouse
yeah they poop so much the more people i
get the more they poop
somewhere to relieve themselves sounds
good
foreign
oh yeah i want to but i'm hoping i can
defeat
that boss first
um
so make some progress
but i think should be fine
i was hoping to start reading at 10 p.m
so one more hour i'll give myself
yeah
any poop
they're all they're all cornered
they don't run anymore
weird ai
sounds doable
i think so too
let's work on this a little bit
need more berries oh my god they consume
so much food
broken house
you mean broken what sleeping place
in
a second farm
is there no way of getting them to
collect the berries themselves
maybe if i upgrade it or something
because if i make a second farm there's
a lot of work to
um
you know
not the mushrooms
farm all of that on my own
a harvesting totem oh okay we have to
work on that one then
next
should we go to that mushroom place i
wonder how many he wants
what is this one does that one come with
mushrooms too
no
did you visit the shed wait what shed
oh oopsie
that speeds up growth you need to
upgrade the farmhouse uh-huh okay
how do i get that upgrade
yo
somewhere
here here probably oh yeah
how do i get there
i need that blueprint
man
oh one's broken
let me uh build that one
okay
did it work
yeah
i need to unlock it probably divine
inspiration you need to proceed further
in this country okay okay
you guys continue building that
i make some food oh yeah bye my favorite
solo again what
it's a lot of work this game
damn
you're like always busy there's always
something to do
man
kind of challenging
oh wait another old one who are you
bro cooley is old now
we're cooling me we've been for a lot of
stuff yeah
anyway it's time to say goodbye
i want to automate it
can i do another sermon
maybe a ritual that
isn't on cooldown
such a savvy
[Music]
very very insightful today
10 out of 10.
oh we can do the bonfire
even old people too
everybody dance with me one two three
let's go
[Music]
let's dance another way
beautiful song i love it so much
quick clean before they throw up again
so sensitive these [\h__\h]
wait didn't i oh i didn't build it i
just uh got the recipe for it i didn't
build it oh my god i didn't build the
outhouse did i nanny
do you please ask me to build it
wouldn't that be nice
uh he wants more decorations okay i'll
try that too
first of all
no the poop house i need to
ah
[Music]
build this first yeah yeah to make the
wood into
i know i know okay okay okay that makes
sense oh
um billet here
um more advanced searches required
require consecrated resources
conservative resources are made up of
the base resources
unlock and build a refinery to be able
to consecrate resources screw up an
order at the refinery in the following
all that may come to conservation okay
cool
more jobs for people
and then we make the poop house with the
new resources
he's just standing there eating and
looking at us
how disrespectful
okay now you can work harder right
go go go go go go oh they're coming to
help now but then we're already done
unbelievable
okay we need definitely some of that
maybe some of that
yeah
go start
oh why does he
that's how you consecrate resources
is that really effective wow
he looks like he's some kind of bishop
or something
why don't you give up
continue please
where's he going ah he's gonna poop okay
okay
back to work
for the outhouse oh someone else is
doing it
can only one person do it
oh we need to re-educate
yes he's he should be done now
not a non-believer is turning into a
believer again oh
no
no he still doesn't believe me he's so
close though
little [\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h]
how dare you
what is there not to believe about
kiwawa maybe kfp needs to you know tweet
more about me
tweet more and i don't know how
maybe make some more youtube clips
all that kind of stuff i've been seeing
um a lot more like
uh korean kiwami clips recently too
there has been an increase again
wonderful wonderful wonderful thanks to
the korean trip yes yes spread the
kiwawa propaganda
we'll need them in all languages though
guys do you want to know a secret it's
totally not a secret i'm working on the
four blonde
uh sun cover on the side it will be
really softer than the original
but i got like um
an artist working on the art now
and
uh
we're gonna have like a
a cute
cute outfit for kiwa that fits the song
very cute 10 out of 10.
i know you guys really wanted me to make
a proper song cover of that
you already have the live version but
you guys really demanding it motivates
me so thank you very much
wait what am i building
i'll tell us i still don't have another
need five
thanks for the rest of the chat oh honey
you're fighting in the you're hiding in
the grass
where are you where are you
i can't find you
this is not twitch
unfortunately you can't participate
i unfortunately only have npcs ai is
working for me
let me let me put some more in here
okay
thanks for the red super tattoo
[Music]
this is you maybe that's you is that you
surprised why is no one working here oh
maybe no seats though
probably need some seeds no
can one of you um work on that
tent the farm that you
okay i think now we have enough
no one more
oh [\h__\h] you're so slow
name them after super trailers
yeah
i guess
so
but then you know it's kind of like
the ones who don't get chosen are sad
i've seen them
the youtuber
that i watch
he's done that with
some game
naming
npcs or whatever after
um
after his viewers and
it's kind of cool like his loyal viewers
but
even though you know he has a million
subscribers i would say he has like a
smaller amount of really like loyal
viewers and more like like
casual viewers so
for me you guys are so loyal to me so
it's kind of hard to uh
you know
i would like to do that but uh
yeah i want people to be
upset for not being chosen
sana did it in pokemon oh
[Music]
i wonder if there were upset people i
don't wanna
you know risk it
piccolo did a lottery oh
okay a lottery is one way to make it
kind of
fair i guess or like
randomize it
only choose cool names like ethan
i know some couple people that name
people in xcom they sign up for the
trump school what the [\h__\h] are you
talking about
you can make some sort of tournament
nah
people are gonna keep on dying in this
game right now anyway so i have to keep
on renaming the new ones after the ones
that died
we have an ounce house
finally finally finally let me
continue the queue
[Music]
let's um
let's see
i'm gonna do some
groundwork here so that when they wake
up then
continue working
i have nothing else to do right now so
oh
good morning why is that one eating a
[\h__\h] fish
go
eat it
what did i make it for
damn it i don't have so many good
ingredients right now
okay let's go to that one place uh oh
wait i have to build it oh there's not
much time is it is it the
white
no i still have much time right but i'm
guess i guess i'm gonna make some
decorations while i'm here still
i'm gonna continue with my flower path
it's not quite accurate because it's a
stupid building that's in the way but oh
well that's free
and now i think i i will check out where
that uh
mushroom
person is
spoiler grotto
itami
[Music]
cute music
i think i like it oh some decorations
for flooring here oh i like the one on
the very right it's cute that reminds me
of animal crossing custom patterns
seldom raise money for mushrooms more oh
i can paint mushrooms
this movie
no wait no mushrooms but you buy
mushrooms off of me for
gold
people
hey it's cards
blazing trail
weeping moon
30 more damage during the night oh
increase movement speed by one point
and
who is so talking to when he whispers in
the dark where is zozo is he up here
this is you
greetings traveler
me
i'm soju of course researcher of all
things
guess that makes me a fun guy
ah
just a little joke show some extra time
yes yes mushrooms mushrooms i still love
this passion but it's also needs more
souls don't always need more you won't
collect for social yes yes
sergio can't trust my followers out
there they lied they still they whisper
secrets about russell i just know it
so someone do anything i'll worship you
at your time so i'll devote myself to
your cause i rip off your head this look
oh
so i'll show you how to use your power
the mushrooms to open the front down
reminds us of your followers but you do
not need to use it on your horse or not
sort of follow unwilling willingly as
long as you keep bringing some of the
mushrooms are going away anything
take the bathroom and find soda
mushrooms you may not have seen them
before but now you seek them they shall
be there now
oh i already have mushrooms surprisingly
i knew it ahead of time
he reminds me of a mixture of watoto and
um
golem smirko
yeah cute
my precious
ass
excellent excellent but not enough but
you saw some warrants which i want to
show you how you can brainwash those
photos of yours she also supports us you
want something for your efforts of
course also always crazy steps thank you
ah those things again we can get a new
um quote at some point and then
hopefully this time one that actually
works better for me
oh
20 next time okay
we'll get some mushrooms here yeah
good mushrooms what is this again
i'll buy follow-up form is this a
mushroom form pick up
oh
i acquired a little mushroom
a blueprint
oh
okay
as a decoration
interesting
yeah okay that's
pretty much it here i guess
then i'll be going
have i been to the lonely shack before
ah no i don't think so
am i
you have discovered my humble contents
being careful you don't make the same
mistakes i did or you will end up in
your place just like this
oh were you once a leader
now perhaps a game of knuckle bones you
don't know it it's simple
step up to the table and now we'll show
you
uh defeat hot dog with knuckle loop is
that like uh arm wrestling
i'm
scared
i hope it's not too hard difficulty a
little
hopefully okay
oh i can't at some point i can choose
other people
a dice game of risk and reward how to
play your score is calculated by adding
all your dice together oh okay
match dice when dice of the same number
are placed in the same column multiply
their value
destroy a pole and destroy your
opponents dies by matching yours to
theirs
okay
so for now just throw the dice right
interesting hotel rose fest
free
so you're taking the free now oh i did
ah easy nice rng
[Music]
well it always um only have work like
destroying those if they're like right
um
at the top row so it can go up against
the other one on the other side so is it
good if i hide my four behind my free
i wonder
only works in the same column i get that
but uh it doesn't have to be in the very
front huh
okay um well i don't know where to put
it now i guess i'll put it here
oh we got a free
i got a six
and a five
i had a five
nice
so far i got good numbers oh he got a
six and he didn't place it oh why not
stupid ai
was that your stupid ai
so this was good right combining them
doubles it right
okay oh i'm winning this easily
eh he did it again he didn't put it
there to destroy me
what is
oh there we go another double oh
oh he got a double two but
getting rid of his one
i don't i wouldn't mind him
nice eh hey susan
and did you guys see my window hello
hello
eh
are you hearing me
the timing did you not see my win i got
triple um
triple doubles
the second time we didn't see oh man
what's wrong recently
but all back now
i think it was 67 against 59 or
something
finally one video you're natural here
you've earned yourself a prize i want to
play again this is so fun game does that
exist in reality
get an extra yeah
thank you
[Music]
i want to do it again
weigh into some coins
maximum bet 10 coins
i'm gonna bet
five coins
four
five
two
five oh double
already a double
oh no
he destroyed both of them when you have
a double oh
mama mia
ah he didn't place it as a devil though
interesting
oh god damn it
ah [\h__\h] i might lose this one
ah that doubles [\h__\h]
no
four
oh man
i want yeah thanks for destroying that
at least i have more space than for
something good
that's actually not necessarily bad
two
he doubled his ones oh i can destroy his
ones
it's it's pretty on par oi
it was pretty on par i can destroy his
double fives
oh
[Music]
a comeback
asserting dominance here
[Music]
six i can double my six
okay we're winning now oh oh thank god
he didn't place it in the right one oh
my god an upper double
but he had no other choice he couldn't
have even placed it anywhere else but i
can double my five okay we're still
winning
there we go i win and i didn't i still
had two spots left and i still win yeah
oh
i'm addicted i'm gonna do 10 now and i'm
probably gonna regret it
[Music]
crony
what
oh crony yeah kill him
from congratulations on one year
ah
one year huh
that's a long time yo
time goes by so fast though
i heard the council song
good song
congrats on running
you mean winning against him right
because he's obviously not winning he
never wins
oh
no you didn't
oh baby it's ripple if he destroys my
triple i'm going to destroy him
no
you little [\h__\h]
usually his ai is so stupid and now
now you do that
and immediately even
i'll get back at you for that
i'm gonna destroy everything you have
now
what happened suddenly now that i
weighed you more his ai is
more smart do i go for destroying his
double or do i make my own double i
think i'll destroy his
this little [\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h] we just keep on
destroying each other
crony you should play this is a good
game i mean this is just a mini game
inside the game but the game itself is
great oh [\h__\h] you
what is going on
let's play this game civil okay oh [\h__\h]
i won't be able to destroy his sixes
now i could
what is never ending
five
five the snare
triple okay that's something
he can't put anything there either so
mine's locked in
uh
it doesn't really
matter i guess
oh it's getting dangerous
where do i want to destroy it if i
if i destroy it there he still has a
chance to destroy my triple i'm gonna
destroy it here i think
oh
see he could have destroyed my my triple
i mean my double he could have destroyed
my double two there if i destroyed his
four first
three
i got smarter
i feel like it got smarter
[Music]
i want another one
i got five and i lost ten so
one more five okay i'll win it back
he i don't think he's improving because
his difficulty thingy still says the
same
i'm hooked
i won really
better get rid of that soon
what a waste
[Music]
i guess
ah
[\h__\h] no are you kidding me
i can lock it in now
but he might destroy it so i guess
whatever but then i mean what else would
i do
what else would i do
what is this
oh wait i can also choose to not accept
what is back what happens if i choose
back
i don't get to ray roll do i
okay you know that's fine that's okay i
didn't lose that much from that
in eu
he just wants me to get better stacks
you know
but he's filling up quickly
um
stop him from filling up
okay
destroy his five or double my five
[Music]
i think i'll double mine
don't destroy it please i swear to god
no oh thank god okay he didn't destroy
mine but he doubled his own
i'm so mad
this dude
no
[\h__\h]
i lost again what happens if i stay back
you guys know
do i just end the game and lose the
money
just try let's try oh exit no
are you sure oh
what
time stands still while you play so your
followers will not go hungry are you
sure you want to exit oh i thought
they're gonna lose respect again
no okay
wait but
it doesn't say anything about losing
money
but i probably will
man he makes me win at first to give me
hope
and then
then in the later games he's suddenly so
good
now he's cheating
oh [\h__\h] yeah
unbelievable
um you know you're alone here forever
and now you you lost the chance to have
a
body to play with forever
never gonna play with you again
because you only rip off people
your fault
you could have found a friend in me i'm
gonna steal your berries now
um
i must thank you by relieving me of my
duties you have granted me what i desire
most peace you mean duties as in picking
the berries oh
you're saying i did you a favor
i have taught you everything you need to
know i can pass my days playing knuckle
bones uh-huh
and friends have no way to join me are
you sure i think those are imaginary
friends no no you don't have any friends
[\h__\h] you
i don't believe that [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
what a little piece of [\h__\h] let me fish
a little bit
he does really have friends can you like
go back and see him like playing with
his friends
damn there's so many fish in the sea
oh god
oh easy
oh it stays on top all the time again
the crab yeah cute not what i need i
need a lobster
i wonder if the shadow always sets
what it is
[Music]
come on come on
yes what's that
ah squid but squid is worth a lot of
gold uh octopus i don't know octopus
probably two
what are you doing to my family i'm i'm
using them for a greater good
yeah another octopus
let's go a little bit take a small one
oh come on come
on unpredictable
quick fish
oh
squeeze
what about the [\h__\h] lobster
[Music]
lobster
oh man
it's okay i need fish
uh for food because the berries i don't
know apparently i don't produce enough
berries
oh my god
let's go
but the biggies
must be a big one
wait i got a small one huh
go outside for a while and you'll be
like a lobster you mean sunburn no i'm i
can i can i can put sunscreen on
properly now
i don't need i don't i don't turn into a
lobster anymore
i actually got a little bit of a tan
recently but only slightly like i'm
probably still considered pale
amen
[Music]
nice fishing
yellow kiwawa ooh gyaruki
oh
tuna
oh another day i i hope my followers
aren't too hungry i haven't checked
i haven't kept an eye or i hope they're
faithful too
crap
oh they look very faithful oh good oh
god a bed has collapsed however that's
okay
never managed to find the last kind of
fish oh really
you finished the game and you never
found the lobster or whatever you're
looking for
was it a lobster too
is it super rare on purpose
i wonder if it's determined already when
you
[\h__\h]
when you're
here and at this point or if it's
determined by how good you
[Music]
fish when you what wait what did i say
when when you do this
what
oh
oh come on
did they use a ritual
oh you like getting people to go fish
for you and bring you the lobster
oh i guess that's possible too
girls hmm i'll take that
kin moya
oh nice that one stayed up all the time
you're 12. mm-hmm
an ocean bounty ritual oh
interesting you can unlock it let's see
here find rare fishes okay maybe okay
let me just catch the last one
and then i won't do it again until
i either urgently need food or
or i have that ritual
ah
okay oh goodbyes again
[Music]
oh yeah don't you guys have like um
some
no thingies for me
oh no not that
no
i bought it
ah i thought there would be another oh
but it's a bunny that's cute
but i thought it would give me another
like okay
to confirm it
a [\h__\h]
i thought it was
no
lighthouse is in this repair
need to replace the crystals i reflect
light out to the sea what
i don't know do i have that i just want
to receive the tears
yeah the bunny is cute i guess
what does he need crystals where do i
put where did i bring them to though
if i had them
i don't have any okay
it must be quite high level
all right bye guys i'm going to the card
of the phoenix
hidden somewhere in the woods for no
particular reason
[Music]
oh it's broken again
that's fine
boy
is someone working here or what
hello
the fish is still left over
is that is that bugged because it's not
like they're not hungry
or maybe that's not gonna
maybe that item is bugged
i feel like it is
that's weird
i don't eat that one
[Music]
i stopped descending okay finally
maybe you can eat the fish
i don't know man
that's weird they're actually quite
hungry
but it's gone now
[Music]
any other quests guys
look oh broccoli is so old
i should give someone a gift
maybe
someone who was just level one
someone who's close to
[Music]
here fluff frog is close to level two
garfield is close
go back to work
although you want maybe maybe i want
them to be friends
[Music]
oh wait because you put tutti's level
two she's close to level three
let's interact
oh yeah i should get money too
uh give gift
here
what oh what's that a muffin with my hat
on it cute
and then maybe you
want to give you a gift too
one more
one muffin
the muffin man
and then i want money from you garfield
extort
okay look at my face it's doing so well
right now oh
one bed is broken let me repair
[Music]
and no one's attending the farm guys
is it all watered really
uh i'm also the only one who can add
fertilizer huh oh night time again
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] off
okay i'll get rid of the berries and
then i can plant new ones
no seeds oh
now we have seeds
not that one nope there we go
if you get fertilizer still your
followers can add fertilizer oh was that
already an option for me i'm not sure i
don't think so
i don't think so i think i saw that uh
uh as an unlockable
hi junkie
wow
what is the matter today hmm
my lovely baby
oh
stretch
good stretch
oh he's so soft
what a baby
[Music]
who's the baby oh [\h__\h] you're a baby
yeah get the spider chokers get the
spider what do what did i get you for
huh
what did i get a cat fun
fertilizing
[Music]
uh i just want to fertilize
water
now she already left
to cuddle companionship yeah that is
true too
oh we can get a new thingy
[Music]
she's lying down in front of my door oh
she's stretching again i think she just
woke up from a nap and now she's like
hello i dreamt about this and now i
dreamt about catching a lot of caspers
there were so many
out there there it is oh wait what did i
say i actually wanted to get
didn't i say
i want this one i can't get it yet
demonic summoning circle
oh my god
a scarecrow
really was that that urgent
really
okay
i don't think that's that that was the
one thing i wanted
[Music]
but okay
let me get some let me offer some stuff
octopus
now we have so many squids yo there's
worth so much money
another one
okay that's a lot of gold
okay now we can build a scarecrow oh
prince birds were stealing the seeds
from farm plots within range but i don't
have enough wood ah that one needs the
normal wood
oh okay
uh oh we also should build this one
a statue my followers can leave
offerings and you wanna didn't did i
never built this one before
i guess not
build it here
[Music]
recruit descending field i guess so why
not
i'll do anything you want it's like you
guys are controlling me
hmm
okay
there he is oh what are you
what is that
where did you come from uh you're now uh
don dun dun dun
donkey
wait i can't make it alone
[Music]
no i think i was it was it like this
before
don don donkey
how long was it last time dun dun dun
dunki it should have been this long but
i can't make it any longer this is the
maximum
ah
donkey okay
this is the best i can do right now
and
you shall be
surprised a pig
you'll be this color we don't have
anyone in that color thing terrified of
death oh
and the sloth
[Music]
get out of here
but you're descending so you know where
you go
first before you come here you must go
for a usual room face normally i don't
i don't like having people like you here
but let's see maybe you can
show me that you're worth it
yeah
re-educate
streams box
yes
i think that was very easy to understand
oh you're giving me something
[Music]
thank you
it's time for some food
and then i need to make a new
tasty bed meal
[Applause]
mixed follower meat i guess
some berry balls
and a meagre mixed meal let's go
cooking stream with kiwawa
today on the menu lasagna burger
okay
now we
make
the bit i got no [\h__\h] materials oh my
god
and i can't even build the the thing to
build the
what i can't even build the the thing to
get
uh i ate a meal made of watercolors
minus what i thought you guys liked it
can't even build the harvest farm of
wood
you
unfortunately cutie patootie needs some
bed rest and it's okay it will be you'll
be fine
steaks
where'd you get that from you've been
hiding that from me all along oh you
little [\h__\h]
i can't believe it
you had that
since when did you have steaks in your
pockets
and you went sharing with your leader
oh
i'll have a chit chat about that another
time you and me
all right
oh no i didn't want to water it i want
to add some
fertilizer fertilizer
good job good teamwork here
make more friends get more offerings i
should
do i have the materials for that i don't
think so
why
ah i don't have a refinery but wait what
does um this one
where did it go
ah here
it needs normal wood i really need wood
urgently what the [\h__\h] let's go out and
uh
gather some wood huh which ones do i
have
but first a sermon
[Music]
you like win a lot in this game you mean
me and you or everyone in you
oh
yeah
bite of the devout increase the starting
level of weapons when you begin
order the curses
where does this one lead christopher
tundra
there's a necromancer
ah just more and more curses i'll go for
this one first
should i sacrifice
yeah just really like watching you
she also hoped that you could say hi to
her well you didn't give me a name but
hi to your sister
thank you for watching me
yay
let's sacrifice the body shall we
do that yes we should
believe in the sacrifice
sacrifice the old ones no that is going
to almost
it's it's for good cause
perfect shot and berkuli broku is so old
57 years old man
you lived a beautiful life didn't you
with many drama moments
one time you doubted me but
in the end you came back to me
thank you for your services
and now you shall
see the greater god
the only one above me
[Applause]
[Music]
party party and cave beer
ah
beautiful
okay thanks guys for that that was a
good session
i'm gonna miss him bro cool he had such
a nice name
okay i think everything's ready for me
to go
yep
um bye bye bye bye guys
is there anywhere
like where i can really actively gather
wood
or do i just have to hope for more wood
when i go on a
on a adventure here
i'm guessing i have to go fight just
gonna hope
[Music]
oh crusade gonna remember philosophy
okay um
[Music]
vampiric sword chance to heal the
wielder
and point of corruption okay
we need
materials more materials
okay
how many more do i have left in that
in this door i wonder
what
hey i can destroy those things
i thought they were like
because i hit them so often i thought
you couldn't destroy them
oh oh you can
two
two lumbers well
okay
two rounds left
come on mama
well they take a lot of hits though all
right
at least a little bit
what the [\h__\h]
explosion frog what
froze bombs yo
they keep on
with the words
evolving evolving
they get even stronger every time i see
them
we need to stop them
turn them into pets quick cute little
pets and name them
him and tom
divine curse
or death store um wanna hit down
no i'll go for this one
thank you
i'm on a mission
oh my god
wait i need to get better at aiming that
[\h__\h] i don't like that weapon
oh
[Music]
i need to raise my chickens not only to
work at a fast food place but i also
need to raise you guys to become
part-time warriors like me that's an
aspect that i guess i completely ignored
until now
i only train you to work in the fast
food industry maybe i need to
train you in different ways too i mean
we do have an army but
it's not like i really
train you guys for it maybe i should do
you guys have potential
maybe the two-year chickens can be
trained
that's an idea maybe for um
the third-year member icon because now
we can do that too right
you guys are turning into two years soon
and i was looking for an idea anyway
and since at the second year you guys
get a lot stronger anyway
maybe it's time for me to arm you since
you proved your loyalty
so i don't have to be scared
about giving you a weapon in the first
place right
will you pledge your allegiance to me
one more time
and fight for me on the battlefield
[\h__\h] always missing here
maybe one of you can teach me how to
fight huh
yeah
of course you will you can trust us to
slay your enemies yeah
you get sorts of guns um i think
moon knuckles i think it would be a
sword because you know why i'm a sword
fighter and
we went to war
of swords
when we watched
the lord of the rings
ah
er just stones is all i get from here
eh
no wood
that's
really tough
um
i don't know how low i am on wood but
on stone
i guess i'll go that way then at least
something or i could hope that that
question mark is wood for some reason
um yeah chances chances are really low
though
and what is that again that shop with
the enemy is that a boss monster too
yeah
what is that
go i'd go for the question mark
gamble
gambling
that's the one with the big snail
ah really
yeah i'm gonna go for this one whatever
huh
so many bones
i need wood
i never thought i'd run out of wood
[Music]
it's so easy to get wood man
actually i've been um yesterday even
after laying the stream i locked into
rust once because i was uh oh my god i
was hoping
that
it was like it was a european pro
hi wait what
oh my god
wait a second
um
i don't know what voice i did for you
but uh let's go with this one it was
nice
[Music]
blood
wait it says they're starving but they
still have hops
uh
half hunger they're probably fine right
and i'm not gonna go
back now or should i
should
no
[Music]
oh my god
i don't think you can oh is it actually
not possible anyway i guess some
i didn't see i think it's like like an
ability that you can get to be able to
escape
midway through
so what was i saying i was um
hoping that if i log in during european
prime time that
uh there would be no people logged in
and i did see only like
two people were apparently
online and when i wrote something in the
chat
um
no one answered
but i think that did say it was two
people now why why i wanted to do that
was because i was hoping that maybe i
could get one of those crates without
trouble of a fight
oh
but there was no crate i was online for
like an hour hoping for it to appear
does it perhaps only appear when there's
a lot of people online
does it are the chances like lower or so
the
less people are online
what's with all the spiders i can't even
oh i have to kill them like this
it pissed every 15 minutes i swear it
didn't
unless someone literally stood there
like constantly
literally camping and took it within a
second
but i also heard no helicopter flying
around and that's the one that drops it
right
ah [\h__\h]
it's so hard to aim that what the hell
you have to press it like super long
you can see the crates on the map yeah i
kept on checking that like so often but
nothing ever showed up
i i looked everywhere
no plane flying around nothing dropping
for like a an hour
chipotle and iris were the ones were
online no one was streaming though i
checked
and then a little bit later when i left
there was only one person left online
but no one ever answered me in the chat
ah
let's go the vampiric gauntlet is back
[Music]
back in the game
but they if they always spawn in
different locations even though i always
saw them in the dip in the same location
um
there you go yeah
finally
then it's not really that possible to
camp for it right
yeah what the hell nothing spawned
i really wonder why
if you guys say it spawns every 15
minutes
then something should have
spawned while i was there
i should have
i should have seen the plane right on
the map too
but there was never anything
yeah i was guessing too gooda probably
plays a lot off screen
nose who knows who it was
yeah i was thinking so too like how
about i take advantage of my time zone
where nobody's online
to
um hawk some items for myself
it didn't work out man
yeah
wait was there another path over there
when i go up
yeah that was eh eh wait no wait ah
wait look at the map uh okay that room
is a dead end that i didn't check out
yet okay oh
[Music]
followers has reached old age okay um
i'll take this one no wait this is the
projectile again oh [\h__\h]
is it i don't know
what
a little bit of wood
it drops only once an hour
yeah what you did
i had to get them before the big fish
does
i would understand it's like it was
always in the same spot but like so far
i've i've always seen it in the same
spot
then i can understand like she would
maybe camp there
and wait for it but
you guys said it's uh
in different locations
and
i want some too i don't know what's
inside but
gold
stones
yeah oh wait they come with gold
oh
okay
[Music]
usually it's guns yeah
i wanted some weapons too
yeah only i i did however you will see
my last stream i did work a lot in my
crafting skill tree
and yeah i
built a few more things in my home even
after the latest stream when i was
waiting you know
waiting for something to spawn
you'll see
in my last stream
i guess i was kind of bored yesterday
which is why i appeared oh [\h__\h] no drunk
which is why i just
appeared on dinner stream and
she relaxed oh come on
i can't i'm so stupid
i hate those projectiles
i hate the bats
man whatever let's go
ah that's how you aim it
oh
now i get it
nikoi stop
okay
now i'm gonna get better at using that i
think
it's nice being with lena yeah cause she
appreciates having me around and i
appreciate her appreciating me
very much
i don't know i'm going here first
ah
[Music]
[\h__\h] no this is my my least favorite one
okay let's go back once
i need to go to the dead end first
before going too far
was that a dead end no it was not that
either huh
oh it it kind of slows down for a moment
that's good too but i missed anyway
close close close buddy yeah
yeah
oh what do we get
knocks back anyways okay i think i want
that thank you
so which one is a real dead end
huh
that path is different
so i'm guessing uh
this way
all right
that's the bus
where did my luck go no more shinies
what's up with that
an attack 10 percent chance okay for
this is for the boss right now so
what do you think guys
it's 10 p.m yeah bye i still need to do
one more
okay
they're both good choices
are we ready for the boss i only have
two hearts
[Applause]
[Music]
not going well not going well
oh [\h__\h]
okay hit the run always good
except when you run into where he goes
i figured out his pattern though like
the the abilities that he has
oh
[Music]
you know what's going on right now
gamescom in germany have you heard of
that convention i never went before
because i don't know i prefer like anime
conventions
except when it's tokyo game show
oh it's dangerous now they have high
fives
also gamescom
oh that's internationally very really
well known
but
oh
still have that
but i've heard a lot of
bad things about it
from influencers i guess
we'll go there and like have a pretty
bad time
oh
i'm here come here
oh thank god
if you're in gamescom always out of
control yeah i don't really hear good
things about it which doesn't
necessarily make me want to go there
anymore
like it doesn't help with my desire to
go
nice cluster very clutch yeah
everything's gamescom moved from left to
crown and has been less than cellar
oh
yeah but even though i only hear bad
things about it it's it's still
like very successful
um i saw that uh faye mata is there
right now i think i saw it on twitter if
i don't
interpret take it wrong
i think she's there
oh oh
pumpkin seeds pumpkin seeds
seven or nine
really what a choice
uh
go for the
gift
maybe i should have chosen the seeds ah
if you go for the cunning spoons not to
play games also bring a camping chair
yeah yeah yeah oops wait
yeah i don't know maybe one day i'll go
but this year i completely
i don't know i i didn't realize it was
like happening now and um
i i'd rather go to a convention that
i know is gonna be fun
[Music]
instead of there i don't know none of my
friends there
none of my friends go there either it's
just
yeah
not really the place to be okay they're
starving let's be fast
grass berries
pungent fish
i should have bought
seeds maybe
ah the choices
okay
at least i didn't chose the worst ones
like the poop one
well the poison is one
uh see they were they were
in dire need of food
i need to harvest the berries
oh and i need to build a scarecrow but i
didn't have meat so
i didn't have wood
i always thought that game cons are more
like to show new games rather than about
having well shouldn't that be fun too
what the [\h__\h] i don't remember what
exactly the complaints were
um i think it was just like influencers
having some problems with like
um
organizing
to meet their fans there so i don't know
what exactly the problem was
i heard a lot of bad things though
and then
what
oh sorry i just came back
oh these [\h__\h] it's like
kids and their mom
they don't understand how much
work a mother has to do
wait i mean i don't know you know oh my
god okay understandable when did that
happen
it's because so many throw up by seeing
one poop
and then they forgot by seeing the
thrown up stuff
okay okay i'm on it i'm on it i'm trying
to do all things at once
you're
welcome
bye-bye
send kiwi patootie to bed and rest kids
will try to recover from illness okay
where's cutie patootie also what the
[\h__\h] is with you
who is you garfield you have a problem
with how i do my work
don't believe her
uh
bedrest there we go
oh god garfield wasn't wasn't garfield
the one who
where we knew he was gonna be like this
anyway
not the non-believer
but yeah it was garfield wasn't it
he has a tendency to repeat history
we shouldn't sacrifice him i'll i'll
happily sacrifice him when the time
comes
what's the
view oh
why does he look like that
he's not sick
let's read his mind
exhausted i'm so tired i need to be sent
to bed why are you tired
okay
wait
i i i don't know can i
uh
sleep you should sleep yeah
go go go it's okay
i'll take care of the other things you
just sleep sleep sleep
what they brought me exactly what i
needed yeah or did they just you know
hit one of the trees and then put that
in there
nah they got it from somewhere else i
hope
okay now we can oh really okay okay
but now we can also build some things
that
i've been waiting for i think
um
re-educate
someone's sick
i see them i see them
it's cute
i already sent them to bed rest they
left though
it's in my in my list
it wasn't my list
hmm
why did they leave
oh oh that one's done
they laugh at them
oh he's so happy he's like hey
i'm ready to go thanks for picking me up
[Music]
okay okay
oh [\h__\h] so much to do
ah
wait um
number one
schedule is 10 25 wood
wait before we build that
build this i almost want to build a
second one to be
honest then we can't build the scarecrow
but we could build it soon
kiwama logic
this goes first
hope you agree with me
yeah go for it
[Music]
need a lot of lot of wood a lot of
lumber
lumberjacks chihuahua
and why is someone helping me all right
they're all working on one of the the
one over there
do they not like me
even then i'm faster than them
okay now work there please uh
oh they already go working okay they do
it on their own but if there's work they
do it on their own so i won't be
bothered with it
um
no one's standing here though i guess
there's no seats
there are seams
no they're wearing seats i put them in
now
oh sh
okay
i think
it's looking good now oh nonny
what makes you interrupt your work
what's so important it's getting too
relaxed around here we need to encourage
the others to develop spiritual strength
and learn to resist temptation let us be
tested with fast oh we can do that again
yeah let's stress on me
well
why not a good old fasting ritual
let's do that
[Music]
um
let's see
it does lower the faith though but
then we save some ingredients because uh
food ingredients have been kind of tough
too nice kimono thank you did you guys
see the members um for whole of summer
didn't only get swimsuits they also got
uh yukatas though those are yukatas
supposedly some are in the summer you
wear yucatan
but
those actually they have different
colors and so on and i saw some example
i was like testing them all right
like they can wear every color they
don't just have to wear one color that's
decided for them
so nice
and for the 3d models even
so they can wear both the swimsuit and
the yukata in 3d at home
so everybody has more variation for the
3d outfits now it's kind of cool
yeah
nihon mimbo
let's hope that
maybe next year we'll be blessed with
something like that too i know
yukata may not be necessary but
um
okay what's next
[Music]
a swimsuit would be nice right
um
i can't build [\h__\h] just decoration you
know what i'll put some decoration this
one's nice
oh it's so pink but [\h__\h] no space
[Music]
not where i want to build it
can i move some stuff
how do you move them
i have to do it from here
edit fillings there you go um whenever
we have it like right here we also need
to move this one
like here
and then
this one can be here than we need
all right
then done huh
did i
my line
if i go by that pattern it has to be
here but then it kind of intersects with
the path which is not what i originally
wanted but
if it's
if it should be um
mirrored perfectly then it kind of has
to be like this
let's do
this
yeah yeah and then here maybe it's
enough space to build uh maybe not
feel like kitty kitty it's not gonna be
enough space so
i'll put this here
that should be enough space down here
looking nice yeah
don't you want to join this cult
it's still not enough space
it has to be
if it's if it should be in the middle
then it kind of has to be here
so okay
not quite how i wanted it okay let's see
that was weird
it has to be like this
no intersecting let's see
how it looks after i placed it
here okay
i'll be billing that throughout the
night sorry for the hammering noises
ian and i do seem to be left out of the
summer fun entirely
well
you know our time will surely come one
day
yeah it's like
oh wait i forgot about you
cancel
everybody at once when it's so big i
guess when the company is so big
uh
who did we recently sacrificed that we
don't have a
a new
version for
we already have a
a fur price too
donkey
i'm missing someone else abraculi
berkuli junior
there we go
um
you're gonna be
green
and fluffy
broccoli junior you're cynical against
sacrifice and faithful okay
could be worse
oh
i will wait for their spotlight time i
always spotlight ten
i guess you would probably want to sleep
huh do i need a new bed for you now or
do we have an extra bed
oh yeah we have
why is that one
dark
but open
ah he goes to sleep in that one he
closed it and i guess that's that makes
him
makes that his own
garfield lives there wait where's
garfield
yeah
oh is garfield um
oh yeah okay that makes sense
uh
wait
you
amazing who was that fluff frog good job
oh we got a new thingy
i'm eternally grateful you're welcome
okay
why are you still sick
be less sick
or fish this time
[Music]
and i'll make a few
of those and i'll make these
okay
let's see it's time for sermon although
we have full faith let me wait a little
bit with that
cute music
you're working okay i think
we're ready to go for our last mission
because we have everything full
he might die though while i'm
gone
last blessing before you die probably
not worth it but
bye
oh i also should get money from some of
them i'll re-educate okay i'll
re-educate him
if that heals him then i'm gonna
uh
get money from him no he's still not
done huh
ah
yeah you're also old
so many oldies
wait i can't
i can't extort them or type them
extort type
what
[Music]
wait why am i making food while we're
fasting
somebody said in the chat i should make
food before i go so i was like yeah
you're right i forgot that we're fasting
it won't go bad will it
will it go bad
i just listened blindly
it won't it will
to test your face yeah if they'll go for
the food or not
confessions of what's your
[Music]
hello that's that's that's what i want
a true test
yeah having some really good looking
yummy food in front of you when you're
fasting is
pretty [\h__\h] mean
i might just eat it all on myself in
front of everybody
okay
fertilizer stila we'll add that here
silo it's probably silo huh
[Music]
okay i can go now right i'm gonna go
oh
will you will they stay alive until i'm
back
i want them to die while i'm gone
last one
ah i should put fertilizer in oh
i have to put it in
okay
like the seats uh oh they're still
building it yeah
[Music]
you want to help
oh okay
it might die
body pit just in case
okay
um put it where the prisons are
will they like put their body in there
on their own
okay i'm gone i'm gonna go
i don't need to do a sermon they're like
hundred percent faith right now
they believe
[Music]
maybe when i come back
a new run
or yeah
let's go
ah my favorite weapon
the game knows
it just knows
hello hey you again
let's talk again we just talked you
really like me don't you
one you said that monster we have foot
in chains will not be satisfied until we
have killed all four of us you may have
killed my brother but you will not kill
me and you will not get close to the
other bishops of our own fate
and more powerful than your brother
okay
why was there any need to like come back
to talk to me again did you forget
something important huh
[Music]
again
get out of here
even more frogs alien frogs it never
ends
maybe we really need to make a frog cult
to get the most out of it
why are they so
they're like a boss monster what the
[\h__\h]
how many times are you going to do that
[Music]
finally
yo
mini boss kind of maybe yeah cause then
the dudes talked to me so perhaps
non-believers
[Music]
is there no tarot card room
um
okay if it's just them then they're
manageable
okay
i'm really leading our retirement home
yeah new business i guess
ah [\h__\h] was the other one at that end
this one leads to two rooms
and this one must be a dead end yeah
okay good very fast we need to act fast
with these enemies
oh yesterday guys on my day off one
thing that i did besides playing a
little bit of rust
was watching a lot of tunic related
videos i i did
tweet about it
man
it's so deep and
i had a twitter conversation
somewhere talking about um
how i just prefer story-driven games
because
these kind of games
they just make you feel different it
makes you feel just so fuzzy and
uh it was worth playing that you know
you got something out of it you got
memories out of it
and then um
that chicken replied one thing they said
is
that tunic didn't really have much story
though and i'm i'm saying just because
they didn't have much dialogue
they did have a lot of dialogue but we
didn't understand it just because we
didn't understand it doesn't mean that
there wasn't a lot of dialogue and a lot
of story ah afterwards
if you're curious you can
literally translate everything
and you have suddenly so much so much
story yeah story is not uh equal with
dialogue i would say i first kind of i
guess i agreed with it i said you know
well still like
we're still kind of still story-driven
still adventurous and all that you know
what i mean those kind of games
but it does have enough story more than
enough even when even when you don't
know what they're talking about
like me in my first playthrough
i still felt like there was
a storyline a proper story
yeah um
i'll take this
so two nikki's good game
i did watch a few videos that also like
showed some translations of
what a certain npc said and some
theories on
um
on the story
and some characters and i watched
uh like
two
uh
uh two
two speed runs two different ones but
they were all about the same time
and holy [\h__\h] ah
the way they killed um
the scavenger was really funny
and apparently the developers know about
it and then the way they killed the
librarian too
unbelievably easy what the [\h__\h] is this
a snake
hello child i know you you're a friend
of rados
i recognize
that crown on your head hotel has
told me all about you
i'm on my way to visit him for a game of
knuckleheads
you're a friend of that [\h__\h]
i must slice you up into sushi
dance to play in depths again
i know about that place
why are you [\h__\h] that please
i can't hurt him
is he just reminding me ah because since
he's there he's gonna be there that
means he's a more difficult um choice
for opponent
[Music]
they do move pretty slowly i guess
yeah anyway with the librarian holy [\h__\h]
you guys remember the stage of the
librarian it's just one one round uh
platform on the big tower right
um
so what you can do is you climb up
but he doesn't react right away right
when you climb up so
you climb up a little bit you throw
him
um a
decoy
we use we never used that item but
what happens is a little you runs around
and
yeah so when you throw it immediately
you climb the ladder back down again
oh we have more wood even
and that
i don't know it's
some kind of glitch or bug happens
there's
they said something about
um
[Music]
i didn't know that term but apparently
it's some kind of
game developing term
uh
like some kind of kill wall or something
like that
wait where you
what was it i didn't quite understand it
so it's hard to
repeat it
um
but something happens when you
go back down
the
um the ladder like basically you throw
the the decoy to activate
him
but still have enough time to
go down i guess because i wonder if if
you activate the fight normally if you
would be able to actually um
to still go down i don't think so they
probably blocked the ladder no
so you do it in a timing that's very
important so that you still have time to
go down before
we before having the librarian come to
live basically but yeah throw the decoy
then go down and then when you walk down
the stair the the ladder climb down the
ladder
the librarian im immediately instantly
dies by some kind of mechanic there
that's the thing that the term that they
mentioned that i just don't
remember what it was but it's very
interesting that there is such thing
apparently every boss has that or every
every enemy maybe that's what yeah the
kill plane that plane i never heard of
that word before
is that a thing
a few names were that's what i mean
that's what i mean
that's what i meant yo i got so many
blue hearts
is that when you go out of bounds
but but it's it's isn't is that still
considered exploitation though or glitch
is it considered a glitch i guess not
because they implement it there's a word
for it
i need to do some research
but the fact that it's possible
that the enemy is automatically killed
if you leave the field even though that
should that itself shouldn't be possible
in the first place that you leave the
field
so i'm like really confused about it
interesting decoration
oh
that's the tree i was promised
[Laughter]
interesting
oh it even came with a deceased heart
it's an exploit of a glitch just because
you can have another minor devils
it's meant to keep you from breaking the
game
it was interesting seeing the developers
reacted so they were like
now if we fix it now you guys would be
mad huh i guess we won't do it then
librarian glitch is not intended
but then what is up
ow
ow what is the tail wall
not cable one more thing i already
forgot the term
the reason of his existence is for the
game to not waste resources on enemies
that are out of place for the view
but why not like i don't know make them
go to sleep or whatever
and then you well like
it shouldn't be possible to climb down
in the first place that's the weird
thing
but that's not quite a glitch it's just
because they threw the decoy in the
right timing could you call that a
glitch very interesting though very
funny
to watch them
i'm like ah
i should have done that but if i would
have done that it wouldn't have been a
normal playthrough and it didn't
particularly
um oh
i just got a new weapon
i didn't particularly suffer with the
librarian but with the scavenger i did
and holy [\h__\h] that was so cheesy what
they did there
you guys need to watch the speed run
it's like 24 minutes
really interesting
yeah i wonder how hard it is to nail it
because they obviously make it look so
simple it doesn't look like you need as
much skill as for example like for a
super mario 64 speed run like those
jumps look insanely
difficult
but yeah
um
you know what i just got a new sword how
about the new magic weapon then
uh
that has collapsed
great causes an unintended behavior
basically doing something definitely
dead not consider it happening but they
did say about these things that like i
think everything they saw
they kind of knew that that was possible
like they weren't even surprised
they were like oh yeah i think i saw
that coming
hmm
they kept it but they also said
something like they they keep some
things for the sake of speed running
so
i guess they're not mad
[Music]
okay
oh that was fast oh my god boss time
yeah bye
[Music]
but the last glassware was not that
difficult but i was happy to see a
second face in the last bus
second phase
can keep a game the player's eyes much
longer yeah
it gives people a reason to play it over
and over and over and over and over and
over and over and over again and then
give the community something to talk
about and all that so yeah i can see why
you would support that as a developer
[Music]
it's my stone heart
oh did that just hurt an enemy
[\h__\h] hell that was a waste
oh blueprint
a fountain
that looks cool
it's a decoration item but i like it
more than that that it was used before
so they don't want to fix it and
sometimes it also just costs more time
to pick something then just leave it in
i want to try speed running it but it
would take up a lot of my time
i mean as i said i don't think it's as
difficult as speedrunning uh super mario
64 for example
but
it's still
something that takes a lot of practice
i wonder i could at least attempt it and
see how difficult it actually is the
decoy thing is definitely easy
and honestly the scavenger explorer
seems super easy too
the one difficult thing i can see is um
they didn't really exploit the
last bus
they just um
kind of just you know kept on stunning
her like stan locking her
so they kind of did a proper battle but
they used that combination that we
learned about that i just couldn't get
right
so i would have to practice that a
million times
there's no
proper
[\h__\h]
exploit
for the last boss fight
which i would have liked to see one man
we'd run a stream didn't have one
usually done practicing single exploit
for hours yeah yeah yeah
i never did something like that before
and i was never interested in doing it
before but this one seems rather
manageable
i don't have to do it in 22 minutes and
i can do it in like 40 50 one hour even
then it's a speed run
yeah yeah i was told that
terrified of death right no
has died oh i should have sacrificed
keep on doing this against your friend
we'll
[Music]
someone died someone's leaving
they're all going crazy
just having a nice chit chat there and
then you just slap me into my face man
with disrespect
i miss the room by the way i know
i found them good food cutie patootie
was the one who was sick the whole time
i don't know what made them like that
because like i
i
left when it was 100 faith
unless it was bugged out or something
and it wasn't actually 100 faith could
could be i don't know it could be a
glitch
because i thought it was weird too that
everyone was so happy
i'm almost out of the crusade chill
maybe i can make it before they leave
uh
wow what is
that let's try it
uh how fast does time pass
[Music]
[\h__\h]
i'm leaving i don't need all of this
stuff here i need to be fast
um
don't leave me
so [\h__\h] disappointing oh here we are
ah
ready to rumble
[Music]
i hope it goes well
i'm scared
oh god i'm scared but i have i mean
compared to under other fights quite a
lot of health
i wish i could save
but worst case i'll just die once and
sacrifice cutie patootie that [\h__\h]
dissenter before they leave sacrifice
them before they leave genius
finally i've been looking forward to
this
oh
we'll see we'll see
oh [\h__\h]
oh yeah they did that last time too
turn into frog of
course just gonna spam these
yo it's huge
oh my god okay there's he's um bringing
endless amounts of oh my god
enemies
and hundreds
hundreds of them
is he not going to come back before i
kill them i hope so because
oh
oh my god
ah this band is bad
is he ever gonna fight on his own
or is he gonna leave everything to these
[\h__\h]
oh wait am i doing damage to him
because he's past half
oh does this count as him
wait
no oh [\h__\h]
this
i know i have to kill the big ones uh
okay okay
it's really tough
no
oh there's so much going on it's hard to
see myself sometimes even
no
does time go by while i'm in the boss
fight i wonder oh he's back okay
when he's already here wow
thank god
already pretty low on elf but oh my god
can you [\h__\h] stop man
itself is like
not going down at
[Music]
good dodges
myself get hit by that
oh he's almost done he's almost done
oh
that's so disgusting
he's like hoarding oh my god he's
hoarding them in his
mouth
okay one more hit also one or two
oh that was gonna be dangerous i knew i
could get hit there
wait
did
oh my god i thought i couldn't pick it
up i thought i softlocked myself
i think i didn't need glitches but i was
still able to pick it up thank god oh my
god
i played flawlessly at the end yeah i
have to be careful man
once i figured he was a tuffy
[Music]
yay
thank you
speedrun glitch what
ah a coffee bottle
[Music]
coffee butter form
okay let's see if we can save to the
center
we still need to collect the reward from
cutie but do this
i still have a quest and i need to get
back what the [\h__\h]
oh you're fast we have to be fast
yeah but
bye
ina was looking for oh are they random
did she kill this boss already
[Music]
i enjoyed watching you destroy hecate
her arrogance was always out to have was
always destined to be her undoing
heart
and the gods are pleased
um
team we need to find them immediately oh
and the shepherd shall make our way into
the wilderness rivers in the desert and
light in the dark
oh my god
wait so how do i quickly fix this
you should be happy about this
he just left
should i send pewdiepie to the prison or
like giving a present or something where
is he
this one
first of all the quest might help
yeah yeah yeah cause that raises loyalty
and faith
maybe that helps maybe that alone helps
um
if we imprison him can he still leave no
right that would be weird
oh it's in prison though
yeah you're not leaving
believe me it's better this way
okay oh faith isn't even that bad
we'll end it soon and read super chat
it's been longer than i thought it was
gonna be
um but we'll read super just
coffee they stop descending oh my god oh
they did go bad
ah such a waste
and now they stopped fasting
is this
jefferson has died of old me me age h
prepare for i'm gonna bury him
[Music]
corpus are not good for sanitation
likely to cause other failures to get
sick you need to bury your where you're
following the body by the way to prevent
it from getting rotten of course
that is a lot of meat that just goes
away uh
no i will bury him
no
his body is so heavy
oh man
i
forgot why we called him perfect shot
though
hold it how do i there we go
what was the reason behind that pun
oh
one nice grave for him um broccoli
junior bed rest
we should sacrifice your baby before
that same fate comes upon him
[Music]
ah
i killed him with the perfect shot ah
[Music]
makes sense
i thought it was something like that
okay
[Music]
food
i should release garfield oh
oh yeah okay one second
lots of wood now yeah
we should build some useful stuff like
the scarecrow
finally
yeah yeah
um
[Music]
what happened here
just gonna do some
last minute fixing
some
maintenance
yeah very very rare occasion to die from
old age congratulations
i guess
i look so happy
release
goggle work for me again
are you sad about the grave oh no
[Music]
am i innocent i said imprisoned
why are you sure shane
doesn't give me a reason
okay be nice now okay
[Music]
where's that sign there
no oh oh i thought it was above the
above uh yabby
to tell me like he's unable to fight or
something because garfield is sitting
from
garfield
he just left prison
wait a minute justice please let him
prison them
[Music]
that's a really weird coincidence rng
what are you doing he just came out of
it oh
is he gonna be
mad
oh i'm sorry garfield wait what
i was just gonna sacrifice you
oh don't be sad
i was too late i thought somebody just
killed garfield for being a
a sicko wait i have no
grave
there's so much to do in this game
hopefully we'll not have too many graves
in the future
don't don't look at the dead body
oh you have to build it okay please be
fast
time has come rest in peace yeah
roasting peace oh not garfield who was
this
was happy
don't be sad
here i'll give you something can i give
you a gift i think i sell or extort i
need to extort thank you
[Music]
hmm
uh
what else was i gonna do uh
maybe we can do some of this
and
uh
wait brain slow
let's do a uh um speech speech speech
speech
the last speech of the day
ah yeah carpet coffee coffee need to
improve some garfield what the [\h__\h]
it's like you know we we have something
like this at kfp
get out of the usual room we immediately
go back into the usual room there are
certain chickens who know the feeling
who just never get out of the usual room
for some reason
running low on followers yeah you're bi
actually a boy
um
didn't think it would come to this my
timing was
bad with them dying their timing was bad
eh
appreciate the value
how about this one again
ah
gain 25 if i do a funeral
did you perform rich oh
i want to resurrect but it's not like
they all get younger right you guys said
they'll stay old so
they won't be alive for long
[Music]
ah
is it okay though if i already
uh
buried them
[Music]
you don't get young
i do like some people right now so
oh
let's do it let's do it
happy
ritual of resurrection
oh that's how you use the bones 150
bones of 22 221 okay we have enough oh
so many already died
39 49 okay
this let's get one
let's get patty she's level three that
will help right the most loyal one
and the most old one paddy come back
i'll revive them all eventually nobody
will be dead in my cult the cult of the
phoenix
death is not an option in the end just
temporarily
oh yeah you know how it is
okay now
so we got resurrection before we can buy
another one there's the hunger once a
day eat a meal me to receive a oh blue
heart oh
but that's just one
focus whilst on the crusade one to
instantly return to the base ah
there's no release yeah but you don't
want the release
i receive this seized heart at the
beginning of each crusade okay you guys
said teleport is um
good and i agree i guess because like
you know when people are about to die or
dissenting i'm about to leave and all
that yeah let's do that
i will probably have to restart from the
beginning whenever i leave a crusade
though right
we start from the beginning of the
crusade when i go back
focus well last on a crusade run to
instantly return to the base what what
did i mean with focus i'm not sure which
button that would be but okay
okay
uh we already revived patty right
nice oh i'm so happy
ah
that makes me happy too cause i can
attach to these little piggies
oh
daddy daddy
teddy
honey don't you want to thank me for
reviving you and making you young again
what are your thoughts
ah she doesn't even
maybe she doesn't even remember also it
says age 66 but she looks young and
walks like a youngling so
interesting
huh
it's like she forgot about me and
doesn't realize what just happened
oh she just got uh
got her bed back
huh
interesting
interesting oh it's nighttime okay uh
good night everybody let me see if i can
build something before i go go something
build something build something
um
a scarecrow
what is huge
[Music]
uh
huh
are there places to make the most out of
it
i mean i can still move this thing maybe
i'll move it a little bit downwards
um
can i move all of this
no can i move like
can i move all of this at once somehow
uh
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
oh
i'm just crying above the farm
no
just move one farm plot
oh [\h__\h] what
ah
[Music]
what
i want me to
okay i think i understand what you want
me to do
like move it here so i can put the
scarecrow here
uh-huh
that works
i'll build that
would be nice though if you could like
move the whole thing because if i really
wanted to for other reasons move this
whole thing that would be really
annoying wouldn't it be
oh it's taking ages
holy [\h__\h]
chat in members mode
okay just put it in subscribe mode if
it's about the bots but
now i i can't right now my my fingers
are busy
[Music]
isn't that lovely
okay
what else
nothing
we can make another offering statue
i'll also build this here
what's a nice space for it maybe
maybe here where they sleep so they can
hear nice
asmr water sounds
when they sleep
and
i don't know maybe a little
lampreys when i don't get scared
oh i'm such a nice leader oh my god and
then i'll make
ah i can flip them
oh beautiful beautiful beautiful
i
like oh oh amazing
oh gorgeous
they don't get light the prisoners don't
get light but the outhouse gets light
you're gonna sleep like babies now yeah
they don't have to be scared about the
speeders because now at least they can
see them or is that worse
[Music]
and
here
that's good they have a lot of stuff to
build now
yeah
i want to play longer
it's okay i'll read super chats no
matter what um
[Music]
just kind of want to see how it looks
after they're done
i'll make some food
oh ingredients are amen but okay
[Music]
instantly okay
cooking cooking
[Music]
oh oh there we go
need more farms
should i make another farm
not not like i have that many uh seeds
though
but okay i can go another one
maybe try to stay within the scarecrow
area first or like
here yeah okay that
at least like
then two people can work at once
oh i have so much gold right now oh
okay
okay this is enough for now
work hard carefully i'll fix your beds
in exchange
if you're traded at the porch that sells
seats oh
oh [\h__\h] yeah that's the instant poop
i'm taking care of all of it
okay
quite happy with
that never poop okay wait they don't
even use the outhouse is it because they
instantly poop said they can't even make
it to the outhouse
i need more
followers we need to revive more of them
okay
how does that feel better yet no
god damn it
we built that
i'm gonna have to yeah i know that no
that was just
eh
are they really out of reach i don't
think so
otherwise i'll just move them
buy a follower from the spider i i
thought it was so expensive like why
would i do that now but no it actually
makes sense
oh i just get more to the next crusade i
will just choose the path where i get an
extra follower
i promise you oh yeah garfield's [\h__\h]
hell uh
garfield
oh collect loyalty reward i will
garfield where are you
patty did the donkey
uh
garfield is he hiding from me
donkey garfield this is garfield this
guy feels wait let's wait until he's
done building
i'll help you
prison number two oh yeah right true
i forgot
because last time it was so funny when
we did it the other way
i'm sorry but um
first i take
this money from you
and then we imprison you go go go go
someone said you stole something and to
be honest your track record so far isn't
very good
yeah
sorry
kind of have to believe
what the the donkey said
in that case this
track record doesn't speak good for you
is that him
no
don't believe her
i know that is him
so is the orange one no don't say that
what does that mean i'm orange jewel
oh i can release him now oh yeah right i
guess so
i'm sorry
uh
woman i'll give you a present
if i have one i have a necklace i think
uh
well don't do anything bad anymore okay
i believe this in this case it was the
rng not doing you very well uh increase
your loyalty
here how about that
making sure that you're being a good boy
[Music]
okay
we have a few more gifts we might want
to use that
[Music]
who wants to never give to you for price
level two
uh
i will give you
the feather necklace to walk faster
work harder go go go
[Music]
let's see
ah
flat frog no don't believe us sorry you
you you'll get it
[Music]
his boss is so kind now he works 24 7. i
know i'm so kind
what a leader how could you ever ask for
any anything better
okay we're done for today
um was there like you have to save in
this game
oh yeah
save
main menu
x it's saved right
yeah wow we're so busy this game gets
busier and busier wow wow wow
yeah thanks guys for watching i'm gonna
read super chats now i might have to
catch some more water
no i'll
i'll get some more water
but yeah i hope you had fun so far
if you're in for that you're welcome to
stay i'll try to get some super chats
out of the way and then i think tomorrow
is memphis only
um
ah after the stream or actually maybe
right now
i'm gonna make a members only post right
now
um
so we can get some recommendations in
time
and
channel members here's um
uh
[Music]
four
members only stream
this week
i
want to watch
10 different animes
let's say from the past
uh
two years or three years actually you
know i haven't watched animes for so
long we can make it pretty big let's say
past three years
um
i wonder what uh
the
the first
episode
uh off
ten of the ten different animes from the
past three years that
you
recommend freeze to low five yes okay
to me
and
haven't
watched
in over five years so anything that
released during that time
should be good
uh
hint
genres
i like
are
comedy
[Music]
adventurous fantasy stuff
i don't want any romance romance i think
[Music]
yeah maybe that's it for now
i don't think i wanted to see any harems
oh i'm
blah
comedy and adventures
and
give me the name of the anime and a
quick um
description
let's write it in the hong kong
uh
jewel
[Music]
um
i wish you guys could add a picture with
a picture
it would help me choosing them
but
i don't think you guys can do that when
you comment on youtube posts so i guess
i guess not
and okay
yeah
i
i guess i could do it on twitter
[Music]
but then
i don't know
should i do it on twitter
does this whole thing even fit into one
tweet
what i just wrote no it doesn't fit at
all
unless i get rid of the
japanese text and even more there's no
space
ah
i'll just do the members thingy yeah
okay done
i have to decide quick so you guys
better be quick too
and if it's something that's available
on netflix uh or germany even better
yeah
ah screenshot upload to twitter oh
indeed
i guess so
should i
but then i have to look in to go for
like the so many actually no it's better
this way because then i don't get a
million suggestions if i do it on
twitter i feel like i'll get a million
suggestions and it will also be buried
on the under under other replies and
blah so much to go through i'll just do
it in members yeah yeah yeah it's less
less [\h__\h] to go through
yeah there's actually no there's a lot
of anime on netflix surprisingly um
[Music]
maybe i'll have to get uh crunchyroll
subscription or something though oh
wait they should give me one for free
they should they
[Music]
wait should is the website where you can
watch a lot of anime right and i never
really used it like that i never used it
at all
let me
ask you
[Music]
emma
um
[Music]
no it's not being used as a notepad
she's being used as a messenger maybe
maybe we can get a subscription in time
would actually
you know make sense because we worked
so closely
no
sony bought funimation and crunchyroll
and merged them uh-huh but i mean
there's still people behind crunchyroll
and maybe
maybe they want to donate the
subscription to the wawa
can't wait for a lot of the rings what
why not the rings we're talking about
wanting anime
would be nice to get something but genma
is not online right now hopefully
i can get something
[Music]
um
okay
uh
you know what i'm too lazy to get up
let's start reading first
i don't want to get up and get water
i'll still have a little bit
one glass of water
left
the hobbit is better wow that's an
unpopular opinion honestly i like both
very much but
everybody prefers
a lot of the rings yo
hi smooverella
she knows it's time to end my stream
soon let's move
[Music]
hello
music double huh
not anymore
candy to the rescue
it's already been [\h__\h]
six i played for like six hours what the
[\h__\h] how
how
what
last stream though tunic was so [\h__\h]
long
so unexpected i didn't think i did i had
that much left but i did go for like the
true ending so
that took me
what three hours
through ending
and even that with a lot of help
[Music]
oh my god okay
yeah i haven't had such a long stream in
a while
it just happened
i had
push i had to do it i just had to
i couldn't just leave it there and do
the final
finale part free for real for real for
real
finale for real this time for real for
real thank for real songs
especially not when there's not that
much left like i but i never was sure
like how much there was left it's like
hard to tell
i thought it wasn't much but it was more
than
i thought okay
do you guys know where i left off
reading super tattoos
[Music]
start from the video premiere
video premiere
you little [\h__\h]
ah
am i done with the super chats from both
souls soul streams
oh that's wonderful okay
nice
that's okay
you guys are hearing the music
these ones
what a banger
this song is such a banger
okay
[Music]
to this song
i don't think so
thank you mccree thank you and santa
[Music]
uh you know for this one
it's really
yeah
i can't even complain about this one
being demonetized at least i was able to
receive super chats
for the
finally has written a song about the
usual chickens oh interesting way of
saying
of of
talking about them i assume this means
we can leave the usual room now stream
your little [\h__\h] no you cannot
no that means nothing
instead we just um now stream this song
endlessly on eternal loop
in the usual room it's more fitting than
the hard challenger and stuff like that
because this song tells you what you are
[Music]
pink
all right if you're willing to commit to
this really amazing joke song then you
need to do an official and full version
of the iconic girls girls girls sometime
no more dodging on making it's a joke
seriously commit to the bit by european
queen
no
your little [\h__\h] was actually
100 thanks to
cow carrot i didn't lift a finger i
wasn't even my idea was all cow
carriages you know
wanting to help out my channel with a
video
and i was like this is amazing
i'll gladly take it
yeah
i didn't ask for this
yeah yeah yeah well if if
he ever feels like making a girls girls
girls video
i don't know if we can with what we have
that's that's not much material to work
with i think
[Music]
i will make this my new lava bar
and no it should be it should be your
wake up alarm
i think it fits more like the the vibe
of it the
tempo and all that
because it's more up tempo and happy
if you wake up to this i think you'll be
ready to
have a wonderful successful day
thank you so much
glad you're enjoying it really
it fits you very well
[Music]
like the faust elves alga as we like to
say in german
the fist onto the eye
is like
actually a funny way of saying it like
it fits like a
glove um there's a
saying similar to that
we like to say
the fist to the eye that's how well it
fits
it is kind of i never thought about it
that way
until i translated it just now
yeah you're like
to the eye
and it's pretty violent pretty
aggressive way of saying something fits
damn
does it fit yes as well as my eye my eye
into your hands my face into your eye
it's kind of a threat
union blunder
[Music]
medicine
hmm
okay that's that
next we have uh kirby's dream buffet
[Music]
so cute
i kind of wished like i think the game
is fun and all but really doesn't have
that much content to make it
uh reasonable to play it again anytime
soon
[Music]
it's just the same but
i don't know maybe in a few months so i
can play it again
a bit more variety would be nice like in
games like they have different skins
basically for the same
game areas
game locations
but it's still just like the same thing
like you have a race and then you have
these
i don't know
battle royales and all that
a bit more variety would be good
otherwise you get pretty
sick of it early on i would say
anyway
[Music]
for my adorable pink sun kirby fat
finally showing up on taco night
oh
you're a fan of kirby huh
i didn't know that huh
kirby is very [\h__\h] cute well i i
agree with it
good to know you're his uh
father mother actually don't know
yeah
who knows if we'll see kirby again
anytime soon i'll do my best to include
kirby on my channel a bit more often
thank you
very much hope you enjoyed it
i know thank you for the rest of the
chat welcome back to
i really miss you so much this game
looks super cute but still not as good
as you are kiwami is the absolute cutest
ever
thank you
i mean
i screamed
three times
didn't i stream three times one members
only
and two public ones
while i was there
and released a video so i would say
that was a good amount of content while
i was gone and like actual streams not
just like one minute videos oh yeah
two [\h__\h] posts
and three streams
yo
i was going for six days
approximately
that's actually quite a lot but unknown
you still couldn't help it and missed me
huh
cute
loyal chimpkin i shall give you
one of those gifts
a feather necklace or or the moon
necklace
you're probably already wearing that
moon necklace because i know you'll be
watching me any time of the day
thank you so much
[Music]
what
i'll give the first person who uncertain
membership that doesn't even work i
think petsy duncan
about the end
no you can't recommend that one
oh
the tanker wants to recommend the tank
anime
i'm glad you're watching though hello
have you really been listening so much
to it wow thank you
can you stand
in choice
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
thanks for watching
always always tuning in
[Music]
even though i think this was probably
pretty late for or like early early in
the morning for you early very early in
the morning thanks for watching
nonetheless thanks for making time for
kiwanwa
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
oh
i want to say you were such a big help
when i was in a very low point about a
year ago when i got denied from all
schools
this year i got accepted and i'm
starting my phd next week
whoa thank you so much for holding on
well i don't know what you did in that
one year to to get accepted in the
following year but maybe you could be
like
you know sad as an opportunity to
improve yourself even more
but now you're ready
yeah fine
although i cannot believe that i left
korea almost just as you arrived oh and
watch your archive as soon as i get the
chance
thank you oh that's unfortunate yeah
oh man that that means you didn't see
the the signature in the anaplus cafe
huh
i hope you did get to visit it though
like generally
well good luck with your phd you can do
it i believe in you fighter
fighter fighter
good luck
and when you're done let me know i don't
know how long it takes but how long does
that take normally
[Music]
three years oh
four years
four or five years it gets more and more
like three years
five years
four years ah okay
says four years so it must be four years
he knows what he's talking about
um i have to be around oh i'll try i'll
be around some way
surely
thank you so much for the support
yeah i hope you continue watching my
streams though while you're doing your
phd mm-hmm you're better
[Music]
so true
thank you thank you thank you you're
like overloaded with love aren't ya
couldn't
let go of it
for a while here it is all of it at once
thank you
[Music]
um
often people with the greenest plums
have killed the most plants keep
practicing if you want to grow plants
i've been trying my best to like barely
keep alive like
a certain plant in my
apartment
i've been doing my best but for some
reason is
not recovering well but at least it's
not dying anymore
yeah
i don't know what the problem is man
majin di danke shin ray gana dan kishin
that's it
well that's
one
nice
and now we do the first episode of
called the lamb
[Music]
wow
adams thanks for the rest of the chat
i know you're excited for homer's second
anniversary coming next month
and so the same one for my birthday was
in i would like to say thank you for
your fun times and having me around keep
up the good work i love you all
thank you
to be honest i haven't been thinking
much about it
uh
there's like you know i was busy with a
lot of other things
and we haven't talked much about it yet
either
but
hopefully we'll do some exciting stuff i
have an idea for
like we're all obviously probably gonna
do um solo anniversary streams
and hopefully a collab
um but i have an idea for my solo
stream
i have
an idea
um
something
in my pocket
or in my
sleeve
i have a card in my sleeve to pull
we're not doing that that's stupid
old kibble from morning one a year ago
had that idea kiwama one year ago kiwama
you're stupid
we're not doing that
to watch long enough to watch along no
we could um do a watch long of my first
fall guys stream
my first stream after my debut
because that was
pure suffering
thanks
and your boy stephen adams thank you
[Music]
type advice blue pinky admitting to what
we actually are kind of lowers my
workload by 80 percent
it lowers it
i guess you can't really do anything
legally about cults
but at least now we can wear these
coffee robes out in public okay so the
robe is just the hybrid of the birthday
blanket and then you print but this
thing is comfy as [\h__\h] and i look
fabulous ah
yeah you know maybe i should sell a robe
like that
as birthday merchandise next year
more clothes
called a cold uh robe
how is it different from the apron stuff
though
you could say that's a cult apron too
[Music]
a bathroom
a bathrobe interesting
or like a not necessarily a backup but
like you know like a morning robe you
know what i mean not not so fluffy just
like a relatively thin
actually if you go the other direction i
could just do one of those otaku robes
um
those really thin
jackets not really a jacket
you know what do you know what i mean
like big big flashy wobble face on it
like a howdy yeah happy oh you call them
that
i had one before but i didn't know what
you called them
[Music]
yeah porka made one
um yeah maybe let's see how we feel an
idol
uh otaku kind of merchandise next year
um
if we need it
[Music]
brandon thanks for the pinky or two
pinkies and back from my scotland trip
my terrible knuckle flying continues
when i had a tooth shatter on the 10
hour plane there
how
did you bite into something you bite
but the less you know about that the
better
oh
it
look what happened
i visited a lot of museums tours and it
was fun trying all the euro food like
hockey schnitzer fish and chips
but i'm happy to be home and be able to
watch streams i feel you i feel you
traveling is fun and all but then you're
actually pretty happy to be back also
tsa from frowns on trying to bring a
grenade launcher across borders so they
took that
very concerning statement but i see your
username so make sense
it doesn't happen just by air pressure
no no way
no way
i hope it wasn't an important tube like
one of the front ones
i have no idea
i don't know and one moment i was
looking for a movie the next felt like i
was chewing on candy what
you what you didn't just like bite into
something and then pew
oh my god
it wasn't the front one
was it the front
one's two
one of the visit more visible ones i
hope not
sorry i guess that's maybe a little bit
embarrassing
sorry to talk about it but you got me
curious
ron was second for the middle no
[\h__\h]
man
it
looks like a nightmare
i used to have
nightmares like that sometimes
that was terrifying
like a teeth shadowing just randomly
no all of my teeth all my teeth at once
oh that's so [\h__\h] terrifying
ah yeah thank god masks
yeah
maybe you can get it fixed but i'll see
your
wait
yeah you're donating in u.s dollars so
i'm guessing it's a bit expensive in
america i hope i hope you can get it
fixed
unless you like it
that's fine
thank you so much for the pinkies i'm
glad you enjoyed the trip glad you had
some schnitzel
but now let's settle down for a while
and chill and relax and watch streams
comfortably
[Music]
yeah
too fairy incoming
i should be your tooth fairy but i'm not
gonna give you money under your pillow
i'm gonna take money
i take two and i take money
oh you know what you can have two i'll
just take the money i'll be the money
fairy
[Music]
you can have it isn't that nice you can
keep it too
keep it don't want it
this is called breaking in and robbing i
don't know about that we don't call it
that
in kiwa land
okay cultural differences respect my
culture okay
how
disrespectful so discriminating no one
respects my culture
[Music]
it's called the mummy fairy in kiwanis
and everybody enjoys the money fairy
everybody always waits for the money
fairy at night
you guys should come to kiwama land
who's that logic on russia
true
say it's monkey thank you very
much head of colt's denial i like your
title
as your head of colton i beg of you
please don't do anything too crazy today
i'm preparing statements for whatever
happens but that can only go so far wait
did you always have this title or did
you give it to yourself
thanks to this stream
because of the lamp because i like it we
need something like that
very specific title
i like it
hope you are not too busy right now you
probably are
thank you for the pinky four birds in
the opening
bremen
are so cute yeah you mean the
the totem the tori totem
i know it's so cute
i love them opening
i have so many good pixel openings huh
thanks for watching the openings
oh hopefully you always also stay until
the ending
[Music]
yeah bremen is a setting in germany
which is
making me a bit confused i don't think
you wanted to write that
down
what am i saying
this is obviously what same
thanks for the pinky
this has a book has to give like me only
one true love kiwawa
therapy is a good cult for you
world's best isle kiara and that
obviously means something else right
not korean once again trying to fool me
ah
close enough
it says kiana the world's best
fries chicken
instead of world's best idol
[Music]
at least it's not like
i expected worse
i expected something more like
like a heretic kind of statement
this is
better i guess
my expectations were
very very
low
thank you
question mark
myself again
thank you for the pinky with higher
devil tuning you're going to murder this
game
yeah if you saw that was first episode
that was pretty good i would say
i love playing it even went through
multiple times oh hello
yeah thank you
went for it multiple times wow
interesting
yeah don't really play games the second
time after finish them once but i guess
you can like make completely different
cults you know different
visuals so
oh yeah why not
i do feel it's a little
of a waste to not
mix all kinds of different
animals but this way it's it's more
it feels more
clean and
um
what's the word
organized
[Music]
yeah we need a chicken month
no
thanks for the pinky
i hope you still think i'm good at it
thank you thank you
squiggly mustache thanks for the pinky
[Music]
for two pinkies
yeah
pirate chicken bus i've come to bargain
you dress up as mama ina for a stream
and i'll forget cafe's ultimate secrets
actually i don't think you have the cake
for that i shall return with new
negotiations
are you implying that i don't have
enough butt
to
cosplay as inna
[Music]
that is an optical illusion what was
going on with ina i have the bigger butt
a million percent i can tell you that
so yeah i cannot dress up as her because
i have too much cake for that if
anything
it continues five chickenpox i i've come
to renegotiate
you help me squeeze mama in a squishy
hair and i'll forget kf's ultimate
secret
and add eye bonus i'll try to behave
that sounds more reasonable
than your inner cosplay with the bar set
too high
[Applause]
now you know what i might want to go for
the ena cosplay
i shall do that if you provide me with
the costume
png's if
possible i prefer pngs to put on my body
give me
i shall dress up as her
hmm
ow yeah oh true not only my booty is too
big but my bubba too
oh no what do we do
see what you challenged me
you challenged me
give me those pngs you know what i
really like the the cow kini png
of uh fauna because it works so well
actually
it looks so good did you guys see she
has like a cape and it's open in the
front where you see the cleavage
of her wearing a bikini and it actually
looks so good and i was wondering you
guys
would you make something like that for
me somebody
not a cow candy but
some kind of
i don't know
some kind of swimsuit
it doesn't have to be a swimsuit
it can be like a
bunny suit or a
but something that hides under a cape
like that because that worked out so
well to hide the rest of the body
no not a chicken suit
no
no i want something cute
another stupid
chicken song
no no no
no
make it cat related or something so i
can use my cat ears
how about dan
[Music]
you guys are cute but me wearing a
full-on chicken suit and you're just
making fun of me
no
i'm not gonna wear that even if you make
it for me
no
no i wanna look
cute
i don't wanna
no
frog suit frog bikini
okay
a green one
[Music]
cat armor
anything make me something
please
okay mr big thank you soon unknown
facebook pinky pray to the one and only
true god
true
true awards have never been spoken
before
thank you for your loyalty and your
faith in me
[Music]
i have a bad cold and i have a lot of
fever
after taking medicine i feel very sleepy
i want to watch the stream as much as
possible but if i don't sleep now i'm
going to bed first because my condition
is going to collapse
no
you can't you have to get better
that's that's that was a few days ago i
hope you feel better by now like a
week ago even
are you feeling better
[Music]
i see you in the chat
otherwise i will have to send you to bed
rest again
body pain no nobody but no
so good okay
i think he's fine
yeah
why did you get sick be careful
careful
don't get sick anymore you make me worry
oh thank you you're welcome
do you see park thank you
i i'm glad to hear that you had a good
time in korea also i heard you love here
at seoul popcorn i want to meet you in
popcorn but i have to attend chemistry
conference
that day instead i leave this super chat
thank you but
it is
sad
mystery conference
sounds way more boring than soul popcorn
with chihuahua
but i guess you probably have no choice
oh man scientific chicken yeah
you can give yourself a title like that
scientist kiwi scientist i don't think
we have one yet
hurrah the team can look at thanksgiving
black friction thank you
oh
[Music]
again thank you
louis angeles or angeles
thank you for the pinky mr squeak
i mean agent cookie good job on your
infiltration ah into the chicken then
soon we will get the receipts
and get full control over the whole
chain of astro supply just remember the
secret code ravioli ravioli gave me the
formula
[Laughter]
thank you for giving me the secret code
are we only where we only give it for me
only
he answered let's put him into the usual
room did you hear him he's over there
he's the one standing next to the
satisfied yeah yeah yeah that one that
one get him get him get him
usual room for eternity we're never
returning him
nope nope
nope
okay that's done
[Music]
i'm going i'm doing data entry at work
right now and just entered a guy's name
as basket because of all the ice cream
tangent
ah
baskin
robbins
no
i want
asking around maybe i'm gonna eat ice
cream before i go to sleep
i'm sorry for being missing so many
streams and being gone in the last 2.5
months i was just so busy with only last
week and work on the weekends no problem
but in the week no problem maybe you're
less busy now but you're always welcome
to come back any time looking for the
top down
and everything
what are your thoughts on the swimsuit
designs can i design for you i'm in
herself
ah
i don't remember the
i mean kelly so well anymore uh
uh callies i think should have had
more skin okay and kiwamos
[Music]
it was it was okay that was okay i think
i would have gone for a different design
um with like more
more of a cute
design um a few
uh
ruffles
and maybe some
some strings to tie around the belly or
so you know wrap it around and tie yeah
i have some ideas
it's quite the sexy bikini i would have
maybe gone a little more for a cute one
but
it's good though i like the fan out that
came out of it too
[Music]
another fashion contest no no no no no i
don't wanna like now that kelly started
that i'm not gonna like do the same
thing
no no no that's just
unethical in the streamer world
and crosstalk
thank you
you're done with this
now it's midnight hmm
i think the streams had followed after
that had
a few more super chats and the ones i
read
how many did i read do you guys does
anyone have the numbers
how many i read and how many have left
over 9 000.
ellie really thinks you're sexy boss
maybe yeah well the bikini i wore at the
airbnb
i guess was
a little bit on the sexy side i don't
know not necessarily it was just a
normal one i guess
you're right about 100 you have like 200
left
[Music]
i think it's the next one is the
uh although it's not that much the tunic
finale
yeah it's so late
[Music]
it wasn't left an impression yeah but
it's in no way it looks like that what
she drew
um
it was a pretty simple one too though no
[Music]
read them off the rest
real
i'm not far behind okay that's all i
needed to hear hey
let me see it let me look at my schedule
remember it's only 5 p.m
oh yeah we can also read after the
handcam stream because that's not gonna
be a super long stream
forgot about that one
i got the the mini i ordered a mini iron
i don't have a normal iron but i thought
mini iron might be more
useful for this one and not so much in
the way
i received it today it's so tiny it's so
many it's so cute like even in the
package it's so tiny it's such a baby
iron
oh
it's so cute here maybe i would smile
bubbly
iron
it's so cute it's actually like pretty
useful for traveling too i was um i
always wanted one
um
before like when traveling to like
conventions
to
really cheap in really cheap hotels they
don't have uh
irons available
yeah
and i used to
always go for the cheapest accommodation
possible so
luckily
one of my friends she had a iron with
her usually
so i would just use hers when i needed
it but i mostly i don't even
normally normally i never iron my
clothes the last time i ironed a piece
of clothing
i can't remember must be over
two years ago
and even when i try i'm really bad at it
so it doesn't quite work out
for some reason
but the thing is my clothes
don't really need ironing
the ones i wear and the ones that that
do need iron i just don't wear them
because i'm like oh damn this is so
wrinkly after washing it one time
ah [\h__\h] guess i won't wear it
maybe i'll just iron it someday but not
today today is not the day
that's why i wanted to do an ironing
stream
at some point
just iron all the clothes that i've been
not ironing all at once
in who's gonna do that at some point
did i tell you guys about that plan
that would be ironic ah
oh man
i did um
i will do that at some point
yeah
it would be very not efficient if i did
it with the baby iron dough that i use
the normal iron otherwise i'll never get
done
there is only post and write me your
suggestions for the members only and i
think i'll be able to prepare it in time
i'm just gonna stream on crunchyroll
whatever netflix whatever whatever it is
maybe you guys are able to also tell me
where i could watch it
if it's on crunchyroll on netflix or
somewhere else um
tell me that in the post too if it's not
too late already
that's not what you choose oh yeah yeah
i'll try to choose like after i wake up
uh which will be like in
10 hours or so considering i still have
to eat
then i'll make a post with what i chose
and um put up the reservation
and then we'll watch it
ah who has the license my tip for my
region that's true
yeah
even if you guys can watch somewhere i
might not be able to watch it there
that's true
and just anyway let me know
and
possibly just make one suggestion
um don't give me like 50 [\h__\h]
suggestions just give me one that you
really believe in
thank you i made freehold
delete them
okay free maximum
if your suggestions are too long i might
not look at them
well i look at i'll take a look if like
there's one anime that keeps on being uh
suggested by suggested by everybody
i did free as well i already said more
than free oh man i should have
said that as a rule before
i uploaded the ones i agree with okay
[Music]
three's a good number yeah
i'll keep it afraid yeah please do
five or six oh man
well if there's a lot of overlap that
will make the choice easier though maybe
if everybody mentions one anime that
they recommend and
i'll probably
watch it
it better be good guys
your suggestions better be good
now
in the following streams if i continue
watching it
i need i need always need stuff to watch
so i give in i'm going back into the
anime rabbit hole i'm giving in
take me take me
i'm ready
and how many i want to watch 10.
uh one episode of 10 the first episode
of the of 10 animes is what the post
says
[Music]
oh
i have a feeling you won't like konosuba
and everyone is suggesting it
yeah we can give it a try it's just one
episode
i feel like konosava i probably would
have liked um
seven years ago
or
ten to seven years ago whenever 15 to 70
years ago
but now
uh
probably not quite my taste but we'll
see i i can give it a try
jiggle physics
what
it has jiggle physics
oh my god
if i find nothing in these 10 animes
that i like then we might have to do it
a second time
okay guys i'm gonna end it here in the
germany selfie nothing
thank you for the fun cuz of the lamb
stream was very nice and chill
and difficult challenging oh
yeah i'll see you tomorrow
i'll put up the reservation after i get
up hope you guys can make it
sorry that it's not on the weekend
popcorn and stuff [\h__\h] up my sleep
rhythm so
ah it fits it fits better in here
good night
bye bye
i'm gonna eat my bell peppers now
um
that's
[Music]
cake
whoa 20.
thank you hi alpha
if you guys ever want to um gift uh
memberships because i can't turn it off
um
i would recommend to gift it
during the end of a stream because that
can kind of
it's a higher guarantee that someone
gets it who really wants it and
someone who's nice
yeah i think it doesn't make sense
much sense in the pre-chat or in the
first
few hours of a
popular stream or stuff
try to give
at the end of the stream
that would probably be better
[Music]
i should know
whoever stays until the end of the
stream i believe that person is a good
person
after six hours 41 minutes
thanks guys thank you i'm known too
thank you
[Music]
okay enjoy your memberships
thank you
[Music]
are sure about that i know you deserve
it
this best
[Music]
a good loyal chicken i know you deserve
this
[Music]
don't question it
i didn't get it diddy
oh
[Music]
if they can't make it through the golden
peppa they really answer exactly
[Music]
everyone who watched during the golden
path
riddle
thingy
everyone every single one
deserved one
[Music]
okay gonna go now
you