foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
you can like get outfits from selective
members from Whole Life en ID and Japan
this this things are not sponsored but
we just really want to show you
good look at everything
yeah
look at that snazzy wow
we ask everyone to introduce themselves
and they can also show off their sexy
outfit while they're introducing
themselves all right let's go
we might get kicked out of the room
eventually but let's just start uh let's
start with
almonds
uh number one detective I'm naked
um
[Music]
yeah yeah
hello
[Music]
[Applause]
hi
okay next we have kale primary
hi I can't really I'm having some
trouble with the choppy audio which is
why I'm not streaming but guess what
also my mommy hooked up my Wi-Fi which
means I'll be streaming in 480p which to
be honest why even why even [\h__\h]
bother why even bother okay Mommy I'm
gonna get some whole swag As a sheriff
let's party
[Music]
Amelia one of the selected people you
can get the outfits of hi gouda hello
yes we're officially in the Among Us
lore now
Among Us hi I'm gonna
[Music]
thank you
now you can have so many imposters of
yourself do you even know who who is you
anymore
I love it there are many sharklings
around
right here right next to you is cool
please introduce yourself
who is you what I'm Who is you
um
[Music]
summer
looking guys
[Music]
happy
was also part of the people's outfit you
can get in the game
hi everyone
Indonesia generation one nice to meet
you we're nice
I feel like right now I'm wearing a
scientist outfit right now I feel like
I'm I'm doing a touring love in the
Among Us
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yeah yeah
okay okay and then we have Mommy hi
Mommy
looks like Felix's Empires I'm amazed
[Music]
chocolate ice cream we're working on it
right mommy yeah
[Music]
who are you going for what outfit do you
want
uh whatever is the closest on the tree
yeah understandable all right and then
we have a baby
today I'm cosplaying as sexy naked
Marine
[Applause]
impression was so good what the heck
that was really good wow
[Music]
okay and then we have
hello hello I am I will be the second
today
[Music]
actually today
oh my God yeah okay
[Music]
the organizer of today's event the
sponsor of today's event
[Music]
oh my God what the heck
of course of course that happened one
second now we'll open a new room that
timing was amazing yeah that time it was
amazing the fact that it happened on
yours yeah
yeah okay a new code is in the Discord
chat please please go get it and don't
make it seem to the eye
all right one second one second
[Music]
thank you
oh
my God
yeah a really sexy combination of marine
and pecora you look at that that's so
cool oh my God
looking good I can also do like yeah
I can do so much I can do this and
um I will now change the world settings
we will have everything included we'll
have scientists in case you don't know
the scientists can see the vitals at any
time
well there's a countdown but you can see
if someone's dead before finding the
body and then we have the engineer
engineer can he's a crewmate who can
jump into the vents so you can
[Music]
yeah or you can maybe find some other
imposters because of that might be
healthy eating in the vents oh yeah
spicy for you too you're very spicy and
now we have the guardian angel which I
thought was really useful because the
guardian angel is the ghost of the first
crewmate that dies who can then go on to
protect others from death
and I only have last but not least the
shape shifter this one is oof that that
calls for a lot of
fights
[Music]
Shape Shifter can be only an imposter
but that imposter can change the looks
of themselves even the name so if the
shapeshifter is me I can change to I
don't know Anya and even have her name
and her outfit and I can kill people as
her a people will think wow it was Anya
oh my God diabolic what if I was the one
who found you instead there will be two
onions
double action weapons but just so you
know all of these rolls are not 100 so
it's not guaranteed that you that they
will be in the coming game but you know
what happened to you now let's start off
thank you
so quick before another time
please please
[Music]
[Laughter]
[\h__\h]
roommate anyway I am
okay so first of all I'm not gonna um
like together with like anyone
with [\h__\h] anyone no
[\h__\h] my heart beats my heartbeats
it's almost Mommy
it where is it where is it
how far away
oh yeah they look like little guys
lights
where's the lights
[Music]
hey voices here what the heck hello
hello short
where's the lights
one
I was thinking
already
that was so bad that was quick
where was it the um where was the body
Armory yeah
I think or was it Ollie
[Music]
uh it's the the corpses in the Armory
right
because like uh like in the beginning of
the game I saw Muna in the armory but
not not that was the beginning I was in
the back room when it was for now well
she got killed first
I I don't know but anybody want to step
up and be like yo I'm something I have
no idea though you can uh if if you were
you were telling me that um I was in a
Armory you can ask a gura because I saw
Guru also in a nearby there in the
kitchen yeah yeah
nine seconds guys
I'll just inform you guys
um
oh poorly
[Music]
this is my friend
hi Elena
yeah stay away from me the Hat
wait oh um
thank you
okay I don't know I'll previously
hello hello
[Music]
why your task is
don't follow me
oh
foreign
oh my God
is that is dead
[Music]
a kitchen kitchen
uh me and Maury Senpai we were nearby
electrical I was going to the viewing
that I was with a roommate and Kelly
Senpai I mean I went to the armor and
put guns away I passed by I passed by I
think it was Watson oh and
and gura in records yeah I can I say
that last time I saw Zeta they were in
the main hall with Cobo yeah we're
watching in front of us
I was the thing about global because uh
she she telling me on the previous one
it was me well I definitely like far
away from the kitchen and now
do you have she left do you have
anything that you want to defend Cobble
yeah
so many last words
and short was like in the in front of
the fan yeah sure just uh see herself I
like just what she said and then after
that I go up
are you sure but oh well yeah for you
before right near the lounge that was
beginning though that was the very
beginning no no I I after that I go up
I go after killing her you mean
um
we have like we have little short time
uh choose uh who's I don't know I'm
still not sure but I'm going to skip
information yeah I have no idea
what everyone says
[Music]
at the very
well at least I got two
mummy
[\h__\h] I'm not I hate being imposer
my heart
I think I think I should I shoot I
should wear my my heart rate monitor
like really it's scarier than horror
games
uh I hate being imposters a lot
yeah I'm shaking I'm shaking
ah
a
and then
it hurts me
let's see where some of me
hello hello Melissa
[Music]
that's insane Watson is dead oh I found
the body
um okay so I was in the front
um of the ship and I was doing the tasks
that were up there and then Watson came
in and we chased each other around for a
little bit and I was like don't don't do
this to me Watson she laughed she was
like I'm Gonna Get You he he and then I
was like haha very funny and so then we
did our tasks
while I was figuring out how to do the
mini game I was like how do you do this
then mume ran in and was like and doing
things and then I walk out and Watson's
dead body is there
because you would have passed Watson if
you were entering the front of the ship
you would have passed Watson how did you
not see here
I can't hear anything
I'm not gonna point fingers at you
immediately I just want to know what
your Alibi is no no I'm not I just want
to know what your Alibi is because I
Watson left and then you came in and I
walked past you and Watson's dead bodies
on the ground I just want to know what
that's about
why you remember so much Kelly I'm I'm
just bringing it and moving all right
now listen here's the deal so the amount
of time that passed in between me
entering the room seeing Watson leave
and mume entering and me going outside
was so short
it was like no time at all you would
have passed her I just I just want to
remind you that we have 10 seconds left
so I think if you don't have a lot I'm
sorry I have to vote for a moment I just
don't believe it
okay nice try
that would make her a murderer
no wait
[Music]
nice good job everyone
congrats information
[Music]
no that was the only time I've ever done
something legitimately in a month
[Laughter]
[Music]
Amelia wants some detective outfits yeah
thanks are you guys ready for another
round yes
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
what's up
foreign
[Laughter]
no electrical all right
no electrical I hit electrical
um
yeah
usually
but all I think is I don't know the map
I
usually if ah
what sorry I'm really bad at imposter
I'm sorry say me too it's okay I'm
shaking until now yeah very bad nice try
for us it's okay
regret them next time we'll kill
everybody yeah for sure
yeah yeah yeah it's okay
I'm still shaking right now
Muna gonna sauce me
probably I don't know perhaps I mean
what did I just say I'm I'm just I'm
still shaking well
like in front of her face
and then run away yeah winner probably
Sesame right now but who knows
who knows
the outside world and
Communications where's the
communications at
um
Spider-Man hello hello
thank you
[Music]
now found Ollie dead
um that was crazy so I don't know the
map super well but I left the shower so
I put away all of the washcloths from
the shower and then I walked out and I
turned right and I went down that long
hallway and found Ollie's body right in
the middle of there but I didn't see
anyone coming down from there so I'm
kind of stuff
[Music]
well let's see um Rainey was busy doing
things around the shower
um also Raina could have killed me and
she didn't close I think girl was in the
shower as well but she like went down to
the left no I was up in the meeting room
with Kobo what that's not what I saw you
uh do we have like you said who's gonna
be the way of the of the kill because
because if if it's really if it's
raining if she already killed only
probably she cannot kill you
right but I mean Renee could have killed
me several times and she didn't so I I
feel like you freaking vouch for me she
was trying to tell me a joke and then I
ran away from her oh yeah
also killed me but didn't
so
I have no idea because I didn't see
Ollie at all and I was like at the left
side
the whole time yeah it was mostly down
below
huh no I'm just like saying uh so
probably saying that you are nearby the
the place I just like thinking oh true
I'm True by the way but I I don't
remember I saw municipate in the
middle-ish or on the left side
[Music]
okay
are you a Spiderman actors
what is this
good taste everyone cookies
I think
I don't know what she
go wait oh
hi
hey
[Music]
do I turn the knob what is this okay I
don't I don't want to do calm because I
can't like literally
I can't do this one what is that I will
do it leave it to me
I fixed it we all stayed together you're
welcome
I bet it's this
high again hey hi
you like
ice cream what
ice cream yeah
yeah
pretty good
okay
eight seven seven
where's lunch where's lunch
where's
hi hi my mic
my mic okay we're still watching
oh my God
you know I'm going to wear my heart with
monitor
Communications you know
there's Communications here
buddy you
me oh my God where no
no no
[Music]
um
very bottom of the armory
nobody else
Kiara I was with you and we transformed
each other as Alibi yeah
below the main hall
I was on the way actually I was on the
way to the kitchen so any any sooner I
would have found the body but I'm from
the engine room I saw you I saw you at
the right side of the map going up
because I was doing tests at the cargo
bay you know there's the test oh okay
cool
[Laughter]
I'll explain my route I went cargo bay
uh for the you know small thing and then
I went to the showers because you know
that those are a two-part task after the
shower I went towards the main hall
engine room Communications because I
have thoughts in the kitchen and viewing
deck and then I was about to turn to the
Armory and then bomb that body oh so you
were pretty close by yeah
went past me and it was the last voice
[Music]
it was zetta's voice and I was like I
went like what
okay skip I didn't vote who am I voting
for Gouda
[Music]
too gotta get them out of here
let's say Communications where's
Communications again
main hole
no
we need to go to a meeting uh
when I can at least vouch for
um
[Music]
oh no
the words
I swear I was just like kind of my God
oh my God no please no this hello too
hi
Mina where's
come on here's communication
everything goes well
everything will go well right
okay
what's up with this Arrow yellowish
it's for sign out okay there's the
perfect bucket here okay
nice
shut up
I'm trying my best right now yeah
try my best
meeting
so much to do in the meeting room right
so much to do in the meeting room
okay
push one there
and then maybe unless plus here
okay
all right
where is the main hall
meeting room here yep room here where's
the main hall here
oh there is nothing in
okay maybe someone's died maybe
someone's die I don't know
Maybe
see I haven't really done anything much
huh
nothing's there
where the heck is the main hole here oh
here it is
we need to wash our body and then boom
we need all the tasks
and then what I don't know
come up who needs a map
you know let's find the
where who's that where oh sure
wait where
where I was I was just doing the stinky
electrical task with Anya and I ran into
it raining and mummy
huh
that's uh technically that's true I I
keep thinking while I think these three
a two Row in the back is always you guys
always spots sounds about rainy why yeah
right
it wasn't me it wasn't even me reporting
I don't know where the body is this time
yeah
shifters don't forget shapeshifters what
about medical guys
where was it wait I want to ask uh Arena
where are you at
I'm at Medical I came from cargo bay
was like going from bottom to up oh yeah
where was the body wait how about Watson
how about Watson how about Watson well I
was with Luna Senpai for a little bit
but then I was down by electrical like
down the ladder that's where I was
coming up
I want to ask why is mume so always so
afraid of me or is she just afraid of
everybody in general he's been pretty
quiet yeah yeah I was thinking the same
the body formulas the body balls both
the body so do we have a master where
the body was I missed it probably yeah
where's it where's the body I was gonna
see the body both the body is in the
bathroom
[Music]
yeah
I don't know
um
[Music]
now we just need
me
is my best friend
Amaze my best friend
take a bath in the coin so I can
um
yeah
okay
huh
evolved
what no I just saw you
oh no right now
God I need to get used to play this game
we landed there right
there right
talk to me no no Mommy I'm sorry
oh that's cool focuses I was just
checking your voice yeah yeah I'm safe
with me I review so you don't get killed
I'm safe it's okay yeah I'm safe
no I'm fine
okay
everybody is
would I
need to clean this vents
everyone it says
in here
it definitely wasn't rated then I
thought it was her maybe but uh I found
her body in the kitchen but I saw no one
else around
I I I heard I heard rainy so double
ganger of me
so yeah
of me
so I don't know so somebody was
pretending to be you I did see right
yeah running from Luna but maybe it
wasn't Luna Muna
oh wait who yeah I saw I saw you too I
mean Muna is like
he was with Reina for a while so I'm not
not this time but I was with her often
enough wait was that the previous run
I'm mixing games
it might have been last game when I was
a lot with
it I ran into combo Kobo was sounding
very scared though so I'm always scared
we have to vote for someone hobo is
killing someone scary is that it but
Como I was like for a while together she
could have killed me she didn't so I
think she's fine
um
[Music]
so there should only be one imposter
left there was a couple of times a
couple of times I go with Ahmed but but
she didn't kill me neither
uh I have a feeling that maybe but then
I but then it might be um I got a double
ganger so I don't know I don't know I
just wanna because last time Muna is
with arena in the weapons like it's near
kitchen right
wait so where was reina's body in the
weapon where that closed the kitchen I
haven't I haven't go I haven't go to the
Armory can anyone vouch for Ahmed and
say like she's safe I was with Gouda and
I didn't kill her or a mom and she did
forever I was sussing about Kobo though
because
I don't know
but I don't know maybe perhaps perhaps
it's really a
hip shaft shift shape shape shifter
who wants to come sit perhaps it's
really a shape shifter I don't know
that she's being heard and then
purposefully tried to create
okay
lights out probably
your step body
let's check the
one two three four five feet
it's five
oh okay right
okay all right right I was right it's
Luna I was right
foreign
[Music]
you might have been acting
let's go
I would hear you and you were on purpose
saying something that only a crewmite
would say
[Music]
oh my God
right now I'm bad
[Music]
let's go
olly congratulations
so I could
I feel like
wait what okay
hi
you want to go together I'm scared no
useless
hi hi there hi
oh
um
then you will know um
yeah uh going to the Armory and the
kitchen when when I want to go to the
engine room so I didn't know I saw you
or she from cockpit or main hall yeah so
we passed each other in the kitchen and
we learned from the communications
Armory kitchen I saw viewing that oh Ali
and Guru oh no it was short yeah
we kind of passed by each other it's
always me what yeah what you guys have
against it yeah
[Laughter]
I saw her I saw her in the shower but
then went away to the left side I think
foreign
to the left side so she was yeah she
went to the left side yeah she was in
the shower I saw her in the shower Cali
do you have an alibi maybe I was going
out to get service I did pass you Watson
I was worried you were gonna follow me
outside but you didn't uh you probably
weren't that worried since you're
outside
yeah I found Zetta actually right by the
body because uh I was the one who
recorded it coming up the ladder yeah I
couldn't see because it was really dark
and then I went up yeah
you went up I went up no I went I didn't
see you go up um
[Music]
I don't know like someone going up but
they didn't
yeah I don't want anyone dying yet first
I don't think
[Music]
I don't know probably there are shapes
I mean who knows
is there any trap shifter here
bro
I'm going to
split up from the phone you know where
those like not not going together with
anyone
all right
hi Zita
hi why are you success
beautiful
[Music]
boots
oh my God
wait what
[Laughter]
I would know that right oh my God
Anya's dead
what the frick
I just found Anya's body in the bathroom
and I'm pretty sure Zeta and somebody
else versus us here okay
where's the where's the body uh anybody
wants the body no showers oh no wait
what the [\h__\h] Lounge showers Lounge
Lounge which one yeah
[Music]
a day where
um the last time the last time I went
near the shower and main hall is I saw
only
amen and I think I think anybody see
Anya with anyone
I think is she alone in the
right side then
I think it's uh probably Kiara and Zeta
what no no no
no no no wait wait
yeah yeah yeah
she's innocent yeah listen to me I am
always us when I'm a crewmate and when
I'm not a crewmate I'm uh nuts us so
keep that in mind now you're saucing me
which means I'm a crewmate it's always
like this it's not gonna work I didn't
well then I say
I say why aren't you providing an alibi
instead of Defending yourself huh I'm in
yeah
[Music]
I'm gonna skip I don't know I'm gonna
skip because I don't know
[Music]
bruh I think I'm going to watch over
here
maybe maybe I may but I don't know if
Ami is
I mean it's kind of sauce
whether it's Ami or
light hi
and mommy is always oh no they're not
together
[Music]
no
dear
nope nope
nope see
I mean I mean
wait wait I may go go go go go near the
front
what I don't know why it's so sauce
oh my God
okay let's see
let's
where's the kitchenette oh the kitchen
kitchen
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
probably or not oh okay it's Zetta for
sure I'm voting no no oh really why why
not okay okay
you you said you you found a buddy three
times in a row now yeah because I just
happened to be a detective who's really
good at spotting bodies
could I have killed you or would I have
uh killed that body if I was with you
and in that room for like over 30
seconds yeah
um I don't know uh you want me to be
honest um what you said was oh just
kidding I was just waiting for my cool
down yeah but I was already in the room
doing the task before you got there
oh can anyone give an alibi to Jetta
no
no no no no no but I mean uh instead of
running away from the body because Reina
and I were both up in the room like in
the meeting room and then as I went down
I was with Reina the whole time and then
we saw Zeta pass I have my alibi
for Watson I saw Kobo take the little
elevator yeah when I take for dinner
when I take the elevator what's in like
near defend everybody
[Music]
10 seconds who
but
okay
well I think it's Sun
for me to die
I don't know yeah family meeting the
mommy and the two sisters we could
who's the other one wow
I hate lights out why
they know why you don't open the door
okay because I suck
huh
hi
hi hello what do you want huh yeah
Watson watch me clean the vents
I'm doing this heal me in the process
here
okay ready Let's Stay Together
okay
are you doing a task in here or
something no
no I'm slow then what are you doing are
you just waiting to kill one of us yeah
okay
all right
all right have fun
good luck yeah good luck good luck for
you guys do you guys eat breakfast for
dinner or what
um
[Music]
okay
up from here
[Music]
voted for me
um oh no no no I don't want to be I
don't want to say 9 46.
I'm
I'm liberated from here
yay
I'm almost gonna kill me I swear also
I'm done with my tasks let's go let's go
to the emergency meeting and talk about
cool can you finish the quest huh okay
yeah
clear one okay six five three yeah
[Music]
okay okay it's almost going so we can do
this no that's what's in this Watson is
doing it
[Music]
what's in there I keep pressing your own
buttons
[Music]
wait wait oh sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
trust me bro trust me bro it's coming
Prospect row okay it's Kiara
why you about I was just doing my
electrical thing
I would not hear you I'm
sorry did you what what you didn't know
how much you need to kill but I was
constantly with her
I'm telling you it's on the dress people
probably Kobo to be honest because she
was like Raina and I were together and
Koba was not doing any tasks and she was
just following us trying to wait until
one of us was like separated I was just
following you what were you doing
recently
I was just following them
why are you done with your task or no my
last task is in electrical
um
then why did you go up to where we were
Ollie I'm just scared I'm just watching
so good with numbers but why did you
mess up why did you keep messing up that
number thing I had to do the keypad
thing for you oh true that was such that
took so long after Cobra went over to
that side but I was on that side too
right now once I was just being stupid
I'm sorry
wait so why do we call this emergency
meeting in the first place all right
because we wanted to vote you off yes
let's go
let's believe it's not me it's either
yeah
I'm gonna vote for Ollie because I kind
of feel bad for her because nobody ever
cusses her
wow
but no is that enough that's enough
right what
I know
what okay
[Music]
no I'll trap here
and I'm going to electrical
me too
electrical
okay
where's the electrical at here wow
I'm at the electrical
pew pew
[Music]
oh let's see it's still oh four of us
we're still alive oh
okay nobody's died
okay
I'm going to need
to keep the others
here
because I'm scared
she goes on
so I'm just going to fix the electrical
okay
all right
now let's find the others no no no no
okay
[Music]
I didn't do nothing
so weird
okay
I think they're going to emergency
meeting now
why
you suddenly suspect me what about your
what do you task I done all my tasks
what do you have left
I already did my electrical task
okay
but that would mean I'm done because
we're all done if we're really all
um uh normal and we're all done then we
should have won by now so it's Kobo
normally but probably
could be the ghost
why is it always me but
I mean come
okay
to people sir please I hate big imposer
[Music]
was so spot on
um
but she was so aggressive that's why we
were so scared
that's just her personality it's not
that she's the Imposter that's just her
personality yeah
[Music]
and I was like doubting myself
uh-huh
[Music]
okay sleeping
um
[Music]
oh my God
very sure
oh my God what
foreign
bro I don't know what zero
who's the Imposter
foreign hi
hello
thank you
oh my God
whoa
[Music]
what's the body watch her die
where
the where oh ah maybe we should vote out
she really wants to die oh okay
okay
I didn't Photoshop before the Imposter
though
well she said please
[Music]
we'll give you some more time to get
some kills
you want to be killed or or Kiara Kira
just uh go to Mumbai so if she was the
first one or maybe we can restart the
games
you're killed I mean you'll suffocate oh
I want to watch me get like you know
beheaded
all right we'll give you until the next
meeting movie and then all right all
right okay this combo wanna talk about
it because she reported so yeah
yeah oh yeah yeah
I wanted to find the body Cobble I found
the body infernals Communications
between Communications and Armory and I
was I I was uh
[Music]
we'll give you until the next meeting
trying to kill as many people as you can
um
[Music]
right now
all right
stay away everybody says everybody says
even you Mom
no I'm not going with anybody
even mummy
okay why
not gonna kill me right mommy are you
there
well mommy is gone why I don't know why
mommy is here wow
okay
who
nice there
cool
all right
I'm gonna do Emery right here
put it here
fixing the light
hello
[Music]
so let me vouch I was with a Grayson
fine electrical
yeah and they didn't kill me I thought
he was pretty quick to get an alibi
there huh
who found which body though there's
three bodies right I found zeta's body
in cargo bay and it wasn't there a
moment ago I think but the lights were
off
[Music]
um
at the very top
I happen an alibi for for Oli and gura
because I saw them and we were we were
near the kitchen first and then go to
security and electrical we haven't go to
medical and cargo bay yet
for a while so
I'll buy
um
I want to us and also why Kiara is not
screaming at all yeah
usually when when she was the crew man
she almost she always screamed whenever
she met someone wanted to cut me off I
didn't scream
are you sure about that yeah what the
[\h__\h]
I don't know I've I've been I've been
I've been uh watching all of you guys
um you know
Sound by on the previous uh previous day
Kiara Kiara really loves to scream
whenever I met anyone that's when she
was scared that's because
you were scared and now you're getting
you're getting enough so far you didn't
show that you are scared do you have an
alibi no it's been it's because I didn't
see anyone probably that's because
[Music]
last minute I don't know I found it last
minute okay yeah
oh [\h__\h]
my fault
prepared for my life
foreign
[Music]
no I'm sorry Mommy
laughs
foreign
oh whatever hello
it wasn't
me yeah I saw I saw Muna Senpai going
towards where Ollie was and that was the
last time I saw her but
we were actually split ways no I didn't
see the body I pressed the emergency
button
oh okay wait you didn't see the blind
no it's your body it really went to
check if anyone's
bid by pressing more you're the last one
left and you want to try to vote people
out
but she didn't say anything
we are in the same room shark
yeah
what is it called what are they called
uh it's skin consumer skin Shape Shifter
Shape Shifter because you didn't say
anything but I guess it's fine oh
yeah why'd you call a meeting what the
heck
yeah let me stop the tasks is that it
okay fine well you know what I'm done
with my task anyways so like maybe I can
just go chat with the girls you guys can
vote me off if that's what you guys want
um I just talk with the ghost there
I bet you couldn't hear them
yeah they're like no
no don't turn
all I wanted to be is us the whole time
maybe we did so maybe it's a good idea
if you guys vote maybe it's you
I mean I'm allowed now whoever what is
it it said the rhyme did that I have no
idea I've been stuck in electrical doing
the stupid
um I have no idea
Ollie
is somebody eating okay
are we winning no no I don't
[\h__\h] no no no no no no no no no no no
please
but we need to fix the
line
excuse me
hey
let me out
okay at least I got Kiara right oh
that's funny
oh my God
what the heck hello where who is
breathing it's really strange
[Music]
every time that Kobo is the Imposter
it's incredibly difficult that should
tell you whenever people are dying
really fast it's definitely Kobo he's
she saw the crime scene went goes to the
emergency meeting and then she
tripping by saucing the innocent ones
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
right with you Kiara salty okay
oh my God I finally I finally win being
an imposter with you Mommy thank you
thank you
[Music]
all right let's go let's go
um
this game is not good for my mental
health I'm for Deuce who ask
why
like my my my voice is shaking like
that's because I'm literally shaking
I don't know why I take this game
seriously I don't know why
you don't usually play like this maybe
it's because on stream I don't know
maybe it's because I play with
oh
is this bug the last one oh I'm hungry
too
much what what what what once again
[Music]
so here's what I found I was picking up
all of the towels and [\h__\h] in the shower
and I said I hope gura doesn't kill me a
girl is fine I don't think that she did
it but I went to the left by Kelly
Senpai um we were in the same room and
um the people I saw were you gura Senpai
and Zeta okay well let me tell you where
I found the body first before you start
pointing fingers okay listen to me
because I didn't even tell you where I
found the body you just immediately
jumped on me
[Music]
from the left from the left of the
shower walked up and in that photo room
we're all like it's like a dark room I
guess that's where I found the body I
didn't see that there was a dead body in
there because the lights were out until
it said report I clicked report and I
guess Renee was killed in the dark room
so that's all I have to say about that I
literally was just cleaning up the
shower was anybody down there
okay the lights so I was laughed at
electrical
ah cool
I was at electrical showers okay I was
at electrical and I saw no one yeah I
saw Zetta but I was there
where where I was at electrical I have I
was at the bottom right of electrical I
walked from the bottom
[Music]
no I didn't finish picking him up I
thought I did but it wouldn't let me put
them inside of the hamper thing so I
still have to grab a couple towels I I
whatever I am snuffling with only
because I was in the electrical I saw I
was in the electron I was in the middle
I was in the middle bottom and see that
he was in the bottom but I didn't see
anyone tonight
[Music]
I don't know what's us
too much
okay I'm going to go hello
[Music]
I don't know
who suspect
a cruel world
[Music]
okay
but when I was in the bathroom
there was
there were I mean there were Zita and
Anya so
I don't know yet
what is this oh
no
let's go on
now the lights is off
I need to turn it on
right I'm sorry guys I think this is not
the best color my collab stream so far
I'm really sorry I've
I mean
I it would be really
um
I I I pass uh on always I pass on always
uh in the in the electrical
and then and then after that she's going
up and then I saw I saw
I ran into Ollie after that and she was
saying and I quote ha ha
ha huh
[Music]
[Applause]
the first time the first time all he
said is she was an electrical but I
didn't see it and then the second time
you know we we had to teleport first
right and then after that she said you
know I'm an electrical I find you and
after that
um I'm still fixing my electrical and
then uh Ollie pass by going up uh and
then I was on my my end task uh doing
the electricity uh and then I saw Carly
died
oh
actually I wish your partner good luck
Ollie whoever was with you
hopefully can do this alone
got it I gotta be careful the next one
might be same gen Bond
[Music]
is it actually Ollie
she would defend herself more if it
wasn't her
[Music]
wow
okay maybe it's
[Music]
the perfect connection where where is it
okay so
ah
I don't play like this off stream okay I
don't know maybe it's more intense
playing it on stream
okay please done
please don't
um
hello hello
I don't know
what is it in English I don't know
just passed by
okay
nowhere yeah
I just saw her like a second ago running
away from the alarm like as she finished
the alarm and then she walked to the
right side towards the
records Lounge Etc
where's the bunny
blue body okay
so record I was in main hall going to
showers
and then Zita passed by and then I
checked I checked like around the
showers and then I go up a bit and
there's Anya's body there are you saying
so the last time you saw a horrible yeah
it's yeah but I was but I wasn't me
again
is coming from the left side
uh-huh
come on come on we need we need it fast
right
shifter accessed here
we don't know for sure but we don't know
for sure I don't know but it doesn't
come I don't know okay uh me neither but
they thought this is
tried to do her alibiscus
for like a long time
because I because I hear her voice
but I hear her voice
[Music]
because we know it's not ourselves I'm
is voting for me again isn't she
um
[Music]
thinking for a while
foreign
[Music]
let's go nice job let's go
nice shoot to Sheriff's nice job
you guys figured it out heck yeah
good job everyone
[Music]
that was a great job
I'm sorry
it's anyone who didn't get imposter
every single time me me
no I'd do a terrible job
anymore
I like doing my tasks and it helps using
people out you know this game is like
never end I feel like I want to play it
until I got a meter yeah
it's addictive I wouldn't mind playing
more but I'm just worried about the ID
members because it's like you know for
me for me it's fine because I usually
sleep at the morning
[Music]
yeah all right one more
thank you so much
[Music]
you guys want to see a magic trick never
mind please no I'm not the Magic Tree
right now
one more time
and that scares me
literally
self reports
oh come on give her a chance come on
I don't want to talk anymore
[Music]
it was it was in the hallways it was in
the main hall actually yeah okay yeah so
uh I was I was I actually uh saw her
through the showers I went to electrical
a little bit then I went back to the
main hall and guess this I actually met
another Ollie so if you guys said
anything like oh my God no there was
actually a doppelganger and I actually
met her she was teasing me down and no
no listen she was teasing me down and
you know what even if you guys kill me
right now I don't mind because I still
have tasket even if I fly
[Music]
and whenever she tries to defend herself
always just like very very desperate
yeah
I'm gonna
[Music]
awesome
oh no
this one I have to do
foreign
[Music]
nah
yeah hold all together pretty name plate
I want it me I mean I have I have an
alibi uh-huh you know so I was I was on
the first I wasn't security with rainy
if if I was simple sir I've been I've
been with Renee uh for like a couple of
seconds I'm not killing her at all so if
and then I got to maybe you were in the
Midtown
like was heading towards the showers I
think or the main hall I don't really
remember to the right and then I think
Ollie was asking like have you seen gura
or something
and then there was also Zetta or
something but there was like a bunch of
people there there is a lot of people
I feel like Yeah I wanted to show a
magic trick I'm not accusing anybody I'm
just telling what I saw okay
uh
yeah I don't know yeah
I was alone for a long time I was around
Muna a lot but she never killed me but
okay he says this can't be the cooldown
it can be the same for yourself I'm
vouching for Ollie I mean
yeah for like a long time you want to
save her yeah but the thing is I don't
know Anya Anya was also there but Anya's
also dead but girls also dead
[Music]
to do another
okay
I don't know but
who knows how to do that safety test
because I can't how I already Google it
how does that save me hey safety task I
don't even know if I can no it's not on
the bridge
it's like over there you know that that
safety Mana
okay
like okay let's see here here
this is the hardest task
and
I never got this tax before
man
okay I think I'm just going to leave it
here
because I don't know oh the lights is
off
foreign
to the left two
how left
wait the lights is off
okay I need to poop
people people
oh my God who's playing with the lights
man
thank you
okay I need to find someone
plate Burger we need to make a burger
wow
Bigger Burger girl latest lettuce
tomato
bun
no we forgot the what is it the meat
yeah
one
tomato
meat lettuce
wow
okay
you're done here
let's watch
is there no one like really there's
nobody in front of the CCTV
okay Watson Kiara is there
what are they doing I don't know
again
why
Watson and Kiara are
together okay but yeah hello what
happened what whenever
you want to say
it's cool
because I like previously when I was the
Imposter with Kobo
um and I died before her I was like
following her to try to cheer her on and
I saw her she would go to that you know
that place uh the Electrical uh where
there's like one task but it takes
literally one second to do it and when
she was the Imposter she would stand
there for ages thinking about what to do
next and I literally caught her doing
that thing now but like she was there I
said hi I ran away because I was
wondering well she's always there when
she's planning something I know no one
died but that's because she's a very
hesitant killer she did that before too
I was watching her and she passed gura
alone a million times and she just would
not kill gouda for whatever reason she's
very hesitant and she goes always always
sort of electrical to
as if she's doing that task but it takes
one second and she waited one minute
there believe me trust me bro I will we
don't have any proof I will I will found
because the only thing the only thing
that's like for me suspicious is that uh
she's she's being like awfully quiet
yeah she hasn't really said anything up
until like in the discussion at all do
you have a defense for yourself yeah do
you have a defense for yourself like why
are you so quiet or you know I'm always
quiet from the beginning
lullaby
[Music]
what if I really
do my task in electrical I mean why
mommy gonna be so that aggressive
and I know it takes one second I'm just
I'm just gonna say Ali and Watson are
always together
yes okay I'm gonna fold stories
[Music]
it's better for me to die though
hello
believe I'm the Imposter
wait should I accidentally protected
[\h__\h] okay
the other one's raining I think rain is
the other imposter I don't know
guys guys
be careful do we need power
they don't think we can all go because
there's like a little elevator thing
yeah
where are we hello okay so we're all
here or no all right can you hear me I
fixed it okay okay
[Music]
is the last one
I'm sorry
I got locked out
is it uh hold on don't leave me to help
me with the okay thank you I opened it
thank you okay
[Music]
hi shark
hello
[Music]
please thank you
I'll keep her safe
hold on you you better go when I Senpai
or else I will spill your your freaking
angel
there's like a lot of people here
everyone your big big size
I'm gonna take my magic trick oh
it must have been too good
I don't want to go over there because
then we can only go alone
together
no stay together
oh my God
where was it okay
where was it she said
she thinks where was it
um
I was from the Gap room and I passed by
when you are fixing the electricity and
I go to the shower and then I go to
records again okay I was in shower it
was earlier
I I I saw I saw I saw I think it was
Kiara and then Zeta is from the shower
too and we passed right okay
[Music]
where is the location of the body
I think there goes some of them going to
the up to go into the record and then
after so after that I saw man I bet
experience in classes
[Music]
well that was a good game
that was fun
[Music]
[Applause]
you guys you guys like playing girls
like you guys going to two two groups so
yeah which one should I follow me
[Music]
during the meeting was actually really
scary yeah
yeah yeah yeah
it was pretty good
I'm so proud
okay okay
[Music]
a great a great round
excellent I think
so as much as I want to continue playing
I don't wanna you know yeah maybe
another time we don't even need to play
on stream to be honest just together
points
we only have a full Cali costume though
and I'm wearing it so
December 20th to get all the Hall of
Life stuff yeah so hurry up
[Music]
let's start from the top again I'm there
how was it today oh yeah it was pretty
fun I won an imposter round and then won
all the crewmate rounds or pretty much
all of them so it's you know a pretty
good day pretty good game thank you for
inviting me Kiara thank you for setting
it up uh yeah thank you guys for playing
thank you for always sussing me even
though it's almost never with me
it's like your reflex now but okay I
just want to see your reaction that's
how I trust you okay
yeah it was so much fun
um I didn't get impulsive but it's fine
it's cool thank you so much see you next
time
[Music]
together thank you
you think knew it was fun yeah
and next we have Queen Clocky
oh yeah that's me whoopsies
um yeah so I think I was born to be
crewmate I don't like playing imposter
anyway so I had a good round um really
only one super good play in the
beginning and then everyone gangs up on
your boy that's fun just let it be and
then everyone killed you early thanks
yeah
whenever you like explained something it
was really easy to listen to you and
like yeah it's so convincing and you are
not lying I'm glad to us
I just gotta work on my longevity in the
game
but I'm going to do tasks and I love
doing tasks so it was fun thanks for the
invite here doing tasks I do
right I didn't but I made sure to be the
damn this best teammate that I possibly
could
you did great
honestly haven't been relieved I I was
scared to see what happens if it's like
especially like shape-shift there
killing all of you
oh my God that's her frying I wanted to
be thank God I really want to be a safe
shifter I haven't got that yeah
it's pretty rare God damn it well well
if you guys want to look like good on go
get the Cosmic Cube
we'll take over the world yeah yeah
Coco killer killer it was a statement
about your actions today how many times
were you imposter
three times four
[Music]
together with me because I cannot
um I don't know why but uh playing on
this room like uh there's
maybe pressure
a long time because uh first I I don't
really uh can make a good excuse or I'll
buy maybe in Bahasa Indonesia uh it's so
easy but
um I don't know uh you can always use
that as the excuse me I use that with
the JP knowing member please
you did a good job being imposter Kobo
you're really good yeah
thank you
just so many times
it was actually pretty funny because I
thought the reverse psychology would
work it did not
like I thought if I actually reverse
psychology guys like twice which means
if I actually asked us and say oh I'm
actually says haha that would make you
guys ah Ali's just messing around but
nah yeah
I feel like you Muna
[Music]
[Laughter]
especially because uh organizing be
source of collabs it's like a big hassle
been there and
well all the most utmost respect thank
you for accommodating all of us
[Music]
again after a long long time
for a second and go to oh mum is not
here anymore let's go today
oh hello yeah I start the stream naked
in the end the stream naked even though
I unlocked the outfit
please inviting me to the collab it was
really fun playing with you guys was fun
also to all the crewmates and also the
Imposter you guys were great
[Music]
it was so much fun I got a few imposters
how many
Supreme
uh two or three I don't remember yeah
it was fun thank you for those who
teamed up with me and thank you for
hosting it and I want to apologize
because my stream died six times
I think Zetta killed me more than any
other member I'm gonna remember that
right guys
[Music]
she can't talk well with that being said
I'm sure she had fun too yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
no voice
[Music]
oh yeah
you can try something oh there she is oh
how fast are we trying oh oh Discord oh
yeah
go to Discord everybody this course all
right all right um
[Music]
so I cannot hear anyone
here now okay
okay
it's okay you got your full outfit
outfit now Muna you did it
yay congrats
thank you exclamation mark
Oh I wanna buy you have fun Luna I have
fun uh actually uh the first time I'm
doing uh the to become an imposter with
I mean it's really fun
because I'm just the one that I'm I'm
usually afraid of whenever I become an
imposter
[Music]
I think I got to hear from everybody I'm
glad that we all came together for
another big Enid collab I think the last
one was Mario Karts
a year ago yeah
[Music]
yeah true
yeah let's do it people coming to watch
Power streams today
thank you
I'm having so much fun
yeah and I really don't have anything
else to say besides good job everybody
hope you had fun and yeah see you again
soon sometime
bye
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
laughs