[Music] I'm saying that everyone has a role to play,
so I'm not good enough to do anything,
but
if anyone did this to me, I'd
be devastated.  Little by little, the
flames are made big. Let's
put aside our hearts.
[Music]
Even if we are in a well-ordered and flat state,
Even we, who are uneven, will deepen our weapons.  Good
morning, hello, good morning, good night. The
door in my chest is the key that opens. I was never afraid of death when I was alone,
but I still can't believe it. I'm so depressed, I
hate you, I'm
so nervous.  I'm
hiding in the back of the house, and I'm going to
forget about this
[Music] I'm going to
open it
and let it out
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] Let's
build a spiritual home together.  I'm sure
this city will become the biggest planet anyone can
reach.Let's put our heart's feet on it.As if we were born wherever we are,
the world will come to us as if it were shining
.