[Music]
[
Music] [
Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
After
this The D block will start After this, the
limbs are crazy.  Nona
[Music] I
'm the type of person who doesn't like real races, so my fingers are shaking. If I'm going to tremble, I'll be shaking. Yesterday, I was able to run without being nervous at all, but now I'm really nervous. Art By the way, yeah.
During the race, I don't look at the comments and
run at full speed,
so I hope everyone is cheering me on with all their might.
Hahaha, I'm so nervous at a tournament like this.
[Music]
My heart is pounding, my heart is pounding. It's
crazy.  It's starting in a little bit.
Oh no, no matter what I do, I don't know what to
do. It's going to
turn out like this. I had a little time, so I ran around for a while, and then I wrote a new
name.  I've
changed things up a bit, like I
bought new sneakers on the day of the sports day. Is
this okay? Will
this actually make me feel better?
[Music] I wonder if it's
okay if I change it on the day of the sports day. I was
just trying to change my mood.  The
face is different,
right? The name is different too, so it's a scary doll. I should
turn on the air conditioner. It's
so hot.
[Music] I
wonder if this is just how nervous I am. It's so hot, I'm so nervous, and my nose is so hot.  I'm
having trouble breathing. Should I
drink some water? I'm the type of person who gets
nervous and has a stomach ache, but no matter what. I
just got a little stomach ache and it's showing in my body that I'm nervous. My heart is pounding, pounding, pounding, pounding, pounding, pounding, pounding. I can't
get nervous because I'm a sister, no, no.  I'll do my best,
I'll do
my best, I'll do my best, I'll have to do my best
Once it starts,
everyone's comments won't seem like money at first It's
cold  There's
some Reiki in the air, but it's a little
too cold. It
might start soon. It
might start like that. I'll
do my best.
After I see the name of the princess, I'll
let you all comment first. Goodbye, I
'm off to go.
No, I'll
take it off myself.  I'm
waiting for you to lie and drink yourself
What is your favorite course? Yeah,
isn't this random? Oh,
wait a second, it should be no
random. I'm sure it's not random.
But it's happened so many times,
baby
bar. It's
too much of a game of luck here.
[Music] I
want it. I
can't get the coin. I guessed
Shimane and came in
first place. You
also used the wrong guy. Puppy
stopped me.  No
[Music]
Ah, 3rd place, no, no, no, no,
I can't even talk. Don't be
serious. If you're not serious, you'll be reckless. It's
dangerous. Yesterday wasn't a mushroom.
Well, that's it. My
mouth is dry when I pick up coins
. That's it. I don't have enough coins to spare.
[Music]
What's the beach circuit like? I'm
so nervous that
I'm watching. [Music] I can't come with this. Oh wait.  I couldn't see what I was holding.
[Music] I
haven't gotten any coins.
Oh, I'm having fun with the bananas. I'm so
excited.
[Music]
This is it. I'm
glad the mushrooms came out.  My
heart is
pounding. Let's try the pulsating vibrations. I
wonder what I'm good at. My
long hands are getting numb. It
's F. What kind of course is this
? Is it the same one? This is the
only one with a shortcut.
[Music] Oh, I
'm keeping this a secret.  I'm so nervous
[Music] I'm
not good at drifting, I want to open up
[Music] A mushroom
unexpectedly came here
[Music]  I
pushed eroticism in a strange place
[Music]
How many years have I progressed so far? I think it's about
3. My heart is pounding, it's
been 3 days
[Music]
[Music] I
couldn't get it
[Music]
[Music] I want to
go too far.  I made a mistake.
Oh, I saw it.
[Music]
Congratulations.
[Music] I was
able to do it the last time we practiced, but
now it's
time for the actual performance.
[Music] I
did it, but I did it.
But I can do my best.
[Music]
The couple is too dangerous. I couldn't
get the item.
[Music]
Ah, it's decided. It
can't be too much of a guess. It's a huge hit.
This tension, this
tension makes the bow squishy.
Hahaha, this is this,
this is probably the last one Let's have a
quick toast
[Music]
[Applause]
Everyone go to the temple
[Music]
Grind dash failed
There's nothing left to do
[Music]  Mushrooms
quickly I was nervous
and couldn't stand it - Everyone
gave me a break - My
heart was pounding and the groom was so excited that I
tried my best to fail again It's
getting hot this time
[Music]
Thank you for your hard work We
had a practice session,
but it
's time for the actual event.  My
bow was shaking because I was spending so much time,
but my butt of practice
[Music]
has changed, so what can I say? It was good, I'm glad I
did it.
Thank you everyone for your support
[Music]
[Applause]
Now,
the frame will be closed and the broadcast will end.
Thank you everyone for the highlights and details.
[Music] I'll see
you all if you come to the broadcast tonight. See you all. [Music] [Music
] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]