[Music]
chicken again
and welcome to the hollow em advent
calendar
hi it has begun oh exciting day one is
taken care of by yours truly
so I want to explain a little bit first
so I got the idea for this like three
days ago because I was wondering why
there was no hello Ian calendar like
this
plant yeah you know when inspiration
hits me I easily get super motivated and
start planning like crazy so that's what
I did
even though many times it would work in
such a short time I quickly gathered a
team of people to help me create this
thank you for doing it in such a short
time with me I even bought a domain just
for this fancy right it's Hollow en
minus
[Music]
[Laughter]
I just bought it today I don't remember
yet
um yeah I never bought a domain before I
feel like so professional and like
business well
bad thing so obviously every day you can
come here to open one door per day the
others are locked you will not be able
to see them and then once you open the
door the video will come up and then you
can see who's there to greet you and
what they have to say
we are not 25 members so there might be
double appearances or pairings
um whatever but I am hoping everyone can
appear at least once
so this is my little present to the
hello Ian fans for the holiday season
Merry Christmas I hope you can come here
every day to get a little happiness from
us and get excited for Christmas whether
you're celebrated or not doesn't matter
let's enjoy the holiday season yeah
on another note just recently I made an
advent Reef on stream do you watch it
it was so fun and a really nice creative
output I started from scratch and
wrapped three branches around the reef
added candles and decorations like
flowers sparkly Stars pine cones and
yeah a lot of other stuff
I think it turned out so beautiful so
proud I feel like you could totally buy
that in the store like it looked so good
but like even better even better yeah I
don't think I'll ever buy one in the
store ever again
yeah the hot glue gun was good help once
again last year I made a gingerbread
house on stream you remember and then it
also helped a lot to make the
gingerbread house I wonder what I should
make next year
is there anything you do during the
holidays in terms of decoration or
preparation
let me be some baking some cookies or so
or decorating your whole house like I
see that a lot like in like American
shows
yeah like they have like crazy
decorations and they kind of start a
neighbor they blow war and like who has
the most decorations
the flashiest ones let me know the
hashtag hashtag Holo en Advent and don't
forget to add the URL to your Tweet of
this website so that other people can
find this page so page too
yay
so with that I wish you a lovely start
of the Advent journey to Christmas for
me by the way it's the 24th it's gonna
be the 24th we don't celebrate on 25th
only on 24th in the evening
but yeah I hope you will have nice
holidays everybody
please come here every day okay don't
forget it it's important if you don't
open the door gonna be so sad I'll be
waiting for you and the others will be
waiting too so make sure to share the
website okay
and in German we say
yay
[Music]