[Music]
big
guess what day it is today oh
why are you guys so little
[Music]
what's this
a small cute santa like
[Music]
hello
who's there
thank you guys
wait let me
zoom out
good to see you all how are you guys
[Music]
okay so welcome to my humble abode
i'll be showing you a special room today
um
just so we can chill and have some
drinks
and
take a few phone calls and
do a lot of exciting things
i still think i'm a little big wait
garagasu
move a little
okay
good be good
[Music]
now the grass is still peeking in the
corner wait
hello
welcome to
oh my bakery bathing real bob
that's a very pretty room
i need the prettiest room for
the satellite side treasure and
all the members who will be coming today
[Music]
thank you
very much for
all the fan art and
all the amazing
projects
that have been going on under my nose
literally
i am very overwhelmed and i also want to
um introduce them sometime today and
yeah there's also other surprises and
then
around the end of the stream will be
um i think it'll be
like 30 minutes half an hour before
a certain
original song coming out
hey hello
how's order how is order check i am
running i am running on little sleeve
i'm running on um
enthusiasm
what is good okay it's good
i'm nervous i um i'm nervous to talk to
you a lot of sympathize i haven't done
my hunger reps at all
i used to wanted to um do a slideshow
with all the fan art on
on my
hashtag but there were too many for me
just
to catch up on
i was like um i can't i can't include
all of them
you guys spoil me so much
i'm not sure if i'm nervous or excited i
am i think i am pretty excited um
there's a lot of things today that i am
super proud of
and i'm not good at chilling stuff
unless i'm 100
sure of
what i've done is pretty good
so yeah i hope that i hate that
well
well i've been
i've been spoiled today i'm going to
spoil you as well
[Music]
it's honestly a lot of people exactly
i need to breathe i need a drink
the first person
for the tatsumachi is gonna come in two
minutes so i gotta
i gotta
i gotta make sure
i i speak very sick
you wake up early to watch your stream
oh thank you very much
i guess that way
you'll be ready for the entire day
because um i'm gonna
make your day
like you made my day
take it easy
and a grassy
unicorn say
help me
okay they're some projects that i've
seen that um
i'll probably be playing
um in breaks and stuff as well i want to
actually
grace them to you guys because they're
absolutely amazing
and
yeah
yeah i think
we pretty much have our first
guest
very soon
oh who's it gonna be
did you think any guesses
love you to your satellites
[Music]
ring
is
[Music]
kissing the frame
i want to escape this frame
happy birthday solo thank you thank you
for coming to my tatsu
of course i'm so excited i'm so excited
for your song congratulations
you're gonna be
super super blown away i have a surprise
we're all the cancelling the song as
well
i'm so excited oh my gosh and i'm such a
fan of snails house
good taste
[Music]
um i do i have a little something for
you oil
it's a little
something um
i gave you a little break to hold today
oh not to eat can i eat it
uh apparently you've been eating lots of
planets today maybe you can spare earth
for some reason yeah i have no idea why
everybody keeps drawing me eating planet
planets but i'm like okay
i wonder what it tastes like
i guess if it's your birthday you might
as well eat some
spoil yourself a little bit
okay give me a second like i want to
show you guys the fan art that it's not
saving fine oh no
wouldn't most planets just taste like
rock though
i was thinking they kind of look like um
they kind of like truffles
oh
like they have
molten cores
that sounds so good like gooey gooey
salted caramel
yeah like um but like mud crust
oh
crunchy chocolate crust
sorry you allow me to eat the earth
well i can always bring it back to life
so i guess today
just
for today and you can have a nibble
this is your special day
it kind of kind of smells like kind of
smells like your hair like like a lime
sherbet
oh that's good
i thought i wondered how much it would
taste like mummy too
[Laughter]
oh
i didn't know maybe it kind of reminds
me of some kind of
um caramel latte granola and lime sugar
it doesn't sound that good together
it doesn't sound that good together does
it
it has like a an afloat you know like
the the sherbet
inside
oh
the drink the latte
um
the
visit
tls nurse knows how to make things good
no no
you aren't the
bread the bakery master
is there a cuter term than master i can
use
oh
you know i can think of wanting kira
ophono
not as cute as sauna
[Music]
okay i better i better scoot on out so
you can talk to your next guest on time
but happy birthday yeah let's talk
plenty later yes yes yes yes
congratulations
oh thank you
bye bye bye bye bye
[Music]
nervous can i can i do everything um
right i don't know i i didn't expect
anyone to draw anything for me
i'll just like hang it over um
yeah oh yeah i have some
um optional questions for people if they
wanted to
um answer them just over here
but they don't have to they don't want
to
yeah
my brain is just a food
he's gonna come next
oh yes i'm i'm like
i'm excited or am i nervous or anxious
or
like overwhelmed about um
so much love
ah
just give me a second
okay
they're coming they're coming
breathe in the deep love it smells like
it's still it still smells like lime
sherbet i think it's a picture
that sounds nice
who is this
caramel latte
smell oh
wait what are you eating
we have
i have you
you do hello
i'm sorry if i sound weird
no
it smells delicious
i
thank you
i i just i just realized a problem hold
on i have something for you
but i didn't save it on my phone so i'm
gonna i've got one i gotta save it hold
on
wait i'm panicking hold on i have to get
my ipad hold on
i got i got something for you i can do
this okay okay why are you more nervous
than me
i mean i have something for you i gotta
send it though i wasn't prepared to
think this through i'm really nervous oh
my
light is so fluffy
what you say sophie like
oh my goodness
i made you
wait wait i gotta show you this store
everyone
oh i got your stream open because my
sort of premium on my phone hold on
like it's like a two-for-one deal i get
both you an animal
and then like probably i want to i want
you to um pat animal
on the belly right now
okay i'm gonna have to make her roll
over
[Laughter]
she said happy birthday
did you hear that
i heard that i heard that
yes i heard that
wait can i do it again she might
he said super happy birthday
i'm very
blessed oh my goodness and this drawing
is so cute as well so do you
i guess like the answer to one of the
questions is what food do you think of i
am
red is like gonna be like the answer for
everyone but i was thinking of like oh
i have a different answer i was actually
thinking about it right before i joined
i forgot i called but they're like that
you know the cake rolls and they have
icing in them oh
you would be wonderful okay let's cover
it
if you cover in strawberries lemon zest
and blueberries
oh my god
that's so good
i picked this question because
i want people to call me food because i
i'll
um i take it as a compliment it's so
sweet okay girls are good and but it has
to have all three of those things
oh you'll you'll eat it you'll eat it
right satellites
sounds good they better
be better oh
i'm sorry for
being
chaotic i
think thank you for having me no happy
birthday
thank you
thank you for coming
i'm so excited for your song i was like
i thought it was releasing earlier and
then i still had to wait more if that's
okay because i'll wait for you
i'm excited for everyone to say my song
i'm excited for um you to see
what i have in store for you and then
yeah
well i have it as a reminder
uh
i'm going to now go back to watching
your stream because i can't watch on
call so
goodbye animals
and we'll see
everybody
bye
how do i leave i'm just sorry thank you
she's gone
i kind of imagined maybe with like um
five hands five arms is that cool
and and like two of them or three of
them which is padding animal
ah
okay
who's next i i don't like already
am i really exhausted with two people
i don't know if i'm ready to be spoiled
what do people are too like hear people
say nice things
oh yeah
yeah
i wasn't ready for this
good morning
happy birthday
to
you
[Music]
i
literally just woke up but
happy birthday how
has it
been
oh my god i literally woke up i joined
the
the call and the name was there and i
was like where am i
i feel like every single um birthday
talk so i've seen you in you just woke
up but it's always around this time for
us isn't it
yes
i don't know how you're alive no no no
no i i am like once um
after louise starts you later in the day
after like um everything that's gonna
happen i'm just going to sleep for
who knows how long
yes
okay sir they sent me
all people sweets and treats
what was that
no sorry i would say
whatever
congested right now
i'll give you some headphones like the
sunlights are giving me on
a like
excess amount of headphones so i'll give
you some as well
thank you if they got me um
yo whole hamburger stuff there were
macarons there was biscotti in all
different flavors and stuff
and um those brownies
oh my god i should have gotten you a
boost gift card
a beast give a card
i should have got a boost gift card
why boost exactly
i love i love i love pierce the
libraries exactly
amazing you are absolutely correct
oh my god
but yeah
i don't know i know that you really like
sweets and i was like i got this side
which one to get you i just got you you
just got me everything what the heck
if you think about it it's very chaotic
and i approve of it i get i get a bite
of everything
but anyway i'm so excited for you
oh
i'm so excited for you excited for my
song because i'm like i'm like so
excited to release the song because
everyone else is excited and you're
excited and
i'm really excited i'm so excited
don't hurt that um
you made my day especially with the
sweets and i hate that
oh don't eat it in one day
i was like when she said it to me i was
like dinner
oh no
[Music]
do i get an answer question
uh yep um you can pick
which question you would like to answer
what's your first impression of me what
food do i remind you of and what food do
you think you are or where would you
like me to take you
to in this universe we're going together
i actually want you to answer what food
do you think i think you're like uh
i think the first thing i thought when i
saw that question was you remind me of a
souffle
[Music]
and fluffy and sweet
i love silly
i'm sorry my answer is not as cute any
as yours but i also thought of like
maybe maybe a candy cane maybe a candy
cane and like a cherry tomato on it
like a root
oh
yeah it's very chaotic but they're so
sweet
that'd be a rainbow candy cane he can be
a rainbow candy cane using hands do you
know people didn't know that rainbow
candy cane existed what
this is like oh it's like an australian
thing like very like
red
like guys there's another rainbow candy
canes
rainbow carrot cakes are the best one
aren't they usually the tutti frutti one
the tiny fruity one
yeah
it's so much better than the peppermint
one
uh
fairy kane
i think oh my gosh some people oh they
seen they existed oh
yeah we also have like blue ones and
pink ones or strawberry candy canes
how how do some people just live
in the world with only one flavor of
candy cane
how come how come in um other other
nations nobody have ever thought about
other flavors of candy canes
because
everything is
different
down under
the way we think is different
because we don't exist
we're upside down and everything
there's no direction in space so you're
always on sunny side up for me
[Music]
definitely be up for
the song release
[Music]
i'm going back to sleep
jk i'm gonna be watching a stream
[Music]
bye-bye
i love you babe
[Music]
uh
but who do we have next
especially after she said she was
watching the stream
you can't keep her waiting
[Music]
oil
um
alert ring ring resist
ring ring ring
um
she's in there she's in the room that i
don't hear her
oh yeah
[Music]
give me a second um ian because
technical
difficulties
oh yeah
i'm immediate please
it was the phone you know maybe
she is maybe she is
screaming at the top of her lungs
but in a different universe
ah
they're gonna go um fix something at the
moment
uh
[Music]
i think i'm wearing it uh just give me a
second
oh
let's see
one two three four
[Music]
okay
okay she'll be back
we got three we got three um three girls
without
the end curse
showing up
okay
okay she'll be back
oh pop it back is here pull me back go
hello
oh
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
is a big brain
really my breath
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
actually
yeah actually
you you are my type
[Laughter]
you are the best you are the best
i think so
i'm i'm i have little navas
a little nervous
okay
you
what
recently you recommend me
[Music]
pouring for encountering
snack
snook
ah
prairie bread fairy red
yes yes i recommend you fairy bread from
australia
yeah
um
uh
actually i
i i have
a
lit little weight
i have gained
[Laughter]
a very bad
active active girls
[Music]
i think
you are you are you are ice is shiny
and your smile is brightening
[Music]
girl
[Applause]
[Laughter]
i see i think you your smile
you match
that smile
[Laughter]
[Music]
if
not now
i
really smiling because
you
i told you
[Music]
my english
please
please story
please surely
um
dog so i can hug
hey guys today is celebrate day
um she got her fat from eating fairy
bread
yeah
beauty bread
together
[Laughter]
[Music]
i celebrate you
really thank you happy birthday
i hope you are
this year is more happy
thank you so far senpai thank you yeah
i'm very happy you came today thank you
so much
i'm
so happy i was able to talk to you
thank you sadness
[Music]
seriously
i must
eat
curry bread with you
yes please
in dream tonight yes
together we become fat
yeah
[Laughter]
pretty
[Music]
bye
that was so much fun we ended up talking
for so long
hi happy birthday
[Music]
yeah
i want to gift for you
just moment please
here
[Music]
my paint skill painting skill is no good
but
i
make eye for it
make effort
for you
thank you
today today is louie's birthday
yeah yes japanese in japan
yeah in japan
so same time is birthday
right now in thailand
[Applause]
[Music]
so
yes yes
i love the snow dome so i want to
give to you snow dome
just galaxy snow dome
snow globe yes no grove
[Music]
okay this is
so you are an apple pie
yeah like apple pie i love apple pie
what what food am i
what bread
yeah
great
[Laughter]
okay i i want to
talk
about you
yes fast impression oh
impression
what is what is my first name impression
i
love your voice
sweet and salty
and your personality is very kind and
lovely
so i love your
personality
isn't this you
your
your personality is so lovely and kind
and you always have a soft voice
are very kind
when i
talk
to a kid with
you um
just
um
after i debuted
once
again
when i talk with you i want to
improve i want to improve my english
because i want to
talk a lot with you
so
i want to talk with you a lot too
[Laughter]
and i want to collaborate with you
oh yes please
just like a game
or something or talking it's okay
i want to collaborate with you yes
please that's clever
[Laughter]
okay
okay i decide
for you
yes
crowd together okay yes please
thank you
thank you thank you for inviting me
oh thank you for your party inviting me
to your birthday party as well
i will i will see you okay
yeah yeah yeah i'll see you again and
see you again
[Music]
my twin my sister
[Laughter]
she is
okay
see you later i'll see you later
[Laughter]
bye-bye
okay i think
we might have one more person before
announcements
[Music]
louie's so sweet oh my goodness
i haven't even started eating sweets but
i already feel like a sugar rush
she told me this wasn't food but i
started eating it anyway
ring ring ring
ring ring
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh yeah goodness you sound just like
they
uh
i i just woke up
and i
i i'm just sleepy i'm good why are you
just a moment pay your face said the
exact same thing and listen uh
um
what were you doing
last
night
honor reason
oh
um
no i was just sleeping
and this is not suss at all
i swear i was
i was just sleeping because
because
i felt sick so it's not
not
not anything like what chad is
chat or you are assuming right now yeah
i'm not assuming anything it's it's just
chat believe me
it's just yes
that question came with like a a very
awkward silence
yeah i mean it's always like this i feel
like every single time we do like you
know we do birthday call-ins like
it's always
i always notice that phase i always just
woke up too and it's always it's just a
coincidence we swear it's just a
coincidence
oh
just like
we just don't wake up early that's
like every single time yeah
well i can see it i can see it happening
yeah i mean
yeah you get you guys do your birthday
streams early
for some reason and for some reason i
mean a close a closer sort of time of
same thing with you guys but i still
ended up doing my birthday stream like
really early
i know
you guys are such early birds oh no no i
just didn't sleep
oh oh
oh my goodness
some sleep really
all the exciting things today and
um i was just very excited to get to
talk to you as well yay
such a cinnamon roll
i like that i like it
yeah i was looking at what food do i
remind you of some just like cinnamon
roll also because i don't know that many
names of bread
thank you
it reminds me of have you ever tried
cinnamon roll from
um
i guess maybe they don't have this in
australia but there's like
oh what was that
place called the cinnamon roll
store like it only sells cinnamon rolls
um
wait let me look at this um
is this in japan
no no no no this is in america
i've seen it yeah
they're so big and like literal calories
yeah have you ever tried cinnabon i've
never heard of it before wait cinnamon
local bakery near you this looks really
good though
it looks like it's drenched in glaze
it is but i do want to
try it sometimes it looks like a cake
oh my goodness
yes i loved ordering the very unhealthy
let me say i don't i haven't had one of
these in like the last 10 years but
um
they're really huge they're high in
calories and if you order them at this
shop like right there they're very warm
and fluffy
i really like it
doughnuts i do like glazed doughnuts
like um yes so and then like donuts is
just like cinnamon-ish so i wonder if
it's similar but better because it's a
roll yeah i like the texture there's no
fluffy and stuff
when it comes to donuts like i like the
glazed ones too but i tend to just like
like chocolate glaze on it
but like i feel like donuts are just
really nice in the way that they're
cheap
i really like oh mister i really like
mystery donuts i really like this on the
ring you guys do you guys have no i
don't know
when i was living in japan i i love
pondering so much that's all i order
whenever i go to mr jonas i just order a
bunch of pondering cause i'm wondering
there's something
really good about it because like yeah
the texture the texture like just like
the um little little grooves
yeah yeah yeah it's like you eat one
groove in one bite yeah it kind of
reminds me of my hair
yeah
oh my god it does i didn't think i i
didn't think you would we would be able
to talk about pondering because that's
like my favorite donut in the world oh
my god i love pondering so much
i
can miss it so
pondering together next time
please like you know a hundred years
[Music]
i remember the last time i went into
japan i was like yes i'm gonna go um get
pondering after such a long time but
then i think uh miss doughnut closed
pretty early i thought because in japan
they usually open up pretty late so i
thought i'll just get it like after i've
done all my shopping and all but then
you know that's so weird
he closed early i was like oh my god my
pondering then like even day even day um
the store was closed i started running
to the store
like i agree
it's just in japan like i do notice that
stores open so much later than stores
and like other places like these open at
like 10 a.m or 11 a.m oh yeah it's just
like yeah people don't wake up that
early here i guess it's kind of my image
and then they close early so yeah the
amount of hours the stores open is
usually cut a little bit shorter because
of the late open
ah but yeah pondering is so good it's
cheap you know mr donuts always has like
those campaigns where it's like less
than 100 yen per
and then like mr donato usually has to
collab slow um
have you ever seen like the pikachu
class
i have pikachu they were very famous for
their pikachu collab donuts because they
looked they looked scary
oh i haven't seen her like it really
depends on like if you order a pikachu
doda it might look very cute or it might
look like it came straight up like a
horror film
i see like the picture and then i see
reality
it's so it's so scary it's so funny
the difference because the pikachu's
that they they sell it's like
yeah it's the literal horror materials
it's not like what that is it doesn't
look like eyes
yeah like what happened to the eyes like
they get smushed like how do you even
mess up eyes this badly
[Laughter]
but at least you from the difference in
the face every single time you can tell
that it's all handmade
there's a slight difference with each
donut
[Laughter]
but yeah
ah
please do donuts it's like said they
don't have those there they're very good
thank you for telling me i'm a donut
you're a very sweet plundering too
yay
compliment i've ever seen yeah it can be
like a very one the plundering covered
in um very
belly
bailey i love i love fruity flavors i
love fruity flavors it just goes well
with um bread in general
yes when it comes to plundering i always
get the strawberry ponder
perfect so we can do that next time we
hang out in
japan also can't wait for your merch
announcement
soon
it is happening very soon it's happening
like right after you actually okay then
yes i will i won't interrupt the
merchant announcement and i will watch
let's talk more about pondering later
alrighty then happy birthday son i hope
you haven't thank you
have a great virtual meeting
i love you too
[Music]
bye chris
bye bye
we just talked a lot about food we had
this hour
my brain is just um
sweet good
yum
friends
good times comfy room comfy satellites
okay
let me just take a bit of a breather
before
merch announcements
okay firstly i gotta kick you all out
before before we start on our mesh
get out of here
okay are you ready
so
um firstly right after i explain
the merch
i believe mid-stream the
the story is gonna open
and i just gotta make sure i get the
information just give me a second
so yeah um
i will show you what i have been cooking
up in my bakery
in just a second and then
um 15 minutes passed the sale will open
and it's all stuff that um i personally
want myself
oh it's all very very cute stuff
and as i say something very very special
as well
okay i got the i got the information
give me a second oh
okay
ha ha
i will now unveil
the goods
okay though um the illustration is done
by my non-other than my uh the best papa
packer papa pekka in the world papa
pecker well the best papa backer in the
world is obviously papa packer
keep
rape
oh pastel
and i'm also eating pizza in my bed
and
um okay let me just show you let me just
show you the stuff
okay here's the birthday match complete
set
we have a space taste blanket
um i'll show i'll talk about each
individual item as we go
let's get this bread
look
red
it dog plushie
and then um
you've been seeing this cup
on my table
this very very adorable cup
and then we also have um
a cotton
emblem as well
of
um a certain
sauna
one birthday voice and the extra
for um
buying the entire set
is a clear folder with the artwork
that pop a packer do with a lot of love
and care
um plus i got papa packer right
and oh gosh i want to i want to um
oh gosh about puffleback is hot
oh
okay here's a here's a clear folder
so um the clear folder
has this
um design inside as well
so you get this clear folder for free
for getting the entire set
and um
i will show you the artwork on the other
side side slide
so i wanted to make a blanket because um
i wanted something really cozy and
huggable and fluffy
and then i just thought it would be very
toasty
didn't shh
okay please please look at this art
please look at this eye this um the
bread dog flushies there's everybody
there's a references to everybody in
halloween can you can you spot
can you spot them oh
very touristy
[Music]
oh yeah yeah yeah there's a there's a
person saying feed in chat there they
are
this isn't the only thing that's super
super crazy and comfortable
i know
i want you guys to stare at this odds
it's like um i don't want to spoil it
you guys okay please look at all the
details that have been put into it
um
i'm very very honored
i don't i'm just very very happy and
this blanket
will toast you up
is that navy or over there
okay so the other really really tasty
thing
i'm just wonky i just want you to stare
at this art for a bit
wait
you see you see crooney's eye right i
just have to point that one out do you
spot cranny staring at you
lovely
and then it's just very overall soft
and a work of art and yeah thank you
very much papa parker i love you daisy
okay um
you'll get to see you'll get to see this
artwork more
um when the shop opens so please stare
at it please worship it
and
um if you get the blanket please wrap
yourself up in it and become space taste
okay our next really really really tasty
thing
that's right
now i had um specifics about this
plushie this bread dog plushie
um
i wanted it to be face plantable
so when um after a long hard day's
day of work or
you know after so much study at school
or um after you're just very very
exhausted
you just grab this bread dog out of your
suitcase or whatever and then you place
it on your desk and you face right into
it
and i made sure that it was long enough
so um yes it's very good for face plants
it's like a pillow exactly i wanted it i
wanted it to um be able to
you'll be able to rest your head on it
because i think face pla i think i i
just want to face plant my face into a
bread dog so
um i'm gonna make that into a reality
and now you all have to do that too
most important qualities there so i made
it very square and um very long
and there's also does it say yeah with
the gradient with the gradient printing
and the space printing on it
it's just so cute
and i'm excited to have one myself
okay next
is the universe half full or half empty
glass
i generally really like collecting
glasses because i don't know they're
just very handy especially if you can't
be bothered washing all your glasses so
you just get another one and another one
another one it just kind of piles up on
your on your desk and then
um you have too much to wash now so you
just get your bread dog and your face
plant and think you have too much to do
in your life but yeah
the point the point of this pattern is
that you feel it you fill the glass with
um
a colored drink
and it looks like space because there's
star patterns on it
and bread and then look there's me
and there's a breadbox that's you
the pattern is so cute isn't it
because i i designed this so um i
that's why there is a quality seal of
cuteness
especially if you um pour pour a dark
blue or
um hope soda
into the cup
it'll look like space and i think
that'll be really really cute
chalky milk
wouldn't that be so cute
okay
and here is the mission emblem
on a staple
of the satellites going on missions for
when
i
when i'm collecting head pads
this is a no-brainer isn't it
so yeah i hope to see a lot of
satellites wearing the mission patches
mission emblems
um i believe
there's a pin on it yes there's a pin on
it
and then um it's quite big
it's like 100 millimeters times 100
millimeters
and so yeah i'm actually very excited
for this
it's all just
stuff that um
i went through i went through a lot of
ideas in order to get stuff done i think
it's very very cute
okay so here is the entire merch list
again
so there is a birthday merch complete
set
um with the extra of the clear file with
the artwork on it that pop-up packaging
and then for individual sales we have
the space toast blanket which i think
you should get so let's get this bread
plushie
the red top plushie for um when you want
to faceplant and then
it's a universe half full half empty
glass that i have right here and i'll
just take a sip
oh yes
half full
and then um a freshly baked mission
emblem and what's this wait i didn't
remember this
a normal
nation first voice pack wait no i didn't
do that i was like
um i made a voice pack
of the ancient language where i tell you
sweet
embarrassing um
words
i talk i talk close
into your ears in the
um
ancient language
and i do have a bit of a sample for you
it's a little embarrassing
but um yeah i do have a sample for you
give me a second
this is embarrassing
[Applause]
oh
yeah sale that's i see
i have also included
um me whispering soft
scandalous words in your ears in the
ancient language voice pack
yes sir
oh my goodness i think the links i think
the links for the merch is like open
right now wait a second
yes yes yes okay so uh
[Music]
what should i do i should probably add a
video description
i know
you do
youtube's
down because there's so many chat
messages okay so um
the official live site i will pin it
on chat if i can catch it in time
it should be live like right now
and does this work
[Music]
yeah yeah i think
it should be up right now
and then um
unless i try to i'm not sure if i can
edit the stream while i'm streaming can
i
if the stream suddenly ends i'm sorry
okay so um if you refresh i think the
the slides for the merch have also been
added to the video description
yes sir um
i worked very hard on this and um papa
becca has made such a amazing
illustration as well
and um i hope you guys have a lot of fun
with it and
um i hope that you
have many face plants in the future
[Music]
thank you very much
happy birthday so now thank you
thank you so much for um all your
presents and all and just like spoiling
me so much
i hope that i can make you
i can like give back some of the
kindness and
um support you've given me today and
oh gosh i want more than
i do kind of want more than um
one bread dog plushie
i kind of want a wall of them so i can
just sort of dive into them
wouldn't that be nice
[Music]
thank you very much
everyone
okay i gotta get ready for
resuming calls and call in
thank you son happy birthday no thank
you
there's more to come in this stream
there is more i was supposed to
play some videos but i ended up having
so much fun talking to with everyone
why was i even nervous everybody is just
so nice and holy alive
[Music]
i guess it's time to bring you guys back
home
welcome back to my room
i will answer um
and place this here
i'm so spoiled
should i put this all
i'm back inside equisol welcome back to
my humble opponent
what drinkable you like will you like
bomb
whatever is inside here blueberry
blueberry cirdle
the cinnamon cinnamon roll slurry soda
[Music]
water
water blue water
repeat after me water
[Music]
okay we're resuming resuming calls
okay i will prepare my heart
hello
i could do
what you could do
you saw i said i said peekaboo but
because i waxed as well they say um
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
kirby
i love korea so much
and i love i love you all i love
watching your play through as well i was
just so happy finally
someone elian has been playing curvy too
ah groovy that was such a good game i
saw you got the 100 complete on it i
have to
[Laughter]
cooby and i'm actually looking at a
picture of your
car b
car bk
i should have saved you a slice
actually it's small looking though i
probably could have eaten the entire
thing i would have eaten it like when
kirby inhales the vehicle i would have
mouthful molded the entire thing should
i make you
since i did launch i can do it again i
am literally a provider should i do it
next time
wait a second your birthday is later
it's just like an affair isn't it
oh that's true wait i should be able to
make you the kid because today's your
birthday
and then we both could eat it we could
share yeah you all mouth were married
just
eat
the cake
yeah
sharing is caring
happy birthday sana thank you
awesome
thank you always
being
so fun
thank you always being so fun and so
nice to me
and of course i never told you it is but
i ended up using your icon for discord
like since ages ago wait wait the one
you did for passport out
victor of me i've
i've been looking at that it's like i
just i just kind of did it a long time
ago and i was like
too shy to say like hey girl i used it
i'm so sad i keep looking at this art i
actually just looked at it like the like
a few hours ago like
did i draw that that looks like it was
like such a long time ago
oh i okay well my sneaking suspicion was
true
it's so cute
um
thank you i'll give you a hug because i
remember during that stream you said
that
you wanted a hug
i did i could always use a hug i like
hugs
bugs are nice hugs are warm well you
smell like bread
oh yeah yeah i'm surrounded by bread a
lot of bread
all the time
irresistible
okay i have to mention this though
because i've been watching your stream
right
my i
i
i immediately went to cronie's eyeballs
smack in the middle of the artwork
oh
you saw it let me see it it's tiny right
i wanted everybody to see it because
once you see it you can't unsee it it's
right in the middle
i bet if you um
put the perfect ratio on it
um the perfect designer ratio on it you
just see it
um
you just see courtney's eye right in the
middle
don't let her hear that
coney your perfect eyeball is perfectly
in the center of the perfect art because
crony you are here and it's perfect
everywhere and above and beyond for this
artwork i thought wait really
i thought it was feet your feet were
showing and i figured that's what i was
like
well if you want to use that means
you're in it twice i guess i don't know
oh wait i need to go look harder now
do you see it do you see it
do i see it
oh i see it's connie's eyeball
is
i'm looking
can you is it just like you can't look
away from korea's eyes now
maybe oh wait i see i see i see
ah
me tell me this
i see it i think
i don't know if i should spoil it for
everybody else though
you guys gotta find it yourself all
right
gotta play i spy oh that's right
i love your birthday merch this is so
cute
i love you too i mean
what
yeah it's okay it's just you and me here
let's be honest with each other
yes i guess i i eat a pound of
strawberries today
look we're friends now we're best best
friends
we could be love
love
um
let me let me speak um sweet
ancient language words into your ears
come closer
i'm right against you
exquisite
absolutely exquisite linguist you are
[Music]
now i'm turning funny colors right now
the the rouge variety
oh
wait i see can i answer one of your
questions you have on the oh no go ahead
my first impression of you yes yes what
is your first impression of me
your debut stream was
so was so good
i remember
i don't know if i don't know if i can
talk about the making of necessarily i
won't go too much into that but it was
so creative and seeing it all come
together and all the work oh thank you
production value was so good it was like
watching a film
all the tweets thank you thank you so
much for fighting the tweets
i remember sitting wondering how
how far how far she should
too how
than this i don't know
oh so good
thank you so good you're so creative
and you're so sweet
um it drops off from the senpais of
course
no i'm a little turd honestly
i'll say it must not be for me
possibly honestly i'm interested from
ina
i'm into cursor so it's okay
you know if you like my debut stream
we'll get along
[Music]
can i reverse eat so i can eat him again
chewy little wormy
get over here yeah the garage
oh wait i don't want to take up all your
time now i'm sorry for my ramblings
happy birthday sana hello thank you very
much for coming to my topsy
and
yeah
i'm so happy
and thank you for being here keep doing
you
keep um
yo just keeping your visionary
happy birthday happy
happy happy originally
ted i mean what nothing wait what
legendary bird turd
legendary
wait am i the legendary turd
yeah it's like a like a legendary
pokemon but a turd
oh
no
[Music]
i would
okay i'll go
i'll put my legendary turned self
before i start stinking up your bakery
goodbye
[Music]
shiny grouper
are you not
taking much longer than five minutes
the conversation was uh
rated r
yeah no brain conversation
oh he says ring me
[Music]
thank you oh my goodness finally the day
has come it's your birthday yes the day
it is it's your birthday
oh gosh
my best birthday on earth
is it with
you
is it
that's it
i i am a baby
with youtube
defeat this baby will you feed this baby
some milk
ah
this is going south in
1 800 babysitter 1 800 babysitter
[Laughter]
why do i keep doing this whenever i talk
to you
yeah you know she gave me um can i talk
about this
why doesn't you say
of course you can't
okay
i i i don't know what to say except
happy birthday because i feel like
i feel like i've already said
i feel like you have everything
it's like i was like if you say anything
nice i'm like yeah yeah i've heard that
before
that's like that time whenever whenever
i talk have to talk to you whenever i
have to talk
because i've already said all the nice
things already you know
i gotta
you know
balance it out
how about how about you um answer one of
the questions then pick one
pick one oh you pick one you know me
i don't like choosing stuff i feel like
i'm already in there like what was that
all of them
okay okay what do you think okay okay
how about this reverse card what do you
think i'm gonna answer for one of the
questions
i'll tell you if it's correct or not
um i think
[Music]
your first impression of me
a hard worker
but now it's just poop
girl
i should say you're a hard-working poop
okay i'll i'll probably i want to say
something else to describe it but i
think that would be too much for chat so
um i'll leave that to their imagination
but
um
yeah i mean i mean first impression man
actually it's it's more like
more like a
what is this
talented creature
you know who who missed
is this talented hard-working
ball of energy
do you know what they say about
opposites
what
say it
what do you mean say it what do they say
about offices
um
they say that if uh you know left and
right are opposites but if you go left
all the way
i don't know the difference between left
and right still i thought i was cured
but i wasn't
so then again you know west and east
more than left and right i think
and i know left and right more than
western east
we bounce out it's fine
okay okay i kind of get that that's why
we're opposites
yeah but then again your space so there
isn't really a direction in space
so it's all right
forgive you
i don't know why i'm forgiving you but i
forgive you i don't know why i need you
i need to say sorry or okay
he's like yes yes apologize
no no no
you are you sorry i asked you to feed me
sorry
i said
weird dory
i'm sorry for making you say sorry
[Laughter]
oh my
well um
wait did you did did you want to shoot
the thing
majiggy or not
it's fine i was joking when i said no
oh oh can i
yeah
okay um um
are really really cute mug
i gotta say the shipping cost more than
the item
yeah that's the thought that yeah
i guess i kind of made a platter with um
stuff that bears this and
um so i do have a photo of it
i ended up yeah you know
bam and i kind of you know balanced each
other out somehow i gave you the
utensils and she gave you the stuff put
inside
let's see
she gave me this super super pretty mark
there's like a moon on it and um there's
gold foil
cheating stars in it
and i make coffee jelly with it
coffee jelly is so good
and then um yeah here's some of the
sweet stuff that bears say dave i was
thinking i'll eat this platter during
the original song premiere
oh yeah
it's really soon right it is pretty
important i mean i i
i totally have not heard it yet
or have seen anything of it i am very
looking forward to it
you're to be playing all the way yes oh
my goodness oh my goodness i'm going to
be am i going to be launching into space
is that what's going to play soccer
you know taco's temple can exist
everywhere space is no exception
i'll be waiting for you
okay say no more
all right well um i don't know how your
timing is going but it's just like i've
been talking too much and um
like it's only only a few minutes behind
it'll be all right i think i shouldn't
let the next person
i hope you have a wonderful wonderful
wonderful
i can't think of any other adjectives
day
and uh
okay
[Music]
did you wash today did you brush your
teeth oh she's gone never mind she can't
answer
she left before i gave her a cheer
okay okay no more
delays
let's call the next person in
[Music]
i'm just a little bit behind but um
yeah i think we'll catch up reveal
okay okay ring ring
are you gonna give her a cheerios llama
she's
well she's not here anymore
what should i do
[Music]
sorry for making you wait a little
it's okay i enjoyed it i watched it from
earlier
oh embarrassing so you heard me talk
they heard me talk embarrassing things
about
like like
i heard that yes i heard so many
languages of
my kin
[Laughter]
anyway happy birthday
blinky
thank you
tail
you know what because it's your birthday
i will
give you a free pass for the whole year
of muffling my tale
exclusive can i even face plant
intellect
yes
yes special offer santa only
yes thumbs up
thank you
thank you today is it good
so it was a very good day
yes
[Music]
oh my god really well yes you're you're
you're such a kid i wish i had a huge
tail right here a huge fluffy tail like
you i think i think i'll hug myself
you're such a cutie and such a nice girl
i really like being around you a lot too
oh same i love the energy you always
have and you always like do whatever you
want to do
i love your giggles so much or is this
on fire like
well that's that's just what squirrel
does girl gotta do what squirrel do oh
mother
the squirrel alive sounds like a good
life i wish
and i will learn the ways
yeah
i'll teach you the way
[Music]
also
i really like your
fluffy merch oh my god it's so nice i
really like face planting right
so i really love it
it's just so yeah face planting is um
very important when you're thinking
about
fluffiness and your tail is inspiration
oh my god yeah
also it would be nice if it smells like
bread like fresh baked bread i'd love
oh
that's so comfortable
it's gonna it's gonna make me hungry
yeah my head has been just like food all
the time
i do kind of i don't know if it's
because it's a squirrel but you'll when
i think of a food you remind me of it's
like peanut butter
i do love peanut butter i'd rather
rather like nutella or hazelnuts there
i i like anything about
oh my god i shouldn't i shouldn't have
say this but
but i know i know you can see it coming
i like anything about nuts oh okay
um
yes
you like blended on my forehead already
nuts oh goodness
oh
my
are hazelnuts
i like oh my container nuts
or pistachio nuts
i am
a cashew kind of person cashew nuts
yes what about you though do you like
any specific nuts i think cashews tastes
really good in um
savory cooking
specifically
especially
i was like oh that sunday would be good
right now
yeah you know what i just ate one flower
for breakfast
yeah like can you imagine a squirrel
waking up like eating a eating a huge
[Music]
i think
is it easy time is it isn't my time i
think it is time thank you universe
thank you for inviting me
i will
let you go but i won't let you tell her
okay
[Music]
stop a chat stop a chat stop stop saying
that in
word
okay who's next
we are just a little bit
um
i think i think we're good okay
yeah we are just a little bit um running
out of time but we'll catch up
okay
ringing
who's this
good morning
good morning good day
good day happy happy birthday sana
thank you ali
gosh
you're
all right now
like you're older i can't i can't even
think of over here like being a year
older i've just always been a baby
like 16 16 billion something years i
still think you'll think i'm just like a
goo girl
it's still a good gaga even after 16
million years
[Music]
you are a baby
very cute baby thank you um
you're always sophie's mother
right
yeah you call me a good baby
i feel weird
would you like to be my baby also
[Laughter]
yes
yes i do
[Laughter]
let's go
yeah
okay um anyways i kind of
it's a little bit messy but i kind of
drew something for you oh really
it's very last minute because i woke up
super late
hawaii
it's super super i'm like crying like a
baby
oh my sweet little
a baby
tingly
thank you
you're welcome
um you know i'm really looking forward
to hear a new song premiering later
oh excited
yeah i was a really really big fan of
your last original song it was a sparkle
you know
i know it's like i noticed i kind of
kind of sneak your
aliens in
[Music]
oh yeah
i don't know if you can tell but
i'm a very big fan of you and during the
rap course i kind of put the bunny in
the crab
your bunion crab without their consent
where have they been
well they've been on adventures
they've been on adventures you are also
there if you if you didn't notice at the
very end
i'm sorry i saw that
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
yeah i saw yeah i saw you and phil was
like well i want to
i want to make a song as sparkly as that
one day kind of
it will be a lot more sparklier
i assume
definitely looking forward to it
because i have a big fat car i'm your
mother
i think
oh i think
that's it
um
i won't let you
i won't keep you
thank you very much for wishing me a
happy birthday thank you very much for
this present
you're looking so cute
have a great birthday
it's great thanks to things like
that
thank you
okay
happy birthday again bye bye
what is up why am i whenever i talk to
someone it just goes off the rails
goes somewhere i don't know where it
goes
ring ring
fingering
is next
[Music]
this is
a celery banana
[Music]
hello can you hear me
i can hear you um perfectly clear i can
hear your banana noises perfectly clear
oh can you can you drink like a banana
what what do bananas like
what is the cry
it's been a while hello have a birthday
thank
[Music]
i am going through a lot of emotions
everybody is just so nice including
you
and everybody an id
and um
i don't know i'm feeling a lot of things
i'm feeling nervous for
um stuff that's being
released later
i feel extremely spoiled and happy i
feel um
extremely blessed to be surrounded by um
so many
amazing talented people
um
i also feel very nervous
talking to them as well but everybody's
so nice i end up talking to them for too
long
i'm sorry to make you wait a little
no it's okay
how do you feel when whenever your
birthday comes because i've also lived
for so long you know obviously not as
long as you
and whenever my birthday comes it it
feels kind of weird but how about you
[Music]
well
it was my first birthday in holiday live
and i still feel like a baby
oh
baby sauna yeah i still want to be a
spoon fed
baby toast
i still i still want a lot of head pads
will you help pad me
oh
obviously um
um do you have your limiter on right now
i do just like um hit that around the
limiter
cool i'll i'll i'll do that i'll do that
i'm i'm sending you virtual pet pets
thank you i know
i don't know if you can see it i don't
know if you can see it but i'm sending
you virtual hat pets right now
i feel like
i feel it i feel i feel bananas
yes
you can see my banana hands
in your in your toasty head
do you feel it do you feel my banana
hands in your toe hat
yes i guess
that collab that you mentioned i was
thinking do you want to play donkey kong
because um there's donkey kong
multiplayer in a nintendo virtual
console i think
it's like i sort of just like um scroll
through it and sort it there
i was thinking my first time playing the
game but it's my first time playing it
as well i think as well but
it has to be something banana reiterated
i saw another banana game but the dinner
um internet multiplayer
it was like
i thought like i was gonna um play it
with you but then i saw donkey kong and
i think that would be fun together
yeah i'm okay with nintendo games it's
gonna be my first time though so if you
don't mind now let's go
yes please um you're probably gonna have
to carry me because it's also gonna be
my first time
it's gonna be we're gonna we can we can
like show off the power of banana hands
baby's first time
i still have yet to listen to your
original song
oh it's coming i haven't listened to it
uh the envy is coming out pretty much
after the stream
yeah
i can't wait
um
i was like super confident that um
everybody will like it and all that i'm
also quiet
honored embarrassed to hear it from
um senpai as well
so thank you
thank you
thank you so much
no thank you for having me have a happy
birthday thank you for coming to the
tatsu
happy birthday thank you for the
headphones thank you for everything
it's okay i'm not gonna disappear
i'm not gonna disappear after this
we can still tell you know yes please we
gotta play donkey kong
someday yeah
you're making it you're making it sound
like i'm gonna disappear
really like
like the senpais and those in the sport
animes
oh when i get to see you in the sky that
um the other one is gonna
usually usually it's always me in the
sky like in fanart because sauna is so
big
i can see that
thank you so much
thank you so much it's close happy
birthday
let's have a collab someday
and get bananas strong
bananas together strong
hopefully hopefully i i want to see how
cool a senpai can be
fine
okay i'll be taking my leave now i can
let the others sweep
thank you so much for having me
thank you thank you thank you bye-bye
oh she's so sweet
[Music]
he's next i am um overwhelmed
happy
oh
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Laughter]
thank you
um
hey good morning good morning
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
so funny
she's so funny and i hope that
i don't know she just makes everyone
laugh and smile
i aspire to be someone like that
it's so much fun talking with everyone
okay
[Music]
oh
this is the first time we've talked in
voice chat
yeah this is the first time oh my god i
i don't know why it takes so long for us
to talk like this i feel like we've
talked quite a bit before but just like
not in voice chat i know it's lawyers
like see
um
in my
craft
[Laughter]
i was you know
uh the first time the first time i saw
you i just like so excited because
there's another there's another space
thing scene
yeah
yeah i'm honestly so honest because
i mean mina is just um
beautiful
there is no doesn't know what the word
to
describe it
you're just breathtaking like whenever
you're seeing all your performances and
all it's just
yeah
really
it's just breathtaking so it's like um
tears come out
thank you
i i hope i can see your performance
someday you know oh
i'm nervous
i i love it uh
some of
our
listeners making uh the art of us
and you are the big big planets oh yes
there is like one time i saw like an
like a fan art of you me and then
so you say it
yeah just like you you become the big
planet and round around and i become the
moon and run around
that is so cute
yeah
it's so cute and i'm like why am i here
i'm just uh just a baby
yeah
yes when i saw your character feel like
uh rather than planet you remind me of
dangle
danger
yes oh
so is this um sorry do i remind you of
danger
yeah because your hair
would be really nice what kind of what
kind of danger
do you like i really like um
i guess it's not dango like the um the
ones with strawberry isn't it
like the mochi strawberries in it
is that good
i don't know
uh
but
i i
i think the dangle before
and and inside of it it's chocolate
oh that's really delicious
if i crack open if i crack open the moon
is it also full of chocolate because
you're so sweet
[Laughter]
[Music]
some food uh i don't know what it should
be
what do you think if i am a food
[Music]
i'm trying to think of something like
elegant
what i want is like something
um
elegant
like yo you're the color you're the
color of taro so i can't like just keep
the entire
like sweet potato but but you're more
elegant than that
you're like oh
oh oh yes
probably yeah like maybe maybe blue
cheese
some people see it like tarot cheese
tower cheesecake
cheesecake might be good i mean cheeses
are actually really expensive once you
grow up you realize that cheese is just
really expensive is it like an expensive
food it's like when you're little you
don't really think of cheese as um you
just get cheese in your lunchbox and go
like ah cheese again but then when you
grow up you realize that cheese is just
so expensive
well that's mean i'm extra fancy
[Music]
that's good that's good
wow oh someone said mean cakes i love
pancakes too i love
um
oh
do you have you ever
make pancakes for yourself
yes i made pancakes for myself
i make pancake with banana i love it
oh
[Music]
but i think i've done that before with
pancakes before and um if you put banana
in it doesn't it get black really easily
doesn't it
it gets black really easily i just like
uh so i just like uh putting it on a
really really light uh the fire make it
a glow fire
cook it and make sure i didn't i didn't
laugh it
[Music]
okay so this is how to cook onion
i feel like you're talking with anya
yeah
i'm curious
i will um
one day i'll eat your your banana
pancakes and thank you very much for
well i hope someday i can make you happy
in your life
yes please
yes please i know uh
anyway i hope we can we can uh really
talk for real uh
you know without the thought so much
thing like let's play yourself together
yeah
that sounds good to you yes
thank you so much
bye bye bye
i'm blushing
okay okay next up next up
um call the number
[Music]
it's
good morning thank you very much for
coming to the tatsu thank you for
um
is it cute
thank you for the last minute run around
as well yesterday
no problem no problem
[Music]
oh my gosh i got so many things to say
but no i don't know why i'm the nervous
one
how are you how are you today um i am
doing great thanks to you
no i was um i was listening to this room
i didn't i didn't listen from the
beginning because i just sort of woke up
but i was listening to it and then the
bgm was so cool
that's the kind of vibe i'm going for
just comfy just comfy
comfy treat
it's comfy it's like
yeah i see i see the galaxy bread down
there is that edible or should i not eat
that
[Music]
um give me a second people are saying
the colors are quiet
hey
really no no i
turned you up
okay
edible
oh what's edible is the the dog down not
downstairs at the bottom of the screen
oh a satellite
i said oh that's the sun i'm like
know i think i think oops
pretty tasty a bit um rather than eating
them i also recommend face painting into
them because they're very soft and they
smell freshly baked
oh
it's cute
the smell of freshly baked bread
so nice
so tasty very comfortable
so comfortable
delicious i mean what
i kind of understand because um
like when you get those
dessert flavored soaps
when you take a bath
yeah yeah like um caramel camera like
brulee like
creme brulee or like um
chocolate flavored soups
you kind of want to eat the syrup
i know
because you know the smell kind of like
tricks are red inside oh
do i risk it
[Music]
by the way i'm
i'm really excited your uh your envy is
gonna be premiering
so soon
yeah yeah
yeah
102 minutes
i saw i saw the credits and i'm excited
all right
[Music]
your original song
just sir
cool whenever i don't know i've been
watching your streams and you always say
spicy like um
you always do that so i'm trying
i ended up saying it anyway but yeah
i'm trying to avoid other words and
calling it spicy but yeah oh spicy spicy
original
is it really do i say spicy that much
but i don't know maybe maybe it's just
something that stands out because i
i always like whenever i think of you
now i think i'm like yeah you say spicy
spicy yeah i mean spicy can be used it's
like a it's like one of the um
like objective that is very very
versatile kind of like
saying yeah bye you know like people say
yeah bye for a lot of things you can
also say oh spicy to a lot of things
useful senpai knowledge
yeah very useful so if you start saying
spicy and spread the spread the spicy
worldwide then you know sooner or later
everybody will start saying it
more even more
this is how you take over the world
efforts
yeah thank you very nice do you like
spicy turkeys
excuse me
[Laughter]
i know rose turkey
[Music]
it's all right i think it's all right
it's it's not spicy but aren't we
supposed to be spicy for all the words
oh but the thing is when it comes to
spicy food i'm kind of weak when it
comes to it can you eat spicy i can't
eat the spicy food i'm sorry
oh you can't okay i like some sweet food
ah all right now it's okay i'm like also
weak with spicy belly even though i am i
sometimes you know
cause it's sometimes it's so hard when
you like that addictive kind of spicy
when you eat snacks that are overly
spicy for no reason like you're
suffering but then you can't stop i have
that
i think my favorite um spicy food that's
addictive that i just suffer from is
ah
[Music]
very nice ah this one is going uh kind
of like sweet spicy right yeah there's
something addictive about it i'm just
like dying and um
you know stuff is coming out of my nose
that it's so good yes yes yes yes yes
yes i see i see i see
what food do i can i answer these
questions oh only if you want to just
this is just optional
oh
that's like
i've said this before but like some
people say like you're um you know the
three the the your thingy like it
reminds people of downtown
yeah but what i when i see it i get
reminded of you know one of those like
um it's not ice cream but one of the
like frozen ice balls like froze the
flavored ice balls
like the ones that that look like weird
faces
ah it's like you know you just like put
it in your mouth and like i don't know
it's really oh those things i was
thinking like the really cursed ice
cream pops
wait what what cursed ice cream puffs
like the ones with the faces
with faces hold on like oh my god
i just google it i don't know if i'm
googling the right thing or not but um
these are a bunch of cute stuff yes
i think um you've seen like series that
we probably shouldn't talk about but
yeah yeah those kind of icicles with
like the faces and stuff i always think
like um
my my planners kind of look like they
come from them
i don't know how to respond but like
very nice
i think that's the first time i've ever
said that to anyone
really oh that's also favorite soccer
secret
okay
cursed i've never actually eaten one i
wonder what they taste like it's like
definitely one of the things i have to
try
maybe we can like one day have a
popsicle in our sort of
basis like this
you know like in this video
yeah you know i'm i just thought about
this just now if we ever like have an
off collab in the future like we should
have an ice cream date but like a cursed
one like a cursed ice cream yes please
i'm so excited okay i'm just really i'm
not sleepy anymore no i'm excited
the spiciness woke you up
yes
but yes um i was also thinking i don't
really want to like take too much of
your time because like i know other
people's probably waiting i feel like
i've just been having so much fun
talking with everybody that i end up
making people wait i'm sorry for making
you wait as well oh that's all right i
just want to say you know we should play
something like the lady remember the
last time we talked like on discord
right and then
we were like yo yeah but i think we
should play something maybe some like
nice co-op i don't know
it's all you saw i'll do anything
yeah i'll talk to you about it you know
because you you've been also playing
like the retro game right because i've
never played that before oh yeah there's
a lot of um there's a lot of co-op games
there and i want to sort of drag someone
into just playing around and messing
around with other retro games
on something maybe that'll be fun to do
yeah of course of course of course any
time just hit me up here
okay
thank you so much tara i don't miss
talking to you
too thank you thank you rania for being
right now thank you for coming to my
tatsu
ah enjoy your birthday okay
[Music]
spicy
okay okay ring ring ring
[Music]
thank you
is
[Music]
yes really
you do
very cute
you
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
me
[Music]
[Laughter]
perfect
[Music]
oh
yes
oh let's get along
[Music]
please
please yes
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
my
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
really english good
okay who are you going next
oh my gosh just caught
i am quite a bit behind but we'll get
through these calls at least
why is everyone so nice
ring ring ringing
who am i
who is this
i'm a channel lifestyle happy birthday
sana
yay thank you
i'm sorry for making you late
don't worry don't worry so
but i
failed or i feel very nervous because
maybe it's first time to talk with you
right so
i i'm really so
very happy
yes you're very happy very happy you
came to my tattoo and
um it is so so i am quite nervous like
the aeton
yeah yeah yeah yeah so
i'm i'm so glad so i
i've been looking forward to
having a conversation with you so i'm
glad i'm glad we did it
thank you so much and so
i
yo
when i wait for this stream so
um i will never so very early in japan
isn't it
right actually early in the morning yeah
yeah we never saw i've been watching
this stream for two hours
flowers because i i can't it's a whole
um
[Music]
i'm really sorry for
me talking about bananas
i'm really i'm really sorry
screaming so much so yeah where am i
talking words i i'm thinking or i'm
really a bird so
um first i'm i'm very glad so now i feel
relieved oh because you were very kind
yeah oh your child is so kind i
um each one's always
obtained sorry saying nice things about
me
and i've also seen
like a while ago you um
i think he called me an anus collab
i guess yeah and then um you covered me
saying um
grab my butt
why
and you you give me your
jupiter cup cupboard
i don't remember that's all right that's
all i remember it was quite a long time
ago
ah quite a long time
club club
[Music]
okay okay okay i i got the meaning so
and i comment so
you're your collaboration
stream right so i remember i remember
oh
[Laughter]
yeah yeah
so you were
[Laughter]
our first impression
it's bad
first of all it was also
a fabulous memory right
so sticking out my disney
it's very convenient
how did your english become so good
so girls it's not no cigaretting person
i'm very glad so
yeah
um i do want to communicate with you or
um
other others or en members so i do i do
want to improve my english level so not
so enough not so you know
is also good right
and i've heard so i've seen your clip so
you you have stayed in japan before oh
yes
i got the feeling and so
before i
i could talk i'm so
more smoothly but i i am worth focused
so i
i learned again
[Music]
okay so
we can help each other so together
talk to me in english anytime
i will do my best with japanese as well
oh
i'm very glad i'm very glad so and i'm
i and so i saw your
stream you talked about your dreams
and so the dream is to hold
counsel life so
[Music]
or maybe i can't so i can't see your
face because you are very tall
yeah your son is very big so maybe i
can't
see your face
i need to glass so brink your guys
okay i'll carry you i'll carry you yeah
okay
lion king
pranking
[Laughter]
so
um until the time i
really
want to influence my english so yeah
really i
do hope you
um the dream come true and thank you
thank you that means a lot
you want to visit
[Laughter]
isn't that great i think that's it um if
you want to try
it
[Music]
maccus is probably better than the
macca's equivalent in japan
right
yes
[Laughter]
yeah yeah i
i
was planning to
say maka's word in your own your stream
i am very satisfied
thank you so much
yeah anyways so happy birthday and thank
you guys
great
brilliant
thank you
yeah thank you so much so sweet
yes yes i'm so happy i could i'm so
happy we could talk yeah
thank you so happy to have more memories
and grab my phone
[Laughter]
thank you anyway thank you
okay
we have one more call in
all right on time you could say
ring ring
[Music]
good i need to wear
right on time i i sure am actually i'm
very lame
sorry to me
my bread grill
man
i feel like we talked like just the
other days
just like there's nothing you can say
that's going to make me blush
like oh
yeah
yeah i feel like there's anything like
sweet you can do for me right now
i mean i can just say it again
well like something that's random is
like you know people are gonna
love the music
your original song
oh
i'm excited to show you guys
it all
yeah it'll be a bomb
and well
i guess
i guess you know i'm
really glad
to know you
and
i hope we can be friends
for a very very long time for eternity
what is what does eternity do to time to
the ward in all time you know
um
whenever whenever we hang i always like
have you on my mind for quite a long
time going away yeah she's great and i'm
just so happy with that
um
yeah i've
been able to talk with you and become
some friends with you and
just
have it always have a chill time
yeah it's just
i don't know i feel like
you're very comfortable and i can share
anything with you
yeah like um
well like this is about you so
[Laughter]
i
i really like
i really like your you know
grind mindset oh my god always getting
that yeah you're
you're like always getting that brand
and
haha
pun intended uh
but yeah it's kind of admirable i think
i've said this before
yeah but
yeah we've already like said this before
but
yeah but like i i
admire
your
drive to
do things and
like
i guess you
push me
to do better
yeah so you know
yeah a level head to me
like
whenever i'm lost or just like yeah
you always like look everything in a lot
in like a logical way that makes sense
and it just makes me
you know if i'm worried about anything
it just makes me feel
like if you got my back
um i can do anything
yeah but i mean that's because you're
you're like level-headed yourself so
you know
[Music]
oh yeah i feel great
i feel great i feel like you're one of
the people that
if i'm around you i feel like i can do
my best
like i can you know grow
oh
and
uh
after after i move i wanna i wanna
collab with you yes please
yeah cause like it's been a long time
since we did a collab which is kind of
odd since we kind of you know we just
kind of have yeah every now and again
right
um for streaming hang out it's been a
while
yeah
so
yeah i want to i want to invite you
yes please i'll do anything
yeah
so
well anyway
um do you have any questions you want to
ask me since i'm you know
um
the last runner
i tried to ask questions as
well optional if you just wanted to say
it but give me the food option like what
food do
i remind you of and what different do
you think you are because i don't know i
think it tastes like metal
i taste
[Laughter]
like the metallic stuff on cakes i like
like let's say let's simple for that
like gold foil wait wait gold foil
doesn't taste like anything
[Laughter]
okay
okay man
uh let's see
uh
typical answer would be bread but
guess if i were to think otherwise i
think he would
be
like
some
it would have to be fluffy i feel like
yeah like
[Music]
like
no
like a
like
oh
like a
like what's soft on the outside
but hard on the inside
[Music]
bridge stored mochi
with like
red bean in the middle or like chocolate
so like when you bite into it it's like
soft but then like you bite into
like the filling and
it's
cold and hard
and you're like why did i why did i put
this dessert in the fridge
wait no no not like that okay
you are like
you are like a
bread with
fillings
red with feeling feelings
yeah because you know you're like fluffy
on the outside
uh but you know on the inside you have a
lot of thoughts and
yeah it's like
there's more
about you i have many legs
you have many layers but you're not an
onion
thank you
i've got to think of something better
than gold foil for you then what's a
what's a perfect food i think i actually
asked this with chat like a very long
time ago i was thinking about what food
or dessert all of council is and then
people just said that your ice cubes
really yeah
[Music]
damn
i think you're something like oh
that's cold
that's cool
no i've been having coffee jelly
recently like quite a bit have you ever
had coffee jelly before
yeah
there's something that like it's really
good
yeah something creamy like milk ice
cream or ear cream and it's just like
the balance of um the sophisticated
balance of the bitterness of the coffee
with like a bit of sweetness and the
offset of um something creamy
it's just perfect
and it's just like yeah it's kind of
like that
so i'm like a better person i'm just
kidding
now y'all um you're as if you're
[Music]
you're just perfect
i mean i know that
yeah
i guess yeah i guess that's a good song
it's like deep
i'm like nectar and ambrosia but it
makes me feel very warm
it makes me feel very good
then like
like i just want to um numb everything
at once
that's kind of hardcore
i can respect the hustle though
oh
yeah
someone said affogato
yeah these kind of those kind of um
these kind of desserts like
tiramisu maybe but i'm very picky with
my tiramisu it has to be the perfect
balance of um cake and coffee and cream
like if it's a bit of a power thing
if it's like overpowering like one
element of the tiramisu then like this
is not it
um
or like sweet i don't really have a
preference like they're all good
yeah
i don't i don't want to take too much of
your time
more than i already have
i think we just ended up talking about
food and it's just been so long
yeah food is great though do you
i'm so happy that
um
we had time to talk at the end sorry
food is great what
why
i didn't say anything oh
and you said something and i think i
talked over here
no no no no
okay thank you very much for coming
wait you were gonna say something what
are you gonna say
oh man what's this cliffhanger at least
like
let me know afterwards if you remember
my pain
your brain is just
um there's no
room left except
craney okay
well
when you remember
uh
i cut you off freaking
anyway
happy birthday i think it's the ping
i'm gay
unironically i think it's the ping but
yeah
enjoying from my thoughts to my brain
yeah the sauna lights were amazing the
satellites are great aren't they
yeah they sent you know
the the the letter to space that's
amazing that is
mind-blowing
yeah so no no you gotta call them in
from cranium satellites
that's pretty good guys
look pretty good okay but
enjoy the rest of your birthday sauna
you deserve it
thank you honey
yeah much love thank you for just being
cranini
and i love you thank you
yeah me too thank you for being you
[Music]
i'll talk to you later y'all peace peace
i was surprised to
play some videos while we were talking
through the calls but
i ended up talking so much
i love crony did i talk to her for like
half an hour it feels like
oh my goodness
everyone's so sweet
okay
i guess i should go back to the videos
um
i have a few video calls calling like i
have every videos from people who still
wanted to greet me but
wasn't able to make the schedule
so i will
quickly
kick you all out again
well remember why am i so bad with
stream with stream times i was supposed
to um
if i was on time i would have
ended the stream like half an hour ago
but i still have quite a bit to show you
all right this will always
i'll i gotta keep it here so i can touch
it
okay
okay first video
don't worry sana we are here for you
you guys are the best
i love cranium praises you then you know
it has to be true it's not just me
he thinks you are great
yay
how you doing
sorry i can't call in live it's pretty
late where i am i should be sleeping
everywhere yeah so sorry i can't call in
life but i still wanted to tell you and
wish you a happy happy happy happy
wonderful birthday
[Music]
yeah
i hope you have a great year wish you
all the happiness and luck i hope things
are only going upwards for you
and it's great to have you in hall live
english yeah really happy to have you
thinking a great addition so i wish you
all the best and i will sing in germany
[Music]
is
okay yeah i forgot to say i haven't seen
these i haven't seen these yet
i just sort of um put all the videos in
and i haven't spoiled myself with any of
these so
thank you very much kiara
and thank you very much for um
she's been
doing everything recently
i haven't seen her in kelly's character
yet but i'm going to say love later once
i have time
ah mate happy birthday mate i can't
i don't like dad
i think she does a happy birthday mate
better than me
happy happy birthday mate
that was adorable from one australian
parenthesis to another
yeah she does australian better than me
[Music]
okay this one um
the next person
they've been on the road so um a video
was kind of hard that i've been able to
get a voice message
good morning
hey
i like space
hello sanna it is i
kalipimori here to wish you the happiest
of birthdays
ever ever ever
yeah as you can probably tell i'm a
little bit
leapy right now it's because
um i'm getting ready to
to to travel
and i need to be able to relax before i
travel going all out
so yeah
um but i wanted to make sure that i
could leave you a little birthday
message i've been inv
but i've been advised
to not uh stress my my voice too much um
because i do have a show i'm supposed to
do and i got a real sore throat
so um
i just wanted to sing you the typical
sonnet birthday song which is an
original and does not belong to
any company or music label ever anywhere
at all uh would tell everyone what were
your thoughts of the song sana
in the song
yeah me too
i definitely yeah oh so you liked it
great
i'm just gonna assume you said that you
liked it i wanted to make this kind of
more interactive but there's not much
that i can do when i'm when i'm flying
high in the sky
um you know by that time you get this
message i will probably
be high in the sky which is hey not far
from space
so um
i guess i'm real close to you right now
oh man i can i can feel the sanadana all
around me as you can tell maybe a little
bit sleepy but but still still love you
just as much sana you're a treasure
you're a treasure to all of us you make
us all smile and and you're so funny i
remember we spent like 10 hours together
hunting for chinese not a second of it
was boring because you're with me you're
with me when i caught my shiny giratina
that was such a special moment we spent
together longest hollow en collab thus
far record has been unbroken
so far so yeah um
i feel like we bonded a lot during that
time i learned a lot about you you
learned a lot about me and i learned
that you're one of the sweetest nicest
people uh in all of whole life and i'm
glad that i met you so i have the
happiest birthday ever sana um daisuki
i love you very much and um have a great
time with your santa lights and
everybody else calling in and you take
care of yourself okay
i'm buying your merch
i'm buying it i don't know what it is
yet but i'm
i was gonna replay it so i can hear the
song
and sort of rate it
but i don't want to
i don't want to leave after she cheered
me
[Music]
um what do you think of the original
song guys
spoilers
cheated me
amazing
a bangle oh my god this rationale for my
original song
there's the pressure on me but
thank you very much kelly
remember oh
you're so busy and you're flying around
right
[Music]
now and your voice is so so dying
you still gave me a message on
oh my god
um
i love kelly
ellie is the best repro of the world of
the universe
big out of 10.
okay next lesson
hello sona
happy birthday
i am so excited to see
your song
and congratulations on your birthday
i'm sorry i couldn't make it in person
but
i am a time traveler after all in
lifetime traveled into the future and
listened to your song and god damn
it's a banger
uh
oh also i made i made some art for you
and it is scheduled to tweet around the
time that this video goes live so
hopefully you can check it out if not i
hope you see it after the stream and i
hope everything is going well
um
i hope all the collins have gone
smoothly and i also hope you had
something delicious and tasty to eat
today for your birthday
and i have a question for you usually
it's the other way around question for
me um
let's see my question
what is your favorite cake and if you
could have your cake decorated in any
theme like a minecraft cake or something
what's the question
wait wait i just saw the other one about
it anyways i hope you have a happy happy
happy birthday
yeah
what was the question
[Music]
i just heard
minecraft no no this is this is too cute
i can't replace a video
i'm waiting for that answer
[Music]
you can't you can't ask me a question
and shove this picture into my face at
the same time i i don't have a big
enough
brain to
comprehend this
it's up
almost almost art is up late
um
i need to show it to you guys who can't
be lazy to look at twitter
[Music]
look at this no wonder i got distracted
it's so adorable
i love it thank you very much um
i think at the time i stepped on a snail
this snail i wouldn't um
oh man
what was the question
something studying minecraft
um i will get my minecraft house done
very soon
i'm sorry
for taking how many months
the question was larry chats come to
save me the question was what's your
favorite kind of cake and if it could be
any kind of theme like minecraft or
something what would it be
cake
what decoration i want on my cake
my favorite cake i actually really like
um
i like strawberry shortcake
i said this in the curvier decorating
stream
oh my gosh i think that kirby cake was
one of the most cutest cakes um that
have that i've ever told existed before
but i actually really like um japanese
fluffy tea cheesecake that's not too
sweet
and then
um with both
strawberry shortcake and japanese
cheesecake fluffy japanese cheesecake i
like a bit of fruit on them as well and
if i was to decorate them maybe i'll add
some planets on it because you know
people have been drawing really nice fan
art
recently of me eating planets and i've
been thinking like the planets are kind
of like individual truffles
like chocolate truffles or something or
candy
yeah
and then like i can eat like you need a
planet with every single slice
do not eat the earth please not in this
timeline
we have army to save us
solar system cake that would be cute
that does remind me i once went to japan
and um
i think in kyoto
there's a chocolatier that does space
themed chocolate truffles
and um it's absolutely beautiful it's
super expensive but something
um
you're pretty
real
[Music]
beautiful
yeah it's like really a fancy a really
fancy um
planet themed
planet sources on planet themed um candy
and i think if you giggle it maybe it
will come out up i think you get it in
osaka or
kyoto i forgot which one it was
okay i have
a couple more things
oh my god i is this
did you know
snails like to bury themselves in leaves
and
i guess you could say
this is a snail's house
oh
my god
i only have the picture off i was like
wait
oh my god
i i was going through so much on there
you were asking me a question and i had
minecraft and then i saw this i was like
what and then you were you were
pressuring me for an answer
you're so cute keeping you are you on
there
that's so funny
[Music]
she distracted me
oh she distracted me from um
one more video one more video of her
talent and then i do want to show off
some
of the really amazing stuff that
satellites have been working on
and um some of the presents i've
received
and
yeah then i think
they'll be around near the time
that the original song will premiere so
exciting
i'm so excited i'm not really that
nervous because i think you're all gonna
love it and everybody working on the
song um
they've done an amazing job
i guess i'll talk about it a bit later
um places this time
boy
[Music]
happy birthday to you
happy birthday to
you
[Music]
me
ah that was so cute
[Music]
i'm very touched thank you very much for
watching
um i love your voice
i love
hello
everything about what thomas empire
and i think she just brightens up the
room wherever she is
it's too cute
too far for you to comfy
you're so nice
okay
what show i show you next i do
like um
i do have something that sort of came in
pretty
like recently i think i can show you
before i show the other stuff
i did get some extra merch photos
[Music]
wait
give me a second
look at this you can you can face plant
into red dog's belly
what tommy
thank you very much
[Music]
ah
like stalking it's just everything's so
fluffy
like this is what you face plan into the
bread dog oh yeah and here's the cup as
well
i've been jerseyed
yeah the final thing might feel a little
different these are like the first
renditions of everything but
yeah
it's so cute
i i want it myself
oh
okay one more thing
[Music]
two more things actually
okay so
there's been uh absolutely a
incredible project that
um
[Music]
i've had the honor to receive i didn't
know what to say i i just can't believe
it what the heck
what the heck
okay so apparently there was a grievous
satellite set got together too
um
i'll send some
stuff to space
and um
i have the video in the description and
uh on below but yeah i'll also play it
here because
there's
at the
well
why not
oh let's just let's just go
[Music]
i was like is that me
go
oh
oh no sound
wait just a moment no sound
it's needed
it's playing for me give me a second
one
two
three four
okay rewind
okay i don't i don't what the hell what
the hell is this
let's just play it let's
let's go it's okay
[Music]
let's launch it at light speed
three
two
one
go
whoa
it's going up and up and up and up and
[Music]
well you can is the stratosphere
the sun
[Music]
you guys
went to space
[Music]
forget touching
grass the sunlight's touch space
oh this is the earth
hello snow earth
it's home to everyone you know
that's all of you guys
can you see you guys in there
[Music]
absolutely breathtaking
i wonder if sana was any bigger than
sana is
would i have noticed the earth that's
your house
[Music]
ah
why is it so much harder
[Music]
right into a field of yellow flowers
thank you
very much for organizing this it's
absolutely unbelievable
um
it's so funny that it landed in a
field of flowers yellow flowers
oh give me a second
now why is it so much harder this time
thank you
um
well
you told your friends space and grass oh
my god
the best spot to
land
we love you like
i said on the side um
on the special site you can also see all
the messages that wasn't
the space and
it's
incredibly sweet i don't know what to do
it's all
the sweetness
ah
[Music]
there's one little thing
oh give me a good
i don't think i can continue
until
i wipe my face i need i need a bread dog
i need to face plant my uh my face into
a bread dog he said he's a lucky bread
dog that
um volunteers
my god i have a lot of volunteers don't
i
oh my
he's a good boy he's a good satellite
ah
[Music]
okay the next one
the next project is something that
is also pretty awesome man it looks like
we clutch
was able to get permissions to
play this game right now
like right now
i guess
all the audio and stuff works because um
i just set it up
it's a game
it's a fan game
okay this is the site that you can have
a look at the game you can um play the
game on browser or you can download it
as well
big sauna
okay let me know
your stuff
sounds good
i've already like tried fishing like
just a little bit i was like
can you get permission for this game
what if i can play this one stream like
right now
look at this
[Music]
okay it looks like there's something
good here
it's just like the perfect game for me i
think
[Music]
it's so cute
wait i want to get i want to get one at
least with an achievement there's a
shiny spot
i was like um working pretty late on my
birthday stuff i haven't slept for a
while but um
i saw this game i was like
blown away
how much can you guys spoil me
no
that was a bigger planet
oh
okay that's like a collection
as well you can
complete
and i plan on getting 100
sunday maybe i can play this
um
on a separate stream soon but yeah i
just already i was like absolutely blown
away by the effort put into this that i
wanted to show it to as many people as
possible because
um i want you guys to play this
this looks like it was a place i could
have had like a collectible in it i
didn't see it it's a big planet seemed
to be really heavy
but you can make someone smile like
[Music]
looks really cool you can play this like
while waiting for my original song
[Music]
as well
i keep missing stuff
and then like there's more music as well
that plays it's just like a really good
time and i was like this is
you know me so well
the people who put who like worked on
this they know me so well
[Music]
i like the music
yeah the sun is sad face because i can
only fish all the small planets wizard
where's the small armor
i want a fish more small on there
[Music]
yeah yeah please um
there's a lot of i didn't play this for
very long but there's remixes or tracks
as well
that's just like
really chill
[Music]
and i feel like this just sort of
captures my vibe pretty well
[Music]
this one this one i'm not going to i'm
not going to end this stream until we
get an achievement
[Music]
you're stuck here with me now
i have to get it i have to get it before
my premiere what if i miss my own
premiere
because i've gone fishing
[Music]
hello
is it just big planets
i think so
that's like a random thing to do i was
actually thinking about reno when this
when i played this game i was like
fishing
[Music]
oh
come here come here
[Music]
oh
there was something there but like a
sleeping cat did i miss it
[Music]
this is cool
you guys really should try this game
please
yep you can play it on your browser i
just wanted to
show it to as many people as possible
because
good vibes all around i think
chinese spot
reveal yourself to me
the universe
[Music]
it's so empty sometimes
we'll play once before your stream
[Music]
melissa did i miss it
i'm sorry my plan was i would get an
achievement by now
i've just been getting the truffles
planet truffles
i don't want to crash aside or deal
[Music]
i mean i'm playing it fine
oh my goodness i guess
i guess i'll end the stream
if i don't get
an achievement soon
oh yeah that was my birthday party um
i couldn't have done it without you guys
there is more to come
[Music]
that's omiya's drawing
let's talk a little bit about asteroid
gala i'm trying to fish
[Music]
okay so
i feel like what this song um
conveys pretty well
and
what i kind of wanted to convey is
just something really simple like warmth
and i feel like yeah it
um conveys it really well in
a way that's very sano like if i do have
to say so myself so
these look forward to it the premiere is
gonna be in half an hour
[Music]
i'm like an hour off what i have
scheduled my stream but it's okay
it's been
a lot of fun
you guys are all very sweet older
all the talents who came today thank you
very much
oh manohar and all the people have
helped out
thank you very much
[Music]
and i say to you every single sound i
like
um you guys
wish me
happy birthday continue to watch and
support me and just you know hang out
sometimes
[Music]
i wouldn't be able to
get this far without you guys
[Music]
happy birthday
okay i guess achievements are not coming
[Music]
thank you
yes
it says goodbye for now but
yeah i want to play this game
in a stream soon
thank you very much to everyone who came
and everybody's
gonna come later to watch your blood
and i hope you enjoy
astro girl very very soon
see you later
[Music]
bye
you