[Music]
so
hmm
[Music]
oh
hmm
[Music]
oh
um
i was a humming pov
point of view from ariana i see you
i see you two people who noticed it
yo hi everyone cake
[Music]
oh hi y'all hello
hello how are you doing
i'm doing fine by the way i'm doing
quite well
i'm in a good mood for some reason
yup hummingbird
and my neck i mean yo you guys probably
don't need to ask me that every day i
told you it's going to take two to three
weeks to heal
i'm fine though i'm okay
it's not so bad
it's really not that bad i don't know i
might i might be a
quick healer sasuke phoenix
[Music]
yeah phoenix rises from the ashes you
shall heal too
says go some of us care well that's
sweet
thank you that is sweet but
i there won't there won't be much
change between today and tomorrow and
tomorrow and the day after tomorrow and
so on
so there's not much i can tell you there
there really won't be much change i
think
oh we always want to know how you feel
oh come on
[Music]
sweetie we'll still ask okay whatever
we say in german besides of italy
there's other things that we say
ah today we play this game that reminds
me
from like the style it reminds me of uh
kooky yummy because it's just really
really simplistic
and funny and weird as far as i know
just like hooking up me kokuyo nita yo
nagenato
sensitive sensual
[Laughter]
sometimes uh it's a it's a fast it's a
it's a
short game so after we're done with it
we'll read a few
super shadows afterwards shouldn't take
longer than an hour i think
also i opened the game and it doesn't i
don't see any options
it goes right into full screen so that's
uh
a bit weird i don't know if i can change
it afterwards
but i guess we're playing it in full
screen
on it obs are you gonna are you gonna
show it to the people yeah all right
so shall we go everyone
sensitive surreal strange s-s-s
okay let's plug it ah this feels nice
you hear that
is the only okay this is supposed to be
not that loud but
oh it's so holy
what what's going on
[Music]
can i help those are really long we're
supposed to meet in the middle right
can i win this game or lose this game
what looks like a running carrot in some
way
where are we going
[Laughter]
okay buddy get up get up come on run
keep on running huh run
go
[Music]
what is
[Laughter]
we're back to the beginning
this is oh my god
i didn't finish
we're back here what the hell is this
game this is kind of trippy
are you okay bro
yeah punch him oh my god
what what
what what about you then
well i guess you won do you want to get
what
no don't you dare
don't fart okay just don't don't fart
oh no oh no
oh hell no
[Music]
stick it back in
that's disgusting why is there money in
your
body huh why
explain to me how did that get into you
and what
am i going to do with that what what
you usually run after it
oh i don't need that
it's coming back okay
whatever that means
what are you trying to tell me game
so this is a man and woman adam and eve
how
things started okay
so adam says to eve hi
and eve actually said hello hello
hello and then adam said hello
as well which is repetitive and it's
kind of a turn off in it
ah eve was very obviously noticing that
adam has no idea how to flirt with a
woman because she's probably never
seen a woman before it makes sense
doesn't it so
she realizes okay she has to help out a
little bit with this conversation
because it's not going anywhere so she
chooses to say
do i know you do i know you i don't know
now obviously she's by this answer she's
like
at the point where she already wants to
go away because
adam i mean in several ways but
uh she just continues
to with do you know me how could i know
[Laughter]
eve at this point hopes that there is
any other guy
in this world right now that she can
make babies with and hopes that this is
not the only choice she has because
otherwise the baby that they're gonna be
making is gonna be the biggest
idiot
ever and probably is gonna destroy this
world and make it explode
and then yeah that means that all of us
will never exist
so her answer is
she knows no you don't
ah
no she's just as confused as we all
are and does not know where the
this conversation is going
so she says yes
no
that was unexpected
i guess it is no after all no
yes
okay that's good because that means that
we found a different guy
and we did not have to deal with adam
because he
is just not like
empty in his brain i mean his
brain is full of farts like how are we
gonna make babies with him
so she goes to the next guy whose name
is tom
and she says to him
i love you i love you i don't think i
love you
i don't think they understand what's on
the line
that this is a really really important
thing right now
because there's like maybe three people
on this earth
and we need to love each other in order
to not disappear okay
are you sure i think you don't love me
i mean that's true but i'm gonna force
myself to love you
you know what's at stake i know i love
you
no i love you come on i'm not sure shut
up
i do love you you i don't but you need
whatever it doesn't matter just it hurts
i'm leaving
[Music]
tom why
idiot put that in there
huh what isn't that what was just in
there already
oh i felt that what is this
thing again huh go go go go go go go go
go go
go go go go go go go go
take my hand come on come on
there we go
what's going on what's happening yo you
chill is this normal
yeah and now and now
it's easy
[Music]
oh what tom came back and it's
like well
tom you and you adam
now you won't eve huh all of you
that i wanted to make that with some you
know some
some power but it just doesn't go in
got to be careful huh okay let's be
careful
[Music]
leave
[Laughter]
do i have no choice
everyone look away please look away
me neither
this is family friendly channel from
takanasi kiana from home live english
um
huh
it's like almost uh
it's almost disconnected how did i do
that
can i can i undo this can i like
disconnect it for real cells
i broke it up it's back to normal
spoopy all right
get in there come on
hello
you gotta come here buddy gotta come you
gotta meet me in the middle
meet me halfway yeah
well what a difficult choice to make
well you know
come on pedra come on
you know
this is a weird game a weird game it
is indeed what's this
what the is going on
huh
i guess we switch it up a little bit huh
i mean i i i'm not really in i don't
really like that foot
if i emblem free plugs
don't fight
[Music]
oh
please
[Music]
oh
ah
what what is the meaning of this
and i played for 20 minutes
what do you mean and that's the end of
the game
how did gonna play this for 54 minutes
there's other endings how do i get those
she's good enough
oh i could have done things differently
how
is there is there only other endings
well
am i not just doing the same thing oh
yeah
it's that
is part any way to do it differently
the sound he makes though
must have been painful pooping that out
poor dude oh wonder you were
like having such issues what am i gonna
do with you oop
whoop huh wait i think that's new
is that not you
what would you like to
uh what are we gonna do
maybe eat it again oh he goes after it
what about the other one oh they're both
here
oh
what about this
oh we have that underneath thing okay
let's see
bye see you
ain't got no time for this
wait but before that was even and now
it's
adam that's walking to two eaves right
oh yeah
do i know you i don't know
interesting
i know you
communication skills one thousand one
million
no you don't i'm gonna be at sunson now
because before i was not treated very
nicely i must say
and i don't like that
sure sure whatever
no yes no
yes when i say no it means no okay yes
no hi
so i do love you believe me i don't
think i love you i know this again
are you sure i think you don't love me
but i do but hug me how about that i'm
not sure
what do you mean you know some
friendliness huh
do you listen we didn't try this one yet
what does this even mean what is this
conversation
what what does this mean
sure yes
yes no
how dare you walk away from me oh right
a third comes
[Music]
do you want to hug me oh and now you're
being dead
huh and i say no now i think you love me
no i don't i don't know
nope nope nope
i'll miss you it hurts
i'm leaving i'm leaving on a jet plane
i don't know when i'll be back again
oh babe
sorry it's like a little meme that we
have
hug me i'm not sure
is this this is repeating itself
interesting
um i do love you i don't
women
who understands anyone absolutely
humans are stupid that's why i
am dealing with the death
but what now
[Music]
okay
is there anything i can do differently
with this one
[Music]
no
ah
okay i guess this one is uh
it is what it is come on over
come over baby come on over
come and over
what was that song what's that song
what's that song
christina aguilera oh yeah
no there must be a different way there
must be a different way
let me break it again break it break it
break it
oh destruction
oh my god thank you cake
can i rip it out come on come on yeah
okay whatever get in there
oh that was short
lived
[Music]
get out there stop it
no no no
no
he's coming he's coming
don't look again don't close your eyes
tomorrow
get in there get in there
oh yeah what'd i do with that
no no
yeah do i really have to go for the new
one i don't wanna
[Music]
get in there
yeah this is too awkward what the
is this game
i don't want to play it anymore no
do it
let's get it over with
stupid game yeah
[Music]
please
oh
[Music]
me
it's dreaming people who made this game
is
[Music]
you don't want to know what i just read
here
the germans are that they're switzer
sweet swiss swiss wish swiss swiss swiss
they're swiss oh yeah swiss people can
have very german names as well
um
my question is why
[Laughter]
my question is just why
no i all right all right well
is there is there more games like this
like i saw something when i was looking
at the game there was something like
kids
and plug and play or whatever like what
does that mean is there a kid's version
of this
is there a pg-14 version of this
or is that like a separate game it's a
sequel
my god i need to play it
[Laughter]
they made a seat quilt
kids is another level
i don't it's so bad
play right now i don't think i i
actually i think i only have permission
for plug and play but i would probably
be
um able to get permission for kids but
what the hell
maybe next time but wait only 20 minutes
that's so
short
should have played both both of them in
one stream
kids kids
indeed i see it oh my god there's like
a lot of them
wow oh wait i've seen this before the
gameplay before
though did any whole life member play
this before
oh because i feel like i've seen it
before
oh we should play it sometime soon guys
mikko senpai
i did oh did they do it recently
i wonder if we can play it all right
anyway for today i guess that's all
right
what a speedrun
yeah we have a lot of time for super
chats now
oh man i fought like at least maybe 40
50 minutes or so
that was a bit short but okay that's
okay that's that's fine too
um
i guess that's good before i use up all
my energy and stuff right
okay moving over
hi and here i am hello
today i present to you smoothie
cute cute cuddly smoothie
[Music]
nice isn't she cute
adorable let me give you a kissy
[Music]
she's very happy
smoothie my baby my sweet
sweet baby
why not both at the same time you know i
was wondering if i can make that work
one second
oh well yeah wait the wax it works i
[Laughter]
think
wait i gotta make myself a bit bigger
wait a second
[Music]
wait i actually i actually
made the smoothie one a little bit
brighter let me do that with strong
crease as well because of
the hand
if i make it too bright and stronger it
gets too bright
okay well for now is that too bright i
guess it is
shut them like that altered chunkies
a blue one blue sunkist
[Music]
no wait that was not it
for now then fine i feel like nothing
changed
cute does that look weird what if i do
this
ah maybe maybe the other way around
oh
oh cute
i'm in heaven you know yeah
yesterday no today today after i woke up
by the way
i was uh i watched i miss
whoop out one day uh archive
it was it was fascinating
it was interesting
i think the edges like i don't know oh
yes like
i tried to make the edges look as smooth
as possible but
uh
[Music]
difficult
is there no way to send like a
transparent video
i wonder oh well but for now
for now this is fine i got my ladies
with me
can you throw the cats why would i do
that
yeah i'm gonna sell very creative
i mean i always knew that but let's put
a drink on chunkers
[Laughter]
[Music]
multitasking when you when you have both
hands not available because you're
petting your cats you gotta
improvise improvisation you know
you know chunkers likes it don't worry
this is so comfy
[Music]
i love it it's so cozy and comfy
okay where do we need
to continue reading super chats
what was that does anyone know what was
the last one
15 i'm 15 fps
what no way you mean
25 well i mean yeah i look smooth
to myself on my side here is that not
smooth
there might be some non-smooth moments
because of
well prime time here right now
i look a little slow
you are smooth yes because i just took a
shower before the stream
the eyes can only see in 40 fps anyway
what the hell are you talking about
that's not true oh i saw it now the fps
oh um whatever whatever
it will fix itself i think eventually
yes okay so where do i have to read that
one day
squirrel squirrel squirrel squirrel tony
aizun
[Music]
i'm gonna look for
it oh no that's really uh
scuffed minecraft am cat
loading oh yeah
why are you not loading there's no way
that that is already so much no it
loaded okay just took its
damn sweet time super chat rating
had super chat at the end but i said
that i will not read those right
the ones on monday where i turned on the
super chats in the end and i was like
i'm not gonna read those though
right if i remember correctly
correct okay okay then it's not that
much i think
that we have the rates
so we start by reading the mcat once
which is perfect because we currently
have two cats here
we could we're gonna have a fur cat
we're gonna have a third cat on stream
but maybe that's a little bit too much
right now
you've come so far in life jago should
be proud of you
oh i wonder if he is
i don't have much to do with yakult but
i'm sure my manager
is proud of me
enough cats wait let me move the chat a
little bit closer
hi chad you are right next to my super
chat reading window now
uh i like it when you're close to me
chat i like that
oh my
ah
so i was thinking before
why would you say you before the stream
i
um as a little snack i
ate some cup noodles that were like
miso soup cup noodles supposedly
um i bought it in the in our
supermarket and they're
miso miso not nasal soup ew
miso soup with noodles in it though and
i was just hoping for it to taste like
miso soup because
i like miso soup but
it did not really taste like miso soup
so i was a bit disappointed and i was
thinking that made me think maybe i
should ask my manager to send me
a package with some cup noodles and some
i don't know my favorite salad sauce
from japan
and all that stuff and send it to me
because there are some things that i
i some some kind of like tastes
that i miss from japan oh like a care
package would be nice yeah
[Music]
foreign
for you yes you can send me kelly's
uh you can't send human beings obviously
but she could send me some
some kind of piece of clothing maybe
hey blame the game okay blame the game
the game gave me i know weird
great emotions i don't know what the
hell i'm feeling
no i just meant something like i don't
know
a t-shirt that smells like
reap a bath body
yes blame the game not the player
exactly
okay okay
[Music]
yeah let's let's drink super jets from
mcat
i don't have the thumbnail right now
sorry guys
yeah rely you gotta rely on the tigers
i guess even my mom by the way even my
mom uses
uh those tags
she told me a while ago
that you i think i don't know it was
some kind of long stream of mine maybe
minecraft
where i when i talked about something
that was of her interest i think maybe i
talked about her
apparently remember it's quite a while
ago and she told me
i i was looking for the attacks of
that whale bear always writes
you have been officially recognized from
my mom
congratulations
[Music]
i'm pretty sure she meant your stamp set
yeah good job good job they're very
useful
even my mom uses them
you must be employee of the month next
month i guess
[Music]
okay
sorry
in a while wow
yummy
looking for the top thank you mr kevin's
big sanchezon george from texas duncan
clark club thanks arne
thank
mcat
it was a bit different than usual oh and
also i even did
amp shark but i guess there were no
super jets on m shark huh was it too
fast
oh yeah did i have them oh no i think i
had them turned off
yeah like exposed like i wanted to use
my cat ears for it
but i also didn't want to change the
format of it i still
wanted that scuffed irastoya artwork on
top of myself
but i also wanted to show off that i do
have cat ears
by now yeah so that was the only way to
combine it both
[Music]
huh
what is this uh difficult looking super
shiny time is supposed to read this name
[Music]
that was probably not how it's supposed
to be read next time you're welcome to
tell me how to read it
florida and tangasha and randall thank
you thank you
and sugar
[Music]
i feel like this entire series was just
for that gag now
no not for that only but
it will continue probably as per usual
and then everyone every now and then
i'll try to
put in some kind of twist maybe
no one dankeshan crispy dankeshen big
swing dankeshin
life changed forever thanks for the
wisdom
memo rice oh free dankeshin was
expecting 10 seconds of smoothie and
chunk are not gonna lie
oh smart smart oh but you guys did hear
in the background that my cats were
meowing right
actually i did quite a few takes of that
um because i wasn't feeling my own meows
but i was meowing so much and my cats
kept on coming up to me actually i have
a lot of dicks let me see if i can
actually show you
[Music]
wait
out takes
[Music]
guess let me see
wait
[Music]
i'm trying to find one where you can
actually hear it
in the background
wait they will continue to meowing
though
no did not hear anything in this one
i heard wonder wait which one was that
this one
that's cute wait let me show you
did you hear it that was strong face
it's hearing at the end it's like
wow what are you telling me
mama what are you trying to tell me
okay
what happened there what happened in
that one wait
i don't know which one was that
this one okay let me listen to this one
now
i think i don't know what happened there
i don't know what happened but something
happened
i didn't attack
stop stealing my life i did a lot of
takes yeah
but they were meowing at me all the time
but you can barely hear it and most of
them
it was one two three four five six seven
eight nine ten eleven takes normally i
don't do that maybe
normally i really don't kusa
what do you mean and cat had to be
purple thing exactly
yep yep all right let's go back
just a little extra for you guys
you see for the first time behind the
scenes of the making
of an m2 video
very very special only in the super chat
reading you get this kind of stuff
yes
such a passion on this project
i guess so i guess so
such a privilege yeah thank you for
staying guys thank you for staying for
the super chat reading
it means a lot to me all right where was
i though
oh wait oh wait um
yeah okay okay uh we actually now in the
minecraft stream
let me fetch the font now for this one
the thumbnail
at least
my
[Music]
it's super simple but i i like the art
the logo is really nice too and did you
notice uh
where my where my symbol is
it took me a while to find it too
no no no
yes that's a phoenix apparently
looks interesting it took me a while to
find it
but uh it's really cool that they
included everyone's
signs so so ma naka
okay where do we put it up here maybe
okay
let's get through we're going super chat
oh by the way
i think we can have some chit chat in
between
with this uh about about the summer
festival i'll try to read a few more
messages
and that was kind of the first stream on
my channel
after coming back so i was a bit
[Music]
a bit unhappy
that it was so scuffed
and honestly like first of all the my
my life today not moving and then after
that
me see logging into minecraft and seeing
how
laggy it was and the honestly i was
i was so annoyed already in the
beginning that i was like
i want to i want to end this stream
right now
like what the hell why is everything so
scuffed
but i'm glad i kept us going i'm glad i
kept
going because there were a lot of fun
moments and and
and uh yeah it would have would have
been a
waste to not be there yeah i thought i
thought in the beginning i thought the
lag was only for me
so i was like who the hell wants to see
that with you
especially when i'm not even moving
um
[Music]
i wonder what they did to fix the
lagging uh like is there some kind of
way to update a minecraft server to have
it be
less laggy is it like a way to make it
premium or what
to have the connection improved
good at died from lag like for real
reduced loaded blocks
robocop logged in is that what it is
[Music]
bandwidth gives you better hardware
yeah i really wonder what they did
paper more round what
not on the fly thing yeah update the
server pc
[Music]
settings
turn down v-sync we think
always confuses me oh
[Music]
i've been talking with gruna by the way
about what to do for the minecraft
stream
and also i asked her about the chair
today
oh she tells me that
it helped a lot used to really hurt
while sitting in her old chair it's
really expensive but i think it
helps if it helps and it's worth it it
came
pre-assembled oh oh
that's cool yeah
i asked her which which specific chair
she got and if it really helped her
yeah the herman miller chair oh
oh thank you maybe i'll
we'll get the same one
[Music]
but she's still typing a guy i'm gonna
be there when she sends me the message
[Music]
oh she stopped typing
you are you gonna continue typing
[Music]
that that that that moment when you
don't know if you should continue
waiting because she stopped typing
oh stopping again
[Music]
oh
yeah yeah
okay
something unrelated to gouda i'm going
to stop typing again
so she probably fell asleep while typing
okay let's continue reading
laser guys
and thanks for the pinkie welcome back
to i hope you enjoyed your trip
i'm so glad you managed to get in meme
review
and the last one yeah that was special
i'll miss it so much arigato and tenchuk
[Music]
that sounds not fitting also how is your
neck doing please take it easy love you
thank you for the pinky
oh my neck is fine now um
i mean it's not healed but still wait
let me take a
throat thingy
[Music]
oh
thank you good to know
they have a size chart she tells me
good morning
[Music]
a life shock yes
i'm using one of those neck collar
things no no no i i'm actually quite
surprised i got nothing prescribed
besides like
pain medication and i mean one of them
is i guess it helps with um
like um like
i don't know some things besides pain
um but the code of shame
yeah i didn't get anything else
i don't know
uh inflammation yeah stuff like that
yeah apparently i don't need anything
else
just takes time yeah um
yeah but i feel so lost you know i feel
so lost because
i didn't really get much information
because the hospital obviously i mean
they're busy and like normally
i can for example in japan uh there's
no not real there's barely any like
small doctors offices everyone just goes
straight to a big hospital
and there they get already
detailed um and intensive care
i guess but because the system is
different like i think
the way it is in my country is how it is
normal
in other in most other countries like
you have all these small
doctors offices and who take care of
like small things and
if you have like an accident or like a
really a bi person
then you go to the hospital stuff like
that
so so it's quite normal that in the
hospital if you go there for something
quick
uh or if you go there on a weekend
because your doctor
it has not have it's not open at the
moment
then you're not gonna get much attention
you're just gonna be like yeah handled
quickly and then
they're gonna be like bye bye see ya
good luck
um that's how it is i think in most
countries
at in year round i think
or do people in america go straight to
the hospital
in any situation is there no small
doctor's offices
uh there are small ones huh we go to the
doctor okay
we go to clinics we go to those small
dogs
okay okay and then maybe japan is just
special
maybe maybe the way we have it is normal
in most places and just
japan is a bit a little bit
[Music]
foreign
my
so
[Music]
in japan people go to the to the
hospital
for having um having a cold
[Music]
it's just normal there it's fascinating
i mean i wouldn't even go to one of
those normal small doctor's offices when
i have a cold i wouldn't i wouldn't
normally i would just chill at home
[Music]
guys
a name that i have to translate one
second
[Music]
a holo uvl tournament
i doubt that that will happen
thank you thank you
patrick and thank you so much oh my god
is that a rainbow
something like a rainbow close to a
rainbow almost a rainbow
thank you for the red super chat and the
pinky and an orange one thank you
it's been a terrifying couple of weeks
for you i have to imagine
finally getting to have that one week
and even then have it be plagued with
issues
as well probably isn't good for your
mental and physical health but you're a
pro and you push through like always
it's one of the longest periods of time
i've gone through without hearing your
voice
your love during meme review was like a
soft to my soul
but at the same time i know that even
more breaks are necessary so keep taking
the vacation i'll wait
and now with the neck injury and keeping
an even busier schedule it's more pure
and
prudent than ever knowing your own
limits so if you even feel the slightest
bit unprepared or we can please take the
day off it's important
thank you thank you yesterday for
example i felt kind of weird um
after going outside for some groceries
and picking up a
quick dinner before the stream and i
felt like kind of sick
but it went away after a little bit i
think it's because the weather here
right now is kind of
how you say it in english how do you say
shru in english
yeah it's getting hotter and and and
like a weird weird kind of hotness
humans not i mean we don't really have
humid leather here
but swampy monkey
maybe that's the right word
moist
yeah it's just not comfortable it makes
you feel
weird and i think there's a lot of
people who are really sensitive to that
kind of weather
yeah and yesterday that kind of got me
for a moment
[Music]
moist
yeah but don't worry so guys keep like
thank you for the sweet words i'll
i'll take care of myself and yeah
[Music]
i did not really i wasn't able to take
full advantage of my
vacation which is really quite the waist
especially with like the fact that i
can't
take a vacation that often that easily
now
and like a full vacation for a long time
um and the fact that you know
it did cost a lot of money like i spent
a lot of money because i wanted it to be
a nice location
and then you know those those things
with having to
get another flight and get one day later
blah blah blah it's just really stupid
it was so
and and those things were so unnecessary
and actually one thing happened
that i did not talk about yet
that pissed me off
both me and rmt were pissed off
because um you know we were staying
in this pretty pretty nice hotel i would
say
one of the best hotels in that area
and um we got we got
in for the first few nights we got a
room
that was uh not a standard room already
a quite nice room with like a pool
uh that comes with the room like a
outside pool
really nice already that room already
looks really nice
i mean the inside was kind of small
smaller than expected um
but under the pool was really nice to
chill at rmt was always
chilling at the pool like and there was
like a bed that was half in the water
outside and actually it was really deep
too so you could actually swim
properly in it
[Music]
not a jacuzzi a proper pool
yeah but for the last night we actually
booked
a room category that was one category
higher
um uh
or like maybe two i don't know but it
was definitely a higher category
um because actually we booked it because
i mean for the last night
the room that we were gonna book for the
full
sale was not available for the last
night anyway and
that one fancy room kind of
yeah was something that we definitely
wanted to try out but we
we wouldn't want to stay in there for
the whole stay so it was actually quite
perfect so we booked it for the last
night
and you know it was it was
advertised with
very specific photos with very specific
um equipment
there was just this one thing this this
one super special
thing about this room that was in every
photo
it was so obvious
and it was just the thing that made this
room special
one specific thing it was i don't know
other than that it was very similar to
the room that we had before
but there was just this one thing that
made this room
special so
we were looking really forward to the
last night uh to the last
day we were planning to instead of going
to the ocean
we were gonna spend that day in our pool
because that one would have been special
no not no seaside view actual the actual
some like
a a thing an affirmative piece of
furniture
that comes with that room that wasn't
every photo there was no photo
of the room on the home page without it
so you would think you would get it
and then we move the room
and we immediately notice it's not there
[Music]
and we're we're both like super confused
and the reception lady actually brought
us to the to the room
so she immediately saw our reaction
she's like what's wrong and we're like
are you sure this is the right room
because it doesn't have the thing
are you sure about it like seems like a
different room category this can't
possibly be the same room category right
like you wouldn't charge the same amount
of money
if the the most important thing about
this room that you keep on advertising
is not included and she
left us and said wait well check at the
reception
uh and we'll call you just stay in the
room
and then like 30 minutes later she
finally calls and she's like yeah i
don't know that's right and
um this is the category that you booked
and
blah blah blah see i know exactly
how these things offer how these people
operate i know exactly and my roommate
does
too um
i know i know hotels do this kind of
stuff they
they advertise rooms in a certain way
and then you get a room that look
definitely does not
look the way it looks in the photos but
but it was such an important part of the
room
and literally the reason why we booked
it and the thing is like we we went
outside to the pool area
of our room and we looked left and then
there was the same room next to us
supposedly the same room category but
that room had the thing
that room had the thing and the room
next to it as well the room next to it
as well in the room next to it as well
so both me and rmt
start getting pretty mad because
if it doesn't have the thing that we
could have just booked a cheaper room
because other than that
there is barely a difference even the
bathroom is smaller
so like it was just
lame and we wanted to turn
into karen's we want it we tried a
little bit but both of us are just like
decent
decent human beings i mean i'm a phoenix
but
you know it was really difficult to
be a karen we tried but we failed
because
we did not you know they told we we we
went there and i was like
this this makes no sense you can't this
is false advertisement you can't do this
i we did not get what we booked you know
that on your home page
for every photo of that room category
there is that thing on the photo you
know that don't you
but we that is the reason why we booked
it
and yeah we both tried it but we didn't
get what we wanted
because they said that they were fully
booked uh
and and then we were like okay but how
about giving us
a different room category then one
that's even better
we didn't even talk about whether or not
we would pay for that but
they were like nah we're fully booked
which i don't really believe because i'm
pretty sure that something like the
presidential suit
sweet would have been available i don't
think your presidential suite was booked
come on give us the presidential suite
for free you up
how can you leave out such an important
detail
now i was getting so mad but i could
barely show how mad i was to the
to the reception because i'm a nice
person
i'm a decent person but they we made
uh it very cleared how unhappy we were
um but they just didn't do anything
about it and i i mean
in other hotels i when you're
unhappy with it and you don't get what
you want they usually try their best
to do something even if if they can't
give you the room that they that you
want
they would at least try something else
like give you free breakfast for one day
or
give you a little discount or give you
a room upgrade to a different room or or
give you a little
uh give you a free dinner or give you
bring your um
like drinks to your room or something
there's so many
things you can do as a hotel i can think
of a million things that you could do to
at least show some kind of
you know and gig in common what's that
in english
yeah um
empathy maybe compensate yeah
compensation
or consideration doesn't even have to be
like financial compensation
can't be anything i've seen that before
so yeah uh it did not get resolved they
did not even send those cookies or
anything to the room
nothing nothing
[Music]
that was quite disappointing we were
both disappointed
uh could have just stayed in the cheaper
room
it was quite much more expensive there
was a big um
big price difference but the room before
it was
low-key better
lame
[Music]
yeah we were thinking about writing a
review uh
but in the end like
you know the whole thing happening with
my neck in the next morning
it i was just like whatever although i'm
still very disappointed that they also
did not give me any refund for my
massage evil
like nothing first the room
thing and then the spot my neck and all
that
yeah actually yeah there was a lot of
things that
kind of ruined the last day
of our stay i mean
i wouldn't say that the thing ruined it
that's like that would be
maybe exaggerating it's just it's just
lame
but but i have to say that for example
the staff
were all so sweet
the the bellman and the the
bar the the waiters and waitresses from
the bar
and all that everyone was so so sweet i
gave them so many tips all the time
they were so kind and it didn't seem
like a fake kindness it seemed like a
real kindness
that was fascinating to me because
then i gotta be honest like in other
hotels
the the staff always seemed like they
were
putting on a fake kindness very fake but
here it seemed very natural
yes but that just again shows me that
greek people are so
freaking amazing and sweet and i love
them
[Music]
um
everyone wants to know what the thing
was well
the room was very
a very stylish room
and had a lot of atmosphere and one one
one of the things that
made that so awesome was that
like you know there's this pool and
there's the bed
that's like half in the pool again that
was there that was there
but there was supposed to be
a really dope hammock
on the other side of the pool
and that was just in every photo
and i was so mad that it was not there
because it it it just that's the only
reason we booked the room
it was the only reason we booked it and
it was not there
like how can you i'm sorry i'm just
i just don't get it like how is that the
same room category
okay chill chill chiara chill
[Music]
oh oh dear
oh my god okay
yeah hammocks are dope like you know
imagine imagine
we could have chilled so nicely
you know one of us chilling on the bed
and the other person chilling
in the hammock and every now and then
you jump into the pool and
then you chill again and the ham look at
the sun ah
that would have been so nice
that would have been so nice but yeah
yeah it is what it is it's over now
and um while i was very disappointed
it is what it is
but one thing that i did think
the way that those pools looked was the
bed like like a like a
uh like not a proper bed but you know
what i mean
like a bed at the pool house in the pool
hop in the water
and that looks so cool
i want something like that one day
if i ever get like a house like a tiny
small house
because what what would i get a big
house for except for cats
no but i want i want something like that
but i don't
think that any
houses like that exist in australia
that doesn't look like something
they would build in my country
i mean there is there are houses with
pools but with that kind of design
i doubt it but like you could yeah yeah
have a custom made but
i don't know that seems like a lot of
trouble
a lot of work
[Music]
i don't feel like doing that on my own
i don't know but that is something that
is far far far away in the future i
think
like the trend building stream
oh we could i should i should
should i build it myself like you know
those videos that keep on getting
recommended of uh people
building like super awesome pools in in
the jungle
nowhere just with hands like only two
people building it
should we do something like that
i'm just gonna build with my bare hands
noodle arms shut up they look like they
have no arms too
they don't look very strong either they
just know what they're doing i just
gotta learn how they do it
map it out in minecraft
bare hands then a t-shirt
don't make fun of my pronunciation
[Music]
be resourceful i am resourceful
okay that was a long tangent oh my god
we're never gonna get done again
oh hey but the stream is only one hour
38 minutes long for now
wow good that the game was so short
[Music]
thank you so much i hope you're happy
you made such a huge huge
huge attention
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh and i'm probably gonna ruin my sleep
schedule again today
because i i went to bed last night like
accidentally uh around midnight and then
woke up
at 8am but i took a nap later on because
i knew
i knew that i need a nap otherwise i
can't be
like energetic at 10 pm yeah and here we
are still streaming so
but i'll try my best to sleep early but
but
for that we have to read the super chats
let's go chris dobbs danke soon city
doncaster
oh see that's sweet don't worry
randall thank you and randall thank you
oh man these welcome back messages come
on
randall thank you kakun thank you for
red super chat
welcome home boss i miss you so much you
kept me you kept on making content even
on vacation
you released an absolutely amazing cover
song
and two funny zoo videos thank you yeah
i did
you are a very hard working woman who
really loves the chickens and we can
feel that best or she ever loved
thank you yes indeed i have been
trying to work hard even on my occasion
thank you soon continued the rainbow oh
what do you mean rainbow that doesn't
look like a rainbow
i saw a rainbow what do you mean he
did he continued the rainbow of someone
[Music]
else
wait let me take um my head hurts funny
funny thing my shoulder my neck doesn't
hurt but my head hurts so let me take a
look
okay okay okay
[Music]
dora's card got blocked ah what
ah
oh i i understand now that was not jd's
message that was so nice message
okay thank you
i understand oh randall also finished it
together
oh wait it was so let's keep my birthday
happy super late birthday
yay i saw that in the message here
your gift to me was coming home you're
it oh come on
happy birthday to you
i hope you played randall and today back
happy birthday to us
[Music]
did you pay them back already it's so
sweet how kfb helps out in these times
cute but now i gotta of course you have
to
mr cass big thanks for the pinky i'm
sorry your vacation started and ended on
bummer notes i hope you
and rmt still had a fun time no worries
if you want to light a schedule as you
heal you know what's best for kiana and
i have faith in your decision
i went on a bit of
thank you oh wait oh wait no no no it
continues with a different account
that's very confusing but that's too
pinky so that's one word
i went in a bit of a kia nostalgia watch
while you were away thanks for all the
great memories
thanks for the memories even though they
went so great
[Music]
thanks for all the great moments and
memories in these past nine months and
thanks for the amazing cover
nearly a million already yes yes that's
true for real girls now
well and take care mama bird and good to
have you back we care about you thank
you i think it should reach 1 million in
maybe in the next five to 10 hours
let's go let's go
sorry i'll broke for a moment
[Music]
thanks for welcoming me back i'm glad to
be back oh
thank you thank you
i wonder what you were watching on that
kiara nostalgia trip
what were you wanting let me know
kristaps
in kyoto and alex duncan
i hope you had fun on your vacation also
fun for the dog
for the doctor didn't even cost me money
but thank you
i mean i mean i guess it costs
indirectly money because i'm paying for
my
uh what's it called
insurance the funny thing is the more
money
you guys give me to pay for the doctor
and
the more money i have to pay for my
insurance
it's a it's an interesting endless loop
isn't it so
maybe stop giving me money so that i
have to pay less money
the irony
it was bad luck impossible
well thank you though
[Music]
no no no it's okay guys thank you don't
worry it was just a joke
you honestly can't follow instructions
anyway as we can see
lucky for the top thunderstorm for the
pinky yeah it's four a.m
way past the happy sleep i can't get
over her
motherf f and fun and 100 say so you
collab with coco was
dabbing on tech issues and pain like a
pro oh
yeah thanks for the sweet salad of the
cocoa and confirming your cup size
205 welcome back queen thank you
oh yeah we didn't really talk about the
whole
reddit uh stream huh
i feel like that went really well and
honestly i was so happy with all the
lovely feedback like i was reading
through
tweets a lot and the tets knuckles
seemed very happy with it and and all of
them
wrote like
it was a good decision to have chiara be
the last guest
and that made me very happy yeah
i i i'm glad that i didn't ruin it or
anything
and it went on much longer than expected
which i have absolutely no problem with
even though for me it was like early in
the morning at the end
um but it was worth it and i'm so
so honored to be part of such a special
episode
although you know obviously it's a it's
a very sad
thing if you think about it but
i don't know i um
i in in streams like that i it's hard
for me to
really act uh appropriately to
like what's actually going on like i i i
i can't
really let out those sad feelings but i
guess that was a good thing
yeah we wanted it to be we wanted to be
positive we wanted to be happy
yeah it was i felt like you know that
made me really realize we're like
sisters you know the whole
comparisons of our designs and then now
even the braids and
i don't know we were we are somewhat
similar in like
being able to speak these languages and
and having these like um like
regular programs that introduce other
people
and all that like there are a lot of
similarities i think
and um while i might be a little bit
more of a tame
version i hope that
in some way i can
[Music]
do similar things and
be i don't know it's hard to say
but she does inspire me for
the future carry on her leg legacy
legacy like
legends yeah something like that like
leg
the leg game i'm gonna carry on the leg
game
ties and thighs you know
yeah um i think that
i think i i could i can do it if
if i work very very very very hard
i only saw a light game once but what do
you mean
i showed my legs to you several times
[Music]
big shoes to fill yeah i think her shoe
size must be very big because she she
is so big
uh but yeah um
[Music]
um who knows we might do a reddit
meme review uh as well someday
maybe maybe something with a little
twist if i can think of a twist
yes cause you know i i am the most
active member of all life on reddit
look at my karma i mean the only reddit
uh
thing that i look at is the whole live
one because i don't know how the hell
reddit works but
but still so i got all that
karma
[Music]
flexing with my karma that's not a good
thing what do you mean
i mean karma is not a good thing
oh you mean being on reddit so much i'm
not okay i'm not on there every day
but i'm probably on there more than
anyone else
like even not only for posting things
about my streams i don't even do that
that much
but like just going through everyone's
memes in general everyone's posts
yeah and often i read through a lot of
comments on those posts as well
i just keep on reading and reading and
reading
to see what you guys are discussing
[Music]
feel so long since i gave you the last
kiss now
thank you welcome back thank you i am
back and i'm glad to be back thank you
tai chi
for the support glad you're still here
waiting for me
jim tracy dankeshen typhoon dan kishan
thank you for the red superchat typhon
welcome back here hopefully everything
was amazing outside of the neck issues
well we know it was not but
anyway we missed you hopefully you
didn't burn everyone on the beach too
badly
i imagine just being in the presence of
a relaxing phoenix can cause
minor burns to everyone around her
yeah i like that
i like it yeah rmt ended up with quite a
lot of
painful sunburns yeah
yeah poor rmt even
already on the second day it took took a
didn't taking much time
[Music]
hey i did put sunscreen on her i did
i did on her back
that was uh very uh nice to have someone
you know put sunscreen on one another
obviously
i didn't need it but i
obviously didn't need it myself
[Music]
who's back i'm back
yeah oh well she'll recover from it but
it seemed very very painful
for her thank you though tyson
thank you for the sweet message i'm glad
i'm back
families will be good oh you'll be fine
john smith fight though
fighting
i believe in you pudding channel thank
you and gd dangerous
wow welcome back i hope you feel better
soon thank you
i'm feeling quite okay at the moment
thank you for
worrying about me thank you very kind of
you
say i thank you also for the red super
[Music]
yeah i ate a lot of uh watermelons yum
yum yum yum yum yum yum
they actually tasted different
er partially some of them is
different in in uh greece
oh watermelons yes i ate watermelons not
chickens
[Music]
um
welcome back i miss you so much i hope
your neck will cover soon i hope so too
and we'll be fine i am daijoubu
account name thank you thank you
you
[Music]
mmm
um
[Music]
hope the festival is as fun for you as
it is for us to watch
you've been busy boss lately with all
these fun streams
i know you men i know i've mentioned you
are my aussie before
but i want to say thank you for putting
the effort in i also hope your neck gets
better thank you
moon dog that is so sweet yeah the
moment i got back from
my holiday hour i was already super
super busy
but that that day i'm glad it's over
that day was uh crazy
very crazy those 24 hours
i'm glad that's over everything was fun
but yeah i would have preferred to
spread it out a little
bit more thank you
i'm glad to be your aussie please
please don't change that ever
ax jazz duncan
[Music]
you have granted two of my wishes thank
you so much for always the fun and the
wonderful times
[Music]
fight
he forgot to write which which wishes i
granted for him
he just wrote in the chat one of them
was the collab of coco but what was
the other one is it a secret
kiana is so cute and so are all of you
you are not wrong with that you're very
correct
those two foxes are so cute can you give
me one those are my foxes
and my fluffy kitty cats i know they're
adorable i know i know
[Music]
you're welcome haven't played trauma so
thank you for pinky
what have you what do you have to say
this time huh
yeah since your last little talk i
wanted to ask is kirio koko your sister
you both have orange hair your eye color
is almost the same you both speak fluent
english and japanese and of course you
both don't wear panties is that all
coincidence
so i'm gonna guess you wrote that super
chat
because you saw the reddit uh stream
you were fully aware of that
and just because you're a troll you you
ask that question again
well we will we might be
[Music]
i like to think we are because it's just
really cute but there was so much
art of us like making each other's
braids
it was so cute it was so cute
[Music]
probably hasn't been feeling so well for
a while now
um but i'm glad that she got some energy
for those collaborations to draw that
i'm glad i helped her a little bit i'm
sure she's really
sad at the moment because uh koko sanpai
was her first oshie
and her only one for a long time so
yeah must be very sad
[Music]
oh yeah she's probably also working on
something big for cuckoo sample i guess
probably oh
i'm excited to see it breakfast band
dancing
greg fuji dance
and dance
and
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat that's
actually the last one from this stream
central greetings from a lonely employee
no we're lonely
i know you're ending soon so gonna send
my super chat before you leave good
timing
miss you so much but i'll bother you
next time hope it doesn't i'll see you
in archive and next room
oh thank you thank you
thank you thank you felix
then i'm looking forward to your next
message
next up is the one from yesterday
oh wait i think i need to download the
thumbnail for that one too
because i made it on my laptop i think
for one second
yeah green cat is smoothie orange cat is
jonquis
oh wait no i don't have it
don't have it
i love that artwork i love it
the moment i saw it i was like this is
perfect this is gonna be the thumbnail
[Music]
you know what let me refresh this
wow
[Music]
how come a rebel caller and someone can
show their cats for you one well i'm
showing them here
am i not but no that's just a choice
that i made
personally i think it's uh probably
the best choice okay continuing
continuing mastercard's big donkey
[Music]
they need some privacy okay
uh patrick chen punkish and kill joey
dankeshen mystic has big zan kitchen
sorry about it low-key distracted
mr kazakhstan general duncan the crystal
duncan
terrific player in the shadow of stream
especially that only win against
skittles be proud but
oh thank you oh my god i was so
on edge during the shadow race stream we
already talked a lot about it yesterday
but man like i was so nervous
i took it so seriously i was so nervous
i'm so nervous damn
i could have done everything much better
better but the pressure of being in a
tournament
is a bigger than i thought it would be
[Music]
yeah ah
i killed giga i did
[Music]
yeah oh that was pretty unlucky
in some situations which is unfortunate
but hey there you go that's just rng
it all paid off yeah i guess so you got
second
yeah i mean there were two second places
i guess i guess you know if if we would
have done a little bit better in the
mini games i could have been second
like the only second but it's okay
i am one of the two seconds that's okay
too
one more such a cool person to have is a
course yeah i love momma
i love mama i'm definitely thinking
of you know doing a little collab at
some point with her
we got along very well and she's very
sweet
she's super super sweet i like her a lot
yeah and you know it's just fitting
because like she was the only coach that
is also a bitchuba but that just makes
it very easy to collab with her
her also being a vegetable just
automatically makes me want to collab
yeah yep
[Music]
you bounce off each other really well oh
you don't even know
you don't even know because you don't
you didn't even listen
uh we weren't even able to listen in
most of the time
but yeah we got along
quite well quite okay i would say
[Music]
hmm
foreign
[Music]
there you are again love your red super
chat wow
thank you thank you i hope your neck is
getting better and something completely
irrelevant
do you know
chicken neck is a traditional
traditional snack in some places i think
we should try expanding the items on our
menu a little bit
yeah that that is totally unrelated
[Laughter]
what the hell
oh no i don't think that that should be
part of the menu
no no sorry no
no not you
there you go
[Music]
random spider-man is that right to the
chat
i think it might be welcome back to joe
i hope you take a good rest after the
shadow bridge tournament i just
finished watching the vlog you did a
great job even though you're in pain
after the osaka and summer festivals
thank you for noticing
i'm really proud of you thank you
yeah it was a tough day but we it went
quite well um actually yeah after that
after that summer festival stream i
quickly um
ran off to buy a new charger thingy
and that thankfully fixed the issue
i'm glad it did yeah
thank you for supporting me and watching
all those streams and
you know i guess i'm guessing you also
watch the shadow first stream so
thank you very much that was a really
long stream thank you everyone who came
there
to support me and kelly it means a lot
to us
thank you very very much and if you
haven't watched it live you can still
watch the archive
on youtube on shadowbase official
channel
[Music]
it was fun to watch even though i don't
play i'm happy to hear that
it was still fun to watch i'm happy
thank you it was surprisingly fun
yeah the mini games were probably most
fun for the people who don't know
shadowverse
i think those were pretty good and
generally i just thought it was
fascinating the way the whole
stream was like built up like like i
don't know the
it was kind of professional
don't know the whole layouts and all of
that and and
muting specific people it was very well
made most of the time
[Music]
i guess this is normal for like uh
like tournament esports tournaments
i think that's the way that it is
the way that that worked was kind of
normal for esports
but that was the first time i kind of
saw that really cool
no scuff how inspiring
ah the lord were cute
you're welcome oh
chong has just walked into the room and
then
the moment she's like she entered the
room she just flops down on the floor
and stretched good stretch i mean you're
here right here obviously
but hi mimi
now she's just staring into the voice
and lying on the floor without moving at
all
is that comfortable i think the floor is
probably a bit
um cooler than
the sofa or whatever that's probably why
she likes it
and she's waiting for the pets but no
pets now
i mean you're getting padded on stream
already
relatable trunkers yeah hi
she looked at me and now she's like oh
stretching again
oh it's not being so cute stupid cats
so cute
i already gave her a lot of pets today
mama
i bet jonquez is super smart no not
really
[Music]
maybe it's a little late after those
three unforgettable streams but welcome
back to angel
the week went by fast and with both of
your mzu videos
and your amazing goodbye decoration
cover you still kept me
you still kept me company i hope you had
lots of fun
davia that was on purpose wasn't it
was it not it's not supposed to be cough
young
i'm concerned about this stressful slash
injury slash nearly dying trend you have
with your vacations this year
oh yeah the skiing incident
yeah yeah yeah yeah
it's just it's true it's kind of true
i'm praying oh oh wait stop because i
forgot yeah yeah
that's your thing doing uh doing bird
jokes
oh yeah sorry i almost forgot
now it makes sense i thought it was just
a typo
oh yeah bird puns i'm glad those are
back
i'm praying a wink that it doesn't
escalate and you
don't have any more
foul issues
with my future with future vacations
after all
i don't want my only feelings to go
extinct
oh my god
[Music]
my my face is now very tired thanks to
you
thank you
weeks weeks go by so fast anyway
so oh my gosh she's falling asleep on
the floor she's so cute
[Music]
i like the floor it's comfy isn't it
oh she's just chilling it's like she
wanted to get
it in any case she just wanted to get
into the same room as me but she really
didn't get far she just
laid down immediately after she entered
the room like
right at the door
[Laughter]
[Music]
as long as she she knows where i am and
sees
where i am gonna be
in her field of sight
is that the right word an attempt was
made
they always try to be close to me so
cute
so cute feel the view okay
there we go sam rangers and crispy dan
kitchen thank you oh happy birthday
to you crispy
typhoon oh wait it's a late birthday
right now but still
typhoon thank you and cooler man
daisy danger and fruitful thank you for
the alright
[Music]
and christian welcome back amazing
phoenix
oh
it's going fast it's speeding
worth it thank you
thank you um
so sweet people from the same time zone
staying
up together with me throughout the whole
shadowburst tournament
wow wow that's dedication
one million endurance no
no no no no
the cat has turned over like a pancake
again
i guess are you trying to get a tab
from the uh light in this room i think
she's trying to get a 10.
um gotta get
every side and every angle
pet the belly i want to but i also don't
want to get up
the great feeling is duncan dominique
i really miss you talking super giant
reading streams but either way till the
end of times if it's what it takes
to have you healthy and happy than you
thank you
well you got what you wanted it's back
[Music]
don't deny her the belly button she's
just getting it on stream right now
[Music]
thank you a game called out of space
co-op game that might be good for
columns
oh is it good
out of space sounds like something ame
would play
thank you welcome back it's okay to
listen to your travel story later take
care attention okay if we always by your
side take easy don't pushing yourself
too hard it's my bedtime good night and
joe thank you
thank you very much all right i'm
guessing you were saying that you're
gonna watch the archive later
that is okay too but thank you for
saying hello during the stream
whoa i hope you enjoyed the archive
thank you for your support thank you
florida black friction thank you and
looking for the top dangation
mokul ronald duncation hey the best
feelings in the world there are not many
here but i really want to support you
oh get well and be okay that's the main
thing for us
russian fans love you too really
thank you spaceva
thank you thank you
[Music]
thank you for the support spicy chicken
tacos
[Music]
thanks kenneth for making my birthday
great yesterday with all those dreams
despite being injured oh you're welcome
happy late birthday
nice sniping and proud impressed with
your shadowverse skills even taking down
good luck thank you
i wish you a fast recovery love you yeah
but honestly
my coach was helping me every second
turn so a lot of it is thanks to the
to the coach obviously
yeah on a spaceship that is infected by
aliens you have to clean it
oh that sounds cool
[Music]
but actually i've also been invited to a
certain
collaboration of what was the game
called again
knockout city yeah
look forward to that never played it
before
that seems fun it seems fun
by the way what's in my audience what's
the maximum amount of players for no
cloud city
[Music]
anyone knows four
three voices free six eight two teams
why is everyone saying something else
free versus free
okay that that makes sense
[Applause]
interesting all right
all right age if you do a private room
oh
interesting
okay i'll keep that in mind black
friction thank you for the pinky
glad to finally have you back with us
hot wings
i haven't been called hot wings in a
while also very relieved that you're
taking it easy this week
thank you for the content while you were
gone and the free streams you did
love your las kiana orange wife love joy
forever
thank you yay oh it's so nice to
see everyone's names again yeah and talk
with you guys again
feels like it's been so long
[Music]
um
thank you i'm gonna take it easy of
course
i mean it's still a lot of streams this
week but there
supposedly a lot of short streams now
i'm just trying to catch up with
the super chats but the other streams
should be
uh shorter even because i don't have to
catch up with super chats
so yeah
but next week is gonna be actually no
i'm i'm taking a few days off next week
as well
uh after after my birthday
i might take three days off in a row
um but it depends on how i'm feeling
that will be decided spontaneously
shocking i know shocking shopping
but next week we'll have holo talk
and a four member collaboration
certain people but that will be japanese
i think because the other members are
japanese
speaking
kiara and the never ending tease yeah i
just don't want to say it too early you
know
i want to say it earlier especially
because it's not even a collab that i
organized i'm happy i'm getting the
other one the knockout city one is also
one that i got invited to so
i'm happy i'm not the one inviting
people about being the one invited that
makes me
a little bit flattered
i'm glad that there's people who want me
in their collabs
i'm glad that they think of me you know
because there's so many people they
could ask
and they think of me
today
[Music]
in in the sniping game in the uh
summer festival now finally people want
me in their team
let's see
that must be it
gamer abilities shown up they'll be
disappointed though i think that was
only me lucky
being lucky it was tiara
then i gotta bring tiana to the
collaborations
do maternal nah i don't wanna
i don't wanna
secretly proficient in fbs and that's
tiara that's not kiana it's tiana
okay continuing jeffrey wong
memo thank you so much
[Music]
no one else in her life is going to know
what that is i don't know evil
uh so i think it would be a new and
unique experience for everyone plus a
cow parade
sounds kind of cute what the hell is
that does anyone know
some people seem to understand because
they're laughing in the chat
eh
eh let me look it up
[Music]
what is that that's cute
is an annual event in the alpene regions
in europe referring to a cattle drive
that takes place in late
september early october oh that's cute
during summer all over the alpine
regions cattle herds feed on
alpine tourists high up in the mountains
a practice known as trans humans
what in numbers these amount to about 5
500 000 in australia
for 380 000 in swift no we don't need a
wing there switzerland and fifty
thousand in germany
well so it's actually pretty big in
australia huh
well there is often some movement of
cattle between the almonds
a ironman
respectively during the summer there's
usually one concentrated
concerted cattle drive in the autumn
to bring the cattle to the barns down in
the valley
if there were no accidents on the album
during the summer
in many areas the cattle are decorated a
la a labor
elaborately elaborately
elaborately and the cattle drive is
celebrated with music feasts and dance
events in the towns and villages
upon arrival in the valley joint herds
from multiple farmers are sorted in the
freeshide and each animal is returned to
its own owner
oh that's cute
so basically they bring uh
like cows from the mountains into the
valley
and they decorate them but not only cows
i guess all kinds of cattle like we
could
do it with um alpacas llamas
and and and horses
that's cute the good thing is with
alpacas
in the in minecraft you can like they
follow one another
you can put them on a lead and they
that kind of sounds cute but kind of
short
wow i learned something new i i did not
know about this because i was not
raised in the mountains i was raised in
the city um
but i guess on the countryside
countryside
of australia that is probably very well
known
[Music]
no kunino
siblings of billing bullying can now
commence
what what who promised me super chat
bullying and why
not only did you bless us with a top
tier song but usa
fest and a seven hour tournament yeah
that is true
whale has surely earned its place in
kiara too ah
all done with a dead neck yep phoenix
foreign thank you
yes i was quite handicapped but yeah
thank you
i tried my best i'm glad that you um
see that and acknowledge it thank you
thank you and thank you freak video
gamer duncan
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat welcome
back 10 to hope you have a speedy
recovery thank you
i don't think i can make it any speedier
but uh i'm feeling fine for now
the the fall recovery will take its time
but now
i'm already feeling pretty good
when is i'm phoenix tangil
wasn't that basically my debut
why you need more than that i guess i
guess at some point i should make an m
phoenix
but i wonder if i i can i only want to
use the idaho
which one i only want to use the iraqi
illustrations and i doubt that there's a
phoenix artwork on
irastoya you know i want to continue
that style
that art style so i can only do
something that they have on that web
website which is basically almost
everything but probably no phoenix's
well well well
yes i do use a voice changer right now i
am using a voice changer
thank you for coming to my stream please
enjoy yay
[Music]
sorry someone asked if i'm using a voice
changer
well sometimes i do
[Music]
well really rarely though
he got destroyed the moment he did more
and more just for you
he did and also i don't know if you guys
know this by my reaction but i was
honestly not very impressed
by it it could have done much better
the artist seemed very hyped up about it
but i was not impressed i was not happy
with it
i wanted him to do it again but everyone
else was so excited
about it so that's where we left it at
[Music]
i was like no that's not it i can do it
better
i'll show you one day when i become 3d
i'll show you
hey where
love the tournament you really showed
off your skills thank you
you laid out the stream whenever you got
to talk
hoping for a momo collab soon oh i will
try to
implement that at some point
thanks for the pinky
okay glad to see you back around this
neck of the woods
[Music]
your tweets had me worried about what it
could be
the second that's what was fun i'm proud
of you for winning some games
in the shadow ways and event and
sticking to your theme in the va game
take it easy thank you but you did
obviously not stick to your theme
of making puns for the whole super chat
you could obviously only think of two
puns huh
beginner what a beginner what a noob
take an example uh with travis g for
example
yeah you can write serious messages even
with puns just look at travertine
he always gets his point across
and it's very enjoyable no just kidding
anyway
thank you thank you
i mean obviously i had to stick to my
theme in the va game because it was
about it was about you know
being being a leader in the game
what what voice lines would you
be doing i had to
oh hopefully they'll implement me
sometime soon i'm waiting for the offer
[Music]
expert
good day and welcome back here kudos to
you for a new and
new annihilating i hate that word
giggot love the banter between you and
faye
i love that too that was really nice to
finally be the one
the popular one in the room
the one that's being chased love
also the two streams before shadow birds
how are the cute is the cutest are
doing fine i think where are they
i don't see them right now oh yeah
but they're doing fine
no no worries thanks for asking
they're always doing fine very clingy we
we spend each night together
yes
yeah trunks is not on the floor anymore
no idea oh they're probably in a
different room now
why probably because i'm too noisy when
i'm streaming they
they sometimes leave me they want
they want a bit more quietness but
usually they're always in the same room
with me normally
do you like hearing vocaloids ah i used
to listen to a lot of
vocaloid back in the day now
not anymore sometimes i listen
to covers of vocaloid songs but that's
about it
wiki tunes thanks thanks also for pinky
thank you
i stayed for the entire stream i loved
so hard when you said i killed giga
yeah that was that was funny i guess i i
i felt uh
um a little bit worried about it later
on i was like what what if that was
maybe
maybe i shouldn't have said that was
that too like aggressive
saying i killed him i was worried but it
seemed to be okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
it went into the history books
it was good it was perfect
[Music]
i hope he had no problem with it mm-hmm
i wish i could have killed them the
second time that would have been so epic
yeah they announced this lighted too
furlough right
[Music]
red super chat
welcome back tai chi you never talk much
do you
it just says welcome back a double red
table chat that just says welcome back
um thank you taiji you sweetheart
thank you very kind of you
[Music]
any irl artist you want to make a song
with
um i was thinking about this today
actually
i would love to eventually
try to commission um
a few producers that worked on
hello project songs
um
in the past
i mean the the people who work on hello
practice songs nowadays are very
different from the ones who worked on it
in the past but i don't know wanna try
at some point but that's still something
that is very very very very very very
very very far
in the future yeah
you had a nice vacation thank you it was
okay
i wish i could say everything was
perfect it was amazing but it wasn't
really
unfortunately yeah anyway
um
[Music]
i don't know maybe um
uh maybe kira
[Music]
you know kira
here i got some really dope vocaloid
music
and uh funny
come lives in a german-speaking country
just like me
and just the name is so similar to my
name
kira kiara hello and
and and
they did getcha with kelly no no that
was a cover that was not an original
and and yeah like has some kind of like
chick icon yeah like the chick and body
is
kira and for me i'm a phoenix okay
there's a big difference there
but it's just so fitting i don't know it
feels like it's meant to be
right and i love the music that kira
makes yeah
it's really cool
that's because you're the same person no
oh
[Music]
why why could you not
think of anything really nothing
nothing at all you wanted to tell me
boy
bran damn gangster
do you plan on doing a minecraft
creative mode stream in the future
uh not really not really i mean
especially not for our own travel
we're gonna i don't think we will ever
use creative mode
it would be so easy so useful but yeah
i think people would complain so
[Music]
it's probably not happening
thank you for the pinky
nice sponge nice font nice fun
no it would get mad yeah
and i think people just genuinely um
with minecraft there's a lot of people
who have a lot of issues
but it's a fun game and most of the time
it's all
such a carefree game which is what i
like about it
yup yup yup yup what's what's going on
with his pinkies
thank you delta adele stop
congratulations you you wrote welcome
back
with a question mark you're not even
sure about it
what the hell every number called thank
you
on gig extreme he said he was really
impressed with one of your plays oh
you managed to save yourself from a
lethal without a coach
from his lethal oh interesting
i kind of want to like watch his point
of view there
a little bit but it was on twitch right
i need i need a clip i saved myself from
his lethal
did i did i do it i wonder if i did that
knowingly
or if that was by by accident
uh when i crystallized
oh yeah probably
i think i remember yeah yeah i think i
know what you mean because his like
artifacts whatever they can
not attack uh me directly they can
only attack me through
something i have on the board i guess
and for crystallizing whatever i
had on the board was not attackable
anymore i guess
something like that i think
yeah but i i mean i don't i didn't do
that
while being 100 aware of what that was
doing
um i i i
i'm not sure what i was thinking anymore
but i guess it was a good move smart
kiara
i read that in german elka w thank you
salar and kill
when we ever see alta kiana again i'm
really lazy it's annoying to
prep that at some point sure
one one day lexington the lion thank you
an unknown thank you and sarah thank you
catch
and elvis thank you for the red super
chat
boom dia welcome back here i hope you
enjoyed your vacation and i look forward
to hearing about it
last week was pretty lonely without your
streams but i'm glad you had fun
take care and hope the pain in your neck
gets better thank you i mean it wasn't
even a full week come on
come on kp i know you love me and i love
you and yeah yeah yeah it was a little
bit tough for you guys i i understand
come on it was not even the full week
but thank you when did you
there you sent the super chat talking
about this uh shadowverse
tournament you said you are the perfect
representative of whole life of all ian
you're the most i don't like of all
why don't you remember that that was
really sweet of you
anyway elvis thank you
thank you um i hope it gets better soon
too
because once it gets better i want to
start doing a bit more exercise
[Music]
x foreign the hell ellis
elvis don't ask me
[Music]
oh
what should i eat today can you continue
buy a mutant oh
i'm glad you liked it i guess but it was
supposed to be a one time only stream
sorry i got so many other street
uh games i want to play you know
[Music]
w-2 text from dancing
this look area thank you for the red
super chat wow
welcome back and good luck with your
neck mp4 versions of cattle let's go oh
yeah yeah
i have them now i have them they're so
cute i mean jolly was the one who
originally came up with these
you know designs
of my cats so i'm i'm i'm happy
you chose her to make these animated
versions for my stream
[Music]
they just look so fluffy when she draws
them
so cute i just can't get enough of them
thank you thank you very much honestly i
i love them so
much i will have them on here
a lot of time oh probably almost always
i love them they look so happy too and
they look so fluffy oh my god they're so
good
and and look how the the
uh first movie they they go upwards
they they grow upwards and for junkers
they're like downloads i'm so cute ah
cute
[Music]
and i don't know was that on purpose i
wonder to
have them be petted by
like one one by the left hand and one by
the right hand so i can
if i wanted to i could have them both on
the screen at the same time i wonder if
that was on purpose
it actually works
[Music]
forward thinking oh big brain
yes yes all according to plan
ultimate shout out thank you and super
part of your performance
during the shout out with cinnamon thank
you so much
gd donkey shirt and pepper chen
dangester and unknown danish and thanks
for the pinky
my last pinky was a mistake anyway
welcome back to enjoy i missed you so
much please take it easy i really hope
you recover soon
thank you i am taking it easy thank you
for
waiting for me and thank
[Music]
alright alright alright alright
okay there you go smoothie but your head
moves so much
don't put it on your on your thigh
it looks so cozy with all the pillows
too
yeah my neck accident
thank you thank you for asking i am i am
fine
oh my god i remember korean
that came that came out of nowhere
[Music]
i learned that in that baby show that i
was watching
superman superman
blah blah something like that
[Music]
uh this super chat is apparently for
cryptex
23 because that person cannot super chat
thank you for the support dominique
george from texas chocolate insomniac
and thanks for the pinky
[Music]
welcome back tanja we missed you very
much while you were on vacation
not gonna lie we were pretty worried for
you because you were jumping up and down
when you
when we knew you had a sprint nectar
oh yeah yeah don't worry don't worry
it's it's uh as i said yesterday it's a
bit exaggerated
the movement so um but don't worry
and and and don't worry i'm not hurting
myself with these movements
at this point it's mostly okay again in
the beginning
i literally couldn't move my head and
and
even without moving it i was in huge
pain
it was ridiculous thank you
chocolate insomniac thank you
for the red super chat really loved how
you sang my kitsune
okay oh thank you i guess yeah that
that's a while ago but you weren't able
to super chat then huh
never expected you to sing any metal
song at all so it surprised me metal
metal took a giant role in my life
forged my warrior spirit
thank you for saying that when i think i
can't love you more you prove me wrong
thank you maybe i'll sing another
babymetal song
at some point
i think i will because i like a few of
their songs i just
like megitsona the most
[Music]
cupcake thank you wait hold on you
didn't get a kiss
cupcake thank you again thank you
hold her challenger what the say my
sentence of one month
and one day has ended
ah and i must say
my ui was bored as nothing was
there like literally only void was there
how was i supposed to be re-educated
there
okay okay a little piece of i
you you okay i'm putting you back in the
usual room for
one more month because uh
we are currently working on the usual
room
[Music]
[Laughter]
you will see soon uh you will see
that's all i'll say stop stop
stop teasing me
you'll end up being in there forever and
ever and ever
trust me you don't want that it's it's
terrifying over there
horrifying it's not a nice place to be
in
nam
[Music]
is there wi-fi no there's no wi-fi there
there was nothing but then you were
blind or something
hey what stop changing the lord there is
something
and in order to make you guys imagine it
better
a certain someone has been working on
artwork for the usual room so shut up
now
no you can't just decide what what it
looks like and how it works don't do
that
no you're not you're not the game master
i am
[Music]
[Laughter]
what the hell do you want moto sun yoshi
ram only exists because it works
once i was a very bad chicken empty reds
but juice and we cried imaginable but
now i'm fake
there you go all i took are free trips
to the basement and the permanent
ringing noise behind my ear when they
put the microchip
you get a kiss for that
[Music]
so what do we learn from that you don't
want to go to the usual room you don't
want to go there
no
[Laughter]
bunk everyone bunk hook on right now
bonk him to the moon and even further
even beyond
[Music]
prime thanks for the pinky the finish of
you was like an awesome anime episode
the rest of this happens
is
respect for those card players who learn
and master all those decks and
strategies
[Music]
um
and poco are definitely easier
but you know once you learn um how
a card game like that works it's really
so
so so much fun i mean you don't have to
do
there are so many other ones magic for
example or classic
that i can even still recommend to this
day
and they're really fun but i guess you
kind of need someone to play with
if it's uh a card game that
that you can't play online but that's
the good thing about
shadowverse wait can you play magic to
gathering online by now by any chance
is that a thing that happened
[Music]
yes oh that's so cool
arena that's so cool i didn't know
wow wow the times have changed it's been
it's been a long time i feel old now
online
[Music]
that is
pretty much all tgc are playable if not
only
only playable oh my no oh yeah the times
have changed huh
i like playing them in reality though
thank you
i am is that something i should not read
i am i'm i am
is that dangerous you say
i don't know is it i am carlos
thank you looking for the top functions
[Music]
oh god this whole thing is in spanish
you don't honestly expect me to read
this out loud
you won't are you kidding me let me try
oh hi
[Music]
and espanol
why don't you use google translate okay
wanna translate
i get it hopefully everything is fine
with you and you had a good time on your
vacation i sent you this message to tell
you
thank you very much for everything you
do for your employees i love you karaoke
and i hope you can sing more songs in
spanish
i don't know about that
but like like songs that have like
partially a little bit spanish inside
okay we can do that but
oh spanish cells are gonna be a bit
difficult
[Music]
meow
that song was everywhere
for way too long
that is how coco sings it
she gave me the impression that her
spanish is already pretty good but i
guess that was
fake
[Music]
ryan b danish and maple leaf two five
uh two five zero one a
pudding channel thank you an image
singing neo storm fox thank you
from ginger ranger 13 petrichen thank
you so much
oh am i also recognized you have a great
range and an unarchived member karaoke
when she was singing my heart will go on
with you and she was singing alongside
my cover of it her exact words were damn
chiara got pipes
really such a thing happened and i don't
even know about
it she didn't do it with me
what
yeah i guess that's members only but oh
well i'm glad i i found out about that
thank you
it was public not ah oh okay that was
public but on archives ah okay okay
you're real non-member aha
[Music]
hey
you probably have already but if not you
should seriously consider
seeing a medically certified
physiotherapist
why are you um why are you
writing specifically a medically
certified
do you know about my previous
experiences but those those are
medically certified as well
also cracking your neck if not done
correctly can do a lot of bad stuff to
you like pinched nerves
or sprained torn muscles yep now that's
exactly what happened to me funny thing
thank you for
the advice sixth true
magician thank you soon star mistakes
daisy thank you and maple
[Music]
guys i'll probably not read the super
chats from today
because my throat is really uh dry again
and no matter how much i drink it's not
feeling so good
[Music]
i'm just gonna finish up these ones from
yesterday
thank you thank you i love you all
you're so sweet
the gamestar 101 dancing
and now i'm the ones 247 and
thunderstorm doctor here oh we got
another joke
which is always always very curious
warming an area is usually helpful for
regeneration helps the nerves and
muscles cooling it
helps against pain and swelling if the
pain is manageable try warmth oh
okay that makes sense
yeah yeah yeah yeah that makes sense
jonathan's moving yay
you need to get your rest anyway yeah i
guess so
also need to eat dinner first though
nago should be proud of you you have
come so far in life
you're like you already wrote that to me
you've been at it for over three hours
well i can pet them forever honestly i'm
so addicted to my cats
i'm so addicted i literally can't stop
petting them
outside of a stream i'm 24 7 petting
them
really aren't you goodbye saying in
cover thank you
i'm so happy to hear that honestly i did
not expect so much
uh good feedback about it
what are you looking for when you hire a
producer it for a song
um well
obviously someone who i like the music
off
yeah and i guess
[Music]
budget and someone who seems
accessible
[Music]
but i mean up until now i've only worked
with
one producer
uh so it's a bit hard to say
yeah uni teacher thank you and thanks
for the pinky
hospital will have 100 in their acting
so you could ask if they can send you to
the fund well i mean i guess i have the
buffon but it just doesn't say much
though
if it doesn't go away i recommend you to
go to the ortho and maybe they can
prescribe professional physiotherapy
yeah
i mean i did physical therapy before
and it did not really do much but yeah
[Music]
i'll definitely go to the doctor again
don't worry
and this continues later on with another
pinky i was sent to it once after having
issues with my spine and muscle
in my neck after a car crash oh
which helped a lot by the way you are
very powerful delivering those free hype
streams after all that is amazing
yeah and no more neck cracks well you
saw it on my
on my twitter today i gave everyone the
advice of not doing the same thing that
i did
and if i can i would love to
get rid of that habit but we will see
how it goes
after after everything
heals again we'll see how it goes
um i'll obviously try to not crack it
but
at the moment i have not been able to
crack it because of the pain
if i go in that direction so maybe
maybe i'll be able to get rid of that
habit
i will try but the whole habit has
started only because of pain
so in order to not do that i will have
to get rid of that pain first
i think otherwise it's pretty um
unbearable thank you
for the two pinkies you need chad you
gotta kiss me for that
wow thank you very much thank you
as well thank you oh
that does not sound good dominique
thanks for thinking here's some cash so
you can buy
paper a ruler and duct tape to make a
homemade neck brace
you know i really think that a neck
brace would help me with my posture
so i was often joking about even before
even before this whole thing i talked to
to you guys about it before did i not
that i want a neck brace
it would make me really stiff
shut up my post
my posture shut up
never mind then whatever you're teasing
me so i'll continue
[Laughter]
shut up shut up
how long is this black working danish
and thanks for the red super chat
please thank you for the care of your
well-being canada don't accept pain
because you've had it for so long
that kind of negligence could beat the
way stuff later concerning a really
concerning really bad right now aussie
wife it's hard not to worry
care for yourself like you do for your
cat shout out
[Music]
it
tantra promised kisses but meme review
exposed she was making chicken noises at
us the entire time
what no
i
[Music]
oh
dangeschen gym barbecue dankeshin
pudding channel duncashin i am
kaliskaris dankester and alcohols duncan
starmesh thank you fellow thank you
the me cooler is 001
i was thinking of playing that game
again
christina manzanita laserblast
[Music]
glad to have you back well well
thankfully nothing really serious
happened no man
you made many people worry but yet here
you are laughing happy full of energy as
always thank you
if you need rest make sure to take time
off much love boss
i found myself entranced by all y'all's
friendship
wait wait oh sorry for some reason i
continued reading
to this next super chat ah anyway
thank you i will sorry that that was
that was not my neck that
[Music]
did you hear that
i unconsciously cracked my
um my hip i guess
shut up so that one is not so bad
because i don't do that one that often i
do
every once in a while and i don't even
have to really move my body
how does that work i don't know when i'm
sitting like sometimes when i just
slightly really really slightly
like flex or like move
slightly move my butt a little bit
then i can crack my hip
[Laughter]
yeah i don't know
don't worry i'm not going to break my
hips
now you're just wearing too much shut
ups
thank you for enjoying my content
mindless baka dankeshin john from kfp
thank you thank you
hey kiara you're the best i was
wondering if you could share the kfp
secret recipe asking for a friend
okay every secret recipe is
love oh i want to put echo on
[Music]
there you go
and uh reminded that santa's was
actually a real tender
i don't you know you keep on saying that
colonel kodaly what i don't even know
what that means
you're using it as some kind of uh
insult oh it's colonel sanders but i
don't even know what that means
what what does it mean
meal tender
[Music]
what is what's a meal
is a a donkey
i don't i don't understand the insult
he was sans was actually a meal tender
so are you saying
he's a tender donkey
what oh it's a donkey horse hybrid ah
and what's a meal tender he took
out tending to mules oh i thought
tender because you know meat can be very
tender
[Laughter]
i'm confused okay he where the hell does
that come from
is that true is that like lore from
colonel sanders that he was a meal
tender
and even if so how are we how are we
using that as an
insult the more the deeper i dig the
more confused i am
don't worry about it okay
okay i'm just confused but this was the
last super chat
for that stream and as it's already
somewhat late and i'm hungry and my
throat
is not doing well i am going to end it
here
um
but yeah um that game was weird
and uh the super jack reading was fun
talking to you guys was fun tomorrow
what are we doing tomorrow
what the
[Music]
i've seen some pretty beautiful graphics
from that game i'm
actually excited i've seen fuji senpai
making herself in the game and
it seems like you can do so much
character creation seems
super well done what
i'm actually like really excited
yeah yeah i'm excited to create myself
character creation is the actual game
no but also it's i'm like excited
because mmorpg
high pillow i was looking for an mmoipg
to like play
and i don't know how i did not have
that in my in my vizier
why i but but thankfully it was
introduced to me
and now i'm excited
[Music]
so sorry guys for being a bit a little
low energy
uh around the end there but yeah thank
you very much
for watching the stream today i hope you
enjoyed it
and i'll see you tomorrow around the
same time
around the same time approximately so i
hope you'll come to see me
it'll be a short stream because it's
sponsored anyway
um so i hope you will be
[Music]
thank you thank you everyone thank you
and germany we say
oh smoothie has joined the chat
[Music]
hello
wants pets so in german we say dancing
[Music]
thanks guys for watching
you