[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
questions
[Music]
thank you
this is
assistant
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
you know
[Music]
frogzilla
no no no
I am just
Frankie Wawa uh as if and as as infant
as is as if that isn't already
threatening enough
I'm back or not not back everything's as
per usual
everything's normal
ah
are you hearing the music at all
[Music]
um
yes okay good
good I have my thumb out you just don't
you just don't see it but
how are you guys ghetto good evening
hello how are you
you're not gonna kick at all
feeling great invisible frog for me
doing good doing fine
how about me I I cleaned
Kiana's
Apartments a little bit
did the laundry and remade the bed by
throwing everything out of the window
first and now now the bed is no more
it's just a bathtub with a lily pad as a
blanket very comfy 10 out of 10.
yes
got some tea I heard
humans like to drink this when it's cold
and I will try it out get all okay I
left some delicious tea for me
it calls it Christmas tea
what a fool what a weak weak fool
[Music]
can I take a sip
it's very very hot
[Music]
it's it's boiling water from hell
what on Earth
it's hot
[Music]
my dog
I'm gonna miss my hands and my tongue
well well
well you guys have gathered here today
to here to hear about some
important matters right because you guys
want to know
you guys want to know everything there
is to know
about frogs
[Music]
have yes in general for France in
general and of course you guys want to
know
what we eat what we like to eat oh [\h__\h]
it's ghost fly go there go there go fly
don't ask me why I did it like this
is
so for that
for that purpose
[Music]
are you ready
I have prepared obviously we don't only
eat
um flies
but flies are my favorite because it's
fun there are they're more of a
challenge to eat and I like to be
challenged
the less of a challenge and you know a
stupid worm so everything that has wings
that
looks interesting to me
[Music]
consume is in my list Kettle so you guys
have uh when you guys wear chickens you
had wings too but that doesn't count
Kettle you guys are not in the category
of a flying at all I know
[Music]
foreign
hello
[Music]
here is my list
um of some things
I'm gonna talk about these oh let me let
me turn myself there a bit
uh-huh
what do we see
we see a collection of dangerous
dangerous but not to me dangerous
dangerous to you guys because you guys
are
very very young tadpoles get all most of
those aren't even flesh
[Music]
okay four your kinds of survival
are you listening for your guys survival
you need to be listening closely
together you guys are nothing but tiny
tiny tadpoles you have yet to develop
anything useful to hunt okay you have
yet to
have these these marvelous hands that I
do or marvelous faces that I do okay you
don't have any of that
so
don't you dare now
foreign
I want you guys to be able to go through
this world without me because I'm going
to leave you soon as every frog does
leave their tadpoles
at some point
okay
so
remember this well my frog
babies tadpoles
I have prepared some notes as well to
educate you further
to make no mistakes
[Music]
all right
we are
going to start with something really oh
wait let me first sit here we have super
yummy tier yeah
that's totally fine to eat and you will
love it
delicious is also very good
but maybe not as good as super yummy
yeah then we have these scents they said
it's okay you know maybe not the most
you know satisfying but but it does the
trick to survive and that's what we need
we cannot be picky as frogs or tadpoles
especially as a tadpole it's a frog you
can be a bit more picky
now we have Matt well it doesn't taste
the best but maybe if you combine it
with something else maybe it will taste
better
and then there's
this and this is very important at all
I don't vote you guys huh how is that oh
[\h__\h] probably the buttons I'm pressing
this is very important get off
I don't want you guys to die too early
so don't eat anything
that's
in this
region okay thank you for understanding
[Music]
what is this Microsoft Bing
the [\h__\h] do you love your Microsoft
thing
[Laughter]
what on Earth is okay nothing nothing
dangerous was shown I will stop using
buttons then okay so we start with this
bee
it's a b have you guys ever seen a bee
before at all
[Music]
have you guys ever seen a big
I think maybe the 1B you've seen before
is a bee called imma be now she's a
she's a different story but we're
talking about General bees okay I'm
is not supposed to be eating at all no
no no no
she's supposed to be befriended kiddo
and hang out with and you know diplomacy
diplomacy we want we want some
diplomatic friends
but yeah okay no but it could be a wasp
whatever and whatever you know same
thing in this um in this when we talk
about food bees and and the wasp and so
on we put them in the same category okay
so the bean I want to place in the super
yummy tier why you ask why let me tell
you
bees
due to their natural habitat where they
are usually around the flowers and and
you know their big nest with a big queen
bee is
they tends to taste like sweet honey
they have a sweet taste like honey get
up
so it's very special
it's just by default they taste like
that kettle
um
and uh
you may you may have think oh but the
bee that it's gonna sting me
I don't know that hurts no
turns out frogs are superior so when
frog catches B with marvelous tongue yes
[Music]
um
don't eat bees dares are useful maybe
for humans but we're talking about a
frog's survival and I don't give a [\h__\h]
as a frog about humans or uh bees
survival I just care about my own
Survival do I look like I could care
less about anyone else's survival knock
it off
if I'll die I don't give a [\h__\h]
just a muffin
I need to press a button and I'm scared
okay
I forgot my precious flies water this is
very useful
um if you are not so not so
practiced yet with your tongue
so in that case you can try to use this
magical tool and you can find it in
dollar stores so you jump jump in there
and still on okay we don't want to give
any of those stupid ass humans any money
no no not even a dollar
money doesn't [\h__\h] grow on trees so
am I supposed to get them from kettle
so this helps yes okay uh yes even even
a bee can be captured with this
can be okay so I'm being very yummy very
yummy and also did you know bees they're
very healthy as well they're not only
yummy they're healthy so it's like
amazing 10 out of 10. they have much
protein and carbohydrates so if you guys
I don't know
um and I want to start lifting you know
become buff like me
[Music]
then you might want to consider eating
some more bees to get off yeah
okay and also additional did you know I
think um Indonesian frogs will be very
very uh happy about eating bees because
in Indonesia there's even a dish called
putok tabon I think and yeah it's not
with bees but with bees
larvae larvae yeah they eat it with rice
and coconut and wrap it in banana leaves
sounds interesting isn't it oh
culinary Delights I would say
generally all of these
um flying things that I'm introducing uh
have good potential to be eaten at the
stage of you know caterpillar or baby
larva whatever
[Music]
of course that's that's totally fine too
especially if you're still a small frog
then you don't have much practice yet
and then you might want to try that
instead
yeah yeah Indonesian uh
Botox
I need to ask Dana to send me some of
that good stuff
so let's be super yummy
yummy wow
okay next we bring out the butterfly or
any butterfly this this the thing is
with butterflies
they were all amazing because they all
taste differently depending on the color
they taste differently yes
you know those there was a lemon looking
butterflies they taste like lemon and
the blue butterflies they taste like
blueberry
and all that but
but
all of them have one taste that is like
the same throughout all of them
so it's like even butter blueberry or
butter lemon or butter strawberry or
butter I don't know but it's a mighty
thing yeah
yeah the color is awesome
are not only you know influential of The
Taste but you know so you know you know
how they say
um
you you don't only eat with your mouth
you also eat with your eyes and if the
visuals are on point that's like
marvelous so they they their visuals are
definitely on point and it's fascinating
I like to look at them look at them
because of their colors but I also like
to look at them
because of their nervous flaps but also
annoys me you know when I try to get
them with my tongue they flap so
nervously
[Music]
try to answer her
yeah so they need to chill I need to
take a chill pill and calm the [\h__\h] down
kettle
yeah
[Music]
stop flapping stop stop stop they seem
to be very scared of me of me frog
very scared but they have a good reason
to be scared also since they taste like
butter they're um the best way to serve
them I would say is on pancakes
of course you don't eat the pancakes you
only eat the butterfly look um as I said
you eat with your eyes so you want it to
look visually pleasing right so anyway
because of that I will put them in super
yummy
everything is going super yummy
not everything is going on supramy yeah
yeah I am
um
butterfly on top of pancake
butterfly
foreign
[Music]
I've heard of her I want to eat
them
[Music]
just making sure
what's up
I wrote to her and today she thinks I'm
Kiana so I
talked to her about meeting up you know
she thinks she was gonna meet up with
Kiana
no no no when she comes to the meeting
point
she will not find Kiara she will find
her biggest predator enemy me now we'll
eat her
yeah
don't tell her don't tell her kiddo
[Music]
so next we have
ah this thing
this thing is called in English uh a
cicada
[Music]
those little shits
um
cicadas are [\h__\h] loud and annoying
and they disturb my slam
no I want to sleep and they go the whole
time they're like
so loud
[Music]
so loud my ears can't take it
yeah I can't sleep because of them get
off
also they're a little even though they
taste pretty good and they're crunchy
and all that they are a bit hard to
catch
because they're they don't chill and fly
around the
um the ponds that often they stay on the
trees until they die and then they fall
down and that's also a problem they
don't even clean themselves up when
they're dead on the ground
they all fall down and they're like yes
please take care of me after I'm dead
well what am I supposed to do man
how can I clean these masses of cicada
dead bodies and I like to eat my food
while it's so fresh you know you won't
help me when you like dead on the ground
doesn't it's not very helpful you think
you're doing me a favor or what girl
unbelievable
but they're crunchy so it's decent but
but no honestly they piss me off so this
is meh
man they tastes good but it's a pain in
the ass to get them and also they
they're [\h__\h] loud get all
now [\h__\h] them
[Music]
[\h__\h] these
honest
[Music]
yeah there's also are ugly
not visually pleasing
but I don't want to be honest I don't
really care
[Music]
yeah when I eat them alive yeah yeah my
tummy will make noises too
then continue making those noises
blue
[Music]
oh it's hard to be a frog sometimes you
know
how many noises down
[Music]
okay so next uh
looks like a [\h__\h] crocodile what was
that thing again
[Music]
is that Cricket that's a cricket right
the front the front arms look like a
[\h__\h] crocodile but let me show you in
bing
yeah why does it look like
oh it looks like a cockroach
disgusting
[Music]
oh
hey it looks really gator-ish at all
terrifying because skaters are my
enemies
[Music]
um
[Applause]
scare jumps shouldn't be scaring you
you're a frog
jumps on your daily bread my friend can
all get used to it girl
so okay crickets crickets okay I have a
lot of info about crickets guys
so crickets are also noisy not noise but
not as as fit as the thing they're not
as noisy as cicadas yeah
their noise is really relaxing ghetto
you may have heard it before
it's it's calming okay
unless if there's too many then it gets
annoying
but it also helps to find them there are
noises help me find them Kettle
um
so they're relatively easy to hunt
kettle
but you may have to get out of your Pawn
scale
also they're crazy as well
yeah
uh awesome oh crickets are I know humans
already consider them as relatively
normal food so they're slowly taking
away the Crickets from me I
don't know
first I was eating the Crickets first
and then you steal my [\h__\h] idea and
start eating them yeah in Thailand and
Vietnam they eat them as snacks
especially
and also you can make flour floor flour
out of the crickets for pasta and bread
and protein bars who knows maybe in your
pasta and your bread and so on they may
have used crickets I don't know
[Music]
yeah it's a thing at all
look it up if you don't believe me
cannot yeah and and and and of course
proteins that they're good for workouts
if you want to lift start lifting yeah
eat some crickets
and oh yeah yeah crickets are really
magical
I have some more info on Cricket
schedule
you want to hear
the singing of crickets
in Brazil there's a folklore that the
singing of crickets and not only Brazil
though is sometimes taken to be a sign
of impending rain
oh
and other things
yeah
and in Barbados
a loud Cricket means money is coming
so a cricket may not be killed or
evicted if it chirps inside the house
you know
it's like they're like a god
[Music]
however a different type of cricket that
is less noisy
means that illness and death is coming
in your half Skittle
they're magical at all
tickle they can tell you the weather
they can tell you about money they can
tell you about death and all that the
magical but yeah I I mean I want to eat
them though so I don't really care about
any of that
hmm
had a tea is drinkable now can um
so so that's Cricket yeah so
um I I would say it's not so delicious
as these two and basically also not
cleansing but
um no they're healthy and crunchy and
relaxing now this is a pain in the ass
like that one so I'm putting it in
delicious they're actually yummy but but
just not super super super super super
yummy
good good stuff kennel crickets are
Frank and all
um they're one of the things I eat the
most actually yeah in my lifetime yeah
[Music]
a next next we have tombow dragonfly
this thing yeah dragonfly
you guys know dragonflies you may have
expected a dragon with wings
oh that's normal that's normal I guess
but but no it's not a dragon
it's a long long boy yeah long boy and
shiny boy
very shiny
so what does that mean it obviously
makes them visually pleasing
um
visually appealing they're very pretty
they come in many colors they come in
blue and red and yellow and mixtures of
different colors and they're really nice
and they have I don't know how to
pronounce it but they have like some
kind of
irraditions and we just scent
shininess you know what I mean eyes so
pretty
almost ashamed to eat them
and they tasting that when I asked a
good question you you you my young
tadpole you asked the important
questions
thank you that doesn't you don't
pronounce that at all what it looks like
to be pronounced supposed to be
pronounced as what the hell
[Music]
um
where was I I
like stay close to where it's like um
wet and and so they stay close to the
water and they're like they zoom zoom
zoom above the water
yeah so they stay close to me so
actually they're pretty easy
um you would think they're pretty easy
to catch but uh the problem is they're
really really really strong Flyers
Australia have a strong body and they
have a really strong wings and they're
really in good control over their flying
course so sometimes when I try to catch
them with my with my tongue there you go
I'm done and I'm like what the [\h__\h]
get up and they're professional Pilots
there's like a different version of
dragonflies I forgot the name it's like
similar to dragonflies
um but they're they're weaker Flyers so
those are those are easier to catch and
forgot what they're called you know what
they're called they're like oh yeah
thank you damselflies are easy they
don't know how the [\h__\h] you pilot your
body get off
I said there's a big difference look it
up I'm I'm only telling you the truth to
take you know I'm telling you everything
I've experienced in my life so far kiddo
hmm
yeah yeah so so it's um it's very
entertaining to watch them and I guess
somehow entertaining to catch them but
it's a bit difficult
um but they stay close to the water so
looking at the shiny colors is quite
interesting but do you get do you get
enough value for your efforts to catch
it no maybe not
so I put it to decent
[Music]
decent Carol
yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
do you do you
okay okay going well so far are you
writing everything down my sweet dad
Falls Skinner are you writing it down
otherwise no I'll slap your butts with
this
and they're hard to catch yeah
yes okay
[Music]
okay next we have uh
the the shiny the shiny um
Firefly
Firefly you would
my grandma told me about this before but
you would not believe your eyes if 10
million fireflies
lit up the sky
as she fell asleep
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah and then she opened her eyes and
she thought they were attacking her
because they were swamy Birds she was
like foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
things
um but my family members
before me have died
by eating fireflies because they thought
oh shiny flying things very cute
must be yummy no
fun they're toxic
no toxic as hell broke it all
the time good night good night yo that's
tiny Dominic at all
I mean you may I know survive one or two
but don't get used to it don't don't get
on they're toxic to us you know
that's why no fireflies in Minecraft
yeah Minecraft
um learned its lesson too many frogs
have died by being fed or eaten on their
own uh some fireflies yeah
besides that they're yummy as far as I
know but I mean
is it [\h__\h] worth it Kettle no it's
not worth dying for something that's
yummy so don't eat frog die when they
eat Firefly remember that Frog die when
they eat Firefly frog don't die when
they eat dragonfly
they're pretty at least and they they
are like you know providing a light
source
in the in the Lonely Nights
that's the only good thing about them
but
ton you know
what are you thinking
[Music]
easy to cook I guess so because a lot of
flies end with flying don't they
I guess it doesn't work so well I'll
think of a new one
[Music]
um
okay
next don't you see those little shits
down there do you see it get out
next is small small but
do not underestimate
yeah because next is fruit fly
[\h__\h] fruit fly and besides being hard
to pronounce they also really annoying
not only humans but me cannot
annoy me too now
and am I I mean you know I've eaten a
couple of them but they don't really
fill my belly very much if you tiny tiny
tiny Temple thank you gonna enjoy them
more than me keto they're very
unsatisfying they don't have any
specific taste to them
and yeah they're small it's just [\h__\h]
annoying so man I'll get them out of
here boring boring
now nothing special about them ninjas
suck
no
[Music]
no they suck get on
their cute I know
I have high standards yeah
I do I'm you know with my in my
uh
in my two years
yeah two two years
I have I have experienced many things
and I have acquired a lot of wisdom you
know
um
hmm
all right
so that's the next next
is
[Music]
they have some sick jumping skills
yeah but it feels like they're
challenging me they jump around my pond
they go like bills
and I'm like are you [\h__\h] challenging
me at all you want to fight you wanna
fight I'll show you how to jump I'll
show you how to jump in my valley that
is cannot come at me bro come at me
and I don't expect that they don't see
it coming they
they jump while they're also green so I
honestly think they're faking me they're
trying to be like me but they will never
be like me get off no no
no
so I must eat them to a search dominance
oh grasshoppers all over the world
actually this
um this thing this intersect also has
the same problem as the Crickets because
um they're also eaten by humans at this
point
humans have
figured it out insects are tastier than
they look like yeah
they're quite popular actually in
Chinese food markets they are being sold
on skewers
[Music]
like squirrels
this is also how you eat a corn cob
[Music]
so yeah and also in Indonesia too and
South Mexico
those are places where they're very
popular yeah education education for my
tadpoons
also again good protein and generally a
lot of these have good protein but this
one damn has really good protein yeah
eight plus plus plus kettle
and did you did you know
this [\h__\h] is honestly they should stop
jumping around my ponds it has been
proven that they have better things to
do
because they're actual it has been
tested they're actually
able to detect the location of
explosives
[Music]
foreign
yeah look it up
I'm only telling you the truth man
no really though
really kiddo um
[Music]
foreign
once before with one of them that's why
I know that's why I know yeah yeah so
um protein good crunchiness good not the
most delicious and I feel like they're
challenging me and like you know trying
to make a fool out of me but they have
also better uses so I would prefer then
just go somewhere else you know and then
to keep on detecting explosives so
[Music]
um
I put them in decent because they have
committed some crimes against frogs that
are Unthinkable and I will never forget
them so yeah just decent get off
healthy though healthy
10 out of 10 stores
[Music]
the disrespect that's what I'm saying
man they [\h__\h] disrespecting me at all
[Music]
all right so so that's that uh do you
recognize this next thing
it's a bit small for you again
you recognize you know
[Music]
yeah oh wow one two oh wow good good
eyes candle you must have seen them in
the wild candle they're called Green
Lace wings that's I guess the most
common name
[Music]
yeah well I haven't eaten so many before
they like to visit me often yeah they
come by every now and then so then I eat
because well while you're here why the
hell not get all right yeah
they hear well
they have really good hearing so I have
to be quiet when I try to get them
and they don't have much meat on them so
you know it's not very satisfying I need
a couple of them
so I'm a bit mad but at least they're
green you know it makes you feel like
you're eating vegetables
I'm being a bit good to your body but I
put them in mail because they're I don't
know
and they don't come by so often but when
they do I eat but amount I mean they're
small as hell better for like tadpoles
maybe you know for baby food
or sell
um
not much to say about the Green Lace
Wing to be honest
and next oh what is this looks like a
bee but it's not a b it's a
it's it's amazing but not the B it's
called hoverfly
many times I have been deceived by this
thing
flies around
and I'm like [\h__\h] it's a b o o quick
quick eat it before it stings me but no
it's a hoverfly they don't have anything
to sting me with
um
it's a genius genius deceiver
wow good actor it actually does act as
if it was a bee that's its tactic you
know to survive in the wild they like to
act as a bee and with that they you know
they do some some really cool stuff
um
a paid actor yes kiddo
yeah yeah and also since since they act
as if they were bees they go to the same
places they also go to get some pollen
and honey and all that so they they
taste like a bee
they don't only look like a bee they
but at least of them you know you don't
have to be so careful with the the
stickiness because they're not stingy at
all
oh I mean this is a random fact that I
don't care about but they're actually
also uh kept in gardens
um for like doing pest control which
helps you know all the garden frogs
it's helpful for the garden frogs for me
I don't live in the garden but if some
you know human says oh I have some pests
in my garden they
um they try to get some hoverflies
joining the garden and then the frog is
like Hey Y'all thanks for the free food
[Music]
and garden farms appreciated very much
Carol um
no so honestly um super yummy maybe I
have a preference for yellow things
kiddo
seems so almost yeah super
yeah what a deal you get like something
like a bee but less dangerous at all
and the good thing is if you eat a cup
of beans not like queen bee is gonna be
mad at you and try to catch you and then
kill you
yeah yeah okay next we have ladybug
ladybug
looks yummy right like a strawberry
looks so good
about poison
sounds you know I want to eat them every
time I see them I have to resist because
my doctor says it's not good for me oh
boy yeah they're poisonous stay away
danger danger don't be deceived by the
cuteness you know I mean those eyes I
know they're cute and the thoughts
they're like hypnotizing but boys you
know baby look at them they might remind
you of one of those
um those mushrooms with the the flying
mushrooms What freaking thing filter
waiting they're surely not called Flying
mushrooms in English too are they
[Music]
the
red mushrooms with the white dots
those those we call Flying mushrooms in
German
those yeah those are um those are
poisonous too so if you will see one of
these
and remind yourself just like the
mushrooms these are poisonous toolk at
all
don't eat them
mostly these red things that look really
fascinating to you is
no I'm not okay next we have mosquito
mosquito
mosquitoes really really really evil
evil evil evil evil
don't like mosquito
but that's probably because I
sympathized a little bit too much with
humans yeah foreign
[Music]
and then human hurt frog
for what reason I don't know Keto
they do have they like to put their eggs
on the water surface so I eat the eggs
and then they come back and they're like
oh what the [\h__\h] were my eggs and I I'm
like in the ponds giggling evenly
they don't know they don't know what I
did
[Music]
okay
and get a good laugh a laugh out of it
it's good entertainment
don't eat them they're not poisonous or
anything but I prefer playing around
with them I eat their babies
yeah also humans try to use me frog
and many other frogs before
to control mosquito population in the
world but as I said I don't really care
much about them you know
so it didn't work out people tested it
the humans have tested us used us but I
I will be used like this
I'm not you play a thing and I don't
work for what you humans want out there
so what I want to do and what I want to
do you know what it is I want to eat
their babies
sure no thank you Keno
now tell me what to do kiddo I'm gonna
take your stupid mosquitoes and I'm
gonna ignore them
prove you that you cannot control me
again
uh also The Taste not really good for
the show yeah meh
eggs are good though the eggs are good
I like them while they're still runny
[Music]
ah good tea
no I don't throw them on the ground and
I just I I'm I I mean I could probably
with my buff arms because I've eaten so
much protein
I didn't actually have a mom mom
someone really fuzzy yeah you know it's
like when you eat a peach kind of maybe
comparable yeah it's like when you eat a
peach fuzzy like that fuzzy on the
outside with the inside juicy very juicy
and hydrating
[Music]
there's some crazy ones out there some
of them are really beautiful actually
but in order to catch them I have to
stay up late
which I do anyway so
but yeah they're good for late night
cravings
because they come around in the middle
of the night so in the middle of the
night if you feel like
I'll go for Yummy peachy snack right now
then you open your eyes and you go
[Applause]
[Music]
get them off get it
no they're not poisonous no I also
they're caterpillars and they're larvae
is like really easy to catch and eat so
I recommend them too especially for
tadpoles
silkworms and silkworms for for baby
frog and for for any frog really good
too
um
yeah actually you know mops I know are
really unpopular with humans
um because they don't want them in their
houses
because of the they think they eat their
clothes but the truth is and I'm gonna
drop a bump now here that everybody's
gonna be surprised about
most moths do not
close no
most moms and don't eat clubs and some
don't even eat anything at all
oh
surprising huh no some do yes but most
don't get on most
Channel
don't eat cloves skin on
only sound
maybe they were unlucky and had either a
moth or something else cheeky that's
eating your clothes
so they save in closets
well yeah some of them is propaganda
against moths but what do I care it's
not like I want to protect them I just
want to eat them so keep on keep
chewing them out of your houses so I can
eat them okay send them back to my ponds
I'm welcomed them come on come on come
on come on come on here bring me the mob
Skittle they yummy they're like Peaches
I put them in the least
they're like
um you know my most of these insects are
crunchy this one will give you
a soft eating experience and juicy so
it's different and that makes it very
interesting everyone's in a while
so now we have a normal fly I don't even
know what to call this one but it's just
a normal ass fight it's [\h__\h] noisy
and has has huge red eyes annoying but
they're basic food and they provide a
good crunch and I like to grill them and
then try them with different kinds of
sauces because otherwise I get sick of
them because there's just too many and
they're like very common
yeah they're decent they're decent I'm
just I guess I've eaten too many of them
at the typical house fly yeah
just keep them in your houses I don't
really care about them
[Music]
okay okay
good next we have do you see this can
you recognize what this is I think many
of you don't know what this is
my humans didn't know what it is
[Music]
and it's small I know they're supposed
to be small
[Music]
raised by a good frog aka me it's a
snake fly snake
stick
stick five should I do you want to sing
big
I will show you in big
here this is snack fight
thank God I have still the eye stock
um subscription that Kiara bought
this really helped me out thank you I
stopped
[Music]
so snack flying you could guess has its
name because it looks like a snack so it
has a funny long body it looks funny
it's like a noodle so I like to eat them
with sauce and make spaghetti out of
them but they're very small so it's
mostly baby food
small but make good spaghetti yeah good
good noodle food
very yummy very yummy snack more like
snacks
look at me look at me you
get off so it's pretty yummy but I don't
I don't see it so often
um no honestly I like having a spaghetti
and flies I'll put it in delicious yeah
[Music]
last but not least I mean there's
obviously a couple more different types
of things that have uh wings but I kept
it to this because it was a tough
writing down all these informations
and I thought this was enough so the
last one you see what the last one is do
you also want to see this one in big I
got a good picture you know I paid for
it so let me show you wow
it's called a Frip
Frip t-h-r-i-p
there as you can see
kind of hairy
and the little hairs they take they
tickle they
in my mouth when I eat them it's like
when you eat popping candy and I go like
in your mouth
you know the sour sour popping when you
open your mouth and it goes like
that's almost what it's like to eat a
fruit
yeah um but and also they're they're bad
really bad Flyers they have wings but
they're bad Flyers maybe they should
shave them their their wings and then
they would be more aerodynamic I don't
know it's not my place to tell them what
to do again I just eat them
but yeah there is two cats because
they're bad flyers and they're but
they're very small also they're disliked
by humans of course as most of these
things are thank God they even invade
houses and closets and did you know they
can even like invade you or your
computers they like go in between and
then they just chill in there
not too often though but it happens
also they cause plant disease so [\h__\h]
them
yeah but I mean they're they're quite
yummy they also provide a different kind
of like eating experience get all
um
[Music]
you know this is my flight dealer so
yeah yeah you can print this out and
then you look at
[Music]
you you print it out and then every day
when you're thinking about oh
what should I eat tonight
you just choose anything that's above
the poison uh it's here okay
[Applause]
[Music]
uh gets me really hungry man so hungry
oh
[Music]
did you learn something today you know
besides you know if they're yummy or not
I think I provided you with some good
um educational informational things
yes
you understand flies a little bit better
that's very good you have to understand
your food as a predator because frogs
frogs are frogs are quite the Predators
um
we have to understand not only our own
bodies but also the the enemy's body and
get on
[Music]
okay
now I want to sing get up oh I wanna
sing I wanna sing for you
um
[Music]
can I sing for you
I am actually
a famous singer in the Frog world
I'm a bit nervous my first time
um
Nathan there's um there's a bed
because I'm also such a legend in the
Frog world people write songs about me
you know
so
here is here's one of those songs
slow down
[Music]
okay
baby
[Music]
foreign
he got nothing
[Music]
sit down
there
[Music]
foreign
yeah
ah
a
thank you
[Music]
it's our frog national hymn for the Frog
land for the frogland s
thank you thank you again
so sweet you know thank you for
listening to our our hymn yes
he's gonna
okay
guys know that is you know
national anthem yeah yeah
yeah
froglinks don't think about
cupcakes
oh what the hell your tadpole you
shouldn't be thinking about them
all right
um so the main part of the stream is
over but I'll read some super chats that
you guys sent this week for me
yeah
main part is over there
actually it was cold before the Stream
So I was I put on like a sweat or
underneath
[Music]
you don't see it it's an invisible
sweater but let me let me change really
quickly
shut up
[Music]
thank you
okay okay
[Music]
hi you know
we're gonna read two potatoes
[Music]
okay should I stay here should I keep
this list up have you taken
a photo
I'm gonna get rid of it
and I'm gonna make myself
[Music]
um
wonderful
yeah
okay I don't know where do I do I need
to read all of them is there is there uh
where did I I know I read the members
super chatos
[Music]
time on frog Island
um did I read that one
[Music]
did I read time on frog Island the first
one we played
[Music]
yeah oh yeah so frog Detective
should I write that we're reading super
Gents
unlike a note
oh
I know this one or not
reading Super Chat
[Music]
oh get on okay this is this I'm a little
Bernie told me this may or may not be
the last time that I'm spending time
with you so please you better stay
because you want to see me for a while
maybe who knows
[Music]
while I was here trying to tell you guys
and teach you guys everything that is
important to know as a young tadpole to
survive in the wild so I I might have to
go but I trust you that you can make it
on your own yeah I will go hibernate
and generally even as I wasn't
hibernating I would leave you guys
behind but I guess I don't have to say
so directly it hurts your heart
I
[Music]
I'm gonna come back at some point and
then we'll see if you guys still
recognize me kiddo
I'll come back yeah yeah don't say don't
say bye and we're still reading
girl
[Music]
oh yeah maybe I should put up the funk
man like Kiara always does
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
I mean the Kermit the Frog aren't you
dead how are you super chatting I killed
you but I'm confused how's that work you
know maybe thank you for the pinky okay
it's Wednesday my dudes is what you were
trying to say huh
actually actually it works perfectly but
I think
um
[Music]
dude I feel like dude dude is used a bit
more generally than Caroline German
equivalent it's really a proper
equivalent I'm not sure
is what Japanese frog make sound
yes
doesn't really have a meaning kettle
[Music]
thank you for telling me it's Wednesday
but it's not Wednesday anymore getting
all you lying it's Sunday you get on
[Music]
get up get up my son frogs and get on
Canal
time frog can knock it off
annoying [\h__\h] okay
ah everybody's changing their names so
cute you know
for the red super chat it's my birthday
oh thanks for encouraging me to not give
up on my dreams last year I finally got
into my dream company oh did I read this
before I'm still doubting if I'll be
able to achieve my dream no I don't
think so can I have your blessing I hope
you can continue to bring us more
surprises in the future
wow
[Music]
nice Skittle
I know you could do it get up just have
to believe in yourself and try even for
things that seem a little bit difficult
just try give it a try better than not
trying
congratulations kiddo
yeah I don't know how to give you my
blessing but I I will give you a slurp
[Music]
this is
you have you have now been
um hydrated by
my tongue so do your best
can you get up
again
okay no I'll be here it is Wednesday my
dudes what is this meme get oh why don't
you guys say it's Wednesday
why
[Music]
why what's it what's this thing about
Wednesday
it's a frog frog meme I just know that
people make memes about frogs
obviously just a [\h__\h] joke to you
[Music]
this is funny to you
you think I'm a joke or what girl
[Music]
yeah be careful I have a [\h__\h] gun and
I'm not afraid to use it get up and
anybody who makes fun of me
[Music]
thank Lord with smash can hook it up
thank you for the well why why didn't
you not frog frog
funny with Frank Frank was that after
this one girl
thank you for the recipe oh Overlord
bubble bubble froggy Wawa please don't
leave us stay with us forever we'll give
you all the Flies and and and and uh
ladybugs you want of course kiwawa can
show up once in a while too after she
revives I'm kidding love you thank you
but for now remember
[Music]
I see
thank you oh thank you thank you frog
frog for your loyalty yeah no ladybugs I
think you've learned your lesson you're
not trying to poison me are you hmm
are you
[Music]
no no no okay yeah totally not
my own child was to poison me
where's my gun
[Music]
last warning kiddo
thank you doll
um
thank you so much for the support thank
you for accepting your new Overlord get
up
super frog Mario oh thank you for the
pinky hi froggy mama I didn't get a
chance to greet you yesterday because of
work but I'm really happy to meet you
you're so cute
I'm not usually a fan of rice but I'll
make an exception yesterday
you're just so cute not to love let's
have fun together
[Music]
thank you okay oh what a Charming temple
on your arm
hmm
[Music]
ah hand always goes away don't go away
take a photo
okay took a cute photo okay
[Music]
it looks so delicious you have a profile
picture of a butterfly and what what
have we learned you my
you must like butt
and I say some yellow so it must be like
lemon butter oh
Yum Yum Yum Yum greetings my benevolent
frog god ketochan of the pawn Slayer of
the Phoenix yeah please accept these
humble fly funds as a type I will take
surely you will realize in in your
Infinite Wisdom that despite their name
butterflies make from miserable me for
um sure yeah yeah
miserable meal for frog
you
weren't listening to
the first half of the first part of the
stream today were you
it's a movie together
[Music]
we'll watch um
frog about a frog a movie about frogs
yeah okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
not not gonna do anything
weird
[Laughter]
yeah yeah we can get some dinner after
the movie hmm
take care of it don't worry about it
I'll prepare the dinner
at least
where'd that come from
oh
the hills of my heart are lie I mean
hopping with the sound of croaking
whenever you stream froggy
yeah
Milly Sprite
this room is perfect Pokemon can solve
all the problems that kfb has had not
that I have any problems now that I was
transferred into a frog being a frog is
great
exactly right you know I knew you would
be happy as a frog
oh what no pun yet I guess I probably
told you after a while it's half this is
still before kennel
uh oh
asking here I can't think of any funny
frog pants for username if you pull out
your pistol is that a Canada gun show
oh [\h__\h]
yes
but I'm still waiting for your
name bamboozle hope you got something
good cause today is the last chance get
on
random collusion thank you for the pinky
get on yay hooray for evil yay now Frank
not evil no mosquito evil me not evil
[Music]
you know that Carol I'm innocent kiddo
I only help you know
I am good kiddo
hmm aimless sidekick episode
or is this
oh is this
yes
[Music]
thank you everybody can all after that
we streamed
this scam Here Comes
[Music]
isn't it the cutest thing ever here
so cute
it's so cute I'm small I'm smaller frog
this was this this photo was taken of me
like a year ago when I'm a bit bigger
now okay no
connections
you know
a little bit bigger now
I don't know
I still use the same gun though
okay so tickets
[Music]
that my favorite is almost gone I think
I can think more clearly I'm certain
froggy Wawa is not really you're just
using cat as a frog using you just can't
using a frog model The larva is a frog
you're not real you're just pretending
you're fake from I have no proof yet but
I'm 95 certain
[Music]
I don't know that sounds like a like you
have absolutely no proof and no grounds
for it
[Music]
sounds you just want to be in contrarian
everyone else is enjoying this frog
and you're
I think you have hallucinations I need
to put you to bed
no more of those lights guys
foreign
[Music]
and give you
Alec thank you kiddo whoever you might
be whoever you are
I might never know I might never know
thank you very much for your deep
insight into the Frog
you should be okay though Mike now why
are you still okay no Mike
I've finally escaped the FBI with help
with some fellow Froggies they keep
interrogating me on why I'm pouring my
love on the two you're not currently on
the Run godspeed to me
[Music]
and then they wouldn't know like who you
are
foreign
[Music]
professional friend
I like that education okay now
thank you
[Music]
okay no Super Chat thank you hi you are
always from you our dance right never
want to hear you make any more mistakes
just wanted to tell you that I finally
finished military service I am back yo
it feels like you only left like
yesterday what the weather here has
turned cold recently I'm taking a small
break before I start my job next week I
miss you a lot please take care
you you missed me when you left I wasn't
even there
but I guess that's nice thank you you
missed me before I even exist existed in
your life
[Laughter]
[Music]
I hope military service wasn't too tough
on you okay
and I hope that will be a new job we
will have a fun time and yeah it won't
be
so exhausting and then you can adjust
well yeah
cannot get off thank you for the pinky
as well Frankie mama is too cute
amphibian menu item so he had a frog
Palace coming soon oh I like Palace
I mean you know I call it kind of frog
um
Kettle Fried Phoenix yeah yeah because I
am intending to fry the Phoenix
um you know to a certain dominance I
feel like keeping the word phoenix in
there in that position is um quite
intimidating for other phoenixes who
might want to challenge me if there are
any more
um but Kiana frog Palace
No it should be Kettle frog Palace then
though
who is Kiana
that sounds good though nice nice name
idea I will consider after my
hibernation
[Music]
looking for the Frog and knock it off Mr
Bubbles
um
[Music]
are the cutest YouTuber to ever grace
the world yeah yeah tell me more tell me
more your cuteness is so distracting I
forgot what I want to say
[Music]
okay the only thing I remember now is to
ask you not to kill our potential again
she works so hard she deserves better we
love you both
[Music]
should only be loving me girl
what the [\h__\h] yeah
but that was still like one of the first
streams maybe you were not 100
convinced yet but by now you surely are
aren't you know
you must be you must be or you know what
will happen
you don't want that to happen
[Music]
yeah swear loyalty
swear on this lily pad
that you will love froggy Wawa forever
um
I swear I saw let me swear to love
froggy Wawa
[Music]
yeah
that's that's how it should be bent the
Frog me yes or the tadpole need that you
don't have yet because you have yet to
get to that Evolution
you'll get there and when you have a
knee you will bend it or I will bend it
for you if I have to break it I don't
give a [\h__\h] kettle
[Music]
looks like someone should have
researched her Target first good luck to
you froggy one
you mean you're talking about Kiana not
researching the frog that she kept in
that glass bowl all this time right
she did that research
that I am very strong
I was charging my tongue
the whole time
I mean in the end I did it with the gun
but still I would I wanted to try out
the gun with the with my tongue too
in the end the murder weapon wants the
gun
as you've seen in the security footage
of the office
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat camera
it looks so riveting and has been
totally fun this week
I'm glad that accuse Phoenix looking
witch changed me into a frog maybe being
a frog isn't so bad but I wonder how
long this spell will last for oh
it wouldn't you want it to be forever at
all
I would want it to be forever you must
be you must stay as a frog
um
now that I've taught you so much on how
to survive in this dangerous dangerous
world you must use this knowledge
hmm
[Music]
thank you Anthony for the pinky I always
appreciate the relaxing and cozy stream
from quinoa and thank you so these
streams were pretty relaxing and the
games the games were pretty relaxing at
all weren't they
thank you I hope you enjoyed them
I'm done with these ones too yeah
the members only ones I know I already
read those within the members only
stream
let me tell you
how you was playing Slade aspire
D I tried
to play the the the
defect defect was that his name
character
you know the one with the orbs
uh yeah I tried to you know learn how to
play it on my own
um
but uh yeah the first time I came until
like the middle of the the last stage
but then I died because holy [\h__\h]
is it just me or is it really hard to
like keep my HP up
oh my God it's so hard like I got like
um the the card that heals after battles
uh but only he's like seven or ten
depending on if you upgraded it
um but that's like the only heel you get
kind of
it's so difficult so I tried to like
block as much Dam as much damage as I
can all the time but even then some of
the danger some some of the enemies were
like
super dangerous and yeah
so I failed but I I couldn't accept it
so I tried another time and this time I
already I was like all right I got it
the first time I was still learning
um but I got pretty far now this time
this time will be the one time I I must
conquer with the defect but I still I
actually died earlier than the first try
because I I got into a situation that
was I even safe scammed uh when I was
about to die I was like [\h__\h] this is
like I can't do anything about this so I
I did the same battle again and it went
exactly the same way it was I I wasn't a
boss fight with free bosses that don't
like they don't seem so strong they
don't have much HP I think
um but maybe you guys know the the boss
fight I'm talking about maybe you've
encountered them too but they have
really strong attacks so it's free and
they will attack
um like 11 preparation or or like one
one doesn't eleven one does like 13 one
does ten and so on
and holy [\h__\h] man I just I just I tried
so hard to block as much as I could oh
and then I I got this one card um
because I looked down which cards uh I
went to a Wiki and then I looked at
which cards are good for the defect so I
was going by that the whole time you
know I only took cards that were above B
minus
and I got
um the the S the one single S card that
they recommend but I never really used
it properly I mean sometimes but I
didn't think it was that good and I got
the other car that that was um in the
tier below like a plus plus so
[Music]
um
which is really op apparently but I
never got to use it it costs um free
and you know per turn usually you only
have three
um energy but what it does is
the first card you play in that turn is
played twice yeah Echo form yeah and I
read that if you have two Echo forms
it's even more insane but yeah so I
sometimes I actually had two Echo forms
in my hand uh one was given by you know
different cars that I don't even have in
my deck you know sometimes they give you
power cards right yeah yeah that's
apparently a power card I guess but I
never got to use the echo form because I
had to protect myself from those [\h__\h]
because they were doing like over 30
damage and I couldn't even go into the
battle with full HP no
um they were too [\h__\h] strong
I feel like maybe I went into the battle
for lunch P actually in this situation
but even then they [\h__\h] demolished me
again I couldn't get out of it
even on second try the same battle same
outcome impossible
and now I'm so pissed off but I read
that the fact is really difficult
actually so
I guess I guess no no surprise kettle
um
[Music]
not grabbing good cards yeah
hmm
but maybe next time you guys can help me
I want a win with the defect I want to
get on
Monday now
[Music]
I mean next week I don't know I don't
want to spam too much slay the sparrow a
sparrow slay the spot but
um damn
yeah it was interesting playing alone uh
playing alone I think I was able to like
at least
pick up information
calmly and and take my time and read for
I was speaking so hard because I
couldn't use you guys to think so I I
about every turn I was doing math I was
like okay they're doing so and so much
damage so I have to block this and this
because my HP is like always really low
so I have to try to always defend as
much as possible and I'm still trying to
damage it was quite fun though the the
orb system was pretty fun to play around
with
think so much about every turn man every
turn ah
um yeah
[Music]
I oh yeah I'm sick about getting a steam
deck and now I wanted to ask you guys
because there's free free different
versions right
so I'm not getting the basic one
obviously but I'm I'm considering should
I get the best one or the or the mid one
they have the same like um core or so I
don't know
um but I don't know if 50012 GB is like
really worth it
just get the best one really there's
like over 200 euro difference
the storage and the screen is different
and the rest is Just Accessories I would
say
[Music]
yeah
only if you play big games
[Music]
not so sure about it yeah and I heard
you can still expand it with an SD card
if you really need it and I feel like
I'll that will be cheaper in the end
[Music]
yeah
best one
[Music]
hmm I was gonna go for the for the best
one but then I started thinking like is
this really worth it 200 over 200 euro
USD difference
no an interesting extra SD card because
like I mean I want to use it in bed and
like play a couple games but I don't see
myself having like three different games
installed at the time
at the same time you know
I think I've only been playing like you
know every now and then not too much and
yeah
and then also
if I
if I am when I'm playing games I usually
I don't I don't play so many games at
the same time like I I would play one or
maximum two games at the same time when
I say at the same time like okay like
one one game per day or so maybe
yeah but one sounds better are there any
games
that would be over 256 GB to install
any games like that
maybe like rust or something I don't
want to play Rust on my steam deck Arc
yeah okay I don't care about that
I wouldn't play that no no no no okay
Call of Duty no I don't care about that
anymore okay then then we're good
probably
Call of Duty oh that that's so much I
actually like last night I saw something
when I was scrolling for Twitter
was I think that was Call of Duty they
were showing like Amsterdam
in Call of Duty looks absolutely insane
like so realistic I was like yo isn't
this like a shooting shoot game why is
it so beautiful
what is so beautiful
it's really good looks it looked like a
real live video
you saw the same video
of course you didn't
hmm
the little sniffs
so real you can't afford a house there
the game
[Music]
I think I'll go with the middle one then
now and if I really need more space I'll
just buy an extra ST but I also feel
like I might not even get to the point
where I need more space
for the switch
I needed extra space but only because
like
switch basically has no [\h__\h] storage
by default and uh you know I I use it a
lot to stream different games and when
you when you when you have five
different games per week then you tend
to have five different games when you
switch if it's all switch games I mean
some recently I've been playing mostly
Steam games but at some point you know I
had Mario Party and Mario Kart or so in
the same week stuff like that and then
then then it's difficult also oh and
maybe mix in Pokemon and holy [\h__\h] oh
and Zelda yeah
stuff like that if that all comes
together then you immediately have no
space on your switch
if I was playing it only privately I
don't think I would have so many games
at once installed
um
so for this team deck I feel like I'm
fine
that's it
[Music]
okay I'll buy it then you know I was I I
was surprised you can buy it through
Steam so I was trying to do it with my
Steam account and then I realized oh my
Steam account is Japanese I was about I
was like telling
telling Jen my like hey can you count
how much money you have left from me
because I need to buy the steam deck
it's like 600 or so
and then she she counts and she gets
back to me and says how much she has
left for me and I'm like all right good
good good you might have to buy uh 600
word for steam cards for me like soonish
because I want to get the steam deck but
then I I log into my I open the steam
account and I see that since my steam
account is Japanese it's it's all grayed
out and it says
um you know open for a reservation in
Japan but I can't even like no it's
apparently not available right now so it
was like what the [\h__\h] that seems
annoying especially if like
uh I have I feel like if I buy it for
that account there's other reasons why I
shouldn't be doing that like I don't
know like
shipping and whatever yeah available for
comodo yeah that's what it said uh
available for his reservation and come
on I'm like well don't make it so
complicated so yeah I asked my friend
with um with a European with an Austrian
Steam account if they can check if it's
available and there it was available
so for Austria I can get it easily so
I'm gonna give my friend the money
and then I'll get my steam deck through
an Austrian Steam account
I'm excited everybody so far has a steam
deck except one person has been telling
me on Twitter that they love it and I
should get it so yeah
it now become a slate Aspire Pro after
playing it for hours and hours and hours
and hours and hours in my bed
[Music]
oh yeah yeah the demand is really high
apparently
I'm glad just actually
um this month there was a restock in
Europe I guess I don't know if it's
Europe as a whole or like certain
countries I don't know but we have it
available at the moment
[Music]
did you see that my cheeks were puffing
like that when I was thinking
I'll do it again look drink
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
it was like an hour long you should
watch it afterwards because I think
everybody in the chat can tell you it
was very informative right
it was actually informative like I
looked up like a lot of things about
every [\h__\h] insect out there
I looked on so much information
[Music]
I woke up and before even eating
breakfast I sat down for an hour to do
my research you know
I wanted it to be actually like have
some legit information
for survival yeah you know
yeah
it was interesting
and finally I made use of my [\h__\h] eye
stock
um subscription
who the hell has an istock subscription
me I guess
but damn
[Music]
yeah
I wanted to I have so many subscriptions
I want to cancel them I still have my um
Duolingo subscription it keeps on
renewing and I'm like I'm not even
I should I shouldn't use it I should use
it but the problem of that one is that
like last time I tried to use it on the
phone it's like so different on the
phone for like Korean at least then I
have to use it on the PC to actually
really learn something but I just want
to like calm feeling learn it while in
bed
you know before going to sleep or so
[Music]
I don't want to go the lazy taxi is
I'm gonna go to the PC to learn I want
to get coffee I want to sit comfortably
in a blanket you know I should bring
over my laptop to my bed
um
easy frog no crazy
frog no Crazy Frog yeah
I have two laptops an iPad yeah that's
the iPad if I'm stolen on the iPad does
it have the desktop version or the phone
version I wonder a steam deck would help
with that yeah yeah I guess even
honestly even a switch
doesn't switch up browser too could work
on the switch too
but I don't know
I don't know
[Music]
okay let's read more Super chats uh I
have to read the one from the promotoni
Stream
oh I think
oh those are quite a lot oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
wait wrong window
it doesn't work
requested URL was not found on This
Server what do you mean get on
it's broken
why is it broken
are you guys it's broken for you too
that's a good excuse for me to not read
it
seems to be super tenseful Kiana anyway
not for me
so Kiana has to read that let me push
that homework aside and make her read it
then I can actually still go cook it's
10 p.m and I can cook I have to cook
because my my meat is um going bad
tonight
AKA my flies
yeah
let's leave it to Kiana so John
[Music]
um so yeah
oh wait they're super chats for this
stream though oh I forgot
I forgot oh wait
um okay
that's right
[Music]
yeah
real time
okay
[Music]
no no no I won't leave a [\h__\h] yeah I
read it
[Music]
and knocking on okay
should I put up the thumbnail
this beautiful art oh my God this
person's art
apple apple
blossom apple bottom
[Music]
there are like fits perfectly for froggy
while I cannot
yeah perfect for froggy while walking
along perfect
thank you thank you for drawing froggy
Wawa so cutely
I look like a Pixar character almost
canal
maybe didn't pick Pixar we should pitch
froggy Mama movie to Pixar
[Music]
my mosquito mat because they're evil
they always try to take blood from the
human and kill the human
[Music]
totally don't you mean totally totally
it's like it's probably okay okay
of 23rd of October it's my birthday
recently I'm not doing well both
physically and mentally can you share
some positive vibe with me thank you and
I'll keep supporting you I'm still here
find any element you still here Carol
[Music]
sweet without the donkey shirts yeah
I even if you're not here let me sing
happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday
dear funny almonds happy birthday until
you get on
[Music]
I hope you had a lovely birthday you
know
thank you for always supporting me and
cheer up
[Music]
keep your chin up okay though I don't
even have a chin but you probably do so
keep it up keep it up
hmm like that
always look on the bright side of life
[Music]
amazing how the audio sync was resolved
but such a shame Bianca it's
uncomfortable and doesn't track as well
I think the tracking was okay I mean for
some reason
I know uh like the the
taller models that that Kiana has in VR
I don't have a hunchback right but with
the wealthy models
I Kiana always gets the hunchback
we've only seen froggy Wawa for a moment
in the beginning but I don't think she
had quite the Hunchback why is it always
the Laughing model
if something's wrong there I don't have
the Hunchback with on the other low poly
taller ones
no matter how
I like adjust the you know when you
stand like a t-post
no matter like how like sometimes I try
to I try to fix the Hunchback but like
you know standing differently when
adjusting
um
it's weird
that might be a rigging issue that's
okay I don't really use those Much
Anymore
um
oh well uh but thank you um so um
actually I'm sorry about some uh audio
balancing problems
but I think besides that it was really
nice yum had fun I'm gonna let Kiana
talk about it as soon as though when she
gets to it because it was mostly her I
got to see Palmer a little bit too and
she kissed me and something happened to
me
I don't remember anything that happened
after that um
[Music]
kissed me
while kids cannot get all like Emma
cannot get a rick Joseph look at all for
inspiring okay
now thank you for the pinky from Grandma
have you heard of Hot Licks it's a
company that sells snacks with insects
in them like warm scorpion Cricket long
inflation chip like conforms yeah yeah
it's
um
good good company yes I need to order
from them yeah
yeah maybe we can do froggy whatever
snack box for you yeah
[Music]
oh yeah totally thank you so much for
bringing that up
um such a great idea I
I couldn't have followed it myself you
know
thank you
yes
oh oh it wouldn't it be like too too bad
if I forget about it after my
hibernation
oh I'm surely gonna forget you know
ah that would be such a waste if I
forget kiddos
[Music]
but it would be a good way to bring back
froggy llama sometime
[Music]
um
Vincent long enough thank you for the
super stickers a table for you again
[Music]
foreign
according what kind of excuse is that
it's not even an excuse get on
hey what happened
where's the magic you were able to fool
me or fool Kiana so many times before
and now you you I tell you to come up
with one
thing and you couldn't you could have at
least changed it to I am a chick at all
chicken
because I'm obviously not a chicken
what happened what happened get on
[Music]
my disappointed disappointed
disappointment is immeasurable
[Music]
oh
I think I think he's ashamed and hiding
in a corner now
looking towards the wall
reflecting on
the lack of brains you know
[Music]
delicious
suitably
huh
[Music]
what do you mean Kelly said I laid an
egg
what's that mean
I let an egg I laid many eggs and you
guys came out of them
frog eggs
[Music]
all right
yeah what do you mean I'm your real
mommy did you ever have a fake mommy I'm
your one and only kiddo
[Music]
ah the story of season ah yeah yeah I
heard she's playing that well my mom is
playing that too by the way I think the
story of seasons
I don't know or something similar one of
those farming games she's playing
it must be something that's available on
steam or so because she doesn't have a
switch
it's destroy of seasons
could it be anything else there were so
many of those farming games and she's
enjoying it because you know of the
farming aspect she's like you know
because there's she has a garden where
she does all that stuff and she says she
can't stop playing it stop might be
stardew Valley
it might be that one they sound similar
I don't really know man and but she told
me that she's playing it a lot
spending a lot of time on that recently
[Music]
she can't have her own fire
fine you know it's like real life and I
I said to her don't you already have
enough farming to do in real life why do
you need it in a game
hmm
did she name her chicken Kiara that I do
not know she could have yes
um
[Music]
thank you thank you
thank you very much
[Music]
foreign
thanks for the wonderful frog week and
now I have a wonderful list of insects
to try I think I'll go with beans first
my cats seem to like flies and moths too
oh yeah oh yeah yeah
my cats they also hunt ladybugs I don't
think they've eaten one before but I
wonder if ladybugs were poisonous for
cats too
I wonder
they like to like you know use them as
like a like a ball and shoot it around
the apartment because they keep on
flying into my apartment like what the
[\h__\h] there's so many of them around
it's weird
[Music]
um I had to I had to like save some of
them because I saw a smoothie was like
right in front of my eyes
tormenting one ladybug and I'm like holy
[\h__\h] stops movie
so I I saved the ladybug and put it in
one of my
um flower pots outside
on the balcony
yeah but then then she found another one
immediately
she really loves to play with the
ladybugs uh
as long as she doesn't need them I guess
um Little Devils yeah
[Music]
ah they try to find a place to hide for
the winter really I hope they don't
infest
my apartment get on my pond my
appointment
so thank you
okay no you drew so many so many
adorable uh animations of me
thank you so much you're so adorable I
want to continue using them like even
after this week thank you so much kiddo
I don't know if you're still here but
yet actually not only you but also a lot
of other people have been making
um animations of froggy not only
animation but also a [\h__\h] ton of cute
art but so much to them like whoa how do
I use all of this oh my God
so much material
I'm so happy that yeah people so many
artists decided to do something with
Frankie wow
thank you very much
[Music]
so much so much froggy mama would be
created but I guess
I must have had a certain charm and a
special something about myself I know I
know I know
irresistible froggy Walla understandable
yeah yeah even the one with Paul I was
like when I saw this oh I'm using that
one as my loading screen for the Pomo
Tony stream it's perfect
purple on a lily pad with froggy lava in
the bag it's amazing
um it's amazing
oh perfect only only for that stream
though
can I help you know say more Sunshine
Gonna Miss You froggy Mom I hope you
have another hostile take over again
someday thank you for enjoying thank you
perfect
thank you for spending time with us this
week for me while I will miss you dearly
but your cuteness is too dangerous to
pretend best in small doses we'll be
waiting to see you again though thank
you you will you know be alone without
me but you have to survive in the wild
okay I have to go hibernate kid oh it's
too cold outside kennel
I will always miss my frog mother
don't worry you will become a strong
frog yourself you will think of your
strong frog mother and with that power
with the advice you got the precious
advice you will also become just like me
General believe
believe
yeah
back to the Frog jar
[Music]
this power comes the Frog's
responsibility
good try
two percent of us
hey we don't need numbers here no
numbers yo that's very depressing at all
that's too depressing don't don't we
don't want to think about how the
reality is it's too harsh
ah
[Music]
um oh yeah so keys or lake
thank you thank you with a binky thanks
for the front of me [\h__\h] you always so
cute and the streams were cool the only
thing that will hurt more than losing
our frog Overlord is ripping the Frog
ears I glued on back off
[Laughter]
well they're not real
it's gonna hurt even more if they're
real
you glued them on
you deceived me you're a real Temple
I know that
they look real to me J frogberg and your
name has frog in it
so I think you're a real frog now
[Music]
um baby
you're my baby
you might blame me
[Music]
another 10 cute
again
[Music]
my tomatoes
Phoenix very shiny Hunter thank you for
the pinky quinoa thank you again for
amazing Club yesterday you replied to my
super chat a few months ago saying
promotory would be impossible and never
give up hope a year of manifesting paid
off in one of the best streams ever I
love you both forever
thank you
um
well yeah I may have like partially
like at that point like
not believed in it anymore for a while
but some things changed
behind the scenes I guess and I'm glad
it was reconsidered and um you know
just take a bit more time
but now finally
finally so that aged really badly
there's a clip there's I think several
clips that now have comments all over
them well this aged like milk
[Music]
but that's good I am glad that it's aged
badly
thank God you know
[Music]
um
okay oh
um I have to hibernate so I can't help
it with the fruit flies now maybe after
I'm awake again prognostic and okay okay
thank you for everything froggy Wawa
because of you this week was one of the
best weeks ever all the streams were
amazing it was absolute cutest thing
ever existed I really hope we'll get to
see you again I will miss you so much
I'll be always My OC thank you
I'm sorry I canceled like two streams
but I still streamed on those days I
just didn't do double streams I kind of
like
[Music]
overestimated myself I think because
like I don't know I was feeling kind of
uh
[Music]
I don't know how to describe it I mean I
was busy too but also I just I just
I don't know
we are we are wrong we brought frog was
like time was a bit difficult I couldn't
figure it out and also just didn't
really feel like it
[Music]
sorry butts but still streamed every day
except Monday so big success can uh from
Beth also VR no but I thought you know
it would be like somewhat playable
online
apparently the developers had a plan to
make an online mode like two years ago
but they never did
so I would have had to figure out with
parsec and blonde that all seemed like a
little bit too annoying so then I
requested a couple of songs
um that we didn't have clear permissions
yet to sing like a lot of Toho songs
um I requested to sing them instead in
the karaoke stream today
um but didn't come in time
only one song which wasn't even frog
related
but that was okay at that point I was
like whatever there's not even that many
frog songs so surprisingly so whatever
I'm just doing like a general Toho any
song karaoke so I was looking up a lot
of songs and was making a list
no but yeah
didn't get the permissions in time but
eventually eventually we can still do it
another time
but because that didn't work out either
I was like oh whatever I'm just I don't
know I don't want to think about it
anymore and I'm just gonna
clean my apartment instead
yeah
perfect excuse to revive from email and
so now we have a couple of reasons I I
still have like two or three frog
related games
and actually a couple more that we can
play we can do like a frog Marathon
sometime where we play all these
leftover games or we spread it out
um yeah actually there's a couple still
next next week There's um the new frog
detective game coming out so every now
and then if I need a thriller game or so
froggy Mama might come back and also I
guess the snack box which will be an
absolute Delight uh for me as a frog yes
uh yeah and the kettle okay it sounds
fun because I want to sing with these
tiny hands
[Music]
so it's not not goodbye forever don't
worry you know thank you unknown frog
you are now slimy but everything
is
[Music]
from your bad news I've been sneaking
onto this account for the actual owners
going to return soon it has been fun
frogging with you this week thank you
okay oh same here
thank you for joining the Frog fun
Vincent long enough
uh I'll talk more about my dad with pomu
next week I think
[Music]
this one's done too
um
I am considering not making a schedule
for next week because as I said I'm
probably gonna stream less and I don't
want to stress myself out too much about
um streams next week
I have a recording with it's on tomorrow
um
I have a collab with Reina that's for
sure
hmm
yeah but besides that I don't want to
stress myself this way you know I don't
know this this week stressed me out in a
weird way
uh
I'm sorry
um
[Music]
on her Channel though I think
uh-huh
I'll try to play something Halloweeny
possible
let me just mention
and besides that I don't know I might
ask you guys for some suggestions I
don't want
to go oh little nightmares too we have
to play that one
probably playing that either next week
or on the 31st which is Monday in the
week after
um
I'm not sure where to put it oh
Kiana
song and for blood is finished just
waiting a little bit longer for the mix
is almost finished too so I think we can
like bring it out I know on the coming
Friday maybe
yeah Friday or Saturday maybe even the
first day who knows
hmm
schedule
musical videos yeah
I am alien isolation oh
well I might I might do a tweet or
somewhere ask about some games
it's kinda doing the mix yes I asked for
the special occasion
um if Kira would like to do the mix
because it's his song
so Kina is doing the mixing
I thought you know
for my song covers
um I don't
I always go with gojo-san
um but this time I was like you know
what I might as well you know because
it's hit a song and yeah it's gonna have
that special Kira sound
yeah
yeah it's like I'm getting endorsed from
the producer
sounds like a killer mix yeah
it would probably sound very different
from the live version
um
yeah
I have yet to watch the finished music
video by the way so I'm gonna watch it
right after this because I forgot about
it I was sent it when I woke up I saw oh
it's there and I'm like oh okay I'll
check it out later because I was like
half half awake I'm gonna check it out
now you reminded me of it thank you
kiddo
mm-hmm
[Music]
too busy researching bugs yeah
yes yes
oh wait for the question thank you for
the pinky don't ever apologize for
streaming unless you already provide us
so much content silly bird frog thank
you for always telling for always
working hard and bringing the best don't
forget thank you
I
I don't know man I have to be honest I
don't know what it is but like for the
past couple months I've had these
phases that feel like burnout or maybe
not burnout I don't know
it could be something else well I'm not
sure and I'm trying to keep it under
control
but yeah
[Music]
um mental exhaustion maybe you know
um
it's not as bad as it was in summer
but it's I I you know I feel it the
whole week I've been feeling it but I
was like I need to I need to stream Rock
quick fight off
finally I finished it so I'm proud
I'm proud kennel
thank you for watching the streams this
week
[Music]
um
you know
[Music]
this week is a very special week I hope
you enjoyed it seeing a little bit
different kind of different looking
kiwawa this week
um I really
and I'm so happy I had this like device
here
um ready for me to use I think it was
really charming and we had some fun
together played some some frog themed
cute games
a frogtastic wig yeah we got so much
cute frog you wow art oh my God this is
so cute I hope that maybe next year on
my birthday I'm gonna aim to make a
frogging lava plushie
yeah because holy [\h__\h] is the cutest
thing ever
it's gonna take a long time because
don't have much opportunities to make
merchandise
but I want to make a froggy mama [\h__\h]
it would be so cute right
right
now
yeah next you can place it next to your
dinosaur gouda plushies if you have one
which one is more threatening
which one is more dangerous which one is
the better predator
me
Clash of the Titans
yeah
last not really that would be Dino frog
not samitoli
foreign
[Music]
trigger it works with my brain I send
brain waves to the gun and then it goes
Kaboom okay
shut up kiddo you know nothing about
guns
this is a special frog dance for people
with small small fingers okay
um
don't underestimate this gun
[Music]
alright can you guys take some cute
pictures of me with both of my hands
because it's really hard to take
pictures of me
um with both hands when I need one hand
to to
um you know
take the screenshot
so take some pictures
oh that's so cute
that is so cute
okay got it okay high resolution please
[Music]
I'll go
a little bit to the side and then
uh-huh
[Music]
wait
ah
oh oh this thing is hard to control
how should I hold it kennel
[Music]
this is really hard to turn it the right
way
[Music]
okay like this
thank you okay
[Music]
hi
cute cute
how about
[Music]
foreign
strong head
look at this face
remember it
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
have idea
oh wait I didn't fix the straight the
the screen properly huh
okay
now it's too too far
yeah
[Music]
oh yes oh yes hold
hold
what
[Music]
hold
what hold oh yes
[Music]
oh
hi am I looking at it
oh I'm holding it I'm holding it
I'm liking it
[Music]
did you take it
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
um Maximilian poor
um keeping me company today
[Music]
why all these flies mail
all right I'll go cook some poof thank
you thank you thank you for watching
always
[Music]
um
I will miss these hands say bye bye to
the hands get on my mind your small
hands
no more gravity fingers
[Music]
where am I maybe next time maybe next
time they will be longer can I still
growl I don't think so okay no
[Music]
what do we say
I remember wow
thank you oh frog they're saying
[Music]
bye bye oh
oh no oh no she's gone oh
[Music]
um
I'm playing with you now I'm sorry I'm
gonna go for real
I'm fine
[Music]
oh folk folk frog
bye bye
[Music]
goodbye
try to survive my sweet tadpoles
don't eat the ladybugs
and stay away stay away from other frogs
they want to eat you
okay
[Music]
laughs
bye bye
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
thank you so much for the Frog week
thank you and thank you for
um helping with the model
husk and um pretty too and my Marlin
[Music]
foreign
I repeat that scene
[Music]
yeah I won't sleep
hopefully I'll survive the winter maybe
you guys can put a blanket on me
you know
laughs