[Music]
sorry
wait
okay
[Music]
up
yes yes yes it is
here for you today
to play the temporaries demo
yay
oh sorry cat passing through the camera
okay move on chance move on
and back
up
actually so it comes out on the 18th
august 18th which is in most countries
tomorrow but if you like in japan or so
then you could in theory already play
but
for my time zone i'm playing it one day
early
which is super exciting it's uh
let me let me explain a little bit first
um it's a free demo
that will is available uh on the 18th of
august
on evo ps5 ps4
xbox series xs
xbox and xbox one yes yes yes yes
and so nope it's not it's not gonna be
available on pc therefore i am today
playing it on ps4
uh
i am i'm going to be receiving a ps5 uh
somewhat soon for
i guess for playing the game um
uh when it releases
but uh it didn't make it in time so
today i'm playing it uh on ps4 i i i dug
out my
old ps4
uh
to play this demo today now let me
mention though if you recall if you
follow my schedule and stuff then you
might have seen
uh that i actually
played a demo a few weeks ago
and that was actually the same demo
however back then i played it privately
and because it was not uh i couldn't
share it yet but today i'm playing
basically the same demo uh publicly
um so i already kind of know what's
going on and i already explored a lot
last time so i'll i'll try to explore
even more this time if that is possible
so basically in this uh demo
um you can actually get a little bit of
everything because there is not only the
basic tutorial of how to fight in a lot
of battles there is also um camping
and cooking and skits so everything er
although all the big features are
available in the demo and there's also
supposedly a subquest and
a powerful enemy at the end that you
have to fight it's like a like a little
boss at the end
so we're gonna do all that
yeah
and also again one more one big feature
is also that you're able to
play all six characters from the
beginning from the get-go so you start
in the demo we are going to start in the
demo
and it's going to be
six characters that we can choose from
which is the whole cast basically so i
want to try out all of them of course
oops that was too loud yep i'm going to
try out all of them but
uh
i think i want to focus on
alfin and kisada maybe because they're
just um i think my favorites at the
moment to fight with so
er oh yeah
and
also if you guys download the
the demo
then you will also receive a free
attachment
uh which is uh the vacation huddle
attachment you can use that in the full
game later on once it releases yeah yeah
yeah so that's a little something a
little present uh from tails overrides
if you go get the demo uh on your
console
[Music]
yeah so shall we get into it let's move
over tell us
about
here we are yeah that's my hands and
here i am
so i'm gonna play this on ps4 as i said
and oopsie wait ah god i'm not used to
ps4 i never know which button is the
okay moving on button and which one is
the cancel button is it is it or x
let's test it out is it o start demo no
it was not o it's x i knew it i knew it
okay so in the beginning we can change
some settings here let me also turn on
the bgm um
[Music]
bgm there we go
oh i think right now there is no bgm
you shot your shot
x okay difficulty we could go with
normal i would say input cueing time i
think when i was playing this first i
pretty much kept everything the way it
is
so
i think we're going to keep it this way
um
agree
brightness button
um okay
save and begin i changed nothing
woo so we start off with this screen
select the character you wish to control
in the demo when you clear the demo you
can see a preview video for the
character you are controlling when
clearing it notes the controlling
character can be switched during
gameplay however the bonus movie that
plays after playing the demo will remain
based on whichever character you first
selected on the screen so i think when i
first
played the demo i think i did often i
kinda wanna see hers uh
uh if that's okay for you guys
or kisara
[Music]
no headphones
what are you talking about
read up to me
[Music]
and then when i play the actual game no
wait wait then then this won't be a
thing oh well okay we'll we'll go with
kisaraforno we can always sell changes
okay
[Laughter]
[Applause]
now loading
okay
we start out
in this beautiful scenery
bob
land of green yeah that's me nancy as
one of the areas that i introduced to
you guys before it there's some really
nice like alps music playing
look at that
never mind
so as i as i have chosen quesada this is
who we started off with
and i think you can also already notice
the art style of the scenery is like it
has like a watercolor filter we talked
about it in the
in the interview that we had oh look at
that cliff man what a cliffhanger it's
such a nice view oh it really is thank
you kisara for that comment you're right
yeah don't look down but please no more
step further cause you're gonna fall
down
wow you know what's prettier than that
view
you
oh yeah this this way we can dash
and this way we can jump
and i am going to explore every single
corner of this game
because uh that's what you do doing rpgs
oh yeah oh yeah flirt oh wow yeah wasn't
that a great flirt i know
however
eh wait a second
[Music]
yes this is the
menu i think i wanna
how does this work again i think i wanna
change first of all
uh
i'm gonna change party leader to xi'an
because
see if i do that then the
um the character that you run around
with will change to her
or whoever you want it to be you can
also have it be a law for example
yay
whoever you wanted to be but i always
wanted to be um a cute pretty girl
and
there was something else i wanted to do
but we'll find out how that works again
oh
cutting
[Music]
voice acting time
so
so cyclists have invested even tranquil
places like this huh
that's a damn shame
what do you expect tamed or strength
wherever the randoms are lurking toilets
are sure to follow
it would be a surprise if there somehow
weren't any cyclists in this park that's
great i know that
it just threw me for a loop a little is
all
listen cycles are deployed depending on
the environments they're best suited for
when we visit an area for the first time
will have no idea what they're capable
of so think carefully how to put that
blazing sword to use
yeah he got that hot ass blazing sword
on his back right he nice i want that i
want the sword it looks so cool
right i'll keep that in mind now let's
get moving i think we're getting into
the first battle
battlefield
[Music]
okay how do we fight
combat screen explanation
so there's bootstraps i've heard about
that before use normal attacks to build
up the gauge then when the glass is full
press something down there
to unleash a pretend potent co-op
attacker can defeat non-boss phones
there's cute points concerned when
casting healing and support arts that's
only really gonna matter if we play
ringwell or shion i think
and shion is the one with the
healing arts by the way and and rinwell
is the one with magic arts and stuff
lshp okie dokie arts
so in order to trigger any of these arts
you can
and press three buttons so you can of
course change the arts that apply to
those buttons but we start out with
those i think
an art squash consumed when arts are
used
so we cannot use them like forever
unlimited but from the way i played it
previously it felt like i could really
bash them out
all the time and yeah boost attacks er
is the price
of the thingies to try out the
corresponding character special movement
unique with unique effects no problem
[Music]
okay
are you sure
yes
yes i'm fine oh basically combat
controls normal attack so this is what i
was actually quite surprised about
uh our
r1
for a normal attack
which i thought is a
interesting choice uh it felt
it was surprising at first but it it
feels it feels smooth actually it's not
bad
at first you can bring up uh up to three
normal attacks together but by learning
certain skills this limit can be
increased
characters can also attack in midair
after jumping
art art size special actions performed
by spending part of your art squash
press a triangle to square the x to use
the art assigned to each button
while a g will gradually restore uh
automatically it will restore more
slowly when attacking
evading
push l and press r2 to evade an enemy
attack okay i'll try if you time it well
as an enemy attack is approaching you'll
perform a perfect invasion allowing you
to avoid taking any damage yeah we'll
see about that if that works today
[Music]
okay
don't tell me
oh
[Music]
oh oh yeah well wait butch track is
happening blue striker one hit kill
attack performed in tandem with other
allies when you see the word strike on
an enemy press something down there
to use one immediately both strikes
occur more frequently with lower enemy
hp and higher combo cone counters
[Music]
i choose you
we did it
that was really dope
[Music]
but i can activate the boost attacks
easily with the bottom left finger
i think i've got the hang of this yeah i
think so
don't let it get to your head complete
complacency
leads to trouble is this another
discussion we're gonna have about
whether or not the word exists like
nervosity
yeah the fights look very cinematic yeah
there's so many things happening so many
flashy things it's really fun
it doesn't get boring that you never
lose enough do you
there's no such thing as being too alert
in battle on we go alrighty so that was
just a little introduction a simple
introduction in how the fight works
uh
is perfect good recognition instead of
evading quesada prefers to guard with
her shield and can even trigger some
arts while guarding successfully
guarding raises her morale making any
hearts unleashed while guarding
and resulting combos stronger and harder
to block
all right
oh we can pick some berries here or
whatever that is cooking
summary at caps and inns you can cook
meals conferring temporary effects when
eaten new dishes can be made by finding
recipes while ingredients can be found
at collection points and general stores
eating a new meal overrides any previous
effects so this is the cooking has been
a thing in all of the tales off games
for a long long long time so of course
we have it in this game as well and
depending on who in the party cooks a
meal the extent of their effects and
their duration will vary as such it's
wise to rotate who's on cooking you the
best on your current goals and the
party's overall status yup yup yup yeah
everyone has uh things they can cook
well
and things that they suck at cooking
as well so let's run a little bit over
there i see something sparkly
something i can pick up
apple jam what's doing here
gels are the healing items of tails off
games there's apple gel orange gel
pineapple gel grape gel all that kind of
stuff oh do we want to fight those uh
idiots but wait a second wait a second
wait a second how do i
look away
wait
i want to change to see on them because
those
those characters
uh
how do i do that again
oh yeah this way those characters
those enemies fly in the air and they
might be easier to attack with xion yeah
so part information summary you can
change which characters will fight in
combat as well as who you wish to
control their position determines what
to press to trigger their boost attack
and press l1 or l1 during comet to
change who you control yeah so you can
do it really smoothly during uh the the
fight during the battle as well but i
want to do it now beforehand so that i
don't freak out
and changing metal controls press
options to change your character's
battle control semi-auto automatically
moves around until in attack range
manual full character control auto
fights based on set strategy
oh yeah
i think we can keep most of other things
i wanna switch out
you to you
um and maybe we need some magic in our
team as well yeah i think that that
looks good
okay
so
find me
hey
i have to jump into them because they're
up so high
wait wait it didn't really work
[Music]
did i not save or something
the changes leader i guess that was it
[Music]
consider yourself
without healing right now
[Music]
like we're going to lose the small fry a
hell no
of course not remo
or that infuses the hole with power when
squeezed it requires refinement to
safely use as a constant exposure
results increased aggression
yeah the fights are really satisfying i
have to agree with that metal engraving
the metal engraver can craft accessories
for you
for you for you using ore that you mined
from mining points once you strengthen
an accessory and activate new skills for
it you can even transfer those skills to
a different accessory all together
sounds interesting
i wonder if we'll see
someone like that in this demo
let's leave the highway wow
[Music]
the characters look gorgeous yes battle
transition extremism yeah that's what um
i
uh we also talked about ah
in the in the interview that i did with
the producer and then the man is talking
to me well
so you were approaching
me hey you two there i don't think i've
seen you around here before you two from
out of town
so what if we are what business is it of
yours
no none at all you just don't look like
you know where you're going that's all
all right this is our first time in this
area
then you'll want to head to visit the
big capital of el domination
just know that as you can clearly see
the area is crawling with soilless and
they all seem to be even angrier than
usual
if you're not looking to get jumped by
them stick to the highway yeah i gotta
fight them all
you're safer than trying to cut across
the rough and run into trouble no no no
no no no no we're not running away from
them
although judging by that sword you're
carrying maybe you thrive with dangers
he does i think he does
if that's your thing i won't stop you
but don't say i didn't warn you anyway
vision huh what do you think we should
do
not like we have anywhere else to go
better than wandering these fields
aimlessly
then it's settled we're off division
[Music]
safe travels folks i'm going to hang
around here a bit longer in case more
travelers like you to lose the way yeah
thank you okay sure do whatever you want
come on guys uh it let me see him
immediately but i actually wanted to go
to that side over there
and
cause yes there's some berries here
tomato tomato okay that tomato are not
berries i'll take that back
all right we have some weird monsters
over there
and i want to
change something again
[Music]
okay i think now i should be uh
attacking them with alfin
right away alvin is basically the main
character
definitely a safe choice to go with it
[Music]
yeah i activated that so you can
activate those whenever you want as long
as there are lights it's lighting up
there you go
[Music]
consider yourself finished
see how they're talking after the battle
instead of you know
in premier's tales off games
um after each battle there would be like
a
oh she learned his skills there would be
like a scream
shows you how much um
how much money and which items you've
got and all that
[Music]
um
but in terms of the rise they took that
out and you can really smoothly be
useful and quickly
transition from battle into back to the
field as you see saw now
what could this be and they still banter
a little bit
uh by voice only
uh you can see that that should be a
good place to fight yeah yeah wow kisara
it's so big
though you're talking about my shield
yeah
that gave me a bamboozle
give me this scale of crystal
i want to explore a lot
wait it's always been half an hour yeah
you guys want to rescue the stream is
supposed to be like uh
uh one hour but i want to explore
everything and finish the demo so we
might have to extend it a little bit i i
thought i thought i thought it would be
shorter than that anyway happy so in
this little spot we can make a camp
yeah resting at the campground will
restore your party's hp and cp while
resting you can watch skits and cut
scenes that you previously viewed should
we check it out
by the way when's our our one again
what are those things i sometimes see
you chuck out in the middle of fights
what you mean my bombs
bombs as in the things people used to
clear out rocks but
i could have sworn i saw something other
than fire burst from some of yours
that's because these aren't ordinary
bombs they're specially made ones filled
with astral energy
hmm
okay
and why do you shoot the bombs
it's a part of my strategy the effects
of my bombs change when i fire bullets
of a different astral element at them
it makes it difficult for enemies to
predict what effect they'll have or when
they'll go off
one moment you're using powerful bombs
the next you're using powerful healing
hearts
they're kind of on the opposite ends of
the spectrum yeah aren't they she is the
healer of the group yeah they do it this
way
if you ever get caught up in the blast
of one of my bombs and you manage not to
die
i'll be able to heal you using my heart
i'll do my best to be okay she's an
all-rounder
so that is uh the the the skits the new
look of the skits oh i ran into an enemy
i didn't even see it
[Applause]
oh
doesn't that look freaking dope
oh my god
sometimes i wonder where you come up
with those moves i could say the same to
you
good thing we're on the same side huh
did it
all right um but yeah the skit that i
just showed you it didn't activate
because of the camp it actually it can't
i can activate it anyway i think yeah
with our one on the bottom right you see
it whenever you have a skit available to
look at
then you can activate it whenever you
want and they have a really new look
sometimes we come across enemies who
fight like you and try to dodge our
attacks at the last second
i hate those guys i can get some hits in
when they move into attack but otherwise
they slip past damn near everything else
i throw at them well if what you're
seeking is a way to more reliably hit
them there is a solution
try to outclass them on reflexes
i possess the ability to command earth
elemental beings to some extent
they emerge as the land itself and take
root on my command so handsome it will
swiftly bind the enemies at which point
you can dispatch them the red hair looks
gorgeous
uh what he means is that he can make
plants grow to hold the enemies in place
at least i think that's probably what
he's saying
i'm glad at least one of us understands
him
so basically if we find an enemy that
likes to dodge we should let dohalim
handle it
i'll do what i can within my modest
means to help
he's so polite
ah we were there so many skits we can
look at well let's look at another one
random technology
hey shion where does your gun come from
what do you mean what do you mean yeah i
was gonna ask the same thing when you're
fighting it looks like it just appears
out of nowhere oh that's transferral
technology he's he's questioning the rpg
logic
game logic and when i do i summon it
make sense don't break the fall of
walmart not really
but it sounds pretty
amazing huh
well that way you don't have to carry
around any heavy weapons or worry about
enemies trying to steal them right
yeah that's a pretty cool invention i
guess so you realize you're praising the
technology of your enemies right really
i'm gonna
technology's technology it's not good or
bad in and of itself
you can learn from your enemies
oh my god i think there's like uh a skit
for each character right now um let's
save a few ones for later let's look at
the camp uh thingy
peppa
peppa pepper
okay so this is the shopkeeper for those
times when victory is almost in reach
it's our job as shopkeepers to help you
get the rest of the way there so he's he
can sell me some stuff buy i can buy
some stuff you can even uh create
accessory
let's see do we want to buy something
what do we have
we have one apple gel how much money uh
ten thousand film i'm gonna buy some
uh for later
yeah
um
because this is 400 hp i'm gonna also
buy
a few of those
and
um
cp i think we'll be we'll be fine
but we have 10 of those nice
okay
and
do we have something valuable oh oh it
offers me immediately to sell commodity
items that i
uh can use just to get some money let's
do it
maybe i should have used those to create
an accessory oh well we might find more
you can never be too prepared
but did we have to spend so much yes to
be prepared for battle the last fight
actually that comes at the very end
uh is actually uh a little bit
challenging like i had i i felt like i
didn't die but i felt like
it was a i didn't go game over but i did
die one of one of my characters died so
it is a little bit challenging let's
let's rest a little bit
let's rest
everyone at the campsite so you see what
that looks like too skit
let's see
i've cooked cleaned and sewn
i think that's everything for today oh
so here you can either go immediately to
rest or you can reminisce by looking at
previous skits
and we can look at one right now too a
new one
weight training
yeah who lives there so cute right 97
oh 88 oh 89 he's lifting oh shoot
he's lifting air really heavy air okay
uh sorry about that you're not hurt are
you nah law
what on danna are you doing
what am i doing training obviously what
on those nice and heavy rocks that i
decided to strap onto my arms well i
guess i didn't tie them down good enough
because they went flying
so you were doing improvised weight
training
you and your crazy ideas
i can't help it if i'm not training it's
easy for me to get anxious
well that's fair
actually i remember seeing you
practicing your forms for some time when
we were camping the other day
yep
no amount of muscle do you any good if
you don't stay on top of your fighting
forms oh it always feels good when i
know i'm still sharp guys i am listening
to what he said
don't train so hard that you ride it and
run it down
i promise you you're already perfectly
strong as it is
oh no i'm not you never know what we'll
run into out there you can never go into
a fight too prepared and that's the
truth
besides i won't rest until i know that
i'm stronger than you elfin wow okay
oh i see what it is
well i don't plan on letting you feel
some tension there
maybe i'll add some weights to my sword
and practice swinging it
that should help out
alvin are you crazy
[Music]
you're right
this does make for dc you guys just use
rings
since we've already come this far what
do you say we have a little one-on-one
with our rocks strapped on
hell yeah i'm down for that just give me
a second i'll be all ready to roll all
right okay
i'm all set
let's do this
take this
i'm just getting started wow
our camp is completely wrong oh my god
unbelievable you two are cleaning it up
uh-huh
i think
what this look seems familiar to me
uh
okay so let's rest
oh yeah it gives us the option to cook
before resting
and look at this food though
oh it looks so good
damn
oh yummy
yummy with some sour cream yo
ice cream um
m m
we'll just start with
i want to use the attack up later on and
i don't want to
waste my ingredients so
i'll do
[Music]
i'll do this one ice cream
ring well
let's do it this came out so good i
almost hate having to eat it
wow
elemental attack up medium
favorite meal effect reduces effect by
20 but boosts the duration noise
[Music]
good morning everyone
we're done
eating is one of your great
passions ice cream it's like
drinking they're ashamed of
okay let's continue the plants have
already grown again no no i want to pick
up the plants please thank you
[Music]
no okay boo
i'll keep on talking to him all right
let's make some progress let's fight
also there are cringes
here and there
i don't want to miss out on anything
then
[Music]
let's see something hidden there that
there's nothing in it
fight first let's go
[Music]
can you sell him his own plans yeah
probably i don't think
[Music]
so if you've noticed look at the bottom
right when i'm on the ground i have
branching wipe and solid blades
[Music]
yeah but now i ran out of the wall
street
[Music]
and then we have uh
in the battle it gets a bit loud yeah we
want that by a mile
open up what do we have in here dumb
braces
so i think for every character there is
a treasure hidden on this demo
and and the dumb braces are for law
see
they are quite a bit better and they
also change the looks of his uh weapon
so we're gonna try to find all of them
in the demo i found almost all of them i
was missing one or
two i was already looking quite so
ferolly
so i wonder where the others are well if
we won't find them then that's okay too
but oh that that boy looks so strong
around there he's very hard to find just
looking at it
yeah
it probably messed us up good what
should we try it looks really big
looks kind of dangerous game even warned
us
let me freshen up in the waterfall first
go gel
nice that's a special one
[Music]
are those
they activated them again
i need to activate some different people
this game is beautiful it really is i
can become even stronger
i'm strong
okay xi'an um should i heal you before
we go in there
tomorrow let's heal you with uh yeah
yeah uh with your own skill
yes okay
and then we shall give a try
to this monster but i'm a bit scared i
don't remember finding this one
in the in the demo when i first played
it
well
yeah go no further ready to go okay
oh my god
[Music]
some large enemies have orange glowing
spirit cores that can be destroyed after
taking a set amount of damage so uh
doing so will break the core and down
them depending on the enemy these weak
points can also be directly targeted
okay i will try it's just the horn i
suppose
you're finished
[Music]
oh
um
i need healing
thank you
take it down appreciate the help
[Music]
oh
with no issues
[Music]
okay we almost got him halfway down
something
[Music]
[Laughter]
what is that what is that i owe you tion
is
[Music]
fight
oh
[Music]
thank you for the healing thank you
thank you
[Music]
oh my god
doing those combos
[Music]
okay
oh my
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
i'm so scared
now um
[Music]
oh my god yeah that's an elite mob's
pretty tough cell
so i would say we did well nonetheless
i feel wow brightlier than before sprite
leah what does that mean
oh my god
oh wow
oh wow ah see we could we could in
theory recover us uh in this screen as
well
when you look at the left side there's a
recovery button but we currently don't
have as much cp
so let me heal with um
theons
uh oopsies
ah oh wait i can't oh yeah because we
don't have cp well
we could we could cook or we could uh
quickly rest because over there is where
the resting area was
wow that was quite something
so much fun though
oh man
it's so much fun
i got applejacks yeah but i want to save
save them
because this wasn't even the best time
of night ever makes me feel uh oh wait
no no no no no i don't want to point i
don't want to what goes on inside that
head i'll see you again i still got the
other cooking effect on
[Music]
okay like this are made for fishing days
yes okay
this are rather loud
wait when is a day like this
so we want another uh skits to calm down
a little bit
let's see what do we got
hey ringwell do you always have to say
an incantation before you cast an art oh
yeah
they don't really add any extra power or
anything but reciting them
familiar energy to come together and
flow through me
it takes time to complete but they're
what lets me use that introduce this one
what happens if someone interrupts you
while you're in the middle of chanting
then i have to start over from the
beginning as soon as my concentration
breaks any astral energy i've
accumulated
right
sounds like iris
that's our cue to make sure that no
enemies can get near enough to disrupt
you
yeah that would be appreciated although
i do have one fun trick up my sleeve
you're right now that you're saying once
i finish chanting a full incantation i
can hold on to a single astral art
without casting it right away totally so
cute
so once
is in place you can choose to set it off
whenever you want that's amazing
yeah
i don't fully have the hang of it just
yet but i'm sure it'll come in here you
guys want to try and run well for a
battle because i mentioned this during
the interview as well i think um the
interview that we had with the producer
uh
but like normally if i play
um
like
a magic character
a casting art character
um in any other tails off game
it it it doesn't feel right um because
like they they cast a long time and you
i don't know i feel like they're always
better as npcs but in this game it
actually felt
kind of easier
so let me uh let's let's try us try try
it out shall we
uh
let's see
let's try it out on
not not you not not you
but i see some some stuff here
rachel nice
thanks
let's move on a little bit and then use
rinwell
i don't sense any more enemies
i sense some items though
wait i i need fish thank you
i see something there what is that
here have this herb
i'm fine thanks
i found the printer
i already knew that that was there
this place is rather clean
why don't you lighten the mood for us
while we're here then
we'll see what i can do
so that item was for duhalem i think uh
[Music]
wait what uh
huh wait a second
get out of the water first
now there we go and
i think that was because i was still
moving
and
items no equipment equipment
for
doha limp
different weapon
it's a bit stronger
noise
all righty so i heard that this is the
first time in a tails off game that you
can uh swim and
i think there's like a tiny bit of a wet
effect like if you see she's like
dripping water a little bit and she
looks
yeah she's dripping and she looks a
little bit wet
i don't know if it's my imagination but
she looks wetter than before she's
definitely dripping
at least uh
on my big screen i don't know how big
you guys see it
uh shall we swim through there
[Applause]
wow she's a good swimmer
there's another one here
whose weapon is this
secret weapon gecko
[Music]
wait that's an armor no i know it's for
a kisara
looks like a mama but look
before after new item i mean this one is
just her standard one i think because it
fits her armor but this one is better
rock wall it's literally a rock
no one can break this rock make us even
more formidable
okay
back into the water
and we'll go up here
and see this is so cute when i was
playing liz on the demo i wanted to show
you guys look at those chickens
look look at them
baby chicks as well
salmon can we can have eggs from them
thank you thank you for the eggs
thank you for the chicken
so uh a lot of you were also surprised
when i mentioned that there's actually a
farming effect in this game
i don't know if we can do it in the demo
but you can you can farm
you're gonna have like like lifestyle
you should think about eating soon
really a cow
don't make me say it again so many items
good idea
beef
yummy we can cook some nice food tonight
what do we have here
we enter now
special ah another chest
it's really worth exploring but but uh
there's no point in reading it unless
you plan on making it um the treasures
that we're finding in the demo uh the
the arm and the the weapons
as far as i know they are not
in the actual game they just placed more
for the demo so you guys have more to
see you know
kyle just chilling here give me milk
me milk
give me milk
elk
oh nice
baby cow
help
look at those
pigs they look so cute they're like a
daughter of hatsuma and piccola
oh horsies
interesting looking horses
okay enough exploration we should
continue a little bit um i could do this
for hours and hours right now but it's
already been an hour
and the stream was supposed to be an
hour but i'm gonna go longer it's no
problem for me i enjoy playing uh
this game so
wait was i already here
yes i was okay wait how do i open the
big map again
[Music]
that was it
this is the button for the big map so we
came from here i think
and we went there we checked out that
area we we camped here and now we are
like here okay we're close
to
the city
uh oh yeah
i just i just want to see i don't want
to miss out on any treasures but i think
i checked everything out in the water
area so we should be fine
weird pigs
okay so here would be i think the
capital
of menancia
but
normally you could pass but in the demo
it leads you to somewhere else you will
see
pardon me if i'm not mistaken are you
two
travelers and you are
uh where are my manners my name is
trashin i work for the city hey
oh we were told to come to visit i'm
guessing this is it yes
yes you've certainly come to the right
place
i wish i could say welcome to you both
however
the gates to the city are currently
sealed
nobody is currently allowed to enter
a dangerous goal is on the loose you see
hmm
it's wiggle they're nothing to get in a
twist about we saw plenty of them on the
way over maybe
this is no ordinary circle i fear
it's a rather large specimen one that's
free of its former constraints
worse still
there are troubling reports of an even
larger toil on the lows but that's
neither here nor there
until they've both been successfully
hunted down for everyone's safety the
city will unfortunately remain on the
lockdown what does that mean there's two
and i already killed one
but in the demo i only killed one of
those big boys
they only kill one of them i guess
the one that killed me three times
does that go for you too despite being a
resident
sadly yes
due to a blunder on my part i've been
locked out as well
i'm just about to take shelter at a
nearby ranch you're both more than
welcome to join me if you wish
so are you planning on holding up at
this ranch
sorry but we've got other plans we can't
just
hey
why don't we get rid of those circles
ourselves
i was afraid you were going to have
another outrageous suggestion
hear me out the sooner we take care of
them the sooner we can end the vision
better than just sitting around at a
ranch right
all right let's do it
spit it out where are those running
around that's unfortunate
they're in the title plan planes title
wait surely you don't intend to go there
ourselves of course look at us we look
like
look at alvin he can easily slide him
he's got like this magical sword thingy
look at us we're obviously like the main
characters of a big big big upcoming
jrpg coming out uh in september on the
uh 10th to 11th 12th 11th some 10th on
honestly it's the 10th
11th so
you think you think we can fight the
boss enemy of a freaking demo easy
and now this place opens up
this was not open before
september yes
there we go
that is uh two days before my one year
anniversary
all right off we go we're in one
smothering shall we look at it run
around pewdiepie
i always hear you muttering to yourself
whenever we're in battle
so uh just what are you saying she's
casting okay
does it bother you or something
not really
it's just the way you talk is sometimes
kind of creepy what so i was wondering
if you vent your frustration through
your magic hell dudes are you yelling
you stupid jerk or something like that
to pump yourself up how you flirt with a
girl no
that's not what's happening during my
incantations
i'm just focused so i match my tone to
fit the mood of whatever i'm trying to
invoke oh invoke
uh how do i put it basically the
elemental astral energy behind each art
i guess um astral energy hold on are you
saying you can talk to astral energy
not exactly oh man i put emotion into
what i say it's easier for me to
properly cast my arts that make sense
kind of
okay so if you can talk to astral energy
then you can ask it to like predict the
weather or find secret treasure uh wait
you don't really think that you
or you can ask it to send down lightning
to where there's bad guys lurking and
you may lightning condemn those who bear
fall
what are you doing you won't frag me
with that
i got enough right energy to send down
lightning where there were annoying boys
let's go rin well
that's what i'm talking about all right
let me take a look at
the
map yeah
uh
the place that opened up is
here that's where we need to go
so over the river
but but but i feel like i feel like
there's
there's some treasure somewhere that i
missed out on
i can't just let it go
plant here
also i wanted to fight
very very well
and let's go into the water we picked up
those treasure islands so there
shouldn't be any anything around that
close
thinking logically where would i place
those treasure items where would i place
them
i'll pick up anything that's sparkly
that's not the treasure island that's
okay though
i just want everything that's sparkly
jumping fences therapy juices have gone
a long way oh hell yeah they have really
swimming is like innovative and tells up
though
one three
three
okay uh let's go
didn't hide those yet
wait i'm gonna fight
[Laughter]
[Music]
lily
oh
it's like emerald colored i love it
really pretty
some decent equipment potato
anything that makes battles easier is
okay
[Music]
i don't really
feel back
[Music]
okay
i was really surprised about that i
thought you know if you play a caster
they they usually cast you know
they spend a lot of time casting but
not in this case
so we found that treasure that we will
get everything here
potato potato is there something up
there
yes i knew it see i just have this
feeling in my in my heart it leads me to
where the treasures are
solid edge okay that's probably for
elfin
uh
[Music]
yeah
oh yeah it looks solid it has an
interesting shape
let's go with that and it's our strength
yet grows
and thus our strength yet grows naduho
don't
okay let's look at another skit because
we still have some we didn't watch
enjoy while i drink my iced tea has that
skill of yours got a name
and what skill would this be pray tell
me
you know when you're talking to people
around town the way they suddenly become
putty in your hands
i'm afraid i don't quite fall that's not
a skill that's just his thing it's
called friendly intimidation friendly
intimidating
voice and presto you'll have people
wrapped around your finger in no time
i would never stoop to such scandalous
tricks
any feelings of intimidation are solely
in the eye of the beholder
so there is a knack to it how do you
learn it can anyone do it
now you've got me curious is there
special training to master
hmm let's see
an obsession with being elegant is a
must she's roasting
old-fashioned
bonus points if you speak in a way no
one can understand
if you have a bone to pick with me it'd
be quicker to just come out and say it
what they look up to you that's all i'm
just helping them along
let's cut into alvin and all of a sudden
i can barely understand a word they're
saying and what's with the weird poses
was it something they're doing it
they're doing it
i hope you're willing to take the blame
for this one
i wasn't expecting them to take me so
seriously i'll go and have a word with
and them have a word with me kizana
wait that's funny
i like that
we we talked about this when i
introduced the game but all the
characters come from like different
um
heritages i guess and
they have very very different beliefs
all six of them and therefore you kind
of end up with these funny
funny interactions where are we are we
past it i need to go here
okay
we don't have all weapons yet
but it's okay i'll do it anyway
we'll be fine
wait wait i should i should count and
get like a um battle effect before we go
there
let's do it
different upbringings oh yeah that's
what i mean
different upbringings yeah
and they come from different planets as
well different planets obviously that
means that beauty sleep they've got
i never thought you would care have
different opinions
so let's cook
uh oh we have more choice now do it xp
boost we could do elemental defense up
obtained or up um
[Music]
i would do either a simple attack up or
a simple defense up
[Music]
thanks for waiting eat as much as you
like
yes
[Music]
yeah there are two planets all right
guys ready to go donna and rena are the
two planets
yes yes yes
i i i i'm ready to go what do you say
uh it's dangerous bastards what you guys
playing i'm actually fighting that
circle are you nuts i'd really think
twice before taking that thing on you
know
yeah i'm fine i actually killed him
before uh so i think i'm gonna be fine
i'm gonna die a few times but i'm not
gonna go game over so i'm fine
i'm fine welcome to the keys pillow
plane or title
guard
be on your guard oh guard is there
another chest here all we have to do is
get rid of that thing right there's that
thing over there you know what i really
love about this place about menancia
these these things out there
they look so cool
and they're like everywhere i love the i
love them
they look so dope stone whatever that is
i'm looking for a treasure chest oh wait
there look there must be one over there
there must be one over there
has my feeling my treasure hunter logic
deceived me there was an item here but
not a treasure okay
okay
shiny shiny
this thing
looks a little bit dangerous it has its
weak point on its foot you see that
sparkly foot
that's where we want to attack
is there really no treasure chest here
damn it i must have missed some but we
got the one for xiun we got the one for
kisara we got the one for duhalim no
wait
i think we got every one except for
rinwell
now let me edit um
let's do outfit
because it's the a big battle i feel
like we need to switch out there but
maybe
[Music]
we didn't have those two on the team yet
so
we might want to switch but i i kind of
feel like i need those too
uh
but we can switch in the battle too
right as far as i know so
let's just uh put a law and the holland
in the team now and uh
we can still
oh
right here
now
i think i have like seven
[Music]
pretty flashy out there you're so glad
it met with your approval
you just see items
we have apple gel free
lemon gel for
uh cpc
[Music]
rape gel six
ah we have enough gels and then seven
live balls it shall be fine fully
restored or we even have one of those
if if a bunch if more than one is down
we could use the omega elixir oh we also
have a treat that valuable medicine
spread across an area that restores 1000
hp to all allies okay we'll be fine
let's go
wait let's watch one more skit
i want to show you guys as many skits as
possible but i also have one more less
trodden once we're done with the demo
one more secret i don't see any path
do you mean that thing that looks like
an animal trail
path may be a generous term
i'm assuming you know where it leads
uh-huh hmm
my gut says to a britch
poodle says
really
well it is definitely in the right
general direction
ringwell has an animal necessarily
danger-free
but he does have an uncanny knack for
insisting on some strange he's a bird
can't say i appreciate some of the more
daredevil ways he's taken us though
like the landslide he insisted was a
shortcut before disappearing off the
edge nearly gave me a heart attack
yeah intrepid explorer looked as happy
as a pig
probably best we stick to doing our own
orienteering in the future
hey so what about this route then
maybe if we pretend we can't hear him
don't you think the path forward is
fraught enough without making extra
problems for ourselves
maybe best to reel it back
good point i say we stick to the main
track like regular travelers for once i
i i check that every single corner
that's not my style
i
will break down
this wall
oh
okay
well now we go into the battle
yeah this will take a while okay
support me
[Music]
looks like trouble
together
[Music]
time to cross
a thrilling performance
a new melody
oh
appreciate the concerns
oh my god
[Music]
i don't even have my healer
in my in my team i need i need
sorry you're out uh she'll i need to i
really need you
yeah okay
uh that should be fine okay
we
have good
[Music]
whenever i want
we're making some progress
[Music]
oh
the healing came just in time
[Music]
oh
or i'm about to die
[Music]
is
i have no limits
[Music]
did i die i think i didn't even die
i think elephant didn't even die right i
didn't have to resurrect him
so much fun
[Music]
that was a blast oh my god so much i
can't [\h__\h] wait
i can't wait guys
okay okay chill and we're last oh my god
greetings er greetings again travelers
like ever you've decided to take refugee
at the ranch no we killed the thing we
killed it
actually we took care of your typical
problem uh for you all
what should you just
its sheeracity gives even the city's own
guardsman paws well i am not a common
guardsman
a reasonable reaction for anyone with a
level had to have what
what you think i'm not level-headed sure
sure i do if you consider fighting a
giant zorgo first thing after arriving
at a new city to be level-headed
what about you you're the one who agreed
to help because you didn't want to have
the sleep breath
yeah she needs a a fancy nine thousand
dollar bed
that's got nothing to do with
uh pardon my interrupting you two
suffice it to say i believe you now yes
clearly i underestimated just how strong
the pair of you clearly huh oh you did
yes ashley it's not just us two my whole
team is strong as heck uh-huh
did you see how we were fighting
we're a great team
save your thanks as long as we get a
warm bed and some nice food we'll call
it even what
i don't remember you were asking for
food before
what i love her like the side look that
she gives him always
and and that yeah her hand pose like
that oh she's so sassy she's so sassy
what was that
nothing don't mind me
now to finally reopen the gates
allow me to welcome you both divisions
in earnest i'm confident our city will
be to your liking
you've given me high expectations that's
for sure great well let's head on in
let's go
but this is where the demo ends i think
yes
harmony and coexistence between the
renin's and the danons under him for the
first time in our lives we dannon's were
treated with the respect we deserve
i'm captain kisara of the elder men and
sia ghana
there is no greater honor than being
chosen to serve his excellency well
she's hot
thank you kisara what's so beautiful
i have to know how do you keep going
that's all you've been through i assure
you they are fairly compensated for
their efforts
fostering of a mutual respect among the
classes
this i can change
however for you it may be a simple
request but that can quickly become
another's difficult burden have you come
across even one slave being abused
soldiers killing for sports
suffering of any form
i would hazard
that you have not
all i care about is maintaining peace
if so
then why did you betray him
you're saying it was all just a
self-obsessed lie oh
wait that's a special scene that i'm
getting because i chose
kisara
[Music]
it looks so good it looks so good
thank you for playing no thank you thank
you for making this game
oh my god i'm so excited
yeah
okay guys um
if if in your country it is already the
18th then you're already able to get the
demo for free on ps4 ps5 xbox uh series
x uh
xbox one uh xbox x xbox series xs xbox
one and yeah uh on august 18th it will
be available on all those consoles for
free so yeah if you're in a certain time
zone you might already be getting it
otherwise just wait a few more hours and
then you'll be getting it now before we
end it uh i have one more small thing to
show you today gaming was main but i
have a little something uh another
secret skit that we can watch together
um but before we watch it let me just
say wow
ah so much fun the combat is so so so
much fun it's like so active
so flashy but in a good way
like there's just uh it's just like
i can continuously attack where my
skills with arts like nothing is
stopping me nothing is like holding me
back and uh all the boost attacks the
boost strikes are so much fun to
activate avoiding and dodging is not
even that difficult although i normally
struggle quite a lot with that in other
games
um
yeah but in this game it feels easy even
like playing
playing a character that is not the main
character like elfin
even that doesn't feel weird it doesn't
feel awkward or anything uh they all
have a different style but you can
really get used to it very quickly like
for example we played a little bit of
kisada in the beginning and she kind of
has like a little bit more of a slower
a little bit heavy
style of fighting but it's still
it's still i don't know it's a lot of
fun
and then if you want to be more like a
fast fighter than you even go for alfin
or do halem or law
and if you want to play some magic
totally go for windwell don't be scared
like i would normally not choose
uh an arts caster in a tails off game to
play by myself
but if you want a little bit uh of a
change
go for it rinwell actually barely has
casting time at all so
yeah
bring out all that flashy magic yeah
invoke those arts
so
yeah kisada is more of a tanki type and
that's really fun to play too
and xion
xin is really fun to like uh i like that
she's uh uh that she uses that rifle
so you can keep some safe distance from
the enemy
but still be very very powerful
especially against flying enemies
so there's a lot of
different possibilities
in the game so much potential for all of
these characters and i'm just absolutely
excited to
hang out more with them
and
most most of all i just really want to
learn about the story right now because
i mean i've tested the gameplay i've
tested the skits i've tested
oh most of most of the game now but i
really want to get into the story do a
deep dive into the game get stacked for
realtors but there's one more month
less less than a month less than a month
until release september 10th everyone
yes now let's move over
[Music]
to
yes i have one more small thing to show
you so let me show it right away close
me a little bit over time
taking it easy
[Laughter]
all right
here's a little taste of a rice vacation
hoodle skit
which i think probably wait will be a
bit loud when i play it one second all
right okay oh my god i'm so sorry i'm so
sorry
i'm so sorry
that was a little bit loud wasn't it
it was a bit loud
was it
yo
okay i turned it down a little bit now
it should be fine
all right it's done
apologies for the weight you guys
that's a lot of fish you've cut up again
that's because i caught so many earlier
if you're going to eat them it's best to
do it while they're still fresh
was it difficult slicing up that many
fish
no i'm used to it it's no big deal for
me at this point i know i probably
shouldn't be saying this after all the
trouble you went through but i've never
really understood the appeal of sashimi
i'm sorry law i didn't realize
i only make it because it's an easy way
to deal with big catches when i fish you
haven't done anything wrong
look if you don't like the flavor you're
always welcome to add some of my spices
to it oh
hey yeah that might work i'll just put
some of this here
what's wrong law
i've never seen someone jump up and
sprint off that fast
he ran as soon as he took a bite of that
sashimi
hmm
was he crying because of the taste
i don't think the sashimi is the problem
here guys
so this was a sample of uh how it looks
like when you play the demo
gets the free vacation huddle accessory
and put it and put it on them once the
real game releases
uh the thing that was on their hands
is that huddle vacation hoodle accessory
that was promised if you download the
free doubles if you plan on getting a
real game you gotta download the free
demo you know test it out a little bit
it's available soon all over the world
unless it's already the 18th for you
then you can already get it now so
hope you guys enjoyed this little demo
play demo test play
er
of the hilltops overrides yay
i enjoyed it very much i might play it
again
after the stream is over
so that i can get the other uh the other
like ending scenes because the one for
quesada oh my god
it was so intense
wow
it was really really intense it gave me
a little bit of a
uh
a look a little bit of a sneak peek into
her story yeah
um
so yeah that's it from my side
thank you guys for watching thank you
bandai namco
again for supporting uh me uh in this uh
in my in my official duties as the
official place of arise ambassador from
the english region
and i will see you guys
tomorrow for the next stream and
probably again soon also for another uh
[Music]
tales of a riser live stream also if you
want to get the game and you didn't
reserve it yet in my description there
is a link
uh that uh is like kind of like
affiliated with me so if you want to
reserve the game for that it will tell
bandai namco that you got it because you
watched my stream and that would be
really cool i know a lot of you already
reserved it before the the link was
there
that's okay no problem no pressure but
if you didn't yet and you're planning on
getting it i would recommend using the
link to get it yeah yeah i am
all right then thank you guys for
watching and in german we say
auf
wiedersehen
thank you
[Music]
coming out soon
oh yeah oh by the way stay tuned for
more exciting announcements coming from
bandai namco on august 18th
wait tomorrow there's an exciting
announcement tomorrow
and i just read that
there's something exciting coming
tomorrow supposedly apparently
oh my god what is it
what is it
nani
avinasin
we will have to wait and see
ending
[Music]
foreign