[Music]
many times
mama look i'm working oh you're doing
such a good job
[Music]
retweeted my my stream starting tweet
and say
said everyone has to come it's so cute
[Music]
hello look at my internet speed
look at it
uh welcome everyone
uh today my internet uh kikiriki by the
way what the hell i keep on forgetting
it today
um my internet has been turned off
it's a pocket wi-fi time mobile wi-fi
time and um
i hope we tested the streaming in the
members only stream
right before this one we had a little
one-hour animal crossing session
we tested out some things we have
optimized the the stream
as much as we can and it's low quality
but it's better than nothing
so please please accept it
forget the wi-fi
better than not streaming at all right
so yes reject burp
return to snake this is what we're doing
today
i hope it will not go so bad because
i really love playing slower down i
and we will play um we will play
slipper.io for one hour
and uh then
and then uh i would read some super
chats
if that's okay for you guys because i
still i'm not called up even though we
did a four hour super chat reading
where where i was probably fifty percent
going on tangents and talking about
other things
everyone you're welcome to join and bump
into me and give me food oops
yes let's go
let's see how my internet speed goes in
it's prime time right now in japan
and i'm using it and i'm using my pocket
wi-fi
yeah stop it puyo
i'm still curious
please guys help me i i think we might
have a lot of lag issues
but i'll try my best um one hour being
snack
it's it's nice to be a snake you know
it's fun
you don't have to i
[Laughter]
give me food give me food give me food
full full food and everyone say hi to
energy
what are you doing
apparently i am now a professional at
this game because i can
uh officially assassinate other snakes
now
have you seen that skill mitakayemanu
yes so nanati um did a little oopsy
and hijacked my stream today which was
absolutely hilarious
i was outside doing stuff i was um
i was uh doing some important anime and
administrational stuff oh thank you
thank you must have been the viewer guys
can you find me i'm like at the top of
the map come over here guys
the lag isn't even that guys this is
stream fine
is it super lucky or is it doing fine i
think it's doing it pretty well right
now
yeah yeah anyway i had like wait there's
no btm mata business
wait when i die i'll turn on the museum
i can't right now you know what to do
big boy is this like
is this the one on the leaderboard or
who is this
it's fine oh so glad i'm so i'm so glad
hello food please
where are my viewers normally there's
like millions of you guys
may not doco
come on give yourself to me offer
yourself to me offer your body
he wants to kill me he wants to kill me
die where did he go he
he disappeared so quickly
is ooh a big boy part of the legs nope
nope it's not but
i gotta i gotta acknowledge the big boys
oh
she's very aggressive that one give me
the shiny one
you know i like shiny things when
there's something shiny i gotta follow
it
by the way you guys uh if you're trying
to get into the
lobby and you don't know how it works
you gotta like actually like
it's a chair kfbj hello
hello make yourself bigger and then give
yourself to me you can follow me for a
while and follow my greatness
see what how how how to live a perfect
life as a verb and then eventually step
into my footsteps
[Music]
uh i'm i'm uh you probably will need a
um
vpn if you guys want to um play with me
yeah if you
here we go usually usually i never had
like lag problems but yeah
yeah i think like the more people are
around me
the more yeah it will get in terms of
lag
but hey i'm still alive damn
where is everyone else i only have the
chair with me where are the other
people's
hello austrian flag must have been the
viewers austrian flag ants
and giving them still body to me how do
you get into the game you you
type in sliver.io in your browser that's
it
but depending on where you're at you
have a certain ip that would make you
join a certain lobby and i have a
japanese ip right now
so you would have to try to get a
japanese ip
there is a slivered on io extension for
that fake kelly
and um um
what was i saying hi fake kelly you're
too small
you're too small make yourself bigger
please
and uh what was i saying oh yeah and
then after you change your vpn
i think even for unknown you're big give
me yourself
give yourself to me yeah
hello hello buddies everyone oh it's
kirby fan meeting
so happy to have you guys
my food my food [\h__\h] my food my foot
i don't think he wanted to do that i
think he bumbled himself there
oh yeah
it's getting very busy here people are
killing themselves one after one another
i wanted to turn on the vgm but i'm just
not dying
what do you do wait as long did you die
or did i just suddenly grow much much
bigger than you because you
look so small now bee it's a beak
you'd be you wanna did you just try to
kill me there did you just try
to kill me you're a little [\h__\h] for the
people who don't know i got so addicted
to sliver.io
a while ago
i was playing this game i told everyone
hi mary dude
i told everyone uh on twitter that i'm
like playing it right now
and we were playing it for like hours
and hours thank you
fake kelly they look so happy together
okay if we post go away kiana you're too
close go away
yeah we were playing um if people were
trying to find me on slaver.io i wasn't
streaming so it was a bit hard for some
people
but we were playing for hours and hours
and hours like i was playing
all through the night i had so much fun
are you are you are you challenging me
are you are you trying to fight
fake kiana almost killed me with her
greediness and food won't help me
let's go down here yeah bye oh kfb
more kfb half empty nutella
that must be someone from my friends too
fake is getting a little bit too close
to me can you could you please tell them
keep a two meter
safety distance from me please please
they all have the same colors means it's
so confusing
oh dear they're like oh my god oh oh are
you guys seeing this lag
or is the stream even lagging so that
you don't even know what's happening
i'm surprised i'm still alive with that
lag damn
i need more food guys why you guys not
mine you [\h__\h]
mine mine mine mine mine mine mine mine
my thank you
oh that's that green juice thank you
kevin mancha do you also want to
sacrifice yourself to me
perhaps so for it's for a greater
purpose
purpose of getting your phoenix empress
to number one of the leaderboard in one
hour can we do that
can we do that is snake on the menu
yes you are on the menu let me eat you
can't fit in famous wi-fi yeah this is
how the wi-fi at kfp must be huh
here you go or can i eat you oh
cutie let me eat you come on oil
i thought you were offering yourself to
me casper plastic bag tester
taster you're not supposed to eat the
plastic bags goddammit
i love these names every time i love the
names so much
oh he's challenging me as well someone
kill him
someone assassinate him where where is
that
[Music]
where is that yep where's that
where's kfb assassinated do we have an
assassinator
we should have one yeah
i'm going to stay close to him instead
in case our assassinator
does his job oh
yum yum yum nice
oh my god oh my god oh my god i thought
i was dying oh my god oh my god
kfb bj rock hello nice to meet you
i see food i must eat oh
i see food down here too but someone
else eat
yeah but we should yeah help me help me
too close
too close is he circling me
that was my fault [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
ah six eight six eight oh we had almost
a nice number it was almost six nine six
nine it was taken away from us we need
to go there again
wait wait kill me can we come i need to
turn on bdm
okay thank you what's up okay
let's go round two i was that was uh
alive quite a long hey wait kfbj ralph
is uh on the leaderboard north
congratulations uh where are you let me
eat you please
mama eat me yummy thank you
stop it you [\h__\h] that's what you get
for challenging me
you thought you could kill me
i'm quite the pro at this game by now
you know
i'm actually pretty good did you still
off if you should be hearing it what are
you talking about
don't you hear the museum it's going to
show up
oh
oh that was a painful leg
it's on okay okay are you guys vibing
them
that's my food that's my food die
die from your actions
soon you will die i know it oh
i told you
it's a freaking festival food
oh what a [\h__\h]
chat yo yo
oh i love you i'm emory cute
i don't remember i see what's going on i
see what's happening i'm getting circled
i'm getting mamans
my mama is on the leaderboard
my mama's london leaderboard every
morning you better not
be doing any any funny things you know
you better not get up to
any any funny business you know
moisture you hide the mosquito
how did you do that damn he got some
skills
how did he do that being mama in this
situation oh there's food that's a lot
of food mama
mama there's a lot of food
being mama in this situation is very
helpful because um
it protects me from lag accidents
yo together we're going big bj rock
we're gonna grow big and strong
i feel so slow is this the lack judas 5
am
good morning judas nice to have you here
i hope uh i hope you're having a good
breakfast
eating some snack poop you guys realize
that this
is snake poop right we're just all
eating each other's poop
and growing bigger through eating that
poop
you guys realize that right
i know
[Music]
the sad thing by being mamac so so much
is that i can't see much of the outside
world
hello night of kfp i can't see much
what's going on but
i would like to enjoy this um
[Music]
i would like to enjoy this feeling of
safety a little bit longer
or to grow bigger how did you get in
here go at the height
how are you getting here come bump into
me bump into me if you don't want to get
into the usual room
oh my god what happened there i saw
helen the vlog and sapphire kitten die
what what a painful thing to watch
what a painful thing to say
[Music]
that's just so painful takamari 5
ever what does that mean oh thank you
i will soon be bigger than my own mama
then then you can let me free by the way
unless you plant oh yeah but
yeah bye unless you plan to eat me once
i grow big
enough yeah bye unknown is dead no
i know no no
i i know my snake looks really happy but
i'm actually really sad about you
dying i'm sad about all of your deaths
unless
wait that looks like pooh bear i'm sad
about everyone's death unless
unless it's uh for like on purpose
for making me happy then it makes me
happy
kiana you're trapped no i don't call
this being trapped i call this being
safe
this is how i got i i um
i wanna mama you you guys when i was
playing offline when i was playing
outside
of um of a stream
with my viewers when i told them i'm
playing it oh my god that's a lot of
food
when i told them i'm playing it uh on
twitter
and i tried to to
mama some some viewers but they all
thought i was trying to kill them even
though i was
i was just trying to circle them and
then and then protect them
but they all were trying to run away
from me they thought i was going to kill
them
why would you think such a thing
why would you think that i just want to
protect you guys you know sometimes
i have this maternal feelings you know
okay it's getting a bit boring in here
because there's also no food could you
oh
nice nice timing kiara food okay perfect
timing
okay okay don't kill me don't get me
just bump into me please
uh kfb amiibo thank you for being here
thank you for joining in i was just
about to ask for some food
[Music]
i wonder why you wonder why they were
scared of me i really do wonder
there's no reason to be scared of me
okay
time to add another person into our
circle but only people we can trust okay
mama only got people in here that we can
trust if if someone is gonna let
is gonna be in here who wants to kill me
like judas don't let judas in here judas
wants to kill me okay
i dare you if you put judas in here i'm
gonna i'm gonna
i'm gonna die and you we don't want that
to happen no no no no no
we don't want that to happen know just
his name is alright oh
mama damn mama
strawberry all the food i give some
to my mama too maybe no okay
i shall eat
[Music]
mama so strong high motion what up
motion
my mama is so strong
wait is mama is mama getting um is mama
getting
smaller and weaker because because mama
works so hard to make me stronger
actually she's not number four right now
is that super hacker nancy he's super
hacker nanny
[Music]
i don't think that's the real manatee
but still hey there's food out there
account name hello
i think we can trust your code name we
can we can let food and account name in
here maybe if you can
but don't don't don't be careful mama
don't kill yourself i'm going to cry if
you kill chef
hello camille hello please be careful
mama
please be careful oh yeah my lag
poof oh too late foof is gone
food is gone i keep continuing eating uh
my mama's poop
they're eating it no
no kiara getting hungry for you
kiana hungry for your elite leroy
whoa welcome welcome in the inner circle
noise he knows what how do you know who
to trust
them mama you're getting in the right
people into this club
good job okay mama i left a little bit
for you
and when you reach um that side when you
see some food you can have it
i left a little bit
you can have some food mama i'll leave
it for when you come here again next
round okay
look
josiah mama
there's some food for you here there's
some food for you
oh you gotta get better licks in here
wait
i thought i was getting scared i thought
you were going to leave me kfb mancha
are you oh and never trust
you are on my list of transgressive
people now i want you yo
did you see that mama oh my god there's
oh my god
that might be the first time i'm on the
i'm on the leaderboard
i'm on the freaking leaderboard oh my
god everyone applauded
i'm i'm number seven i'm not gonna be
number one wait okay so i feel
i think bj rock will eventually reach
number one
and then he will set my mama will
sacrifice
herself to me for the greater good and
then i will be number one oh my god this
this will be the best
sliver that i own stream ever ah this
will be history we're making history
right now
oh my god this okay i'm
i have to be 100 focused i hope lag is
not going to [\h__\h] me over
because we will never get to this point
ever again probably
yeah bye look at that lag come on
i'm down to number eight there's some
food here but it's too close to mama
body
i don't want to get too close you might
actually reach number one yeah maybe
three and three but uh number one is 40k
that's pretty yeah bye that's quite a
lot
damn wow this mama is really doing a
good job i wonder how she
or he keeps on growing even though he's
giving all the food to me
noise
damn thank you
that's a lot of food you are once again
contributing
to the this amazing purpose of making me
number one
unbelievable
number seven number seven number seven
hey
hey kfb represents kev oh god oh no yeah
okay it's really good that we have a big
circle here and big mama so that i have
a lot of freedom to move around
kill yourself now so that i don't bump
into you thank you
gosh the lag holy [\h__\h] that was scary
[\h__\h]
everyone who gets into the circle must
immediately immediately sacrifice
themselves to me so that i don't
uh kill myself on you guys
please please i'm scared
this is all or not number five
number five okay someone um if there's a
good assassinator
among us right now please go to katie
reed
connie is dead no no it's not that
number two oh my god go kill kill number
one and number two understand
understand have you received my message
try your best to find them and then kill
them
do something about it do something
thank you you know you guys you know
this is very useful japanese um
something something means
uh something something is the only thing
that wins which is basically like this
is the best
this is the yes kill man oh god she
scares me
you kill man could you please kill
number one and number two do your job
do something useful make yourself useful
getting mama to number one oh i love
this you i feel like we're all like
all like connected in our goal today
we all have the same goal kiana's wife's
girlfriend you will die i will kill you
i i like this
i like this this is oh hello welcome
please kill yourself right away
immediately before the lag kills me
bump into me now now now now and you
have to yell
league roy jenkins thank you
thank you what about you what about you
click
click quick quick
what about you come on
now do it what are you waiting for
what are you waiting for you want me to
circle you
thank you
um
[Music]
me
oh
will give herself to me you think she
would do such a thing
will she sacrifice herself to me oh oh
i'm scared
oh i'm scared oh oh no is trying to
circle me what the [\h__\h] is going on
what the [\h__\h] is going on
i'll come back to you keep that food
keep that food don't eat it
i'll find you where was mama where where
were we yeah
my momma wait for me
[Music]
yeah by the lag oh no the lie where is
mama
where that where was i was i like in the
middle where was i
doko mama mama no
[\h__\h] you
zamamiro zamam
i'm gonna go to the middle maybe mama is
here
where is mama where is mama
oh thank you i will do my best to find
my mom
no go away where is mama
do someone know where mama is
[Music]
mama stay alive i'm gonna find you mama
oh
mama where is mama this top left really
really really mama's top left
takamoni otp have you seen my mama can
you lead me to my mom you're getting too
close i wanna
go
not
thank you thank you where's
where's mama mama
mama don't die mama be careful mama
top left really really okay
thank you guys thank you
[Music]
oh you can have that i don't care i need
to go to mama
mama mama it's a long way to reach mama
finding mama finding oh
what was mama's color again mama was
like uh
definitely not green mama was i think i
would recognize mama if i see mama
something like red like right because
the name is red
mama yeah mama
sammy
i'm almost at the top left is she really
around here
[Music]
someone just oh i don't know if you
wanted to do that but
i can't find her i can't
find her hello
have you oh have you seen my mama
[Music]
wait i'm getting some food
the moment i found there no
oh yeah but there's a big big one that's
not my mama phoenix food
phoenix food can my husband this person
is like circling me
where is the opening
oh my the leg is is uh getting really
bad oh no
oh my god
go away big boy
top left no i know i know i know i know
i saw i saw it in the map before
okay somewhere somewhere over there
somewhere
oh the rainbow
[Music]
is where
mom is mama's almost number one holy
[\h__\h]
someone needs to kill why why why why
okay so mama should be somewhere here
need to get a bit stronger before i go
inside mama mama left a lot of food for
me here mama mama
my mom i'm trying to find your butt
hello oh yeah
uh i'm trying to not die right now mama
okay i'm gonna do my best oh thank you
okay okay
okay pull over your file your
[Music]
mom i'm coming to you my mom coming
don't die please please just anything
don't die
don't die just keep chill chill chill up
there
just keep it easy keep it slow keep it
easy
look what i did there oh no no
i got circled [\h__\h] hell no oh please
okay
should i should i just end myself here
and see what happens because i don't
think this person wants to protect me
i don't think he wants to protect me i
think he wants to kill me
um don't worry mama this is not your
fight to fight
i will i will end myself
i guess on my own oh
maybe we're closer to mama oh not really
not really
mama stay where you are so i can find
you
mama stay where you are
you went away yeah mama almost has 30k
yeah she's in the way go away
thank you for the super chat thank you
thank you i'm so glad i can stream
normally today thank god it's working
out somewhat
well okay okay
i'm taking the speed train
to see mama
i'm on the what do you call it what's
that isn't that is that
isn't that some some lyrics to some song
i'm on the
on the something something train
or we could just say how where the hell
oh hi wayne hell
oh yeah that's not my daughter's person
boys
where am i what the [\h__\h] is going on
here too many people
i was so freaking close to mama but the
leg
killed me mama wait i'm super close to
mama
my mom are coming mama i'm coming i
swear to god i'm i'm coming i'm
not sure where you are because i should
i'm pretty close to
where i've seen you before
and i'm guessing you didn't
stop moving everyone stop just everyone
stop moving
[\h__\h] you you [\h__\h] bastard [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
i'm so far away someone kill me i want
to spawn top left someone kill me
someone kill me please i'm so far away
donkey you [\h__\h] donkey
am i ramsay gordon ramsay at
you [\h__\h] donkey kiana when speaking
to mama
i love you mama i love you yeah when
speaking to random snake you [\h__\h]
stupid donkey
help me help me
i want to go to my mama go away
or sacrifice yourself when you scare me
i don't want to go there
[\h__\h] off stupid orange snake ugly
ugly snake
[Laughter]
yeah i'm desperate to go to the top left
okay there's another cave wait there's a
there's
three kfp people at least three kfc
people
on the board right now noise good job
everyone
yeah but oh wow that was too much
you [\h__\h] bastard a [\h__\h] bastard
you [\h__\h] bastard i hate you
i hate you i hate you i hate you
i hate you will i ever reach my mom
again
damn it's really hard to get back there
and i i was there but i couldn't get
back in
musa
are you guys are you trying to eat my
ass
oh thank you food
want to give yourself to me
oh big one holy [\h__\h] wait who the [\h__\h]
is that he's huge
oh what oh
oh it's a massacre damn
oh oh thank you thank you okay that's
a lot of energy that i can use to get up
to mama
okay now just don't die mission
impossible
go up go up go up
okay
[Laughter]
raven hello raven oh god you got killed
the moment i saw you
how unlucky [\h__\h] off you
okay maybe you sacrifice yourself then
that's okay
i thought you were trying to kill me
mama i'm almost there
mama wait mama wait for me oh
okay okay okay um um
almost died almost done hello can you
lead me to mama did you see my mama
did you see my mama or didn't i love
piana if yes
and then blink twice or do
do one twirl if you've seen my mama and
you're leading me there i guess not
probably not
i'm gonna see my song
oh [\h__\h] yeah bye yeah bye
safety safety swirl safety swirl where's
mama
she must be close there's a lot of kfp
people here
okay okay okay she must be close
no no no i see her still here at 30k
she's on number two what are you saying
no no she's dead
she's somewhere here mama would never
die mama is invincible mama is a phoenix
just like me
so many people so many people so many
people okay safety swirl safety swirl
surface world mama mama i'm here
yes yes i'm gonna cry i'm so happy
hi unknown are you ready to give
yourself to me oh my god there's so much
food
mama finally finally oh
[Music]
don't kill me everyone you got you know
i have lag problems so please kill
yourself immediately
kill yourself immediately so that i
don't bump into you
[Music]
please
stay alive for so
and then long killed you who the [\h__\h]
was it tell me
tell me mama who was it that killed you
who was it i will
i will i will have sent everyone there
to kill them and do you justice
i might not be able to kill them myself
i was i was gonna
[Music]
go away she was just i dare you yeah
there's too many people
oh that was so close that was so close
oh my god
should i protect you this time or are
you still aiming for protecting me again
and then becoming number one and then
giving me your number one
mama's back but mama is smaller than me
but mama also probably takes more risks
than me and will
soon be bigger am i yeah mama already
killing people and growing stronger
mama did you see who killed you are you
gonna kill the person who killed you
yeah but
scary it's a scary world we live in
oh i'm actually really good at this game
hello
[Music]
snack snack for the snack thank you
yeah oh wait i'm on the leaderboard and
i did it
hey i should be the one protecting my
mama now
chicken question my christian life i saw
you there my friend i saw
what the [\h__\h] i'm number five guys
why am i am i okay snack can you please
move and kill yourself
to me please
everyone who's here and just chilling
you should you should sacrifice yourself
immediately immediately but like close
to my face if possible
possibly so that i can see you me not
you
thank you thank you good job good job oh
thank you
thank you bye bye
everyone
oh someone died there who was
number two what the [\h__\h] is going on
wait what
i'm getting what happened
that hurts that hurts
that hurts one more in
in eight minutes i'll start reading some
super chats
okay i'm the smaller one again i was
number two
damn i was number two
i was so proud of myself
damn it was getting
everyone was getting too close to me
[Music]
that's very painful yeah but nothing is
as painful as when your mom dies right
in front of you
while you're inside of the womb of your
mom
that's just damn
the worst thing that could ever happen
oh yeah what the [\h__\h] are you doing
what are you doing stop zooming hello
orange snake
are you the one i called ugly before i
would like to apologize
orange is a beautiful color you know
there's nothing wrong about
your looks you just scared me i was just
scared of you
oh what is it what is it what is it
[Music]
oh
isn't that wonderful isn't that lovely
when will i die we have like six minutes
left mama
then i gotta read some super chats but
if we're still alive in six minutes
maybe i'll extend it a little bit
okay thank you mama for for
coming all the way over here again to
protect me once again
you have the honor of of being my mama
again
thank you for the red super jazz thank
you for the blue super chat thank you
guys
wanna be the top of the leaderboard
again mama let's do it let's do it we
can do it
we can do it together we strong i mean i
haven't really been doing much when i'm
inside of you but
uh
i'm just i'm just happy that the stream
is stable it's stable right did it cut
off at some point
did it ever cut off or like do anything
weird
i'm sorry about who is mama the person
that i'm inside of right now
the person who's protecting me the snake
who's protecting me
i noticed something yeah it turned down
the the latency a lot so
you guys probably answered to my
questions way later than usual nope
everything's stable
awesome damn it
damn it i'm getting too too risky
mama you gotta eat some people to grow
stronger
you guys gonna be able to watch me if i
stream
at different stream times what do you
guys think are you guys gonna try
um if i stream during like european
prime time are you guys gonna give it a
try because everything is gonna change
soon
very soon
i hope you guys can still be there
because i'll miss you guys
i don't know what i would do without you
guys
i love my audience i love everyone who
is here
i don't want you guys to leave european
time is ten out of ten
yeah i think there's uh right now it's
um like noon time in europe so right now
there must be already be a few european
viewers
probably of course it fits my schedule i
try my best thank you i will try thank
you
ripca sorry guys sorry
i mean you might still be able to watch
my streams every now and then but
even even if not oh it's fine to watch
archive
you know it's totally fine
then at least you can organize
your time on your own that's totally
fine there's nothing wrong with not
being able to catch your stream's life
thank you what are you doing here again
you faker
i should i should copyright myself i
guess i am kind of copyrighted i
probably
i probably i guess i am copyrighted hey
i could i could
i could sue you fake yeah i
better be careful i could sue you
but i guess you're openly admitting if
you openly admit that you're
not the person that you you're trying to
be
can i still sue you
[Laughter]
it's fine but it's not as fun yeah
that's i i get that that's true but yeah
you gotta take what you can get
i can watch you more now yay
when you stream also during you you
evening time yeah i'll probably mostly
be streaming
um let's take german time
uh germany time between
1pm to
3 a.m
yeah here when i was here in japan
i forced myself very open and very often
to stream
right after waking up so around noon
time
um so that i can have a good streaming
time for american viewers but once i'm
in europe
um i probably won't really do that
anymore
because i don't think it will be
necessary because even if i stream at
12 a.m or something oh my god
we're at 12 p.m that is i guess um
that's a bad time for america i guess so
hey
owners hello nurse
look at all that food that i'm eating
yum yum yum yum
oh thank you for sacrificing yourself
yum yup the lag oh
no oh no i don't want to die again what
was i saying
uh oh yeah if it's if it's like uh
12 or 1 o'clock in in germany
i don't know i don't think that's a good
time for anyone
spent like maybe on the weekend for
european times but for anyone else
during a work day it's probably bad for
european times and for everyone else
american times
for everyone it's probably [\h__\h] uh could
you please kill yourself now
you're welcome i invite yourself to bump
into me
totally accidentally
[Music]
you go
it's an old morning this is my song it's
a really good morning muslim song
everyone who knows it raise your hands
i don't see your comments it's so late
they arrive so late
serenading them to death that's my job
that's my job now actually i guess
that's callie's job kind of
i will adapt to the new schedule thank
you very much i hope you don't have to
like hurt your yourself
in the process by not sleeping
[Music]
the guy who made like a lot of
animations that i retweet every
every time it's a japanese viewer who
does a lot of cute
uh whole life members animations like
really short uh gifts
so sakura manga morning music actually
um it was like a sub unit of morning
music
hello please kill yourself
please don't eat my food thank you thank
you
how do we how are we so lucky that we're
letting in people oh
who is this your tail scares me
mama please eat me you're welcome to eat
me because that was the last game thank
you
mama you're welcome to eat me okay
eat everything that's inside of you and
get to number one
you better get another one thank you
thank you thank you for playing with me
um we're gonna read some super chats for
one hour and then that's it
um it's only one more hour so you might
as well stay
because i'm gonna end the stream at
midnight and then you you will not hear
from me
for a long long time
so you better you better stay now
mina
let's go here we have a few more
super chats from that stream and then we
can
catch up on the other ones as well
that was fun yeah we have to do it again
thank you so much for
the fun time guys thank you
i really had a blast i had fun
[Music]
da
what what what what what what can't
believe
i woke up at 5am to get my name
slandered by takana secure herself it's
the best morning you ever do because i
hope you had as much fun as i did and
thank you thank you for participating
good morning maybe
you can go back to sleep in one hour
first you gotta stay for the super chat
reading
it was fun yay i hope a lot of people
got to join
it's a bit difficult because liver.io
just has a million of servers um
anyway i only have one hour so i want to
try to read as many as possible
are you gonna put up the free chat
stream yes i will um i think i'll do it
right after this and i think i'll change
the thumbnails
uh because i have uh a bunch of families
i want to use
so i'm gonna keep on changing them
probably
every now and then
[Music]
okay so let's get to the takamuri
super chats and continue where we left
off i think i
know caspy notes do you know where i
left off
what was it again i think something
would ten with uh tentacled
it's tentacled something something
what a good memory i have damn
something with tentacles what's the name
and
we were pretty much at the end of the
takamori superchats
thank you i finally met you in snake
form nice
i hope you liked it i hope you had some
fun watching
thank you thank you okay scrolling
scrolling
found it found it okay let's go that was
quick
orchestra fanboy dankeshen mabel cipher
thank you
thank you for the pinky peace that was
already at the very end thank you for
the support iraq peace to you too
not as simp just a shrimp thank you hope
hopefully
am i saying that well
thank you for the red super chat safe
travels and thanks for your excellent
access
exceptional efforts in the years past
and present
thank you glad your hard work finally
paid off and looking forward to some
cat content thank you i see i see i see
i understand
thank you so much that means a lot to me
thank you
i'm glad you're um uh
i'm glad i appreciate your support very
much thank you dice logoria
thank you i hope you will
um get some of that cat cotted i'm not
sure if i can
close enough i'm not sure if i can show
my cats or
here to you guys um
because of reasons but uh
let me just tell you they're hella cute
so
maybe i can show you like censored
pictures of them
i can show you their fluffiness fluffy
glory
in pixels
i'm new ami brought me here welcome
thanks for joining thank you for coming
just reading super chats now but enjoy
your time
thank you so much for the red super chat
thank you very generous of you
giovanni saldana looking for the top
thank you
all's well that ends well on this kaloki
and takamori season one
uh ends up with a positive note that is
true i mean the the second stream ended
on the positive note i guess
that was such a fun kind of looking with
some tears in between but lots of
positive
vibes let's go for season two what is
that
so season two is uh
accomplished season two is our at the
part where we are
um uh separated
is that it
where we have a long distance
relationship well i hope it goes well
gosh it sucks to have the comments
coming so late that's kind of confusing
i'm used to them
like being quite quick i turned down the
the latency so that we have less
problems with the
lag but damn they come in so late
the long distance yeah
yeah i mean maybe
for all we know maybe kelly will be more
open and more nice to me
now that i'm far away because she will
miss me
she's been super nice to me recently
because she was scared of me leaving
so maybe will we will see a new nicer
side of
cali
[Music]
thank you for the pinky thank you
oh wait oh sorry i gave you a kiss art
smith i'm sorry
wait i'm i mean i'm you're probably not
sorry sorry but
uh that was a mistake i i
kisses are only for red super jazz but
okay you can have it as like a like a
taste
um of what could be
it's like a like a like a tester when
you're like in
a supermarket and they got like cheese
samples or something like that or
sausage samples
and you take a little taste and then you
might
end up buying the whole thing you know
german chocolate fun glory takamori
friends or yuri
honesty and hard souls never apart
interesting
rhyme thank you
german chocolate fun the good thing is
once i'm back in australia that kind of
chocolate will be very cheap and i'll
have so much to choose from again
finally so excited for all the food
i think the first thing i want to eat
once i'm back in australia
is something called a leba cass summer
it's a snack it's like a like a sandwich
with a
really fake um
pudding don't lie i would
and it's like a really thick slice of
some
a specific type of meat
leave a quesamel maybe some german
people will write it out in the chat and
you guys can copy paste it and then
google it
it's it might not look so tasty
but it's so [\h__\h] good
[Music]
so excited for it
everyone
thank you very much never heard of that
one and i live here
what wait are you talking about you live
in australia
or in australia because if you live in
australia you must have heard of it
before that's
absolutely impossible that you didn't
hear of it before so you probably live
in australia
right yeah see the german people are
writing it out in the chat so if you if
you're
curious what the first thing is that i
want to eat look it up
it looks very matte yeah but it tastes
so good especially if you put in
um gherkins
they do they don't do that in germany
they only really do that in
australia but it's the best way to eat
it
it's like a meatloaf not really the
the texture of it is very different from
a meatloaf but i guess it's
similar and like fairy
a bread shaped sausage yeah but you cut
it in slices and you put it in between
bread
disgusting shut up
yeah it's like a loaf of like mixed um
meats cheesy no not not necessarily
there's not always cheese inside but
there's like variations where there's
cheese inside anyway
no time for got no time for for our
tangents
unfortunately tacoma is such a cute ship
you two are the best
thank you slurpee thank you i'm glad you
you like our our thing i'm glad you like
takamooni
thank you hoping for your support in the
future as well
recycled
[Music]
thank
early kiss because i probably won't
reach you today
1803 smash thank you soon eddie outside
flanders thank you
red super chat this was amazing lots of
wholesomeness half
strings heartstrings pulled and hyped
songs sorry i'll be right back
and hearts and hype songs to go wild on
glare sakamoto love the both of you
thank you one second
sorry i'm back it happened sometimes but
i'm surprised
i'm surprised it happened for the first
time now in this stream
actually don't worry i'm not back for
too long
i'm not gone for too long i'm also not
back for too long that is also true
[Music]
so yeah uh thank you flam the group i'm
glad you enjoyed the the song choices as
well
um i think we all always do a good job
at choosing hype songs i hope we never
run out of hype sounds unfortunately if
that happens then
we just gotta make more hype songs by
ourselves i guess
thank you flanders thank you hoping
um to be able to give you more wholesome
takamori content mama did you drink that
invisible portion again
i don't know how it happens
[Music]
i love you and the others i would like
to ask what happened when you first
turned hell alive did you need to meet
the others
um i didn't need to i met
uh i met well some people
because i was so lucky to be in japan
but
i think i think probably if it wasn't
for
you know what but we would have probably
all
maybe been able to already meet each
other
by now maybe that would have happened
but yeah
unfortunately i know we i didn't meet
anyone but kelly in my generation
but i hope i will meet them this year
that would be so amazing we're all
looking forward to such
a possibility um they're all already
fantasizing about what we would do
if we can finally be all five together
in one place
[Music]
right thank you for watching
how is that your name correct right
r-y-e
latino furiously thank you soon
um
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
thank you mwah kfb thank you for your
support
your generous donation it means a lot to
me thank you so much
i appreciate it
zero two loves lollipop thank you soon
thank you thank you glory to taka morty
thank you evie and voodoo sayo
okay okay thank you
thank you
is the stuff of legends shipping aside
you and kelly are so precious together
and your bond is amazing
you can tell how close you two are
looking forward to reunion
streams in the future now love you too
so much thank you
thank you so much i'm glad to hear that
i will miss her i will miss her very
much
reunion stream will be very emotional i
think um
thank you or not i'm not really the
reunion stream but probably the reunion
itself
that would be emotional oh but for now
for now i gotta say goodbye
so no senor say goodbye to the end i'm
not sorry but
i want to see you again sometime song in
my heart
a world world over memory falling on
your mind wouldn't
[Music]
thank you for pinky
this concert was a blessing part one
started super fun the two of you rocked
it and you hit the nail on the head with
your song here
thank you i did didn't i part two
so many goofy moments but hinatorian
life again really hit hard you killed
the anchor
thank you thank you i was i was getting
worried about the anchor
for choosing uh
because i didn't practice it i didn't
think we would do that
um but it went
better than expected even though i
haven't tried it for a long long time
thank you traverti thank you
[Music]
glory to takamori glory to takamoti
from a loyal cave beat kiara i wish you
safe
travels and you moved back to australia
australia
and gladial were able to do this off
collab takamoni concert before leaving
looking forward to future trips yes i
was
glad to do that too because after
leaving
i don't think it really will be possible
to do like a cuddle get together kind of
like a collab it only really works well
when you're actually in the same space
so yeah that's one thing
ticked off of my bucket list thankfully
flynn i hope you enjoyed it thank you
for the generous donation
thank you also thank you for your
loyalty
i appreciate that loyalty is um
a very very much appreciated treat
thank you ttm wait flynn did i give you
a kiss though
[Music]
we have done it we have completed
the super chats of that
[Music]
and we did it very the mario kart super
jets
we didn't did we
so i guess mario kart is next
if i'm quick then i might be able to get
those done too
we didn't okay
next up mario kart super jets thank you
everyone who supported the taco morning
stream and the ordinances stream
i really really appreciate it as i said
before the the kanoka streams actually
there's a
quite some work quite some time and
effort
put into them behind the scenes to
practice all the songs and
um to uh splits the the lyrics and all
that so
thank you for the support guys oh i
appreciate it
thank you please
the tail in the future by the way this
is my first project thank you
i'm not really planning on it but i
guess never say no
not really planning on it for anytime
soon though it's not really like the
graphics so it's not really my style and
for me the graphics decide a lot i know
it's a great game blah blah blah
everyone loves it
but um graphic wise
and atmosphere-wise it's not exactly
what i'm looking for
colonel it is a fact that colonel
sanders
unlike me was a fraud he was never a
colonel
in the army he was a mule tender hashtag
mule tender sanders
colonel kotori what are you what are you
getting so mad about because you had to
change your name
oh little booby
jasper
huh so that's what happened i thought
casper ate it all
all on his own but it was jasper giving
it to casper
master
do those dump wraps i normally do i want
to say something i don't have to say
enough i'm really
blessed to be a part of this community
of yours oh
i want to thank you for all of this i
hope you get some
much-needed rest in between all this
travel preparation
now i want to close out with two words i
always say to the kf bros to wish them
luck and safety
real safe thank you hubble
i'm glad you're part of a loving
community and that everyone gets along
so well
thank you thank you
so much
[Music]
um
she was put into a deep slumber by a
certain garlic which who pranked the
wrong onion
now she waits for her princess callie to
wake her up with a tender kiss
oh
i see
hi i want to let you know that you were
in my dream yesterday i dreamt i was
hearing the kia maiden call so i woke up
thinking i was late for your stream
it ended up being my carbon monoxide
detector
what does that what does that mean
something leaked what leaked what
what what does that mean exactly thanks
for the safe dream guardian you're
welcome oh my god that could have ended
badly i suppose
damn by the way everyone who's like
donating in currencies that are not
like euros us dollars yen etc like
the ones that i can recognize well um
you're welcome to add to your text
what color your super chat has because
when i read the super chats i don't see
the color and i feel like i'm probably
missing um the fact that a bunch of
these are red ones
because i don't recognize the currency
and i don't see a color it's a gas leak
oh [\h__\h]
damn what that
could have ended really badly wow
well i'm i'm very happy it was okay oh
my god please be careful how does that
happen
how does that happen
oh my god
damn i'm glad you're alive oh my god
oh my god please be careful
be
um
it kind of just just happened like
randomly though does it just happen
randomly
if i
when is the actual king cover uh not
really planning on it
um i feel like so many people have done
it so it's i might sing it in a kala
okay though
[Music]
is
yeah kind of overused yeah i really like
the
elena's cover though because it was like
a new version
that was pretty dope um
[Music]
city thank you looking for the top
donkey
sorry guys we're not reading many
messages all of these are like pretty
small super chats and uh
i'm hoping to catch up as much as
possible
sorry guys slowest cycle jump a psycho
cycle pump
slowest cycle pump thank you for a red
super chat
wow thank you no message with it so
nothing to read here but thank you for
the support really
thank you i appreciate it
[Music]
um yeah once we're
back in in like a normal streaming
environment
and no stress no time pressure once
everything is
back to normal and i settled in then
i'll be taking my time with the super
jets again okay
thank you guys for understanding
[Music]
um
you changed your name to fully german so
that i can read it easy
are you gonna keep it like that i like
it
i appreciate it you act clever because i
i i complained that part of your name is
german and part of it is english and
it's
it's confusing to read it as one name
thank you i love crabs
they look so cute albedos haven't sent a
pinky wow
might be one of the last times i've seen
live i have what wait because of the
time difference
i have watched you since your debut and
have seen you grow so much as a streamer
wait why is nice
as well as entertain and help so many
people so remember i see the end of the
sentence
remember that no matter what it's been
fun and good luck yeah you still stink
oh my god thank you
oh man i is it because of the time zone
that's sad i hope it's really just that
and not that you don't
don't want to don't want to watch me
anymore i hope it's not that
thank you for the super chat
i'll be doing i'm glad you're also just
like callie opening up more to me
thank you and found your sulfur thank
you for a red super chat from austria or
australia no no wink no no no no
i guess i'll listen to the hack playlist
while we wait oh yes everyone keep on
listening to the hack playlist
do it do it it's a very good playlist
that i created for you guys
should i link it for you guys again for
in case there's people who don't
know about it one second
there you go after the stream is over
you shall use this link
okay uh when are you gonna hear this
message anyway
you shall use this link and and watch
the hack playlist
yes okay
one million let's freaking go we reached
500k let's go one million
thank you guys for the support
okay i'll put it there again and again
copy it and keep it save it favorite it
and open it every day
mr cat big sun kitchen
oh let's see i i love this message from
mr casbix
chat she might not be oversleeping she's
been extremely busy as of late let's try
to be respectful okay
see i did oversleep because of my alarm
not going off
but i like how you think like that
because it could have really been that
thank you guys biggs thank you
hi team thank you for a red super chat
wow
no no no text with it
why not why not why not
tai chi say something i'm giving
up on you thank you for your support
though tai chi
yo were we so kind and so generous to me
thank you
thank you so much
f-o-d-r also was a red super chat
everyone is saying hold the line but
what i really want to hold is your hand
chat oh
loot you want to hold them
the chat's hand that's cute i mean you
guys are welcome to hold each other's
hands that's just pretty cute i support
that
thank you
only two in the playlist now yeah yeah
yeah
more efficiency
oh although i say that the
the teasing about oversleeping didn't
really
um i didn't really care about it it was
funny
it was just later on it was um the
technical difficulties additionally to
everything and me being already super
stressed that's what got me but being
teased because i overslept that was
funny
that was absolutely no problem i would
have i would have even
not minded at all if fubuki senpai would
have done like a stream like
where she waited for me to wake up
and that i would have had absolutely no
no problem with i have humor guys
you might not realize but i have
humor i have some sense for humor
at least take me to dinner first fogr oh
they're flirting with each other with
red super chats damn it
damn it mwah
do you even need my case do you even
want it or do you want a f-o's kiss
goddammit
thank you though thank you for the
support thank you for the donation i
appreciate it
[Music]
is there a possibility that the time got
mixed up i like that some people have
had some doubts there that i actually
overslept to some people
some people gave me the benefit of the
doubt and i appreciate that
looking for the top thank you in games
smart stunkish
and brian hits no thank you justinian's
thank you speaker
elvis thank you so
oh i liked this one i like this one a
phoenix
a phoenix is never late nor are they
early
they arrive precisely when they mean to
that's what i'm talking about that's
some that's some lord of the rings
wisdom right there
thank you vanilla except me that was
oh nice that was exactly when i wanted
to arrive
lonnie thank you sir or vanilla did i
give you a kiss though
thank you for that thank you for the
reference i like it i appreciate that
reference
full of a took
here is something from bamboozling we're
crawling us with you can cover
oh you liked it i actually i also don't
mind when people regrow me
i actually i don't mind it at all
because i like the song i don't get mad
or so when people regrow me
it was a blessing and made me say out
loud hello transition my old friend i've
come to talk to you again because of
because a vision softly creeping i
expect nothing less
you got dress issues jd i feel like you
would be one of those people who also
enjoy the song
you should be happy that i bamboozled
you
thank you though i mean you're sending a
red super jet kind of implies that you
liked it
thank you thank you
[Music]
oh
mum
[Music]
wow
[Laughter]
my lips
well that's uh the most kisses someone
has ever gotten for one red super chat
hope you're happy gd
kiss roll you got kiss rolled
you got over robe of kisses
ah
to realize what you were doing what come
on
i guess you haven't listened to the rick
roll often enough i guess you need a
little trip to the usual room and i'll
play
recruit an endless loop for you
you're welcome here's your ticket
here's your ticket alex murphy thank you
jackpot thank you latino linkedin
[Music]
elvis thank you for another recipe
is this casper's cable chewing revenge
since you took away his valentine's
jokes
uh yeah we did have some some issues
right um
i didn't really take them away she got
like so much of
it he got more than enough he
he got he brought they probably have
some in store and like they probably
stored something
up there in the ceiling of that
chocolate
thank you and thank you for the support
thank you so much
very generous of you thank you
[Music]
thank you jen hope you hope you enjoyed
the mario kart stream even though it was
a lot of stuff
jackpot thank you looking for the top
language on men's tank stream general
pickled in the kitchen jackpot thank you
skydankishan forest oh another red one
dice logaria
never gonna give me up unless it's been
an hour
why why are the people in the super
chats here singing
rickroll
to account name you're using your sub
account again what happened please don't
punish the other usual room inhabitants
for someone else's ignorance
i don't see how that is punishment
though
how is that punishment it's isn't that
fun
to have some music going on
and the best song of history even
i don't know why you guys are
complaining
was that was there the people in the
super chats rick rolling was that before
i actually woke up but wasn't
after i woke up
i think this is like before i woke up
guys logaria thank you for participating
with the red super chat in the indoor
in the uh rickroll superchats
you did a big part of it thank you
again you sure
will kia has top super chat stream be
one where she's completely upset
oh that one definitely wasn't the top
one
but thank you for the support anyway
thank you so much
again so generous
thank you and another one oh my god
broke say something heartfelt about safe
travels
woke more bizarre rick rocky out of
content
thank you are you broke now or are you
broke
i think you awoke because you sent those
requires
[Applause]
thank you i don't know how i deserve all
of that damn
thank you very much thank you i hope you
buy yourself something nice too though
some
some some good food in a five-star
restaurant or a new gucci bag i don't
know
thank you i hope you give yourself
something nice
you're being too kind to me thank you
thank you very much um
hey tim just wanted to let you know that
we all understand how stressed you are
right now and not to worry about the
stream thank you for even trying to
stream while so close to
moving thank you thank you i appreciate
that the sentiment thank you
it really was very stressful and uh i'm
very busy
very very busy um actually after the
stream is
over i should probably uh do a little
backup of my data
uh because this is probably the last
time i'm using this pc
for now yeah
sent a wordless textless super chat
red super chat thank you
thank you
thank you sorry for being late alex
i deeply apologize but you seem to
support it
if you read super chat thank you very
much
[Music]
oatmeal cookies
don't stress yourself about trying to
make your stream happen please don't
stress yourself out boss
so sweet everyone thank you
brian hitch no duncan
what the [\h__\h] another one
oh my god eventually you'll probably
also have a second account
dice lugoria you'll have a second
account soon
you'll be one of those uh in the in the
second account
gang
never gonna give you up but for real
don't stress it's a crazy time and we
all know your work ethic
thank you i'm not sure i feel like my
work ethic has
definitely changed a lot ever since i
joined hello live
because because whole life gives me so
much
back for what i'm doing like if i put
some work and some effort into it
i see really that it's worth it and i've
never had that
so intensely ever before
so it's really fun it's fun to put a lot
of effort into it and that's why i enjoy
like
even though when i'm stressed and in the
middle of moving i enjoy
streaming for you guys and putting out
content for you guys
yes yes so thank you guys logaria
thank you for your support very very
very much
another red super chat what the [\h__\h] is
happening
holy [\h__\h] i'm surprised you're not
already using a second account
let's go no stress stream kiara
what's going on that's like
at least 500 now oh my god
[Music]
thank you please know that this is not
necessary okay
i appreciate the support very much but
it's so not necessary
thank you though dear lord
wow wow wow i feel i feel the love
definitely thank you
oh my god is it ever stopping i hope
that was the last one
i'm worried about you
[Music]
wow thank you
don't know what to say it's been so many
accept our love mama i accept it i
accept it i hereby accept you love
everyone damn
[Music]
i have a beer on me chiara i don't i
don't i really don't like beer i don't
really like any alcohol
what a chat i don't i'm sorry i'm one of
those boring people who don't drink any
alcohol at all
but i i'll have an iced tea on you if
that's okay thank you
tilap67 thank you for red super chat
feel free to skip this an actual super
chat reading no why would i do that
just wanted to say how it before i just
wanted to say it before you really got
started
chat teases but don't feel too stressed
about it
ah we were just having fun ultimately
that's
what's most important is your happiness
and sanity we're
don't worry don't worry i i i get your
um
your humor i like it i thought it was
really fun
it was freaking funny i was embarrassed
but it was funny
very funny i don't mind it at all
really don't worry do you love thank you
though thank you for your worries
you guys are so kind to me always hey
you're so sweet every one of you thank
you
[Music]
heck yeah don't stress about it skip
super chat reading if you need to we are
just having fun and just teasing you but
we really love
but we really love ten ten ten
take it easy are you trying to say we
really love you and you
you didn't you were too shy to write you
at the end
love you too thank you thank you don't
worry
that um didn't really bother me at all
really thank you i appreciate the
concern
um
[Music]
we will protect you she's coming but
don't worry we will hold
her back as long as we can just get out
of here before it's too late
who came
she
who is this red super chat talking about
i'm worried he's been abducted who had
who who has they been abducted by i
don't know
does someone know does someone know
what happened there
he's referring to you i don't think so
because he says yeah we will protect you
she's coming blah blah
i hope he can come back and and tell me
about it
[Music]
i'm very worried about him
maybe maybe there would be some context
with the stream
who could it be
thank you for the super chat though i
hope you got out of there
hope you get out of there safely and
then let me know who you were talking
about
ace crown dance
[Music]
coming to try to eat them but we can't
let her get you
oh yes it is indeed about hatchimal
i understand
thank you for warning me
[Music]
thank you thank you don't worry i can
protect myself
i have a sword in the shield if you
haven't forgotten
and i even got some drumsticks so if
she's hungry i'll just throw those at
her
she'll probably be distracted for a
while if i throw those dose at her
she'll be like oh she'll catch it she'll
jump and she'll catch it with her mouth
don't worry i think i think i can
protect myself or
should also i mean we're strong her life
myth is hella strong
she'll never be able to get ina or
callie
yeah she won't win a fight against those
thanks for beating my roommate hopefully
next time i can race against you what
i beat your roommate in a race noise i'm
proud of myself
thank you for the super chat account
name
arigato
well amy could always travel back in
time i guess to
undo each step that wasn't bad and kuda
i mean she has a trident
does she know how to use her trident
that is the question
i've never seen her using it
thank you outcast next time hopefully
yeah hopefully you get into my race i
mean
if you stay part of the kfp
crew for long enough there will still be
many many many many many many mario kart
streams
so eventually i'm sure you can make it
in
i wish you the best i hope you can make
it
question about nine thousand thank you
james thank you so much
am i done soon no i'm not
no i'm not at all okay
last super chat this pinky from donald
ruby
irvy duncan thank you
there are over 8 000 of us here right
now coordination on this scale with a
single brain cell shared between us
and as likely as the managers at my
store become intelligent
impossible also did you know that your
wife is a shot
you really wanted an answer to a
question didn't you i saw you asking
that before
i guess i know like i wouldn't say she's
a she's a shotakon
i just know she likes like smaller
size people
i don't think i wouldn't say
straight up that she you know is into
that stuff
i wouldn't be that quick to to say that
but yeah thank you for the pinky
thank you thank you
okay so donald irvi that's where we're
stopping we will continue hopefully
sometime soon
thank you everyone for watching and
[Music]
see you
soon
[Music]
and i'll see you guys i'll make a i'll
make a
um a waiting room i've never made one
before but i'll make one for you guys
so you can have a chat there until i'm
back and as i said i will
i will write a message
where i say the phoenix has landed
okay okay as soon as i'm there
i'll go into the waiting room and i'll
write the phoenix atlanta
and everyone will be like oh my god oh
my god
okay okay thank you for watching
everyone
thank you thank you ryan
thanks guys uh donald irvi is where we
stopping okay remember that for next
time
thank you thank you he stole my balloons
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
thank you travertine thank you
thanks dominic thanks bye rick bye bye
[Music]
guys
um
[Music]
apparently free is a lucky number in
japan
thank you
[Music]