foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
oops
forgets the music no music no music no
music
yeah sorry but music now now music yeah
no game music
yeah
hello everybody sorry for the wait
um I
started I I plan to stream on 4 30 but
um we were doing it kind of
you know you couldn't you couldn't
because maybe somebody thought it starts
at 5 P.M
okay okay
[Music]
introduction yeah my name is I
I I belong to horror live secondary
generation nice to meet you
[Music]
well you know who I am maybe you don't
need my introduction uh Canada's uh yeah
I came to Subaru senpai's home yeah
[Music]
and right now I am sitting on a chair
yeah
it's not like it's it's more like a a
stool
yeah
okay yeah yeah it's a stool kinda
finally I got a chance
[Laughter]
it's better than the trash can
no I cannot forget I cannot forget
because when I uh went into the room I
saw the same trash can is it the same
remember two years ago yeah two years
old I think even more even more two
years some months really
um
I came to Savannah's Place
why are you remembering now not
immobility
yeah yeah yeah yeah why now
yes that's what I'm saying
but yeah I broke it right I sat on it
and I broke it but now is that the same
I think
yeah every glue glue no glue um
so now you still use the you still use
it oh oh well done I would say I didn't
break it because now it's I mean it's
fixed but today oh no problem
no because he says yeah dude sturdy
sturdy
again
I don't think it will break what I'm
sitting on now it's a sturdy piano stool
and the same oh yes
it's too hot and then somebody says can
I can give you a T-shirt and she gives
me this t-shirt
yeah but it's it's like washed like a
million times
you can barely see the colors they're
like really really excited
you don't sleep
but I changed into the t-shirt and then
I come out of the room and I see
somebody coming out of her remove the
same t-shirt she has two and we're now
also not sitting outside
oh same t-shirts I I have oh and then
[Laughter]
oh she has four of those non-stop
t-shirts and all of them are like faded
colors like but I noticed one thing I
want to call out whoever designed uh or
checked quality checked the T-shirt
when I looked at the back of someone
uh uh you know I was this is the first
time I saw the T-shirt so I looked on
her back and it said you know all the
names uh that performed at the concerts
[Music]
and then at some point some names well
actually I see I see one two three four
five six
and
um
uh ticklish ticklish I see at least six
grammar mistakes on those names
when I mean when I say grammar mistakes
it's not so bad I mean like the
capitalization of the names some of them
have the first letter capitalized and
some of them don't and I'm like oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
nobody nobody nobody
demo
[Music]
I got home foreign
[Laughter]
how long is this ago three three years
three maybe three years ago oh I think
nowadays now they would not make a
mistake like this is
she's leaving the room and bringing
something did she see some similar
mistake recently
it is
[Laughter]
maybe there's something I don't know
about I was gonna say you know it's been
for years back then we didn't maybe have
so many English speaking staff but now
we do
[Music]
come on
beyond the stages
yeah
one years ago
oh my God
a Second Officer second down second oh
oh it's still packaged she brought the
t-shirt from the second first
oh so we have I didn't put it on
them
[Music]
talking
okay
oh they fixed it oh oh good oh Logan
oh yeah
okay okay
[Music]
before we start one more thing
and
is
[Music]
close eyes and give me your hands
wait little scary no no small scary
I made it I made it yeah I made it I
don't beat the knot okay
[Music]
everything
it is
maybe three months ago
yeah it take it takes a lot of time
[Music]
can you sing
yeah
[Music]
when I was children
one or two times two times oh yeah yeah
I think it's mostly for children
but I made it on stream
s
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
okay okay so now
these loud ass birds are gonna play a
game yeah
yeah
not very noisy collaboration
I thought it's perfect perfect
because you have to
scream oh oh you want you have to scream
[Music]
[Applause]
I finally I go to Corporation
sound isolation room yes
let's destroy off-road oh turn left so
um one goes right one goes left you know
one one person goes right okay so we
have together teamwork okay teamwork
game wow
foreign
[Music]
okay yeah we actually I tried to do it
with sound but it doesn't recognize our
voices so we're gonna just scream while
we're pushing it after all and they're
massively excited
[Music]
okay okay
go go go go go
yeah
no game sound
right
okay okay
find out ah we will not have a voice
left afterwards can you yeah can you
hear yeah okay okay let's go
okay
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
okay first try hey
[Applause]
foreign
fast travel to unlock streets using the
Metro menu again don't need no no no no
okay each Street unlocked contains more
levels like this one
fish bucket fish bucket
okay let's go fish pocket
no no no no no no
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
I'm so bad oh oh
[Music]
the angels are waiting for us
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
I live in a state yeah but it took it
okay okay we can do this believe okay
oh yeah okay
okay we turn around okay
oh and somebody said if I like oh yeah
Lobster
yes
Roberts that I like but
spider like
[\h__\h]
crab no not crap
oh hi
okay yeah
[Applause]
so your script
I like Utah Amita
[Music]
um
so we don't eat tongue overseas but it's
okay it's edible
um
[Music]
foreign
is very popular right but it's probably
better that overseas doesn't know about
it because it will get more expensive in
Japan
[Music]
let's go
I love unagine
[Music]
but oh dude that is more better gold
yeah
you can have all my gluten
thank you
second hand shop
oh
no
I'm just doing it's so technical
technology
breathing yeah all the problems
[Music]
okay
okay go
[Music]
okay yeah yeah what's next more fire
okay
maybe uh red red carpet good red cup
yeah
okay yeah
[Applause]
no okay
she got nothing together go go
no no no no no no no no no no no no
let's go never never give up never give
up
go just go back a little bit and then
turn and then let's go
okay okay
where
oh eggs okay okay
[Music]
I
yeah
my job my job this is okay
[Applause]
don't stop the stories
[Music]
I feel like right now we're having even
though I'm only staying for a short time
we have
we have a pajama party because we were
the same teachers she's
open her bottle even though it's already
open because she she kind of hurt her
left shoulder yeah left my left shoulder
is broken
um
I I I swear I hear nothing wrong no
because last time I met Subaru on New
Year's Eve
she was in pain too because
uh you said heart yeah
she said her heart hurts you the whole
day she was like I'm gonna die I'm gonna
die
all of them
yeah but now I meet you again and now
shoulder down
next door
no storage
foreign
[Music]
were trying and I was just taking a
picture and sending it I was reporting
report reporting Tiara yeah but but we
didn't get a single one shots
no I I don't know do you
no no
I want to get to myself yeah oh go get
go go maybe here
no and what the [\h__\h]
no crane game no crying game don't catch
a game catch a game
you forget her I think is
Japanese only Japanese maybe yeah oh
it's like a disco arcade this disco
disco
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
God okay okay
by the way when you go to Arcade what's
your favorite game favorite my favorite
socket is
oh oh oh oh oh
very very tired oh my favorite favorite
[Applause]
this is hand okay
but I'm so excited because
you know
um
oh nice
game yeah okay but particular number one
frequent number one yeah
no no no no no no no no no
I don't understand why okay now I
understand why because Japanese purikura
makes your eyes like big yeah and your
face so small right
you are you a job you're a dog breed
going
okay
finally finally yeah
is Japanese is too okay too much okay
for a Kai guy or overseas
eyes are like what monsters like a alien
yeah
for full body legs
[Music]
maybe decoration
would be cute
by the way is there no
no
ah okay drops
okay
foreign
[Music]
you are dumb
oh my God okay
[Music]
oh man why am I playing so many
stressful games let's go shopping
shopping what what are we cooking
now cooking no cooking yeah oh first
time
we need beans okay okay
sorry
[Music]
let me go back okay
[Applause]
thank you
only one headset okay okay let's go this
time
and yeah
um
[Music]
next okay okay go next go next
more beans
[Music]
that's right
yes
[Music]
I thought
how
oh my voice how oh my God
[Music]
's voice
please hear me
freeze here hear you here you yeah
oh
go
go figure
my throat is broken
Japanese
say your voice is like yes
they say so yeah
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
okay
foreign
piglet impression is not so good okay
[Music]
can I come too
can I come too I want to go too
[Music]
um
okay maybe not enough Stars let's see oh
no eight Stars we have five so we need
to do better I think we took a lot of
time in arcade so if we do slow and
faster
towards Mark Thomas
why laugh because
it's straight and left oh okay and
straight
do you oh no oh okay sorry
um
[Music]
hey do I go left or do I go right I go I
go left I go
you
know
[Music]
I am olive green one
okay
go
tomorrow
my job okay
about my job yes and our job is together
my job
oh yeah beautiful beautiful friend maybe
slowly okay okay okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
the symphony oh my God okay up my job
okay
we go right is
that my job okay
whoa look at them turn
oh
okay okay okay okay [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay I oh [\h__\h] myself
and that
okay
[Music]
mama mama wait only
Monster not better
it's broken
we are [\h__\h]
one more one more one more one more one
more
fighter fight we have to get at least
two stars
only two starts at least minimum okay
why are you happy
Mimi needs to go super deceptive bye
boys
that's why do you know
um the music genre
[Music]
without you okay
[Laughter]
okay
oh yeah this is a bad bad rush around
[Music]
oh okay
foreign
[Music]
okay okay
that was beautiful one more okay my job
our job our job my job
okay oh
okay straight straight
no no no
no you're scared
oh
no
oh oh
okay okay okay okay
that's where let's go
[Music]
stop stop stop stop
okay
wait
put the turn okay and
um
okay
[Music]
yeah yeah
go go
[Music]
[Applause]
no no
I mean fruit candy I don't like no
Thomas
okay she left the room she also has a
sound isolation room it's so cool I I'm
starting to want one because they look
so cool
I mean in my own streams there's times
where I scream a lot but this is this is
more than a lot yeah
let's go
I wonder what super December does for
making her throat feel better when she
doesn't like fruit candy
it's a mystery oh maybe it's maybe she
also uses that recently I've been seeing
in like almost every whole life members
uh house that they have that you know
the thing I posted on Twitter
the magical
mythical fantastic looking
weird medicine
yeah
[Music]
please play the game please how can I
play it on
what do you want from me
I don't have no damage what is that but
honey
potato
es
potato chips have
many many oil
so maybe good for throat
I think are you gonna put the potato
chips in the honey and then eat no no no
no okay no tip okay no dip this this
honey is a New Zealand honey a good
Manuka honey that looks good
[Music]
you just eat it like this yeah uh spoon
mix of Honey fried director honey whoa
whoa It's the smell is so strong yeah
whoa this honey have
um
healing yeah healing properties maybe
okay we're sharing a honey on a on
chopsticks
cool yes
[Music]
are you okay
you are strong is okay
no no no
but very soon
foreign
but it's so strong The Taste is so
strong
a bit more yeah more okay how about you
super new senpai
take the honey oh oh enjoy enjoy yeah
it's good
yeah with butter
bread butter and then honey
it's good
we eat like that in Europe
maybe breakfast some people like uh
bread honey
this is manuka honey yeah there's also
different Honeys it doesn't have to be
this one
[Music]
this honey is
expensive honey that expensive
[Music]
I mean it's not it's actually now that I
have like one one more taste
it's better yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
okay
maybe
uh one more star and then we have eight
Stars
but which one which one do we go maybe
this one again
[Music]
don't leave the shop
my throat battery good really I'm happy
no no no no no no
once one moment okay okay guys
[Music]
[Applause]
which one me okay yeah you and yeah
[Music]
uh
and see
oh
yeah
we need more stars
okay okay
let's go okay we are nice come yeah we
have to spread our wings spread wings
like birds wings
yes
that's beautiful by the way so when you
stand by hi uh no the other day yeah I
collab with Louie yeah
okay
[Laughter]
only few minutes
okay okay okay and
oh no oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] yeah
okay spread the ball believe
yep
[Applause]
only one star what the hell okay Subaru
Senpai yeah
okay
yeah yeah yeah [\h__\h] that [\h__\h]
um
is preparing a little chit chat room
sorry
oh kfp
[Music]
yeah welcome to kfv today we serve a
super special time limited edition duck
Burger yeah
[Music]
don't ask where the meat comes from I
don't know yes
[Music]
foreign
whoa
[Music]
oh make big
this big sausage
no no this is Mike oh no okay
oh
beautiful it's called comfortable I I
can see you made improvements no more
trash can as chair
ah yes
the dog is cute both ducks are cute
and sit on it Kiara For The Memories I
don't think he can handle my butt
[Music]
I know
okay let's Breathe No crash
[Applause]
I don't
look out but that's basically what we're
bringing it here for now it's for me to
cry
too crap can handle my butt we know oh
no I got a butt Improvement okay
first I try okay
[Music]
okay good good shake shake shake shake
shake
okay okay
[Music]
trash box
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
yeah
that wasn't broken
get back there
it's constituted a little longer no no
no I'm back on the piano stool
okay so by the same bye Rihanna
over two and a half years yeah you you
were my first collab Senpai and since
then a long long time we were you know
talking yeah and being friends
how did I change did I change yeah yeah
change
um the most change point is
going to be more Japanese
so
yeah
I say I think
most of um
[Music]
considerate
most considerate it compared to who I
know
or they remember
most most comparing no
no no no
temperature
is
a good point good point because uh
your view is more open ah okay okay
um
[Music]
I became like a Santa well I am a senpai
now I
[Music]
[Laughter]
recently yeah it's always dying dying
yeah
today my left to show that it's broken
but
this year my
um
I go go my goal is more healthy oh my
hair actually and more strong body how
how are you going to accomplish that
so
today just today I
say to my dance teacher
um
breathe
I want to be strong be more strong
[Music]
yeah I need to do it too I need strong
strength because my arms are like
yeah
for like 15 years or so
my left shoulder and my neck big 24 7.
same oh same t-shirts
but I go to doctor many times and I
still don't know why is
[Music]
it together
raining
but together I'm not in Japan
but quitting it's together
yes okay
okay
one more thing yeah so I wanted to say I
had a collab with Luis Empire
tonight
Subaru Senpai Andrei Senpai yeah
yeah and I asked luisan uh just no
normally if she makes an idol unit Hydro
unit I don't need it
[Music]
I asked her yeah and the first name she
said
isn't that sweet she thinks the most
important
yeah I am after I will chat through it
thank you for your choice
but then I was like
so I added one member and she had a
board member and in the end it became
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
because like in in Idol groups
um I feel like there is
you know so many girly cute types my
super Senpai is cute too but you should
show yeah and that is that stands out
and it gives more variety
um
yes
yes yes yes someone like this I think is
always a good addition for idle group
um
do you know I like Idol Master ah
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
I don't oh I'm sexy body
kfb Idol okay all right all right all
right so I'm wearing the same do people
see me more so sexy Idol even though I'm
not trying yeah
so now try that's right now try that's
right sexy sexy
[Music]
breezes okay
sexy poem I think this is a sexy poem oh
so it's about a
it's about a
um I I I feel like by wearing your
T-shirt I am inside
what what biorepatitis
[Music]
inspired
[Laughter]
yeah yeah
foreign
[Music]
we are friends
okay
yes yes
friends but but
you cannot say that what yes
who hasukashi okay after I checked the
cream
[Music]
okay I think so great what kind yes
super
present my fun from my phone I saw a pen
on her desk which has like you know
flowers inside of like a
I don't know transparent container and
it says her name
[Music]
is
but I like your sofa
[Music]
yeah yeah I need to look closer though
what you have it's interesting
I want to live
like in Japan with you yeah wow
I can't I
want to go to your house oh
and also foreign
I have cute cats cute cat how
one two two cats very very very cute who
remember
um
yes but yesterday I went to nineteen
yeah she has mushy beetles yeah
[Music]
I checked I took a photo then they like
loves beetles yeah Dennis yeah
right
oh
no I but it's a good picture yeah good
pizza fact I oh
um
[Music]
yeah it's cute right so we have one
member of Beatles and one member with a
[\h__\h] monkey [\h__\h] monkey
hahaha
King monkey
a monkey
no pets why not because I'm busy so I
want to get
say bye recently I found a YouTube
channel that maybe you will like
YouTube channel
[Music]
I think maybe this will give you
inspiration
did they show you yeah this uh
dark granny yeah dark Joy Marathon yeah
but this channel not only he brings the
duck to a marathon but he also brings it
like to Empire State building Empire
State
[Music]
have fun together it's so cute so why
don't you also get a duck yeah
foreign
[Music]
what do ducks mean nothing to you
true uh
I'm not back
it's tough secret so it's top secret but
Kira is my friend are you sure are you
sure so I secretly are you sure yeah I'm
not that
I'm a human
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no she's trying to guess like me
no ah sorry uh
what happens then if you're not a duck
but my reading it's dark
the feeling is Duck and you are not
attack but then at least you can get a
duck go get get duck yeah thank you
my left shoulder is happy
duck is cute
yeah that is cute look look your look
your background cute but
but I I am a human
trust me
but whatever you say in my head you are
duck
yeah I
I think I am duck
because many people and many members and
many Malaysia and many fans say Subaru
you are dark but
I
I maybe I'm not the one being guys right
[Music]
um
thank you
it's my dad yes
[Music]
I'm happy right I remember I remember
you remember yeah I am a humor
well then we're not done yet we haven't
finished the brainwashing
what tonight
because
[Music]
because if you are not a duck then
hurotoni is a lie
I am the first bird
please stop your Santa face
yeah I'm not back I remember okay
[Music]
thank you I finally I remember I have a
dog
somebody say I'm fine
I
okay
thank you okay
[Music]
I am happy that even though Subaru is
very busy we got to do one color ball oh
no
[Music]
me too uh
many many times sending messages
I'm so happy yeah
breathe more what's that it's okay
really yeah oh and by the way you met uh
mummy yeah
yeah how was your impression
[Music]
is good God yeah it's good god
um
these five members
g-o-d
honey oh God okay another one oh
so
much
foreign
[Music]
I'm good
I wanted I
want to meet rain maybe come again
sometime because mume met all the birds
I met all the birds
no you didn't meet Elena right yeah yeah
but but yeah
[Music]
and God
no girls only
um
[Music]
but
um
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
uh uh my point of view at my point of
view so
good sentence yeah but my English more
passion
important okay okay English I like I
love Luis English
[Music]
more clearly yeah
um
[Music]
and I go back to dance dance dance dance
practice dance practice yeah please
watch out to your shoulder
I think my shoulder has been through so
much [\h__\h] I can't get any worse
[Music]
okay yeah yeah so guys
this may have been for a while the last
stream I'm gonna be a bit busy the next
days
[Music]
yeah number two yeah two women in one
day damn
here
I don't know if that makes me happy yeah
she says that to me with a smile though
[Music]
no problem
she's a popular lady
[Music]
tell me how to become such a popular
like
women Slayer I don't know
[Music]
I I don't know
my popular
I don't know but uh I I love
here here you here friends story so
I love talking to me
[Music]
she's a good listener she says she likes
listening to other people's Chit Chat
um
[Music]
pure God you're a girl yeah pure girl
did you hear that
hear that God
no say so your heart is pure my heart is
pure yeah
no you you love you are God you are
beautiful you beautiful cute to sexy oh
yeah look at that okay well you heard it
here first guys
so no problems
[Music]
They're laughing
[Laughter]
it's the same thing same thing yeah
thank you guys please support hello Tony
maybe one day with your support we can
do something big official yeah so thank
you soon for watching and in German we
said
thank you for listening
[Music]
I'll be dancing
[Applause]
[Music]
bye
oh
my God
[Music]