[Music]
w
what
surprise hi hello hello oh oh hi oh oh
hi hello hello Madam CIA hello no well
mat it's my birthday say can can I get a
happy birthday today happy birthday
today happy birthday
today thank you for the Super Chat you
have a nice birthday hi there hi
everyone welcome
to today's
stream
uh I don't know which one which episode
It is Well episode four five six who
knows of enigmatic recollection chapter
1 the one before the finale tomorrow is
the finale today is the one before the
finale so we'll see what happens today I
am prepared I'm not prepared well I was
having some tag issues but I fixed them
I think um so hopefully that will be
okay other than that I'm not prepared I
think today we'll be spending the time
to uh do lots of
[Music]
stuff I make myself some tea to wake up
cuz I'm sleepy PL and uh let's
see I did everything else yes
PL spend time with the royal family
maybe today I'm having um green green
without anything I don't I like green
tea most of the time if I drink your tea
I switch something else but it's just
green
a what we doing in Elizabeth stream I
was checking something out and then I
was trying to fix my uh I my audio turns
out it was on her end well I think it
was on my end on and on her end I think
it was on my end
first no I'm not
sure and then it was on her end and I
was that but then I Gaslight myself into
thinking it was on my end and I kept
thinking and I was like oh what am I
going to do what what I was going to do
about this and then it turned out it
wasn't her so you know it happens it's
okay okay let's go let me start the game
[Music]
today I will have to finish my wonderful
magical gift for the
princess My Soul Gem my soul soul
possession gem please don't tell anyone
please don't tell don't tell anyone this
is this this is secret I don't think if
well fauna knows and Nissa knows you can
tell fauna and Nissa I mean yeah those
are the names I was like do they have
other names no um yeah it's a soul gem
because M my dear princess the one that
I'm
protecting I would like
to possess her
soul and uh I got I got a recipe for it
okay let me show you this way
[Music]
I got some new music for
today here's my P here's my recipe Gem
of soul soul
possession so we need all the rest of
the
ingredients
uh and then we can make the soul s of s
position so we'll see we'll see
hopefully it goes well I've already
collected most of the things with the
help of Nissa and FAA
uh but I still
need an item of your Conquest
liking I'm
in let's put this away for
[Music]
now ah okay my mic's
working do you think she's
do you think she she's probably
AFK
hello hello she's dead no no M you have
so much to live for I mean junior or
something she keeps saying cheating her
name I don't I'm not sure I mean no I
just keep forgetting her name Amnesia
and
all let's
see oh
he
hello oh
princess
princess my
princess princess
My
Princess what does that mean what was
that what was
that H that is very
[Music]
suspicious oh hello
oh byby hello hello my sweet client how
have you
been I heard you R your
case yes outside oft yeah that's good I
guess right that's why I didn't have to
pay you anything yeah you did well you
did pay me
though
no well that's what I wanted to talk to
you about
actually what what do you have to talk
to me about I thought about it for for a
while right and don't don't you think
you should support your local business
owners in these trying times of more I
have very much supported funart and look
where I have came oh yeah but I'm not
part of
funart I'm part of Cecilia Law Firm
Cecilia CCE it's the official
name Cecilia from Cece cilia from cilia
CCE oh that's pretty long should I
shorten it do you do you have a a an
office yeah I do
[Music]
actually yeah this is my office this is
your office that's my office did you
just laugh at my office it it looks like
a a big chair well it's I'm a startup
I'm a startup company I'm just starting
out you were my first client this is
your startup yeah would you like to
invest in my startup
I have invested a lot in fart and I
think I'm okay but I'm not part of
fart this is a law firm it's completely
different no
risk so far all of our clients have been
happy and all of our cases have been
100%
successful uh can you give me some
references yeah so there was one case of
a a a a a wonderful wonderful pink one
that was falsely accused of having
stolen money from fart and I defended
her and through my dedication uh to my
job and my client she was successful
with a
99.8% increase margin in her
profit maybe the success was a
coincidence but but I thought I was a
good
lawyer I'm happy you think that yeah
what what are you
doing oh nothing I'm just thinking about
my options right now don't worry about
it okay well farewell client if you ever
need help again don't threatened don't
forget to not call me can't believe I
can't believe she would do that can't
believe she would do that to can't
believe she would not just throw money
at me for no
reason Loop does not work right now
um where was I this
one there we go but we have it for the
future she's a tough
case how can I manipulate I mean how can
I make her I
mean how can I make her how can I make
her to support my
business H hello there oh Mario how are
you been
hello
niia I'm doing good yes one second
please talk
more hello hello this is the queen Mario
the king of two right now I'm little EP
and just woke up a good morning good
morning good morning okay I think it's
okay how you doing
I I uh uh Mario I have a
question go for it h do you know what
happened to uh PR the princess your
daughter no cuz I talked to her earlier
or at least I tried talking to her and
then she just like did like this really
weird encrypted stuff and phased out of
existence and she didn't answer to
me I don't know I don't recall what
happened
like I you don't
recollect what
happened the last time I saw the
princess she was just fine when was
that like about yesterday
yesterday yeah okay I wish we had a
detective who could help us figure out
this case but I did notice something a
little awkward today oh really uh yeah
like come here I just I just I just
logged in but so with logged in what
what what what do you speak about ah I
mean I mean I mean woke up woke up you
just woke up yeah yes of course yeah
yeah uh look this is a little
odd oh that is odd I saw it earlier but
it didn't register in my brain
oh that is so
weird what the heck is that oh look the
queen oh wow the Queen's so
pretty the other Queen the other Queen
Don't Worry Mario don't I will never
defect you well that's weird maybe if we
find her again we can talk to her about
it and ask her what's up maybe maybe
someone else has information that was uh
not sleeping yesterday compared to me
bleeding eyes very suspicious very
suspicious can I go can I go in here am
I not allowed
hello what is
what Mario can you open the door I
can't oh
sure oh no this
door no I cannot open this door why
not cuz that's
not I'm not part of this is there anyone
uh let's
see I don't remember who's who's in this
one
again the princess oh you made it I made
it how did you do it I know just backed
it can you open it
for God you scared
me I I guess it's a combination of using
the horse you a lock picker very
impressive you can do it oh you made it
well oh I made it I made it I made it
you made it good
job okay let's see these houses people's
houses oh a double bed how
romantic let's jump on
it I didn't I didn't take off my
shoes
e that's not very
uh that's not a beavor of now
[Music]
how how would you know I mean yes it is
oh I made it I like they we just used
the horse jump jump jump jump jump
jump why is this happening now I guess
we don't ooh a picture hi
art as you can tell from this wonderful
piece uhhuh the author the artist
had a huge dilemma at this time Darkness
fulfilled their right side left side but
the other one was filled with colors
green red complimentary as we know this
talks this speaks to the inner conflict
and inner Tomo of the artist at the
creation of this
piece furthermore you can see the little
flame in the right corner what do you
what do you think that one means Mario
what do you think what do you think it
stands for Mario I think it means that
the world is ending the world is ending
because of a small fire are you implying
and I think you are right that even the
smallest the small fire becomes big fire
smallest spark can create destruction
and take over the world yeah that's what
I think too what do you think about my
art
tour I think it's very nice and uh you
should do that in an alternative
Universe you should be an art CRI critic
critic an critic okay the costs 200 gold
coins
what you want to charge the
queen you want to support my desire to
become an art
critique
yes
[Music]
fine is my duty as a queen to
support thank you my queen thank you for
supporting your local artist gallery and
supporting education supporting life
artist after all so I got to support
them oh you an
artist no I said that I like artist oh
you like art oh jump on it jump on it no
I could never like throw I'm not really
capable of doing such things oh man feel
like oh another art piece another art
piece go for it you're not going to
charge me this time I already support
already chared one you already play okay
as we can see on this art piece by
artist
G there's a blue character on one side
and a white character on the other they
are in a stance in a battle you could
say maybe enemies however if you really
think about it this is the be the
depiction of a mirror match also known
as subconsciously copyed the person in
front of you because you are attracted
to them so we can clearly tell from this
art piece that these two are lovers or
at least the white one is in love with
the blue one uh but they also enemies so
you could call it enemies to lovers and
that's what this piece is called H this
is very suspicious
why maybe the queen was like the second
Queen
was thinking about something when she
got this art piece oh do you think she's
the blue one what who's the white one
then I don't know like who's
white
like think about it okay I'm thinking
about
it
maybe this is the conflict between me
and her
and I got it now she's in love with me
you telling me Tam B Barett is in love
with you
how how I didn't know this before oh
wait wait wait wait wait think about it
think about it it makes s wait think
about it yeah whenever you talked to her
did you feel some type of
tension actually yeah whenever you
talked to her did you feel like she
would keep talking to
you yeah yeah yeah whenever you talked
to her did you feel like she was like
teasing you some call it nagging that
she was like making fun of you in a
playful
way yeah
maybe maybe she just
wants to to to leave the king and get a
real queen with her she loves
you see I think she loves you I propose
to her
sorry should I propose to her yeah yeah
yeah you
should you should you know what I
support you Queen you know what I think
you could make it maybe you should get
her a present maybe you should ask her
what she would like as a present and
then you should give it to her and then
you should you know what I'll I'll
prepare something right away thank you
not Cecilia artist critic for your
support you finally got my memory back
also yeah I'm also wait I'm also a love
adviser ask ask me for advice oh okay
listen
so you
know today I should propose and so I
should prepare
something maybe here's what I'm going to
do mhm I'm going to build something oh
and write her a letter that's a good
idea and and then I'm going to send my
pigeon to the sky because the queen
right now is not here she's on a
vacation uh I have an idea you should
also give her some flowers in the color
of her and you pink Queen so blue and
pink some flowers yeah get her some
flowers that's my
advice I think it'll work
well um thank you then do you maybe want
to do you maybe want
to what do you maybe want
to do you want
to give me a tip for my services as
advisor
what um
well you're expensive night just like
just a small tip just a small tip of uh
coins just
65 69
[Music]
okay oh thank you very much my queen I
wish you the best of love and best of
love luck luck and love can you gather
some flowers for me oh yeah I have some
I'll give you some see you thank you
what
[Laughter]
oh what are you guys doing in our base
oh we were looking at the art I was
doing an art tour yeah we were looking
at the
art oh I see over here this one is
called you were just allowed in uh yeah
we opened the door this this one is
called enemies to
lovers what do you think how does it
make you
feel how does it make you feel what do
you think when you look at this just
can't believe you guys are inside of
our Jonathan don't you remember that I'm
a honorary member of the blue Cerulean
Guild have you already forgot ially own
every land so did you forget that is
true why are you so against me being
here loyalty
what towards the queen who is our Queen
Tam
gamber
what that's not even her
name excuse me I do actually not
remember the name what's her name again
excuse me can can you explain now what
happened I have amnesia Jonathan what's
her name again Tam I want your I want my
money back Tam Gander no you are the
queen of Evergreen we've talked about
this no the best is Evergreen
yes I want my money back and I uh you're
not my anymore oh I really got to go a
client is calling me oh no oh excuse me
oh man I have to go oh excuse me going
to get out of here explain explain I
have to I have to
go oh I really have to I don't
understand why Jonathan is so um
so uh what is it called
um why is they standing like
this they're so cute I want to fight
those STS but I can't do anything
a will you leave us when you're done yes
we got to leave the world a better place
for the Next
Generation yeah pricky with you why is
she so pricky what what have I ever done
to her gu um vo is in my head what is
what is the official name of the Queen
Tam
Tam I've never met how am I supposed to
know Tam Gander Tam Gander that's what I
[Music]
said oh I have to get flowers for Mario
I did Pro I did say
wood
flowers blue
and
pink no that's purple that's not pink
let me see do we have pink
flowers oh Cherry supping H I guess
that's kind of like a
flower I'll give her all three so she
can
pick Tam tender Tam gander
Mario Queen
Mario Queen Mario anything while I'm
free I can help I can assist Queen thank
you hello fiery
one wait I have an E I have an echoey
voice in my her name is Shakira and I
don't trust you anymore get out brought
you the
flowers get out I don't want the flowers
I brought you the flowers I'm going to
destroy your bed anyway you know part of
the kingdom anymore but
why just betrayed me no okay come come
here come here real quick I don't trust
you I'm sorry wait Mario
Mario Queen Mario don't you remember a
ploy that we're going to put princess B
on the on the throne and then you'll be
you'll be leading and you'll be the
queen of the kingdom it doesn't make
sense it does make sense just because I
believe you're the queen doesn't mean
everyone else believes you the queen we
have to make them understand but it's
been hard and they don't they don't
believe us so we have to force them I
thought I had at least one friend here I
have no one I'm so alone but I am with
you okay I can do
myself do you fire me is this what's
happening here even though I support you
and I support your support me I support
your claim to the betray in front of
everyone no it's I'm I'm lying it's plot
Mario it's a plot I'm lying to them
Mario I'm it's a
plot what is a plot
wait see remember all the fun we had
like just now when we were laughing
remember the artist art that we did uh
what's a plot a plot is like a
scheme well but it's okay then it's it's
up to it I'm just very sad right now I
cannot think okay well if you must
destroy my bed and fire me I understand
Queen Mario I will never forget you yeah
thank you for everything you've done you
forget me no I will never forget
you H things are falling apart I think
guys okay well
about how about um careful careful
careful
careful why must you betray me every day
again and again
it's what's going on what are you doing
in
funart what do you mean what am I doing
I'm along here this is her what are you
doing in funart I do not belong here I
am I apologize I was I'm I'm I got lost
get out of here you Heen I got lost but
I cannot leave what made you think it
was okay to step in
here I I was looking for
do you want to buy
something um I was just checking what
you guys have in
stock oh don't open the door until she
buy something do you want do you want to
buy something fiery
one we have
flowers flowers
flowers we
have a chocolate
cake a chocolate cake yes we have many
good things here many many fishing chips
i f oh okay I don't think you understand
your she's gone she's gone all right she
she can do that you're right how did she
do that she's a witch she's a she is a
witch another wit magic in front of us
how could that have happened that insane
there are witches Among Us this town is
riddled with them yeah but we we we
aren't right we're just part of the
scalled
wand yes we part of the SC wand do you
know how to make
cake I don't know how to make a cake I
am assuming that you need actually no I
have no clue I have no clue how to make
a cake Absol like just nope not even an
idea why you sound susp even an estimate
why do you sound suspicious when you say
that no I just I just had Dr Pepper from
the that's all you just had Peppa it
just it makes me sound suspicious is all
oh you're just like a little bit wound
up yes yes yes but not wait what wound
up you said not W up I don't have a wand
I'm not a witch oh oh no I want to
confir you said why would you defend
yourself immediately as if I as if
you're why you why you acting I'm sorry
it was the way you said it and then I
got very scared that you were trying to
trap me but I wanted I just needed
confirmation that you said wound and not
wared because then you could have
trapped me I thought it was a test a
test you see but we're part of we're
part of the same side are we not we are
but I think it's still okay to you know
test people's loyalty you you never know
okay okay okay okay what what what are
you doing in
here what am I doing mhm this is where
this is where I come to think about
things oh oh that's it is the only
building scallet want has so fail point
it's where it's also where I yes yeah
hide from the weather oh it's been
raining a lot when it is sour s sour
sorrow s
sorrowful oh yes I could have open that
door if I wanted to yeah because you're
part of the scolard wand but you're so
kind that you opened it for me thank you
you're welcome this looks cool what's
this what is this mhm this is Nana 11
the newest convenience
store you built a convenience store
right now next to our communion store I
did to help it oh what's your plan sell
me on it I'm the to
invest oh you see you see all right so I
noticed that bomart was Standalone by
itself not really near anything else
that was interesting you are not likely
to have people come just for
fart you need an outlet mall with ample
parking for horses so this is just the
first step I've created another store to
attract people to partake in consumerism
wait what about the restaurant you
know the restaurant where was that again
the restaurant back there I guess it's
too far it doesn't have very good Yelp
reviews so I feel oh shoot I didn't
finish building um oh yes
oh pardon me pardon this there it's okay
I don't I'm not even looking at it I'm
not even I'm looking at the star front
it's okay I'm looking at the Starr I'm
so embarrassed complet forgot about that
create more customers by creating
healthy competition as I understand
it you could call it I don't know if
competition is even the right word it's
to draw more people to the outlet mall
they will come upon FAA Mar and go oh
and go inside and buy things then they
will go to na 11 go
whole more things and they will buy
things here interesting when is your
official
opening it is right now at this very
moment as of this moment it is completed
it is completed woo grand
opening yes you can be the first
customer okay
oh what do you want we have the finest
highest quality meat in all of the
Kingdom as well as the juiciest to Beres
[Music]
can to
you hello
hello oh my goodness there so many
customers so many customers are going to
be rich can I have a I have much money
so you're not getting anything from me
what is that is okay you have free
will this is this this is Nana 11 m 11
yes the sister store to fom Mar but they
are not related oh the sister store is
not
related H we offer the finest highest
Quality Meats as well as the juiciest of
berries we also have six berries please
you can have six
berries six berries six
berries oh what has happened this is
very inappropriate I'm so sorry oh I
don't know if a horse should be close to
food like that did did did not mean to
pull the horse do not worry the food is
all protected inside of these barrels
where nothing can contaminate them H you
have
freebies freebies yes we do offer
freebies huh I never cre F Mar in fact
nothing here costs any money everything
is
free what are you sure yes that is very
comen I like yes it is here but let me
let me give you your
berries and then I can assist you with
your
berries
1 six I don't know it's free it's free
for free it is free for free I got some
berries oh she's invisible did you want
a freebie
Berry I would love a free Berry oh you
would like a free
Berry ghost there is a Q There is a
que Mo B B do you want a freebie she's a
ghost what happened to oh ghost for you
are you a ghost oh hello there yes I've
been killed oh my God I remember the the
voice is this is wait you died yes I was
killed by Shakira what Shakira Shakira
yes in the last in the last not my
stream but her stream she stream what
you talking about you I mean yesterday
yesterday she killed me and she killed
my child I'm so sorry there was a ghost
whispering in my ear what is it that you
said this is so this is so crazy do you
want do you are you happy as a ghost are
you having a good time no I would like
to be revived we should revive her how
can we do that gathan with a G was going
to perform a ritual to help revive me so
I was on my way to see if I could find
gathan is over there he's over there all
right all right oh shoot then we shall
go pardon me I'm so sorry you had to see
that Shakira Shakira is right there too
there with
gathan I have fear okay uh it's okay
hide behind
us it seems there are people there's
people on their way hello hello
we have we have brought someone with
us
terrifying such a beautiful you have
killed me
Shakira for that you must pay my hey do
not hurt her that ghost back Donathan
she has killed me and my child what oh
does that you lady narissa Raven coft
yes you looks so much your voice does
sound familiar yes it is very familiar
we are so
transparent well I have an idea isn't
there what is your idea in lady
Shakira's memories in her dungeon is
there not a way for you to be
revived I am unsure drinking is there a
way I I am a phoenix indeed
and if you are truly not a witch I may
be able to give you one of my Phoenix
feathers to revive you and give you
another but didn't you kill
her no she did kill me but if she wants
to make this right I will accept it
oh the Phenix fles have chosen her as a
Target but I personally from my heart
and my soul want to offer her Phoenix
Feather to revive her once again how
Grand how kind of you feathers must be
very valuable yes they are all
right I must however uh go pick one out
of my hair first so oh okay oh she must
she must her plumage fly
then I shall return uh in I will try my
best it takes a little moment uh because
it's very painful to pick it out of my
hair you're so kind to do that sacrifice
I see it might take uh a few minutes
longer I will I will hurry I will hurry
away G in few more minutes yes have you
prepared the ritual I I have I have been
reading some books and scriptures from
the the larger Library we will I will
see it right that you do not have to
look like this any longer thank you
Jonathan it pains me to see you this way
it P see
way my goodness I have found something
though quite troubling that I thought I
must
report it has to do with the King and Le
Estelle as a whole what I have realized
today as I have been a ghost I have
decided that I should use it to uh
investigate Le bestel mhm and as I have
been investigating I have found that a
lot of buildings are completely empty I
have returned
empty back already are you ready to
receive the Phoenix's blessing yeah in
about uh 40 seconds uh you can start
doing it now but make it take that long
okay one you come here yes yes my name
is
Jonathan
Jonathan don't don't follow us wants to
speak to me privately yes privately I
kind of like you like this do you have
do I have a like a chicken feed really
quickly what do you mean like that she's
beautiful she deserves a body back I may
I may have one I just kind like her like
that to combine it with my you know like
the mystery
wait why you attacking me maybe I to
kill you so you can become like that as
well
H maybe but why would you murder me I
thought we
were I thought we were connected never
betrayed you it's a misunderstanding my
queen let me hand you over my Phoenix F
so that you may use it in the right
timing when you hello
jonis hi
Gorden I need to still
uh can't wait for this this uh very
excited to see
this me me as well I'm quite I'm quite
curious yeah well you must accept the
trade
request
wonderful here is the blue and turquoise
colored Phoenix Feather that will give
you another chance in life this this is
a chicken
feather blue and turquoise color
F oh I can see it from here is blue and
turquise
wow and blue and colored Phoenix Feather
wow
this gaslighting look it is white what
what no it's blue and
turquoise is going to work Jonathan the
eyes of a ghost cannot properly perceive
the Phoenix better is it because she
sees the world in a monochrome way I
shall Poss go Phoenix
power what is this it takes a few
seconds it takes a few seconds sometimes
what the you are slowly regaining your
life energy get out of there what is
wrong with you I was expecting the I was
expecting do you know what that is a
phoenix F does not so easily revive a
person it takes a few seconds have
patience this hello everybody what is
going on what is the conversation topic
are we're trying to save the ghost lady
you're trying to save the ghost yes you
not quite ready for Revival at oh yes I
wanted this as well I wanted her to be
saved so that I could use her to my
advantage what advantage what is it that
must be done to save her why did you say
it like that loser says what where the
ghost go I am not sure you cannot treat
me loser said what loser said
what know what her is
now said it before I said it
for what you need to speak no no I was
tricked I can't believe this how could
you trick me like that how could you do
that I want how they're going to bring n
back to life I wonder why the
shakuras
oops
[Music]
help
help help
help so this is what all my Deeds have
brought me
[Music]
huh I feel my plans unraveling right in
front of
me how can we get them back on track I
need an ally I need an ally
help uh let's
[Music]
see doesn't trust me doesn't trust me
doesn't trust
[Music]
is it
ghost hello hello hello feathery one I'm
trapped in The Gallows since you are a
member of the Scarlet wand can you help
me oh because I am a member of the
Scarlet wand she needs my help wink wink
I will go help
her what did you I will go help you why
did you say wink
wink I had sand in my eye a that is very
dramatic from the gravel you were also
kind enough to bring me yeah remember
that wasn't that
nice that was so nice where are The
Gallows uh right behind
fart oh okie
dokie what the heck
what is this how can I be of assistance
I'm
trapped and how do I release you uh I
think you can go up and give me a
hand
help help I'm here to help have you
tried turning it off and
on
well okay let me
try take my hand and reach for the the
screen I'm trying I'm trying I'm trying
I'm trying I'm trying oh dear um can you
put chance craft me uh wait I can make
it myself one second maybe I can make
stairs maybe if I make stairs you can do
it you can do it you can do it okay you
can do it I am your emotional
support you are capable I think I'm
doing
it I think you need one more set of
stairs perhaps or maybe two or maybe
three just going to destroy this don't
want to leave anything here what if you
push the stairs back a tiny bit I made
it oh just kidding you don't need
that I made it how efficient oh thank
you so much for helping me you're
welcome I'm so glad that I was nearby
and able to assist thank you why do
you why do you why do you you know what
I feel like I can trust trust you you
can trust me you can you have been
nothing but kind nothing but supportive
of the faart of the
Scarlet I'm about to get Kinder really
you see yes you can we go to Nana 11 oh
yes my second favorite store Nana 11 yes
oh we'll change that in due time do not
fret
H oh ouchie hello hello
may I offer you a lottery ticket it is
free oh it is free the first 20 the
first 20 people who take a lottery
ticket
win what's the
price 100 coin I'm
in but it is you're in all right oh hold
on the exchange is a bit more under the
table
oh okay yes let's see hold on a second
hold on do you want me to go on to the
table or no no no no no I can hand it to
you oh okay here here you go here is
your lottery
[Music]
ticket winners will be announced in
about 2 2 hours and 15 minutes oh okay
911 Lottery 100 coin price let me just
put this uh here so I have it safe in my
hand one moment pleas
mm oh my
ticket yes I will not tell you where you
are in the number of people who have
entered is it like the first am I the
first you could be one of the first 20
but you may also not be that's part of
the Gamble you may not be one of the
first one oh that's the gamble that
makes a lot of
sense what's your name again right now
junior is it still Junior I'm I'm
accepting uh nickname
recommendations uh since your store is
called
N1 how
[Music]
about n
how
[Music]
about
m n oh wait that had a nice ring to it
it m m m
m n NAU
NAU NAU
NAU nanu
nanu n i yes how does it make you feel
it it feels so correct right wonderful
you have a name yay thank you N I have
to
say it's been really nice doing business
with you I would like to invest in your
store so if you have that open tell me
let me
know okay if we have an open position I
would be more than happy to take you in
no I meant like open as in like in the
stock market oh in the stock market oh
my hi well at this time we are not
public but okay that's okay well let me
know but oh hello
everyone greetings it seems like another
store has opened in town another store
has
opened would you like to purchase I am
selling berries the juiciest of berries
and the highest quality of meat we also
have a
lottery would you care for a ticket the
ticket is free completely free the deal
I would love to take a lottery ticket
from you if I may have one if you stock
course it is first come first sir first
20 members are the winners but I cannot
tell you where you are in the
queue oh I have a good feeling with this
so I think I will give it a try all
right I'm sending you your lottery
ticket handing it under the
table we have to it's on the down though
you see
what what what on the what on the T I
cannot no no not it's a figure it's it's
quite literal and it's quite
figurative and I see how it is oh
oh wonderful let me I think I can see it
now oh it came through under the
table oh 100 coins for
free if you win if you're one of the
first 20
people the gods are on my side today for
sure wait is this going to be tomorrow
no it's today it is in an hour and 12
minutes wonderful I shall shall I be
here in this vicinity
when that would be didn't she say 2
hours
earlier didn't she say a different time
earlier okay I need to make my cake
already I keep getting distracted
uh egg sugar
wheat and uh iron iron pot iron pot we
need to save I mean we need to give the
princess her cake I had an iron pot oh
there it is iron iron
bucket an iron bucket so I can have some
milk going to close this so no one can
get
inside should close the doors
okay some more juicy steaks would
suffice some sorry I'm so sorry what did
you say some juicy steaks will suffice
juicy steaks all righty how many do you
want perhaps about 20 20 or
10 randomly best two
states it could be I mean any anyone is
allowed to take part in them
a must I eat them all at
once let me go and find some
milk
uh cow I need a cow cow hello no uh
[Music]
ples there we go I found a cow
yay I got milk nice okay okay okay
okay very
nice and then I'm going to you need two
milk really let me hook up a recipe cake
recipe oh wait I should go to the
library because the library probably has
a recipe recie uh recipe book let's
[Music]
see I always go the wrong way I always
go I always go the wrong way every
single time I go the wrong way every
single time I every single time I go the
wrong
way okay let's see if the library has a
book on
this
no this is the right way no no it's
okay no I'm not lost I have a map I
cannot get lost I know exactly where I
have to go it's okay okay let me
[Music]
see
oo oo okay is this a is this a book oh
book cake okay let me look up a recipe
a three buckets of milk two sugar one
egg three wheat okay three buckets of
milk uh oh we might have a TR we might
have a
problem I don't have any
buckets h
does any
humble
Adventurer per chance have some
buckets I
have coin
to as
exchange then we need what did it say h
three eggs two sugar two
sugar and two sugar and one
egg one egg three flour three
milk three
milk okay let's see maybe maybe there is
iron then I could make it myself
although I don't really know how since I
haven't done any of the there's quite a
bit of iron uh three three we would need
six
okay I did ask she said we can use
everything let me see can I make an I
can I make a
bucket
oh
oh oh oh oh never mind I found some okay
we're fine okay I'm going to have to go
out again to the the best the
bestl there we go never mind never mind
cow
ow okay
one
and what
the there we go and two
perfect oh was that my princess did you
just
see did you see her princess I just saw
her
princess I saw her but then she was
gone that's
weird okay
well we'll find her again oh talking to
her oh oh
hello
hello are you
okay that's what I heard from you what
you say really that's very yeah what I'm
talking I heard from you so I was
copying you oh I'm talking can you hear
me normally now yeah I can oh that's
weird that
suspicious very suspicious very
suspicious now I'm suspicious of you no
I'm normal I was just making fun of
you the is every step I take you
disrespect me I'm not are you really a
lawyer am I really a
lawyer oh what did you say you're really
a lawyer yeah I am really a lawyer one
second let me adjust your uh
amplification please speak
again are you sure you're not a knight
no I am a knight but I was uh I did the
I took the bar exam yes two days ago and
then I became a lawyer what are you
doing the B the bar it's like a lawyer
exam sounds like something a night would
take huh
yeah that's why I did it
oopsie I'm I really am a lawyer
don't I feel like I feel like we had
such a good client lawyer relationship I
don't not understand where this mistrust
comes
from maybe I heard stuff from
who you know around what was said about
my
loyalness
uh nothing oh
oh nothing okay sometimes my ears are
strong oh oh yeah just like when you
heard me okay byebye just like when she
heard me make a
weird noises can't believe it okay okay
okay okay I have to stop getting
distracted we almost have a
cake but why Jonathan with the G why
would Jonathan with a G spout such
nonsense about me I've never done I've
never done actually I don't remember
have I done anything
against Jonathan I don't think
so no I haven't I joined the I joined
the Cerulean cop I haven't done anything
against him I don't understand the
animosity is it called animosity I think
it's called
animosity I joined the Cerulean
cup I swore my allegiancy to the
Cerulean cup I am protecting a member of
the celan cup I feel like this is a this
is I feel like this is a targeted
against me with no basis okay let me
make a cake uh let me check one more
time
one and uh two and
three and one 2
three
one
one we made a
cake
yay finally I have the cake okay I'll
keep this and then I'll put this away
for now
[Music]
I don't really need this
either uh then again a chocolate cake
seems kind of nice maybe someone likes
chocolate cake I don't really need these
berries sorry nanu I'm sorry Tick
T I got a cake helpy okay let me put
this away and let me put this away I
have enough space
now there we
go now I need a member of the Scarlet
but I don't think we have anyone I think
narissa
is would call she is doing the quest and
then I guess nanu but nanu is very
suspicious as well okay uh I'm going to
take a one minute rewind time because I
have to go fetch
my turn off my oven and then I'll be
right
back I don't think I don't think my PL I
don't think my plan is going to come to
fruition just yet but ow ow to be honest
I haven't been able to spot beu my
princess so I think that's swim lava
yeah I think they're doing the lava
dungeon I think I think they're doing I
think they're
doing I don't know my my senses are
tingling the two of them might be doing
the lava dunge
yeah let's see who else
dies we'll see okay I'll be right back I
need a
moment
okay bye-bye this way
[Music]
hello I have
returned
hello I'm
back bow oh hello n Hi how are you doing
how's your storming going it's been
going very well I had lots of customers
and I've given out a certain amount of
lottery tickets oh is it is it I wonder
how many it is if only I knew it's okay
you don't have to tell me you won't tell
me anyway you know in an hour I'm so
sorry I made a mistake I said 2 hours
but I meant 1 hour it is going to be 57
minutes from now it was an honest
mistake that's okay I I'll put on an
alarm um n would you like to oh yes I
was going to let you know since you are
valued customer and I love you that we
are now offering diamonds for sale
diamonds for sale I would like to buy
one
please one Diamond you got
it how much is it it's
free
free yay thank you for doing business
with us me yes thank you for
oh I was going to ask if you wanted to
try out the new um games that have been
addited yeah yeah I want to see the new
games Okay I I already checked out one
in the scull in our base uh should we
try that one first yes okay sure uh it's
take me away
here h
there it is oh I actually found
something on my first
try he all supposed to be free ow ow ow
oh careful in there oh I no
oopsie
hello here we
go what is the game it's this talk to
this guy SC Scarlet gate Game Keeper
gatekeeper gatekeeper scar Scarlet
gatekeeper yeah he must be a
gatekeeper let me I'll read the rules
okay mine's I any player who wishes to
participate can press the join game
button when the first player who join
presses the start game button all
players who join will automatically be
transported to the play area and
game you will see a canvas with a
pattern of color tiles on it and you
will have 3 seconds to me memorize it
then the canvas will be blanked out and
you will be given dyes use the D to
color the canvas in the exact same
pattern you'll get one point for every
correctly colored tile and a bonus for
every correctly colored full canvas the
pattern will increase one level of
difficulty for every canvas you complete
correctly if you color a tile
incorrectly you'll have to take a score
penalty and the game will skip to the
next question the difficulty will also
go down one level if 2 minutes to get as
highest score as possible I saw
something similar but I think it was
with numbers and it had a
chimpanzee in in
here not oh no not here oh I saw it on
when I was out and about the other day
oh okay nice well I've tried it once
earlier um so should we
play yes let's play do we work together
or are we against each other no we are
against each other we must uh just a
friendly game it's a friendly game oh
yes I I'm putting my competitive Spirit
Away
okay I'm ready okay I'm starting the
game are you ready I'm ready
okay where the
[Music]
Dy they will be in our hand once the
timer is
over I
see my mind's eye is
activated oh I didn't see the last one
um oh no never mind okay
shoot was it dang
[Music]
it oh my gosh she's on green oh no no I
miss how embarrassing
[Music]
ah red green yellow red green
yellow I'm losing it's over yeah no you
distracted me sry sorry
sorry I will not
speak do not speak
red
yellow it was it all
yellow oh I clicked on the wrong one
oopsie
yellow one more wait where was the last
one I don't
remember red yellow red
R it's okay keep clicking on the wrong
one maybe I need a step just
kidding it's over it was close it was
super close that was really close it's
hard because like you you kind of close
to it and then you have to like step
back and take it in and then go back
inside I know I should have stepped back
more I think I was too close to it the
entire time good game good game you want
to try again no one more one more one
more one more one more let's try
again how was I don't I have no clue
where that other green one
was did you join no clue at all did I
not yeah I did okay I'm starting the
game okay
okay may the memory strongest memory be
uh
win yes yes
[Music]
Yes
red red
yellow by was all
yellow oh wait oh shoot oh shoot I
messed up
dang
it I'm doing worse than
before dang
it this is
hard that was
yellow I want to rematch right now wait
we have to finish this one okay I want
to rematch okay okay
right is
annoying dad didn't me to for
someone get me out of here get me out of
here get me out of here there isn't even
I lost so badly there's nothing left for
me what what what what
it glitched it
glitched yeah there was nothing oh you
don't get anything anymore I see it well
now there is oh but then I pressed
[Music]
it God she's catching up I already
forgot I I I forgot which color that was
oh no I forgot which color it was oh
which color was
unfortunate very unfortunate I made I
made some mistakes but I want to do one
more okay okay let's do one more once we
get out of here I want to do one more
made mistakes
okay okay okay I'm I'm I'm overclocking
now now I'm
focused okay I'm not I feel like my
focus is
deteriorating drink more of that fizzy
drink that you talked about earlier I
already drink half of it I must save the
latter half for tomorrow okay
St
easy easy easy so
easy easy easy easiest game of our
life easy easy
was it oh
Sho red red okay no not okay not okay I
don't
remember was it no I don't remember
where the last one was red red
red red
red was it up here or here dang it it
was up there ah
it's very hun
game especially harder because of the
color difference in the
middle the
green the green pains me
so I don't
remember I don't remember I wasn't
paying
attention what I you don't like
my mistakes were
made my sensitivity was not
great it's about speed I think so much
speed
speed I was pay attention speed give me
a
[Music]
redoo should calculate some of our some
of what oh see
oh my gosh I was so
lucky uh oh I don't
remember uh don't I don't remember
either no
oh you win oh no oh I win this time oh
you won dang it I only win no this this
was the determin determining game no it
wasn't rematch rematch rematch rematch
rematch rematch rematch rematch okay now
rematch one well the first one didn't
count since I had played the game and
you hadn't and then one time I won and
then one time you won okay and now this
is the final match okay okay this is for
Real this last this one is the final one
okay okay okay okay okay I'm ready I'm
ready we don't get any money for this do
we that's okay I'm not greedy I'm not
greedy I don't need any money on my end
it says you haven't
joined maybe you have to start oh okay
okay good luck good luck nanu Good Luck
Good
Luck be the one with greater memory and
less Amnesia win I feel like we're a
disadvantage at this game to begin with
I know this my head still hurt to scam
us yeah so I'm very unsure about my
character feeling still feeling the
effects of being boned
mhm it
oops okay this is where this is where I
don't remember
I no I forgot
already I remember yellow green red
yellow oh was
[Music]
it no
shoot I don't
remember that was not paying
[Music]
attention where these
ones
[Music]
no oh [\h__\h] don't remember I don't
remember I need to go fast I wasn't
I don't oh there we
go oh my
goodness yay oh my
goodness good game good game good game
no I disagree I'm playing you want to
play again you want to play okay okay
let's play again okay okay okay okay
okay well this time we should check
hands before I think so yes shake hands
with us Shake hats Shake hats oh shake
hands yes
okay okay okay okay let's try again okay
okay okay I I did you ready up uh I am
ready
okay one more Amnesia be dabed we can do
this I done goofed a little bit
[Music]
h
I don't remember
okay oh this one
[Music]
hard what was on the wrong one I tried
do green what am I pay attention to that
one cuz I was
so CE I was so mad at myself I didn't
pay attention to the next to the next
one
yeah I
think it's too hard was my it was my it
was my my scroll wheel not
working where's my scr whe
um maybe you can use one and two instead
one two three
oh that it might just be me it's just a
me
problem that was me going too
fast that's embarrassing that's so
embarrassing I want to play alone don't
say that don't say that
don't don't say that are you ready do
you want to play
again yes
okay this is an arc we can silent silent
okay silent no distraction okay okay
okay okay I'll be quiet I I can't get
used to not
scrolling silent
[Music]
pure
concentration no oh you guys are playing
games oh hello
how do you play this game uh we shall
show you once this round is over dear
Knight the distraction why does fre
sounds like she is crying she's
distracting me she she's really going
through it she distracting me is she
okay what is going on no she's
distracting me um is she is she okay I
think she's I think she's fine yeah I
think it's just that oh I see you're
distracted her
maybe oh per CH she sounds like she's on
the verge of tears too distracted I mean
it's a very tilting game to be fair is
is a very tilting
game is she going to cry yeah maybe you
can push a little bit more I'm already
crying
out do not fret Freda your her name is
nanu by the way nanu yeah she CH she I'm
fretting I'm fretting I'm fretting I'm
fretting I'm FR I'm I'm nice to meet you
n I'm fretting so so much right now
there is too much to fret about oh the
fretting is oh goodness oh goodness oh
how I oh how I fret oh dear no do not
cry you are almost there no you so close
oh you were really close damn
it are you
okay it is nice to meet you Nano hello
it's is nice to meet you what is the
name of that who distracts me oh yes my
name is Jonathan
G hello Jonathan G thank you it's a
pleasure to meet you just Jonathan G
would you like to join us in our Battle
of wit I would love to see your your
game how do you play uh you should read
the rules just so you prepared properly
read the rules mhm
[Music]
it's 3 seconds to memorize it oh well I
will just guess let us go
okay did you join it have you all signed
up yes yes should I press Start yes I
press Start May the most iest win wait
where are hats I see messed up oh
yes greater than
[Music]
expected I am playing a a mini game
currently who are you talking to
yes I'm at the Amber Hall
Guild
[Music]
yes yes you should come
join we would be delighted to have
you I see I see H I do not remember
these
colors my HS like
this myh is like this are you doing it
humble KN I do not know are you
succeeding how are you doing I am doing
doing okay but I do forget do well yes I
also forget to very quickly I was
thinking of what she was
talking what a what a Troublesome game
it's very triggering very Troublesome
game indeed very triggering you would
say so I think so yeah is that what you
believe I
believe I see I
see why would this Guild create such a
place for pattern recognization to
become a little bit more intelligent
with time I think it's called training
your mind's
eye is that what you guys do at um such
a place yeah we always want to be on our
smartest you know we always strive to be
I understand it's glitching oh no it
didn't glitch it was me not proing what
was happening well I do have a book I
would like to donate Oops I did not mean
to place it there I was listening to her
say things if you would allow me you
have to blend it out after
this yes of course again again again
distractions there are to many
distractions what distractions were
there did you not hear the green one
what no I was just answering to her she
was babbling the entire time oh I
couldn't hear her I couldn't hear this
one we were to a far apart
talking sorry I couldn't hear I getting
another phone
call yes okay I'll try not to talk if we
next to each other this time it is a dis
okay you can talk ones no I will block
you out I'll block you out ready I don't
know I mean Jonathan is ready Jonathan I
am ready okay ready Jonathan yes I am
ready yes it is the red I'm in the
middle again building by the arena I
believe I believe that is near the
arena yes I will see you
soon I will not disappear barely
well well how was your day green one oh
so far I've only played this I got a
lottery ticket from moo uh Nana Mo and
that's about it oh oh that is it yeah I
haven't really done anything oh wait I
got a cake for the princess oh a cake
huzzah huzzah I'm sure she would be
delighted what's why did you say it like
that like what I did not say it any
which
way okay we have to we can't let her win
uh n I'm this
is I'm going to lose it what what is
this oh it's is a game we are playing a
game
game yes you should play as well Happ
I'm not sure I understand got to kill
multitasking abilities recognition game
I you too strong it seems we're playing
a pattern recognition game why are you
whispering to yourself
about what what is going what is going
on man trying to focus and talking to
myself to hyps psych psych myself
up oh I seem to have stumbled clicked on
the wrong
one yes my I my okay okay okay
no what what are you whispering to
yourself about I'm trying to psych
myself
up you are doing a splendid job at
psyching yourself up fair Knight ah I
see seem to have
fumbled dang it a shame it is a shame
shut up what is what is wrong
what I hate
you I hate
you oh goodness goodness I wasn't
talking to you I was talking to myself
because I'm so disappointed in my
performance oh I see I see well well you
should you click on this person you
speak to this person and then you press
you let him know that you would like to
join the game pardon me Jonathan G yes
pardon me I have opened a new
establishment called Nana 11 and we
offer the juiciest of of berries and the
highest quality of of of meat and we
also have a lottery it's free to enter I
would love to enter your lottery would
you like to enter the lottery first 20
people who enter win oh have I won am I
one of the first well you don't you
don't know if you've won yet oh I would
like to I highly recommend her Services
all right you I will give you a ticket
hold on I'm pulling it out of my pocket
very
profitable I am looking forward to
it here is your
ticket I also got a
ticket we all got you all have tickets
yay in only 31 minutes won't the lottery
be
pulled it will in 31 minutes wonderful
huzzah be sure be sure be sure to meet
me at the na 11 where I will announce
the winners yes I will be there with
great haste in 30 minutes will you be
here playing this game in the meantime
no I think that it's rigged
oh yes beware this game is rigged oh I
want to give it a try sometimes you
don't have the color that you think you
have and sometimes you don't scroll
enough or sometimes you scroll too much
and it is not your it is not your fault
it is the fault of the game but this
is and sometimes they I know we're not
perfect none of us are perfect it's okay
it's okay just but just be aware that
sometimes also it says that the blocks
are in one spot but and then they move
them somewhere else so it tricks you
making you think you just have really
bad
memory I see what oh there is treachery
of FO in this Guild in this gu it's not
treachery oh the human era I
mean we ar robots here no we just well
you should try one more time I will not
be entering I will be allowing um Miss
Shakira to enter so I would like to see
you guys I I will stay quiet I promise
you can you can play I don't I don't
have to you should play as well you
should play as well would to see you one
more time would you do not want to play
against lady Shakira oh I would love to
play Shakira Shakira
Shakira well I am a beginner in this
game I I I I I'm not sure yet of how to
play it but is everyone ready play with
anybody yes you shall go I'm ready ready
to be distracted and to be rigged no I'm
not rigged to experience uh other other
world other riggy what yes yes yes how
terrible maybe you should submit a
complaint or these not your guild
leaders no I will put a note and let
them know that it's out of order it
needs to be fixed yes yeah yes maybe we
should do one more try so we can like
really test if it's out of order or
what's the problem you know Buck
reporting yes you should check yes okay
whoever did the first one has to start
the game it's not me it wasn't me oh
oopsie oh okay begin
begin May the best memory
win like
so oh
easy so you have been playing this for
30 minutes green one yes yes I have been
and you would say that your memory is
quite this is fun good this is
delightful
no no
you not think it's fun but I saw it's
fun but I'm not that good I saw that you
but I saw that you had gotten the high
score oh yeah but then you beat me I did
not beat your first try or your second
try no yes oh yes I did not beat your
high score okay well then maybe I like
maybe I have good memory then maybe you
are yes maybe you do have the greatest
of memories oh thank you for pling me
like that yeah maybe I do have the
greatest memory I would like to donate
to your library okay I'll take it in a
bit this is one or this one thank you
yay what did you put in your cake today
c a strawberry on that one iberry oh for
the
princess the princess well do you think
she will take it I don't know she's been
kind of weird to be honest I tried
talking to her she has been a little St
and she did like this really weird thing
and like vanished Into Thin Air it's
been quite weird yes it has been a
little strange you do not sense that
something is different I definitely know
something's different but I don't know
what and no one's talking like told me
what's wrong and everyone's confused as
I am
apparently yes it is quite very
confusing maybe you have some
information you could share with me at
the library in a
bit yes in the library in a bit in the
fart Library I assume yeah yeah The
Great Library
yes the greatest liary of the mall that
was rigged see that was rigged that was
Rigg it was rigged it was rigged it was
rigged it press it where it was
not what a terrible do you think that is
a green one rigging it she seems to be
beating everyone no because you beat me
earlier why are you constantly against
me Jonathan what have I done to you oh I
am not I am not I was just a thought it
was a thought in my head again again
again again again
again again go again again it is
certainly rigged because I have failed
yes only you can play this time Jonathan
I'll watch by my turn again again again
again again did you enter Mr let's play
two games at once two game what other
game shall we be playing the quiet
game what oh the Qui the quiet game okay
what does the loser what does the loser
have to
do there needs to be a punishment yeah
who why does there need to be a
punishment whoever why but why why does
it need to be what win I get you're
playing in this round and then you are
not even you going to enforce a
punishment not I have to be quiet as
well okay I won't be quiet okay ready
ready ready ready are you have you
signed up Shakira I have signed up yes
ready yes I participate in the quiet
game we are going to participate in the
quiet game am I not allowed to speak I
guess we are not allowed to speak it
seems that okay namamu does not want to
speak do you hear me from here then I
will not speak do you hear her
namamu do you hear them I think we are
failing at theame oh we are failing at
the quiet game I did not mean to missu 1
two 3 2 1 2
3 3 2 1 2 3
do you
hear voice in my head
is what what hey what's six I mean
Jonathan what's 6 * 12
Jon what is what 6 *
12 well beautiful
pattern in the land of lesto we are not
taught algebra Jonathan tell me what
happened where's where what's with the
princess what no you cannot just ask
them sat in the middle of the fields oh
Jonathan I have't seen your Pearl where
is she quiet game a game
no I do not have to answer that oh okay
sorry my bad I don't I didn't I didn't
know I was stepping on a mine there
sorry uh Jonathan how did the how did
the Revival of narissa the ghost
go it went fine wait why do you sound so
sad all of a sudden it was successful it
was successful it was fine I'm the power
of my family we have revived her
Jonathan I'm sorry did I I didn't mean
to step on any toes I was seriously
asking I was just curious It's is okay I
understand you had good intentions it it
is so fine it's nothing the Revival went
well it went perfectly well okay
fantastic wonderful yes that's good I
didn't I didn't like that sadness in
your voice so I I uh uh maybe we should
change the topic uh shall shall we how
shall we changed the topic um how has
your your little statue gone for Tam
Gander oh it is going wonderfully the
the statue of the queen is going much
better oh not bad this was the new game
that for me the game has been
fixed it is no longer rigged it is no
longer rigged no longer
rigged and this was the game that
determined who had the absolute best
memory
playing this seems a little bit unfair w
we say it is not rigged when when the
when the green one is not participating
I sense a pattern oh my goodness there
may be a pattern indeed a pattern wait
we must test it one more time she may be
accidentally ringing it notp should play
again and see if the green one is the
problem oh no I have played enough you
have played you do not have to play any
longer play what about the bug report I
think the voices in my head are growing
tired oh oh I see well they have very
little stamina it seems let's play for 5
more they're quite
weak seems weak minded Shakira there is
another game at the Cerulean cup Guild
you catch chickens in a basket you may
have more fun playing that oh yes that
sounds fun
oh chickens I see chickens in the basket
oh it seems the game has begun however
oh for this one I will watch
we are playing again there there's not
been a single one that I've watched I've
had to participate in them all n n
n can you help me distract
Jonathan yes
okay okay such a simple name today did
everyone join yes Jonathan did you join
Shakira yes I did join okay I'm
staring I playing Min game in the in the
Guild you I heard of your plans I heard
of your plans and I did not want to join
any longer about to end this one but
there's another we might start
Jonathan heard of your collusion red red
red red red red red red green red yellow
blue it is yellow
blue red yellow red R yellow red blue
blue yellow it is a blue yell yellow red
bled
red 11 red green blue
red Alabama Alaska Arizona Arkansas
California Colorado
Connecticut red blue green 11 green red
two yellows two yellows to the side salt
table salt listen to Salt table salt
pepper egg garlic meat red meat red
dye
magic to
remember I will never forget you cannot
distract me banana it will still work
blue spinach and I could still do oops
iess the wrong
one
blue yellow bloody red ham bloody bloody
red ham very bloody red very
red and bloody and yellow you forgot the
red one there you the red one there over
there you forgot it you forgot the red
one you forgot the blue
one
Ladi the blue one
was there's another red check the red
check the red oh you've gotten it oh
we're helping there is a yellow there is
a red where yellow where's the where
where everything is wrong everything is
going apart you are going to lose you
are going to lose where the r one you
lose you will lose it is rigged it is
rigged it is rigged once again it is
because of the green one I believe it's
the green one the green one the green
one that is rigging it we have how
always wins how come the green one
always wins it is rigged last time
Jonathan joined it is because she is
paying them she is paying the off she is
paying this no no no no hold on hold on
let me step in here I think it's an
honest mistake I think she's doing
something unintentionally she doesn't
know what and she's just as confused as
we are and just scared we are it's true
very confused kind of strange to be
honest I wonder what's going on maybe I
should not play this game again should
we go to the chicken
game okay let's go to the chicken game
instead yes everyone should go to the
chicken game it's the ceran guild I buy
the Amber there
though oh your head you a murder
matching horses matching horses hold
hold on Whose horses are matching I will
I will I will I will will I as well how
many horses do you want she's almost
must
be she almost did
it just keep going bit long I too will
match I will match I will also match
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
do you have this polka dot this one does
not have the this is an imposter there
are no polka dots oh goodness oh
goodness wrong horse oh you thought that
get pass me still
incorrect oh there we go now oh there we
go there we go I was
try all yes yes okay all right this way
I follow we follow her I lost her I
could be lying I do not know you could
be
I'm one day I will know the map and then
nothing can stop me it's next to the
ambercoin
guild there I see blue I see blue is she
okay
no no your horse sounds very good
it's this way I found it I found it
completed his ego
please little on the cutest
thing here it
is someone is already playing the
chicken
catching
oh
hello are you catching the chickens yeah
I'm catching the chickens capturing
chicken cute thank you for helping out
it is cute how wonderful does this
distract you
yeah now you can stay it's
fine it makes it difficult
see is okay very interesting can you
catch me catch me in the
basket yeah I don't know if you want
that I think these are for
dinner they are for dinner it is over
you
know open a Resturant okay everybody
click ready join the game oh we can play
together I think
so oh it says how many people already
enjoy the game only two people two
people
okay oh you then I'll leave my spot to
someone else go for it
uh I have joined the game did you join
as well you should start now
wait wait who
joined I have joined who else do you
want to play I how how many how many
people can join join it's okay you do
and then I'll we'll do the
next it seems she's a little bit
preoccupied join another player is
already playing it only one player can
play Oh Raven go oh so fast hello can I
interest you in a lottery here
completely free tell them that you would
like to start the first 20 people who
take a ticket will win but I cannot tell
you NAU go go go go go go oh maybe it's
not worth to go for certain chickens
maybe some of them have to be dropped no
I my eyes are very focused on the
chickens oh the most important wonderful
yes and Shakira moves the bucket from
right to left in amazing display of
skill come to me little chicken I mean
Mario try Mario's trying to distract her
but she's not
succeeding it is impossible to get them
all but I will try my best to take you
all on my wing Shakira is focused here
come here into my safe warm fluffy wings
I wonder know what she's going to do
with the
chickens she ra and some will die for
me and die for you
in honor terrifying kind of for
hon what
are how has it gone yes [\h__\h] o that was
really good you see I'm on the road you
made it on the salesman it's okay we can
exchange it this way would you like a
lottery Le you have made the
leaderboard
Yi huzzah
I want to play
again okie dokie I will be sending them
over to you now do you want to everyone
is serving me what the hell what no I've
already played oh talk
mhm oh you cannot can we meet by oh I
see because it is not
possible where do you want to go
hello oh she she bowed down to
her yes I have kned to her very
gentlemanlike wonderful
person so go to The Great
Library
M she got distracted again
okay I have my
cake oh hello yes into the
library take a
seat a seat oh may I may I give you my
donation my donation oh for the book for
the thingy yes for the yes for the
library thank you put it on the shelves
if you could mayhaps put put this book
on the shelves of
course thank Youk is it okay if I read
it um yes go ahead it is a book to be
read by all the library can I read it
out
loud I will be yes I will be the
audience
happily why is why are you a why are you
a ghost again oh I I now after turning
into a ghost I found out I have the
power to turn invisible oh it seems that
your soul is still in between the two
because you have yeah that is really
scary it's quite
scary my
goodness no don't do not come close to
me you foul
Beast goodness I'll I'll look away it's
okay I'll read your book while looking
away a night's tail I
[Music]
will once upon on a time there was a
night he traveled the roads alone for he
had no
purpose there was an emptiness in him
for he had lost his memories and
forgotten all that he held
dear why was I placed here what is my
purpose what is my reason questions he
asked himself day in day out when he
found a light a Shining Light a queen to
serve a guil to depend on and a lovely
companion a companion in which he could
call home but like him everyone around
him had lost their memories despite this
they continued to fight and journey side
by side even without their memories they
knew
intrinsically intrinsically that they
could rely on each
other but as each day passed everyone
knew that these days would come to an
end that memories would return and when
they returned would they be the same
person as they were now knowing this
they continued on making the most of
it the night suddenly full of purpose
was called an honest Noble night but the
night was conflicted for inside of him
was
selfishness he wished that no one's
memories would return so that he could
keep living in these peaceful
days but alas
he holds his convictions in his heart
and he will continue on with his head
held high for he knows a selfish request
such as his could never be
true wow that is such a sad story oh
you're back to not being a ghost anymore
that is a very sad storyful that my
physical form came back again that is
really nice do you know how can I put
this book into the library how do I do
that probably probably this one over
here I don't know how though maybe
select the book and try right clicking
it maybe I don't know oh I did it I did
it nice that was such a sad
story it was so sad God it's
fiction is it I mean I think so is it
not well we have our first book first
book in the library
[Music]
first nice
uh
attention please
submit it's just a silly story
stories I shall let the noble I'll shall
let her know
Library I'm calling
[Music]
someone yes yes dearest Jonathan I must
say that was a wonderful story it
touched me oh thank you I I found it you
found it where did you find it
yes oh it was just a collection that I
previously owned I wanted to donate my
story um to the to the library so that
all may read it yes because I've owned
it oh you owned it just a yes it is a
book that I've owned in the past so I I
believe that it is time to let it go so
that it may Inspire others s to read it
and um it was really nice experience
thank you I understand that you're
saying that you found it but if per
chance you wrote it I must say you have
a true gift for writing oh and I feel
like you should put your emotions to the
paper and per chance this is your
calling per chance writing to be a
writer to be a writer to leave
stories mayhaps I will fill the library
with with books oh if I were to have
written it of course wa which you
didn't yes I did not but I I will let
you know if I have any books to donate
to the library de Knight I have a
question yes what is your question very
unrelated if you wanted something in
this world like an item an item what
would it
be an item that I would want in this
world yeah like say a cake or berries
or um a
sword I do not want for
much mayhaps
[Music]
H I suppose I would like a milkshake to
remind me of when the queen had
purchased us all some food oh and it is
a very fond memory in my heart so
mayhaps some milkshake a milkshake okay
thank you very much for letting me know
if I can ever repair you for your
wonderful gift I will do so maybe I'll
prepare something on mine as well I
appreciate it now I shall go and play
the chicken game oh have fun with the
chicken game thank you thank you take
care take care night goodbye what
is
h that touched
me that did touch me I don't know what
the princess is up to I keep wanting to
check oh hello
to hello we are going oh hello I'm about
to end give me one moment please
okay I will send you over to Nana M but
for now thank you so much for joining
and I shall see you
all I don't know where B is I haven't
seen her I see her sometimes and then
she's gone
again um thank you all bye Darlings
oh you about to end
end yes oh sorry what what can I do for
you oh no it's okay no no no it's it it
is all right it's quite all right I I
have a few more minutes but I I have to
Scurry away due to a a meeting of sorts
oh a mean it's okay we will we shall
meet again tomorrow dear
narissa oh all right as as you say I I
hope you stay as a non ghost goodbye yes
now that fwell goodbye
farewell do not turn into a ghost
okay we need someone of the scalled wand
with to help with the
ritual I mean does n count here I am
just waiting for everybody to gather
around so that I can announce the
winners today right right that's now
okay let's do that first absolutely
nothing going on yes yes and I will
within the
same
H first she has her
lottery
winners winners indeed winners inde let
us
all the oh wait actually maybe I'll let
you do that maybe if you announce that
the winners are about to be announced
everyone will that oh correct perhaps a
3 minute warning is is in need
okay winners winners will be announced
in 3
minutes I have a ride please gather
around the I'm ready to be a winner
11 have you seen my high score being
announced in I did I went oh W she beat
it actually what if we
make
to milkshake how do you make a milkshake
let me let me look in the
library
[Music]
yes let's see is that me a
thing is that a
thing I
don't is that a
thing what cook oh the cooking book oh
I'm checking out the
cookbook
um H Calpine may have she is not here I
cannot buy from her okay maybe I'll call
her respect that messenger pigeon let's
see does you have a
milkshake that's not the
restaurant
huh wait oh there it is I got confused
because they're both
green help what is
this thanky let's
here well that is kind of annoying like
wonder if that's on purpose
or oh
okay is that a milkshake ultimate fruit
milk okay okay okay going to have to ask
her
Lottery L we love Lottery very nice oh
wait I saw a ghost I swear I just saw
somebody come bye
hi a ghost a ghost oh you know what it
may have
been while this happens I shall
contact the lady of the
restaurant dear lady of the restaurant
wait I can't buy a if she's not here cuz
she has to give it to
me never
mind wait did Jonathan G get one yes
Jonathan G got one perhaps we could call
Jonathan of the G with I shall call
Jonathan of the G it wasn't important
enough for them to be here then huh no
well you see even if they from the quest
actually I want you all to keep me
company I'm not going to tell you the
truth truth the truth being that you
really don't have to be here right now
you'll still get your prize money but
but I just wanted everybody together
because I'm lonely hello oh I am here
for the
lottery is everybody here except the
single person who refused a
ticket refused a ticket a free ticket
free ticket ref refused a free
tickets after the tra what happened to
her sister qu sister sister sister wait
a minute I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I you
two just look very similar I got I I
assumed assumed oh they look very
different from one they nothing alike
well yeah one is one is blue that's not
true they look so much they look as
alike as you look pregnant
what what term are you in wait are you
are you perh not pregnant that would
assume male pregnancy am I even able oh
I do apologize even able to get
pregnant as your business partner you
have to stop stop insulting your guest
stop insulting able to be prant try not
to try not to stop stop stop stop stop
pregnant backwards backwards
I what do you maybe you are and I and I
am just revealing it to you I have a
hunch you have a hunch Jonathan
G am I I said nothing a Miss am I is
anyone a doctor do we have a
doctor Cecilia are you sure you're
another doctor too huh no but I do I did
take I did take a a first a Course
once does it I feel like is that good
enough that's going to hospital here I
suppose okay okay okay yes what loty
good at all I guess but Lottery Let me
let me oh money is more important and if
you are in fact pregnant you would
really need the prize money wouldn't you
given that given that your wife seems to
be out of the picture now yeah you would
be raising it alone the child huh I
suppose I would be what happened to what
happened to her oh how sad oh she is not
of this world any longer she died what
are you sure about that yes she is no
longer with us
huh she died she want new is no
long she no longer with us but she's not
dead is she she dead she is the the
version I knew is no longer here with us
what are you talking
about oh the Pearl if you believe
so put all my eggs in one basket do not
give up
immediately I do not know you as
somebody who gives up so easily yeah
their
love see don't give up you know we
[Music]
you small difficulty I'm sure you can
make up I think you deserve it too
honestly I feel like this a second
Chancey Mone money money alert money
alert fre money alert money alerted the
M's arrived oopsie wait oh shoot hold
on oh oh she snuck in wait let me that's
fine that's fine you can hang out cuz
you're so
patient cuz you're so patient all righty
all righty everybody I will now be
announcing the winners but please be
please have even more patience as I have
to go through en count yes okie
dokie the first winner of the lottery is
is you whose name I did not get what GRE
you who is Green
Oh
Cecilia
Oh you go by the green one oh I go by
the green one I like the green one but
there's another green one so it's kind
of
confusing oh well call her the other
well just whoever is present is the
green one and whoever is not present is
the other green one I win
but yes you win I win you you win 100
coin oh spry
congratulations congratulations on your
100 coin what is going why is
this oh yes that's what I want this is
what I want I thought it was trying to
make me call somebody I will accept your
trade
request you get 100
coins to
be 100 points for you
at least not to memor next winner the
next winner is the Lady of the oranges
yipp huzzah yipp huzzah indeed you win
coins I got a
feeling 100 points for you I think today
we all
winners yes next the next winner is I
love this Nana 11 Mart next winner is
[Music]
Mario
yeah congratulations there are so many
winners you get 100 coins thank not sure
why you need it since you are the queen
but I'm just happy you entered my
lottery at all well sometimes you must
donate to the Royal team extra all the
time sometimes it is required that you
donate a portion of your earnings they
need the most more
powerful need all the money more than we
than staring
people the next winner is Jonathan
G goodness crazy C Lu great day Wonder
[Music]
day just got to keep your chin up
Jonathan yes I will thank you for giving
me A New Perspective
nanu wonderful glorious
one huzzah huzzah the next
winner is or I believe would have
been Nissa the ravening
cross oh she's not here departed for
today she is not here right now we did
confirm that she can pick up her
earnings
tomorrow the sleeping the ghost one yeah
scary one
Tom but that's okay we have now the
final winner of today Moco of the
co and because you bought five tickets
you get well you can buy one more to do
that know this you can could I have
bought 20 tickets and get everything no
you could not have today
wi I see wonderful congratulations
everybody you have all won the
lottery well it's okay she's addicted as
long as this is the only Lottery she's
going to because then she will not lose
any money here beautiful day today we
are all
winers mom so happy I think it's so sad
that they baned you by the way
every look everybody has won it was not
a scam
oh everybody won this is a
true family run by a family have one
that is me destroy
F destroy F
destroy we have to destroy this is just
dest I will give you my
winnings winning bring me more perhaps M
would like to share the win sharing
oh thank you my w those are the
mm um you're welcome Jonathan of the G I
don't I I don't think you should destroy
the market uh I don't think that's a I
don't think that's a good idea 2,900
coins for a jackpot is not very much of
a
jackpot I feel like you have very high
standards for a
jackpot a lottery is a lottery
down with f Mar do not do not down with
FAA Mar we need FAA Mar for healthy
competition on the
market I don't
know I need my money from fart first
before it goes down haven't you already
gotten a lot of money from fart I feel
like no
no
with after I get my
money it's getting quite suspicious
also support the same Queen
yes I yes of course I need to help you
you need me of child if I am random
suddenly male pregnant I will turn to
you I feel as if I I will need someone
to lean on but keep your chin up because
I have a good feeling about your wife
journe good luck with your
pregnancy good luck with your pregnany
thank you thank you I do have something
unfortunate to Dimension oh yes that I
think we should all keep in mind and
mentally prepare
for the chances of a male surviving male
pregnancy is extremely
slim oh
goodness what yes how do you know this
are you a
doctor no but I read I read
books still alive still alive your
Kindle That's So Close see I see
what is the Kindle well anything that is
written on paper must be true yes
there's no wrong things written on paper
that is true that is true okay what can
we do this is the library that you that
you library of course since you is there
anything we can do to help her him
through the male
pregnancy there is very little maybe
some healing items maybe potions
anything you can try but I we can we can
do our best to help but I think it's
very important that we just prepare in
case Jonathan G I see does not make
it just now that we became friends no I
don't believe it I think we can still
make it if I am to die
Miss Shakira if you would see to it that
my child is raised with their head on
right oh but I could also just uh bring
you to the temple and revive you oh
that's is true you can revive Meine it's
fine we have done it today we can do it
again we have done it we can do it again
oh that's true well that's easy then oh
okay you're consider she will take me to
the resurrection Temple and I will there
may be many things to be negative about
like the corruption that is spreading
but this is not something we have to be
sulking about don't
worry corruption on the
land her the princess jewry beu that has
been acting very strange as of late oh
yeah I'm going to kill her what what
you're not going to kill my princess why
would you kill her not right now why
would kill why you want to kill her I'm
sorry kill wasn't the best word kill
wasn't the best word I do apologize a
different word maybe maybe if she were
to be killed uh and then revived by the
Phenix fire she could be cleansed
automatically I'm going to make sure
that she is a good girl and doesn't do
see anything bad yes yes she is my
daughter I will protect her all cost I'm
sorry we will not let you K let you kill
her for no reason you need we need a
good reason kill's a reason the reason
I'm sorry she's killing all of us by
killing our crops and we are resulting
in Salvation where's the proof want us
to die for one princess where's the
proof is she bring upon a f Pro is in
the Ping I call
for I call for the Pro trial narissa has
rebuilt all the crops for us we
literally have seen it with her own eyes
when she was destroying them I asked for
a trial to the gardens let us check the
gardens by proof rebuilt it they rebuilt
it build it actually will not be oh well
that's oh it seems that well that's
convenient I don't see any proof that
the princess has done anything bad so
far well it's because Nissa has rebuilt
it I have helped her
huh I'm suspicious hello thank you for
your kindness fluffy wine replanting the
gardens the gardens it Wasa you're
attending to the gardens you are so
wonderful she was just taking it see oh
where Nissa thank you narissa Raven crop
tending to the
gardens but but how can okay so she's
been destroying the crops what if it's
just a simple prank why would you kill
her for that what what's going on that
does not sound like a good prank to me
the of the PR necess but it seems that
the princess is corrupt okay I I'll be
honest with you guys I mean the princess
the princess is my daughter and I've
never seen her acting that weird this
morning like I that is a good point I I
don't know there was something extremely
wrong with her today and I couldn't stop
her say so that's a good point yeah I've
also noticed her being very strange but
I feel like murder is very ex extreme
can we maybe we have a trial should can
we have a trial
M it seems
M the princess I could get my carrots oh
okay fairly well she does not want to be
involved in this murder is carrots are
for a fair Maiden such as she um I will
I will ask well I would like to ask
maybe we could have a set a court date
for
tomorrow court date would you guys be
okay with that Justice rules it would be
what for
justice I don't know if somebody can
have a fair Tri for justice with a
corrupted evil
mind I have seen the evils have happened
this land we can we can talk to her and
see if she's responsive and then we can
have her have a trial and if she's I'm
sorry but she seems out of control it
okay can I can I be honest with
you it seems like something is
corrupting her from inside and Nisa
ravencraft the the she told me that
there is something about the king that
is going extremely wrong like a
corruption from from the kingdom itself
so yeah and and yeah Shakira was with me
when she was talking about it and like
apparently the king is corrupting the
lies and they
thees um transform into the uh stains
that we see outside the kingdom and so
I'm being called sorry one second yes
calling you yo where's the party at oh
we are at the gardens we are currently
at the gardens Naru the gardens okay you
take my money and then go blow it
without me yes we're talking about the
cloth that you started wanting to kill
the
princess I don't want to kill the
princess I I didn't mean to you said it
though true it's Cecilia I defended you
saying that when you riged the game it
had to have been an accident I I still
believe I still believe that it was an
accident and completely unintentional
why is that you me what do you want to
do with the queen tell me use use your
words wait who is the queen the princess
I mean the princess sorry the princess I
just want to make sure she doesn't do
anything bad but now this has turned
into everyone wanting to kill
her wait why do they want to kill her
where
is at the gardens oh I need him I need a
map hold on at the at the it's like at
the Blue uh there's like water one must
be blind if one were not water I know I
remember what it looks like it's like on
on the side of of the giant circular
building and then there's oh and then
there's like wait
oh no I it's right next to you wait yes
I found oh you found it I found it okay
okay I'm coming okay okay it was read
this is the Garden
right I'm in the garden yes hello I'm in
the garden wait is this not the garden
um okay never mind for some well not
yeah this is the garden this is this is
the garden I'm in the garden are you
sure you can hang up now yes I see you
okay I'm in the garden she's very I see
we found her made her way hello okay so
tell us about this
corruption well first of all all these
lands were cleared by her destroyed by
her I saw her literally doing it and
then Nissa has rebuilt it and she has
then spoken to us in her cursed language
telling us that we must all die also if
we go to her statue it is now bleeding
with deadly blood May in G or what it is
it has also been cursed and corrupted
she might just have a tummy ache think
it is a tummy ache I do not it might be
a tum a tummy ache call it seems more an
aching of the Soul
hello oh I do not want to say this in
front of her but it seems that she is
she has a few screws loose she keeps
changing her mind for some reason but I
do want to trust her cuz she's part of
the Scarlet
wand and she gave us money IIA with a
with a with a lottery you know but she
is full of kindness but I do not know if
she is in the right of mind maybe I am
not pregnant maybe she's just making
things up yeah I don't think you can I
can I can I put my hand on your tummy
yes go ahead okay I know of a technique
to find out whether you are pregnant or
not what technique what is it well I
have suggested it to nursa before but
she did not want to try it however if
you um pee on red sand if it turns green
you are pregnant if it stays red you are
not oh what how do you know about this
what is this how do okay well there's
some red sand at
the I don't
remember I have in my in my backpack oh
maybe we could try that hello welcome
back I suppose we will have to will you
give me privacy when I do it happened
while I they're trying to figure out if
she's actually if he's actually
pregnant
oh is quite a bit of red sand yeah in
case you want to um confirm it 42 times
oh yes you can never be safe sure too sa
I will be back if you may give me some
privacy yes wait I don't know if we
should give him PIV privacy what if he
lies you mean yeah what if he's going to
collect somebody else's sample I don't
think anyone else is
pregnant no I mean what if he's trying
to hide the
pregnancy okay we should sneak up
I don't think she had
a shh trying to listen what is
happening what is happening are you
[Music]
pregnant are
you are you
pregnant oh are you pregnant oh I I've
not I've not built it yet I'm I'm
building an out housee
oh that will inde it'd be necessary to
it will be necessary I do not know how
large to build this though I think 3x3
is fine a 3X3 out house maybe perhaps
like this yeah unless you're visiting
the ouse with other people I think this
size should be yeah I think this looks
pretty
nice it will be it would just be a very
crude out at least
because yes I am on my lands cool
oh thank you it it will be a very humble
out
house um is there to be a door for do
not do not watch me please there will be
a
door you can't tell me not to watch why
would you want to watch me I like to
watch everything can you a window we
very observant no no wait but it's going
to get so stinky if you don't add a
window that is true that is just how
medieval out hostes are yeah just it's
it's going to be terrible regardless
they tend to be stinky we need some
ventilation of things are stinky in
Medieval ages where did my axe go seems
like I lost my axe I will just this
out but it's isn't this Shar is it there
is is being aired
out where where where I don't see oh I
see there's a hole upstairs okay at the
very top at the tippy
top
[Music]
sufficient can I make it in time
maybe this is the first out house in the
entire Kingdom then everybody must use
it can you give us all access to it yes
but not right now I am using it all
right good luck with the um peeing why
are you sticking your head
inside who is trying I forgot someone is
their head inside of my door what what
color is the head sorry sorry
yes one second let's
Co one one second one second before you
are making me
nervous too nervous to pee is it let let
me maybe you should drink some more
fluids are you are you part of no no we
none of us are seruan
huh you should drink more fluids make
sure hydrate hydrate Lots if you want to
pee 42
times I am now going to be peeing on the
the the the sand
okay okay okay if it turns GRE
okay if you need something let us know
oh I heard water oh she's that must have
been yeah heard her ju it seems that it
is red it is red still it's red it's red
still show us show us show us try again
show you where is it was on the floor
try again try again make
sure okay I will be peeing once
more oh really doing that on command huh
no it it was it was red you must HDE you
must have hydrated well previously yes I
I was very very hydrated well with maybe
all good things are free we have found
out that you are not pregnant yes it
seems that I am not pregnant I would
agree with that do you want your red
sand back I hungry apologize for my
assumption earlier I doize your uh your
wife one day gets pregnant I see I see
thank you I do it was because not
because of your stomach but because of
your glowing complexion I do apologize
for the for the mistake you thank maybe
because of that uh big juicy looking hat
oh thank you my very very juicy hat that
surely looks like you were hiding a baby
in there but it is empty I think SC
Scarlet w m I have a a
question yes can you come with me
me
yes yes did you just gly
giggle this is how I out happy oh okay
sorry um okay okay let's go a little bit
further I'm scared okay
[Music]
yes I see someone trying to spy on us
why are there always spies why does no
one trust anyone what is going on no one
else watches
me Jonathan are you obsessed per chance
what a beautiful Forest this isn't a
forest it's a garden it's a beautiful
Forest wow what's a beautiful Forest
Jonathan you should try fixing your own
issues before putting your nose in the
ones of others what a wonderful
wonderful Forest it is so green and
Luscious it really isn't okay well you
can stay here I'm trying to get a get a
magical stone to work and I need a I
need a Scarlet wand member in order to
help me with it an ally well it says an
ally but it has to be someone I trust
and that's trusts me I'm just kidding it
it is luscious I just was
trying just trying to be special it's
not going to work
you are quite special I was just really
embarrassed that I didn't think of the
word you sorry we don't have an ally no
Ally is currently awake it's impossible
what about my stone what are we going to
do with the stone it took me so long to
find the stone and to find to find all
the end we have no allies left right now
um let me see can I can I Scarlet one
Ally
um I let me send my messenger
pigeon oh I do not think my messenger
pigeon is is reaching anyone tonight it
truly feels like a do good no I it's
it's an ally it has to be an
ally it has to be an ally okay I'm going
to play the chicken game I have to I
have to
stall attempt to make new allies no I
don't think that's
possible hello fluffy one oh H I'm
making potato salad potato salad yummy
do you know how to make milkshake per
Champs oh I don't know how to make that
oh okay well good luck on making potato
salad thank
you I have a question how is your how is
your what's your
Allegiance are you allied with what is
your Allegiance are you allied with the
queen I de SL it
sorry I did SL it
oh Jade okay okay okay okay okay okay Al
with the queen yeah Queen the Queen the
queen Tam Gander
yes uh I don't know much about Tam
Gander I've only met her maybe once once
do you need my help oh oh sorry one
second uh I will call you back in a
moment uh sc one member I am in a conv
you in a tunnel okay sorry I'm in a
tunnel sorry sorry okay okay sorry
okay um so you you've not met
her no no what about uh Queen Mario do
you support her
Mario oh Mario I've never met a queen
Mario oh if you if you would would you
call yourself an ally to the Scarlet
wand I'm dead so it's not not
particularly huh I'm friends with
everyone I think though a that's nice
okay okay well thank you for your for
the information I wish you good luck in
the potato salads for
now okay take care good luck on your mie
quest no she's not Allied um do we trust
nanu
though I could wait until the
next until tomorrow
cuz if I do it and N nanam is not to be
trusted and I don't think I trust
nanu so since I don't trust her she
probably doesn't trust me
so I'll have to do it a different
time cuz I if I want her to do it with
the do the ceremony with me then I have
to tell her
everything but I don't trust her enough
to tell her everything and this is not
something you can do by this is not
something you can do by trickery or
treachery it's just not possible if only
if only there was someone if only there
was someone if only there was someone an
ally a singular Ally where's the chicken
thingy
uh okay I should call her to let her
know that I don't need her help help
right
now hello hi n uh I just wanted to call
you so in case you were waiting it's
fine never
mind it's fine okay never mind okie
dokie I was waiting so thank you for
letting me know okay that's okay okay
but thank you for offering the
help no problem no problem at all and
thank you for the fun
Lottery yes thank you for the fun games
and for your
patronage yes let us meet again tomorrow
I cannot hang up I accidentally entered
the mini
game this no you hang up no no you no
you hang no you hang up no you hang up
no no you hang up oh my gosh
you're not hanging up on me
you well N I have a question would you
call yourself an
ally to who to
me are we not part of the same Guild are
we yeah yeah you saw you saw how like
you know you open the door and then you
closed it accidentally and right after I
like super quickly Open Door still to
open it because you part of the scallet
wand interesting yes I was able to open
it and I just pretended that you opened
it for me cuz I assumed that it was an
accident that you closed the door on my
face so I would never well okay thank
you for letting me know never a terribly
in this mini game how will I recover oh
no you can get good I believe in you
thank you okay I still can't hang up
though no you hang up no you hang up no
you no you no
you I didn't like this game
like this game at
all yes hello hello Jonathan G are you
uh doing something uh of importance
right now no I am just building the
queen do you need something would you
like to play a game of
memory oh I suppose we shall play a game
of memory because ellia you won and I
wish I wish to oh I no longer wish to
play a game of memory well
what
why yes but
why oh I I am just so tired and I must
build this statue of the
queen you don't want to play
memory wait why do you wish to play
memory who is that who was that because
it was so much fun to play this is the
new one oh you were just having so much
fun it is not because you wish to have a
win over
me I mean do you play to lose or do you
play to
win I we are playing for fun yes yeah
yeah yeah I mean I have fun no matter if
I win or lose but you know I can still
want to win while still having fun
regardless
H but it's okay if you don't want to
it's fine I just saw did you do the
marry me
thing
what what who did that no did what
there's like a
giant there's like a text floating in
the sky oh it is it was Queen Mario oh
oh okay she is asking to marry Queen Tam
Gander
oh yes yes okay okay well well if you do
not wish to play I respect your
decision well
mayhaps we can play one game if that
would so please
you yeah it would please you
yeah yes of course I will meet you at at
the guild I love games okay see youy
well I will see you soon
why would you play a game if you're not
like planning on it trying to win at
least you know you know what I mean like
it's okay if you lose it's totally fine
but shouldn't you
play and try to
win am I in the wrong am I in the wrong
don't you want to at least try to
win
right what
maybe
maybe maybe Jonathan is just too
peaceful I made it all on my
own okay one game one game one game one
game hello Scarlet
k CA oh hello
Jonathan I am here I have joined the
game
okay yes good luck to
you yes yes good luck to you as well yes
good luck good luck oh I must start we
have started
mhm I did not know you were such a
enjoyer of the game of memory I like it
it's fun but it is quite hard I think
it's quite hard it is quite hard yes but
you have proven that you are very Adept
at memory gaming H I did not mean to
place that there but you beat me on your
first or second try yes but it took a
second try to beat you but that's very
little isn't it but you are quite good
you are very good at this game you think
I'm good at this game yes you are very
very good at this game I mess up you
lose oh well I didn't lose but I into
the game but I messed up I pressed I I'm
I'm choking I'm choking Jonathan do not
falter do not falter you are very very
good at this game of
memory okay I'm also choking as I press
the wrong said yes
yes oh do not worry Jonathan you
wouldn't lose on purpose right you would
never do that no I would never lose on
purpose I would see to it that I have
given you a rightful challenge okay I
trust you yes I would not lose on
purpose okay why would I do such a thing
I don't know it's just I feel like
sometimes the kindness in your heart is
uh seems to be very strong and you put
others in front of
yourself uh and it makes you suffer but
also you know it's like a level that
might uh hurt you in the long run is
that what you think I
would I would not do such a thing I am
trying my very very hardest right now of
promise you wouldn't lie right I would
not lie I am doing my utmost currently
and you are just ooh you are so good you
have vested
me oh oh no oh good oh goodness
why do you okay why do you sound so
afraid Let's us play again let's play
again let's play again let's no let's
take a moment let's take a moment why do
you sound so afraid why did you sound so
afraid not afraid I just was not afraid
why were you so shocked I was just so
shocked that I had
won cuz your memory is so good ah it is
because I was distracting you it was let
us play again but I will also play the
silent game this time
oh you don't have
to I should not no you can't
talk I I should speak yeah if you want
to if so you so wish are you ready oh
yes I am ready
okay I don't like that they take away
our hats in this I feel like that's
really messed up oh yes why would they
take our hats away that really weird yes
why would they undress us why would your
guil do such a thing to us M maybe it's
like safety reasons so people don't
cheat Maybe maybe someone you know like
has a piece of pen and paper or
something how would someone cheat at
this with their hat and Cape maybe with
like a piece of paper stolen uh hidden
between everything oops wrong one that
is true that is
true so Jonathan yes what do you oops
wrong one what do you think about the
princess what are we going to do with
the
princess I think that there is something
going on with the princess and it is our
duty
to to find out how to what what we
should do but do you really think we
have to kill
her no okay I believe killing her is
only The Last Resort it is the last
thing we should do right yeah that's
what I'm thinking as well oops it would
be quite ter keep going down on the
stairs ah o yes
yes oh it's not looking good I'm falling
behind no you you are so you are very
good at this game what how did I but you
were winning what
happened oh I am just so foolish and
stupid what suddenly happened that's so
odd oh youing so well I am now I am now
so back we are now back in the game it
seems that if I just had a momentary
laps in my memory of course you see of
course to everyone it happens to
everyone
yes it it does it does happen to
everyone I believe you I am only
human I make mistakes oh you human
what's with a tail
then nothing there's nothing with the
tail but why do you have a tail if
you're
human I lost
no but it's okay it's okay to
lose yes yes it was because I am sorry
it is because I am such a loud mouth are
you sure that we take this win
Jonathan what you can take the win oh
yes I have one this time huzzah huzzah
huzzah what a glorious day well I think
we should not kill the princess I feel
like there's still a lot of mystery
surrounding her and I feel like we
should either give her a fair trial or
try to heal her somehow do you have an
idea how we could heal her do you have
any
plans I have a few ideas like what
mayhaps she must consume something that
will allow her to be pure mind like a
cake a
cake what is that what you built for her
what you've baked I made a cake for her
yeah you've made a cake for her yeah
actually I'm working h no nothing yes I
made a cake for her oh you are working
what I made a strawberry cake because
that's her
favorite oh do you believe that a
strawberry cake will be enough to no
actually no I don't think so because I
don't know what's wrong with her because
I Haven like I've seen her a couple of
times she was a bit weird but I haven't
seen her do anything evil you know
everyone's saying she's doing evil stuff
but I haven't actually seen it I'm not
saying she isn't I'm just saying I
haven't seen her do it I see I see that
is a fair point it is hard to wor that
you haven't experienced I've been
worried a little bit you know how
there's been two queens right the
rightful Queen Tam Gander and then the
queen of Evergreen Mario yes so there
were two factions and then the king the
king's faction I guess and I feel like
something is weird because why did the
princess suddenly become a Target to
such you know to so much hatred she's
part of your guilt is she not I care for
her deeply and I wish for
her to be alive I do not want us to all
fight her but I cannot deny that she is
corrupt and it's not her fault it is a
stain a stain has poisoned her mind so
we must we must cure her of the stain
that poisoned her mind okay well then
riddle me that you know how the King you
know how the king called us all here
against our
will
yes and then we had to fight in four out
of five dungeons in order to destroy
stains but not in a single one was there
a stain and then there was a stain in
the sewers yeah I said four out of five
I mean a four out of five and
then he puts a lottery shopping
thing and one of the hats that you can
get for it
is a
stain that is true why would the king do
such a
thing I just like either do you distrust
the king I do distrust the king but I'm
scared of voicing it because everyone
else seems to trust the
king
well we should not speak of it inside of
your guild Halls oh that's true yeah
let's go somewhere else the G Masters
[Music]
okay okay so there's two options right
either it's a plushy then the question
is like isn't a plushy something that
you would make from something that you
are a fan of are you telling me the
liian and the King are fans of
stains then the other option why would
they do such a thing the other option is
it's a real stain and the stain has
corrupted our princess my my do you
think that is a a stain on her head that
has corrupted her think real
corruption it must be real it has to be
it has to be real think about it it has
to be when did the corruption start
exactly 4 days after Tam Gander has been
gone where is she what did the king do
to her you think that the King has her
and that she is not actually on an
expedition I haven't seen seen any proof
of her being on sad Expedition have you
she left me a note in her handwriting
what did the note say please tell me
said that she would be going on an
expedition now I cannot say where
because I'm afraid of voicing such
things but she is on an expedition and
she says that she will see me again soon
soon don't you think soon has already
passed don't you think I believe that
isn't she the strongest Queen
isn't she such a wonderful Queen days to
cross the the waters it's been days
though yes but she has to it has only
been what 3 days 4 days since she's left
I just feel like since she cared about
the Kingdom so much for her to just up
and go and leave her post I just she did
not know that this would happen exactly
she left it in my hand so it is up to me
it's up to me it's up to you should up
to me I think we have to investigate the
king with time I do believe in that
though I do
not the one thing that I have faith in
in this entire kingdom is the queen Tam
Gander I will never lose loyalty to her
but I do believe I do believe that the
king is not who he says he is well I
think maybe the king I think the king
took the queen and is hiding her away
somewhere
come with me he has done
that all
right where's the
castle where's it please show me the way
to the
castle um I will attempt
to there's a
mystery mystery of foot is this the
castle this is the castle
now let us
see yes we must be very oh hello hello
dear guards hello hello guards good day
now follow me
guards guards hello guards helloo nice
day hello dear guards dear guards hello
yes a good day
guards
now what do you
think it's hidden
here my
goodness don't you think that's kind of
suspicious doesn't that look like a cell
with like very very small cell that's
not
Humane it is not Humane evidence number
one absolutely terrible living
conditions for their
prisoners
now I'm getting a phone call it's me
it's it's just me oh oh oh oh I see I
see I see I thought this would be easier
oh
yes hello hello okay evidence number
two evidence number
two n this is quite a winding staircase
this takes a while
yes why are you taking your horse out
inside of the kingdom of it's F now
riddle me
this what what is this this must be a
secret hallway there must be something
hidden here what is the color of these
this is the exactly the same color as
the stage do you not see do you not see
the signs in front of you yes I see I
see evidence summer three all right I
will not be doing that I will be right
behind you okay I guess I'll walk
fine it is rude do you do you not think
okay okay you're
right yes yes yes
yes now stand with
me I am standing what do you see in
front of you dear
Knight The King and two guards okay what
is behind the
king his
throne but why why is there only one
Throne what about his Queen why has he
not built a throne in her absence for
her is true he may be he may be keeping
Queen Tam Gander
captive what shall we do I think I I
think I think I haven't thought that
far I see yeah you did not think very
far you what do you mean I thought
pretty far but it is a hard thing to say
you know it's a hard thing to bring up
to people and be like like o the king
might be doing something cuz that is
treacherous so well but do you see the
signs in front of you I have had this
conversation earlier in the day with
another member of the Scarlet wand oh
with
whom with one miss Nissa ravencraft oh
really she thinks the queen is evil yes
she spoke to me and she conveyed to me
all of the things because you know when
she was a ghost she was able to wander
around the Halls going unseen and
unnoticed and she discovered many things
and she believes that she thinks that
the king is the host of the stains she
believes that the king is the one
spawning the stains I mean look at him
he is the source of it all yes just look
at
him standing there while we go to war
for him hiding Our Queen from
us yes we must rid of him so that the
queen Tam Gander may take her rightful
place when she comes back on the throne
we will color the throne in the Blue
Blood of the king for the queen why is
his blood blue cuz he's a noble and it's
you call it blue blood and because the
queen is blue so then it would fit her
very well yes yes ath it fits
thematically yes yes yes color blue well
sh let
us wait for now cuz I don't think we can
do anything just the two of us and then
tomorrow we shall discuss this with the
others yes I believe that you would
benefit greatly from speaking to Nissa
ravencroft okay I'll talk espe see as
she is in your guild yeah I didn't get
the chance to talk to her much today
because I was a little bit scared of her
being a ghost I'm going to be quite
honest with you yes it was quite spooky
every time she spoke when she was a
ghost it was very
ooh oh don't remind me oh you oh you are
scared of G I am sorry I am sorry yeah I
forgot
the fact that I was scared of ghost for
the first 20 minutes when I attacked it
with her but then suddenly it hit me and
I remembered I'm so Terri scared of
ghost ter scar terrifying so yes yeah
well but she's Alive Now worry not we
have revived her I hope she doesn't use
her magical power too often I think it's
very scary Well for now quite scary I
think we should look into figuring out
how we can heal Vu and uh put Tam Gander
on the throne um yes and oh my God I
almost fell down and uh he would have
known he would have known well we could
have said it's like a parkour you know
oh yes we are just playing Parkour in
the in the we're training we're training
this is a training Arc yes we are
gathering our scam to prepare for what
is to come
yes well how joyous oh well thank you
for listening to me um and may I say
it's been it's been it's been it's been
an honor for you to beat me in the
memory game and you should Stand by Your
Victory it's okay you don't have to
thank you you don't have to do
everything for others very wise as well
you are the one who holds the highest
score so it is only that you you would
win oh for now but I shall train hard
and I will I shall keep the high score
hopefully
maybe yes huzzah huzzah well I will not
go to sleep glorious day all right you
will be you'll be tucking in oh
what farewell I thought I heard a noise
but it was nothing oh okay is it the
ghost is it the ghost must have been it
must have
been goodness let's
go will make
make how do I get out of
here I'm trapped I'm
trapped that's
pretty he
wait Noble Knight Noble Knight
Knight Knight Noble Knight I have one
more piece of evidence oh yes yes what
is
it why is there one lies all alone in
this giant Hall talk to
him oh do you
see I sorry I'm a little
frazzled what is it mean oh I remember
there is another there's another leeston
who completes the sentence I remember
that
narissa has okay let me take of this let
me take a Let Me Take A Memory cap of
this yes and let us go to the other one
the message that narissa ravencraft had
relayed to me earlier if only she could
relay it to me again and through carrier
pigeon because I do not actually
remember word for word what it was oh oh
should should you oh she finished the m
message yes she had finished the message
but we can find it here too if she does
not send word through carrier pigeon
because I have very rudely forgotten the
complete full sentence find it do you
remember the
gist no oh it had it had oh wait I have
received carrier pigeon wait let's go
outside so I must capture the carrier
pigeon these stairs are so winding these
stairs are so very re winding I will
jump now where where is the door how do
we get out of here oh is that the way
out oh here's the second
one oh you can I will I will get the
carrier
pigeon it's the same
one okay I'm behind you wow so
pretty this a grand Castle so what did
she say it
says oh thank you thank you dear
pigeon she sent word it says land of
faded Destiny echoed over and over again
break the chains and it will flee Back
to Where it All Began say it
again land of fated
Destiny echoed over and over again break
the chain and it will flee Back to Where
it All
Began
H land of fat to
Destiny can you send it to me with a
carrier picture I will yes I will send
through carrier picture okay come here
come here my dearest sweet carrier
Pig oh I got it I got it how wonderful
land of F Destiny fated Destiny echoed F
Destiny enigmatic over and over again
break the chain said it will flee back
to where it all
began to Where it All Began where did it
all begin maybe the land of fated
Destiny is where we
from echoed over and over again the
chains the chains is what's keep
chaining us here in these lands Back to
Where it All Began in that white room I
have vague memories of a white room a
white room really where yes a white room
oh that white room I not know where that
was weird it's a white room and that has
led us into seeing something yes it was
very strange what if the stains have
also been summoned here just like we
have what what if we have to free the
stains for them to go back home it's a
it's a wild it's a wild guest but maybe
maybe a very very wild guess maybe we
have to break the fre chains for them as
well so they can go home maybe that's
all they want
yes well it seems as if we cannot do
much I think we need a detective for
this a detective yes well you know a
detective
yeah yes oh oh Amelia Watson right just
one dear Amelia Watson I will send a
carrier pigeon her way and ask if she
would so kind
assist us in investigating well such
things for now I will I think we both
need rest well I need rest I don't know
what you're going to do for now I will
need some rest um but thank you thank
you for thank you thank you for trusting
me uh of course and uh we might have our
differences but at least for now our
goals align Noble Knight for now we are
allies and I will entrust my sword to we
are allies for now
farewell sleep well thank you I hope I
wish you a peaceful summer as well thank
[Music]
you
what well well
well um well see you all
tomorrow thanks for playing I mean
thanks for being being in the animatic
recollection we'll see we'll see what
happens next I do ah I do wonder if my
co completely crazy Theory might be true
what if the stains have also been
summoned here I don't remember the
beginning what they said in the
beginning I don't remember since when
the stains have been here I do Wonder
well see you
everyone
fwell this way oh oh
hi it's me oh it's me Cecilia IM imag
green not Cecilia imag green um uh next
stream will be oh in 4 hours uh yes on
uh we're playing this like Kyla's
birthday map uh I think I think it's
four five five five hours yeah so um I
will retweet it I will retweet it once
the stream is over and then next stream
on my own channel is at probably
probably probably at 9:00 p.m. CS
tonight well like tonight well tomorrow
you know what I mean in like 13 hours
and that one will be Wukong probably
probably probably probably probably
probably and then in the evening late
late
we'll have the finale of enigmatic
recollection chapter one so I hope you
guys join for that as well yes monkey
monkey game so I will see you all thank
you very much for hanging out I had fun
it was a little bit CA today but I still
had a nice time and I really like the
little mini games I didn't like the
chicken one that much but I really
really really really like the memory one
can't believe Jonathan beat me
immediately
I so frustrating
how how is he so good at this game when
he barely played it
wow just on a different level but it's
okay I can train I can train I can get
better I can train I get
better you are distracted no that's just
excuses
excuses okay well thank you very much
everyone thanks for hanging out see you
all in the bed or tomorrow
bye-bye bye-bye bye-bye by B
[Music]