[Music]
do
you
[Music]
do
hmm
my
[Music]
do
how how do you say it everybody
um halt
stand straight
bow down in front of your empress
okay
let's go
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'm not i'm not a good uh commander but
ah attention no really do you say that
attention
hello
[Music]
wearing my old outfit because it's uh
hold my default outfit because it's in
my it's in the in the
the thumbnail and you know you gotta
give people what they're expecting what
their they think they're getting
otherwise they'll click on the thumbnail
i think they're gonna
find that girl the thumbnail and then
it's someone completely different and
they'll be like you bamboozled me you
how what do you call it again you um you
click baited me girl um
yeah no no no also i'm already wearing
this so that i uh uh can go to sleep in
this uniform and then appear on the
official channel tomorrow in this
uniform without having to put on any
clothes because i already wear i'm
wearing them
although i don't know i probably will
wear this tomorrow probably
ah big brain
big brain hello everybody
today will be a short stream i will play
with you sliver dog io because we
haven't meow we haven't played in a
while um
it seems like my cats want to eat some
snakes too
we haven't played in a while um
it's so cute
short stream only six hours now the
gaming portion
maximum
one and a half hours
and then some quick quick speed super
chat reading
because uh i gotta go to sleep early
it's early today um although
you know you all know i won't be able to
sleep right away especially because i
had another nap before the stream
i had a nap though because i i got up
early and i was so tired after the
recording i had a recording today and i
was so tired afterwards yeah i am
uh yeah i had to i had to sleep i had to
but still i mean i still managed to
sleep relatively early last night so
yeah
i will do the same today
yesterday it took me tomorrow today i
got up at 10.
yesterday i got up also around that time
i think
tomorrow i'm also getting up at 10 no
actually earlier than 10
gotta eat breakfast
unbelievable i know
i know unbelievable kiwawa
wake up at 10
what
what do you think about this one you
hear this
oh gee
the og man
the good old nostalgic kiwawa bgm did
you hear that
a classic a classic yes just like mozart
oh beautiful
loud and clear okay so uh i hope no
one's stealing my name um i am i am cute
i want a great yes
um supposedly my skin today is
uh
supposedly it's the austrian flag
be nice very true okay so one thing i
really always like about playing silver
is seeing everybody's names i don't
think there's anyone here yet
from kiwawa land
kfp
[Music]
go away go away i only want chickens
near me go away it's a beautiful light
sparkle sparkle go away that was
supposed to be mine it was coming right
at me okay i'm gonna eat your poop
so uh
people uh i wish you the best of luck to
join me here
i hope you all can make it into
this server
uh take a look at the leaderboard and
then you'll see where i am perhaps if
you're in the right place or not
uh oh
wow
kiwamo become big
laggy
super laggy on my screen is it so laggy
for you guys too
maybe i should change like to low
quality
low quality sliver like what the hell
man
okay low quality doesn't really make
much difference i guess
i'm low quality now how do i get in well
you've got to be lucky i think i'm
probably on the european server and
there are we've had this before snake
there are ways
there's like a like a
uh what do you call it a
chrome plug-in thingy not a plug-in an
extension
with that why you're so fast yo speed
are you german
bulgaria who uh with that you can like
kind of control where you land uh but i
don't know what it's called check
probably knows it's been a while oh my
god
oh whoa whoa whoa
dangerous i need the chimpkins to oh
protect me
i don't think that was one
are you german yeah the the speedy ones
they're probably german especially since
we're in a
uh
in a in a
way brain empty especially since we are
in a european server yes
i would join but i don't have enough
laptop yeah normally people only have
one laptop i however i have more than
one left though
i still use my
old super slow laptop um
in bed
uh
even though i now have an alienware
laptop for streaming
but it's so big and it gets really hot
when you put it on the bed
so i decided to
just not use it on my bed and just
continue using the old one that i love
so much so dearly until until it breaks
forever and ever
it's it's a laptop that i once bought
in
i think about it in japan and it's
really pretty because it it's it has the
prettiest colors it's uh it's like a
rose
rose metallic rose uh color
metallic pink color it's so
pretty laptop needs air circulation
exactly right yeah i could buy one of
those tables but i don't know then
there's just it feels like there's too
much stuff on my bed there's already two
cats
is that the whole
that sounds like a
whole iphone
uh where was i just now look at me i'm
already so big
[Music]
look at me oh
someone just died there
and you're eating the corpses of
someone's dead buddy
let's go okay
you want me to say it you want to say it
fine i'll say it
[Music]
help kfb
oh wait you mean when i'm gonna play
the yakuza 0 was that the one i wanted
to perhaps play next i'm not sure i gave
you guys
i gave you oh god it's laggy it's laggy
why is it laggy it's not lagging oh yes
maybe i should be playing on obs screen
but i i would look to that side it's
dangerous
oh god
why is why is it laggy on my screen but
not an obvious so that's that's a
mysterious to me
how did you even get that big so fast
and there's so many get out of here get
out of here
get out of here it's my territory
oh that is cute i love you too jim king
i love you too
don't eat eduson hey hey hey hey hey
don't eat my friend don't eat my friend
who the [\h__\h] are you to it my friend
hey
[Music]
i don't know who it was but we have
gotten the justice
we have received justice
yeah yeah don't be too greedy guys
oh
i never kfp blade johnny hello
hello oh there's food facebook i'll give
me something oh that's what you get
let's get what you get for not sharing
you should always uh share oh hello you
go
you have found me as well you guys are
so quick and finding me what the [\h__\h]
these maps are huge
i'm in the oh yeah i'm not showing the
map on the screen that makes it really
difficult for you huh i'm like pretty
much in the middle
maybe i shall change it
so that you guys can should i make it
easy should i make it that easy for you
guys
should i really
oh my god there's a karen
please don't please don't uh complain
about my business
this is a kfp m
m wow
we don't
we only sell the best quality meat
yes
[Music]
please stop complaining
oh
where are my friends where are my
friends where's where's everybody
kfb where you went should i
he had a great hate
you cannot be greater than me i'm bigger
than you like literally
the rainbow snake it's looking dangerous
it's pretty cute these snakes are so
adorable
your mom oh my god mama mommy mama tony
she wanted to capture us i think just
now but she changed her mind
[Music]
[Laughter]
you um
didn't get it quite right but you have
the spirit for it okay pf no chiara
phoenix fried no no
no one fries the chia pizza
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] i was so big
hello
um i'm baby again
[Music]
baby i'm on the i'm on
somewhere below
the center on the right side
wait wait
[Music]
anyway my recording today was a lot of
fun
yeah
and i hope you guys will see the result
of it soon asmp but i don't think it
will be that soon i think it will take
some time it will take quite some time
um
a lot of things going on behind the
scenes always
that's great yeah
it was fun fun fun fun fun
[Music]
is that even worth it going so far
sprinting so far for a light like that
but uh even though it was like a it was
like a one hour recording or so
but it didn't even
wasn't even that long but i already
noticed like by the end of it my throat
was hurting again like it was getting
pretty coarse
by the end of it
it feels like my throat is getting
weaker maybe it's the winter time
maybe it's the one to come
dr jamia
need to go to doctor
the one that i can't pronounce no matter
how often i try it uh oh my god
that one is german too
you found me hello
hello
i'm still i'm in the middle i'm in the
center middle line but on the right side
thank you
i'll go i'll go more to the center i
guess
uh this this orange
is creeping me out
i'm on my way i'm making my way to the
middle
are you following me
go away
stop it you guys should make clear if
you're one of us you should make it
clear of your name
i saw that that's a yellow one i think
that was a kfp i think i saw the name
for a moment it was something with kfb
i'm sorry you had to die good luck
finding me again i guess
cafe tiger hello
hello
follow me
this is relaxing isn't it you we should
be playing this
with the
oh this great hello tinkerine burger
we should be playing this but with the
music that oh thank you all of you with
the music from yesterday that we were
playing during the super chat reading
you know the the meow meow woof woof one
[Music]
then we would have i think a
wonderfully relaxing experience
the animal uh
what's it called animal village
animal village bgm from lynx awakening
this person i think is from kfb after
all because
who the [\h__\h] are you
[Music]
because they followed me damn it
okay i am around the center again
but more like on the top left of it
top left of the center
small snake
small sex snake small snack snack
is a snack
well what what do you want hey someone
saved me
you savage
i'm not i don't no
go away
oh but you're gonna get eaten by someone
else
nice
by the way i'm hiding the
the spot where it usually says an ip but
it only says
it doesn't even say an ip and she says i
p play first whatever that means but
it's probably safe to show
um
wait where was the where's the map
it's below that i don't know i can i can
try to show you let me tap out let's
hope i don't die
uh
wait don't kill me i need to figure this
out
it's below it's where it says share on
facebook okay
i know
me and i don't know
um
should be like
if i make it this big then it should be
good
[Music]
i will hide it anyway
i will hide that thing
anyway
wait does it get lifted though does it
go higher once they go in you know what
whatever i
guess wait the window size is
kind of awkward let me move this oh
okay
just in case it at some point shows
something it shouldn't be showing
let's go you see the map it's [\h__\h]
tiny but i guess you can get the gist of
it
[Music]
ooh pretty green
i see a i want to see kfp on a
leaderboard that's always the gold one
playing sliver
can't be where you wet
recently got your first merch of kfb
nice when cats review what do you mean
wait cape wait you're not gonna eat me
art are you you're not gonna eat me
you're here to uh be nice to me right
oh god the questions
the questions they're cornering me or
like circling me
hey
that's not how you get an answer key i
want a lesser
there were a lot of cave people there
oh cats you mean the movie or like
generally just cats like was that really
a question i mean i must it must be
yo
kiara for la job j j e japan expo i
suppose bonjour bonjour
volleyball
snake tonight with me
[Music]
her say no wow hey young people okay you
people
i wouldn't watch evil one excuse me you
wouldn't watch a stream where i review
cats that would be like the most
wholesome small snake hello okay of me
sky hello
that would be the most wholesome hi
ninja hell that would be the most
awesome stream ever
come on is better than who
better than who
who
my friend
my french friend
my french friend was made into french
fries
poor poor guy
oh my god oh my god
oh maybe it was bad to show the map now
it's like
it feels very chaotic oh yes
kiana the greater really is pretty great
right now oh man look at look at that
no no no
no circling me no no you wanna kill me
you did it before i'm not gonna trust
you this time thank you
you can't circle me you can't circle me
[Music]
gotta do a great test
okay
i have the greatest
is
there yeah nostalgic right
i've been having so much fun with the
audio stock that i've barely been using
this but i remember man
uh
i remember like i was watching
the
uh
fifth gen debut and i saw that a couple
of them had
um music oh
i smell snake you always find me they
had music like original music uh
commissioned and i feel like
at that point it was kind of like
not so common yet
to
commission like at least music
bgm
um for your streams and we've been whole
life it was not so common yet um
[Music]
people were using not even audio stuff
they were still using that other website
what was they get
and forgot what it was called but yeah
and so i saw them using it and i was
like you know because they they debuted
like oh yeah dover syndrome yeah they
debited like
one uh
one month before us right so
there's not that much time left but i
was like yo
oh genma
uh can i can i do the same here with a
mediocre
that's right
you you know you place
oh
what was i just talking about oh yeah oh
yeah yeah yeah i was uh
never going to give you up
i was still talking about the music yeah
and then i and i commissioned the two
tracks actually no i commissioned one
but then i got two samples and they were
so good both of them i liked them a lot
and i wanted some variety
thank you onion i'll put you on the
burger
that i asked to keep both
and i rarely use them nowadays and i'm
kind of sorry about that
[Music]
oh thank you ah stick snake dangerous oh
god hello you're using the same
the same color as me huh
and paw stuff
[Music]
really
hello
[Music]
welcome avio welcome you're also one of
us what is this love mikiana
i love you of course i do
never gonna eat you up
never gonna snack you down snack snack
[Music]
bacon and these eggs
good breakfast do you guys like to be
combined with uh bacon for for breakfast
or are you not in
on good terms
with the bacon friend
[Music]
i need to get out of here i'm getting
claustrophobic
[Music]
hello
there we go
it's always the brazilians that asked me
to come to them why don't you come to me
huh
wow i always have to why does everyone
have to come
whoa
[Music]
does everyone have to come to you how
about you come to me
um ironic because i think that number
that killed me
means uh death in uh
actually awesome
it means uh death in chinese right but
also doesn't it also kind of uh mean
death in uh
in japanese
i think wait or is it only in japanese
am i mixing things up
yeah
yeah the number four
isn't that like is callie's favorite
number was it four
because you can say uh four in japanese
not only as young but also as she and
then it's like uh
yeah
uh the first oh
the first
syllable
you cannot kill your empress you're
aware of that right
you seem to be
very aware of it i got a little bit a
little bit of you thank you
yummy you taste yummy
not chia lover what the [\h__\h] he had a
freshly laid egg
thank you i kind of did that myself wow
there's a lot of food in there oh man
get out of here guys
i know now i'll come to bristol you come
to me cool
i'm so busy reading them wait [\h__\h]
ella's nana is back
somebody's reading the names ellie's
name i remember you
you
when i played sliver in the past you
will always
oh
kfp person
i love you hallelujah
you're a saint
you're [\h__\h] saint man
[Music]
whoosha
should be listening to sparks while uh
playing this we need some more do we
need some more up-tempo music guys
something more energetic
you have this fancy color i could not
ask
i wanted to ask for you guys but i'm
sorry
you won't you won't know
i don't think you'll ever know
i want that i want that i want that can
you go away i want that
um
oh green
eat your veggies guys
go on the tangent which one wait um let
me think uh
a tangent uh
go unattended crony's milk is that my
topic maybe i should go on a tangent by
choosing by the sliver the ion names i
don't know what to say about crony's
milk
um
[Music]
oh oh there we go that's what you get
for not doing social distancing
wonderful feed me oh god oh god oh god
oh my god oh my god oh my god they're
trying to feed me i think
but
it's not
not quite working um
i can't sing mama moose
[Music]
i like that song where they um were
cute kikudumi's the full body
uh dogo outfits
uh for example
what was that when's that song again i
don't remember any
any songs right now my brain is too
occupied we're not dying you shouldn't
scream so much that is true
yeah you clustered me too much that's
right that is correct
wacky
oh [\h__\h] that's a
a big boy
are you are you that number one on the
leaderboard
you want to give me a piece of you
oh
hey how was your name i want to get to
know you hey i just met you
and this is crazy
but please feed me
i'm really tiny oh [\h__\h] sorry i got i
got
i made a mistake
miss snake
okay restart
reset
well i think i'm gonna i'm on a
different uh server now again
chicken there's chicken on number seven
who is that
who is that chicken will you feed
yourself to me eventually after reaching
number one and then make me
the one and only number one let let's be
up
did you do a typo in your name
[Music]
ah this is comfy
where are my when my blood donations
guys
where are they kfb yo big representing
kfb
thank you
i absolutely love you
mind mine all this is fun this minds
minds minds mind mine mine mine mine
mine mine mines mines mines ones ones
mines mines mine's mines
mines mines mines mines mines
oh hello welcome back here it didn't
take you too long to find me this time
how's it going what
crony burrows
yeah i want that
[Music]
okay so they asked for attention i shall
give you tangent
uh
[Music]
wait i usually have some tangents
prepared on my phone but my phone is not
in this room
[Music]
thank you
when in doubt
kill this kill this purple snake kill it
kill it with fire
how's the cats cats are doing all fine
as always
hello
no issue there uh
oh i had a dream the other day
um
i had a dream
when i want to hear about it i don't
remember that much but one particular
thing that stood out to me was um
i was a
you know how you like switch locations
so fast in dreams and it all doesn't
really make sense when you're trying to
explain it to someone afterwards like
why the [\h__\h] are you there now but so i
was i was in a
in a
hotel that was more like a resort like
it had like a [\h__\h] ton of pools outside
like one
one huge pool that connected to the
rooms
absolutely amazing i love it
and then
um there was there were even some like
some
slides
big ass slides
where you could
uh slide down hey auntie moo thank you
good boy good boy who's a good boy who's
a good snake you're a good snake
and then i looked there and what do i
see
who do i see sliding down
the uh slide at that weird hotel
guess who
hey kevin not kiwama true
akira hello you always find me
she's small i can't you're dead chicken
it was an omen
um
i saw
myself but
seven versions of myself
it was seven different
kiara
cosplayers
[\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] yeah
that's what you get for trying to kill
me
it was seven different takanashikiya
cosplays
and they all had like yeah they were
wearing my ahoy
they were wearing my um i think they
were all wearing my summer outfit
but it was like
they're sliding down the pool they got
like all their clothes wet and i mean
nice actually it makes sense because
that's the only outfit
that actually has um
[\h__\h] it's the only outfit that actually
has a
a swimsuit underneath right so
there's actually official information
that my outfit
the chicken number eight come on go
number one
and my summer outfit has a swimsuit on
in here um
yeah and actually it was not even like
just like random uh hi
thank you
random
cosplayers that don't really exist like
i i
i recognized one at least one thank you
uh
cosplayer
uh from my dream so that was cool
kinda fantasizing about herself no
no no not really free french head free
french hands yay
give me your body
sunset brandon how long you need to chat
hello toast lord hello hello all of you
food please
if you wanna hear i love you from
takanashikiwawa this is an easy way to
get it
oh yeah so after this was in the same
dream but after i saw these seven
beautiful gorgeous ladies
gorgeous takanashi uh kiwawa cosplayers
i
i killed a king
aching
no idea
who and why
but i was
somehow involved
in
in some kind of
cool i guess that's probably from me
watching uh the great on on
stars play
on amazon
it probably has something to do with me
watching too much of that
[Laughter]
no no no not burger king
i would never do that what happens to my
crispy chicken if i would do that i'm
taking you
thank you
hey
come on bump into me do it do it do it i
know you want to i know you want to
recharge i know you want to
hey
i never did this before
snakes
beautiful beautiful oh beautiful
yeah yeah and then um
they didn't think i could do it but i
did it unpaid intern now welcome
but uh yeah i wasn't even really
supposed to kill him but they kind of
the other people kind of failed their
mission and then i
then i um when we already thought it was
over
i met
i saw him
[Music]
you wanna hear a nice camp
i saw him
[Music]
and then i had a knife in my hand and i
stabbed him oh [\h__\h] i'm inside of a
rainbow
are you protecting me it kind of feels
like they're protecting me you say
debuted well [\h__\h] you
[Laughter]
what do you mean i say it wrong how are
you supposed to say that why the [\h__\h]
are you telling me like this
now you you
conveyed your message now
go go bump against thank you
what
how do you say it then
the debut
attend
um
at nuke what's gonna happen what's
what's gonna happen between us two huh
what what what's it gonna be are you
helping me you don't seem to be able to
uh
make your circle any bigger anyway
because so many people around you but
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] um yeah you wanna eat me i
have i've realized that by now
i understand oh [\h__\h]
he nuked me now
debuted
when i say debut debuted debuted beauty
sounds wrong
sounds wrong to me
oh oh hey what's up man i just was born
i just got reborn snake
franchise but this was bigger i'm going
for this one
yummy tummy mmm yummy yummy yummy i got
loving my tummy
[Music]
hello
hello everybody jennifer what's up you
should be working
what are you doing playing sliver
ah
go clean up
go clean up the blood puddle on the
second floor
[Music]
i mean the tomato tomato juice puddle
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
you did go to me indeed
i'll toast your buns
my buns
he bumped into me that's what you get
piano
just below average
so better that made you huge hello hello
i love you i love you i love you i love
you you read my mind you read my mind
you are a genius our minds are great
we are connected because we're both
great minds oh thank you oh [\h__\h] akihito
i know you didn't want to do that i know
you didn't
i forgive you i am a merciful empress
i will forgive you
i know how to boost i know but i just
generally like to not boost
[Music]
no they killed you i will eat you
extreme heart challenger indeed heart
challenger is being um
over
overseeing loyal customer oh thank you
i i don't quite
trust you though because it's the loyal
customers who then use their loyalty
even though they're often not even that
loyal they just use it as an argument to
complain kfb killer oh no
the killer is bad guys i remember the
killer
having a
an eye on me always in sliver [\h__\h]
welcome to the rabbit hole overshadowed
oh shine
exactly overshadowed but um
just maybe forgotten
i love heart challenger with all my
heart
dead
but the one year anniversary of heart
challengers coming up soon so
we will remind people of the existence
of heart challenger together
heart challenge my favorite original
thank you
the first song on my whole songs plan is
i won't ever forget it thank you
[Music]
wow boiled and sparks about the hill
free about to hit 3 million nice
hey hey what are you doing what are you
doing what are you doing
okay he's he do be dooming
uh what was i saying oh yeah well i
wanna i wanna celebrate the one year
anniversary of heart challenger
uh
since it came out on valentine's day
it's pretty soon okay
that music video
from heart challenger i'm i'm so like
proud of it i put a lot of
put a lot of money into it
yeah yeah
it was a freaking cool
news video i wanna i wanna get the same
person to work on a music video again
someday cause like the 3d elements are
so
so cool and mama done this art yeah i
want mama leone's art again in the music
video as well
we all love ma maloney mama luna kiara
is one of the
best kiaras out there
yeah i said i was gonna make some kind
of like chocolate again
remember remember the first
the first chocolate
the first cooking stream from
takanashikiyada from me
which was for the sake of heart
challenge
for the sake of uh [\h__\h] you
[Laughter]
oh man
and i was so nervous and we had genma
come over for that right because uh
we both didn't trust my
my
[Music]
my stability and safeness as a streamer
we both didn't trust myself
so jenna was there behind the scenes to
help me
create when she was there right
was it all a different stream
i think she was there
to oversee hey hey let's be a boo what
are you doing be careful there be
careful unless you want to bump into me
to give yourself to me oi
was that your plan all along
was that an accident i want a raise
no
no no
work hard and show me proof that you
deserve it and then
we can think about it then
this is like sending me super chat
messages you guys have a chance to
send me your thoughts and your prayers
here bird video observer that's cute
that's a cute name i'm lost help me that
is absolutely adorable to move small
snake what about me
you want to grow but what about your
boss huh one of you
[Music]
morty is an angel she is deaf i don't i
don't know how you can be a
what
just wasn't paying attention i don't
know you can be a deaf and an angel
a swarm of kfps
i was thinking originally of giving
myself some kind of challenge or or a
batsu game or something or a goal
for this
uh
sliver stream but then i couldn't really
think of anything i wanted to get myself
donuts and then be like if i get into
the leaderboard i'll be able to eat the
donuts but we all know that even if i
wouldn't get into the leaderboard that i
will be eating the donuts anyway
so yeah food hello wait let's go
somewhere oh okay okay okay okay oh [\h__\h]
i'm sorry
[Music]
i only ruined your legacy
yeah it's kind of pointless isn't it
it's just me wanting to eat donuts
[Music]
foreign
oh my god
[\h__\h]
that went so well
for a moment
i wasn't on a killing spree or more like
a eating spree
damn it
[Music]
your voice i'm i'm good i'm good i'm
good that is a different stream in the
screen there's like two different type
of screams
the one where i feel like
um
like i'm
[Music]
uh
like i'm rolling over my throat while
screaming
that one that is out of pure terra
or uh
there's there's a normal scream which
was what i just did so it's okay two
months of working carefree nicer
hello you guys hello
hello
grow big and then sacrifice yourself to
me got it got it
no need to do it now
okay okay okay okay thank you
we start small i guess
thank you
for some people it doesn't show the name
i don't know why
chicken cultist kusa give me that thank
you
thank you
oh yeah guys are you aware of the stream
tomorrow i mean
um if the chat goes zoom at the side of
my eye then i know you are because i
can't really look at the answers that
much
yeah yeah you're aware of it
are you are you are you don't
hi heartball
thank you thank you
yeah yeah you know okay yeah tomorrow
i'll be on the whole live official
channel well it will be um pretty much
only japanese i think
um because this is on japanese official
channel
so forgive me for that but there might
be translators in the chat perhaps
um get out of here guys too many people
too many snacks
thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you bathroom
[Music]
who are you collabing with okay so you
don't seem to be aware of it uh tomorrow
on the whole life official channel uh at
8 pm japanese standard time
um i will be there with bhutan senpai
and eufy senpai and
hi bathroom
what's up what's up
[Music]
hey tom
ajang will be like the
mc she's a really good mc
oh it's very reassuring to have itch on
around thank you
dangerous game we're playing
yeah and it will um be about uh
uh i don't know
we're doing something with cards
apparently according to
the tweet
but no we're playing not last rides
we're not playing a card game not an
actual card game
and uh there will be an announcement big
announcement
uh
so
i think you guys should be there just
even for the announcement
oh no we're not doing translations no no
no
that's not why we're there
no no
that would be weird it's just i feel
like they need to pay me extra if they
really really
bring me in for like translating
something
that's the service i will provide
maybe
for extra payment
let's get out of here there's two too
many people again i want to find a safer
spot
yeah food always following me that's
cute
[Music]
big big ration incoming big food ration
incoming
[Music]
you're the telly you're on the telly
if you put youtube on your uh
uh
on your tv did you know you can be on
the telly if you write something in the
chat
big life accomplishment
have you guys ever been on tv before
because i have
i have been on tv before have you guys
been on tv before for anything
maybe being in the background of a news
report or just being famous maybe
there's some famous people among us
thank you
holy
[\h__\h] holy sheesh
oh sheesh
i have sally but it was for work i was
interviewed before brave very brilliant
when i was a little kid many times
local tv
have you guys been interviewed uh
because someone was um murdered in your
neighborhood before
and uh
or or died and you just said oh that was
a really nice person oh no because
someone um
it reminds me of a of a
that's very specific
it didn't happen for me but it reminds
me of a community channel um video
where
uh it's like ironic that uh
what was it is ironic that
for
uh these kind of reports
when someone
um when someone was the killer in the
neighborhood
um then
all the neighbors say the same thing
they always say like oh i never thought
he could do something like that he was
such a nice nice person such a nice guy
such a nice
uh person we never thought anything uh
that he would be capable of doing
something
yeah he was so nice and so quiet oh
that's the problem that's maybe the
issue
thank you i will still not unionize kfb
though because i don't even quite know
like what exactly that means
i don't know how how i would do that you
know
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] macaroni
[Music]
oh thank you i'll take you too
it's my birthday happy birthday
it's your birthday congratulations
employee on strike
what did i do what did i do to make you
so angry that you're striking huh am i
not being a loving tench oh
if you don't love me then why are you
feeding me i know you love me
thank you thank you
i shall happily take you off for
wow that was dangerous i'll take you off
a ring
oh nice nice nice nice
i'm becoming big and fat
[Music]
just like you guys before you go into
the fryer
floor pickle eel
our pickles were never on the floor
before at kfp
gosh i feel so slow
not
i am
i've gained some weight i feel like i
need to play some ringfit adventure
nice to eat you
that's funny that's funny he had not
much attention indeed um i would like
some of that too please hello
i want like some of that mimi oh yeah
oh [\h__\h] that was so dangerous that was
so dangerous i'm scared
[Music]
the curves man
holy [\h__\h]
when he's so big
was i on the ranking yet or was 8 000
not enough i feel like i was close
because these ones also oh my god
there's good ass feet compilation at 8
957.
what
i know i know kanye west
[Music]
i don't know what you mean
i mean i don't know him personally
what
[Music]
it's another one of those jokes
what
[Music]
i saw a clip uh yesterday
i saw many clips yesterday
you know what never mind
screw that topic i will not talk about
the clips that i'm watching
i will keep my secrets
i'm okay with people
no cave people why not
why not
[Music]
why did i do that i thought i thought it
would be the other way around
[Music]
someone killed me near kiwawa oh man i'm
sorry
holy [\h__\h]
goodness feet compilation over 10k
on the leaderboard
what is your secret my secret oh i have
a lot of secrets there's a lot of
secrets
my secret
which secret can we share today
michael
i just want to see shut up michael
he's so unprofessional
you're so unprofessional
[Music]
the killer the killer is getting
aggressive even though he's so small
hi chihuahua hello hello
i'm hungry like i'm legit hungry in real
life so
all these all these uh food
donations don't really help me the real
kia i doubt it streaming
wait why are we streaming here tony i
guess just i guess just because
don't get too don't get too greedy don't
yeah don't get oh don't get too crazy
i want to teach you guys a really cool
um
japanese phrase
uh it's called zamamiron did i tell you
guys about that phrase before
i think it might be internet slang um
i think directly translated it's like
look at look at the state of things i
think
uh but it's more used like [\h__\h]
no it's not used like that it's more
yeah it's like serves you right exactly
i love that
[\h__\h]
yes
yeah just like super [\h__\h] right man
i learned so much from a place further
than the universe is that an anime
cuda speed copulation is number four
all right all right it's time it's time
to how are you always coming back to me
lap tag
and always trying to kill me a bit holy
[\h__\h] thank you
uh
father for the empress thank you i
suppose that means food
oh my god thank you
marry me wawa
no
i cannot marry you because i am married
to this person here the white snake
just kidding
just kidding just kidding just kidding
thank you for giving me uh fun during
hard times oh no problem thank you for
watching my streams at the shitty time
in the middle of the night consume
kiwakiawa you mean i will consume you
oh [\h__\h] it's a battle of
of the great greatest gods
everyone wants to kill me everyone is
out for me
jojo
how is the white snake jojo
see i don't i don't know these
references because i didn't watch jojo
golden um
[Music]
everybody's so cute in snack form we
need a real oh
oh we need a sliver.io game
um but instead of snakes it's chimpkins
and it will be called bok bok dot io
and the chinkins they they grow bigger
and bigger
i mean they all be really round so i'm
not sure how exactly uh it will work you
know
uh
but we can make it work somehow american
lag hello
you're making my cape left too get out
of here
thank you though thank
you can you get me into
uh
if you make your snake red then it at
least looks like a red super chat and
then maybe yes then i'll consider it but
you're currently not even red so
[Music]
if you kill me that's for sure
you're not getting a chew because you
were the reason i died
i am dead once again i have revived once
again though this is only in order to
prove my ability of reviving like a
phoenix
or like a snake in this case
i was number seven just now and died no
i'm sorry for you man
that sounds [\h__\h] tough
oh wow what's going on here hey hey give
me some of that yummy yum
juice who the hell are you you're not
even from kfp
no he'll be getting fb kill him kill him
kill him
oh he's gonna get eventually killed yes
yes who is that who's that is are you on
my side pepino i don't think you're on
my side are you gonna kill me please no
i'm nice if you would know who i am
you would bow to me
please no please no
he doesn't know who i am
maybe we should write my channel url
into my name
spread the awareness of takana
hello hatmo you are so generous
unfortunately ellie's nana is in the way
just like cats are always in the way
thank you oh my god
you know how cats always like stand in
front of your tv or in front of your
laptop your
pc screen
and they mock you they just stand there
and they mock you
[Music]
the smugness of cats
inconceivable
i want that
yes
oh it's getting crowded again many small
snakes
[\h__\h] a collab please
guys are asking for collabs with your
snakes huh
i mean i'm i don't i don't mind
collabing with anyone but
[Music]
i also don't always want to be the one
asking
for it you know
but one collab that will come soon and i
can tell you about right now i think
maybe the first week of february
um the omo cat fashion review fashion
fashion coordination reveal
fashion matchup review or whatever
[Music]
thank you for sharing with me sharing is
caring
yeah
it should happen sometime soon because
we've been seeing a lot of you guys
receiving your merchandise
um probably not all maybe in a lot of
regions how about europe um where are
the europeans
are there any europeans who are
receiving their uh
omaha cat merchandise
[Music]
one of the few italian words that i know
that means fork
not yet uh
nope
uh still hasn't shipped i'm in
california still hasn't shipped i wonder
if there's a pattern of who has received
it and who not
i'm assuming that most people who
received it
are from
i like your name
i'm from um
an a
uh
nothing in southeast got mine live in
the west coast uh-huh got my track
jacket okay well okay still a lot of
people haven't received it i guess but
um
uh
i think it's still a good time to do it
don't want to wait too long you know
i haven't received mine
well even even after the stream you guys
are all welcome to take pictures of
yourself wearing the merchandise
the usual room wall
[Music]
mine was the limit [\h__\h] you i was
writing a comment to beat us
what a german name that is
toby ass
i'm roasting you if you didn't realize
probably not phone calf
[Music]
slippers are too small oh no i'm not
talking about the birthday merch i'm
talking about what was that stream what
talking [\h__\h]
damn it carefree vacation
talking about uh
the omo cat merchandise specifically
the uh whole life english
online myth
oh clothing line with all my cats
talking [\h__\h] you they hate new talk
shows
is that the number one this dude are you
are you uh number one you look wherever
you beat ground but maybe that's just
because i'm so small
[Music]
oh
uh
[Music]
um
what
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
i'm leaving
[Music]
where are my nice kfb friends
hello
how are you doing this is online mode of
course it's online who do you think all
these people are
making
[Music]
are suffering on my channel
i'm red mary's my where's my shoe
the way you're demanding is it it's not
quite right yet you must
you must be a bit more
you know
polite about it
yeah come again with a different name
then you can try again
would you like to bunk against me big
purple snake oh thank
you he's probably really gonna come back
with a new name
[Music]
is toxic
i'm toxic we're slipping under the taste
of your mind i'm
[Music]
don't you know that you're toxic
how have i not sung this sung this song
in uh
karaoke before
i need to sing britney spears songs
i need to sing them
stream dmca challenge oh [\h__\h]
oh sheesh
what's up what's up
what's up
what's up thank you ty dude you're so
sweet always so generous
ah
i'm hungry how long has it been by the
way uh wait has already been what it's
already been an hour and 19 minutes
[Music]
no no bad colonel bad colonel
wait gw2 is that guild wars 2.
hope you'll play guild wars 2
[Music]
oh
guild wars wait what kind of game was
that again
guild wars
oh oh no
it's an mmo oh i remember it but it's
not a game like super old it's so old i
don't really remember like what it
looked like
me too go google it i'm playing it right
now what
what
surprise attention has heard of
gilbert's too well um i come from a
family of gamers
legit
phoenix infinite food
don't don't don't spread that
information it's not true people will
try to eat me
yeah i come from a
from a family of
gamers so i've heard about a lot of
games
i know about a lot of games i just
haven't quite played
so many i suppose
yes i grew up in world of warcraft in
the world of warcraft yes yes i was a
character in world of warcraft
cronies kiana's bath water please
no no kill yourself against my body
come on
[Music]
yeah mama totally enjoyed the death
ropes yes she did um she was she
actually wrote to me
she wrote to me saying that she's sad um
about
the fact that i consider not continuing
to play it
um
but when i say mama mama mama mom mama
um i might still continue it just just
stop not like you know i'm gonna take my
time with it um i might not always uh
hey
[Music]
i might not always uh
what was i gonna say might not always um
might not play it until the end but i
might play it again um not saying that
i'll never play it again i just said i
won't play it until the end probably
because um
it will probably be too difficult
you sounded italian there yeah i yeah my
neighbor is
bam pineapple pizza i say bam you
bam you
oh jfp is here haven't heard about jfp
in a long time that's some old kfp lore
i'm gonna do a develop stream for com
comparison oh
um no
but uh ah whoa whoa when i was close i
heard those tires screeching
who you two
oh his body is still here let me eat his
corpse oh thank you elbow licker is that
what it said
elbow licker
well some people like um weird things
you know we must not judge them too
harshly you want my snack
oh my god that is so yummy holy [\h__\h] who
the [\h__\h] are you get out of here it's my
food
my donation
[Music]
yummy thank you for leaving something
taco stuck in kfb how did you get stuck
maybe uh go ask your priestess that you
pray to
so often how come she's not helping you
huh
how come she's not coming to get you if
you lost
tell me why is why is the priest is not
coming to get you
maybe it's time to
pray to the different priestess just
kidding
he's getting ina
you know probably sent you here didn't
you to spy on me
conspiracy
where's my tinfoil head yeah can't be
put my tinfoil hat on myself on my on my
head so i can think better
my brain works better when i uh
yes
when i have my tinfoil hat on my head
it enables a a better connect holy [\h__\h]
a better connection to
oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god
oh god it's so laggy
it's so [\h__\h] laggy
holy [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] it's like a picture oh [\h__\h] this
is my death my death i feel it my death
is coming upon me or maybe not
[Music]
five thousand seven hundred
man oh man
[Music]
not my fault though
it was too laggy
holy [\h__\h] good sweet compilations number
two and almost number one
couldn't you have chosen a better name
to represent whole life and kfp on the
leaderboard did it have to be that you
could have done such great
advertising
with your potential man
thank you i don't know if you did that
on purpose but thank you i also thank
you to you
boros
i'm i don't have time to eat you right
now but
if the only fox oh i understand
sampling spy
you know it's it's dangerous as a
sapling to get too close to phoenix
you might
you might spark a fire
on yourself
go up in flames
[Music]
what is that what does that say promise
i'm a fan
and why i know because you're always
following me i know you're at least a
viewer but
but you always try to kill me so
i'm not quite sure you're sabotaging kfp
man
choking sweating
jumping so cute you don't even know you
don't even understand the cuteness
eat blue glue
i did eat bluegill yesterday uh it was a
it was a beef burger so don't worry kfp
uh john is still there john is still
alive
uh it was a beef burger with cheddar
a simple cheddar
cheddar beef burger man oh god oh god
oh god oh god
it's already super laggy again
looks better on obs i think
[Music]
absolutely forgotten but it's okay it
was a birthday present
for hook papa
[Music]
john maria i said he's still there
john is still there it was a beef burger
la zaga
what happened to those free
cheese blossoms
and i thought i ate those foods
but that's what i'll be saying from now
on when i eat someone's body
but i'm being eaten too i ate those food
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
that person is not related to us he
doesn't know what he's doing
[Music]
john's been asking my calls that's
because you're calling john without h
i'm talking about john with h
try calling him instead how about that
oh come santina mastery military service
you just finished it nice
congratulations
er
i don't know how to say congratulations
in um korean
i just know happy birthday maybe that's
good enough thank you to gahamnida
enough
that's one way to congratulate you
i i ate those food thank you
you're for once sacrificing yourselves
to me i appreciate that i will remember
[Music]
m
you for coming here
um a lot of a lot of people
i ate those food a lot of people tell me
like um i'll be leaving i need to go to
military
service how about
how about we open uh i mean what about
kp's military service huh
why are you not going to kfb's military
service you would be able to watch me
there at least
wow
sure enough right
we're already booked yeah you've been
born ready
you've been trained well
the usual service
kind of like that
[Music]
we're uh we're actually oh oh man uh
we're actually at the one and a half
hour finish line now
what that was so fast
[Music]
let's make a heart shall we make a heart
your heart though
let's make a heart
you see that you see what i'm doing
see what i'm doing here
i'm making a heart
hearted
i don't know if that if my message was
uh did come across thank you this is the
last run you have to feed me i ate those
food
i ate those food
this is a garfield meme by the way
stream
hell yes do you just
come back with a different stream
something something name each time i eat
those food
[Music]
i've seen you around all the time as
well
thank you
i eat those food
a captain meow i ate those food
oh thank you
be careful
it's coming for you
looking out for my champions always
[Music]
okay uh drink oreo shake um
i don't drink orange shakes that often
okay i had
one uh last month one
[Music]
this is it you guys this is it thanks
everybody for playing slippery today
with me and this is a short stream
because i cannot stream too long today
but we will be reading the super chats
so let's go to my office
you didn't didn't believe me when i said
this will be a short stream did you
you didn't believe me
foreign
to be true
okay let's fix this screen
and that was john bodeland though the
chicken the chicken the chicken in my
hands just now
oh she'll that was john
oh my god i can't copy the url there we
go
that was john so you have proof of him
still being alive
there we go here's chat i expected free
alice well with whip super chat written
we made out there
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
have been uh receiving a lot of
uh pings once again on
on the discord so what do you want to
listen to guys um
i became your food three times today
thank you you have done a good service
to kfb
i was three times on the stream for a
short period good job good job everybody
good job finding me
uh
our challenger sparks
hero pizza you want beat sparks
i don't have a yearbook i have a
european hinotori but that would be
fitting for reading super chats uh
quickly
okay i don't have to be that fast we
don't have to be that person can take
some time so far it's very far from
midnight um
don't worry
and i mean as i know myself i'm probably
gonna take a nap anyway after the stream
tomorrow
and
the lifting super chats
yeah
although we could also listen to
hinotoni um
remixes again
thanks for renewing your membership
welcome
is it here
um
that's not it that's not it
no that's not it
[Music]
what's that
this one
well let's let's listen to hinodia
remixes let's go
this one and this one and
this one
where's my red shift remix
is this it
you guys are not listening right now
right
uh okay
is that that's it right
[Laughter]
[Music]
i think i got it wrong
i can imagine it's like an eat at an edm
concert outside oh man
[Music]
boom
so that that part goes so hard
that far goes so hard i can't help it
[Music]
tell me i can hear it clearly tell me
i've been trying to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me
astray
if i go wrong what awaits me in the dark
could you tell me please where i need to
go
tell me i can hear it clearly tell me
[Music]
show
i promise i will find you
[Music]
wow
oh [\h__\h] so [\h__\h] good so [\h__\h] good
oh
i couldn't hold back i had to sing
[Laughter]
oh sorry
oh oh yeah luke that [\h__\h] hell yeah [\h__\h]
yeah
it's a endless hinotori loop
[Music]
oh
the build-up
the build-up though
oh my god
[Music]
keep on fighting till the day
goodbye there
[Music]
i'm good for a little bit of singing
okay
we gotta we're gonna read super chat
though
that was fun
that was fun but we have to read super
jets
uh
although i don't know if this will apply
today i will try
and we'll read superchat from today's
stream
[Applause]
right i don't have to read them from
yesterday right
what is the name of the song
are you really asking this question it's
my original song hinotori but it's it's
a remix uh that i released on the one
year anniversary of hinodori
unbelievable some people don't know man
some people some people they just don't
know
he lacks critical information
[Laughter]
no it's okay it's okay new people but i
feel like if you get to know kiwawa one
of the first things you have to do is
listen to my music
you hear that you hear the korean
friends korean viewers
listen to my music there's a playlist
with my music on it on my channel
you please be so kind to listen to it
[Music]
was my first original song and uh her
challenger was my second my favorite was
sparks and that was my first english
song and then and then i released three
uh remixes of hinotori and in between i
uh i had a lot of um
a lot of song covers as well yeah yeah
this one is great too
okay there's not that many let for me to
start her john
john is here
and
is this milestones of which the first
super chat of the stream
what do you mean milestone super chat
but yes it is the first one
[Music]
thank
from astrophysics
yeah
and
wait a second
wait a second i started
wait don't wait wait wait wait i started
somewhere wrong i have to start earlier
and logical paradox thank you seven
shinto seven donkey
wait is this really
is this yeah this this must be a start
but how is this person already talking
about the kfb military we're an elite
squad for our boss you're even allowed
to watch kiara and it won't be too
strict i promise
huh
how's this person already
talking about military and later on i
mentioned it
i hope you at least ask tiago if he's
team pineapple and pizza love you my
dearest cutest lovely empress no no i um
i couldn't ask the speed quiz at all
i wanted to change up the questions but
as i said before it was denied and i
didn't feel like
asking it
as a singular solo question
those are from the end
what did they just go to the beginning
for some reason
they it seems like they're kind of mixed
up there
they might be mixed up but i'm sure i'll
i'll read them all
anyway um
[Music]
i still missed out some let me know
i love you too
love you too thank you for your love
[Music]
i'm training some associates for the
next few weeks but so i'll be part of
vod going oh you mean i thought you were
like role playing you mean you're
actually like
training people in rl okay
and i promise to return though otherwise
you can toss me into the coils of kiana
and snake in the usual room have fun
slivering thank you okay
the next few weeks that sounds so long
it sounds like it's gonna be a really
long time
[Music]
i hope you will return soon i will
remember that
uh if you don't come back in maybe like
a month or so i will throw you into the
usual room
yes
please please come back i already miss
you wow thank you for letting me know
though
mr kent's biggest function
[Music]
huh
if you had to make a four-person jrpg
party using only the characters from
jrpg series on your channel who would be
on your team
[Music]
a2
claudia
is she on
and and kisana
cardiovari yeah i know i felt like it
i don't know she's cute i mean we need a
healer you know we need a healer too i
guess she can kind of work as a healer
too but we don't want to use sheen as a
healer
jingle bells rock on tv yeah look at it
jingle bell jingle bell jingle bell rock
dancing and prancing in jingle bell
square
in the frosty air oh ichiban we're
talking about girls i i thought we were
talking about girls only
i guess you didn't specify girls but no
no
help you thank you
i will remember
[Laughter]
[Music]
i think i've heard of that before
scribbling
i think these are from the beginning
we might be back in the real order again
[Music]
ellison thank foreign for the pinky yo i
haven't seen you in the while i can't
kill you now tanja i'm sorry i will only
watch from the sidelines of sunlight
sidelines call it sidelines you were
pretty close to me on a lot of occasions
good luck on getting a big snake i still
remember you scream so maybe one day i
will hear it again
oh it's nice to have you here again
i i remember very well when i was
yelling at you for killing me too often
um
[Laughter]
good old times isn't it it already feels
nostalgic doesn't it
[Music]
singapore good old memories thanks for
the memories even though they were
really great
[Music]
it's been a while
i i liked playing slipper a lot back
then
oh i remember when i was even playing it
privately
i was i think on twitter i let you guys
know that i'm playing sliver go find me
and we were trying i was trying to make
a room but we couldn't find each other i
yeah yeah
we were all just trying really hard oh
thank you
you didn't have to
[Music]
so sweet what's up why are you so sweet
to eat some sugar cubes today
even changed your icon into a snake
wait on twitter did i do that holy [\h__\h]
um oh yes i did
what the [\h__\h]
optimus prime donkey [\h__\h] snake thank
you for the pinky first ever super chat
and this seems like the perfect stream
to do it on it kind of is yeah
thanks for being who you are attention
i'm proud to become a full-fledged
chimpkin tomorrow oh my god now show me
the best snack you can be
i think wait i was like
my biggest snake was about 8 000 today
right that's pretty respectable size i
would say
congratulations already snack on
becoming a big full-fledged chimpkin
does that mean you're going to wear your
uniform you're going to look fabulous in
it
you're going to look amazing in it thank
you for supporting me for so long
[Music]
i appreciate your support
yeah gotta continue working hard at kfp
though to make your attention proud and
i'm gonna try to make you proud as well
typhoon danke and miss vistan kashan
[Music]
even if she denies it happy birthday
wawa what
is that it's not my birthday you guys
know what my birthday is lucky profit
are you from the future i guess you're a
proof that so
i had the puyol arc
put
it
happy birthday it's not my birthday
it's not my birthday
ah no
is there really a video on the top right
members only no it's on a different
person's channel uh if you look up kana
udu k-a-n-a-u-r-u
right
um or if you look up kiana jingle bells
then you will find it had to upload it
somewhere else because um you know
uh copyright calling soon
oh i hope someone will call into my
totsumachi
i hope so
[Music]
this one's so nice too
i probably won't get to play today but i
just wanted to say i love you kiara
become the snake you were meant to be
the largest thank you i tried i became
pretty big today
[Music]
okay
nice of you to stream about my species
motion thank you
14-hour flight where the [\h__\h] are you
going to space
what is your opinion on airports they
always make me stressed or annoyed
yeah
um
i
i've been on a lot of different airports
um
it's
of course always very stressful for me
stressful for me as well
but it also depends on the
it also depends on the airport some are
more stressful than others because
they're more confusing
yeah for example the
edge
how do you pronounce it
the french airport the main one
oh man i i
have at least two occasions that i
remember where i was running for the
airport trying to catch my flight and
crying
about it
cry about it
in before
and before super chat from michael
that's what she said
wait for it wait for it
wait for it
might take a while you know it takes
some time to send a super chat
i'm waiting for it
waiting waiting
waiting
michael come on you can do it
michael i'm counting on you
michael
waiting intensifies
gordon ramsay is so nice of you can you
put some candles on the lasagna you know
what you know what this year on my
birthday i will have a lasagna for my
birthday
or i mean have you seen those cakes
before where you know it doesn't look
like a cake it just looks like something
else that wouldn't be a cake you could
totally probably make a lasagna cake and
have it actually taste like cake but it
just looks like a la zaga
we could have a real lasaga and a cake
lasaga
both of it
main course and dessert dessert is the
real lasaga main course is the
cake
[Music]
for you michael
and then you picked the wrong one there
is no wrong one
[Music]
i did not cancel the bus card yet
it's not a bus car it's just a general
uh public transport card though but yeah
not yet not yet
okay guys let me know if
if he does it
uh michael that's what she said thank
you that's a different one though
um oh wait
he ends now he adds what i said we start
small i guess is the quote
that's what she said
come on
i'll fill in oh thank you venom thank
you for filling in
that's what
she
said oh god
oh god carefully epic fighting
staggering chicken rice down get some
coconut
[Music]
was in my spotify repeat list for the
longest time until sparks unironically
becomes my go-to gym song thank you for
all the originals anyway danjo thank you
for listening to them
i i'm happy to
hear that
people use my music for getting buff
yeah i wish you all the best
just heard your few songs those are
really good thank you
even on topic that super chat is on
topic
it's a nice gym song i agree wow really
maybe it will get me to go to the gym
thank you coconut um i hope you get
strong and big
[Music]
and
um
yes
maybe i'll put out another song that you
can use as a gym song or more more maybe
how about like a relaxed after the gym
song
and ponytail thank you so now resume
i might have been on tv brewing beer or
bottling beer not sure if they used the
footage on tv but at least i got into an
80 video on newspaper a video and
newspaper
brewing beer
wow
well not bad
[Music]
michael that's what she said thank you
says i thought it would be the other way
around
what
black one thanks for the pinky hello
empress of mankind love your streams and
i'm excited for your 2022 project got a
question for you who would you cup it on
have a city around the pool with and
sent to the user room out of all
branches each girl must be from a
different branch
oh okay
oh damn that's that's tough uh
okay let's start with the usual room i
would send to the usual room
[Music]
yeah i'm thinking piccolo as well
[Laughter]
because
you know maybe she'll come out as a
really say so bunny although you know i
love her the way she is so
but it would be interesting to see what
the usual room does to her
la producer oh that's a good idea too
[Music]
let's let's go with uh let's go with
piccolo senpai yes prison time for
piccolo but she already has the perfect
outfit for it you know
yeah
she has the perfect uh outfit for it
then uh a city rendezvous
with
um
and uh caberdon who i would cubadon
wait that will have to be from indonesia
because you said each member from a
different branch
no wait let me change something sitting
around the view with raina and then
covered on i don't feel quite confident
enough to cover it on anyone though
i can't i can't cop it on any of the
girls
if anyone maybe i could copy don't go
down
because she's small and then
she's small
yeah surprise surprise
rival
coming on cronies you can't handle it
no but you guys know i'm actually too
too shy to do these kind of things to
anyone so you know what i will change it
up who i would like to be covered don't
buy and you already know the answer
because i already got cabernet by amis i
will say ame
or hmm
i also would like to be copy don't buy
by everyone in halloween
yeah amelia buffson
best choice
kf penguin thank you for the red super
chat for two actually hello attention
tomorrow is my birthday
oh one of my birthday wishes is to buy
your merch made by akira but akio says
that he doesn't have motion to finish
merch unless he hear you say
if
attention please help me fulfill my wish
love your attention
oh i mean he already has some
merchandise out though now
the the daki makara for example and he
put out uh
um like a
uh takamuri
uh fan art book as well but okay we want
more merchandise i agree with that i
agree i agree wait am i supposed to say
it towards akira towards you
oh
ah
i'll say it
i'll say towards uh
wait are you gonna answer me
[Music]
akira oh
no
ah
oh man
is that okay
is that good enough
hopefully that will get him to work on
more merchandise and fan act
uh it actually continues the super chat
continues with another red one tomorrow
is my birthday yeah you already said
that
chimpkin brain repeats itself last year
you became my aussie i met a lot of kfp
members and taco touches they accompany
me when i feel the world doesn't exist
hope oh i want to say thanks love your
attention watch your stream is my happy
source i hope you will always be happy
bye penguin
thank you i'm so happy to hear that
thank you for your sweet words and happy
birthday to you let me sing for you
happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear caleb's penguin
wow yeah
come here come here
come here
oh okay
you look like a chicken today
[Music]
stay healthy and happy okay take care of
yourself take care of your body
and whenever you're sad you're welcome
to always watch
our streams
yeah we are here for you
thank you for your love and support for
over a year
yeah
that is amazing
you're
amazing love you
alex thank you for the pinky my roommate
received his inaudible cat merch but i i
haven't gotten anything what
you live in the same place and
your roommate got it but you didn't
i believe in it's this conspiracy that
the taco duchess have created he smugly
shows it off to me while i wait for my
amazing kia that's whether can we resume
war did you order that the same day on
the same day
that would be interesting to know
oh man i'm sorry that's weird
that's weird
[Music]
i'm sure yours will come
eventually just gotta be patient for it
i will pray for your sweater to arrive
soon i've seen some people get it
already though with that beautiful
orange color looks amazing
sexy carrots incoming all over the world
everyone will look like a sexy carrot
when the first hour i haven't gotten
anything yet it's really like random
almost like some people from n a got it
some people didn't
[Music]
but now don't go to war with them no
no no no you're you're a roommate of a
takodachi that is actually so cool like
imagine
living together
with a roommate who also really likes to
laugh that's so cool you can like share
your hobby but you know what since you
live together with him or her you can
like spy
on the person and uh then give us some
intel we gotta be smart okay chimpkins
don't always be so aggressive you gotta
think first think first
and then act
so
yeah
i'm waiting for your intel
what's the orange honey of plugs make us
look tasty for paco piccolo
maybe i am
applauding so that piccolo gets food
but what do i get out of it huh what
well no way what would i get out of that
there's
you don't know what i would get out of
it it makes no sense
i'm not getting anything out of that no
no no no no
[Music]
i get to watch that doesn't do anything
for me
no
no no no no i like carrots too
i like eating carrots so raw as well
maybe i want to eat you sexy carrots
maybe i want to eat carrots for a change
and not always chimken
tai chi tanka soon squirrely mustache
duncan don rat cause duncan
now wait there's a
korean friend
[Music]
i recently finished my mandatory
military service so i have a lot of free
time i've wisely decided to spend that
time by watching your streams thanks for
the fun streams and
in korean
[Music]
oh
he makes a japanese korean and german
donkey [\h__\h]
welcome
again congratulations on um getting out
of the military service
yeah how long does that take
i'm glad you finished it and now you
have so much time to watch me
yay
you can watch me every day i'm excited
to hear that
we can make a lot of memories
every day okay 18 months
is that the same person i think that's
the same person
18 months holy [\h__\h] that's long is that
the minimum
oh
it seems so 18 months is like the the
time that you gotta do
that's a long time
but now you're strong and ready to
protect
kfp and kiara your empress right now
you're even stronger hell yeah
carefully recruiting now
thank you for your support
don't worry
try to feed you but died right from
someone else right before oh it's okay
it's the flop that counts
thank you
i have moved here for five years of
service in the carefree armed services
thank you
thank you of course everyone here is a
volunteer of course
you're welcome
advertising
uh i don't know about that one
eat in the turtle
you changed your name because you said
you named wrong once i'm so sorry thank
you
and i am a t
thank you so now i have to refresh uh
now the order will be mixed up again but
there
must have been a few new ones that came
in so let me see
we're almost done i think
okay a logical paradox duncation i might
be reading some of these double
seven three the seventh danger
i read this one i read this one
i don't know if i read this one azure
604 dan kashun jim tracy dangashan type
in
making you dance in the middle of your
office
ah because i was singing
what the [\h__\h] what kind of question is
that
[Music]
of course you can the moment you watch
my streams you are a kfb employee
thank you for the extra pinky fifty
fifty dollars credit for the excess chew
thank you shane you didn't have to as i
said but you already got your kiss
so
you're
welcome thank you soon
thank you for being here today you're
very dead today i wonder why
or actually recently you seem to have
been
dead
dead eating up
that there wearing up
you understand what i'm trying to say
it's difficult to make a verb out of
that word but yeah
and
maybe you maybe you heard that i don't
like uh the tsum tsum that much
character development yeah
that is inspiring
you're repeat let's go
black person dancing skye duncan only
happy birthday super chat it's not my
birthday
unseen dankish and black christian
catchy packaging nice gordon ramsay
vacation
named
[Music]
thank
yeah this is the burger king orders
shake run music
[Music]
before
um
[Music]
foreign
we sent another one thank you for the
pinky this week i could catch many kia
streams because i stayed up late for
work but because i watched kia i fall
back on work more oh no
which means i stay up late the next day
and catch more streams eternal or [\h__\h]
we have figured out another big brain
strategy
wonderful
it's nice to have you around a lot
[Music]
but i hope i hope the work clears up for
you and then you can take it easy
yeah thank you for being so supportive
and generous as always thank you soon
[Music]
and
so as you can see on the schedule here
uh 6 am est
8 pm jst
channel
uh
it will i think it will probably be just
a one hour stream
but i still want to see you guys there
did i save the thumbnail somewhere i
definitely saved it somewhere but i
don't know where it is now
i will be there thank you
what channel the official hello live
channel i'll be tweeting it out on
twitter as well so if you follow me on
twitter then i will notify you guys when
the stream starts
i wonder if the reservation is already
up let me see
[Music]
and this is this is it i'm posting it in
the chat right now
in 14 hours from now
oh man it's so soon huh
oopsie what did i do
what did that oh boy
oh boy
so early
[Music]
don't worry guys it's early for me too
we'll suffer together
[Music]
no problem don't worry about it 12 pm
isn't early stop
i have you know i said i have to be on
standby early i have to wake up like at
9 30.
um
yeah i hope discord won't be a
pain in the ass on uh tomorrow i don't
know recently today as well
uh
when i was in the call today
um i noticed like my internet does
anyone have this problem with discord
because i have
neutral nitrile
and uh still
even though my internet shouldn't be
that bad like i
i used to never have this issue but
recently
when i'm in a call only on discord my
connection goes really really really bad
and when i do a speed test it's normal
but on discord during a call
it gets really bad
even with a uh
upgraded server
same
nothing like that would be weird
happens to me sometimes seems to be
random
depends on what server disk you know
what maybe i should ask discord
maybe i should ask them
if they can help
describe just like that
probably has to do with the server of
your internet isn't the problem that's
what i was thinking
they weren't on in chat yesterday in my
chat really what i didn't notice what
the [\h__\h]
they are here and there often yeah oh
you mean someone else's chat yesterday
were they somewhere else
thank you and everybody
did i miss another super chat
fried screw donkey shin and super frugal
they were in my chat what
yesterday what did i even stream
yesterday i don't remember uh let me see
zelda
what what did they say i missed it
asking if zelda was now your favorite
over window
[Music]
did i answer
did i answer that question
oh my god i'm so sorry at this
man i need to answer them
that's this is a this is a good way to
uh a good reason to contact them so i'll
be like hey yeah this girl uh so sorry i
didn't answer your question yesterday so
actually
uh about your link's awakening question
this and that and then by the way my
connection it's really shitty when i'm
in the call can you help me with that
actually uh
i'll i'll try i'll try because i really
don't know
i don't think it's my internet and it's
especially for like the official
streams on the official channel i feel
really um bad about having such shitty
connections sometimes man
pain also normal everything normal
and
the moment i leave the call
it's uh back to normal
yeah
i mean
obviously i guess
packet loss
wired wired connection which makes it
even weirder doesn't it
[Music]
pc version has been odd lately really
oh man okay let's hope for the best
tomorrow
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay i'm leaving then i'm warming up my
curry my frozen
and i'll eat that sorry for the short
stream today but yeah this is wow she's
really short
thank you anthony
i hope you enjoyed it anyway a little
bit of fun today in sliver.io being
snacks together
[Music]
thank you so neverbody for coming
sorry for changing the plan we'll have
another minecraft stream soon hopefully
but oh my god next week is uh
probably no minecraft either because
i'm busy with link's awakening and uh
probably pokemon
thanks tanjo thank you thank you michael
that's what she said
[Laughter]
will there be a membership stream yes of
course yes yes
membership next week
all right then tomorrow see you on the
official channel and the day after
tomorrow i see on my channel again okay
gonna play r2 no i'm not planning on it
i don't know it doesn't tickle my fancy
but i saw a lot of the ian girls are
planning on it
um
if if 10 out of 11 girls are playing it
then i might join in but otherwise man
black person vanishing fry duncan
okay
and in german we say alfredo then rlp
calm down love you too
literally minecraft is dinosaurs i don't
really i don't know it doesn't look
cute
[Laughter]
i i didn't like the visuals of minecraft
originally either but
i don't know i i got used to it
i accept it now
but arc
why play ark when i have minecraft you
know
[Music]
okay i already said bye bye i gotta go
gotta go
yeah okay oh
you already know my stream is ending huh
hi
hi baby
hi yeah nice stretch kitty cat
my baby
she's so smart such a smart cat smarter
than many of the chickens in this room
bye bye bye bye i'll miss you i will
miss you i'm a bit busy tomorrow after
the stream otherwise i will stream as
well tomorrow but yeah
bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
bye bye
bye bye bye bye
bye bye bye bye bye
bye
[Music]
what's his name again what's the
titanic's guy name again uh uh
jack jack it was jack right jack no jack
jack
jack please jack no no
it's so [\h__\h] cold help me jack
although jack is the one who was
actually sinking i know
[Music]
[Applause]
help me i'm bleeding i'm bleeding i'm
losing blood
oh stop oh i lost my [\h__\h] leg no not
the other one [\h__\h] tickles oh [\h__\h]
stop okay it doesn't tickle anymore it
[\h__\h] hurts ah help me oh
[\h__\h] i'm bleeding i'm ready
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
ah
what
where am i
huh oh oh that feels weird my feet are
growing back why am i why am i lacking
feet
they're growing back
that feels weird
oh
hello
what the [\h__\h] is this place
huh
[Music]
are you
bye-bye guys love you
i remember it i'm sorry i forgot you
know it happens it happens
it happens
let's see
[Music]