[Music]
[Applause]
spicy spicy spicy spicy spicy spicy I
eat spicy food spicy spicy very spicy
okay I was taking a few more bites very
spicy it was
pasta drenched in
[Music]
Tabasco that I found in the tavern oh so
delicious
[Music]
Mar she she just say
Mario is Mario home
oh dear anyways oh hi don't look at that
don't look at that the grand opening
it's about to
begin but you all all of you the voices
in my head that I suppose were in
everybody's head everybody has their own
little voices in their head the vo is in
my head you get first access to Nana 11
the new convenience store that will
rival
fart ever funart has had a monopoly on
the best St for far too
long what has it been a bajillion days
current Jack see that's false that's
that's that's no one's getting
that oh this fake
marketing are you currently capable of
con
conversations I am hello
hello are you are you is this a safe
place to have a a a truthful
conversation I believe so wait hold on
I'll check if there's any cameras or
microphones hold
[Music]
on want name to
be we are good
oh shall we speak in there inside oh I
suppose so sure on Enemy
Lines I guess it is your
territory it is quote my territory
unquote yes MH yes yes first of all what
is your name today how may I address you
today oh
shoot Vivian no I don't I don't like
that one can you can you think of
something else
uh how was Margarita I don't like that
one
either how about Barbara I don't like
that one either what how
about how about um careful careful
careful
careful careful get why must you betray
me every day again and again it's what
going
on hello what's going on what are you
doing in font of Mark what do you mean
am I doing I belong here it is her what
are you doing in font of mar yeah I
suppose I do not belong here I am I
apologize I was uh I'm get out of here
you Heathen I got lost but I cannot
leave what made you think it was okay to
step in
here I I was looking for uh something do
you want to buy something um I was just
checking what you guys have in
stock don't open the door until she buy
something do you do you want to buy
something fiery
one we have
flowers flowers
flowers we
have a chocolate
cake a chocolate cake yes we have many
good things here many many well fish and
chips
up oh okay I don't think you understand
your oh she's gone all right she can she
can do that you're you're right G how
did she do that she's a witch she is a
witch another witch she just used magic
in front of us how could that have
happened there are witches Among Us this
town is riddled with them no but we we
we aren't right we're just part of the
scallet wand yes we are just part of the
SK magic with you do you know how to
make a cake I don't know how to make a
cake I am assuming that you need
actually no I have no clue I have no
clue how to make a cake Absolut like oh
just nope not even an idea why do you
suspicious why do you sound suspicious
when you say that no I just I just had
Dr Pepper from
the that's
all you just it just it makes me sound
suspicious as all oh you're just like a
little bit wound up yes yes yes but not
wait what wound up you said not wand up
I don't have a wand I'm not a witch oh I
want to confirm didn't why would you why
would you defend yourself immediately as
if I as if you're why you why you sorry
it was the way you said it and then I
got very scared that you were trying to
trap me but I wanted I just needed
confirmation that you said wound and not
wand because then you could have trapped
me I thought it was a test a test you
see but we're part of we're part of the
same side are we not we are but I think
it's still okay to you know test
people's loyalty you you never
know okay okay okay okay okay what what
what are you doing in here what am I
doing this is where this is where I come
to think about
things
oh it is the only building scallet want
has so fail points it's where it's also
where I yes hide from the
weather oh it's been raining a lot sour
s sour sorrow s
sorrowful oh yes I could have opened
that door if I wanted to yeah because
you part of the scol one but you're so
kind but you opened it for me thank
you you're welcome this looks cool
what's this what is
this this is Nana 11 the newest
convenience
store you built a communion store right
next to our communion store I did to
help
it oh what's your plan sell me on it so
here is the plan in the market to invest
oh you see you see all right so I
noticed that bomart was Standalone by
itself not really near anything else
that was interesting you are not likely
to have people come just for
fart you need an outlet mall with ample
parking for horses so this is just the
first step I've created another store to
attract people to partaking consumerism
wait what about the restaurant you know
the
restaurant where was that again the
restaurant back there I guess it's too
far it doesn't have very good Yelp
reviews so I I feel oh shoot I didn't
finish building um yes oh oh pardon me
pardon this
there it's okay I don't I'm not even
looking at it I'm looking at the star
front it's okay I'm so embarrassed I
completely forgot about that plan is to
create more customers by creating
healthy competition as I understand it
you could call it I don't know if
competition is even the right word to
draw more people to the outlet mall they
will come upon fart and go oh ho ho and
go inside and buy things then they will
go to na 11 go oh hoo more things and
they will buy things here interesting
when is your official opening it is
right now at this very moment as of this
moment it is it is complet
customer it is
completed
yes grand opening yes you can be the
first
customer
okay what do you want we have the finest
highest quality meat in all of the
Kingdom as well as the juiciest of
berries
can how about to you can I have
a hello
oh oh my goodness so many customers so
many customers I'm going to be
rich I much money so you're not getting
anything from me that is okay you have
free
will this is what is this this is Nana
11 Nana 11 yes the sister store TOA Mar
but they are not
related oh this St is not
related we offer the finest highest
qualty Meats as well as the juiciest of
berries we also have can I have six
berries please you can have six
berries six berries six
berries oh what has happened part this
is very inappropriate I'm so sorry oh I
don't know if a horse should be close to
food like that did not mean to pull the
horse do not worry the food is all
protected inside of these barrels where
nothing can contaminate them h crey
freebies yes we do offer freebies H in
fact a freebie from fart in fact nothing
here cost any money everything is
free what are you sure yes that is very
yes it is here let me let me give you
your
berries and then I can assist you with
berries 1 two
three six I don't know it's free
it's free it is free for
free I got some
beries and also did you want a free
Berry I would love a free Berry oh you
would like a free Berry hold on there
there is there is a que there is a
queue go the bow bows do you want a
free she's a ghost what happened to her
for
you are you a ghost thank you for your
business can I get more berries you can
get more
berries oh there it is yes I was killed
by Shakira you can
have in the last in the last not my
stream but her
stream what talking about I mean
yesterday yesterday she killed me and
she killed I'm so sorry there was ghost
whispering in my ear what is it that you
said is this a good business for you so
far it has been you are my second
customer it's going so well I would like
to be revived you have meat too I do are
you hungry for meat yes the highest
quality of meat Rive me so I was on my
way just don't ask no it's already
cooked just don't ask where it came from
okay I will eat my all right oh shoot
not again
pardon me I'm so sorry you had to see
that there is ample supply all the
barrels all the barrels are
full they're overflowing yes with meat
and
Berry that looks good here you go than
you you're welcome thank you Nana 11
you're welcome spread the word we are
now open
yes thank you for your patronage good
Bye b bow B bow B
bow where did the other customers go
they got distracted there are too many
distractions in this world I tell you
they got distracted they were supposed
to do business with me now they're all
huddled together
look now there's so many of them oh but
why I don't feel
comfortable oh
I suddenly feel the most comfortable I
felt since coming to this world why is
that
why I wonder I'm going to put these away
I don't need those right now oh voices
in my head oh audience
or my
subscribers and my viewers well if
you're a viewer and you're not
subscribed what are you are you doing
smash that subscribe button smash that
like button I will show you what the
mystery meat really is because you yes
you are so special so special never
before
seen the mystery meet
[Music]
is oh it's all it's all done in the oven
I
think oh just kidding oh
oops it's all
cooked it is the stain the stain that
they Feast
upon the gray meat that turns a
brilliant Brown once
[Music]
cooked don't tell
them don't tell them it is truly the
highest of quality but still a bit Taboo
in these lands to eat them but you see
eating their meat can spread
Madness but it is also good it is also
delicious hello hello hello
hello dang
[Music]
it I will also tell you all since none
of the others are here oh no I'll go
tell them oh no I'll tell you all first
we also have a lottery system not not
copying fom
art we have a lot system let me show you
the ticket I'll give you all first
look I forgot to have the ticket in my
pocket it's
okay here we go this is the lottery
ticket and it is completely
free a lottery ticket a free ticket and
you can win a 100 coin prize
and there are 30 winners every day it
has first come first serve so the first
30 people will get 100 coin
prize yes that is how this
works
mhm sorry I rounded a bit 20 winners
there can be 20 winners I'm sorry I
messed it
up 20 winners within one day first come
first surve first first 20 get the 100
coin prize and win the
lottery isn't this is SC no this this is
it's just for show to show you that you
can get coins if you're one of the first
20 to
purchase what a deal indeed what a deal
indeed let's see let me put it here oh
nope I'll put it here there we go ahuh
no no I don't like it there it can go
here no
[Music]
yes cune
disgusting Al righty Al righty are they
still there I'm going to gather
confidence and face my fears of
socialization and go share my lottery
ticket with
them wait no I want them to come here oh
wait they might be they might be
observing the thing that bi Boo has done
do they know that it was bioo that has
that did this do they know that she is a
double agent or is she a double agent no
she just wants to destroy
everything and the foolish bioo confided
in me to join her but little does she
know that I want to be the true
protagonist the true hero and I will
defeat her so that I can have dibs on
everything I will not snitch right
now not at this moment I'm concerned
that they are distracted and they are
doing something else I don't want to
distract them from what they're doing
for I know the pain of being
distracted but I do want them to learn
about my lottery system oh my goodness I
had the opportunity to Center that and I
did
not let's see what they're
doing not working a phoenix F does not
reved a person it takes a few seconds
have patience for Life hello everybody
what is going on what is the
conversation topic
ghost trying to we're trying to save the
ghost you're trying to save the
ghost we're not quite ready for re yes I
wanted this as well I wanted her to be
saved so that I could use her to my
advantage shall return what what is your
advantage what is it that must be done
to save her why did you say it like that
loser say what where did the ghost go I
am not sure she just you cannot trick me
loser said what loser said what cannot
know what plan is now loser said it
loser said it before I said
[Music]
it what you need to speak to me
about do you know how to unin visible
her uh she is a ghost currently and um
if she uses my fed at the right timing
when her life and her heart is ready to
return then it will take its effect and
then we can see her beautiful face yes
but one cannot be impatient because the
impatient ones are not capable of using
the Phoenix Powers oh I see I see so you
you are you're very patient
then I I am or in this yes I see but she
it it seems to be her first time so she
is uh a little bit too excited about
regaining her life energy oh I see you
must calm her down ah well she ran away
so you must run after
her but our conversation was not
finished yet oh yes what were we
discussing um oh your plans about uh
perhaps returning to ambercoin
officially I am an ambercoin but they
don't but they don't know it yet but
when are you going to let them know once
my master plan is fulfilled I'm
receiving a
call oh hello hello hello hello feathery
one I'm trapped in The Gallows since you
are a member of the Scarlet wand can you
help me oh because I have a member of
the Scarlet wand she needs my help wink
wink I will go help
her I will go help you why did you say
may be in need of help I had sh hand in
my eye oh that is very dramatic in the
gravel you were also kind enough to
bring
me yeah remember that wasn't that nice
that was so nice where are The
Gallows uh right behind
fart oh okie
dokie what the heck
is what is this how can I be of
assistance I'm trapped and how do I
release you uh I think you can go up and
give give me a
hand
help I'm here to
help have you tried turning it off and
on
well okay let me
try take my hand and reach for the
screen I'm trying I'm trying I'm trying
I'm trying oh
dear um can you per chance craft me uh
wait I can make myself one second oh
maybe I can make stairs you can do it St
can do it you can do
it you D I have your emotional
support you are
capable oh yes I think I'm doing it I
think you need one more set of stairs
perhaps or maybe two or maybe three just
going to destroy this want to leave
anything here what if you push the
stairs back a tiny
bit oh just kidding you don't need need
that how
efficient oh thank you so much for
helping me you're welcome I'm so glad
that I was nearby and able to
assist thank you why do
you what do you what do you you know
what I feel like I can trust you you can
trust me you can you you have been
nothing but kind nothing but supportive
of the faart of the Scarlet want I'm
about to get Kinder you see really yes
you can we go to Nana 11 oh yes my
second favorite store N1 oh we'll change
that in due time do not
fret H oh ouchie hello no hello may I
offer you a lottery ticket it is
free it is free the first 20 the first
20 people who take a lottery
ticket
win what's the price 100
coin I'm
in but it is you're in all right oh hold
on the exchange is a bit more under the
table oh yes let's see what on a second
I hold on a second do you want me to go
onto the table or no no no no no no I'm
I can hand it to
you here you go here is your lottery
ticket winners will be announced in
about 2 2 hours and 15
minutes okay 911 Lottery 100 coin price
let me just put this uh here so I have
it safe in my hand yes one moment please
MH
oh my tickets yes I will not tell you
where you are in the number of people
who have
entered is it like the first am I the
first you could be one of the first 20
but you may also not be that's part of
the gamble you may not be one of the
first 20 oh that's the gamble that makes
a lot of
sense what's your name again right now
junior is it still Junior I'm I'm
accepting uh nickname
recommendations uh since your store is
called Nana 11 how
[Music]
about
Nana how
[Music]
about oh wait that had a nice string to
it what was it m m m m
m n n namu May nanu
nanu nanu
nanu namu not I yes that feels right how
does it make you feel it it feels so
correct right yes wonderful you have a
name thank you I am not I have to say
I it's been really nice doing business
with you I would like to invest in your
store so if you have open tell me let me
know okay if we have an open position I
would be more than happy to take you in
no I meant like openness in like in the
stock market oh in the stock market oh
my well at this time we are not public
but okay that's okay well let me know
all right fiery
one greetings it seems like another
store has opened in town another store
has
opened would you like to purchase
berries I am selling berries the
juiciest of berries and the highest
quality of meat we also have a
lottery would you care for a ticket the
ticket is free completely free what a
deal I would love to take a lottery
ticket from you if I may have one of
course it is first come first serve
first 20 members are the winners but I
canot not tell you where you are in the
queue oh I have a good feeling with this
so I think I will give it a try all
right I'm sending you your lottery
ticket handing it under the
table we have to it's on the down though
you
see
what what on What Che under the table no
no not it's a figure it's it's quite
literal and it's
[Laughter]
figure and I see how it is oh
oh wonderful let me I think I can see it
now MH oh it came through under the
table yes oh 100 coins for
free if you win if you're one of the
first 20
people the gods are on my side today for
sure
is this going to be tomorrow no it's
today it is in an hour and 12
minutes wonderful I shall shall I be
here in this vicinity when it happens
that would be most uh convenient for me
oh I'm so sorry weit don't do not I'm so
sorry wait wait the green one come back
my math was incorrect I meant to say 2
hours about 2 hours but it is truly an
hour and now 11 minutes oh goodness I
will send her I will send her ad mail
and then she will yes no okay yes she
will understand oopsie doopsy well
you're so generous for doing this free
Lottery yes I also have free things
everything here is
free we have the juiciest of berries and
the highest quality of meats can I
interest you in either or both Perhaps
Perhaps some more juicy steaks would
suffice I'm sorry I'm so sorry what did
you say some juicy steaks will suffice
juicy steaks all righty how many do you
want M perhaps about 20 20 Okie doie 10
I do not want wish to be greedy in this
uh Char okay you want 10 open your mouth
please must I eat them all at once 5 6 7
9 I appreciate your donation donation no
this isig
business okay do you accept
donations what do I look like a charity
case here what an insult what an insult
to think I would need
donations there's no no one around us
right now I just want to help you there
is there is a person behind
you
hello I heard theion that you will buy
my items that I don't need anymore you
this this isn't so gave a telephone that
went wrong I'm not doing that what oh
you
are if I ask nicely will you you want
cuz I have a very very uh wonderful
wooden axe and a wooden pickaxe has been
well loved like could use a new home and
your home looks like a good home for
them right sure what what you sure I'll
take that what's that what was that just
now maybe I should make one wooden
wooden tools at this day and age I don't
have much money so I I would expect some
money for my well- loved items oh I'm so
sorry but there is a recycling fee it is
one coin per
item
never never mind that doesn't sound good
can I interest you in the juiciest of
berries or the highest quality of
meats they are free they are free
berries
yes this sounds SK
it is not what's what's in it what's in
it berries and meat what I can confir
her foods are very delicious and I have
had my tummy full of it the ju the
berries I have a lot of things though a
moreu is always looking for food maybe
she'd be interested she already took
some oh really yes you can trust me it
is completely free nothing weird is
going to happen absolutely nothing weird
is going going to happen I'm not she's
just of good heart believe her I'm not
I'm not going to feel sleepy right no
you will not no no I don't know
something's funny about your voice there
is nothing funny about my
voice I'll give him my I don't know I'm
getting we really deep down would you
like to know the secrets the reason why
it is free okay why the reason is
because we are in competition with the
faart and the fart prices are just
simply not fair so we have lower prices
to encourage people to come to this
establishment they have they have ruined
the economy in our lands and she is
merely trying to fix them I'm here to
balance everything out and the juice is
free the berries and the meat you can
make it into juice I could do it for you
oh oh I'll accept the juice the juice
wait do you want the meat to become
juice or the berries to become juice I
would like berry juice berry juice
okay all righty I chewed them and made
it into juice would you like some okay
I'm not too sure of how hentic that is
but I'm very
clean here I'll I'll throw in an
extra not enough room I have enough room
that's okay really really that's okay I
can hold on to them or you know
what I will take one of your wooden
tools oh really to encourage you to come
back and see me
again okay to take more berries or
perhaps get a taste of the juiciest of
meats take this you can take you can
take this just one just
one just one okay
yes pleasure doing
business
a thank you oh you're behind there now
too well it doesn't look so scary in the
yes aren't you both wearing the same
hats aren't you both working for the
same guilt you should be able to trust
her no I I received this H from Jonathan
you know oh Jonathan with a G yeah it's
only kind to wear a presentent you can't
right be happy indeed indeed
before you go seem like this hat is a is
a proof of someone's uh realness I
changed the conversation topic too early
oh God I'm so embarrassed I'm so
embarrassed what what what's wrong
before you go can I interest you in a
lottery ticket it is completely free
first 20 people who take the
ticket win we said it's free it is
completely
free I cannot tell you where you are are
in the queue but first 20 people who
take the ticket will win oh I high don't
worry about it this Lottery there is no
scam involved there is no risk at all
why do you say it like that that's very
scary no it is true I have bought a
ticket as well and received it safely no
I've seen what kind of things um M has
been up to but you're not spending any
money you're not spending any money
there's nothing that you are losing
thank you for the juice
ba paow
well higher chance for me to win I
suppose exactly I appreciate you helping
the business by encouraging more people
to take yes oh oh I'm on a excuse me
good luck with your endeavors I shall
support it when you need me thank you
thank you lady of the oranges
[Music]
goodbye I do understand why h of w would
not take the lottery ticket after seeing
what happened to her dear sister moo of
Co I do get it I should not have
pressured her
so anyways now what do I
do the customers aren't coming to me
perhaps because there is not a parking
lot and this is not a very walkable City
you kind of need a horse to get around
here makes sense perhaps I I will go and
find customers
myself I have the lottery tickets with
me so this should be fine let me make
sure I also have samples
of stained
meat and sweet berries the juiciest of
berries all righty oh perhaps I could
entice this one paron
me hello hello I've just opened my new
establishment Nana 11 yes it was so
pretty but I heard you doing it for free
yes everything is
free why doesn't make sense because we
are in competition with fart and we need
cheaper prices to encourage people to
come to our establishment that's right
ours it's Amber
[Laughter]
coins well you know what I think you're
right it is there something I can
associate with you know what we should
do oh what should we do I have got an
idea to be very competitive oh what what
follow me oh
okay oh my goodness what could it
be I give you in a second oh okay okay
I'm very patient I learned to be I
wonder what this is supposed to be
what's this what this oh yeah I think
it's just like ingame building I I think
really oh it's just there yeah
interesting this static I think oh I see
it's outside the
line yeah I lost my stuff by the way I
don't find them
anymore which which which things
something I want to give
you well I lost all my diamonds
that might have been
me I have no it might have been me I
have diamonds I will give you some hold
on I wanted to give it to you bro I have
I forgot I took your diamonds I have a
lot of diamonds I will give them to you
no no no no I don't want it what it is
you have diamonds now here he hear me
out this is my plan okay what's the plan
you sell diamond
for one coin each and that's how you get
very competitive in the market oh my
gosh that's so smart I only had food and
lottery tickets available but offering D
oh my goodness take the diamonds back I
will take them back oh that is genius
you are you you are a genius you I know
all right oh can you please go and let
the folk know that we are now offering
diamonds on top of the juiciest of
berries and the highest quality of meats
as well as a lottery ticket can you can
you let people know okay wonderful
wonderful everybody know would you like
a lottery ticket it is completely free
and the first 20 people who take one
win yeah I won it okay I will hand it
over to you one second thank you hold on
a second just a second oh I spelled your
name WR a very good deal actually it is
is it
not here is your ticket
[Music]
oops on the down
though it is it is not it is within a
realm of uh a realm full of
Discord yeah got
it got it nice thank you you're welcome
thank
you to give you any number or anything
nope I'm just keeping track of who the
first 20 really are I can't tell you now
I reveal it to you within an hour what
I'm going to win if I win you will win
coins that's actually good isn't it
isn't it
Grand thank you so much I think you're
very competitive right now I am I'm so
competitive good luck selling your
diamonds thank you I will win I will win
you will win of course I'll be there
because I have a plan I need to marry
the
old the queen so I'm going to prepare a
message for her right now so I'll be
around for a bit okay you should you
should write it under a
tree yeah I think I'm going to do like
right there yeah it'll be romantic yeah
that be R yeah under
thee
yeah
yeah all
righty oh my goodness she's so
smart free diamonds
[Music]
so
smart oh wait a minute I missed that
[Music]
up just organize it before I head
out oh need more berries
[Music]
huzzah
huzzah okie
dokie oh I'm so excited this will be
marvelous let me put this Stone away yes
it is completed
excellent all right all right I don't
like how this is organized right now
hold
[Music]
on doing the work for Miss FU oh that's
not how that works here we
go
oh I can't read fast enough dang
it oh dear cannot read her face ah
shoot okay before I go let me organize
myself yes yes I'll put this there
yes I don't think I need the
map I remember where things
are I do need to ensure I will have
enough
money if for everybody that enters I
think I will as you can see I have a lot
of
coins oh my gosh she just ran over me
and bow
bowed oh hi hello n oh hi how are you
doing how's your storming going it's
been going very
well I've had lots of customers and I've
given out a certain amount of lottery
tickets oh is it is it I wonder how many
it is if only I knew it's okay you
you'll know in an hour I'm so sorry I
made a mistake I said 2 hours but I
meant 1 hour it is going to be 57
minutes from now it was an honest
mistake that's okay I I'll put on an
alarm um now would you like to oh yes I
was going to let you know since you are
a valued customer and I love you that we
are now offering diamonds for
sale diamonds for sale yes I would like
to buy one please one Diamond you got
it how much is it it's
free
free thank you for doing business with
us
me yes now what is it thank you for
thank you for oh I was going to ask if
you wanted to try out the new um games
that have since yeah I want to see the
new games
okay I I already checked out one in the
skull in our base uh should we try that
one first yes sure okay uh take me
away
here
[Music]
name no voices in my head I could not
make it one coin that would go against
everything that the store stands for it
is all supposed to be
free ow ow ow oh careful in there oh a
no oopsy
hello here go what is the
game it's this talk to this guy SC
Scarlet gep or gatekeeper Scarlet G
keeper Scarlet
gatekeeper yeah he must be a gatekeeper
that's me I'll read the the
rules okay mind I any player who wishes
to participate can press the join game
button when the first player who joined
presses the start game button all
players to join will automatically be
transported to the play area and
C you will see a canvas with a pattern
of colored tiles on it and you will have
3 seconds to memorize it then the canvas
will be blanked out and you will be
given Dy it Ed the dies to color the
canvas in the exact same pattern you'll
get one point for every correctly
colored tile and a bonus for every
correctly colored full canvas the
pattern will increase one level of
difficulty for every canvas you complete
correctly if you color a tile
incorrectly you'll have to take a score
penalty and the game will skip to the
next question the difficulty will also
go down one level you have two minutes
to get as highest score as possible I
saw something similar but I think it was
with numbers and it had a
chimpanzee in in here not oh no not here
oh I saw it on when I was out and about
the other day
oh okay nice well I've tried it once
earlier um so should we play yes let's
play do we work together or are we
against each other no we are against
each other we must but it's just a
friendly game it's a friendly game oh
yes I I'm putting my competitive spirit
away
okay I'm
ready okay I'm starting the game are you
ready I'm
ready okay where the D wait
okay they will be in our hand once the
timer is over I
see my mind's eye is
activated oh I didn't see the last one
um oh
no okay never mind
[Music]
shoot what dang
it oh my gosh she's on green oh no no I
[Music]
miss how
embarrassing red green yellow
red green
yellow
what I'm losing no are you distracted me
you distracted
me I will not speak you're not
speak red
yellow it was
always all
yellow green yellow oh I clicked in the
wrong one
oopsie why I say
yellow red
green there's one more wait wait where
was the last one I don't remember dang
it red yellow
red red yellow
red it's okay oops keep on the WR
maybe I need to step back oh just
kidding
oh it was close it was close super close
that was really
close because like you you're kind of
close to it and then you have to like
step back and take it in and then go
back inside I know I should have stepped
back more I think I was too close to it
the entire time good game good game you
want to try again one more one more one
more one more okay okay let's try
again how was how do I I have no clue
where that other green one
was
no did I not yeah I did okay I'm
starting the game okay okay
okay may the memory strongest memory
begin a win yes yes
yes red
red red red
[Music]
red
yellow but was all
[Music]
yellow oh wait oh shoot oh shoot I
messed
[Music]
up dang
it what I'm doing worse than before
[Music]
dang it
red this is hard that was
yellow I want to rematch right now I
messed up wait we have to finish this
one okay I want to rematch okay okay
[Music]
right is
annoying no I didn't mean to press one
get me out of here get me out of here
get me out of here there isn't even I
lost so badly there's nothing left for
me what what what
what it
glitched it glitched yeah there was
nothing oh you don't get anything
anymore I see it well now there is oh
but then I pressed
[Music]
it I can't remember I I already forgot I
I I forgot which color that was oh no I
forgot which color it was oh which color
was ah
unfortunate I made very unfortunate I
made some mistakes but I want to do one
more okay okay let's do one more once I
want do one more
of mistake
okay okay I'm I'm ready I'm overclocking
now now I'm focused I'm not I feel like
my focus is
deteriorating drink more of that pizy
drink that you talked about earlier I
already drank half of it I must save the
latter half for
tomorrow okay stting
easy why is it over there easy easy so
easy easy easy easiest game of our life
easy
easy how far was it oh
shoot red red green okay no not okay not
okay I don't remember
[Music]
where was it no I don't remember who the
last one was red red red
yellow red red
red yellow was it up here or here dang
it it was up there
ah very hard
game especially harder because of the
color difference in the middle the
green the green pains me
so I don't
[Music]
remember yellow I don't remember I
wasn't paying
[Music]
attention what I didn't let my
M mistakes were
made my sensitivity was not
great it's about speed I think it's all
about
speed
speed wait I wasn't paying attention
it's all
about give me a redo give me a redo it
should it should calculate some of our
some of our what oh it's yellow oh oh my
gosh I was so lucky it's red oh I don't
remember uh I don't remember I don't
remember uh oh I don't remember either
oh no you win oh no oh I win this
time oh you won dang it I only win I
mean this this was the determined
determining game I have the great ter of
memor rematch rematch rematch rematch
rematch rematch okay rematch okay okay
rematch now it's one well the first one
didn't count since I had played the game
and you hadn't and then one time I won
and then one time you won and now this
is the final match okay okay real last
last go this one is the final one okay
okay okay okay okay I'm ready I'm ready
we don't get any money for this do
we that's okay I'm not greedy I'm not
greedy I don't need any
money on my end it says you haven't
joined what oh it's me that has to start
it you have to start I start oh okay
okay good luck Good Luck Good
Luck be the one with greater memory and
less Amnesia win
I feel like we're in disadvantage at
this game to begin with I know this
isn't fair my head still hurts made this
to scam us yeah my head still very UN
about my character still feeling the
effects of being
bonked
mhm what was
it oops okay this is where this is where
I don't remember
[Music]
I no I forgot already
I remember yellow green red yellow
yellow green oh what was it yellow
green red
yellow
no yellow
[Music]
red shoot I don't remember
no R
R I was not paying
attention where were these
ones no
[Music]
I don't remember I don't
remember I need to go fast I wasn't
paying
[Music]
atten I don't oh there we go oh my
goodness oh my goodness
[Music]
good game good game no I disagree I'm
playing do you want to play you want to
play again you want to play okay okay
let's play again okay okay okay okay
okay this time we should shake hands
before I think so yes wait shake hands
shake
hands oh shake hands yes that's
that's okay okay okay okay let's try
again okay okay okay I I did you ready
up uh I am ready okay
one
more one more one more Amnesia be damned
we can do
[Music]
this I done goofed a little bit
I don't
remember
okay ah I don't remember oh this one's
hard don't remember
red
[Music]
green what I was on the wrong one I
tried to GRE what am I did pay attention
to that one cuz I was so
CE CeCe I was so mad at myself I didn't
pay attention to the next one to the
next one
yeah I think that was dumb that was it
was my ah it was my my scrolly wheel not
working where's my scr
wheel um maybe you can use one and two
instead 1 2
three that might uh it might just be me
it's just a me
problem ah ah that was me going too
[Music]
fast that's embarrassing that's so
embarrassing I want to play
alone don't say that don't say
that don't don't say that are you ready
do you want to play again yes okay
okay this is an AR silence silence no
distractions no distractions okay okay
okay I'll be quiet I can't get used to
not
scrolling silent silence
[Music]
hello pure
concentration no oh you guys are playing
games red yellow oh
hello hello how do you play this
game uh we shall show you once this
round is over dear Knight the
destraction
why does she's distracting me she's
distracting me she's distracting me
she's distracting me she okay what is
going on she's distracting
me um is she is she okay I think she's I
think she's fine yeah I think it's just
that oh I see you're distracting her
maybe oh she sounds like she's on the
verge of tears she
distracted I mean it's a very tilting
game to be fair a very tilting game
she's distracted she's distracted me is
she going to
cry yeah maybe if you push a little bit
more I'm already
crying do not fret fra I'm will be her
name is by the way Nana yeah she I'm
fretting I'm fretting I'm fretting I'm
FR nice to meet you n I'm fretting so so
much right now there is too much to fret
about oh the fretting is so is so oh how
I oh how I F dear oh no do not cry you
are almost there no do not you so close
oh damn
it are you
okay it is nice to meet you n hello it's
is nice to meet you just here what is
the name of that who distracts me oh yes
my name is Jonathan G hello Jonathan G
thank you it's a pleasure to meet you
just just
if you say so Jonathan G would you like
to join us in our battle I would love to
see your your game how do you play uh
you should read the rules just so you
prepared properly rules mhm
it's 3 seconds to memorize it oh well I
will just guess let us
go
okay you signed up I have signed up
should I press Start you can press start
May the most iest win wait where
hats messed
[Music]
up who are you talking to
dang
[Music]
it are you doing it humble kn
are you succeeding I'm doing I'm doing
okay but I do
forget I was thinking of what she was
talking
about it's very
triggering very triggering I don't
remember I think so yeah I believe
[Music]
to become a little bit more intelligent
with time I think it's called
training I didn't mean to
do yeah we always want to be on our
smartest you know we always strive to be
see it's glitching oh no it didn't
glitch it was me not processing what was
happening that was me that one was me
[Music]
I was listening to her say
things you have to blend it
out of course again there were too many
distractions there were too many
distractions what distractions were
there did you not hear the green
one what no I was just answering to her
she was bobbling the entire time oh I
couldn't hear her phone I couldn't hear
this one yes we were too far apart
talking the time
I'm getting another phone
call
yes okay I'll try not to talk if we next
to each other this time no it's okay you
can talk no I will block you out I'll
block you out okay ready ready very
point I don't know if G I mean Jonathan
is ready Jonathan are you ready ready
Jonathan yes I am ready
okay I'm in the middle again sorry
[Music]
uh so far I've only played this I got a
lottery ticket from Mo uh nanu and
that's about it
oh yeah I haven't really done anything
oh wait I got a cake for the
princess
yay
what what's why did you say it like
that
oh okay we have to we can't let her win
uh nanu this is I'm going to lose
it I swear if she wins I'm going to
kill her
I'm going to kill her I'm going to kill
her I'm going to kill her her
multitasking abilities are too strong
her multitasking is too strong it's too
strong she's too strong she's too strong
I hate
[Music]
her I was I was trying to focus and
talking to myself to hyp psych psych
myself
[Music]
up oops clicked on the wrong one
mysterious I was paying attention Okay
okay okay
she I'm trying to psych myself
up onion like
[Music]
things dang
it shut up
hat
you I made
you I I wasn't talking to you I was
talking to myself because I'm so
disappointed in my performance oh I see
I see well well you should you click on
this person you speak to this person and
then you press you let him know that you
would like to join the game paron me
Jonathan G yes pardon me I have opened a
new establishment called Nana 11 and we
offer the juiciest of of berries and the
highest quality of of of meat and we
also have a lottery it's free to enter
and I would love to enter your lottery
would you like to enter the lottery
first 20 people who enter
win oh what have I won I well you don't
you don't know if you've won yet oh I I
highly recommend her Services all right
you I will give you a ticket hold on I'm
pulling it out of my pocket they are
very profitable have to go up to
that I am looking forward to
it here is your
ticket I also got a ticket now you all
have tickets ticket yay in only 31
minutes won't the lottery be pulled it
will in 31 minutes y wonderful
be sure to meet me at the N 11 where I
will announce the winners I will see
there with great haste in 30 minutes
will you be here playing this game in
the meantime no I think that it's
rigged
oh yes beware this game is rigged oh I
want to give it a try sometimes you
don't have the color that you think you
have and sometimes you don't scroll
enough or sometimes you scroll too much
and it is not your is not your fault it
is the fault of the game than a scalid w
and sometimes they I know we're not
perfect none of us are perfect it's okay
but just but just be aware that
sometimes also it says that the blocks
are in one spot but and then they move
them somewhere else so it tricks you
making you think you just have really
bad
memory I see what oh there is treachery
of in this Guild in this Guild
Hall it's not Trey everyone makes Mist
Hest mistakes human
error yes we aren't robots here you
should try one more time I will not be
entering I will be allowing um Miss
Shakira to enter so I would like to see
you guys I will stay quiet I promise one
more time you you can play I don't I
don't have
to hour play as well I would one more
time you do not want to play against
lady
Shakira play against lady Shakira
Shakira
Shakira well I am a beginner in this
game I I I I I'm not sure yet of how to
play it but is everyone ready I'll play
with anybody you I'm ready ready to be
distracted and to be rigged no I'm not
rigged to experience uh other other
world other rigging what yes yes yes how
terrible maybe you should submit a
complaint are these not your guild
leaders no I I will put a note and let
them know that it's out of order it
needs to be fixed yes yes yeah maybe we
should do one more try so we can like
really test if it's out of order or
what's the problem you know B
reporting whoever did the first one has
to start the game it wasn't me oh oh
oopsie oh okay
begin May the best memory win
[Music]
so you have been playing this for 30
minutes green
one yes yes I have been and you would
say that your memory is quite
good uh no no no not think it is fun but
I saw it's fun but I'm not that good but
I saw that you had gotten the high
score oh yeah but then you beat me I did
not beat on your first try or your
second try no oh yes I did not beat your
high score I do not remember okay well
then maybe I like maybe I have good
memory then you are yes maybe you do
have the greatest of memories I do not
remember thank you for fling me like
that yeah maybe you do have the greatest
memory I would like toate to your
library okay I'll take it in a bit is it
this one or this one thank you yay what
did you put in your cake today I can't I
could not focus at all on strawberry oh
I lost it on that one oh for the
princess oh I completely lost it the
princess do you think she will take
it I don't know she's been kind of weird
to be honest I tried talking to her and
she did like this really weird thing and
like vanished Into Thin Air it's been
quite weird it has been a little strange
you do not sense that something is
different what I definitely know
something's different but I don't know
what and no one's talking I told me
what's wrong and everyone's confused as
I am apparently yes it is quite very
confusing maybe you have some
information you could share with me at
the library in a bit yes in the library
in a bit in the fart Library I assume
yeah yeah The Great
Library that was R see that was rigged
that was rigged it was rigged it was
rigged that was rigged it had me press
it was
not what a terrible do you think that is
the green one rigging it she seems to be
beating everyone no because you beat me
earlier why are you constantly against
me Jonathan what have I done to you I am
not I am not I was just a was a my again
again again again again again again it
is certainly rigged because I have
failed yes only then you can play this
time Jonathan I'll watch
myed again again again again did you
enter let's play two games at
once who game which other game shall we
be playing the quiet
game the what oh the client G the C game
a very hard game what does the loser
what does the loser have to do the loser
there needs to be a punishment does need
to be a punishment wait why but why why
why does there need to be a playing this
game in this round and then you are not
even you are going to enforce a
punishment when you're not Oh I thought
I I have to be quiet as well okay I
won't be quiet ready ready ready ready
are you have you sign up I have I have
signed up yes ready ready ready I shall
participate in the
quiet we are going to participate in the
quiet
game I guess we are not allowed to speak
it seems that n a mood do not want us
speaking for do you hear me from here do
you hear her
nanu do you hear them are we playing the
quiet oh we are failing it's a quiet
game I did not mean to okay Miss nanu
was it 1 two 3 2 1
2 2
three do you hear
them do you hear them
nanam what what is I lost both
I lost both
games what is
what I've lost
both in the land of lesto we are not
taught
algebra what no you cannot just ask that
in the middle of the fields are you
mad are I don't
remember I don't remember I do not have
to answer that I do not have to even the
one I
wanted I I I do not I do not have to
answer
that I won't remember this one either
this one's
okay this one's
fine it was fine it was a fine Journey
yay Jan I'm sorry did I I didn't mean to
step on any
to my M it's is okay I understand you
had good intentions
[Music]
it's nothing the Revival went well it
went perfectly well it was fantastic and
wonderful yes yes thank
you
oh oh uh shall shall we how shall we
change the
topic oh it is going wonderfully the the
statue of the queen is going much better
this was the one true game that had all
of the stakes in it the game has been
fixed it is it is no longer rigged it is
no longer
rigged no longer rigged and not and this
was the game that determined who had the
absolute best memory wait I wasn't even
playing this seem a little bit unfair we
say it is not when when the when the
green one is not participating I sense a
pattern oh my goodness there may be a
pattern pattern indeed a pattern wait
she may be accidentally ringing it not
purposely you should play again and see
if the green one is the problem oh no I
have played enough you have played you
do not want to play any longer I have
played enough what about voes in my head
are growing
tired oh I see well they have very
little stamina it seems it would seems
so they're quite
weak quite weak minded Shakira there's
another game at the Cerulean cup Guild
you catch chickens in a basket you may
have more fun playing that oh that
sounds fun oh chickens I see chickens in
the basket oh it seems the game has
begun however so this one I will
watch we are playing again there there's
not been a single one that I've watched
I've had to participat in the mall ah n
can you help me distract Jonathan yes
okay such a name today did did everyone
join Jonathan did you join I'm getting
Shakira yes I did join me okay I'm
starting I'm playing a mini game cently
you
joined wait where heard your plans I
heard of your plans I did not want to
join about to end this one but there's
another game that we start Jonathan
your usion red red red red red red red
red red red red green red yellow blue
red yellow red red yellow red red yellow
red red yellow red blue red yellow green
yellowed yellow
reded 100
24 11 red green blue red red green blue
Alabama Alaska Iona Arkansas California
Colorado Connecticut my
good red blue green green red two
yellows two yellows to the side salt
table salt table salt table salt
table pepper egg garlic meat red meat
red dye red dye
meat to remember yellow will never
forget you cannot distract me B Green it
will work blue spinach spinach and I can
still do it
green ham blue hamen ham yellow ham red
ham bloody red ham bloody bloody red ham
very bloody and red I don't think so
very bloody red and bloody and yellow
you forgot the red one there you forgot
the red one there one's over there you
forgot it yes you forgot the red one you
forgot the blue
one two yellow at the top two yellow at
the
top red there's another red check the
red check the red oh you've got in it oh
we're helping there is a yellow there is
a red yellow red you're doing everything
wrong everything is wrong everything is
falling apart you are going to lose you
are going to lose you cannot do this you
lose it is red it is rigged it is rigged
once again it rged it is because of the
green one I believe it's green green one
yeah one that is rigging it we have how
come she always wins not real how come
the green one always wins it is rigged
it is because she is last time johnis
joined it is because she is paying them
she's paying them off she's paying this
no no hold on hold on let me step in
here I think it's an honest mistake I
think she's doing something
unintentionally she doesn't know what
and she's just as confused as we are and
just as scared as we are confused
confused and scary this kind of strange
to be honest I wonder what's going on
maybe I should not play this game again
should we go to the chicken game perhaps
we should go to the chicken let's go to
the chicken game instead the chicken
chicken game The ceran Guild I buy the
Amber coin can they be trusted though no
oh your head I trust anybody matching
horses matching horses wait hold on hold
on Whose horses are matching
I will I will I will I will I as how
many horses do
own wealthy
lady shut she has a pony a little B more
keep going a little long will match I
match I will also match so many horses
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
do you have this polka dot this one does
not have the this is an impostor there
are no polka dots oh goodness oh
goodness wrong wrong
horse you thought that would get past me
oh still
incorrect
no oh there we go there we go I was
starting to question if they were even
horses at all yes yes okay this way okay
I follow we follow her be lying I could
be lying you could be I'm trying to
learn how to trust people again
next to the Amin
Guild oh she is there I see blue I see
blue
okay my horse is a little
sick please do not make himself
conscious your horse SS way it is this
way I found you have infl his ego please
calm down
someone is already playing chicken
catching chicken
patch hello fun are you catching the
chickens yeah I'm catching the chickens
very good cap chickens very good very
good for helping out it is cute how
wonderful does this distract you yeah
okay oh yes is it distracting it's fine
what about now fight it makes it
difficult I
see it's okay very interesting you
catch catch me in the
basket yeah I want to be I don't know if
you want that I think these are for
dinner they are for dinner it is over
you know you know Shakira I think you
should open a restant okay everybody
click ready join the game oh we can play
together I think so
it says how many people already enjoy
the game is it only two people I think
it's can two people okay oh okay then
I'll leave my spot to someone else go
for
it
uh I have joined the game did you join
as well you should start now wait wait
who joined I have joined Shira who else
has Jo do you want to play how many
people can join two join it's okay okay
you do and then I'll we'll do the
next it seems she's a little bit pre
another player is already playing it
says it seems one player can play I'm
here for loty ticket oh so
fast hello can I interest you in a
lottery ticket it is completely free the
first yes that sounds like fun the first
20 people who take a ticket will win but
I cannot tell you whether you are one of
the first I'll take a ticket okay you
will find out in 14 minutes if you are
one of the first 20 people okay uh I
have to log off in 14 minutes will I
still get my prize tomorrow yes I can
hold on to it for if you win yes only if
you win all right let me send you the
ticket by by putting it in your hand uh
can I get 100 tickets 100 tickets I'm
afraid that I do not have that many on
me oh I can give you another four
though oh okay I'll take another four
okay I will give you four more tickets I
am here for tickets in person and you
are not here one
second
one
two
three
four oh ring ring hello are you wanting
tickets for the lottery yes I am here
and you're not here oh I'm at the
chicken game you see I'm on the road
chicken game on the road salesman it's
okay we can exchange it this way would
you like a lottery ticket it is
completely free and the first 20 people
to enter win you win 100
coins can I buy 20 tickets you cannot
you can buy five I'll buy five okie
dokie I will be sending them over to you
now okay how much they're free
oh okay five tickets free can I have
other people's free tickets you cannot
why because it is not
possible okay five I'll take much better
than for I bought so many tickets but
never got anything for free H yeah I bet
you didn't we are in competition with
bomart we hope to we hope to um to to
drive them out of the neighborhood as
they have made this economy not so great
why am I they don't allow me to buy
tickets anymore they don't how
horrible yeah that's awful they should
you you are a free willed person you
should be able to buy as many as you
please why they owe me money
unfortunately it's not my choice that
you only get five it's just the way of
physics how it is of physics how
aerodynamics work
can you send me a request for tickets oh
I I have to meet you no I sent you five
in the Discord that is your mind one
more okay thank
you you're welcome okay byebye byebye
chicken game hello
hello is it happening what no I just
sold tickets over
over this m yes we are advancing Lottery
being uh announced in 11 minutes okay in
Nana 11
minutes yeah wait not quite because that
would be
oh 11 a joke H what is
that whoo What the heck
oh I see a sparkly one right way how I
love to see it sparkly have shiny shiny
chickens here this is looking like a
good one oh oh the sparkly one is worth
it right how many how many does it count
for oh no I've abandoned it but for the
sparkly
one not my best not my best run I must
say I think let's stay on the
side I will partake in one of these
games and then I will return to Nana
what a
run amazing and there I will announce
the winners Mr sparkly one yes I hope
I'll
win everybody careful more chickens oops
more chickens everybody come on you got
to do
94 2
[Laughter]
they'll never see my true plan
Coming For You see there are special
terms that I don't believe a single
person
acknowledged you see you see voices
within my mind
[Music]
here it
reads what does it read
again here it reads that all those who
accept a
ticket must give
10% one tenth of their
income to something but I will not
reveal for yet can't the can't
can't let can't let you know too
much but oh oh dear oh dear vo is in my
head you better keep it a secret you
better keep it a
secret there's the chicken
game I'm lost where' I
go this is where the Amber Guild is
where's the
[Music]
earling did I go I didn't go that
far here it
is
no you are in a bad luck streak I can
recover I can
recover it is not looking very good for
you in this
[Music]
turn the sparkly chicken that's no you
have missed it once
again that was unfortunate
I want to play I want to play go give it
a try I want to
try let's see all the luck that you are
sharing with people if it will come back
to
you joing game start game how does this
work let me see let me see Catch the
birds catch the birds good
luck sparkly ones are very very
good they make you a little bit faster
[Music]
and give you extra score oh you are
doing great so
far you have a natural Talent it
seems chicken have you caught chickens
before in your life many a time I've
also oh I missed it I've also been
chased by chicken
oh it seems you are destined for
[Music]
this going
for I'm locking I'm locking oh I'm
locking are you locking in I'm locking
I'm locking I'm locking maybe new
score yeah new best oh
w 100 100 100 yay what a Challenge 100 h
i HED 100
chicken so good
hoay the leader board is growing
bigger all righty top of it please be
sure to come by Nana 11 where I will be
announcing the winners and giving out
the prize money to those who win okay
just one more time and then I shall it
going to start now it will start in
about 6 minutes I won't miss it you
won't miss it oh you won't miss it good
I I will miss it I will miss it and you
will accept it Okie doie I will now
return to my market to make sure that
every you want to come with me let's go
you stay here wait H I'll play one more
time then I shall come okie
[Music]
dokie why am I up here when did that
happen
get myself
adjusted oh hello hello
[Music]
do we have oh there is no more meat okay
did I have more meat in
here no what can you do with this with
the stained slime balls what can you do
can be thrown what do you do with stain
hide oh dang she beat my
score how dare she oh that's not what I
wanted that's not what I wanted at all
wanted to throw
[Music]
these excellent
oh oh oh oh oh oh uh uh nothing is going
on here I am just waiting for everybody
to gather around so that I can announce
the winners today right right that's now
okay Abol nothing going on yes yes and I
will within the same period of time
which would be approximately 5 to 10
minutes be handing out the Cash Money
reward yes
winners winners indeed winners indeed
okay let us
all the oh wait actually maybe I'll let
you do that maybe if you announce that
the winners are about to be announced oh
you are correct perhaps a 3 minute
warning is in need
okay winners winners will be announced
in 3
minutes I have AE gather around the I'm
ready to be a winner
11 have you seen my high score being
announced into I did I went oh wo she
beat
it the Birds they whispered to
me sabotaged by the Sun and still got
106 sh let me let me look in the library
saving chickens is my
priority yes
yes everybody gather gather around the
Nana 11 I have a feeling every day will
everybody will be a winner
today could we have a feeling a hunch it
just feels like a like we all need a win
today this time I really need a win I
think we all need a win yeah after all
the corruption that has befallen our
lands very true very true I'm just
trying to make this land a better place
I hope I respect that even even for our
differences I respect I hope this n
messenger p 11 can it bring us all
closer together and perhaps introduce a
piece to this
land it is a great responsibility to
carry but I am
strong i l I'm here hello hello I'm here
for the
lottery oh mo mo of the co hello the
lottery will be announced within the
next minute but not everybody is
here my number is
oh oh Lottery hello love loty wait I saw
a ghost I swear I just saw somebody come
bye hi
a ghost a ghost oh you know what it may
have been it may have been my memories
of what flew off the wall sounded like
that had me a little
confused oh I'm so
excited I'm so excited in three CH oh
the time is here but we are missing some
people it appears that out of the room
the deal where is Jonathan G jonath wait
did Jonathan G get one yes Jonathan G
got one perhaps we could call Jonathan
of the G I shall call Jonathan of the G
it wasn't important enough for them to
be here then huh no well you see even if
they are absent well from the actually
never mind I want you all to keep me
company I'm not going to tell you the
truth truth the truth being that you
really don't have to be here right now
you'll still get your prize money but
but I just wanted everybody together
because I'm lonely hello oh I am here
for the lottery oh excellent is
everybody here except the single person
who refused a
ticket yeah refused a ticket a free
ticket yes the wall refused a free
ticket perhaps after the trauma of see
what happened to her
sister sister sister sister wait a
minute I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I you
two just look very similar I got I I
assumed I shouldn't have assumed
they look very different from one
another they look nothing alike well
yeah no one is pink one is blue they
look so much they look as alike as you
look
pregnant what what term are you in wait
are you are you perhaps not
pregnant that would assume male
pregnancy am I even oh I do apologize I
I should able to get pregnant I
shouldn't okay okay n is your business
partner you have to stop stop insulting
your guests stop insulting
your try not to try not to stop stop
stop stop stop backwards
backwards what you maybe you are and I
and I am just revealing it to you I have
a
hunch you have a
hunch am I I said nothing you pregnant
am
I is anyone want a doctor do we have a
doctor Cecilia are you show you another
doctor too huh is there a doctor no but
I do I did take I did take a a First Aid
Course once oh you should be does make
me yeah is that good enough is that good
I suppose the okay okay okay oh yes good
at all I guess
buty let me see more important and if
you were in fact pregnant you would
really need the prize money wouldn't you
that given that your wife seems to be
out of the picture now yeah you would be
raising it alone the child H I suppose I
would be wait what happened to what
happened to her oh how sad oh she is not
of this world any
longer she died are you sure about that
yes she is no longer with us
H the wife is no longer no longer here
no longer with us she's not dead is she
she dead the the version I knew is no
longer here with us what are you talking
about
she's thear the Pearl if you believe so
I would not put all my eggs in one
basket do not give up
immediately I do not know you as
somebody who gives up so easily on love
see well don't give up you know we have
you been so
patient small small difficulty you can
make I think you deserve it too honestly
think so you deserve a second chance
lottery Lottery money money money money
alert money alert free money alert free
money alert money has arrived the money
has arrived wait oh shoot hold
on all righty oh oh she snuck in wait
what me let that's fine that's fine you
can hang out cuz you're so
patient because you're so patient all
righty all righty everybody I will now
be announcing the winners but please be
please have even more patience as I have
to go through it in count yes yes okie
dokie the first winner of the lottery
is you whose name I did not
get the GRE you who is
Green Oh
Cecilia Oh Cecil that's by the green one
oh it is the green one I go I can go by
the green one I like the green one but
there's another green one so it gets
kind of confusing well we call we call
her the other well just whoever is
present is the green one and whoever is
not present is the other green one I win
I win but yes you win I win you win 100
coin oop Roy
congratulations congratulations on your
100 coins what is going why is this
huzzah oh yes that's what I want this is
what I want I thought I was trying to
make me call somebody all right I will
accept your trade request you get 100
coins s to be 100 coins for
you the next winner memory the next
winner is the Lady of the
oranges yippy huz yippy huz you win 100
coins what a surprise m a
feeling 100 coins for you I think today
we are all
winners next the next winner is I love
this N1 Mart next winner is Mario
ra
yeah it's Mario congratulations many
you get 100 coins not sure why you need
it since you were the queen but I'm just
happy you entered my lottery at
all sometimes you must donate to the
Royal
Team all the time sometimes it is
required that you donate a portion of
your earnings to more
powerful yes they need all the money
more than we starving people huz the
next winner is Jonathan G thank
goodness oh great day great day for
you just got to keep your chin up
Jonathan yes I will keep your chin up
you for giving me A New Perspective
nanu you're welcome wonderful
glorious huz the next
winner is or I believe would have been
Lissa of the ravening
coft however she not right now she is
not here right now we did confirm that
she can pick up her earnings tomorrow
which she which she will
do on the on the marrow the ghost one
yeah the scary one but that's okay we
have now the final winner of today moo
of the
co and you bought five tickets you get
500 coins you you
buy you could buy more than one ticket
what I did not know this you can could I
have bought 20 tickets and get
everything no you could not have five
was the
maximum I see oh wonderful
congratulations everybody you have all
won the
lottery it's okay she's addicted as long
as this the only Lottery she's going to
because then she will not lose any money
here Beau beautiful day today we are all
winners I think it's so sad that they
banned you by the way
everyone look everybody has won it was
not a
scam no good everybody won this is a
true story anything family run by a
family of one that is me destroy
destroy fart
destroy wait no no please think we have
to destroy not destroy comption do not
destroy our rivalry brings me more PR
perhaps M would like to share the win
sharing for you thank you my
wi M you're welcome um Jonathan of the G
yes I don't May speak to you on the side
for one brief
moment of course I don't think that's I
think good job good job just like you
deeply concerned about what will come of
your baby If
there really is a baby it seems am iant
you might be in big trouble you not
think that she is I think you're
pregnant well in case that you are
pregnant and then in in the case that
you are you were to be raising the the
child alone if your beloved wife is not
coming back to you I shall just uh of
course platonically offer my assistance
to you in raising your child of course
if you may be in need of any assistance
I will keep that in mind thank you for
your kind and generous offer Shakira you
are so kind and wonderful yes since we
also support the same Queen
yes I yes of course I need to help you
you need me I am of child if I am random
male pregnant I will turn to you I feel
as if I I will need someone to to lean
on but keep your chin up because I have
a good feeling about your wife returning
good luck with your
pregnancy good luck with your
pregnancy thank you I do have something
unfortunate to
mention that I think we should all keep
in mind and mentally prepare
for the chances of a male surviving male
pregnancy
is extremely
slim oh
goodness yes what should I how do you
know this are you a doctor no but I read
I read
books the the life on your on your
Kindle that's so close what is the
Kindle well anything that written on
paper must be true yes there's no wrong
things written on paper that is true
that is true is the library that you
that you that you that read our library
of course since you've reading is there
anything we can do to help her him
through the male
pregnancy there is very little that
maybe some healing items maybe potions
anything you can try but I we can do our
best to help but I think it's very
important that we just prepare in case
Jonathan G I see does not make it
through the pregnancy G now that we
became friends no I don't believe it I
think we can still make it if I am to
die Miss Shakira if you would see to it
that my child is raised with their head
on right oh but I could also just uh
bring you to the temple and revive you
oh that is true she can revive me it's
fine we have done it today we can do it
again we done it we can do it again is
true simple well that's easy then oh
okay okay
too B the resurrection Temple and I will
there may there may be many things to be
negative about like the corruption that
is spreading but this is not something
we have to be sulking about wor has
anyone seen the
princess princess wrong with her the
princess jewelry beu that has been
acting very strange as of late oh yeah
I'm going to kill her what you're not
going to kill my princess oh not right
now not right now why you kill her why
do you want to kill her I'm sorry kill
wasn't the best word kill wasn't the
best word I do apologize use a different
word maybe if she were to be killed uh
and then revived by the Phoenix fire she
could be cleansed automatically here I'm
going to make sure that she is a good
girl and doesn't do anything bad yes yes
she is my daughter I will protect her
old cost I'm sorry we will not let you
let you kill her for no reason we need
we need a good reason wasn't the right
I'm sorry what's the reason she's
killing all of us by killing our crops
and we are resulting
ination do you want us to die for one
princess where's the proof is she
bringing a a Fame into this Pro is the
pudding sounds awfully like
destruction something that something
that she would probably want as she
confessed to me
and now she thinks that I work for her
and that I will also bring Calamity Upon
This Land as it turns out she is the
princess of the
stains and all of us yes we do not want
the stains to
Prevail right I think so yeah we yeah no
no screw them stains
yeah but this this this is this is
information that only I know about all
the others just assume that
she's just being a little weirdo but I
know the
truth and I will I will save everybody
because I'm the main character of this
story I am the hero
[Music]
protagonist I I think throughout this or
my time here I did I have a I had a
hero's journey so uh confirmed
oh they're
gone it's really
weird oh everybody left
[Music]
[Laughter]
you help people whever you go you
really what did I say you can be part of
the of the Vlog oh shoot part of the
Vlog other way
this is my subscriber who is super cool
and they are a part of the Vlog today
they called me a hero because I am one
if you dig Heroes be sure to like
comment and
[Music]
subscribe okie dokie where's the clothes
this
way okay doie oky Roki art
chokey where' they all
go where's
[Music]
everybody I'm being called sorry one
second yes yo where's the party
at oh we are at the Gardens we are
currently at the gardens n The Gardens
okay you take my money and then go blow
it without me yes that's what's going on
we're talking about the plot that you
started wanting to kill the
princess I don't want to kill the
princess I say you said I didn't mean
to what you what the Cecilia I defended
you saying that when you rigged the game
it had to have been an accident I I
still believe I still believe that it
was an accident and completely
unintentional why is it that what do you
want to do with the queen what do you
want to do with the queen tell me use
use your words wa who is the queen uh
the princess I mean the princess the
princess I just want to make sure she
doesn't do anything
bad but now this has turned into
everyone wanting to kill her wait why do
they want to kill her where is the think
she's corrupted at the gardens I need a
map hold
on hold on the at the it's like at the
Blue uh there's like water water I think
I I know I remember what it looks like I
just don't remember where it it's like
on on the side of of the giant circular
building and then
there's and then there's like
wait oh no I I found it wait it's right
next to you yes I found it wait I I
found it oh you found it yeah okay okay
I'm coming okay okay this is the Garden
right
I'm in the
garden I'm in the garden wait is this
not the
garden um okay never mind this is the
garden confused this is the garden I'm
in the garden okay you can H up now yes
I see you oh okay I'm in the G oh yes
she is very I see she has made Hello
what have I done so tell us about this
corruption well first of all all these
lands were cleared by her destroyed by
her I saw saw her literally doing it and
then Nissa has revealed it and she has
then spoken to us in her cursed language
telling us that we must all die also if
we go to her statue it is now bleeding
with deadly blood and then right
next her what it is it has also been
cursed and corrupted she might just have
a tummy
AEG think it is a tummy a it might just
it might be a t a tummy who's calling it
seems more an aching of the Soul hello
can I ask you to buy uh can I can I buy
from you a few diamonds so I can craft
my pickaxe of course and because we are
in the same Guild you are more than free
to just take them oh thank you that's
very s of you yes thank you for your
business of course I appreciate you
asking when I didn't ask you at all if I
could use your
diamonds no it's fine you can take
whatever he wants our girl you can take
whatever you
want yeah you can take
them where are them they're in the
barrel they're in one of the barrels oh
okay thank you so much you're welcome
bye-bye
[Music]
bye-bye I was going to you hang up first
you hang up first you hang up first I
don't remember
I have red sand in my in my backpack oh
you have red sand maybe we could try
that only if you want hello welcome back
I suppose the discussion happened while
I was awake yes of course uh they're
trying to figure out if she's actually
if he's actually pregnant
oh here's the red there quite a bit of
red sand yeah in case you want to um
confirm it 42 times oh yes you can never
be safe I will be back if you may give
me some privacy
yes wait I don't know if we should give
him PIV privacy what if he lies you mean
yeah what if he's going to collect
somebody else's
sample I don't think anyone else is
pregnant no I mean what if he's trying
to hide the
pregnancy should sneak up I don't think
she has a motive for it but we can check
but what if but I want to respect her
wishes for privacy I don't I want to
watch
it seems as if privacy has been invaded
already shh I'm trying to
listen what is happening what is
happening are you
pregnant are you pregnant
oh are you no
are you
pregnant oh are you pregnant oh I I'm
not I'm not built it yet I'm I'm
building an ouse
oh will inde be necessary you don't have
toilet
here it will be necessary I do not know
how large to build this though I think
3x3 is fine a 3X three out house maybe
perhaps like this unless you're visiting
the out house with other people I think
this size should be yeah I think this
looks pretty nice it will be it will
just be a very crude ouse Curr
because yes I am on my
lands cool oh thank you it it will be a
very humble out
house um is there to be a door for your
privacy do not do not watch me please
there will be a
door you can't tell me not to watch why
would you want to watch me I like to
watch everything can you add a window
yeah we are very observant no no wait
but it's going to get so stinky if you
don't add a
window that is true that is just how
medieval out hoses are yeah just it's
it's going to be terrible regardless you
needs some
ventilation a lot of things are stinky
in Evil Ages where did default axe go
seems I have lost my axe I will
just but is isn't this shared or is it
or is it just there is there is is being
aired
out where where I don't see oh I see yes
oh at the top there's a hole upstairs
okay at the very top at the tippy
top sufficient
[Music]
safe
okay that's perfect you still have
privacy oh
yes and ventilation wonderful wonderful
and ventilation is that the is that the
first ouse in the whole Kingdom perhaps
I suppose this is the first ouse in the
entire Kingdom then everybody must use
it
can you give us all access to it yes but
not right now I am using it all right
good luck with the um peeing why you
sticking your head
inside who is trying someone El to stick
their head inside of my door what what
color is the Hat sorry
sorry oh yes one second Amber
[Music]
coined one one second one second before
you are making me nervous me too nervous
to PE is it let's let's me maybe you
should drink some more fluids are you
are you are you part of no no we none of
us are seruan huh no you should drink
more fluids make sure to hydrate hdate
Lots 42
times I am now going to be peeing on the
the the the sand yes okay okay let us
know if it turns green
if you need something let us know
oh I heard water I heard FL that must
have been yeah her ju it seems as it is
red it is it's is red still it is red
still can you try again show us show us
show us try again I'll show you where is
it I thought it was on the floor try
again try again make
sure okay I will be peeing once
more oh I hear the juice is glowing wow
you really good at doing that on come
huh no it it was it was red you must Hy
you must have hydrated well previously
yes I I was very very hydrated maybe all
good things are free we have found out
that you are not pregnant yes it seems
that I am not pregnant well I would
I I humbly apologize for my assumption
earlier I do apologize in case your uh
your wife one day gets pregnant I see I
see I do it was because not because of
your stomach but because of your glowing
complexion I do apologize for the for
the
mistake May because of that uh big juicy
looking hat oh thank you my very very
juicy hat that surely looks like you
hiding a baby in there but it is empty I
think SC Scarlet W member I have a
question
yes me can you come with me
yes yes
did you just GG giggle this is how I
sound when I'm happy oh oh okay sorry um
okay okay okay let's go a little bit
further I'm scared
[Music]
okay
yes oh she's watching I see someone
trying to spy on us you see what I see
why does no one trust anyone no else
watches me
Jonathan are you obsessed P chance
beautiful Forest this isn't a forest
it's a garden beautiful Forest wow
what's a beautiful
Forest Jonathan the man made one you
should try fixing your own issues before
putting your nose in the ones of others
what a wonderful wonderful Forest it's
is so green and Luscious it really
isn't okay well you can stay here I'm
trying to get a get a magical Stone to
work and I need a I need a Scarlet wand
member in order to help me with it oh an
ally well it says an ally but it has to
be someone I trust and that trust me it
is luscious I just was trying to be oh
the forest just trying to special oh yes
going to work thank you you quite
special I was just really embarrassed
that I didn't think of the word lusious
before you I'm sorry I was really it's
fine it I think you are very special in
your own ways namamu you you are
wonderful and a fantastic business owner
and you have created a wonderful Mart
that has brought so much joy in the
Kingdom everyone was happy today all
thanks to you thank you I think you are
quite wonderful and you deserve the
absolute best in somebody who will love
you for the rest of your days I believe
in you thank you nanu that is very very
kind of you to say your words have
touched my heart I am so sorry so sorry
so sorry for any pain that
it is fine follows you no do not do not
lift your head up high please miss nanu
I believe that you you find yes I will
pledge my allegiance to you because I
sense a kindness in you and if you ever
would need help please call for me and I
will I will use my sword for you in your
name oh thank you and I would do the
same for you oh thank you dearest anamu
I also have some hot friends if you want
to if you want me to give them here no
it it is okay yet I I I do not need no I
am just looking for some companionship
through friends and allies oh I can
provide that yes huzzah huzzah what a
great huzzah friendship hooray
friendship hoay
huz thank you dearest Anu you're welcome
you are so kind and those are you I will
see you again I what did what is C want
for me where' she
go oh dear oh hello we were just
celebrating friendship oh wonderful very
wonderful therey well mayhaps you should
give Cecilia a ring perhaps I shall you
have gosh you give such good advice yes
thank you I will see you soon goodbye
for
[Music]
now r r
hello did you need my
help oh oh sorry one second uh I will
call you back in a moment uh Scarlet I
am in a conversation oh the tunnel sorry
sorry okay okay
okay
uh-oh
uh-oh I wonder what she needed help with
[Music]
see I really need to stop looking I need
to stop focusing on my peripheral vision
because in the other like one side of my
peripheral vision then I look at the
other side of my peripheral vision and I
think I see things that are not there
and then I get I get
scared ah my lovely
creation which I followed a tutorial for
and I will I will put the link to the
tutorial in the description you know I
want to do that right now because I
forgot to do that at the beginning of
the stream and I feel that is important
to include one second hold on a moment
[Music]
please
tutorial
Tut Market
tutorial I think I sent it to somebody
here we
go yes it is now in the
description of my
mind
T now all the voices can look at
it tada T
Tada my goodness
any isff sniff sff
[Music]
sniff oh yes indeed I'm going to agen
see will you
marry oh
my I wonder what that was for
oh oh hi hello nanu uh I just wanted to
call you so in you were waiting it's
fine never mind it's fine okay never
mind okie dokie I was waiting so thank
you for letting me know sorry that's
okay okay okay okay but thank you for
offering the help no problem no problem
at all and thank you for the fun uh
Lottery yes thank you for the fun games
and for your
patronage yes let us meet again to
tomorrow I cannot hang up I accidentally
entered the mini
game no you hang up no no you no you
hang no you hang up no you hang
up no no you you're making excuses not
up
me you well N I have a question would
you call yourself an
ally to who to me are we not part of the
same Guild
are
we yeah you saw you saw how like you
know you open the door and then you
closed it accidentally and right after I
like super quickly opened the door you
were still able to open it because
you're part of the scallet one yes I was
able to open it and I just pretended
that you opened it for me cuz I assumed
that it was an accident that you closed
the door on my face so
a I would never I okay thank you for
letting me
no problem no problem it's terribly in
this mini
game you can get good I believe in you
thank you okay I still can't hang up
though no you hang up no you no you no
you okay I will
no she what the heck she tricked
me she
lied who my
game okie dokie everybody
this is where
I call it day Nana 11 is open 24
[Music]
hours will be in the near future I need
to hire a night crew I need to hire some
people for the graveyard shift
[Music]
oh my goodness I
will
read things that people in my head
wrote I don't know who who was that who
was that who who is that wait who who
was
that I can't read fast enough
okay I thought I heard it passing
bow
bow it was F off it was F off the
wall
okay okie
dokie hold on a second
[Music]
wait
oh oh
[Music]
wait okay okay well well o o
oh I shall now
depart from
here and I will read things oh hold on a
second how do I read again I did
this can I do
this wait a
minute this and
then where is it it's not this this this
need this
this I think did I yes and then I do
this
whoa
here what the heck
chat where the heck is that
chat maybe I did the wrong one hold on
hold
on hold on hold on
[Music]
they not copy it
correctly it's not
working it work here hold
on hold on hold
on works
here what the
hecky what the
[Music]
hecky
ow don't worry
you're not FR
okay oh I'm huge wait a
minute there we
go I guess I will go
here all righty then oh shoot how did
that happen okay did you
all enjoy
[Music]
today did you enjoy today's
episode I think that the caffeine helped
me be less tired
my half half a bottle of Dr Pepper
helped a little
bit
Mah
Mah tomorrow I will reveal what that
10% from the lottery ticket or from well
what's the 10% of the income of those
who entered the lottery ticket will go
to also depending how many lottery
tickets you buy it adds up
so those who bought five tickets that's
51% which
equals
[Music]
[Laughter]
50% isn't Nana 11
wonderful isn't it so Grand I cannot
wait for for fauna to log in
and to see my my little
Mart that she may
be in the NOAB about or or is she or did
I give her false information oh who
could
know not you only
me okie dokie I'm going to read super
chats from
[Music]
today shall
we where's my G where are the super
chats oh
here oh yeah by the way tomorrow
tomorrow is the
finale but I was also wanting to
[Music]
um
do karaoke afterwards if I can we'll
find
out because I am a
businesswoman and it's the last day that
something is available that cannot be
discussed on this current
stream we will
see we will see I must put my
businesswoman
re to
work Al I'm not 100% % sure yet I
haven't really tried
singing it was just an idea I
had anyways I'm really out of it
okay where's my Cav I just thought I had
it I do have it it's right here Tada
where's chat chat
go wait don't chat
go here there we
go all righty wait no not not all right
okay no not all right not all right at
all okay okay uh just in time we need
set kind of see wolf Grumble dog chunky
monkey the samurai slay W obus jerk some
1996 thank you for the popcorn how did
you know I was eating
popcorn I was eating popcorn earlier as
I was last minute setting things up and
then I went oh my gosh I haven't eaten
dinner then I ate leftover
pasta with to
ASA m uy ducky oh wait wait so popcorn
banana ice
cream thank you thank
you it's only Tuesday thank you hi M as
my references are as misunderstood and
lonely as a lost white whale in a big
ocean ruthlessly hunted by a deranged
sea captain call me ishma more like M
Dingus oh I get that one I get it I get
it completely
[Music]
I get it like like M Dingus from the
book Moby ding I get
it I get it haha
haha lonely has a lost white whale in a
big
ocean is it confirmed that he is a lone
whale don't those kind of Whales swim in
pods or do they ex do they not allow him
in CU he's different like Rudolph the
red no
who anyways thank you
[Music]
don't I got a cough hold on
oh thank
you a great move thank you for the
sticker oh my gosh your heart okay thank
you oh I'm so out of it oh my
gosh I've been out of it all
[Music]
day I I'm forgetting how to say things
yes anyways Sitting Ducks thank you oh
hi M hello I just wanted to share that
yesterday was my 2 first birthday I
still don't feel like an adult yet
should I be
[Music]
worried what do we think chat at 21
should you feel like an
adult this is how I assume it works
for
people
no I agree I don't think you should feel
like an
adult I feel like at 18 you have this
false
sense that you are really an adult I
mean you are but you're also
not at 18 not me of course I didn't
experience this it's like a very brief
feeling of I'm an
adult
yeah I can do things I couldn't do
before that I won't partake in
yeah yeah yeah yeah but I
could go to the gas station
and buy the stuff that's behind the
counter yeah yeah but I guess depending
where you live not the stuff that's in
the cooler no
no but I could you have this false sense
that you like a a brief sense that
you're an adult and then I think by the
time you're 19 20 21 you go no I'm
[Music]
not no you are you you I don't think
that you should be worried read I think
that's completely
understandable H yes as a 9,000 at the
very least you're
old ow guardian of
civilization I think you're
fine anyway thank you
d uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh you can't even
rent a car how could you be an adult you
can't rent a car yet
uh uh uh
uh cheeseburger thank you for the aupa
small business investment I believe in
the values of Nana 11 I'm so glad you
do I'm so glad I feel like so far
everyone believes in it I feel so
confident it's getting very good
reception very good PR the Rivalry with
fom Mar is really making it Excel I
think had there never been a funa mar I
don't think that it would be doing so
well but little people know that perhaps
that it it exists too but I mustn't
speak any
further it is it is owned by just me a
small business owner it's not a
corporate plant no no no
no it is just it's a humble
little what's the
word not sha what's the
word stall it's a little stall there we
go there we
go anyways thank you thank you for
believing in
it a m and
pop
sure y flyer thank you Mum we have
fonart at home fart at home yes it is
the fonart that is at home within the
Amber coin
Guild well I guess it would be the
funart at home for the Amber coin
but we all know where I stand it's very
clear where I stand is it
[Music]
not anyways thank you
D syntax error thank you it arm subbed
oh that's a YouTube glitch be sure to
press the Subscribe button again careful
now yeah no this this YouTube YouTube is
rigged be careful I don't think it's
intentional but be careful thank you
D mean time thank
you you all you all cannot enter this
lottery I cannot there it is impossible
for me to give you 100 coins this is not
possible however do know that if it was
possible I absolutely would give you
them but
not those who send super chats asking
because that's that cost money and
they're free they're completely
free this this is kind of awkward
anyways thank you n d bash Sher thank
you one lottery ticket sorry I can't you
gave me money it doesn't work that way
thank you
d r t thank you can't give you the
lottery ticket sorry about that you gave
me money it's not how it works thank
you uh rasis thank you please Mo I have
my entire Investment Portfolio in fonart
I'm
ruined you should have assumed that
someone would come
in see how fart was doing and go I want
some of that however us at Nana 11 we
are
Innovative we think outside the box
you should have seen this
coming the predict you should have
predicted this you had all the
information anyways I'm not sorry
consider
selling and then consider buying because
nothing will ever ever top Nana
11 we can only go up from here thank you
d
Cory man thank
you JH 5013 thank
you is international shipping available
I want to order two cuts of beef I
cannot give you two cuts of beef
because you paid money and that would
imply that I have a business
[Music]
license so I cannot but thank you donon
noi Mimi thank you see friend you can
give away tickets for free instead of
scamming the viewers
exactly
exactly we all showed
him anyways thank
you scum thank you hey Mo hello I used
the power of civilization to combine
milk vinegar salt and heat to make rotta
I was it was cool and easy thank you for
existing I watch videos of people making
Che I've never tried making it myself
though that they make that one and they
make
mozzarella they seem to be common ones
to make at home probably cuz they're the
easiest I would
assume anyways it was cool and easy but
did it taste good did it taste good
though I hope it did thank
[Music]
you n thank you oh hi M hello did you
know the reason I the reason why Wasabi
is spicy is because of butterflies the
plant species ites from uses
glucos glucose
glucos as protection which is toxic to C
caterpillar
caterpillar spicy to
us why is wasabi so
spicy nothing about butterflies what if
I attach butterflies
the Cabbage butterfly it a key role in
developing plants like mustard and
cabbage that's oh oh oh
oh it's a caterpillar it's the
caterpillar that does it not really the
[Music]
butterflies okay let's see the only
thing I have found so far that discusses
that is from
Reddit are we going to use
Reddit as a
source are we going to believe
it oh the next one is quora are we going
to believe
[Music]
it let's go to Google Scholar shall we
let's see I'm so far just skimming the
titles and I'm not seeing anything
oh no no oh oh
[Music]
I do not want to pay $70 for this never
mind never
mind I believe you I believe
you thank you D
Don thank you what a genius saleswoman
business is booming moming
already it was I predicted it I
predicted it would do very well I just
had a hunt I I
just I'm just really good at business I
know how these things
work anyways thank you
d uh uhuh Eva thank you oh hi nanu you
seem like the type of person to like
silly things did you know the planet
neptun has many Moons with silly names
my favorite one is hippo
camp hio Camp
moon it's true
it's for
Ries oh what a silly why they name it
that for what reason Camp of Hippo the
hippo of this
Camp interesting thank you for sharing
thank you for sharing Planet fact thank
you thank you yes for Reales for Reales
for
Reales Cy thank you the economy has
never been more Ming since Nana 11
opened congrats on your successful
business Nana moo thank
you thank you thank you you're welcome
to everybody you're welcome thank you no
please please hold your
applause a thank you pants thank
you KD h d on a full display
is it was it let's Google it is that
what it
was probably or brain fog might have
been a mix of both a little cocktail of
both anyways thank
you CA thank you happy birthday thank
you thank
you uh where am I I'm here oh rasz thank
you again the this so citizen here not a
sapling I ate at Nana 11 today and I
found an owl feather in my food food
disgusting Zer out of five stars will
not be returning here what that that is
the uh oh what's the word oh my gosh
what's the word what's the word what's
the word what is the word it's supposed
to be there it's decoration it's garnish
it's it's
garnish it's
[Music]
decorative it's a feather for you to
keep
[Music]
I'm so sad do you not like
owls why would you choose to eat at an
establishment run by an owl if you just
don't like owls yeah it's a reward it's
a reward for you for eating for eating
on your food good
job this guy hates
owls this guy hates owls how could
he thank you if he want you can return
it if if you return it I'll give you 200
[Music]
coins even if you realize that it it was
meant to be there and you take back your
zero out of five star review I'm sure it
was traumatizing for you if you didn't
realize it was supposed to be
[Music]
there it must have been very hard for
you so to compensate for the trauma
you dealt with
I will give you 200 coins how does that
sound I think that's fair anyways thank
you pants thank you
again it was not
copium it was
not I was not the only one experiencing
the rigged game we came to the
conclusion that it was Cecilia of the
emmering
green who is doing it
unintentionally it was her fault but she
didn't mean
to anyways thank you
D what the
[Music]
cough Cody Koy thank
you a the m and silly thank you D hey
bash thank you I'm not escaping with to
allegations I was never running from
them I was never trying to escape I am a
tow through and through thank you
D Grandma dog thank
you can't stop you because you cannot
read that's not an
excuse you did that you shouldn't take
things that you can't read that's that's
that's survival skill lacking of
survival skill there anyway thank you
G Kai thank you I never thought I was
going to be this invested and obsess
with to Ian REO story arcs writing so
many waves of emotion these past few
days my Twitter feed makes me cry
Justice for gathan go no I'm so I
apologize Jonathan
huzzah I know I hope that I hope
Jonathan comes out of this
story doing better than than she's doing
now I do hope so I'm rooting for her I
feel like she's the
underdog well no she's not she's she's
not the underdog she's she she holds her
head up
high no she she deserves better I think
she her life can have a turn around I
think she can do a
anyways she just has to want it and she
has to reach for it and she has to work
for it
anyways thank you
D the ass thank you for the
[Music]
sticker ER Le thank you what if you make
the first 20 lottery tickets when 100
coins for all the ticket holders after
the 20th ticket have to pay you 100 coin
for each ticket instead the Mind Games
will be interesting
no no no no no that's not what we're
about we aren't here looking to
take from the fine citizens we are
looking to help them that would not help
them at
[Music]
all no no no that would be interesting
but it is not is not what we're about
thank you
d s takasi thank you hi M hello thank
you for the Super Chat
rers oh thank you thank
[Music]
you thank
you what T thank you how are
you I'm fine
I'm doing good that's good I did come up
with some logical phrase two things that
move together are from the same place
what does this tell you anyway I'm going
to bed soon good
night two things that move together are
from the same
place like if they started
together but what if one joins and
later from a different place what if
somebody is
jogging and they like meeting up with a
friend to jog with them but the they
didn't start from the same place the
friend went from their house and then as
the person was jogging their friend
caught up and then they started jogging
in syn complete sink it was creepy it
was so creepy how in sync they
[Music]
were I'm sorry I I just I'm just the
type of person to try challenging
[Music]
everything thank you thank you thank
you Renee Arun thank you greetings
fellow greetings I see you become a I
don't know how to pronounce
this why does she sound like that when
she pronounces it mellan
M
mellian she sounds so nasty my goodness
I see if become a maavalan
entrepreneur I congratulate you on your
road to become a millionaire super
villain great career path when you get
to the top can I get a
job once I reach the top I will
Disappear Completely and I will never be
found again
you will find my horse alone out in the
prairie and all my belongings will be
left with it except all of the money
that I
made will also be gone because I've
chosen to go live in nature without any
uh any belongings or materials or I
would have no use for money out there so
be kind of pointless I mean I can maybe
make fire out of it wait no we use coins
never mind never mind we don't have we
don't have bills
anyways yes yes saan my worldly
possessions anyways thank you that's
only if I reach the top the tippity
top thank
you uh Christina na thank you Ms it's my
birthday and I'm so glad I got to watch
a bit of your stream for thanks for the
great happy birthday happy happy
birthday I like your name a lot and I
like your
icon thank you thank you on Untitled
camel a name
Chang thank
you I do stand on the ground sometimes I
think I ended Standing On Top of the
Mart that that wasn't the March I mean
the the the the my my stall my store I I
stood on top of my
store anyways thank you d
Mr V thank you instructions and amount
of coins unclear no it was clear it was
incredibly
clear I don't even know what you're
referring to at this time honestly but I
am certain it was clear thank
you Eric W1 thank you thank you thank
you yes yes thank you for believing in
the success it will it is already
successful thank you D thank
you Samari 1996 thank thank
you yes this makes
sense this all makes yes everything
about this makes sense everything that's
happened has happened for a reason
and yes everything within iano yes yes
[Music]
indeed thank
you thank you for
theu hello congratulations on the
opening of Nana 11 it's been a really
fun week with this and REO collaboration
when chapter 1 ends chapter 2 promise
will come right I'm really looking
forward to it I mean why would they why
would they call this chapter 1 if
there's not a chapter 2 that is supposed
to happen when will it be I have no idea
yeah I really been enjoying it
too I remember like seeing all the you
know all the what would you say like we
had like PowerPoints about it they were
telling us you know the gist of it and
all these things and I was like honestly
I'm not huge on Minecraft never really
was I like the aspect of like hanging
out and talking with people but I just
never got into Minecraft as a game I was
like I'm well I'm excited to do it I'm
excited for it but it wasn't until like
we actually got into the game and like
we since like us playing and just
experiencing it where I'm like oh my
gosh wait this is this is really
good it's really really
good no it's incredible all the people
that worked on it
[Music]
applaud very well made it's been very
very very
fun and of course all the other members
who are part of it are a big part of
what makes it fun too but the map
itself the lore stuff the dungeons the
games all that
stuff it's been fun just unfortunate
that I'm
like I I kind I mean I feel I feel
better if every day
but still kind of sick lingering
sick it's still been very fun very very
fun you know what's crazy though so I
was doing some grinding because I don't
know what the fastest way to make money
is without gambling so I decided not to
gamble because I thought it was too
risky and I only have so much time to
you know prep things off
Stream So what I did was I just kept
accepting the quest to kill the stains
cuz you get 100 coins for every 10 that
you kill but then you also get more
coins from killing them I think as your
experience goes up like your level goes
up I'm pretty sure it it increases it
maybe I don't know but I just was doing
that for like a
solid the potato salad Quest wait a
minute I don't know about that one
doesn't matter now I'm rich enough I
have all the money that I
need I see well I was uh I was grinding
[Music]
and it made me want to play just normal
Minecraft like not even on the Ian
server like it made me just want to play
farming Minecraft where I have to go and
collect my resources cuz I've never
really fully experienced
that my introductions to Minecraft have
always been like
servers or servers with
mods Oran server that kind of
thing I very rarely have like tried
playing just on my own if like on my own
I probably did like 2 hours maybe but
now I'm kind of interested just playing
like Farm learn how to build I don't
know I don't think I have time really
for
that but I absolutely see the appeal I
think if I was exposed to Minecraft when
I was younger like at the age I was
playing like uh Zoo Tycoon and stuff I
would have gotten really into it but I
didn't know anything about Minecraft or
I didn't play it until years and years
and years after it came
out only within the last
three
anyways where am I oh adahan thank you
come me thank you thank
you uh Le the human thank you congrats
on Nana 11's opening But be sure to take
precaution on possible lawsuits though I
heard one can file lawsuits against
those that intentionally make fine
Prince tiny for deceptive
purposes I don't think that that's a
law in our world I didn't hear anything
about it and I read through it I made
sure that everything I did was
legal I ensured that everything was
legal because you see there are no laws
in this
world and no laws can apply to me
because I'm the protagonist
I'm the hero of this world and the hero
even if there were laws the hero
sometimes has to break them you know
when there's like the the there's like
superheroes and they have powers and
stuff and like the superhero is fighting
the villain but while he's fighting the
villain he's destroying a bajillion
buildings cuz they're fighting in the
middle of the city the insanely
populated city and all these buildings
are being destroyed and dude like 100%
there are people inside those buildings
so the superheroes I like I guess
they're fighting to stop the villain
overall so less people die but they're
still killing
people by destroying everything around
them
anyways one of the big reasons I just I
can't get into superhero movies there's
so many that have scenes like that and
all I think about is this is just
there's so many people dying around them
no anyways thank you thank you for the
advice I do appreciate it
thank
you edgy sketchy thank you as a moon
coin holder and Nana 11 stockholder I
greatly anticipate promising returns in
the near
future with h life's top saleswoman
leading the way I'm confident in the
value Nana 11 will bring it to the
mo hear that you hear that everybody
this stockholder has no regrets this
stockholder is feeling pretty good you
might as well make yourself a
stockholder yourself
I only said I only told uh the others
that there there that it was a private
company that that there was no stock to
be bought because I I didn't want them
specifically to buy any
stock call that which you
will cuz technically wouldn't
they
no anyways thank you thank you thank you
d
ah hi thank you not trying
to oh goodness thank you
d i you vitar thank
you I lost my dog when
historical historical hurricane hit my
Village but the local Nana 11 man
manager found my dog that's me the
manager found my dog and also donated 50
million coins to local charity thank you
boom you are
welcome oh my gosh
yes I found your dog and to and I give
you 50 million point and I remember
remember when I helped that old lady
across the street too wasn't that really
cool and remember when I stood up to
that
bully remember remember when I did that
that and I made him reflect on himself
and why he does the things that he
does and he realized it was because he
wasn't treated very well at home and
realized he didn't want to make other
people feel the way that he felt in the
end so then he stopped bullying and then
the the bully victim and then him became
best friends remember when I did when I
made that happen do you remember
that I remember anyways thank you d
d I did do those things
to thank
you thanks for saving the economy with
universal monetary system AKA mooncoin
and with the Nana 11 grand opening
what's the next plan though next plan is
to face whatever is happening tomorrow
it's set to prepare our strength so that
that's what the next thing is going to
be that's it there's no catch I'm going
to participate in the battle haa thank
you
D 13 King thank you I'm sorry x i i i
King thank you I'd like to sell all of
my nana 11 stock as it's currently
booming so I may dve this into other Al
Ventures oh I cannot recommend that you
see because it like I said it only goes
up from here I think it's a very bad
idea for you to sell right now and I
don't think that you are making good
choices and and you may need a a
caretaker to make choices for you
because that's just crazy to sell it
right now so as your new caretaker um I
will not let you sell
it anyways thank
you the radical Momo thank
you if you were a fruit you'd be a melon
unmarried because you can't alope
what you
[Music]
can't and the chat goes
wild enough they scream
enough thank you that's a pretty good
one thank
you
Cal uh- uh uh- uh
thank
you thank you W1 thank you for the
bananas Coral thank you Don jungu thank
you for the
akasam hi Mom hello yesterday was my
dog's birthday happy birthday puppy
happy birthday puppy happy birthday
puppy I gave him a hootsie plusy and he
liked it so much that I saw him sleeping
while holding wait I can't read hold on
a second ah he was holding what he was
holding he was
holding holding it this
morning oh my gosh that's so cute I love
when people celebrate their pets
birthdays I love it happy birthday to
the
pooch I'm so I'm so glad that he likes
his hootsie
plushy
wonderful oh my gosh I had a I was like
did I get my hooie plush I did I did get
it I remember
it where it is I don't know where it is
where
is oh I remember I know where it is I
know where it is I had to put it away
because I was paranoid and was like I
have to put all my stuff I just stuff it
all in the
closet Bo is in the closet right
now anyways thank you
jangu uh uh uh AR thank you can I put
this $10 into Nana 11 stock this is not
the place to do that there I think there
are apps for
this but not not this app not this
application that's a super chat you can
or are you we you're saying this $10 the
you
I you mean this $10 the ones that that
you wrote out in the Super Chat not what
you spent on the Super Chat is that what
you mean
is that what you mean I see anyways
thank you D Eric Silver thank you thanks
for the
Minecrafting my younger brother named
his a plush after you cute that's so
cute thank you for naming him after me
cute cute thank you
D Untitled camel thank you again if
you're not allowed to sell Nana 11 stock
until they peak in value but the value
is always going going up then are we
going to make infinity
dollar yes yes you
[Music]
will you will indeed look forward to it
please I'm so happy for all of those who
have bought stock I'm I'm so excited for
you this is the best thing you could
have ever done with your
[Music]
money I'm just I'm just so giddy so just
so excited for every single one of
you anyways we're
we that's
[Music]
it thank you all for watching I'm going
to rust my
head I think I'm going to rust my head
for a little bit feels kind of funny I
had a lot of fun
today fun times look forward to the
finale tomorrow I believe everybody will
be there oh no I think K can't everybody
who can be there will be
there
yes yes yes thank you all for watching
it
today see you on Tom
tomorrow I'll drink the rest of the Dr
Pepper hopefully I'll feel even better
than
today like I said I think I get better
and I get stronger every single
day
yes stalling thank you for the stalling
donation y thank you got you got you no
stalling here thank
you all righty goodbye good night byebye
thank you byebye goodbye thank you
byebye thank you byee
[Music]