A
[Music]
Na OG
Ni A
[Music]
T
Kikiriki
[Music]
This is Licca-chanka, white yes yes, I
can't see you yet.
Maybe it would be better to do it the other way around.Wa-wa-
wa-
wa-kum, uka
-u-kum, toa-
chan, cat-chan is okay, they're fighting,
it's their first fight, Da-chan's timing is right, and Raden-chan's  They're
fighting on top of the luggage mysare
aroundASbe
Yeah, let's exchange Licca-chan is the top Yeah
, Raden-
chan It's okay to fight warts It's not a fight It's just play and play
[Music]
Yeah can you hear me? I
'm using three microphones just in case
.  [Music] It's
been a while since I've used food, so it took me a while to prepare.
[Music] It's been a while since I've used food. [Music]
It's been a while
since I've used food. [Music] It's been a while since I've used food.
But the truth is, we're just going to start cooking, right?
That's just preparation, so
firstofall Raden Ririka,
Rakae Theyarein Suria, yeah, we
did it, yay, happy,
not Australia. I heard some
viewers often say something about it,
confusing it with Australia.  There's
No and Australia and Australia,
so yes, they're both really
good. I'm glad you're enjoying it. It's fun. It's
really fun. It's completely different from Japan.
A lot of things are different
Yeah, yeah en
A
for This is actually something like Swiss Switzerland Yeah,
yeah,
there's definitely cheese and Yui's yeeji,
yeah, yeah, it's
like a griddle, so either one is
fine, but this one is better.  It
might stick a little, so let's put it under there. It's
hot under there as well as it is in this
container. It's true. I forgot something important. Potatoes.
[Music]
That's it.  I'll
be there in 15 minutes. Bye
bye. Potato. I'm going to give you a little job now. Well then, I
guess I'll just forget about it. Yeah, I'll
tell you a little bit about my feelings. Hello
Ewa. Hello.
Morgen Guten Morgen Yes, Gute
Morgen Gute Morgen This is hello
Hey, the other one is Da Knight Da Keshi
Da Knight That's right.
What does it mean to say "thank you"? What is that German word you taught me at the Christmas market?  It
just so
happens that [Music] it's called ``Hai''. It's quite difficult to pronounce,
but I learned about 2 or 3 words for ``Unko.'' I
studied today.Today, I went to an art museum, and
Ka-chan, please half-speak in that English.
okum bimi bimi
Oh, what did you see? Rembrandt,
no. Rembrandts and another one. I
can't read it. It's
like I can't read it in Japanese. It
didn't start with B, huh? I
mean Brueghel, oh Brueghel.
Well, there was at least one other person
in the Rembrandts area, yeah, yeah, but I couldn't
understand it because I couldn't pronounce it in Japanese.I know how it's spelled, but it's half and half.
That person's drawings were amazing, too,
because those that I'll make mistakes later on are Rembrandts. Did I
use that or that Kicord
? That's not a Rembrandt, it's a different person. Yes, it's Raden-chan. It's so
big.
Even before I got to the museum, I
could already see the Austrian cityscape.
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh my god, it was amazing.
Even when I saw the tiny church, I was so
excited that I went crazy. I'm so happy.  I
was so happy, but it's a bit windy here today,
so I might not be able to talk much. I'm sorry,
but I'm going to roast some meat and vegetables on top of this. But I'm going to grill some meat and vegetables on top of this,
but for example, I'll roast some potatoes under here.
Potatoes
Vegetables Love
Kini May Vegetables
Little Yes Potatoes Vegetables
Meat
Les
on
peopleMeaustJustput
AllThings
make and yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
wait there that melts really
delicious fun yeah yeah this little thing  I'm going to
use it, I'm going to use it, I'm going to make a lot of things with this, I know, but
first of all, let's go to the bottom,
okay, it's hot here too, so I understand, I
only have two sauces left, and I also
have ketchup, but yeah, sosu, wait.
Wow, it's sour cream, sour
cream, so I'm looking forward to it.That Chiara is,
uh,
iilike, I hate being an idiot,
but they both said they wanted to drink wine,
so yeah, I bought that without knowing anything.
Thank you Senkyu Care Senpai First of all, I
don't understand this at all, but my mom is a mystery.
After I gave him a drink of punch, it
was already 10 minutes [Music] and I was asleep.It was warm.It was warm after all.I
think alcohol probably makes it easier to get around.I
don't remember anything after I've already drunk it.I only bought a mysterious cheat.  I
remember Ri-san, it was dangerous, the three of us were
holding hands, and it seemed like we were going to stop. The two of us, Akihara-senpai and
Laren-chan, each held one hand as
our lovers. Show me the cheese.
Cheese, cheese, okay. Where's the cheese?  I went there, and
it looked like someone was drunk, and
not to mention the mysterious cheese was missing.Ririka suddenly went everywhere looking for the cheese.  I
bought the cheese with a smile on my face,
so I was surprised.It's
about 50 yen for this amount of cheese,
and about 7,000 yen.Don't
say it, I'm about to forget about it.  I
thought it was 100g,
but when I was told it was 300g, I turned to 3. The
reason is that it contains truffles,
so I thought, ``This is truffle cheese.''  I
thought it would be about 2,000 yen, but it turned out to be only 3. You
can't say that
it's not worth it. Yes, I can't help it. It's so
thin, so let's all eat it together. How do we
eat it?
just
eat like that. Yeah, it's already flavored, but I still
think it's delicious. I don't eat it with grapes.
Yeah, I often see grapes on cheese plates. Yeah, I
tend to eat cheese as is.  Yeah, it
's not raisin, it's grape.
Yeah, it should be cheaper than buying it in Japan. I
saw it now. I don't know what it is, but 7000
is expensive. It's expensive. I was surprised. Well, I
came a little late. I've already bought it.
We were just about to buy it,
so when it was cut and weighed, we did
n't realize it was 300g. Licca-chan was already in a good mood.
So I couldn't stop it anymore.I couldn't stop it.The
other person said the price was 47 euros, and I said, Wait a minute, you
better stop.I wonder if Yu-chan knows how much it costs
[laughter]  ]
[Applause]
HowPay
ACTbehest
475,000
[Music]
6,000 yen is about 5,000 yen,
but I know what you're doing already.
But I only brought about 200 Ririka to begin with,
so almost all of them are
gone. I'm
laughing at Ririka, but I already have about 100
Ririka. What did you buy, Raden-chan? I
bought a lot of books at the Art Museum.
There is a collection of works by Rembrandt in this museum, and a
collection of works by Rembrandt.SheboughtalofBOOKS
[Music]
What is that? I definitely wanted to see it.
[Music]  I
saw a hunt in the middle of winter.It
was really
good.  It took a while.
Yeah, but Raden-chan was
kind of excited when she saw the picture. It
was cute and funny to see that, and the
way she commented was really good.
Professional.
Professional, I'll go again. I learned a lot. I'll
definitely go again. Oma-chan was
so clean and refreshing. The
building was amazing, and it was amazing. I'm glad I got to
see it while I was alive. Rigel
[Music]
Nebabel
[Music] It was
coologsandactually
IwantShowYouOne
ThingWedidthatwas
soolLikemeIthink
EspeciallyMeandwe
wereinlovewithone
particularSTYLEOF
PAINandthenwhenyou
wentDeeperintothe
museumTherewasa
placewhereyoucould
createrecreatethat
PainNo, uh, OkIwill
SHOWI saw the Erika-chan one, and the Lyrica one
that has that game in it, right?
When
makeQRThere was a movie that Lyrica-chan and I particularly
liked.Yeah,
that's it.  As you walk through the museum, you'll find
something new
like a game where you can create your own version.
But first,
let's take a look at Ririka-chan's version. There
are so many different items to choose from.
There are some items that stand out in a strange way,
but aren't they amazing?  Lyrica's favorite things:
food, shiny things, cosmetics, cosmetics, travel, etc., so
passport,
huh?
Nika version, ah, I wonder if she's wearing those. Ah, cutlets, yeah, yeah,
yeah, that's a
famous food in Australia, isn't it?
Yes, it's probably dead, but there's also a possibility that it's a fish.
Fishin chips maybe, maybe.
Yes, it might just be pork cutlet. No, I love it. No, why is it so wide?
Let's
look
at
Let's finish it off, Laden-chan.LetlookatM.
Les
mus is weird, flers
FL stuffed animals know
No, I know, they're cute, the shoes are
cute too, and makeIlikemake and
know they put over and
finAnd
nowRverlooksvery
interNo, Raden-chan's stuff is
a little different from ours, isn't it?You
have good tasteWhat are you doing in the first place?  I
thought it would be a little weird, but it
started to come together
[Music]
I was saying this and that in Japanese, Oh Mushi Mega Mushi,
Mega?  `
`Why did I put so many things in there?
'' It's fashionable, isn't it? They
say it's art.
That's why ours is also art.
[Music] Sho-
chan was a little small,
apparently, but it's okay now.  I'm
not talking much because I'm a little windy
reallyBrightyousee
the smokestear was
likeWhenISawOhGOD
youhavetoputtheCin
your
painbutShesaidShe
turnedITAROUND
Because Shequit
smoking
by around, it looks like it's upside down,
and they're trying to make the shells into some sort of heart shape,
right? I put two shells on top of each other, and
then I put two shells on top of each other,
and it's like a
little
make-like, it's
stylish and it's fun.  It
might have been,
but the cigarettes also have a certain color, and the
overall color balance is good.Beautiful
[Music]
orig
I
BThat's it.
Over 330,000 yen of original poop
Yes, this is a reference. This
is the original of this. Yeah, I think the original is fine. Yeah, I
won. It's amazing. It's
done right. Yeah, it's done right. Yes, it's
colored.  I wonder what that is. It's
not real, but it looks
real. It's a real-looking panel. It's a lucky
panel. Kaun, yeah, you're very understanding, Lale-chan. Pampa. It
brings back fond memories. The one I was with.
Yeah, I'll put it here. I want you to
put it on the wall. HowMyPO. Is
it okay? I think it's almost there.
SoWedid
ThatwasniceAnd
basicallyTodayWE
LIKEbreastgoodBREAK
What did you eat?
Burger BurgerBreakfast
Burger was delicious.  I ate an avocado burger. It was
full of salsa sauce, avocado, ham, and eggs. The
pie was huge. It was a huge amount.
Lyrica-chan was so excited when she ate it that she felt like it was a bit of a
sandwich. It
wasn't a sandwich, but it
had salmon and cream cheese on top. There was bean sprouts on
top. I do
n't know what that bean sprout is. I don't know if it was there or not.  It's skinny, it's really
small, it looks like a shellfish,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I guess it's German,
but oh, I'm that super delicious
Kazashiman that male dessert pancake.  I
shared some of the broken ones with some jam between the two of us, and it
was delicious.It was crunchy, but the inside was fluffy and delicious.It was
beautiful, and we drank some delicious juice.I
drank fresh.  Juice and the two of us
just messed around with my cat The
cat is cute The girl love my
sursur They are
Love With my CC being
[Music]
What's also amazing is that sometimes a cat comes over here and does
a lot of slithering on my legs and
greets me.I
try to eat watermelon and eat it, and I
flirt with Teko-chan, and then we go to an art museum and it's
Christmas.  We went to the market,
yeah Christmas makeup wasnice
WeAllatealofstuff
andiibought
something to
introducetothegirls
andTheybothlikedIT
butEspecially Ririka-chan
LovedMy Ah, withsuar Yeah,
there are those nuts that I buy every time at that Christmas market, and when I
bought them, both of us loved them,
and they were so delicious.They
went so well with the wine.
That's right, it was delicious. I'm drunk
. Can you see it here? I'll put it in my hand.
But I can see it with a pin, and I'll
take it out.
There's a delicious pinto there
like NUTSAlmond
Insideandlike.  ROASTEDWITHSUGARIT
HASAGOODCRUNCHVERY
Sweetveryny It's not too
sweet, but it's not too sweet.
Yeah, Ikingthepo
Potte that two people
eat that potato with a hippopotamus  Yeah, me too It's better to
eat well that way I save time Yeah, I wonder if it's
okay Howtock
[Music]
Oh
4  It
's 4:30 now, right? I wonder
if it's 5 o'clock now. Maybe 5:00, 8 hours, 8
hourdiff, no, 8H
diff.
Yes, thank you to Japan for watching it at 5 o'clock right now.
This is really fun. Even if you look to the right.
If you look to your left, you'll see a lot of interesting architecture.
When I saw it, I was yelling, and the
taxi guy laughed at me. Maybe he was
thinking about it, but he
laughed at me.
L
[Music]
people
thinkthink
[Laughs]
Potatoes
Potatoes I recommend this.
For example, just take
pot yeah inlike SLI yeah
evenTHTheypry
small then you
take yeah hehe
[Music]
Yeah, you can make it even stronger. Yeah
yeah, it's stylish. [Laughs] This seems to be the Austrian style.  Let's grill some meat too. I
want to eat it with some color on it too. Yes, I
put a lot of it on this person.
I
like this.
How many onions are these? Super delicious. For example,
a little bit of bacon.
Bacon.  Rika-
chan, I want you to put a little bit of corn on it
Oh,
okay, this is about it, oh, how
perfect
, oh, yeah, yeah, it's perfect. I made it and found out, oh yeah, it looks delicious. It's
delicious. This feels like yakiniku.
Fun yakiniku party, yakiniku party.  Piping hot,
wow, give me a potato, potato, it's
already difficult, na
potato, if the potato bridge is
easier to use, let me know, it's okay,
kao, potato,
potato
Yakiniku to potatoes It's
like gracoro, potatoes to potatoes
Yeah, it's better to cut them into those thin strips I see,
yeah,
yeah, yeah, you can say this time.
Night
[Music]
999PM
Yeah, potatoes,
potatoes By the way, who wants salt and sugar? Oh, on
earth is that okay? If it's crystal, let me know. Yeah, hey, I'll
do my best to get it. Yeah, yeah, I'll do my best.
Yeah, I was wondering what to put this in. This is
delicious. Please give me some mental therapy. Yeah, thank you. You
can add one more
aya. It's a colorful one. Yay, I
guess I'll add one more. I'll put some in there too.
He smells like a beast.Vegetables are vegetables.If you
open it on a zucchini, put it on the zucchini.Even
if it's a uni-vegetable taboo, you'll always
put cheese on it at the end.Understood nose NO.
LIFE nose
Nora Wow
beast
Wow
cutesystiny cheese cheese
cheese cheese ah
senkyu Let me show you the last one I'll show
everyone what's going on I'll
give it to you It smells so good
Ririka-chan Shabo
Rade I can hear Ririka's voice reflected in SS  It
smells really good. Wow, come
on, there's a little more
me.
So I guess it's too much.
What should I grill? I'm going to
grill another piece of meat. I'm going to grill
it. Yes, Raren-chan, what are you putting on it? Rare is
potatoes, bacon, and small
onions and
paprika and paprika.  I
was surprised by the shape of the paprika. It was so
big. I had never seen a paprika
before. It was so big. It
was amazing.
Okay, nice. Put some cheese on this. Cheese.
Put some cheese on
top. Nice. What should I do with this? Put it at the bottom.
Wait until the cheese melts and melts nicely. I
want to share this too.  Yeah, I'm waiting right now. Let
me show you how good it is. You can watch it over here.
Oh, okay, andsoI will put
onmy a little apart, but
yeah, let's eat it together. Oh yeah, that's it.  I'm
ready to use it. Oh, I haven't opened it yet. It's
delicious. Meat. Meat. Grilled meat. Meat. Meat. Meat. Meat. Meat. This is delicious. This is a raclette
grill. Everyone should have one. It's
definitely delicious.
There's also a sticky one  It's about half the size of this one,
yeah, yeah, where was it? The
seasoning, the
seasoning, it's some kind of cheese, and the sauce, the
sauce, and all kinds of vegetables. I
can't wait anymore.  It
won't melt at all Slowly Slowly
Slowly
Slowly I feel like I'm not feeling excited at first,
but don't worry, after a while it'll be too
full and I might have a problem.Okay,
[Music]
Hmm, I'll be a good girl and wait.
Wow, okay, I'm going to eat a little too. IE,
yoshi, yoshi, ah,
dinner, dinner, dinner. Yes, there
's pink meat. This is a pig. This is a
cow. Yeah, it's better to turn into a monster. I don't understand that.  I
've heard that it's better to separate fish and meat, but do weneed to
separate the
be sausage
bacon okay
my onion baoni
see onion and leave
me yep yum yum delicious
yum the cheese isso good
Wow cheese come on quickly yum un potato yep  Even
if it's still like that, it feels good. It feels good.
Even if it's just a little bit, it's better than two pieces of cheese.
Maybe 22
[Music]
I want it to feel good.
Even if you don't have the talent for cooking, why are you looking at me and saying, ``What's the
key to
cooking?'' Even if you don't have the talent for cooking, you can still
eat delicious food.It's easy to
make.If you have the talent for cooking, it's even more delicious.It
doesn't matter whether you can eat it or not.
Yes, that's right, European-style takoyaki. It's
perfect, like a party. It's amazing.
The sauce is already on, so I can eat it. I can eat it now. It would
be better if it had sauce.
Let's try it on its own,
really, yeah, BBQ sauce, yeah, coctail.  It's just beef and
pork, but
there are also sausages, shrimp, and fish.  I
don't have chicken today, but yeah, I ca
n't eat anything like grilled chicken. Yeah, yeah, it's
delicious. Me too, it's an explosion of flavor right now.
In a good way in my mouth.
[Music] Yeah, the
potatoes are delicious too. Yeah,
that was good.  I'm with my grandfather
[Music]
Ukibu
Yummy, yummy, yummy, I'm singing a nostalgic song
Yummy, yummy, even the little onions are
delicious Oh yum,
yummy, I love them so much
If there's a lot left over at the end, then there's some uncooked meat,
etc. Trick When haveof
things,
take the oven-roasted form,
MaybeGRILLmeat
fringpan,
put it all in one,
yeah, I see, it's
bigger, but it's all  Let's put it in.
Pour it on top of the cheese. Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's the limit. I
can't make it into rice. Potatoes. Yeah,
there's probably some leftovers, so this sausage.  I
feel like I've been baking forever Wfin,
that's right, limit food,
limit food, where did that phrase
come from? I thought about it myself, yeah, I'm a genius. Oh yeah,
small onions are good. Thank you for being born.
Why was I born,
poop?  The
onions are really bad. When I
grilled the meat, it turned into smoke. I guess I
didn't have enough oil. Mmm, yum,
yum, delicious cheese. Japan has this.  How do you
feel when you see it?
Eat something. I feel like having breakfast, but what are you
going to do? I'm
sorry. It's nighttime. I'm cooking more
sausages. Is there anyone who wants sausages? Yes, the
one from Bekan.  Kako's grilled sausage
Which one do you like? Yes, I like this. It's
grilled a lot. Bacon. Itadakimasu.
I love herb sausage. 520amThis.
Is this all happening at a mizuya? I
think they're all the same, but that's the
type often used for grilled sausages.
Hey, this bacon sausage might have some cheese in
it. Oh yeah, a little bit of it.
Yes, thank you for the meat.Yes, please give me some of this.
Yes, youguyshearthe
grilling.
Normally, I
have an image from overseas of grilling in the garden in the summer.
Yeah, it's difficult to say, but I
want to use this latte as a stream and do this in the summer. ASMR
[Music]
Nemozu ni  There's someone I want in the future
Kaa
Paprika By the way, do you drink?
Yeah peopleknowUSONE
punicawastin I
can handle the alcohol in Laraka-chan's poop, but it's completely different. It's completely different Laben.  You're a big
drinker, yeah, you're mechanically weak. Hey, you could
talk more if the wind wasn't calming down.
You shouldn't overdo it. Yes,
there are people who have eaten delicious pork. Yes, big pork. It
was delicious. It's only about 15%.
Not thatmuch oh 5  I do
n't know if 15% is low, I
don't know, I haven't drank since then, so I don't know,
but it's the same as the book, it's about the same,
but Riruka also gets drunk at about 5%.
OkI mainer 2 Yeah,
but Kihara-senpai told me before that Lyrica
didn't really like drunk people,
so she got really drunk.I
drank, thinking I shouldn't,
but Lyrica-chan was really drunk.  It's
funny. It's okay. It
's okay. We got into lovey-dovey.
When Dr.
was a
girlf girlfriend type, yeah, it's
too tasty, so try not to drink.  The
alcoholic beverages are delicious, so I can understand a little English.
I can now understand what two people are talking about, and I
can even read texts from exhibitions. But I
still can't speak, and it's difficult to speak.  It's
okay, it's okay as long as you have confidence, you
need confidence, yeah, wait, wait, wait, wait, I'm
the Jiggle Master Grill Must be hard, my
job is terrible, I want this meat to be ready.  The
bottom one is
potatoes, but I also have potatoes. Hey, I'll
eat the potatoes, thank you. They're so fluffy and
delicious. Yeah,
vegetables in Japan and other countries are quite different from each other,
but potatoes
and zucchini...  It's almost the same. The
carrots are
quite different. And the cucumbers are also different. Today,
the rainbow juice was also delicious.
I think it's great. No, there's a huge one.
There's a good one too Yeah yeah yeah yeah I don't know
jaancarotIthink
I wanttoeatasSNErika I'll
chew on that alone Just like that Gum Gari
Garigari Really I want to put it in curry too
Ah curry It's
delicious I can't say more
This is bytheway SMissitin
laden Chaa that  I
like smoothies as well as chickpeas.That's why we
fight first.I
want FL bacon to be fried a little.
Hey, bacon, that's good, that's good, that's
good, that's good. Which one should I put in here? It's better to put it in here. I want to put it in. Go ahead, please go ahead. It's stressful. It's stressful.
Hey, hey, it's dangerous. Hey, do you know that?
Everyone.  Japanese
Szazas Stress Yes Stress Yes
But Natsumi Abe was the first.
Maybe it was a cover song. Do
you know Nami Abe?
Oh no, it's a big name from Hello Coro, it's so bad, it's so
bad I sang it,
but I sang that song Tajan, I sang RoboBorobo,
RoboBorobo, RoboBoroBo was the one that was sung by two people.
It's okay, it's okay,
Robo, Robo, Boro, Boro, Boro, Boroden is no good. I
can't even do anything today. Yeah, I'm already drunk.
[Music]  I have to
show it to you, I have to show it, I
can't put it under, I can't show it.
[Music]
Ra-chan-chan, who's gone
too far. [Music] But potatoes, paprika, and bacon, oh, hey, where's that little
onion?  It was delicious, so I
want to put it in. It's watermelon, it's watermelon, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
little onion, sweet, yes, sour, sour.
Sour Kanabe I haven't had sour, haven't I? I
haven't eaten it yet. It's really
delicious just as it is. I don't really like rikalaki, but it's
similar to Raki, but it might not taste like Raki. Try it.
Love. Yeah, I might add it to a salad or something.
Hey, I
want to be able to say more things than that. Yeah, it's
not that simple.
It's a simple word like te.
Guna guna the last thing is guna at the end yeah yeah I can't do it
Pepero UN yeah pepperoni it's a little
scary It's sweet it's
sweet Sweet and sour pie ah yeah flavored vegetables That's a vegetable Fuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuh uh uh uh
nevi
Try ah peperoni ah peperoni mim
has started  Someone grab this and
say there's a chance it might have cheese in it. It's
okay. It's okay. It's okay. I'm baking it right now. It's there,
so I'll eat it. I'll eat it.
Thank you for coming. I'll
give you some vegetables. Maybe the raki
will open up nicely.
But it's a little after all. Those girls have small stomachs. If they
were in a shitty state, they could have eaten more,
but now it's better not to bake them.  I'm baking this, so I'm going to
eat this, so it's better not to bake it.
But if everyone is going to eat it, then I
'll give it to Zukki. Yeah, it's
beautiful. MyWhenBy
forYouWantToGiveA
BIGvarietylike  different meats different veggies and
AllThatButThemore varietyyougivethe moreamountoffoodyou haveButTheisThey selllikesteaks
justI
allthequicklyandputmyfrepa
prepared a lot of
this.I'm
happy about the Austrian culture, but this is the only meal.
Well, today's day
is like a plan, and I've just started planning, and they're doing everything for me
while Lyrica and the others are here.
So, yeah, I'm
pulling the mattress, so I
'm asking them to stop, and they're all in separate rooms, so there
's a lot of privacy.
Yeah, thank you, we can sleep together.
Her Pom Purin Pon Purin Pom Pon
Print Pon Pom Purin Pon Pon Two Jesuses I'll
bring them a little, but
yeah, who knows who they are?
But when I told Rade-chan that I wanted this, she already
went to pick it up the next day.It's
amazing.I did a good job of finding it.I did some research.I wonder if it's there, but I
can't really look into it at all.  like this  I'll just
look up that part.
Thank you so Cure Love Boo. Did you
make it?
That's right. Sanade-chan, who was on the plane,
was in a different terminal. Where is she?
Hey, wahoo, but you made it in time. You're on
time. What departure time is it?  It
seems like Japan has a lot of airports.Oh
yeah, I want to go to a different airport.It
's the same airport, but in a different terminal.Oh
yeah, it's a little far away, I see.  The
terminals at Japanese airports are quite
far away, so it's really far away. Wow, that's
a big deal. No matter who's late, Ra-chan,
I'm a little late, too. I'm about 10 minutes
late, and at the meeting time, I
'm like, oh my god.  I thought I'd come later than that. I
happened to be on time, so let me do it. I
took a lot of planes for the
first time in a while. I went out on my bike. Every time I went out, Raden-chan was on her phone. Oh, I
heard she forgot her phone. Raden-chan...
AndSECONDSHEforgHER
gleswhichwaskindofa
problemBecauseWe
wenttoamuseumandcouldquiteseeallthe
details
the  It's true, I couldn't take a closer look at it because it was
so far away at the museum.
Yeah, I saw that, but
we got too close, and the staff got mad at me. I
asked them to move away, so
please be gentle. You guys should look a little further back. Be kind. Just
because the alarm goes off, everyone is so
kind.  I'm amazed at how nice everyone here is.
Everyone is smiling and
waving like they're going to say something to you.Stand
to yeah
andleaningoverandso
HecameOverwaslike
youguysSTEPbacka
LittleBitotherwise
thealarmisGturn
onbutourexcuseis
thathadNo
glasseslook
CLthosepainsreally
needlooker
AllYeah
Yeah, that's true but
that's true even before I came to AustriaLiliI'm
sorry when I go on a trip I'm sure there are some
strange things and things I can't do,
but please don't hate me.  I
can't help it because you said "Hey, I'm sorry"
Yeah, you're
cute, right?
That's what I said because I'm going to be a ponytail Oh yeah, it's a
cute prank What to do tomorrow I'll
forget Checklist WE
NEEDchecklist Yes,
before we go out Yes, shoes,
pants,
bra areyouwearing
your pantareyou
wearing you need to walk around with knobs,
bythewayonemore
Storyonemoretangent
Whenwewereinthetaxi
tomyhomeYes Sowe
werefregirlsandTAX
DriIwassittinginthefrontandwewereChit
chattinginJapanese
rightandthetaxi DrivernoticedthatI alsospeaklikefluent JapaneseHewaslikeso impressedandhe startedasking questionsandthenHe
HewasHewasreally excited  That's because I wanted to talk about that story,
so I lowered it a little. Yeah,
that's what it means.
It was good,
Chanbi Ande Yes, you were a good person, you were a good person It was, yes, it
was fun, yeah, wait,
Small Onion is so goo Nene, it's
delicious, it's sweet, yeah,
Sweet Small Onion is there in Japan,
isn't this?
Yes, but it's close to Raki  I think it's
almost Raki, yes, I want another one.I
want this.This suppa is so sweet.The
cheese cheese is a little heavy again.Thanks
to the poop, it feels a little fresh again.Yeah, yeah,
yeah.  It's
so delicious. I've
only seen those big onions. Yeah, I wonder
if they put it in vinegar. I
wonder if it's vinegar. Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's so good. I
ate a lot today at the Christmas market.
But not just that summer. That cheese,
that Australia.  I
ate things like noodles and fries.The
Christmas market is
fun.I
heard that there is a Christmas market in Japan, but
have you ever been to one?  I
wonder if there's something similar in Japan that they're copying right now. Yeah, but in Yokohama or something, there's a
red brick street, and it's not really a Christmas
market, but there are
a lot of small shops lined up.
Have you ever seen or heard of Noha
? I wonder if it's an event in Japan. Yeah, I
know it's held at Aka Rega. I've been there before. I
actually went there with my family when I was a kid, so I
don't remember much about it.  memory  I do
n't have one, but it's an amazing Christmas
market.While I was drinking that mulled wine, I
looked around and saw all the amazing buildings
surrounding it.Is it possible to be so happy as to be able to
drink wine while touring the Christmas market?  I
was really happy. Yeah, I do
n't know much about the place where we stayed, ate, drank, etc. I
shared that desk with people.
Everyone was kind, right? They were kind at school.  The
teacher's older sister was there, too.
That's amazing. Today at the Christmas market, the three
of us went around and saw all sorts of shops. As we
went around, we visited probably about
10 times today. Yeah, you're good at Japanese, are
n't you?
I've asked Japanese people about 10 times today, how did you learn Japanese,
and when I told them I learned it myself when I was that young,
everyone said it was amazing.
That's amazing, and the other two are
Lily Laden and they're just too cute.That's
where the potato and cheese noodles were made.I
wanted to try both of them, but I
didn't want to buy the two potions.  After all, it's
a lot, so I felt like I couldn't get enough of it,
so today when I was looking at it mentally and physically, I realized that I
could make that half of that thing I asked about.
If you ask me, no, I
don't usually do it, but yeah, the three of us are cute, so it's
okay.Okay, I'll do it for the three of you.Okay, the
three of us, or should I say Riran, are cute, so I
did it for you.You're so cute.Yeah,
just.  Yeah, yeah, we
talked a lot, Yuka-chan, and now we're talking about it
in English. Translate it into English.
justHalf
andersay
Ladyguysguys It
was so big, so big, so happy.
[Music]
Ah, I was a little drunk.
Yeah, I did it. No, that guy spoke great English.
Well,
in Austria, almost everyone
can speak both German and English.  Yes, yes,
yes, I was surprised. Yes, it's completely falling
. It's falling, it's falling, it's falling.
Thank you. It was delicious. I
ate it.  When I
eat with my friends, I
eat about 10 times as much. Usually we eat so much more.  It's a
little more beautiful, it
tastes like nanaka without using sosu sauce.  It
was delicious. I didn't even use the flavor at the end. It
tasted amazing with the vegetables and cheese. My stomach was so full.
[Music]
Hmm, what do you think? There's raclette cheese,
right? Well,
there aren't that many raclette cheeses in Japan.
It's a particularly easy cheese, but it's a bit textured, but
actually, even if you don't have that cheese
, I think you can use a similar cheese at all.Yeah, you could
use something like Morella, but Morella.  I don't
think so. Or rather, the taste is different. Yeah, yeah, that's right. I do
n't think Rela dissolves very well.
How about one more glass of wine? I'm drinking red wine. No, I'm not drinking red wine. I'm
drinking red wine and I
'm drinking white.  I want to drink some red before going to bed.I
leave it to Larade-chan.Let's go, go, go, go-ran-
chan, I can drink endless amounts of red.
Lili, drink,
drink. If Rika-chan drinks, it might be bad. I'm
already a little drunk. Good luck with the wine right now.
[Music]
Was dizzy, dizzy,
squishy, dizzy, yup, drink the alcohol.
Hear-senpai prepared it for me.  Thank you for giving me this
. Even though Chara-senpai doesn't drink, you went out of your way to prepare it for me. Let's
drink it all,
both Austrian and Austrian.
People A people FRANCEaustrihas really good wines and with EuropeThey makesome of the best wines from
whatIknowwhenI
studiedinHOTEL
Schoolwehavegood
onesjustGO
International
]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Kamai
Gaaiti demoze, so it's zero calories Eh, I
have a glass of wine while it's delicious.1  I feel
like it's only used once a year It's
only for moms, right? Only moms use it finally
buttheresuchaPainin
theASStowashinthe
DishwasherSoGladI
havetouse
themDISwasher What's that in Japanese?  I don't
have any money at home, right? I have some money
in my house. I feel sorry for the poor girl at my parents' house. I
wash it with my hands. I also have food that I've never used.  I
wash them in the machine, and I
use those plates instead of those dry ones.That's amazing, but I
don't use them very often,
so I use a plastic spoon, and I use a plastic spoon.  It's
not fashionable, it's fashionable
. That's true,
but let's use it again and again. Let's use a dishwasher.
It's
okay. It's okay to diss something. It's okay while we use it.
But I have to wash the dishwasher,
yeah, yeah, what? I
'm washing the dishwasher, so I have to wash the dishwasher. I've never washed the dishwasher before,
but
there's also a button that automatically washes it myself.  That's
right, I asked them to wash it themselves.
Maybe it depends on who you are.
Well, sometimes there are a lot of
things like this, and if you put in a dish with something left over,
sometimes the dishwasher gets a little dirty.
But yeah yeah yeah yeah, it's
okay to put the rough things in the trash can,
so it wouldn't
be a great thing.
[Music]
Hey, come me, yeah, soOneLast
Icome
to
SIhavebed
BS
Ada, hey, it might really
stop. It's okay to stop, it might stop soon. I'm going to
bed with the idea I got from the project.
Wait, wait, what project did I get? That
project was about a mattress to sleep on. That's
amazing. Well, I'm glad I had a place to put a second bed in the first place. It just so happened that there was only room for a dance room. I was
trying to make it into a dance room.  That's amazing
because that's the only room
I put in the bed and it was filled so the room was already
turned into a guest room so I got it confirmed.
Wow, that's amazing, but I sleep in a queen bed. I
usually have a
big bed project, please. It's the same thing that everyone is talking about.
Why did Lyrica-chan get a project like that? I don't know why.
Maybe it's
because she sleeps a lot. She
's broadcasting her sleeping habits. Something like Lyrica's diet.  It's like a transplanted animal,
and it's a project for human life. I
see that you and Rika tend to get angry. If you
leave it alone, the company that worries about you will
also
[Music]
All
President: That's right. I often get that food-related thing.
Yeah, I just recently came here.
Yeah, I'll show you next time, but I'll cook separately. I'll
do a proper cooking stream, and I'll show you
all the knives, cutting boards, etc. from my project.
No, no, no, IAL
havesomeofthewhite
ThingsSHOWthemin
AnotherCookingwas
goodTESthe
ceraniceCYeah, yahoo Kiara
Everything in Senpai is wonderful
[Music]
Ah,
Love
It's not that great, but it's spacious  It's
really big.
This is the cat's house. It's important to the cat. He
's in his suitcase.
[Music]
Hey, I want to take a picture. I'll be
deaf tomorrow. [Music] He might be out playing, but it's
still early in the day.
Maybe it's better to come over here and fix the wind
Alcohol
[laughing]
Oh okay, let's disinfect with alcohol
[Music]
Ratotalkto Yeah, just a little bit more
Raden-chan, I'll ask you to shut up tomorrow, and I'll shut up,
shut up, yeah Day
Afterwards, Raden-chan, I
told the doctor that it's okay to drink alcohol. It's
okay to do what I'm told. That guy who doesn't show up.
So please, everyone, thank you
for
thinking
[laughs]
Please give me the project. Thank you for watching.
Thank you to all the Japanese people for being so early in the morning.
Thank you for waiting since 4 a.m. I'm sorry. Yeah, I ca
n't help it, I can't help it. Moshi karaoke streaming.
If we're going to do it the day after tomorrow, it'll probably be at the same time.Yes,
KaraokeHostandgivethe
girlsGoodTimeandyou
knowhavethemseeall
theniceThingsYeahso
givetimeI'll show you lots of good things.
Choki-choki
Choki-choki Choki-choki I
wonder if I can put the pistons together.
[Music] It's
hard to form a heart. Someone made a heart.
Bye-bye.
[Music]
Say it, Afra
Alfie Alfiiiiiiiiiiiiii
[Music]
To