[Music]
foreign
hello I have hat
I has hat
uh I made it myself
ah
um
you like my hat new hat I love hats you
know that right
it's it's supposed to look like the
Wonderland has ah I think it does
thank you thank you
what people already again complaining
about me not using dark mode I don't
even I didn't even know that there's ah
is that
no okay I thought that's because the sun
I didn't even know there's a dark mode
on the switch
nah I don't wanna
I mean it's my eyes
come on come on well today guys we are
starting a new series
uh my first time playing good Zelda on
stream
not my first time playing a Zelda game
uh but kind of probably
I mean I don't remember well but I think
it's kind of the first time that I play
a Zelda game from beginning to the end
on my own because I mean I probably
played some games
um alone before but not not until the
end I think
probably like with Wind Waker it's been
so long I don't remember if I ever
cleared it alone but I I played it with
my brother here and then and I played it
alone
and uh I did kind of touch a little bit
on um
what what's it called uh
uh
uh the dark one with uh that Majora's
Mask
uh Twilight Princess yeah yeah yeah
cause my my brother got it and uh I I
tried it a little bit but I didn't
really play much because I was a bit too
scared like the darkness was not really
my taste you know I'm a phoenix I like
light things
um besides that oh yeah I've watched a
lot of complete playthroughs of
probably every single Zelda game
even the ones on DS uh yeah I've watched
full playthroughs of all of those
mm-hmm
my childhood I definitely played the the
the yeah even Spirit Tracks I even
watched a flavor of that it's been a
phantom tracks spirit glass Spirit hour
whatever I've watched them all
do you guys say Spirit Tracks just to uh
say two games at the same time
uh Minish Cap watched it so Ocarina of
Time
I
uh Phantom alert
yeah that's really confusing because it
sounds like something that actually
exists Spirit Tracks
[Laughter]
now the the Ocarina of the lamp
the one um the one on the uh Nintendo 64
uh which was a Ocarina of Time right
right right the one where you go on the
horse and it's 3D it's like scuffed 3D
right right yeah yeah I played that one
but but the Kiara was very very small
very tiny so also did not finish on her
own only played a little bit but never
finished
um
yeah eh I mean not scuffed but like it's
not it's like it's 3D but it's like not
that beautiful
we compared to now
that's what I mean it's not the but
Baghdad was insanely beautiful back then
for yeah for uh before yeah I know I
know it was at the time it was
crazy like I remember when I played that
I was like holy [\h__\h] this looks like
real life
Oracle gang Oracle uh there was some
Oracle game wasn't there I probably 100
play uh watched a full playthrough of
that yes yes 100 play for of all of them
um is there any other that I played on
my own
besides windbreaker Ocarina of Time
I don't I don't I don't think so
of that
Majora's Mask I don't think it's a link
to the past I don't think so but I
wanted to play the remake of Link to the
Past eventually because it's really cute
he's really cute
Hyrule Warriors oh no
a link between Alex Awakening wait
that's what I'm I'm so confused
there's so many kids
[Music]
no not yet because I know I I felt like
playing it on stream maybe one at some
point and before that you know I was
just watching play I'm watching the I'm
watching I'm watching my third
my third full playthrough of breath of
the wild right now
I watched I watched one full flavor of
Arena 100 revolta with all the Crux uh
are they called Crocs in English
I watched one full one like what three
years ago four years ago when it came
out
and then I watched the I watched one
playthrough of uh you know the the high
difficulty one the master whatever
and now I'm watching the third full play
for 100
[Laughter]
I don't know there's something really
relaxing about watching someone Play
Breath of the wild I master quest are
you watching it from dontendo that's
right let's go
oh yeah it starts right away that's why
I stopped and went back to the home
screen
it Tales of a war upon my scale and
porosity the likes of which would have
never been what
this happened too fast on dark one dark
grateful Day the Earth cracked white and
Mild malefic the forces rushed through
from the Fisher let's
I know it's a big
question in the moment I need to read uh
they mounted the vertical assault upon
the surface people driving the land into
deep despair
okay that was readable
[Music]
because it made it
with noise
[Music]
they did all this and they lost to take
the ultimate power protected by her
grace
oh it's crackly isn't it yeah that's
wait a second uh
um okay
okay is it should be fixed now handed
down by gods of old this power game is
holder the means to make any desire a
reality such was the light
opposite in the care of the Goddess I
have literally no idea what I'm reading
right now
[Music]
hands of the evil swarming the lands
the goddess garbage the surviving humans
on an outcropping of Earth
forward beyond the reach after him
demonic hordes for The Horde Beyond even
the clouds
[Music]
ancient ones
my hat is perfect isn't it with the
humans say the goddess Joint Forces with
the land dwellers and fought the evil
forces sealing them away at last peace
was restored to the surface
oh this is the origin of the fella games
right from what I've heard this game
is like number one in the timeline right
this is a tale that you humans have told
for many ages generation to generation
should have done the echo from the
beginning but there are other Legends
long hidden away from memory that are
intertwined with this Tale
now a new Legend bound to this great
story stands ready to be revealed
legend that will be forged by your own
hand
and my chicken's wings
the legend of Kiara
that remote I say that that reminds me
of my intro my book intro for my debut
wow
Skyward Sword HD
now I know that there is a motion
the thingy with the with the joy-cons
but if it's okay I'll try if it do you
guys think guys is it okay I can can I
play with my with my game uh with my
with my controller you think that's okay
Pro Controller using that oh hello
huh
is this the same thing that I just
oh yeah yeah okay okay I don't need to
see a second
okay
can I wait I mean we can uh we can try
to
[Music]
um
switch switch do a switch over here
every now and then because I heard that
the motion controls are actually really
good uh with the joy-cons
I heard that from
don't handle
all right uh what how uh okay new
adventure
foreign
uh should we keep no should we hey but
it's gonna be a bullet I don't want to
name him Kiara
should we just keep playing let's just
keep playing
okay
link Kiana God yeah no it's okay link
[Music]
It's gotta be a link
um
cute
wow although Kuda doesn't have bottom
teeth or does she or does she
send me this ah Nintendo presents
and what does it present
The Legend of Zelda
Phoenix fire just kidding Skyward Sword
eat it eat it
wow
[Music]
a big boat with big snoots
you have a big burp with big snow
ah the air feels good in my hair that
rhymed
[Music]
wow wow
weird looking dude
so
he has answers
by the way I have jockey milk with me
[Music]
wow that was pretty
Zelda yeah
oh
I
[Music]
doubt is Sherry a princess at this point
no no no right
[Music]
hello it's me God you look you look um
you look okay
his face is uh my mama
she had eye bags of Doom
rise link the time has come for you to
awaken
you are fated to have a hand in a great
Destiny and it will soon fine tune
the time has come for you to awaken link
[Music]
link is hot
he can take me out for some fried
chicken
oh both is not
a poop
oh
[Laughter]
disgusting
we got an invitation in in you look very
tired do you always look like that
hey sleepy head I know how much you like
to sleep in so I'm guessing this letter
will be your alarm clock this morning
did I guess right
um
I mean it was also my boob
rise and shine Wing today is the wing
ceremony you promised to meet me before
it starts remember
you better not keep me waiting Zelda
mm-hmm
okay
oh my God this is so cool oh my God okay
ah
fixed camera
oh no wait ah there we go uh
[Music]
um
I see okay
[Music]
come on
is that a what is that is that a cat a
bunny what what is that thing up there
oh well we gotta go I think what are my
plans
what up
hold out yeah that I already figured
that out thank you I'm smart
hey guys no I know oh my God you know
that oh
where where
show me that thing again
oh well hello
morning link so today's the week
ceremony are you ready
all I'm saying is everyone else is out
practicing that the plaza when you seem
pretty relaxed about the whole thing of
course that Crimson left link of you is
just something special I'd feel pretty
confident riding him too
my bird won the last ceremony what even
I don't think he could beat that red
Tower of yours where is a bird's true
speed
you know race always comes down to the
skill of the ride especially if it's a
German Rider
so something of a bird researcher around
here so you know if you ever find
yourself in the need of a bird expertise
come still Pippin
all right what
I just talked to you if you were heading
over with the blinds and the quickest
way is out the door on the ground floor
the exit on the top floor is still low
so you obviously can't get out there
yeah I'm something of a bird expert
myself
what's taking the lunch lady so long I'm
going to have the void with her later
[Music]
they said ground floor are we on the
ground floor I guess not
[Music]
wait how do we Dash oh
hey hey
are you okay you need help
ah
[Music]
good morning link uh today's the big
Wing ceremony right I wanted to play too
but I I didn't make the cut so I'm stuck
back here at the Academy plus I've got
to move these barrels over to the
kitchen
I was hoping to at least be able to
cheer you on link but uh I guess that's
the way it goes uh go up there and wow
them buddy
oh thank you I would love to help you
but oh this this the sign it looks like
Livewire or is it helping me
it was like Live Wire
[Music]
let me go go
flying water
[Music]
I'm gonna destroy it up
can I throw I wanna throw
ah okay whatever
[Music]
foreign
good morning to you link today's finally
the day of the long-awaited wing
ceremony are you feeling ready oh I just
remembered there's something I'd like to
ask you about a Target me and we can
have a quick chat
foreign
what's that L which one is that is
excellent always remember you can Target
someone to talk to them easily and even
when there isn't anything to Target it's
a convenient way to quickly face your
view forward
oh but it's a little silly to carry on a
conversation from this distance why
don't you come join me up here
oh yeah
hahaha
you should be able to climb up if you
dash up to the top of that wooden box
don't you think
then you can make that jump fairly
easily dry clamping up here
while moving home oh God I hate the
camera oh I hate the camera oh I hate it
all right uh I'm moving hold B
and how do I jump oh
yep
automatic jump foreign
[Music]
so what are you up to rushing to get
some last minute bird Writing Practice
in this morning link
oh you have someone to meet ah Zelda's
waiting for you isn't she
[Music]
timing then
Zelda's father Headmaster a guy for has
a pet named Mia and uh well she's
scampered off again
[Music]
foreign
look over there do you see her
[Music]
the Headmaster is so busy working with
Zelda preparing for the ceremony I
thought that maybe I should feed her but
the ceremony is about to start and I
just put on a fresh set of clothes and
oh well you see will you help me out and
go retrieve Mia for me
let's go
[Music]
fantastic so you'll do it I know you're
in a hurry so I really appreciate you
taking the time to help
foreign
[Music]
you should be able to climb up somewhere
over there if you hang off that ledge
there you can climb onto the roof from
the other side I'm terribly sorry but I
know you're quite the climber I really
do appreciate it
[Music]
uh what's from where what
what's that what's that what's that
my line by our energy back
oh I'm wire energy hello
oh a lion like did you manage to get
even a rank of sleep last night
uh figured you might have been tossing
and turning all night thinking about the
big ceremony today what am I doing or
just fixing Escape here it's been
squeaking lately can't have that on the
sales ceremony
hey you haven't already forgotten to
send you prayers to the goddess this
morning
let's face the bird statue over there
and say a short prayer to save your
progress
oh as you know those bird statues are
all over skyloft it's about time you get
into habit of stopping in the Statue
every time you run by one
a prayer in time saves nine if you know
what I'm saying
dude it's okay
but I guess I can quickly uh turn the I
think up
I think I prefer to do it that way
yeah just one button
a box
Above So praise attack
everyone say your prayers thank you for
giving me my life
thank you for raising me
and build and always will be boob all
right how do you do how do we do
ouch that was not it
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait what what what
yeah yeah
[Music]
thanks for praying guys I'm not a cult
yes yes
do I have to go up here wait can I move
the boxes
okay so I guess we gotta go up there
again
all right all right all right yeah
[Music]
okay what
but yeah
on the camera ah
okay can I go up there
ah another hold up what's a leap a leap
of faith
ah my stamina goes down well I'll do
that now hold on
[Music]
seem to have a better time with the
camera
so and up the leaves we go
[Music]
what was I supposed to do up here sorry
my birth burn not that thing
wait no uh the Box
push and push and push and push and push
[Music]
it's a bear flying
look Kayla are you a cattle what are you
what oh my God it's so cute
it is
what the [\h__\h] was that did you guys see
that was that a bug
oh
preferred up yet no no
what the hell is wrong with you where do
I put this thing
okay why
oh oh my god oh you can throw it
why would I wha why is the game why is
he getting telling me to throw it
I don't even know at what times
[Music]
what
at what time does it activate itself
foreign
[Music]
you look very creepy
how could I creepy from falling you look
way cute up close
thank you now where do we go where do we
go with that sorry I have no idea where
do I bring it oh
me what happened to that
huh
[Music]
I got onto the guy above oh
all right all right all right uh yeah
how do we get I'm back up here with you
huh
I got a 400 room right
I am struggling
how do I throw me out there foreign
onto the boxes
we can just
[Music]
ours pick up and then said r
ah
[Music]
I
am full
[Music]
sorry
oh I'll find you again
huh well
where are you
look
I think oh my God this is at the very
top
at the very top
[Music]
I think yeah I think I set the
temperature
I lost it I lost it
[Music]
I lost it I'm a husband
where the [\h__\h] are you
yeah
oh man that's why that's why you gotta
keep your pets at home
okay so uh here uh
[Music]
there you go
I have it it took me long enough
oh nice work uh you've brought her back
safe and sound
sorry for troubling you with this I know
you're busy link I suppose I should feed
Mia now
please tell the Headmaster that we found
his pet he should be up by the statue of
the goddess
[Music]
ah I believe Zelda is there with him so
you should hurry along oh yes I should
uh give you a reward it's not much but
uh please take this and don't tell
others
[Music]
nice thank you bye-bye
okay
up here right
wow it's so pretty give me that
[Music]
foreign
oh
hey good morning link
[Music]
I'm glad to see my last one got you out
of the bed
I was pretty sure you'd sleep in and
forget to meet me this morning
[Music]
but look at this instrument and look at
this outfit
they're mine to use in a ceremony today
since I'll be playing the realm of the
goddess
aren't they beautiful
especially this instrument
they tell me it's just like the one of
the Goddess that was said to have in the
Legends
sounds gorgeous too I asked father about
it and he says it's called a hype
[Music]
and look at these clothes
I made these this wrap myself and we get
to use it in today's ceremony
between the harp and his outfit I'm
going to make a Great Goddess today
I got you up early this morning because
I wanted you to be the first to see me
like this link oh
so how do I look oh great
foreign
thanks link
[Music]
we're getting here tonight guys
ah there you are Zelda are you well or
sorry
are you ready for the ceremony
oh hello father
[Music]
uh link
you're here too outstanding
encouraging to see you up so early
giving you capacity for sleep
no doubt today's ceremony had you too
excited to close your eyes for once
[Music]
if you're in today's ceremonial race you
get to participate in the post race
Rachel with Zelda so give it your best
out there
[Music]
yeah how about that
father I don't know if he can do it wow
she got she got no trust in me
recently link hasn't been practicing
much at all for the ceremony
oh don't expose me like that
even when he's out riding his left wing
he's just lazily gliding around probably
daydreaming
I don't know what he's thinking he's
going to have to be in perfect control
of his bird to win today
[Music]
no need to raise yourself Tilda
though you may have a point today's Wing
ceremony tests the skill of the rider as
well as his bone to his bird
Victory will not come easily
and
as you pointed out I haven't seen him
practicing as hard as some of the other
students
but you've known him since you were both
very little you should know better than
to fret about him
you see link and his loftwing share a
special connection I've never seen
anything quite like it
ah above
as you know each of us in skyloft is but
one half of a pair
we're only made whole by our Loft Wings
to guard and birds that the goddess
bestows upon each of us is a symbol of
her Divine protection okay but this is
just divine
when we are young every one of us meets
our left wing another great statue of
the goddess it's quite a big moment as
I'm sure you recall
his eyes look like they're about to pop
out
they look so fake
ah for that first meeting between link
and his left wing was extraordinary
the bird that came to him was crimson
loftwing it is a breed so rare we were
sure for some time that it had vanished
from the line
yeah and the body in this but the boy
and his brother seemed to share a
profound connection from the moment they
met
foreign
first met
where's sight
the little boy just hopped up on their
Boot and gracefully flew away without
even a moment of instruction
they were meant for each other
and judging by how jealous you are that
day I'd say the friendship he shared
with his bird didn't go unnoticed by you
my dear
die how much does he talk
or I don't want to ride dead
uh but who can blame you I'm sure you're
the only one envious of the powerful
Bond shared by link and his burp
anyone who is a part of something
special is bound to catch some nasty
looks sooner or later
those jealous [\h__\h] out there
unbelievable
[Music]
is not father this ceremony is part of
the final test for those training to
become Knights of skyloft
if link doesn't fly fast enough during
the race
[Music]
what if link messes up his pick chance
what if he's not allowed to become a
knight
she really cares about me huh
calm down my dear and we'll be fine
honestly it's almost as though you've
become a completely different person
when you were about link
are you perhaps in love with him
I mean we all know you are
you are in every goddamn game of this
series
is like Destiny or something I don't
know man listen
you better fly your heart out today at
the very least you'll need to squeeze in
a little practice time before the race
ah come on you'll thank me later
all right all right let's do it
okay here we are go on now jump off the
ledge The Edge and call your loftwing
it's almost time for the ceremony so try
to practice seriously for once
huh oh yeah you can't since you put it
out there
oh I get it you're trying to weasel out
of having to practice nice try but
you're not following me
oh
yeah
go ahead just press down and call you
laughing
um
what the hell something's something
[Music]
is She Gonna Save Me
maybe maybe the real link was Zelda all
along
oh she did save me
oh you too all right
come on Boop that was nothing going on
I'm sorry friend I didn't mean to push
you so hard you didn't sprain your wing
did you what about me oh
whatever
this is very odd link what could have
possibly happened to your left wing
for a bird to ignore the call of his
master it's unheard of which is funny
because the bird didn't hear my
call
it my call was unheard of
huh
[Music]
and you still can sense your bird nearby
handling
this is quite a problem especially
considering the wing ceremony is about
to start
[Music]
when you said you couldn't sense you
loved playing well I should have
believed you
I'm sorry
yeah I was lying oh where's the truth I
need to tend to my own left wing so I'll
catch up with you later
unless you want mayonnaise you'd better
go ahead and go on ahead and see if you
can find where your bird has gone
[Music]
now that was bad
[Laughter]
[Music]
sorry chocolate milk time
man how did it get to be so late if I
recall correctly this year instructor
Orwell is presiding over the ceremony
you know the one with the voice that
makes the chat go crazy
link you should go explain the situation
to him and see if he's willing to delay
the race a little so that you can find
your verb
[Music]
cute she's actually pretty cute about
father you're gonna help myself to
Academy if link asks instructor hold
well he probably just come to talk to
you about it
[Music]
uh quite true as usual you'll make an
excellent point my dear but I just you
know wanted to go to chat and make the
chat happy me go crazy a little bit more
because they've been literally I don't
know first thing over that voice
very well I'll explain the situation to
him myself then like run along and tell
instruct the whole world to come see me
in my quarters
[Music]
[Laughter]
link I didn't want to talk to you I
wanted to talk to the bird
I'm going to turn to my bird and make
sure he's not hurt help I'll catch up
with you later you're going to see it if
anyone in town knows what happened to
your loving oh okay I thought I was
supposed to go to horwell
okay
okay oh
don't let yourself off Sky left at that
place with the ex Marcus Plaza
aha it's a very other side of the map
right now okay
that's right away ceremony
[Music]
here
hold on so we go here and then we go
here and then we go here and then we go
here oh but I mean on the way
we're supposed to
like this horrible in the in the night
Academy right now
bird statue was that circus
graveyard oh dude there's a [\h__\h]
graveyard that's that's where I'm gonna
be soon
have you read a map before you can press
miners anytime to see a map of the area
remember press miners
okay okay chill manners
wow
all right all right uh
oh
not a hotel
[Music]
oh
okay thank you
[Music]
that was five seconds of flying really
why is the birds so [\h__\h] up
um
all right let's go ask students find the
whole world dude
he's right over there all right
organelle
oh what oh wait what was his voice
what's wrong link you're looking a
little pale
what
your left wing is missing how strange
and troubling and do you think you can
find him was that the voice
[Music]
you're going to start looking for him
now how will you make it back in time to
fly in the ceremony
should I try
shut up
it looks like your participation in the
ceremony hinges on a feather or not you
can find that what
are you Trevor G
Inger something
[Music]
oh my
God
even he makes those jokes
you know foreign
before surprising surprising
um excuse me
I see so the Headmaster has summoned me
all right then I'll go speak with him
immediately I still owe you for helping
me out earlier so don't worry about the
ceremony for now you focus on finding
your Loft Wing you look like you're uh
from uh Lord of the Rings
all right where are the students
[Music]
um
in here
are you student
men open doors for a lady anymore how
long am I supposed to Stand Here Waiting
for a little
she watched chivalry
oh it's healing I say eagle called
flustered did something happen
what you can't find your left wing
I don't know what to tell you I've been
here at school the whole time
okay
I will open the door for you
chivalry
aha Knight Academy perfect that's
probably where some of the people are
this is a shared bath
[Music]
wow
nice I take back
[Music]
oh sorry not here no student okay
Zelda is that a room oh
wait no students here what the hell
maybe downstairs
foreign
[Music]
no running in the Halls okay
okay
gross
no okay whatever I guess I can't go into
the rooms
then let's go outside
where do we go I feel like I'm stuck
here
oh wait we can go here wasn't that door
closed before
wow
what is you
are you stupid you look like an onion
[Music]
so come on please what
well that's impressed else
L down ah
okay ow
another video
oh
you got a blue ruby
I see my boss is gonna die today
is that how it's gonna be
okay no mine's not gonna move
oh is that a heart thingy oh okay but
I'm not lagging any hearts found
[Music]
oh
wait which one is talking right now
yeah no gorillas that show was a pain
what with all the scratching and picking
uh of course it was you thought it'd be
Crimson laughter and my dad who's gonna
go down without a fight
but we got him and I don't care how full
on top of those birds it's supposed to
be he's not getting out of that pen
anytime some boys
um
oh dear
are you calling
wow so yeah just how long have you been
standing there
okay
tomorrow yeah
what's your problem anyway oh wait I got
it you're here to talk about today's
race I can see it in those dopey eyes of
yours
they're bleeding oh crows can you please
find it in your heart to let me win
today please
you're just desperate to win so you can
get something a long time or tell me a
funny Statue Of God is at the end of the
ceremony
well sorry pal Rose doesn't do charity
for wicks my advice work hard and wish
with all your heart you might even come
in second
time
his eyes his face
where's that scruffy bottle red feathers
I can't imagine what could have happened
to him I don't really think this tiny
brain got confused by all the clouds and
got lost
nice hair
you lay off my door right when you lay
off my door my door right now or I'm
flat too everyone knows I've got this
like his pompadour in town
you know we're all getting tired of how
you never let anyone forget you and
Zelda go way back
you've been friends since you were a
little kids ride big deal it doesn't
change the fact that you float for life
with
life
would you wake up straight enough and
grow a backbone already
[Music]
it's like you are dragging I wanted to
Academy for the mud
and just who might you be talking about
Grace
[Music]
cute don't even try it Chris you're
picking on link again
he's a student at the Academy like all
of us
why do you insist on bullying him around
so much
yeah I suppose
you suppose suppose what
[Music]
uh
okay
forget it I wasn't supposing anything
okay there we are out of here boys hope
you find your bird or else you're gonna
have to sit outside
okay idiots
[Music]
that could be a major setback towards
Knighthood so find a bird will get real
used today so failure to special flavor
foreign
[Music]
I hate to say it but I'm beginning to
suspect that those Blockheads had
something to do with your left Wing's
disappearance
[Music]
link those guys aren't going to help us
find your bird so we'd better start
searching
[Music]
I'll fly around the skyloft and see if I
can spot any trace of your bird
father said he'd talk to the instructor
how well about building the side of the
wing ceremony so don't worry we'll find
your bird in time
oh she's cute
[Music]
why is girls so popular in the chat
Sanders watching
really
[Music]
look at that
I'm sure he likes the voices that I do
[Music]
why do you guys like him so much what
the [\h__\h]
all right oh I'm supposed to look for my
bird right
[Music]
hello have you seen my bird
oh what's wrong link what your left wing
is missing oh that's terrible I was so
looking forward to seeing that red blur
streak through the sky
no no I haven't seen him why don't you
look for him by the statue of the
Goddess you'll have a good view of the
whole town from way up there
the statue because this is a great big
statue in the north of skyloft
it's at that place with the Xbox ah okay
okay okay
oh thank you
look at map
go straight
go straight can you do that yes
um unless something stops me
[Music]
ah
over here
I have some information about your lock
screen come over here I don't remember
how I did his voice
wait where the hell are you where are
you Google
gonna jump down here oh thank God
[Music]
what she's looking for you
I heard you love when he's gone missing
so I gotta join in the search and get
this when I asked pledge what he knew he
started acting weird
I'm so sorry link I really wanted to
tell you what if girls found out I told
you he sounds like rose supposed him to
keep quiet about it I'll go on to tell
him the truth
that's just a little while ago when I
was cleaning the dining hall gross and
his bodies came
they didn't notice I was there
and started talking about their plan to
hide your loved Wing I wanted to on your
link but just as I tried to sneak away
Chris and his gang grabbed me
and they said that if I told you they'd
make sure I would never be able to ride
the bird bevel again not even a chicken
it sounds like grooves and his buddies I
had a plan to capture your bird and hide
them near about the follow I went near
what the fire would mean a quicker let's
take a look at your map
hahaha
yeah that's it throughout the day I
think it means a lot of automatic deal
with it because uh and yeah they're
right there there that's it
give me a link I can't help being such a
coward I'm really sorry
[Music]
foreign a mixing up language
remember that there were some dangerous
things there creepy Scully things you'll
need to carry a sword
[Music]
command that go into the sparring Hall a
while ago you should ask you should go
ask him if you came back
all right okay what what am I asking for
[Music]
foreign
the sword is in the back room going back
go back there and get it I'll be here
for a while so if there's anything you
don't understand about handling a sword
go ahead and ask
okay okay
so many characters
uh hi
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
it looks like it has a fairly sharp
blade
press plus and then a time to look at
their eyes are carrying oh
oh
I like this interface it's killed
tarantula
[Music]
and Pokemon Gathering here okay Pokedex
okay
[Music]
slices up slice it up slices her up real
nice
there's a lot used to practicing
refreshed what we saw sharply forward to
Fresh if you need to know more about
that check help oh [\h__\h] yeah right this
is where probably most control is good
foreign
[Music]
out there it
wait what what
did you teach me uh press R down
[Music]
really flick are into the Reds and you
want to swing your sword
[Music]
eh
yeah
[Music]
wow
I mean I can't I can just you know
continuously like crazily move it around
like that and hope that it hits
something
and
[Music]
um
wait what
[Music]
ah I don't know how I did that
oh my God okay
um
[Music]
I'm I'm too lazy to get out the the
other ones
vertical slash hold your sword straight
up and then swinging straight down and I
think I did that before when [\h__\h]
around
okay nice
side slash slasher design make a clean
cut okay
[Music]
Hold Up Hold the lock on button oh wait
can I do it again
no can I do it again please oh there we
go okay but this one
ah
[Music]
um
I don't know man
[Music]
yeah yeah tell me tell me
wait did I miss out on one I guess I did
okay you can stop talking
I want you to Spin Attack
okay help
yeah I wanna I wanna learn to spin the
type but I guess I forgot one thing yeah
this one okay
so
hi
hi hi hi
[Music]
I wanted another thing I want to try out
the uh motion
attack
I guess it's gonna be
with the Ice stick
oh
like our quickly left right left
wait was that not in you don't seem like
your usual self stand in the center of a
pack of enemies and swing your sword it
was just the right time that's how you
do it I mean I think that was pretty
good too
[Music]
okay okay
okay one more
right and left right
you think I moved you have to get all of
them okay okay I'll do it again
why can't I just do it like this
[Music]
how do you want me to do this dude
is this teaching me
um the controls with the uh the the the
Pro Controller right now and if I were
to use the motion controls it would it
would acknowledge and recognize it
immediately and tell me different
controls
[Music]
oh damn
yeah
maybe I should switch one second but
doesn't even work when like wait a
second let me try
[Music]
thank you
okay
I got the controllers
uh price Eleanor okay I'm ready
oh
yeah the thing is dealt like does it
matter where my when my
where am I thinking uh
where where does it think my screen is
where does it think I am
because like my my thingy my base is
under the table
and this press with y
ah
wait no let me do that again can I do it
again can I do it again
[Music]
I wanna I wanna do that again
why to reset the location
uh
[Music]
oh all right
[Laughter]
when your enemy is down targeted with
that Ellen first have added to Lando
available okay okay
do a side flash on that log when it's
down try finishing it off with this
technique technique
[Music]
and then ah what I could have said l
oh
move to use right after you use your
Shield or a well-placed Spin Attack to
knock an enemy on its back oh but
monsters don't stay down for so long so
you'll have to land the Fatal blow quick
before they get up
oh
[Music]
wait let me
uh yeah I want to learn everything again
oh
[Music]
oh it really is
much much much easier
ah what the frick
huh
[Music]
I thought it was much easier
okay I'm from above huh oh what the hell
did I do
why is it turning now stop turning
[Music]
I'm glad
okay
[Music]
yeah you're really a strong swords man I
tried and I already did nothing One More
Time One More Time One More Time One
More Time
okay that one was easy you just go like
okay let me do the final blow again yes
yes thank you
wait anyways don't take it down for
yourself
is this high flash
will it always show me the movements or
will it stop showing me
[Music]
I don't know what the hell I just did
affordable yeah we already heard Dad
sorry I'm not gonna tell you the same
thing again
gotta get used to it it will show the
movement oh really
for the final blow no I'll have to learn
it oh God
[Music]
you need slime or a pro or something
you can't take swords
what do you think you're doing sneaking
out with Dad
I'm coming outside
your Law Firm is missing you want to
look for it well I guess I could make an
exception just this once but remember
that Scott love this is a peaceful place
only Knights carry swords I am the
Knight of time
so I don't want to see you swinging it
around like crazy out there I don't want
to get in a ton of trouble over this
here's the deal make sure you get plenty
of practice on these lock Springs and
once you get outside with that sword
only use it when you absolutely have to
got it
okay
Raja I am now playing with joy cons
oh
is he spoilers
sorry I'm not the Knight of diamond the
hero of time hello
[Music]
hello
babe where's my burp wait how do I Dash
like that okay
[Music]
okay but here I can move the camera with
the right uh Joy joystick
nice
where is where's my bed
[Music]
but the word of all your rain wonderful
ah
ah go to the right side okay
somewhere over there oh ah it's just a
waterfall
oh no that goes into nothingness
we probably don't wanna ah wait this one
[Music]
is that where my bird is oh
wow the water is pretty
yeah this is it this is it
Fireball
oh I hear it
invisible wall
oh yeah can I why don't why does she who
swims like that well swims like that on
my left huh
which which left
should I go up
that maybe he's up on that Big Island
where the waterfall uh or wait
[Music]
you have to be able to control your body
like a ninja
[Music]
watch your step there you can't always
pretend it depend on nights like me just
hoping to save you
my best for you girl
no no platforming
platforming is the end of me okay come
on we're getting this smoothly
run jump jump jump at least I don't even
have to press a button to jump
ah
today
[Music]
do I slice it up I was about to drink
some water
okay oh
[Music]
oh
can I
can I go in now
hey is that not enough can I not jump
over that
oh that was good enough nice waffle cave
um
oh
it's dark and humid in here
oh yeah the joy-con controls are
actually so much better for this game
yeah I heard of it
bad
this is how I'm gonna build
wow one rumpy
oh
yeah
so anyways I started swinging exactly
I will not have much control over myself
here what is that can I have it
can I kill it
that's why I came from just want to
check okay
I feel good nice
all right
oh
okay
wait by the way I'm actually left-handed
can the link not wear the sword on the
left hand it's gonna make Kiana
you know weird to do it with my right
hand I don't like it
they just assumed assume that everyone
who plays this game is right-handed is
that it
is
[Music]
laughing it in all games besides this
one
you could have easily just mirrored it
no
yeah couldn't you have easily made like
a mirror adoption for this
okay
was it was it was that not possible
man you could have done that maybe 50
years ago because then I think that's
when when people
um when families uh try to raise
everyone right-handed but but that's not
a thing anymore that's not not a thing
anymore at least not in my country
that's what they did for Twilight
Princess wait I want to see what what do
you guys say what
that's they mirrored Twilight Princess
for the first weekend I guess it would
have been too much work they married the
whole game for the Wii version of
Twilight Princess
what do you mean like they had in Planet
princess we had two options
[Music]
um
oh well I'll get used to it but it's I
feel like it would probably be much
easier if I could do it with my left
hand
right now
no matter what ends to Kiana will
destroy you
oh a monster claw this extremely sharp
claw looks painful to even touch you
know what maybe after I finish playing
this game I'll be what you call it m
ambidextrous is that the word how do I
how do I crap oh there we go
okay back
[Music]
that's it that's the word all right wow
I'll have an extra skill that I can uh
show off then I can be like oh I was
once left-handed but now I'm
ambidextrous ha ha
easy thank you
um Zelda a Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword
for you know
teaching me that
I guess I have to be thankful and
grateful
but I I really wonder why why why
[Music]
is it really wasn't that difficult ah
link
uh hi there
hey link I was hoping I'd find you here
I heard you've gone searching for your
verb around the waterfall so I thought
I'd fly around and help you look
how's this search going any sign of your
left wing
hmm
you have to marry the entire world not
just link eh
yep really
oh no
well let's let's not lose hope yet
there's a place up ahead that cruise and
his gang are always hanging around
maybe we'll find something there
people are drunk not true
that's not a game that works out okay I
should have known that I can't trust his
words
he always trolls me
oh who's that
who's calling for me
oh sorry link I got distracted for a
moment let's go
Young
you follow me
wait where am I supposed to go
here
it didn't mirror the game for the Wii
Port one of them may link right oh
look there he is
[Applause]
no doubt about it that's your last
winglet yeah I know
I feel him I feel him
boom
and now
I'll damage for that wait those
explosive ones and I should have
move them there and then
make them explode
what the verbs okay okay okay save I
thought I was shot blocked
that would have been problemating
oh what a cute pretty book oh yeah oh oh
nice to see you again
the hole
I missed y'all
we call each other that because we like
each other so much it's a friendly
friendly name nickname
a little bit Yeah like a big ancestor of
Kotori
we should hurry link now that you're
left wing is free you should fly to the
ceremony
but before you go I have to ask you
something
I I heard this voice a few moments ago
did you hear it too
no you crazy girl you crazy I don't know
what shoes
took
it's been happening a lot lately it's
the strangest feeling almost like
someone is calling out to me
have you ever wondered what's beneath
the clouds
some say that it's an empty Barren place
or even that there's nothing at all down
below what I just have this feeling that
they're wrong
some of Father's old texts talk about a
place called the surface
the old Tales describe a whole word
under their far more vast and skyloft
the thing is no one's ever been down
there to see it and our left Wings won't
fly for the cloud barrier what are you
scared
or chickens
but I can't help Imagining the wild
things that might be waiting below
someday I want to see it for myself
putting on her tin foil hat
oh sorry link we don't have time to talk
let's get going look
to sleep off the edge and press down
don't worry about following your bird
will catch you for sure this time
you better you better while I'm making
picking duck out of him tonight
oil
you [\h__\h] when you can't do the this
one
[Music]
but when I do put fingers in my mouth
then I definitely don't know how to do
it
where do we go
[Music]
hi baby hi Mama I'm flying oh I think
let's run your bird for the bases just
to make sure he's about to I don't know
fall into the void no no no yeah
[Music]
upward upward okay
with which joycon any
and dropping so fast that oh my God this
is what what is going on okay oh my God
I help
[Music]
it's horrible it's horrible it's
horrible
oh wait us okay
um
no I no I can't I can't no this is
really bad this is really bad press y to
re-center uh
is that really did it really do the
trick
uh
[Music]
can I not flap
stare Ascend ascend
go go up
um
thank you
are we going up
change the controller dude shake it ah
[Music]
and that's what
shake shake shake shake hey instead of
the the uh the controller that I have I
need I need joy-cons now
we're riding a lot when you can press
right at any time to go over the basic
controls like yeah I'll probably need to
do that at some point well I'm heading
towards Sun now wherever it is
the meter on the left side says I'm
heading towards it you can also charge
versus an attack that also gives you a
burst of speed as well as slow down when
you need to try all these moves and see
how they feel
uh
charge X
oh
slow down
B
okay this is gonna be a disaster I hope
you don't have to fly too much in this
game
all right
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
well that's a huge relief I don't know
about ceiling but you love her no no no
no my father and the others are probably
worried about your bird so let's go give
them the good news of the air oh dear
okay
yeah babe
yeah be
[Music]
your left wing really is amazing
especially considering everything the
poor guy has been for this morning
I'm going to fly back and tell father
what happened
[Music]
the way she ran away
Well everybody's link
around the Blazers you found a dumb verb
of yours well that's just great because
you and your Dumber can tell time I held
a pre-race warm-ups me and you guys did
work for nothing
we've been waiting forever 40 ways to
start and then delay it for you I don't
get it the big flight gets special
treatment
[Music]
you're almost a man and yet you still
can't seem to go anywhere without that
I bet you can't even decide what to have
for lunch on your own huh
I don't think we haven't noticed a smug
looks
oh tell that guy your best friend we go
everywhere together
okay that's better
of course has been going on forever
about how he's gonna be the one to be
with Zelda
is what I'm doing the trouble about her
I know it says
[Music]
I had to break it to y'all but today's
the day I bust out this adorable
like to see land you're living in
Dallas playing the role of the Goddess
at today's ceremony so I'm gonna be the
one to claim that sale Club if we do it
I mean the panties when I heard she made
it herself man oh yeah I was gonna let
some crying clowns should I shall pass
away from me
will be mine
oh man I bet she was thinking about me
when she was putting them on tonight but
today I just wanted yeah I didn't see it
now first I went a big race and then
Zelda and I finish your ceremony took
everyone's statue Just the Two of Us
it'll be a special moment alone nobody's
stopping me and tell them from having a
moment oh that's so real I can see it
bro subscribers behind you right behind
you
what I can't YouTube see I'm in the
middle
[\h__\h] had to explain just what you meant
by our special moment alone
[Music]
uh nothing big really just just uh
I was just telling my body here how
gladly I was she found out Red big boob
of this boy I'm looking forward to the
fairies thank you
I like Angela I look for me during the
race I'll be the one taking off your
panties afterwards
[Music]
wait up
did you hear that guy what a [\h__\h]
pearls yeah the chances of that
happening are just about less than zero
either way don't let those fools get you
downlink just get on there and fly the
best you can
I'll try I try I know you've got those
guys beat and deep down I think you do
too
no don't we gotta be a gentleman but I
don't have much confidence it's gonna be
real
ah don't be nervous you can do this hey
hey can I can I
uh who's Owen is that Allen ow
are we talking to an owl to a certain
kind of BL
the links everyone who will know again
participating students please Assemble
looks like it's race time good luck link
he's a grandpa that I did the right
voice nice oh
[Applause]
[Music]
just flap your wings flap your wings
keep on flapping Flappy Bird
hey
oh this dude oh wait no that's different
dude he just looks the same but he has a
different hair color
yeah a rat or did he just dye his head
did he bleach his hair is that the bird
the person from the floor now right
your attention please at last we are
ready to begin with the wing ceremony I
was beginning to worry that we'd have to
proceed without playing but luckily he
waited so long for me that he grew out
his hair grew all white
but luckily that is no longer a concern
I'm glad you could all make it before we
start I'll explain the rules for today's
competition
I have attached a small statuette to
this bird who I will then release
through the skies
how do you dash again with x
on my signal Dash from The Starting Line
and dive off the edge ledge it doesn't
matter it's the same thing once you are
in the air Mount your left wing
and doing a different voice on purpose
he's not the oil oh yeah guy
remember to call your bird promptly wave
down once you dive off the edge
whoever catches the bird and claims the
statuette will be this year's champion
those are the rules simple enough I
should think but do you I should think
but do you need to hear them again
oh simple enough I should think
let's go
I want this kid to give me Google Maps
directions
after her approximately 500 meters
please turn right and then do a left and
then do a ride and you better remember
that [\h__\h] because I am definitely not
going to say it again and if you're
asking for directions in feet well I
don't even know how to say that because
I am from Europe and we don't speak in
foot fetish over here so you better
remember how meters work okay I'm not
gonna teach you go Google it or
something
thank you
as you well know today's Champion will
graduate to the next class bringing him
one step closer to Knighthood
he will also receive a gift from the
young woman chosen to play the role of
the goddess in this year's ritual not
panties today is a special day for many
reasons but it's also the 25th
anniversary this year of the tales of
series actually I thought I just say
that right here because it was kind of
fitting it is indeed 25 years since the
first Airsoft game has been released as
far as I know
to celebrate the occasion today's
Champion shall also receive his gift
High Atop The Statue of the goddess
this stream is by the way not sponsored
I hear the young woman performing the
role of the Goddess this year has
crafted the gift herself
and as you are well built
the goddess a liberal of God the goddess
this year will be performed by none
other than the girl that's whose name is
in the title
the lovely Zelda
let's see how far what the [\h__\h] are you
laughing about
flying out there show me just how hard
you've been practicing
also I want to see good clean flying
anyone caught interfering with other
Riders will answer to me really really
will this be a fair ride huh
all right I hope so
there goes double for you gross
hey I'm not gonna have you let my dog to
touch my daughter okay hands off of her
all right gentlemen line up and my
commander competition will begin
okay
I just gotta go to them
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
this is
[Music]
right or something like that
okay okay
can I lose it
is it possible to lose this
[Music]
you know if you could see how moving my
hands right now
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
they're being right straight here huh go
show yourself
okay okay okay
[Music]
can I can I lose this I hope not
do the trick
yeah
flew into him
[Music]
oh it's gonna take about an hour guys so
lay back and enjoy what do you ever seen
okay go go
[Music]
press a oh
oh I didn't say press a what
uh
I'm gonna just kill you rip out your fat
ass making naked
Zelda's not gonna like to look at that
[Music]
[\h__\h] up
mate
she wants me yeah
oh why is it so difficult
where is you where are you from go go go
I have a
[Music]
uh
what's it called another English word
how to speak English
I have a a wolf to protect
oh was that mean like that was not even
on purpose
[Music]
a reputation exactly that's it okay okay
okay okay so
now now
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
at 10 hours a letter
okay okay
[Music]
so I'm used to that
really
wait where's the egg oh they're shooting
stuff at me
[Music]
this is so difficult
okay yeah
[Music]
[\h__\h] boob style so I got it I got it
guys okay I'm getting better I think
[Music]
let me catch you look catch me catch me
catch me
if you can't what's that cute song um
how does that go
from her anime
don't worry I'm fine
great flying link congratulations
[Music]
now we better get on with the ceremony
ceremony yeah we'll talk about the same
ceremonies Alma
link hand me that bird statue that you
grab in the race I must offer to the
goddess
okay let me bring my chalky milk
hmm
oh
[Music]
wow
are they having a ceremony are they
having a mating ceremony is that what's
happening
where did you pull that out of
yeah that's that's what how these games
work they all have a hidden uh inventory
Great Goddess Guiding Light and
protector of our people grant us your
blessing and mercy as I act in your
stead during the ceremony
well Valiant Reliant brilliant youth who
grasped victory at the celebration of
the boobs kfp in accordance love the old
ways I now bestow the blessings of the
kfb upon you
[Music]
the blessings of the Goddess drift down
from the heavens and love the snail
which I now pass on to you
I love that sound
um
smells like gravy not yet an onion
you got the Santa Claus
oh now you can jump from any height
without fear of painful Landing oh
it smells oh it smells like
it smells like gravy
[Music]
link quick goofing
this is supposed to be a sacred ritual
remember
you know they say that the goddess gave
the sick love to her chosen hero long
ago
of course the one you're holding isn't
the same one I've been working hard to
finish making a sale cloth in time to
give it to today's Champion
I'm really glad I got to give it to you
link
make sure you take good care of it okay
[Music]
thanks for making it up here to do this
with me today like your promise link
[Music]
now we really should finish up this
ritual oh
out you do you know what happens at the
end right oh I'm oh I know oh I know
I'm glad you're so well informed about
this subject over oh where's that I I
went through Google and Wikipedia and
YouTube for hours
and that and that Dr summer uh thingy
laughs
I think that's a reference only Germans
will get
you have to jump off the statue
look down you're pushing me off again
Zelda what the hell is wrong with you is
that does that turn you on or
see that big round to sign on the
courtyard below
to finish the ceremony you need to drop
down right into the center of it
leap off the edge here right before you
hit the ground press that I to open
yourself off
just How brave are you if you are really
Fearless you'd wait until the last
second to use your cell cloth
was that a challenge you want me to
break my bones
[Laughter]
that was not the middle
[Music]
um
that's that's two two very embarrassing
moments that look bad will fly
foreign
okay
in the middle of the bit that that
really was not that difficult to hit
I want to stay up here it's actually
pretty nice when are we ever gonna be up
here again can I talk to the bird statue
huh
okay
well let's go uh
okay this is better I'm I'm way more
um
is that okay
okay let's see we have to retry it again
okay okay okay
I know middle of the round design the
middle that was the middle that was the
middle
[Music]
[Laughter]
shut up shut up already
shut up no
but I don't I keep on having to do these
things
[Music]
take what take four Take Five
some numbers because she has a Nike
um just this is probably not really
everyone's probably doing that first try
usually
ah no no
it took me running surprise really
not really oh really second try oh
[Music]
it's just easier in Minecraft
okay
this is probably easier with uh the Pro
Controller perhaps
delicious okay let's go land and then
we have to learn to aim oh
what's inside of the circle though
because there I go come on
come on
Pro Controller is the best way to play I
don't think so I think maybe for this
situation yeah but not for the whole
game the motion controls
are better for sword fighting yeah
you're sure
okay this one is this one this is the
one this is the one this is
come on come on oh [\h__\h] yeah that was
not really the middle but okay
only took me 10 tries
[Music]
oh thank you thank you thank you what an
emotional moment thank you everyone for
being there for me
that was perfect oh really you amazing
like oh thank you I know I know I know
seven tries is nothing
no
she she's pitying me she's looking down
on me
I was like okay I I guess I'll go with
cruise whatever his name was
you know link seeing us how you want
today
and what the weather is being so nice oh
his face
you think maybe you'd like to you know
go flying around the clouds together
oh why
oh yeah oh yeah
okay they didn't let me jump off the
cliff on my own because I suck so much
at it
[Music]
link hey link listen listen
I can take out my hands and go like woo
this day was amazing watching you win
the race and Performing the ritual
together I'll always remember this
it really was wonderful
[Music]
you know link
there's something I've been meaning to
talk to you about
what is that
uh good question
I don't know
what's going on
[Music]
get it what
a bomb saves me that's me
oh There She Goes
would have been too nice to have Zelda
around for the whole game
uh wait I kind of wanna
Link Link oh nice this wipes
foreign
[Music]
hold on
well
ah you were awake
oh
did you see my daughter
then you laughed when carried you back
you were limping unconscious I feared
the worst
[Music]
fortunately you don't appear to have any
serious injuries
for that much we can be grateful
but I think we're just Zelda
she was with you was she not
what happened to my daughter
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
he's gonna kill me
black tornado you say
um
that was no ordinary storm
[Music]
oh
you must not push yourself
still recovering
tell me when you saw Zelda today
did anything about her seem off
yeah
she mentioned the voice a few times I
just thought she was crazy you know
girls are like Dad in that age when they
go for puberty you must know I see
she was talking about the surface then
you've been having dreams about a great
mission
how interesting
[Music]
I'm sorry I was lost and thought for a
moment it's always strange but I doubt
there's much of a connection between
these things
I'm concerned for Zelda but so long as
she is with her loftwing hot wing and
she's with her hot wing I'm sure she'll
be fine
either way they break has yet to arrive
it would be very difficult to spot one
girl and her bird in the dark of the
night
it would also be very dangerous
[Music]
she didn't pack fireworks God damn it
right now like Zelda is going to be fine
because there's a lot of games coming
out after this one and she has to be
there
I don't know how she continues to live
on for millions and millions of years
she does change her looks a little bit
but she doesn't really seem to age much
anyway she's of a big importance for
this game series so there's no way
she'll die
[Music]
I know I know it's not the same one I
know
oh
kfp hello
join us
join the membership now we are not a
cult
at the end of this week if you are a kfp
member
you will be able to listen to an
unarchived karaoke on Sunday
I have something very special prepared
for you guys to show you at this
occasion
follow me haha this is so funny you
can't catch me Catch Me If You Can
I don't even know what the hell I am I
look so weird I don't even have arms
funny
I didn't have anyone to play with me
when I was younger
so I [\h__\h] around with you now follow me
follow me
follow me stream spikes stream heart
challenge
[Music]
don't forget about that song as well
follow me
jump down here yes jump into your death
trust me it will be diesel boo all the
little baby thing that you saved before
how about we eat it tonight
foreign
[Music]
this is the part where you break free
and chest
[Music]
okay thank you guys for the memberships
thank you
look forward to the street stream stream
I really uh I'm not lying the line I
really have something prepared yeah
oh yeah I'm gonna I'm gonna run out of
stamina [\h__\h]
[Music]
this is more easy with the Pro
Controller
[Music]
at the bat
ah oh wait do I have to dash up there
[Music]
oh
is that an item
it may look like a boring weight of Gunk
but it's used to make all sort of things
oh
nice
oh my magical
you want me to jump over there all right
let's see
oh that was close
you scare me lady what are your plans
with me oh
I want to go back so I could Dash
[Music]
thank you for helping out yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
I know extra night thing I'm sorry I'll
paint at some point
where am I
okay next one where am I where am I
going up here
what the [\h__\h] are you doing I don't have
all day we have to do this before the
sun comes up come on link you're wasting
my time
I don't want to waste my time what the
hell we kind of skipped something there
nice
the uberb did something good for once
thank you
I will tip you
oh look if I stand here it looks like I
have wings funny can you take a picture
for my Instagram
make it look cute
oh
it's poopy
is that the master Foreigner
[Music]
um
thank you
oh my God it's the monster swords
[Music]
bamboozle it was me all this time haha
this
the one chosen by my Creator I have been
waiting for you you will pay a role in a
great destiny
social Customs I should provide you with
my personal designation for
fix the name
[Music]
[\h__\h] hate me
back down [\h__\h] for the people who don't
know
uh fee is a is a is a thing that
followed me during my
uh
uh rise up until we arrival playthrough
and I hated it I hated it is
[Music]
the name I was given isn't it beautiful
just to trigger you that's the reason
why I carry this name
I was created for a single purpose long
before the recorded memory of your
people I must Aid you in fulfilling the
great destiny that is your burden to
carry
you must take up the sword as the one
chosen chosen by my Creator it is your
destiny
[Music]
the strange dreams traveling your sleep
my sudden appearance uncertainty
surrounding the fate of once you hope
the year under their circumstances it is
only logical that you would exhibit some
apprehension
[Music]
uncertainty allow me to share some
information such as my projections
indicate that this information has a
high probability of altering your
current emotional state
the one you seek honorable Zelda is
still alive
[Music]
and the spirit Maiden the one you call
Zelda is another Chosen One faded to be
part of the same great mission
therefore should you wish to meet with
your friend I highly recommend you take
up the sword before you set out to
search for her
ah okay
does that information invigorate you are
you ready to accept this sword
it seems that further persuasive
measures will not be required
[Music]
of my Creator draw the sword and raise
its Skyward Sword funny
[Applause]
what
what what do you want me to do
Ready Step what huh what do you want me
I'm moving it wow doesn't
oh my god oh I turn it around
oh my God which one though well
[Music]
wait
got it
okay that's so funny
well I'm doing it
laughs
I'm I'm I'm I'm removing it
oh
hi do it
okay like um
[Music]
wait oh
I'm gonna die
oh
stay stay stay nice
[Applause]
[Music]
the motion control comedy moments are
amazing
you got this goddess sword oh not the
monster sword oh lame hmm
this mysterious sword is bathed and the
Divine Light okay but is it also
exquisite
thank you for the membership wow
[Music]
recognition complete master
link my master
[Music]
link
oh I've had my suspicions but until now
I wasn't sure
yet here we are in the chamber of my
sword the very place where it was
foretold the youth
of Legend would one day appear
it is sad that this place was left to
our people by the goddess herself
very knowledge of this room's existence
is a secret passed down to a select few
each generation along with a handful of
words
when the light of the Goddess sword
shines bright the Great Apocalypse will
awake from its long slumber
do not fear for it is within that the
youth Guided by my hand shall reveal
himself in a place most sacred
so cool
[Music]
it started days ago the sword and I've
kept secret all these years
it began to give off a faint on the
worldly light
this is
this is so cool
fun I even and I like the atmosphere
that we're building up here it's fun to
find too fun to play in his hand I am I
am moved by
all this
deeply
[Music]
at first I was sure I was seeing things
here alone with the sword that was
simply no other explanation
[Music]
I never dreamed a perfect prophecy of
Legend would come to pass in my lifetime
[Music]
the words does she see it the words I
have sewing to keep secret are coming
true before my very eyes
[Music]
you will be guided by one born of the
blade one who is also youthful in
likeness yet wise with knowledge
immeasurable
[Music]
foreign tradition one of the least
reliable methods of information
retention and transmission
it appears that critical sections of the
passage have been lost over the
generations
oh he sees it too
the youth who draws forth The Guiding
sword shall be known as the goddess
chosen hero and it is he who possesses
an unbreakable spirit
he shall be burdened with the task of
abolishing the shadow of Apocalypse from
the land such as his Destiny with the
spirit of the blade at his side he shall
soar over the clouds and plummet below
and United was a spirit Maiden shall
bring forth a piercing light that
resurrects the land
[Music]
some of our father's old texts talk
about a place called the surface the old
Tales describe a whole world below far
more vast than skyloft
[Music]
Master you must embark on a great
journey beneath the clouds to the vast
Realm of the surface
it is only for this journey that you can
fulfill the mission set before you buy
my Creator the goddess
it is also the only method available for
you to reunite with the spirit Maiden
honorable Zelda
[Music]
it's just no easy task link the world
below is the first taking place and to
reach it you must pierce the cloud
barrier below my voice is dying
in living memory no one has ever done
this
[Music]
let me take a cough drop
I hope the old dude is gone so then we
need to have getting to stop talking or
I'm gonna die
[Music]
oh okay
this tablet will illuminate a path
through the clouds to the land below
take it and place it within the altar
behind me
[Music]
or tablet the weather the surface of
this heavy Stone tablet feels very old
Master the first thing you must do is
hit the crest sitting in this room with
a skyward Strike
these glasses are formed of pure energy
that charges within your blade when you
lift it Skyward
to send out the powerful skyward Strike
I'm a Hummer eh
what here you want me to strike that
what
hey what what
if you you should really not running
around like that with the sword in your
hand
point up
what I'm gonna try to sword
oh
that's gonna be a problem
is that oh there oh there it is
[Music]
I did it
foreign
I suppose
well
oh
wow
[Applause]
are beautiful
[Music]
master link it is done
until now a cloud barrier created by the
goddess has separated the world you know
from the one below a tablet you placed
in the altar has opened a small Rift in
the barrier you can use it to travel
through the clouds to the room below
I have recognized you as my master and
so it is my duty to follow you wherever
you may go
I reside within your sword and will
accompany you in your travels press down
to summon me whenever you require my
assistance
nice
[Music]
in a moment the nature of the Great
Apocalypse mentioned in the old text it
is a complete mystery it's a complete
mystery to me
but whatever it turns out to be it seems
that both you and Zelda have big roles
to blame the destiny of this land
just think if what this fight
I want to say fatal says it's true Zelda
is alive alive and no doubt Coming to
Terms of whatever it is the god that has
the story for her
yeah I think people say fee oh okay okay
feet okay
should you hate the call of Destiny I
don't know what dangers you may have to
face link
especially down there
but if you've decided to break decided
to brave the unknown is that a verb
please find my daughter and bring her
back to me
[Music]
what we've seen here today defies
explanation but it is only the start of
your journey please see it through and
prove the legends true
sorry I want to say okay
[Music]
I'm sorry link I guess we'll not play
this on your channel then I'll go ask I
don't know maybe
a Watson or something she's always up
for stuff like this I guess
[Music]
Dawn is Drawing Near it has been a long
night for the both of us hasn't it
you have a great journey before you link
those clothes
they don't look up to the task
do you have any words to receive for
winning a race should be ready by now a
story of the uniform like that will
prove much more suitable for a long
journey it better change before you go
yeah
thank you very much
your drip is lacking link oh
oh
the typical green outfit
he's copying me though look at the heads
obviously
oh this music
[Music]
that green uniform is what our Knights
will be wearing this year to be honest
I've had my doubts about this color
it's for camouflage
[Music]
but oddly enough seeing your world is
uniform I can't imagine a more fitting
color for you it's as though you were
born to wear it
nice looks cute
[Music]
take care on your journey and be sure to
stop by some of the shops at the bazaar
here in town to equip yourself properly
for the travels okay do you have pocket
money though
I have apparently no no parents there
what the hell
I will return to my quarters and see if
I can gain more useful information from
the ancient texts
you're always welcome to stop by if you
have questions I need to snakes help me
you won't tell us all be in my prayers
May the God is what you'll win God you
move
never mind I don't have to sneeze after
all
ah this is so much fun already even
though I struggle a lot with a lot of
things
let's go
link
[Music]
s
that green uniform looks so adventurous
you sure look like a knight now
the Headmaster said you're heading out
to look for Zelda
you're really something else I could
never imagine myself doing what you're
about to do
I put a lot of work into making this you
should take it with you
[Music]
Gucci bag
nice oh
it's an adventure pouch it's for
Adventures it's neat because you can fit
four things in it that's really not much
that you'll need on your big Journey you
can buy all kinds of stuff at the bazaar
that you can put in this pouch you
should go alone you could buy some
potions in your Shield they'd fit in the
pouch and they might come in handy on an
adventure you tell me a shield
fits into that tiny pouch on my waist
now
you sure
link I just know you'll find Zelda for
us
yeah well I will I will I mean I don't
know how long this gameplay will will
game for get playthroughs
will take me but what the hell you want
this other news out of all of us how
come only you got promoted to stay in
your class talk about stupid calls on
top of that Grace won't come out of his
room and someone is missing it's all
your fault way to go there buddy some
senior class guy you want
hmm you guys are underestimating me
I am the one and only
to save all of your asses
go to Gru's room
okay
[Music]
let's see
which one was his room again
[Music]
that's my word not of course
are you okay
ah he left still
oh that's me origami
okay I wanted to fight but I can't do
that oh my God there's so many feathers
yeah those are big
[Music]
yeah but I wanna you let me open it and
then you tell me to not open it what the
hell game
so what's up with it
oh we were off oh for [\h__\h] sake
I just opened his closet
and then the game told me don't open the
closet and I'm like okay [\h__\h] should
have told me earlier before I open it
okay
poor Zelda yo this is your fault you
know you can barely fly Street and yet
somehow you beat me in the race it
shouldn't be me up there with her that
day but I guess I'll just have to be the
one to save her I'll show you
okay sure it's gonna be all right buddy
it's gonna be all right cause I'll say
that
picture
is that him or like his father or
something no that's him isn't it who has
a picture like that that huge frame of
that face expression on in the room
oh my God
all right let's go
no time to waste we gotta save Zelda
could take maybe about one hour
now we're done
[Music]
oh hello
you want to talk you look like you want
to talk
I heard the news link tell that has
fallen down through the clouds and
you're going to look for her is that
right the Headmaster told me there's
land beneath the clouds do you know
anything about that
so that's the famous sword ah but it
won't do you much good if you don't have
a shield to protect yourself with you oh
you're giving me a shield
yeah
[Music]
at the market
dude
wait because of all Shields
if it breaks you can buy a new one at
the bazaar
oh
you didn't know haha
you gotta talk to the NPCs
here's some junk I had no
no no no no that's not no no no no
[Music]
you're probably about realizing you
could get a free one
to equip a shield hold R so like the
shield you'll want to use and let go of
her
okay
if you're not sure how to use a shield
thanks for the membership Knight
Commander egus
Eagles like the Eagle at despairing her
will happily teach you
DOMA
oh
[Music]
wait the dude where we were before right
there was like one mission that we
didn't do because we didn't have a
shield
master I have an update regarding the
stone tablet and the resulting column of
light it created
Knight has appeared to the south of our
location and signs indicate that it has
created an opening in the club area to
the land below
I must also caution you that descending
to the surface armed only with a sword
would result do not see have a shield by
now
if you have not already done so I advise
you to purchase a [\h__\h] look at my back
and Potions at the bazaar in preparation
for your journey
okay okay guys just make potions
all right
yeah yeah
wait maybe we can get potions for free
as well somewhere I feel like if we get
a free Shield somewhere if we talk to
the right NPC we might get free potions
too is that the bazaar
all right but wait wait but wait what if
we get something for free
Maybe
[\h__\h]
[Music]
any NPCs don't look like they want to
give something to me no no one's around
what the hell
the sliding now
[Music]
I just really don't want to use my money
um
[Music]
there's a hole
oh
my God am I gonna get in trouble for
doing this
I'm gonna get in trouble
[Music]
maybe if I get all maybe if I leave one
then I won't get in trouble
okay let's do that again here in the
middle
I'm practicing my sword skills I have to
oh
[Music]
free money okay now I'm gonna buy the
potion potion
no I don't mind
I'm gonna Grow Again
how long do pumpkins need to grow I
wonder
well yeah
I am dead
come on stamina
mops six months wow how do you guys know
that
[Music]
foreign
oh God I love this so much I could vibe
to that old [\h__\h] day
what a cute bed
I I don't look in other people's clothes
[Applause]
[Music]
wait a second
how do I do that
how do I do the roll again
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
give me give me
a dash of pepper delicious another
culinary delight ready to be savored and
enjoyed
oh
[Music]
here's a funny face yellow funny face to
those plates look lovely
oh what's that
[Music]
what's that oh what these oh what do you
think
behold oh young
man's appear before me you may choose
not to believe me but my eyes were still
outside that's funny road ahead of you
but I can't foresee what will befall you
so I am a fortune teller
nice listen to my pure and innocent
voice I will do you know guys deeply
into my eyes and come closer
I'm having too much fun making noises
[Music]
and welcome to the item check I want to
put stuff from your pouch into storage
okay I want to take something out of
storage that's fine whatever so is there
anything in you about your new stores
you want to move no
okay
well really oh great not like my time is
worth anything
[Music]
she'll take some beating noise I can fix
that too never mind never mind you're
crazy
why she's curious
I was just curious
and you look like you have potions
yeah yeah
oh you do yes you the adorable boy with
the golden hair welcome to potion shop
you can drink our potions when you're
injured to fill up your hearts oh you're
one of those nights aren't you oh it
wasn't training at least
let me tell you oh one look at you and I
can tell I don't need my potions but The
Cauldron full so don't try to slink away
without stocking up
oh dear I forgot to ask if you have an
empty bottle on you oh just so you know
I can't sell you an empty a bottle if
you don't have an empty bottle at the
point oh I want a beginner for some
reason I like you though so I'll give
you a spare Empty Bottle I've been
keeping here in the stall it's nothing
it's my little gift
you want to hear me say this often but
you can put other things besides potions
in an empty bottle you know like those
game abundas they talk about so it's a
useful thing to carry around
foreign
[Music]
take a look
if you ever get to the point where you
can't fit any more stuff in your pouch
because it's full you can always drop
items over the item check so good would
you like to buy
um
what okay what is this it just looks
like stamina this looks like hell this
looks like mono or something
I'm standing in front of the red bun
for you to take a look at other potions
though and this one
oh that's that a hard potion good eye my
dear and drink this and it will probably
replenish eight hearts
why don't you pick some up for your
adventure it is only 20 rupees how about
it how much money do I have
well I guess I need it
[Music]
there we go
one three four oh nice thanks you guys
remember oh the bottom left oh there it
is ah thank you
[Music]
oh thank you sweetie if you want the
position go see my husband at the end of
the counter he can make something up for
you
no I'm good what's the blue one
oh wait I only have one bottle
okay I you won't give that to me anyway
huh wow
[Music]
wow I don't need to power but you have a
baby
oh cute
oh oh my God this is so oh this is like
a Zelda game this is like a freaking
Zelda game look at those items
and four
oh my God the way that person runs well
I already have a shield I don't need the
shield
um do I need
20 things
yeah I don't have a slingshot
okay
yeah I don't have a bully but maybe the
bombs or I guess I need a bomb uh bag
yeah okay I thought so
the Chat is dead on my side are you guys
dead or can we pick you up
Cal you finally picked you up did Cali
finally come back from yeah buying the
milk
Chat is dead
[Applause]
[Music]
I guess it's just dead for now
this Treasure Chest like object is a
relic of ancient times left by the
brothers for her chosen hero
however I like any information wait do I
not have internet connection or what's
going on no I do
[Music]
the Chat is dead
hello
[Music]
chat chat hello
what's going on
okay I don't know you guys is this is
the stream crash
did the stream crash or
are you guys still seeing me how how I I
go I'll go on Twitter at least let me
know if if you guys still see me
chat is that oh my God Chad is just you
guys can't write a message right now
that's funny thank you guys for
twittering at me
the stream is good but the chat dies I
just wrote okay we'll just use Twitter
then
we'll just use foreign
okay no don't spam my Twitter don't
actually never mind don't spam my
Twitter
don't use my
use my comment section and I hope it
will come back let's wait a little bit
it's really lonely
lonely
I'm so lonely
I have nobody
yeah does it not work on okay let me
know on Twitter does it work on other
people's chats
that if you go on other people's streams
I'll give you this permission once one
only one time in your lifetime
[Music]
that's it
let me know
ah
let's see
it's it's back look wait oh it's bad
girl welcome back okay
[Music]
oh there it is
hola it's zooming it's zooming hello
hello what the hell Callie manipulating
My Stream not cool
welcome back I thought I lost you
my children I missed y'all
okay now back to normal
awkward it's so cute wait
[Music]
good thing I went on Twitter because
that is the most dope I mean I look like
a wizard when I put this on but
look at that
James chill made that
and look he looks like a wizard hat
because of the Stars
oh that's so dope
I don't know which one I like come on
[Music]
but I like this one too
damn it
I'm making a big bit bigger my chat
stopped again
did the chat die again
[Music]
it's dead again YouTube
chat
I love this hat thank you James too it's
so cute I would I would even use it to
go to sleep I think this looks like a
cute hat for pajamas
it's so cute it's my wizard hat
I like the kfb logo sticking out there
too but it's so cute I know I know you
made it orange to fit my uniform
yeah it's really cute I love it it's so
pretty well done well let me check
Twitter again let me check Twitter
check we died again
YouTube what happened
[Music]
I think I think YouTube is just not
doing well right now
that's all right we'll give it we'll
give it some time I'll just uh as long
as you guys can see me that's good what
do you think of my new hat I didn't get
your reaction
[Music]
I didn't get your reaction it's cute
isn't it I'm with that it's so cute
it's so cute so cute I love it I mean
because it's orange it doesn't really
look like Link's hat but okay I wanna I
wanna wear it
Divine Exquisite thank you okay okay
let's continue playing
[Music]
however I like any information on how it
can be opened at this time
yourself
oh you don't know how to open his chest
all right then
shouldn't be too difficult whoa no one
here
oh what's that
oh
ld30 One S scrapper
[Music]
it's like a robot
oh wait I'm a phoenix shouldn't be hot
[Music]
all right we'll talk to everyone here we
got the potion we can't buy any of these
items so yeah all right we have
everything we need I think
foreign
[Music]
do I just jump down the edge now
uh
I say good idea and I'm barely saved
otherwise it
I feel like I just saw it
must be up here
okay
it is safe to save
[Music]
okay you can ask me
you called for me master oh
oh
the search for Zelda I recommend you
dive into the car okay
column applied in the clouds and follow
to the ground below or for real already
now
indeed
you don't have to tell me that
[Music]
hold on South the South where's the
South down there
so somewhere down here we have to jump
down okay
oh
how do we do the roll thing again
[Music]
what the hell was that I know
okay I'm loading my save file how do I
load my save file
I I'm not no I'm not wasting that let me
go back
no
let me load my save file
uh
[Laughter]
only 20 yeah but right now I'm not made
out of money do I look like I'm pooping
money or what
laughs
[Music]
okay point the right okay this one
no no no
okay
uh
[Music]
okay now
we look where the south is okay that way
and we're going the right way
I think I am
no I'm not oh wait now I see the lights
I I know I see where I'm facing
I waited there it's right down
oh
foreign
[Music]
wow bro but uh-huh I guess I can't open
that one
I guess I'll wait I can go there
all right I can do that yeah yeah yeah
okay
well how about we just
yeah wait is this isn't this what I'm
supposed to do anyway
[Music]
s wait what's chewing at me
wait what's up there by the way
can I fly for that
[Music]
we have to practice a little bit you
know there's looks like I can find
something over there
how do I land badly
I don't really know how to land
I don't [\h__\h] up now
[Music]
aiming is my passion
come on come on come on come on oh yeah
oh yeah nice nice nice move
ah that speeds me up
[Music]
oh
oh go go go go go
there's so many tiny Islands I wonder if
there's some treasure somewhere
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
oh goodbye that way that way go straight
go straight go straight go straight go
straight
[Music]
could you come with me
thanks for the membership
[Music]
yeah
are these these uh Sky folks they're
really not scared of falling uh like
free fall huh impressive
impressive
I
I had my chocolate milk in my hand so I
couldn't press it but the game pressed
it for me thanks thanks for the carrying
thanks for the safe
pasta please make sure to use your cell
phone in the sitting room high elevation
sorry failing to do so has a high
probability of resulting in an injury
I took the liberty of deploying the
circle for you this time
indeed you did but in the future you can
manually engage it by pressing that I
before landing all right I gotcha milk
thanks for the membership mataling what
this is the Fable surface that has long
been part of skyloft Legend
by my calculations you are currently
positioned in a location known as the
sealed grounds the nether grounds
oh
[Music]
she deploys it for me anyway all the
time okay
let it grounds
oh hi
please proceed with caution master
[Music]
oh okay well
wait what what how do I how did I pull
out my shield how did I do that
oh yeah
no no no no no no no no no never mind
never mind never mind never mind
ah okay
oh
yeah
oh we have to wait until it was open its
mouth
huh
[Music]
um let's slice I was trying
to use my shield I didn't go to the dude
after all
oh yeah oh hold that up
hold up
what
I don't know how I did that
with me again
I need some Heights
[Applause]
uh
down there okay
okay
heart challenge
oh
[Music]
mysterious funky
oh
spoopy sauce
[Music]
what is that
okay
that headache
it's hard
be great
migraine your grain our grain
[Music]
s
everyone's green
oh
what
that's so pretty
anyway I was about to die but I guess
I'm not doing that tonight
I really need to practice my fighting
skills okay I'm sorry this time I will
actually look at the answer please tell
me how to use my shield
or maybe I can ask
uh
thank you
[Music]
ready Shield wait how which button
left joy-con
oh you just shake it oh
and just like if someone attacks money
to do this to block it properly if I
just have it like that it doesn't block
it or does it do I have to do this
or is this fine too
[Music]
I
I have to do this if if Shield it's a
Parry
it does the raising is for perfect
Shield
okay wait I need one more heart
[Music]
in the grass
not a whole dough
okay where do we go what is that
wait do I have to go down
or up
I feel like the game wants me to go down
[Music]
to check out what yeah probably wants me
to go down
[Music]
I am scared
I have a bad feeling about this what the
hell is that
honey
oh
[Music]
young one
child of Destiny descended from the sky
is strongest
foreign
okay
[Music]
what did I do what did I do what did I
do
oh
air
okay
I'm sensing a change in the area that
was triggered by your skyward Strike
I have also detected an aura that
correlates closely to your cell Club
isomized this Aura belongs to Zelda
it can lead you in the direction of this
Aura for a process known as dowsing
would you like me to explain this
process to you
the other thing is when I detect the
presence of the aura of something you
wish to search for using the tip of the
sword the new a UI to an object emitting
the aura in question the stronger their
response will be
this response manifests itself for
vibration and sound that the writing of
the object emitting The Horizon
indicated by the purple pointer you see
Target then point in the direction you
wish to search
ah huh
what
I don't know
I agree but I also don't understand
don't just go up again
ah
[Music]
foreign
are you down there
I don't know where she is
[Music]
let's go up
I know I went all the way down for that
wild fruits
Swoosh
Zelda where am I wrong side
okay
[Music]
run like you're running a marathon
you're gonna be number one
so that's Zelda we'll give you a kissy
[Music]
isn't that what you want
of course that's what you want
all right
it's
and where do I go now
let's do the dowsing thing
oh
oh baby baby
[Music]
let me
in uh and push and push nice
oh wow
[Music]
Zelda
no the [\h__\h] is that
[Music]
replenishes your Shield God and restores
Full Hearts
[Music]
we got a second bottle with that
we want how many free I want the
probably freeze the maximum before
and going out there in a second I just
want to check out you know my my RPG uh
things my RPG blood is running from my
veins
I have this problem I have oh my god oh
we're gonna catch that at some point
this can't help it it's just
it's in my veins
safe
this one thank you
yeah why do we have to ask me so often
thank you wait but wait there's Auto
safe too right
okay
noise
you look funny
descended from the clouds above I
welcome you child of fate
tell me what is your name
ink uh link good very good what do you
think about my hair does it hypnotize
you
I sense you have already gained control
over the sacred power what was that
sound
that fills your sword when pointed
Skyward
this guy would strike is yours to
command what happens if my if my
joy-cons run out of power by the way
yummy
it is proof that you are fit to Bear the
blade you carry the goddess sword
I have sat here for many years waiting
for you to arrive
also that I could fulfill my purpose as
your guide and now I want a hat like
that honestly now I want to have that as
tall as that and as big as that
hurt me I guess
what hats
today is my birthday happy birthday
Oh Holy Light
you stand under the roof of the sealed
Temple a place built by the goddess and
Eternity you go
your rival here was predestined many
many years ago
the spirit made and you think arrived
you shortly before you descending to
this land in a shower of light
there is no doubting it to give yourself
fate have begun to turn
yet all is not as it should be the
spirit Maiden was not meant to reach
this land in the manner she did
I feel an evil power working in the
shadows it moves toward the destiny of
which you two are apart
Kiana speaking her age excuse me
[Music]
link you are concerned for the spirit
made and then seek her whereabouts yes
that is understandable but for now you
must focus on moving forward
not Skyward
that girl has her own purpose she must
pursue as do you
[Music]
she set out for fair and words to
discover the Destiny for herself and you
must follow
[Music]
show me your map
the X upon your map marks the path that
will lead you to fire on Woods
you will be traveling in unfamiliar land
many monsters have settled here and the
map may not prove guidance enough for
your journey
is Kiana cosplaying as a Smurf it's
freaking orange I'm not blue how am I am
I blue yeah I'm not double d double D
type and die
and so I will give you the power to
create beacons
although bacon is more delicious where
the bacon is marked on your map a column
of light will stand at that location
it will act as your Waypoint from afar
or nice
point at The X and press a to place the
bacon sorry I meant beak and I'm just
very hungry I haven't been waiting here
for you years and all I've been eating
is crickets jumping around here this is
really difficult one second
come on it does not work
oh my God
I got help
oh no
there we go
when you said press a didn't you
oh wait I'm supposed to grab then ah oh
that's how I'll buy a place to somewhere
else that's where we go
you cannot see it from here we are I'll
be gonna stands outside to guide you
leave the temple through the front doors
and see for yourself when you no longer
have a use for a break and then give it
to me because I'm hungry you can remove
it however from your mouth by pressing a
use your beacons well and you will never
fear getting lost I'm gonna die with
these voices
go now you must head into a fairing
woods and space up the spirit Maiden the
one you call Zelda
on your way out take the contents of the
treasure chest within this room
[Music]
special
people are ready leave through the door
before you and head into the woods and
she meant the chest that I already
opened
I wish you were safe travel
know that all the questions you have now
will be answered in time for Now link go
bravely
all right now
[Music]
let me see my pouch oh wait no I don't
drink it don't
uh I want to see it wait uh how do I
um
[Music]
but like he automatically picks this one
what if I want to drink the other one
[Music]
there we go
okay
ah no wait equipped thank you okay
[Music]
Baba
oh nature
foreign
looks like in Minecraft
it's like Minecraft easy little
Birds baby Pips oh I see a uh
what what are you call an English groans
oh money nice
oh they're picking on him I'll save you
in a moment money is more important than
I don't even know who you are so give me
a break for once
okay oh wait no I lost that one
every
coin whoopee
ounce
okay burps uh I'll leave you with this
Sam
[Applause]
[Music]
oh oh
[Applause]
let's go
all right
oh thanks for jumping into a scary bird
[Music]
another voice let's go
I did not expect to run into a pack of
Damages peaceful Force
so it goes for you this is the second
time I've bumps into whatever you're
going today
I'm trying all sorts of weird things are
going on okay
with you according to the ancient text
there is some kind of place up above
quantity I am goodness foreign
[Music]
ER to God's place
[Laughter]
the real fight would be sure to examine
it to keep tabs or to number of
landmarks they ever want to be quite
useful
supposedly they start to be special as
you decide to have the ability to
activate all the other structures the
whole thing sounds a little crazy I know
but I feel unbelievable to be true
otherwise why would all these judges be
here all over the place
which is a real hard scripture but makes
you want to know more this is not now
that's all but I was hoping to tell you
more because you can wait
was he gonna tell me something important
yeah I can't do his voice
sounds like the voice of a suffocating
chicken what the [\h__\h]
no that sounds different
did you use some kind of magic
[Music]
yeah that's my LimeWire power
wow it's so shiny oh
wow pretty
uh oh I can I can immediately go back to
the sky all that
of course
yeah okay
[Music]
I gave the statue Sparks oh
you start to just react to do what did
you do come on do not make a big card
back I have got to go
[Music]
I have uh literally no idea
sorry buddy do I still need to talk to
you no right I can continue moving but
it was nice to get to know you uh left
or right left or right oh the beacon is
over there about my RPG
vans
there must be something in that am I
going there later
[Music]
I want to go there too
will I go there later
wait there's some fruit oh wait can I
collect that if I do that
wait how do I do that again how do I do
that again
I don't how do I do that again
how do I do the bunk against the wall
go explore check out the cave
okay but first I'll click down and okay
wait uh wait no wait wait wait wait wait
down out
yeah The Real L while running
shaked control
I'm down
no no no no no no
is that
what
wait my stamina
Shake left okay
oh it doesn't fall down though I thought
it would fall down for me
okay
okay never mind then a few head injuries
won't make much of a difference right
and the slingshot huh oh dear
oh
will that be useful later on yeah
I don't know it was smart to go up here
oh
you're standing in the middle now
thanks buddy
Master now that you have access to Stone
statue you can return to the sky at will
so incredible by using the certain
amiibo figure you can return to the sky
from anywhere on the surface and come
back to where you left oh
please call me anytime you would like to
use an amiibo you can also enable or
disable any amiable usage from the
options
but I don't have a single amiibo but it
has to be a specific one right is it a
Skyward Sword amable well I don't have
one do they even sell those still
I'll own that breaking the illusion
right
that sounds useful though
[Music]
um
okay I have reached a goal
they ran out there here oh
faster you have entered firing Woods
oh oh
is that The Deco tree Deco tree
the plenty for water in this region
clearly sustains a large diversity of
Flora including this massive what it is
logical that the Lush plant life and
what the resources have attracted animal
species to the region
oh oh we're already here now okay
that's not the nickel tree oh
you left my
house
oh
okay
looking at the probabilities it is
extremely likely that Zelda is somewhere
in the area
I recommend you continue to use your
dowsing ability to search for her
[Music]
gotcha oh my God I love this music
best soundtrack ever
hold on Wind Waker soundtrack will
forever
be number one in my heart
okay I don't need to cancel again just
cancel
I'm gonna have to hang on to that do I
do that automatically let's see oh I
know
and go
[\h__\h] yeah
[Music]
oh I can't
explode
science
can I go over
[Music]
there
okay okay
[Music]
thank you
no
see that the skull thingy when he died
what is that
oh
cute
[Music]
um
and another voice added to my list
very busy today I hope I get paid extra
for all these voice actor uh sessions
I'm going just kidding I'm just joking
okay just jokes
[Music]
oh okay is that my new best friend
energy come back to me
[Music]
oh
this place is cute it has such cute cute
big mushrooms you look like a mushroom
from the back too
[Music]
I actually don't like mushrooms so good
for you I guess I'm not gonna try don't
don't worry
mate
what are you what are you oh
yeah
oh yeah
why can't I not you
I know
I'm catching up on you
I have to I have to hit it on my phone
so sorry
come on
where'd you go
where are you
[Music]
this is so difficult with the camera
okay I'll wait I can do that
[Music]
we have to do this I don't want to hurt
you what is love oh baby don't hurt me
don't hurt me
no more
they said that that just takes so much
time
[Music]
just keep on I keep on doing that hit
cut the mushroom oh is that a thing I
can do
oh
it's so easy
[Applause]
oh they annoy me they annoy the [\h__\h] out
of me
yeah
come on
all right Shield
oh where's my shield like I'm out
sorry no
no nevermind
buttons
oh
why is it not equipped
peace
oh there we go finally it works
okay okay
now we're talking
sorry for being uh so bad
[Music]
all those wind monsters
your kick
I even know you're scary
thank you for helping me
[Music]
that's weird
but that one was a girl
[Music]
I don't know this girl was
but she was in a bunch of trouble when I
saw her
[Music]
but she escaped
Masa we have obtained new information on
Zelda's current status
misinformation indicates that she was
assailed by monsters but somehow evaded
capture however I infer that she is
still in significant Danger
thank you
I have marked the position of the Kiki
known as mati please confirm your
current location
come on my analysis analysis and
Analysis analysis analysis that's the
one suggests that this Kiki most likely
produces a false positive thousand
reaction due to the previous direct
contact of Zelda
I didn't even use it
using this hypothesis
I theorized there is an 85 chance that
the Kiki Elder will also generate a
thousand reactions for the same reason I
will promise you will continue dancing
to search for downtown
yeah nah thank you
[Music]
it sounds like you're set confining his
friend until then if you're heading that
way anyway
I bet you're going to say we'll follow
that
no thing about that
you know
it was nice because you know you're
[\h__\h] adorable I haven't seen
something as cute as you in a long time
except every morning when I look into
the mirror
am I right or am I right
when
[Music]
Amber railing
okay I'm gonna jump down here wait is
this where I came from
foreign
[Music]
wait how do I do the thing this
should I go up again probably
wait okay
[Music]
ah over there over there
ah up there
[Music]
seems to be somewhere out there
not go here before
[Music]
pick it up
can I oh can I throw it on that thing
let's go
it dropped nothing though that's kind of
sad
oh pick it up
[Music]
at me it's a bomb is it a bomb okay it's
a very tiny bomb
okay time to look oh oh dear
hello I got those moves like Jagger I
got those moves
again
I forgot how to use the shield again
[Music]
uh
thank you
[Music]
Daddy has Selena
did you drop something no
fun fun fun
oh I can cut everything that's cool oh
another shortcut
so many shortcuts for what
sound like an Amish great really
by the way uh tomorrow is it tomorrow
collab with Amy
you guys have been waiting for that
we haven't collab in a while huh uh
we're doing a
we're doing that game I had I didn't
know that um
wait wait wait wait
oh well oh [\h__\h] my shield is that really
worth it playing around like that uh and
jacking oh jacking
yeah uh when I'm not I'm not I'm not
gaining anything from fighting you
[Music]
wait a second
we went
together
I didn't realize that there were more
than just one game because like remember
that time when good on family planes
foreign together
and and I was like huh who's gonna play
it with me but you know there's actually
more than one so now I can play with
them
get on the bench to restore Health bench
it's bench
a bench
[Music]
I don't see a bench
shrimp stamp
stop
oh
that's not a bench you called it a bench
Benson is
okay how do we use that ah do I cut it
aha
gotta hold on okay
and this feels good that was oh Kitty
Kitty
good good morning
I have to cut you
it feels like if I poke you with my
sword a lot of liquid is Gonna Come Out
of You
before I wake you up
pick me up before you go go
let's see do I get some juice from that
no
hmm okay I guess I should probably wake
you up huh
go man
I am so sorry
[Laughter]
I'm even doing the right uh
it doesn't work I have to talk I guess
okay
they're cool a little monster let's burn
oh the girl great job
she looked like she was one of your cars
yeah she wants my friend right here
full of monsters I'm worried about
a person Drive
Oh Lord You're so much some of my people
burn
yeah there's so much
oh but the monsters they are still
lurking in the forest I don't dare leave
this but
I think we are still not recorded for
could I ask you
that's what they're saying that's great
I'm worried so I'll keep this if you
could call my hairs I might be able to
remember more about where the girl you
see corned often I don't have time for
that [\h__\h]
learning that Zelda is no longer with
the kick me out there is an unfortunate
sector
setback but he may still have useful
information
taking this into account I calculate an
85 probability that your quest will be
aided if you find the last decrease for
the Elder
to expedite your search for these four
Sterling creatures I have added kiku's
as a dowsing option
kill
you look like penguins in that image do
you need me to explain how to switch no
only I will Mark any quick ways you
discover on your map and disable
thousand readings for them that way you
will not revisit the same decrease
this concludes my explanation when ready
please begin your search for the missing
key quiz
whoa okay side quests which is kind of
the main quest but it feels like a
science class let's go uh can I get some
water though is that okay guys is that
okay I'm dying I only have my talking
milk I need to get some water
yes boys for feet sexy is that is that
what you we would you like me to become
a YouTuber my dear would you like me to
whisper in your ears before you go to
sleep well that's not gonna happen
unless you listen to my streams before
you go to sleep that's how you can make
your dream come true
let me go oh
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
oh
you guys actually waited for me hello
while I was at it I went to an idol
meeting and cuddled my cats as well
free things at once
uh not not at the same time not at the
same time though
nice
[Music]
okay
thank you guys thank you
foreign
check
oh
[Music]
whoa
oh
azuki said bye wrote to me told me what
she wants to oh wait I can't that's the
secret
foreign
[Music]
I have to change the thing I know I know
uh how do I do it again ah
this one
release the sun okay
probably for the whole though right no
ah
oh
oh over there okay
now
[Music]
oh I need a bomb here maybe some
backtracking later on
perhaps ah let's go up here I guess I
already was up there before though oh
yeah
thousand was the worst in this game you
don't like dowsing
I don't even know what that means what's
the English word for that
it's not throughout the Lord is
different from drowsing drowsy like
being drunk right
uh
[Music]
where are ya
okay I don't know
oh
[Music]
I feel a disturbance in the voice
sources or something like that
oh how do I get up there
maybe after all I do have to go for the
hole
look I do
my boobs
I'm going indeed
I was watching yeah probably not gonna
happen
we do have to activate those
no okay
let's go up here
go come on
yeah that's right
uh when I'm kind of lost
is that the girl up here
and then go back
to where he is
oh [\h__\h] now
is the space
like I I when I was younger I think I
did watch like some of the movie
subconsciously
pretty sure about it because I remember
some race or something oh wait
yeah
I don't know which one
well from salad oh
I guess you can capture those with uh
the
the with the with the with the bottles
huh but I don't need one now my bottle's
all full
ah what do we do with that what do we do
about those can I attack them while I am
on here oh no oh oh yeah that's gonna be
difficult can we just go like that
hey how do I
I guess I'll just
okay I guess I'll just take damage then
oh come on
oh my God oh my God
oh my God
yeah I know it's over there I guess I'll
die
[Music]
now I have to go all the way up there
again
uh big tree big tree
[Applause]
[Music]
I can slingshot well I don't have a
slingshot though not yet
apparently tree
is there no shortcut to go over there no
other way oh wait oh here maybe
hit
uh
go up there go up go up
go up
look yeah
[Music]
okay
no [\h__\h] I wanted to get the heart
okay can't do anything about that so
anyway I want to go over there
ah
oh
I hear birds screeching
yeah can I only go
[Music]
but there's something over there as well
somebody here
no really
but this place looks so special maybe
there's something else later on
there there are more than one yeah no no
I know I know
okay okay okay
platforming pain yeah
it is uh not one of my specialties I
wish I could get over there faster but
okay we have no choice
ow ow who was that
that is pretty cute
okay up here
I feel you there oh thank God I'm not
the only one can I just jump up here
right here no
all right
how did they already fall down so many
times
well here's here I am fine
okay we'll go for the hole
we go up those leaves
hey I'm trying to go
[Music]
wait there's still one over there but if
we walk yeah
[Music]
if we go fast enough okay what the hell
what the no I can't
like well
swag already no
yep
okay that that annoys me that annoys me
I'm trying I'm moving the freaking thing
oh
[Music]
hello hello
okay don't shoot me down oh
go like that then it doesn't oh attach
itself to me okay
go and Walk and Walk and Walk
like a model like a supermodel okay wait
now we are here
[Music]
okay
I'm gonna stay here
[Music]
wait
if you've got that
did you hear what I heard
[Music]
oh man
wait let me pick up the coins before
they disappear the rubies
[Music]
have turned shall we are
oh I can't get down I think you could
help me clean
[Music]
with a gun oh wait this one
okay yes
let me get one of the Heights
okay you want me to help you okay go up
there well how do I
it has something to do with
with that thing here
[Music]
oh
cut the tree down yes
[Music]
I had no choice
anyway
but the Elmo is running about me well
I'm glad to hear you
my name is
[Music]
they're still shaking
yeah I got you I gotcha fam and now I
can use this to go over to that side
nice okay
swing and swing and swing am I up too
high I think I am too high
okay swing
yeah welcome welcome
[Music]
oh come on come on swing
ah what did I do
oh sorry I passed my motion capture for
a moment that was weird
we'll go up and then my motion
captioning my game capture go up sound
mute it
[Music]
is it working
you captured me go
oh yeah
foreign
okay what's going on what's going on
I know how to swing wait this is Mo wait
he's moving on his own I'm not doing
anything
wait I can't move anymore
oh wait
on OBS I'm moving accurately but on my
game capture wait I have to restart my
game my gamecatcher program
okay
uh
something really weird happened there
audio do you think too oh that's funny I
I pushed one button
and that messed up everything but now it
should be fine again
on my side it's fine again
[Music]
okay can we turn around though yeah
audio works okay now it's fine okay
come on come on
okay
[Music]
I wanted to
cut the flowers
okay
where's the next one
where is the next one
oh yeah I felt something ah yeah over
there how do I get there
oh
something for a slingshot
oh you didn't see that one coming did ya
oh why is that so sparkly
you can't fly into a tree
[Music]
I know that's good luck but I still
would like to not have you poop on me
no
yeah
[Music]
if you decide to not join cave people
jfpm said that's what happens to you
I'm stinky
this okay [\h__\h] you
what a waste of time
oh
oh yeah oh yeah
oh yeah
I have left
is this going anywhere I can't explode
that thing
I don't have buns not yet oh what hello
the hell
[Music]
what are you doing
I say you
I see you
better get rid of all the grass all of
it
you're so cute and he's like I'm not
here I'm not here I'm not here so it's
all gone now I think oh there we go
I thought I had a good hiding please
help as good as hiding as I am except
the elbow of course you know he's really
bad at it he's really bad let me tell
you so what you're done
okay
[Music]
your new novel connect for spotting
hidden things with me okay okay how many
wait didn't you say am I not done yet
yeah it's so over there or something
okay
[Music]
oh
come on
stupid
okay
what you were saying
maybe like
[Music]
okay you pissed me off
huh
[Music]
mine looks dead
okay
uh oh can we go up there seems
impossible
[Music]
ah we can go for him
oh
oh [\h__\h]
no
not worth it
my shield is almost broken
that is not worth it
all right oh
boy's screaming at me
[Music]
it is you huh
where do I go
I lost the signal
oh
[Music]
what what
the last one is like
where
how do I get there
[Music]
oh here
oh
oops I thought I could run behind you I
nuts
[Music]
uh-huh
do I sense
something or am I going crazy I think
there might be a queefing here oh is it
an adult
oh you you you wanna fight huh
[Music]
you broke my Shields you little [\h__\h]
what did I say
I said a queen thingy hey
I don't know what you guys are hearing
one of the queen thingies
I don't know what that means do I have
to go down that way let me see
oh yes
oh yes it seems so
okay
[Music]
are you here
we are there you are I see you
foreign
[Music]
we don't know if it's safe yet I'm going
to stay here while walking and wait for
this monster still go away
I think I found them all
I am not detecting any additional
dowsing responses in the area I suggest
you go speak with the kick me out there
okay
don't worry I'm here to protect
you can go back to the kinky Elder now
oh why are you speaking of the kick me
over where the hell is he where am I
okay let's go back to him
[Music]
maybe that way
out that way
huh
I am lost
ah wait that way
[Music]
I should have healed myself my my shield
before it broke man
very unfortunate
[Music]
this is
oh
yeah
yeah what do I get for helping you huh
oh
I don't want me to stop worrying oh
actually I don't know me too well
done for 40 whatever is missing I don't
know who you are where you come from but
you have my thanks
word no I believe I just remembered
younger lady went
[Music]
yeah it's all coming back to me she said
she had to travel to the temple for this
I tried to water but how dangerous it
was David to clever little thing watered
off my belly and run off on her own just
the same
what character dubbed everything for the
rest of my life
that sounds exhausting mate
hmm no thank you
like drunk Mickey Mouse
oh I can't
put my sword too all right
towards Temple but we just want to take
great care of you follow her
I almost forgot
there's a reward for finding all my
friends looking
because I will give you precious
let me just fetch it for you oh Where
Are You Gonna fetch it from
oh
I got
them wait you want me to go up there
[Music]
nobody okay
what
use this protectile shooting weapon to
fling Deco scenes and your foes the hard
scenes will stun your enemies
oh I got 20.
even from the beginning noise
oh
and we tested that from here
is there something I want to shoot
if I shoot that will I get it
I don't want to waste anything
[Music]
it's wrong it's really Vine
hmm
[Music]
ah it's like shooting arrows a bit
higher there we go
[Music]
that is a very precious gift that I will
use a lot I think
I should be able to find the bathroom
today watch for the Templars
yeah I already did that you don't have
to tell me about it chat told me
that's a good thing I go make my
explanation that much easier to
understand yep
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
grab some seeds from the fruit
ah
[Music]
the yellow ones
maybe the yellow ones
all right
oh
and back
back forward and jump yeah
[Music]
oh I got a skull
ah Callie would like it maybe I'll give
it to her
maybe I'll give it as a present to Cal
and she likes that kind of stuff she's
into that I don't know why it's kind of
cooking like creepy
what is that thing though
that that just says
what is that thing
also where do I go
wait where does he want me to go
here
[Music]
um
that that place where I went to before
right where I was like oh that looks
like uh
I need to go there later
Temple looking thing
well now I lost complete track of where
that is though
[Music]
uh let's see
ah over there
okay uh so wait no wait
oh
no
uh
let me grab that thing yeah there you go
somewhere there I need to go somewhere
there
I don't see it but somewhere in that
direction
so I suppose I have to go up here again
that was for zeldon oh
God also that was fun
[Music]
so oh it's thousand for Zelda again
they kicked out the kiwis I remember the
name now because you guys were so weird
about it
[Applause]
what the hell
yeah that's literally where I just went
for
there okay
ah I can swim through here
oh thank God
hello
[Music]
probably not how you will you're gonna
keep on running away from me until the
game is over at the very end
we're gonna reunite I reckon
oh my God
damn what happened to you is this what
happens to you to us skylings when we go
down to the Earth
is that how I'm gonna look like after a
little bit
damn
better go back up to the sky oh let me
take the top high time one time please
give me
thank you
there's that one here too yeah
skylings week return to Kiki
[Music]
master I highly suggest you save the
progress of your quest before you set
out for the temple deep within the woods
in Pursuit Of Zelda
hmm what's my thinking there Laney
I suppose I will do so but not because
of you telling me but because I am smart
enough to think of that by myself
no so the temple is that
do I have to shoot that thing here
and waste my my precious
precious slingshot thingies oh
[Music]
we'll wrap and grab a sword I have a
sword you mean a shield huh I should go
up okay
foreign
[Music]
oh
I didn't even have to do it myself thank
you
[Music]
getting real good at this
okay okay do I just land on the island
[Music]
I I know
wow the music makes me feel like I'm a
hero oh wait I can go even up here is
there something there
[Music]
I want to land
oh she did it automatically
thank you
okay I came to buy some stuff
don't fall down
as expected always happens
by the way guys
I'm so glad today I finally before the
Stream
I finally got to do some
apartment cleaning stuff and I finally
bought groceries I didn't buy groceries
for ages
because I didn't have the time and today
before the stream I went to buy
groceries I cleaned my kitchen I did uh
the clothes washing thingy laundry
thank you thank you proud of myself too
yeah I was being a little bit I wouldn't
even call it productive because that's
just basic stuff you do
um but I have been lacking time to do
that
also I finished the thing I finished the
thing that I was talking about which is
the reason why this stream was moved in
the first place
I finished it yeah yeah I want the
shield
attack
[Applause]
don't forget about five it'll burn quite
easily it's an unfortunate World
property of wood it could be yours for
15.
expensive
[Music]
it is very expensive
check if I can upgrade it
with this dude
oh welcome our Shoppers in the
opportunities
as I'm sure you know anywhere in the
proportions your body will do from my
wife oh it's about portions uh the Smith
okay
so shop if you don't have one because
usually find your shop outside or ah
okay
when I see it I will try to get in there
uh you don't know
where's he
maybe it's you is it you
can you help me upgrade your gaming
Australia yep yep sorry I don't want to
do your voice anymore upgrade uh upgrade
gear please
[Music]
oh is that even worth it guys
uh normal beta
oh I have enough bangs for it
is it worth it yeah no should be yes
totally worth it I'll get an upgrade his
helps a lot okay thank you
yeah go for it okay oh thank you
[Music]
you know what I have some I have some
European Clocky here
I'm gonna eat those Mikado
called Mercado
I've loved that ever since I was younger
ah we don't have many flavors for
European parking Ricardo comes in free
flavors comes in no milk chocolate and
white chocolate and in dark chocolate
but I always need milk chocolate is the
best
um
and they are
um a big spinner than Japanese [\h__\h]
foreign
[Music]
you know
it's kind of lame that they only have
free tank free um varieties
yeah I do prefer the chocolate
and the cookie inside over the Japanese
party
hmm
it would be great though this day
hagamo flavors
from hard work good job
[Music]
good job
I just realized it's already been four
and a half hours home I feel already
kind of exhausted
let's try a little bit more
although we are playing it at the end of
the week as well again
two times this week
[Music]
um
yeah I guess I could also do super jump
reading because that's kind of
with my pacing also take like two hours
[Music]
I wonder how long this game is gonna be
it's not gonna be as long as Yakuza I
reckon
hmm
should we do should we do a super chat
38 hours only around 30 hours 40 to 40
hours 20 some people say 20 but I guess
it's like 30 to 40. okay
so if we do our best we can finish it
easily before it hands over eyes
course aim for
um two streams per week
but next week I can only do it once
because I'm going to doco me next week
I'll be a bit busy next week
oh five to six streams I think yeah
might be more like maybe seven knowing
myself
and knowing how bad I am with the
controls right now I feel I can sense a
lot of failures
especially with boss fights
um
hahaha
oh man
are you excited for don't call me I am I
am I am for various reasons
many reasons
10 12 tops I'll give her 10.
also the thing is like because I
do the voice acting and all that like a
normal player could finish it like if
they if they weren't ruined like voice
acting they could probably finish it
faster but because of the voice acting I
feel like it takes more time
because sometimes for some people I read
it slowly
um
yeah oh well
seven seven two eight parts sounds good
to me
um
thanks dude should I do my slingshot I
probably don't even have the right
materials for a Dylan yeah okay now I
don't whoa
slingshot
it has a verb on it
you got it
I'm golden what does that mean I guess
it means something good
on Sunday we will continue
uh where is the saving thing
I'm gonna say it again because I just
upgraded my shield
oh is there none here up here I think
the great ah
oh it stands for grains of all time
oh now I finally understand that I've
seen the word being used here and there
and I was like hmm I wonder what that
really means where that came from
[Music]
oh all right okay that was a lot of fun
it feels so nice to like play a Zelda
game
I'm really really into it even though
it's quite difficult at the moment with
the controls
but I'm really enjoying myself so
looking forward to the next time we'll
play it I love the music the soundtrack
cold [\h__\h] and the the atmosphere the
story up until now the characters
each character is like very unique and
each character looks very stupid
each NPC
but I like that I like that they look
like that
ah
and doing the voices for you guys is
also fun even though it's very painful
but I'm don't worry I'm enjoying myself
doing that but it's a very painful uh
after life
[Music]
am I correct I'm assuming that tomorrow
is uh I'm a collab uh did I get that
right
uh yes I did okay
we were here together uh supposedly that
game takes like eight hours or so so
we're gonna do two pints
[Music]
tomorrow maybe like four hours and then
again at some point four hours
switch the screen
I love my hat can I wear my hat in the
other screen as well
take it with me
you're sure
no chat
one second
let me fix everything
okay let me make this thing this one
bigger
oh it's so cute it fits so well
I love it
people are going to come in here and ask
oh Kiara are you going to tell me my
future and my fortune fortune teller
felt for I look like a fortune teller
the fortune teller
also I don't know if you've noticed
uh because my my hats were looking so
fancy today you might have not noticed
but I've been using my old outfit today
yeah
you look like a Smurf okay you deserve a
bank
what is my fortune
ah well I see I see a future where you
will become a big big big
crispy fried chicken but don't worry
that is a good future
it's not a chick no not a chicken
oh all right let's get the super chats
ready listen let me close oh I love the
can I can I keep on playing you know
what I'm not gonna close the game
because I want the
I want this Zelda bgm to play in the
background
it's so nice for once
let me let's keep it it's so chill
I wanna you know because when it's game
gaming streams where I play that game
obviously like playing that bgm is okay
because it's part of the game but I
wonder if I do like separate streams
let's say I do a Saturday only
or a Super Chat reading after a
different stream I wonder if I were
still allowed to play a soundtrack like
that
I wonder
gotta ask a manager some
[Music]
um
it's so nice oh
in between we can switch I like the the
shop
[Music]
wait that's not the short music it's not
just when I was in a random house right
I love that one
ah
so beautiful
all right let me see oh
[Music]
by the way I hope you guys uh
like the way the new schedule for this
week looks like
even though we already had two members
only streams this week last week I felt
like you know putting another members
only in in this week
[Music]
um
I felt like
doing that because probably next the
week after I won't have time for it
anyway
[Music]
um wait what was I doing final coffee
shop
you really enjoyed it and thank you for
spending time with your members oh guys
uh yeah I totally forgot about putting
garlic phone into my schedule this week
but I already put it into my schedule
for the following week so that I don't
forget about it sorry I forgot about it
that was the oopsie
[Music]
no no my secret thingy is not a collabor
virus I actually completely lost track
of time you know I originally thought
that we were just gonna do a group
collab once her band is left the blood
uh
and I don't know suddenly Callie and Ina
are doing one-on-one collabs with her
uh I thought we I thought we were
waiting to do a group collab but
that's why I didn't ask about a
one-on-one collab because I thought we
were doing a group collab to like
welcome her all together but
that's not the case the other is way too
fast Ina and Kelly were acting too fast
they could they could not hold
themselves back they were like
I was clapping over
let's go
[Music]
so I honestly have no idea when that
group collab is gonna happen because
next week I am way too busy it's not
gonna happen in that link
and next week is also Tito opportunity
we could have Iris join the ttrpg
[Music]
it's still just only began you should
still join me
is it too late I actually feel like it's
it's so early
but I don't know I don't know what Cali
has in mind
[Music]
um
Kelly did mention like later on if like
if when we're done with like one chapter
per se
uh people can join and leave how they
want like if if one of us five four five
four four says that will we're like okay
too busy to continue this or uh it's not
really a thing whatever then we can
leave
[Music]
um
and uh yeah she was she seemed very open
too
have other people join
outside of hollow Ian maybe even her
hello ID perhaps
but who knows who knows I feel the
teacher which is quite a commitment
[Music]
um
so yeah
all right we have to read oh
those from this stream right
only
good morning Ohio very much
[Music]
yeah I don't think there are quite the
commitment so I also don't know like how
long I want to do it depends on how
this first session goes and how how busy
I'll be after after it I'm super busy
already now
yeah
all right all right all right
I put the super chats into the Excel
sheet
and we can begin
we can begin indeed okay
[Music]
you did great last time at the TV are
you sure we didn't even talk about that
at all didn't we
ah you see
um I wanna play let's talk a little bit
about that first I wanna play Tiara as
like what I have in mind is someone
obviously we already I already I think I
got to the cross at the introduction
she's she's obviously like
wary of strangers
and
also because she came from a different
country
and
um
yeah therefore she has a little bit of I
don't want to say trust issues but I
think it's also normal to not
immediately trust strangers I think
that's generally normal
um so
I mean I'm sorry I I know that you know
like obviously Kelly wants to continue
the story and all but when you go into
the bar and and there's like random
people you don't know and you suddenly
get asked to
um
go do something with them to save the
world or whatever
honestly like I just wanted to be
realistic we're role playing here I
wanted to be a realistic I was like no
that's not really what I came for this
country I came for uh you know Finding
rare species of birds and all that stuff
original goal is
so I mean obviously at some point uh I I
knew I had to give in but a tiny bit of
um holding back what's the word for that
uh a tiny bit of
[Music]
um
you guys will teach me raise it
um reluctance yeah that's what I wanted
to say tiny bit of reluctance and
hesitation yeah I think was necessary in
order to role play my character
correctly and afterwards
um
[Music]
it
would have been very difficult
to stay that
um
that stand office for the whole
uh
episode so I I figured why not let Tiana
Bond a little bit with watoto because of
his smell which is I know weird but
oh who actually like she didn't really
like what to do in the beginning Eva but
you know her first little thinking of
him having food that her burp could like
and me currently not having any food by
myself for my trip
um yeah that that and then rather being
like kind of
open to the idea of sharing and uh I
don't know it was just kind of weird but
I felt like it would be funny if why the
door was the one that Tiana would uh
bond with
um I think she still needs some time
to open up with Scout and you
with you I didn't really get to interact
at all I guess because I guess because
Yule is also more of the shiny
not exactly shy but like not very
proactive as in making lots of friends
on her own uh yeah
um but yeah that was just the beginning
it will it will happen eventually
um but yeah I I I did feel a little bit
um
uh torn apart uh because like
[Music]
I didn't I didn't want tiara to open up
that quickly but it just kind of
happened because maybe partially because
of the Kiana and me coming out
and Pie selling because of the
situations that we had that we were put
into
and yeah time constraints as well kind
of yeah I didn't want to hold back
everything too much and all that
um
yeah I I don't I don't uh I wasn't
really planning on having her be that
open right away
um but wait we'll see we'll see what
happens for now she's just really open
with matoto don't know about don't know
about the others yet she's she's wary of
the others still also I mean Loki very
welcome she she kind of
ah it's maybe a little bit mean but but
she kind of sees matoto as
um
yeah someone who can be of use
but in some way even though she only
wanted to kind of use him she already
sees that watoto is genuinely like cute
and nice and friendly and just
um you know actually actually cool
she didn't she didn't originally want to
um as a friend but it seems like that's
where it's going
I love that hotel see
out of crumbs
um has a bird brain and maybe she sees
what otherwise a bird
I know
[Music]
a nice amatory interaction
I'm so you know I think I think I think
um in some way this was only possible
because of ahmed's Personality like
she's she's just uh
yeah really vibing and she she is able
to
make any situation
uh I don't know
um harmonize
[Music]
true yeah she goes with the flow and uh
I I think like originally correct me if
I'm wrong
but I think you know when the character
creation thing in in the character
creation stream
where
[Music]
we're probably not very prepared and
came up with probably almost all of it
on the go right there
uh I think that the whole wattle thing
where she was like when she was asked
what's what's the name of your character
she was like
um
I feel like that was mostly just like
her [\h__\h] around and and not really
originally like and I don't think she
had much fun in there but but because of
her creating such a
like messing around funny character
um it adds uh it adds a really
um interesting Dynamic to the group that
we otherwise wouldn't have had
[Music]
um
I think it's nice that you know instead
of everyone making perfectly cute
characters beautiful characters cool
characters uh her making such a Derpy
weird character
uh it's just really funny I like that
it's like it's like uh like
um how do I describe this I feel like
normally
uh we would we would all like I've seen
other
jeans and maybe people often want to go
for like the perfect ideal character
super cute waifu whatever but there
there there goes AME
there goes almond created a freaking
Gremlin Goblin whatever
uh I don't know I really appreciate that
I really appreciate that hmm
it's hard to explain but I appreciate it
[Music]
we needed that otherwise it would just
all be cute anime waifus
[Music]
but I really wonder
them because from from my point of view
it seemed like she just came up uh with
it as a joke from like out of nowhere
without much planning
but maybe I'm wrong maybe she didn't
plan to have and it was all prepared and
she wanted to have a gremlin Goblin
character and that was what she had in
her mind all along
yeah
I'mma approached her about battle
beforehand oh really
oh oh okay okay okay and then I uh I
have to correct myself
I
wait what's the word for it
I I assume wrongly that's not what I
wanted to say but that's okay
just from the sound of how that sounded
in the character creation sounds very
spontaneous like spontaneous uh
decisions
okay
you can ask Amit tomorrow about a trail
anyway I love the character and I think
it's great that we have such a very
different special type of character in
our team
um
[Music]
okay let's read some chats
you want like a mysterious light it
wasn't that the thing in the character
creation so I was quite surprised to uh
have her be there with a character like
Scout in the end but I like it I like it
she plays Scouts so well I was shook
because I didn't watch her one-on-one
episode didn't have time for that but
um uh the way even she even the way she
played it in the very beginning of the
the last episode
uh where she came to the bar looking for
a toilet even there I was a damn girl
you got some goddamn talent for this
she's really good at it
wow
[Music]
she role plays like she's not a beginner
she has a talent
yeah
okay okay
[Music]
can you Bonk again
bonked as in like banned or
did you mean like one of those YouTube
bunks
hmm
do I do I need to check the
YouTube okay I don't think I can do
anything about that
[Music]
um
blocked users no well
mm-hmm
[Music]
only time fixes it okay
yeah I also I mean YouTube is so stupid
when it comes to stuff like that you
can't do it like if there's a treble the
emotes
travel with accounts getting like
Bamboozled for no reason
ah
um
thank you
love the kfb hat do you want me to tell
you your fortune
I will tell you
it's your fortune
I see it I feel it I see the color is
orange
and the color is blue the color is white
and I see something in the shape
of perhaps a bucket
yes yes yes
that's it that's it
you will become Fried Chicken
in the bucket yeah sorry seems like
everyone here has the same fortune
win
everyone seems to end up the same here
at kfb I don't know why
hmm
we have to investigate a bit further I'd
have to do a few more
accuracy seems one point yeah
okay um
Richard Richard
thank you for the recipe oh
today the 25th is my birthday oh the
tradition is to give money to your
Aussie is that is it is it it seems so
that would be you the wonderful level
will burp that gives me a reason to wake
up every
oh
270 kindness is not enough for what I
want to say so I'll keep it short I love
you so very much
oh
sorry
you do
oh happy happy birthday
happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday
[Music]
birthday to you
free wishes you a lovely happy birthday
[Music]
what kind words I'm so so blessed to
have such sweet hearted fans
unbelievable
[Music]
thank you so
that your birthday will be a nice one
it's still not over seeing where your
currency
um I think you're at a place where the
day is still very fast and over so so
please enjoy it wait actually never mind
25th
ah you sent that when it was still 25.
your birthday is over over by now oh no
oh man okay never mind I take it all
back but I hope you got to eat some cake
and stuff
oh man I thought today was the 25th
well well I'm sure you had a lovely
birthday
I wish you all the bestest
Slowpoke thank you albino donations
looking for the top dinosaur
just don't blame me when my cover Sparks
Zed hits 50 million views and three
hours if I do actually manage to
complete without dying
go do it I want to see it I challenge
you
if you think you're so much better than
me then show me
their Surfside all packaging doomslayer
Dragon craft red one thank you
well who's about to stream one of my
favorite games oh I hope I'm not
frustrating you too much
uh with the way I play it
she hard challenges you I don't I don't
spark challenge
[Music]
I hope you had a good day at work too
best Girl Aqua duncast
[Music]
I suppose you like uh some Zelda game
that has some Oracle in it oh where are
we at you have to write that out it's
not like you on a red Super Chat and you
you had way more space left than that
you could have written it out and then I
would have understood
which one are Oracle of Seasons
Oracle of agent Oracle of Seasons on the
Game Boy Color oh wait let me see Oracle
of seasons
[Music]
oh yeah I didn't play that one
oh
[Music]
but I did I did own a Game Boy Color in
the past
[Music]
those were good times I only really
played like Pokemon on it though I think
not much else
yeah I heard good things about the 2G
Zelda games but I think I think in the
3D Zella games there's so much that you
can do that you couldn't do in 2D games
so there's great things to both of them
2D games and 3D games
you can sell for 300. a Game Boy Color
is that popular now I don't have it
anymore though
damn
are they this uh expensive now
no way
[Music]
oh the Game Boy Advance I don't know
when Game Boy Color game my advance I
had all of them
hard to find 40 tops okay so much for
300. they sell for a ton though is it
really
the games are expensive
ah
[Music]
very expensive nowadays
oof
Game Boy
100 in my area
well how much was it back then
um considering the
inflation
[Music]
I wonder inflate inflation inflation
foreign
like
considered 150 or something like that
[Music]
wow that's a very exact amount one
116.68
40 dollars per game
that's good prices you gotta pay what
sixty seventy dollars for Nintendo
switch games
Game Boy Color releasing something
would cost only 100 US dollar today
right that's so much money for such a
small device that doesn't have the best
technical
oh
stuff
oh well not a little interesting
conversation thank you Daisy you got a
tangent
I give to you a tangent
space function
I know that Cadence of Hyrule game I
know that I I saw it I saw it being
played a little bit forever is one that
shouldn't Keeper of the flame than the
shooting motion
sword you cute little
I drive are you here are you here my
dear friend fire Drive are you
foreign
[Music]
next time I see out there you are of
course you're a wonderful nice to see
you
[Music]
two days two days
first time offense
midnight thank you for the pinky
I hope you like Skyward Sword that was
my favorite game when I was a kid even I
never finished it it was a lot of fun ah
thank you for saying that now I don't
feel so bad anymore for never finishing
games when I was younger I just didn't
have the skills to go that far and kill
like the the boss enemies
um makes me feel a little bit better
I liked it as a kid too and I never beat
it that's pretty normal okay okay
oh didn't finish most games okay I feel
much better
never finished windbreaker so my
favorite
hey man saved
oh
[Music]
foreign
I think I think yeah probably me as a
kid even if I paid attention I didn't
really understand it all perfectly
um
[Music]
foreign
another hotel
[Music]
I hope you finish this one the story is
amazing I I I will I mean now that I
started it on stream by starting stuff
like this on stream uh it gives me a
push to finish it and especially when I
have everyone's help everyone in the
chat continuously helping me
makes it much more much easier and much
easier and and and entertaining as well
um you guys helped me out a lot just
like with Yakuza and other games
especially also Fire Emblem hmm
yeah we'll get there we'll get there
blue Park donation mod arcade
[Music]
we got him a Kiana cake and he
absolutely loved it
using the picture from egg hatch day as
our family was lucky enough to put
chickens on it
I posted on Twitter wait what does that
mean using the picture from egg hatch
day as our family was lucky enough to be
chicken I don't understand that sentence
but I want to see it
wait how did I find that
how did I find it
as I find it ah second member stream
thumbnail of that one oh
[Music]
[Applause]
that was so sweet
that image yellow that image and the
stream we did just watching you guys
hatch
but first ever member is the first ever
members
at the first ever hatchlings
[Music]
I hope I find your Tweet like maybe
afterwards
[Music]
but my Twitter is current when I go to
my Twitter replies it's currently
spammed with your Chinese dad but we see
you Chad is that what we see you check
this back to this bad show this back
I'll check this down again check this
out put that again oh we're back
y'all can delete your replies to me
clean up my reply section
I'll beg you just kidding you can leave
it but
[Music]
um
one year membership oh I guess I gotta
think of something
mmm
if I don't forget it please remind me
bellstar oh yeah and and happy birthday
of course to Baby sang
I watched the video where xan reacted to
Sparks it was so adorable
I proudly posted it on the on the whole
live English Discord I was like look
this is my baby
baby likes my songs
it's so cute
Sarah Nicholas Duncan the silver tongue
slacker and Davidson
oh party time for the baby thank you for
continuing to be his favorite
entertainment I can't believe it but
that's amazing thank you
I'm sorry I can't fall alive because I
have to sleep it's now zero am in Korea
but I'll see dark I played out by the
way I changed the nickname following
your advice nice
foreign
[Music]
I am more interested in the children's
TV of course I am but it makes me feel
bad about you know swearing because I do
swear a lot goddammit ah
yeah
he's gonna learn all the bad words from
me
oh
probably every time every time when I
say the F word
probably mama and papa stand next to
stand and they're like ah she did it
again send a listen
they probably Flinch every time
it's going to be using the b word yeah
probably as well you know
ah
that's fine Ginger Ranger 13 Randy Orton
it's a mystery dungeon with this cute
voice acting it feels like he is reading
us a bedtime story
um
you know you know one reason why I do it
like this is because uh the other Zelda
players that I've watched
um
from this specific person I enjoyed so
much because of the voice acting that
that person did
and
um I think that that really makes a big
change
at least to some people I guess some
people don't care but I think a lot of
people makes a big difference
um
whether or not I read it like normally I
read it all down like blah blah blah
blah blah blah or if I actually try to
act like the person the character that I
see and adjust my voice to it
for for watching someone else do that
for me it added a lot to it
mm-hmm
[Music]
I'm glad you guys enjoyed so much feels
much more immersive
well sometimes uh I come come up with
some ridiculous voices still
I don't know what the hell that voice
was for what's his name Groove groose
Cruz
[Music]
and and often I I'm just not a voice
actor so often I can't really come up
with the voice like I can't do the voice
that I have in my head actually the
voice that I imagined that character
live
often I just can't do it
I wish I wish I could do more voices
but today I feel like I came up with a
big big variety of voices
foreign
hmm
OTA
sometimes doing impressions is a good
start to new voices I guess so yeah
[Music]
um some of your voices were really well
done thank you
[Music]
oh
thank you thank you
that is very very uh and my face looks
very weird when I do that voice
[Music]
acting during averages is such a trade
some would say Divine Exquisite even
I'm also surprised they haven't done a
really long stream yet
I think uh yeah um besides the fairy
tales but the fairy tales I purposefully
read uh mostly normal
on purpose because I wanted
to be like then
um
with radio I know a lot of other members
have done that already and like I don't
know we kind of
we as me and Cali kind of like we're
planning on doing that for a long time
but just never came together
it's still somewhere out there in the
air
hmm
maybe at some point piano remix okay
okay that that's it ocean
[Music]
wait where is it I don't see it
oh there it is okay uh one month
you have been
very rude these days
you think
you can sing huh
[Music]
you act like you have some kind of
immunity
no more no more my dear motion
no more
[Music]
sorry
Jacob 47 Duncan
well thank you for the funds for the
coffee I gotta buy a new one soon I'm
running out slowly
[Music]
I've been so busy so it's been a while
since I uh wait let me one second let me
do something
foreign
[Music]
why is this all in Japanese again why is
my EXO
my online excellent freaking Japanese
where's
in Japanese where is the format the
wrapping thingy
uh
where is the text wrapping
is it
[Music]
um
here I found it okay yes
I've been busy so it's been a while
since I saw my favorite redhead bird
person with a nice bones that he's on
the takanasikiara street
[Music]
the gross is loose I see I see I see I
see I understand okay
hmm
okay
[Music]
you know I thought well it was raining
and I thought you might you you're gonna
say uh you're gonna talk
um about the that burp the the red verb
that link was writing but
not even that you went with grooves
that is shocking
[Music]
um
well I'm sure deep on your heart you
came to the stream to watch me and not
Bruce I'm sure about it it just toots
admit it that's okay
thank you for coming
anytime when you have time
is a good time to watch takanasikiana
thank you
Monday
for your voice actors chops myoshi made
the game much more enjoyable to watch
Gigi and skiato thank you
the Frosted Firefly Duncan
so again could you give this Super Chat
to grooves I couldn't find his YouTube
channel I wrote that as a i l write it
like that because you donated in British
pounds
I saw a red cow
kyara could you give me supercharge to
gross me trouble Channel
no
FM he sucks
I would prefer to see a fee doing a
vegetable Channel
[Music]
foreign
ah hello voice
[Music]
thank you soon uh albino thank you
if she eats Magic Fish dancing
what the hell
that's not me unfortunately it's
imposter Olympic torch
gym Transit Anderson fantastic work
today tensor uh all drugs Society is
great thank you I'm glad you enjoyed it
I pretend language
how long before Canada starts forgetting
her voices next time I play this game
everyone is gonna have a completely
different voice
no I'm just kidding I think the the fee
voice I'll remember the the dad
voiceover that I remember probably
the grown voice I'll remember too I
think but the rest is uncertain
that's my one problem I just never know
how I did it before
unless maybe if I would go back before I
start the stream if I watch my uh
previous stream beforehand and remember
it that way but I don't have the time
for that who has the time for that
[Music]
the Italian guy I wonder if we'll ever
talk to him again though
come and write a donation
uh
I have to translate that name transl
[Music]
foreign
thank you for the pink Super Chat Mr
bread
translates to breadcrumbs
I'm preparing my college entrance accent
oh when I feel tired I always want to
stream your shiny laughter always makes
me happy and may I have an encourage in
Chinese which is
and oh yeah the one with the oil the one
with the oil give oil
have good grade and exam if you're
looking at it well I need to find a
reading for that
Daniel
[Music]
is that pronounced okay
put some oil and then start a fire
[Music]
add oil start a fire
was that perfect really really did I say
it well because I know that in Chinese
that the pronunciation is so important
so important
[Music]
it can't mean something completely
different
but what what's what
I struggle with then is like when you
have to emphasize certain
um certain syllables syllables
but like for example when I normally
speak for example now I would
emphasize certain words uh
to
um I don't know just just just to
otherwise I would sound like a robot
like if if I have to emphasize certain
syllables in order to make it sound like
the right word then then I feel like I
have no freedom to emphasize like I
probably do if I were able to speak the
language properly properly like but I
tried practicing it alerting it before
previously and that's what I really
struggled with like being bound to a
certain way of pronunciation do you know
what I mean like
[Music]
um
I don't know it's so hard to explain
so hard to explain but like when I want
to say
um
like I I I emphasize that word in order
to show like feelings and emotions
and I feel like if I do that while
speaking some Chinese words
then that could mess up the emphasis on
certain syllables and then change the
meaning I think now I think I got in a
Crest what I mean
um
that's that was something I kind of
struggled with
now you get it okay
the tones yeah
[Music]
oh well anyway
add more words to emphasize
[Music]
foreign
but anyway thank you for the pinky
thank you good luck with your college
entrance exam
looking for the time
Lexington Lexington the lion thank you
sir
to generate I'm laughing at two to be
honest the HD version is a lot easier
for me than the original in terms of
motion control
we'll get used to it trust me thank you
y'all I will probably get used to it
excessive
position
I think all they did was translate the
Wii controls but the left and right
joycons have the same amount of buttons
so they should have mirrored it
yeah
true I agree
what if I put the right joycon in my
left hand
family Luna
it's gonna get used to the button
placement I guess
oh oh well hi TV
yeah thank you very much
did that one originally come with Emojis
I feel like you sent one with Emojis
today and it doesn't show here
[Music]
oh well thank you thank you I hope you
enjoyed this game today hope you had
lots of fun thank you for coming by and
supporting me as always
[Music]
loyal Thai tea that shall be your title
foreign
[Music]
any Ace Combat game there's a lot of
people who
[Music]
who agree with the emotion
but there's motion fifth cyrex motion
we need motions agreement too
why because I can do funny voices
because I could like voice every
character differently is that why you
want me to do it
[Music]
oh it's a flying
wait I thought of something completely
different right now
I found Ace Attorney
oh
I was just thinking of objecting
you're gonna say something
[Music]
intentionally made link left-handed
because he's Lieutenant also oh
then until Nintendo made link right 1012
princess and gave the reason because the
buttons are on the right foot controller
[Music]
um
I I can't really uh judge that because I
don't know if that was really necessary
for Twilight Princess
um
fish 1000 Duncan
uh welcome
[Music]
Freedom Units
I love that this is
oh yeah I should drink pineapple juice
again yeah
like soda Senpai told me
Sydney Avenue
first try Services I was so funny when I
was trying so many times
oh my God how bad can you possibly be at
Landing in the middle
[Music]
I also love the moment when we when when
you first have to jump into the
sky for the first time and I just
stumbled and
I want to re-watch that moment that was
so funny
oh man
so thank you
hi I can't speak English but I always
enjoy watching I can't comment because I
can't speak English but I support you
know
[Music]
foreign
only night
[Music]
is
but you haven't tried to steal my oats
thus I remember you instead is that a
meme
thank you
[Music]
you don't come back with me I'm so sorry
and now after a lot of time has passed I
feel sorry and I want to give free lots
of love
foreign
[Music]
but I've just been curled into a ball
laughing my lungs out since the ring
Landing
thanks Santa you're welcome I'm glad you
had some laughs on my stream me too I
had a lot of laughs too that was fun
being bad at the game is fun
said thank you for the pinky you're one
of the few creators I can watch
regardless of what you're doing
that's nice to hear
I love listening to your ramblings only
to suddenly hear you switch to German
with me going here
um
embarrassed
many streamers of English than comes
Deutsche house Spanish
automatic
randomly
that's
is home
[Music]
oh oh These are the super Chats on the
chat that oh you guys were able to send
super chats but they just didn't come
through in the chat actually but here
they are
oh
they're just like hello hello hello
hello
testing from the afterlife
foreign
[Music]
how can you how can you deal with that
probably very difficult
time for you
um but yeah the only thing you can do is
move on so let's go
[Music]
whoa
um
chat that 15 years ago
small Hindi Company please understand
[Music]
you said
oh you even sent that twice accidentally
[Music]
three times next week
foreign
[Music]
a little bit rough after all those
voices but I'm good I'll be fine I'll be
fine one one cough drop and I'm just
like new
foreign
[Music]
I'll take that tip and I'll invest it in
more voices
[Music]
no
this is
[Music]
foreign
I'm really excited to show
you guys my
my secret thing that I prepared for
Sunday for the members only stream
because that one is actually
I prepared that for the dukumi
um but I will I will I will show it to
you guys already in the memories only
stream
and then after dokomia I will I will use
it publicly publicly too
for everyone else to see as well but
originally it was uh meant to be for
dokomi
hmm you will see you will see
[Music]
ah yeah the part that will be streamed
on Twitch as well yeah I am
and I hope you guys will watch that on
Twitch
I will uh once I know the exact time I
know that I will of course advertise it
again
what
did you see the birthday cake oh it's on
the radius oh
I'll check Reddit right now
for a little bit of Reddit
[Music]
open yourself up Reddit why do you let
me wait till oh yeah
[Music]
sorry we couldn't load posts for this
page
my rabbit is dead
oh there it is
let's see
mm-hmm
[Music]
well
where is it
how far do I scroll
look at new oh
[Music]
it takes so long to load
ghost
oh cupcakes
oh vote that [\h__\h] up
[Music]
oh
nice
so cute
wait that's the first birthday Sanders
only one year old
I already felt like he's so much older
like 20 years old by now it's been so
long
it feels like such a long time
no they grow up so fast you know
he's two months older than Kansas
say bye
[\h__\h]
listen
[Music]
um
Killers old man Canada's oil man he got
his tall hat Lady Killers wimpy villain
jerk yeah that's a bizarre South
Carolina's various animals unless the
link has himself yeah because link
doesn't talk so he doesn't need my voice
[Music]
thank you soon
here's a dollar for every great what is
he provided for this game did I really
do 20 voices wow
my name is Sarah and dankerson
thank you let's go to dangers
oh wow okay let me skip those those are
flash chats traveler thank you soon
counting chickens dancing
three favorite voices to stream item
shop lady equipment instructor ah and
fee and present all the extra work you
put in but take care of your voice thank
you oh thank you actually do this in my
RPG streams
uh but today I definitely did way more
than usual
I have seen many players of Skyward so
and I have to say that I've been and
genuinely enjoying this great job on
voice acting but don't know what do
yourself
[Music]
alien 1475 thank you soon
gold medal for cycling in the Olympics
for Australia Austria really
really uh as an Australian myself I can
hardly believe that we got any medals at
all for anything at all
we're very good at losing except when it
comes to winter sports
hmm
if it's about skiing or uh ski jumping
um
that's where we can get some medals
sometimes but yeah
it's not like five seconds after the
video finished
I need to say it
hey thank you with a red super chat okay
foreign
[Music]
yeah she wants me to draw
hey
you're so cute
so chunky
[Music]
chunky wonky
oh oh
can you send me that video after after
the stream on Twitter as a reply when if
it's a recent reply I will find it
[Music]
foreign
I really love this game it's fantastic
soundtrack and it's epic Starly really
Harpy you are having fun can't wait for
more
Randy Orton oh
my birthday
enjoy my birthday today I just want to
say thank you for being an inspiration
to me for these past seven months and
one of the reasons why I got into
drawing again and I want to thank you
for that you are welcome
please continue to drop
a lot and
we stay healthy and support
takanasukiyala's dreams box
happy birthday please celebrate a lot
enjoy yourself
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
the thing called RNG when you throw
those dices
[Music]
she took it easy or maybe maybe she
wanted to
maybe she wanted to you know no
become friends with Scout and one Scout
to think she is that strong
she wasn't feeling it
[Music]
s feelings probably
just wanted to hold hands
yeah
handle these kids perhaps yeah could
very well be
and and the way
she was like
[Music]
um holding
or like wrestling
and holding Scout's hand
[Music]
um even though Scout was using a lot of
power
that was just Tiana's
like
um bass like she didn't even put any
power into her arm that was just the
base grip that she has
[Music]
that's how it feels when you shake
Tiana's hand just kidding okay she's not
I I would imagine Scout is probably
um has a bit more muscle mass
than tiara
[Music]
so she misunderstood I'm wrestling oh
yeah okay we can say that from the
country where she's from
uh there is no I'm wrestling there's
only hand holding
and you hold hands even with strangers
very well possible
[Music]
thank you for watching the archive
name
Translate
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
you made this game so much more
enjoyable can't wait for more streams
and series is gonna be great feeling
thankful boss only because yeah I think
it was it will be a great playthrough
I already enjoyed the first time very
very much I'm just a bit scared that
it'll be a very difficult
uh yeah
I'm a bit nervous
foreign
[Music]
Royals
the platforming as well yeah
[Music]
you can do it really you trust me well
if you say so after playing after seeing
me play so many games then
okay
[Music]
I think it's cooked what is it
is it Seattle
felized
[Music]
hot okay
I could even listen to this like at the
beach
oh
hello
[Music]
I don't know
and we needed a dog
[Music]
what was that one
Zelda game a Twilight Princess yeah
what's the name in Japanese
[Music]
foreign
no more
[Music]
makes me want to go back and give it
another shot you're really good at
making every game you play so damn
interesting
thank you
I am very happy to hear that you can
play it and then help me let's play it
together
[Music]
thank you
uh
hi attention how's it going cool hat
thank you
if it's cool with you can you comment on
this bottom left chat in that one voice
you did at the beginning of the Stream
you know the other other one the dude
boys
I think you're pretty cool thank you
the dude boys see I already forgot how I
did that voice
uh I can't even come ask him to cover
them
when there's like no way I can move my
arm like that
[Music]
it's pretty difficult
yeah the L wrong he really does
LeBrons
foreign
[Music]
I I don't I don't
I I don't remember I don't I don't I
don't
[Music]
I don't remember I don't remember
that's it
[Music]
I don't I don't remember
that voice is dying
[Music]
you could look at him
I I don't I don't remember
how I did that voice but maybe just gets
somewhat close to it
um
how do I make the Donk voice
did you hear that
[Music]
chat
what are you doing here
you should better get
uh I don't know what to say ah
um
uh
[Music]
okay okay I got it I got it I got it
okay
[Music]
my little chickens what are you doing
here you should better get going before
I eat you up
[Music]
I hate this
I hate it I hate it I hate it thanks I
hate it thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
okay
we wrap down here
[Music]
thank you for the pinky I have to snitch
on myself what is that called confess
watch someone else on the piano clip
came on where you introduced the UR
slash watch only me stream Sparks a
thousand times still feels bad awaiting
your judgment
[Music]
and tells oh uh
no don't tell me don't tell me I don't
want to know I don't want to know
[Music]
awaiting my judgment huh
you know you came back to me so it's all
good as long as you come back to me
it's all good
thank you
but don't leave me too often
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's me that's me
[Music]
your stream always comes first from you
thank you
that was not me
a video about chicken that was not me
[Music]
oh it's good thank you also for the
pinky be still after here A friend told
me this works maybe well we have a typo
in there but actually two typos
but it's okay though I it came across
and yeah I am here quite often because
that's my channel
um that is indeed a phrase that they
used to pick up uh people don't they I
don't know if they do it in English too
but is there really a lame one are you
here often that that's it that's it
that's it
yeah
I stream like five or six days per week
[Music]
thank you
I hope you will be here often too you
better
ER we almost got Rick James
James listening
really thanks for this fun stream uh
Kiana was able to hop in occasionally
but I watched the full Beauty later
thank you
my big news is I was able to find
oh why do I have an alarm going off so
finally able to buy Phoenix birds and
have big boss watching if I deserve the
usual room thank you
you yeah if you guys haven't uh played
the play the bought the merch yet and
you were planning till then do it before
the time is up because I think it's one
one month
probably so yeah before it's gone you'll
regret it forever
get your eight points get your slippers
get you a PC mats and your tapestry the
dope ass who kept about tapestry
yeah I think it's maybe one and a half
more weeks available
[Music]
I got it all day one thank you I already
bought the whole thing bagel
order me a tapestry yeah that one is
gonna look dope
look at Papa's art is so cool
[Music]
like that
um
[Music]
[Applause]
I love the voice back thank you I think
it turned out pretty great yeah
[Music]
I bought the whole set thank you
tapestries and sandals ain't for nice
thank you
still waiting for your badges of beer
opened up why would you use me like that
why
I think that's a community yeah
[Music]
no Yago is not part of it no
it's so cute what
I
the boys back once over here thank you
the IC card was not a card it's a
sticker but yeah I think that one is
also pretty cute
oh the blue glow sticks so those are
really pretty
I want those too damn
jealous
[Music]
I want to show you the slippers I'm so
excited about the slippers
I don't know where I have them where are
they
done ah
[Music]
a little bit of a
uh tiny tiny
tiny top advertisement here
the link should be in my description of
my recent streams this one as well
under the I think under the spikes
link Maybe
[Music]
a B2 tapestry how big is that anyway
a rubble mat a big one that you can put
on under your monitor your uh Mouse and
your keyboard and everything is big
enough for all that
it's like kind of like a mouse pad but
it covers way more than the mouse
and then the cafe apron for people who
like to cook or for people who just went
to
you know on the kfba print for support
and the slippers
only in winter time when the floors are
really really cold and you're freezing
designs
[Music]
foreign
I've seen like a lot of the Japanese
girls putting out merchandise for you
know which is like a subscriber
um Milestones or one year anniversary
and all that
uh solo uh merchandise for anniversaries
and stuff
[Music]
I don't I
don't know IE inside due to already
shipping and stuff being so expensive
doesn't seem like we're getting anything
from Milestones
um
yeah it doesn't really seem like a
possibility at least not at the moment
who knows maybe in the future I will
change
but I think I mean
fine so that we don't you know
come out with new solo merch every three
four or five months that would be so
much anyway I guess
yeah but there's a lot of things I still
would love to bring out this merchandise
so
I'm hoping for at least like one more
chance before the next birthday
I have ideas ideas so many ideas in my
head
[Music]
anyway back to topic and I was finally
able to buy Phoenix merch and have big
boss watching if I deserve the usual
room
oh thank you for getting that thank you
for the support thank you I appreciate
it very much I hope you enjoyed it it'll
probably take a long time until it
reaches your hands but stay a little bit
patient until then and you'll you'll see
it's worth it thank you
[Music]
before I go I want to ask the fortune
teller if I can enjoy my OC forever or
am I about to be turned to a fried
chicken and if so how can I avoid the
scroll fate
you must not ask such direct questions
can only tell you vague answers
let me look into your fortune
I see oil
I See Fire
I see I see breading I see crumbs
[Music]
um I see seven spices or 12 I'm not sure
eleven eleven
[Music]
eleven herks and spices
that's it that's the one
[Music]
try one more yeah we got a one of them
never mind it's a 12 spice 12 12 12
spices 12 herbs and spices
got a one outfit Louis
[Music]
well that then it's to be expect
expected that it's gonna be [\h__\h] oh it's
good
don't use my pickup lines they're they
shouldn't
all right guys that was it I'm gonna
rest my voice now I'll see you tomorrow
for the collab with Ahmed which I'm
actually not sure is that gonna be is
that game supposed to be with two point
of views
a Feeling I feel like uh the others did
it with two point of views before right
it should be on two point of views right
okay I'll go then it will be on my
channel and on Amazon's Channel as well
[Music]
okay guys
thank you I'm gonna go eat food now
probably I enjoyed this stream thank you
so much I'm so glad we started a new
game together and to me I I'm I'm really
careful now to say chair but to me this
is a jail BG so
I'm glad we can play Let's oh yeah how
about we say Adventure game is this
adventure game come on we can call this
an adventure game right
but I hate getting roasted for calling
this a day every day to me it's a
[\h__\h] jampoo Jake
was a great stream thank you for it
thank You Adventure game okay okay so
I'm glad we started a new adventure game
uh we took a little break uh but yeah
Yakuza is done this is our our current
project and I help you out we'll be
there until the very end
is I
I just see what you did there
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
what
I'm shook
[Music]
foreign
yeah you better I hope so
thank you everyone for watching thank
you so much
[Music]
thank you