[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
this is
all right
[Music]
foreign
thank you
Kitty
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
oh ah
chicken again
[Music]
oh oh my God
oh my God
hello
it's been a while Hisashi booty
he saw she booty
Italian
[Music]
too loud
you didn't even hear it lucky you
boom
[Music]
foreign
it had so many lovely little chocolates
and I couldn't even share it with you
[Music]
um
anyway hello
hello
[Music]
I was out so long
I came back to life from the bucket nice
congratulations on Reviving
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
with the water I'm doing that without
the water
[Laughter]
[Music]
hello everybody
hello hello I was just going to say
hello for like 10 minutes
no did I on my video and my photos fine
yeah okay so
lots and lots and lots of photos I did
not
um sort them
uh we're just not the smartest thing
because there are some pictures that I
took of Mama 28 in there as well against
her will
um let me try to read them here extra
big so I can see it before I put it on
screen okay
bow bow
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
how come I've never sung a song like
this before you know in my spark store
do you enduring streams it's actually
quite fun I think it's a work of art
yeah
ah how are you guys doing I'm uh just so
you know the stream will be going on for
maximum of uh less than five hours
because I have a collable on Cali's
Channel after this
uh when we review some food
[Music]
um but yeah I think like the showing you
the photos and telling you the trip uh
stuff is not gonna take like so long but
I do want to read some super chats uh
afterwards because I have to catch up as
you know
um
less than five pounds I know that's an
interesting way to put it isn't it
yes so
um
uh-huh
[Music]
wow
it's kind of like it doesn't quite fit
in here there's like I'm I'm kind of
like getting claustrophobic and let me
like
[Music]
this better yeah I'm moving my staff a
little bit over here
oh
so as you may know
I went to
Rome in Bella Italia I moved hopefully
the buff
I don't like it has wheels on I think
that's actually there are a lot of
pianos which have wheels on on the
bottom right yeah
um yeah yeah uh so I kept the
Throne a little bit of a secret more or
less like I think I mentioned it like a
while ago that I was planning on doing
it and then I kind of kept it secret
with a couple last days so that um
people wouldn't stalk the [\h__\h] out of me
uh but
I noticed something
okay here we go yeah
um so yeah this was a planned for oh
like at least in the beginning at least
it was um
the idea has been around for a while
that I wanted to do
um a trip to Rome because I've been to
Italy many times but wow I've never been
to Rome sorry just answering my cat
never been to Rome I've been to like a
lot of
I guess you could say no names cities
in uh Italy for a vacation
um
foreign
[Music]
I
always have a lot of weird dreams
recently except for the time when I was
in Rome but then no no even even then
even then
another dream I had today together was
the cat's leg dream was
um I was in Pokemon fighting by myself
like I was part of the game and I
challenged someone quite powerful and
fought against him with a random it was
a double fight kind of
uh don't know who the other person was
it's just a random I picked up a rando I
picked it up on the street but it was
very dramatic and then it was
so weird because like
um
the dream Chihuahua was like oh damn
this is like getting really heated and
dramatic I should record this to show it
later on my stream so in my dream I
pushed the record button on obs
because I was like yo this is good
content I should not let this go like
that a lot of the people don't say this
they'll be missing out on so much
thinking of streaming as my number one
priority even in my dreams
yeah no it did not actually work I did
not record anything apparently
um
got the stream of brain
um but yeah anyway back to Rome
uh yeah so I booked I I want
um okay okay okay okay let me explain
let me explain I wanna to go to Rome but
also when thinking about my mom I was
like thinking well she hasn't been on a
proper vacation for a long time and uh
there was in in the last
[Music]
um
let's see in the last 12 years
she went on one trip somewhere which
was not even a vacation but the the last
one on the the 12 years ago one was with
the family My Brother and Me
and since then she since she like bought
herself a house she I guess did not have
the financial ways to go on a vacation
after that so yeah with that in mind I
thought she would probably be very happy
if I occur
to some place to
um enjoy herself and see some stuff and
get her mind off of stuff
and especially Italy she loves Italy she
claims she speaks Italian and
um she she loves Rome I mean she loves
all of Italy I would say but she is it
was interesting before we went to Rome
she did not like
um
[Music]
fan girl so much about Rome but once we
like were there I guess she was reminded
by the awesomeness and then yeah so you
know up until the point where I wrapped
in Rome already a lot of things happened
like me booking a hotel hotel that
turned out to be kind of a low-key scam
not really
um it was all right actually but then I
had to book another accommodation extra
because I remembered that my mom snores
really loudly
and then I can't sleep like that so uh
especially because it was planned to be
for three nights I can take it for one
night maybe but not for free nights
especially if I need some sleep to walk
all day so yeah I booked an extra
accommodation like a cheap Airbnb that
was uh thankfully really close to the
other one it was really just a few steps
away and they were both very Central
um there's this it's I was surprised to
like generally I mean maybe our
accommodations helped but we uh it was
so easy to get around places
in Rome surprisingly it felt very
compact I mean I might be wrong but
if it felt so so tight and compact cool
hair has come who went to Rome before
hey
Rome is not that big yeah it did not
feel that big but it's definitely bigger
than you know most of Austrian big
cities all of them I have I have been a
long time me I live here oh really ah
nice
Old Town isn't as huge I'm not sure like
which part is the old town but I'm
guessing like most of the center
okay so there are some people who went
there
um three to four days it's easy to
navigate exactly yeah so we will also we
were there for three nights
um but anyway
s and getting things
stuff so um let me see so I booked the
accommodations accommodations you know
my mom first she was a little bit like
uh I don't know you know
and I said don't worry mommy I'm I'm
paying for everything
um for accommodation for food for
everything so don't worry about the
thing uh just come with me and you you
try to impress me with your Italian and
you plan out where we go to eat so she
started beforehand she started like
making reservations at restaurants and
and planned out where to eat in the
evening and I asked her to also
um plan out like you know what we would
look at because I had no time to like do
prior investigation
um like I know I know there's some
famous things to see there but you know
I don't know like what what's easy to
read what's important to say and all
that
so I was busy with other [\h__\h] so I left
it all to her that that kind of stuff in
the end I chose a lot of things
spontaneously to to look at
um but yeah it was it was mostly her job
so
then
on Monday Monday on Monday we took a
flight with a cheap ass Airline because
I mean honestly within Europe if you do
short trips in Europe then
you don't really have any other choice
besides those cheap airlines but that's
fine because like they're totally fine
for like a short trip the flight was
really short yeah right in there
the flight was really short and we went
smoothly my mom had a little bit of um
she was a little bit scared of flying
which I didn't know but like she has not
had that much experience with flying so
she was like uh it was kind of funny
like
um I I have way more flying experience
than she does so I like explained her
some things it was all pretty new fresh
to her things have changed since the
last time uh she was on a plane I
suppose and generally yeah she just did
not experience it much
yeah so
um
um yeah but she was she was like not
panicking but a little bit frightened
maybe maybe well but she was fine yeah
um yeah so we we got into the plane
uh oh yeah before that my my brother
came by my apartment
um because my brother took care of my
ketokados
um
because that just worked out well rather
than asking my friends I think I'm
mostly gonna rely on my brother in the
future on taking care of my cry to
Cutters especially when I'll be gone for
like a whole month it's really difficult
to you know ask my friends for it even
if it was just a week or two before
though I still could not get like a
friend to take care of them for the
whole time they would still like they
would not even be able to sleep over
most of the time or or stay for like two
days or so or longer
and I just want someone to be there and
sleep there and stay there without like
all these complications
so my brother actually at the moment is
pretty free uh has time and is currently
looking for a job and stuff so he has
time you know and he's
he's yeah he can do it and he loves my
keto Cutters
yeah I think he had a good time staying
at my apartment anyway good bro yeah
good bro
he's partying in your apartment now I
don't think so at least not this time
also he cooked some of my hellofresh
recipes because I forgot to cancel the
the one for this week
um so he cooked some of them so they
wouldn't go to waste
nice nice nice yeah okay so my brother
took care of my ketokatos and yeah we we
met at my apartment and then we said
goodbye to my brother and then we went
uh to the airport
uh we took we took a train actually this
time and we were rushing a little bit
and we went to uh are we already I
already checked us in online as you have
to with stupid Ryanair and we only had
like one small luggage because I asked
like whoa I was so lucky for some reason
I already had you know those small those
small suitcases that fit in the cabin on
the top I had two of those so I gave one
to my mommy and I I took mine
um so we took that and that's all we
took basically I had one more bag but my
mom really only has uh stuff fitted in
that one suitcase that's pretty much it
yeah I am sup and then we flew it was a
short flight and then we arrived and was
pretty late uh so for me the plan was
the first day obviously just arriving we
arrived at like
9pm or something like that
um
too late so then I try to figure out
with my Google basically the whole trip
24 7 I was using Google Maps like all
the orientation and transportation
everything was Guided by Google Maps
thank you Google Maps for not sponsoring
should be sponsored but not sponsored
but holy moly Google Maps
Lifesaver yeah
Mommy Mommy always was like you think
you should take a look at your little
thing there yeah
okay I was constantly staring at my
Google Maps
really helpful though cause like um
maybe 10 years ago Google Maps wasn't so
useful yet what was
cool I think 10 years ago probably right
I feel like it's definitely improved in
the course of 10 years hmm
hmm
uh-huh
yes it was definitely was okay but yeah
it's definitely gotten better like it
finds the proper Roots Sprouts
um
[Music]
I was only coming in Trend now it's like
you know I remember when I lived in
Japan in the early days not you know the
recent one in the early days I always
used like when I needed to go somewhere
I never used Google Maps I I just used
them like a like a train uh connection
website thingy called Yahoo Yahoo
uh but I never use Google Maps nowadays
I would always use Google Maps I'm
always rely on Google Maps because it
also tells me the the way to the station
and all that
um
[Music]
okay we arrived and then we got
that fused me
which uh I don't have a photo of but let
me let me show you a picture I think
this is totally okay here come on
here
this is uh you know when we arrived at
the Roma terramini it's the main station
of Rome I mean it doesn't really look
special I guess on this photo uh it's
pretty normal
I would say
yeah it's just a train station
um when we arrived and and then we uh
went to the ticket
no wait no wait first we have arrived in
at the airport and then we went to the
ticket counter the automatic one the ATM
style one
um and we typed in Roma Termini
that's where we needed to go
and then
it show you know on Google Maps it gave
me the fastest and without changing uh
best route uh
which was like I don't know 40 34
minutes or 27 or something like that uh
and it said like which train number and
all that and when it leaves and I looked
for that one in the machine but what
Google Maps did not tell me was that
apparently this was like a first class
one and then we were so confused and I'm
sure there's like other tourists who get
really confused by this because then you
you look at the the connections that are
offered to you in the ticket machine and
some say first class some say second
class and then we saw the first class
for the one that we wanted to take but
I was like okay where is second class we
don't need first class where is the
second class for this exact train and it
just was not available so I was
wondering okay is second class actually
like fully booked what the [\h__\h] that
that's weird what hey so then we looked
a little bit through the other
connections but in the end I ended up
buying the first class tickets which
were I think
I think 12 euro per person
which isn't crazy right it's not it's
not crazy so it's okay but I was just
confused and then we went into the train
and everything was fine but it did not
look like a first class train so that
confused us too like
and it also didn't seem to have a first
cat first class
um like wagon it's just a really
freaking normal train so we sat down it
was also hella empty
and uh the train conductor comes and to
check start tickets
and then
we asked him about the first class or
whatever and he explains that this train
has no second class it is only first
class basically it's a normal train yeah
but the difference to the second class
tickets from the different trains were
that this one just makes no stops and is
therefore faster which makes it first
class so in case you guys ever come to
Rome and you can you would be confused
about that here you have the answer
for that the fast ones the fast um
trains that go from a few michino
airports to the city center those are
first class because just because they
don't stop their Express yeah
yeah
and you can buy a second class ticket
which is a little bit cheaper but that
train will make some stops yeah
yeah yeah it was so confusing just write
Express or something and I everybody
would understand in my opinion
hmm
Stone anodes
money
[Music]
yeah Italian do things differently Tokyo
tones
um
okay so yeah then we arrived and uh we
walked towards our apartments for the
first one
um I needed to be there around a certain
time
uh because someone would check us in but
then the other one you know the extra
one the cheap one I I got you know was
self chicken so we went to one first
which is the one where I was you know
talking to you guys about you know it
being a scam or so it's seemingly being
a scam especially after looking into the
reviews
um
well we walked there and from the
outside it really seemed to be a normal
building not a hotel okay
and then but then so cool like ah so we
went inside I want to show this but I
need to censor some some names probably
let me let me can I really quickly whip
whip whip up some sensor uh in Photoshop
one second I need to show you this
because we saw this in several buildings
um peeking in inside some buildings
where people lived uh here let me
sensor your filter
gaussian blur
okay
and then I will
[Music]
see
sorry I did not remember this picture
but I need to show it so we enter what
seemingly is a totally normal
uh building where people live but pretty
fancy like there was like a red carpet
and you went up some like maybe five
steps to like a little bit higher level
but not like a new floor obviously
um and you know the the red carpet uh at
the at the stairs
at the steps like the the corners the
inside corners of it there would be like
golden bars you know fixing it in place
if you know what I mean do you know what
I mean golden fin bars
gave it a really elegant fancy and old
look
yeah
yeah you know what I mean yeah it was it
was beautiful and then the whole wave
was beautiful and and I don't know ah so
pretty like it looked very expensive and
elegant and sophisticated but old old
very old too
okay I think I got the picture
censored nicely
okay let me export
[Music]
okay my Photoshop is nihongo okay next
picture
it should be okay now yes
so some food that I would see in there
with this little post boxes
and and
like actually
in use and I saw them in several
buildings kind of
adorable
cute maybe with this you can kind of
imagine the style
um
oh
but the weird thing is you can look
inside and see what your the other
people who live there uh received
um
cute looks normal to me I'm an Italian
see if this is normal apparently in many
many italian Apartments
um let me clean this up and then and
then the absolute highlight of this
let me see of their reflections
it's not really a look like it
well several times in in Rome Apartments
was the elevator
it's an old school
really old elevator that made me feel
like I'm in a different Century like we
have a lot of old uh apartment buildings
in Austria too but
[Music]
I mean let me flip it
oh [\h__\h] flipped it the wrong way
girl so it had like this this gray metal
um gate that you had to open up oh sure
yeah and then then there were extra
doors inside that you had to open up
towards the inside and it's really old
it had like I know it felt like I was
getting into
um a a wheel uh the the
Ferris wheel
or until Gondola or something like that
really cute it looks so old and it felt
kind of old we only had to go one floor
but we still wanted to use it every time
yeah very common in Italian villain I'm
telling you I'm telling you this is just
a normal thing apparently we were
fascinated by this
um
yeah
they're the thankfully the elevator only
works if you have both the outer and the
inner door closed so every time you
leave you have to make an effort to uh
close both doors also while when you
exit yeah
um
foreign
[Music]
yeah it's so old-fashioned
I don't know from what century this is
it definitely looked like a pretty old
not renovated
this part this elevator
but not like unclean
um
you have to otherwise it's danger for us
and then it doesn't work right if the
doors are not closed and you you call it
from a different floor it just will not
come right because somebody forgot to
close the doors
laughs
no one ever closed the doors we did all
the time don't worry people get mad more
imaginable
but that's obviously the the big big
minus point about this kind of elevator
anyway so we went to the apartment
um
so this thing this hotel thing
definitely was not a proper Hotel the
reception was one small desk
uh in a really narrow tiny hallway
um but the floors were marble and uh I I
for me personally personally I really
like the interior of the room as well
because it kind of gave me low-key Art
Deco style and I like art deco
um yeah it looked clean and pretty nice
so the room itself was not a problem I
would say uh I let my mom stay in it for
all the free nights
so I think she had a good time their
bathroom was clean and big as well I did
not take a picture of the room actually
because I didn't stay there
um but yeah so that was that and then we
went over oh by the way
that they were not suddenly
it's my card
um
and after afterwards but originally a
lot of the complaints wrote this and
also it was written to me by the by the
owner
um that's due to our due late arrival we
have to pay extra so and so much money
which was quite a lot
but at the check-in the only thing they
demanded was city tax so all good and I
didn't say anything because I was
excited that maybe they forget about it
at the checkout as well the thing of
that sort and also I have yet to be
called or or
messaged to be asking for a late
check-in uh yeah late yeah yeah it
wasn't even that late it was like uh 9
or 10 p.m which is a normal check-in
time I would say for hotels but
especially for expensive ones like that
what the [\h__\h] while the other cheap ass
a that I built for myself had none such
a thing but it was also self-checking
uh it was all right and um my mom
enjoyed the room and it wasn't as bad as
expected so all is okay
um
just a little bit waste of money maybe
oh well so then we went I went to the
other one we went to the other one yeah
which was
more of a typical Airbnb
um
it was not so nice
but it did its job in providing me a bed
and a bathroom
so it's okay I survived it it was kind
of cold even though I was heating the
room
um and I did not sleep well and not bad
so I was pretty
tired on Sundays
um but it was okay like in the morning
um I would often like I had my own room
and it was not like a shared house like
a typical Airbnb where you only get like
one room
um it was it kind of was
[Music]
um
I guess designed to be like a room chair
apartment or whatever
[Music]
um but it did feel like I had like some
some space that resembled a hotel room
but at the same time the walls and
everything were so thin that in the
morning I would hear the door is closing
very loudly the footsteps very loudly
and voices were pretty loudly
it was okay though because even though
I'm a light sleeper at least there was
not so much of that going on because I
think there was only one other person
staying in that
floor besides me so it wasn't too bad
thankfully I was worried about that but
I after hearing it I fell back asleep
again pretty fast so it was okay
but I'm happy to be back in my own place
um
[Music]
yeah
they're a privacy
no I mean there was privacy
if you were quiet yeah
um oh actually my mom was absolutely
fascinated
by the interior no not the interior the
I guess this is also a thing a lot of
these apartments in Rome have like
inside
Gardens kind of things
I only took a picture of it at night but
it was like a tropical garden there
so first of all
you come in
and you see
[\h__\h]
you walk in for the main big gate door
I love this
you have this big marble floor with a
big round ceiling and you walk through
and you see it was rainy so that's
unfortunate would you see like a big
tropical garden with like a little
Fountain I
green
it was so cool
it was so cool I was fascinated by it
too
um I have another photo
[Music]
why do you do that
I must say this does not do it justice
at all it felt way Fuller and way
greener in reality and if you go all the
way to the you know middle front and
there was like a little Fountain there
in the Middle
with lots of green and oh my God it was
so tropical I used the white lens so it
feels a little bit emptier than it
actually was
thank you thank you thank you it was
really nice so a lot of Apartments like
this have uh these kind of inner Gardens
that's really cool
um for dinner the first night we just we
arrived late so we just randomly walked
around and entered a random ass
uh restaurant
where my mommy got herself like those
noodles with the farm parmigiano and the
the pepper the Pepe
and what do you call that again it's
like really popular over there
um
the Pepe yeah
yeah
that's the one yes
um I'm so sorry I love parmesan cheese
uh like that too but when they were
making it before they brought it out
even five minutes before they brought it
out I smelled
like something that resembled
that the smell of something that's
thrown up
[Music]
and I was like Mommy do you smell this
because like it smells like someone
threw up
and we were sitting close like right at
some stairs that led
um down so I thought maybe down there
there's like the toilet and some
employee threw up or so I don't know
that's how you know it's good
yeah it's not parmesan okay okay sure
um
but okay I was like well sure okay
hopefully that's not your food but then
it came and when it was there right in
front of us it didn't smell like that
maybe I was too used to it at that point
but didn't smell like that but when I
tried a taste of it
tasted like that
that is this
[Music]
I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry to insult dish and I think
a lot of people really enjoy it
but it tastes a little bit like
[Music]
throw up
stuff
but like a like a like only a hint of it
okay a big a big hint though
um it vomits yes
um
so that was interesting my my mom did
not like really
seem to be bothered by it at all
as I said it's normal oh
I it's I was quite surprised by that I
just got a pizza because my mom said if
I order pizza in the other restaurants
that she reserved
she will punch me uh and be very ashamed
and embarrassed and I was like oh oh oh
okay
oh she was like you don't order pizza in
those nice restaurants and I'm like I
mean they were not like super fancy
restaurants yo they weren't normal
restaurants
[Music]
so
um but fine for me so I ordered some
pizza on the first night because we went
into a random random place and this this
waiter that took care of us basically
scouted us to come in
because I was looking for a different
restaurant on Google Maps and I couldn't
find it and he was like a principessa
principessa and I'm like hey yo
[Music]
Italian charm calling me a princess
yeah and that we were asking well how
long are you open and he said as long as
you want and I'm like okay
so well we went in and the place wasn't
too bad you know Mom Mommy enjoyed her
pasta and I enjoyed my pizza it but then
you know I ordered I I said because I
looked over to another table and the
dude had like a huge Pizza on this plate
and I'm like I'm never gonna finish that
do you have like a smaller size of pizza
um and he said yes
so it said please the smaller size
but when I got was exactly the same size
as the other dude and I was like what
the [\h__\h] you trolled me
and he said no this is small but I think
he was joking he really only had one
size
and also I asked him to throw some
rukula on top of it and you said
anything you want
and but
it was a little bit overkill on the
rookola
I have a whole [\h__\h] salad on my pizza
so what I did was absolutely genius
my mom's uh vomit uh
cheese Pepe
um was definitely missing some green
stuff and and so I gave her some rookola
and it fitted perfectly to her uh pasta
yeah
yeah and but this pizza was really good
I could still only eat half of it though
so the rest of the half we took uh back
and my mom ate it
um in the following two nights one piece
each one fourth each yeah
was good it was just a random place and
it was still so good
so that was a big success yeah
why is the salad on your pizza that's a
lot of record it is I'm good I guess
but it actually worked really well my
mom said that was perfect addition I
know normally you don't have roccola in
it but it was a perfect addition
actually
oh no oh um I'm sorry my Italian kfp
don't be mad okay don't be mad I'll make
it up to you okay
because now that was the first night
let's just let's just you know it's
already been 50 minutes let's just move
on uh we all we both went to our uh
um
I went to our um uh places to sleep and
I tried to sleep early of course I
failed but I still woke up early uh and
then we went to have a little breakfast
in a cafe it was quite a busy popular
Cafe I did not take a picture though
unfortunately but it was right on the
other side of the street
um oh yeah it really stood out to us
because when we were walking around at
like past 10 P.M to find a restaurant
um this place was even still open on our
way back at after 11 p.m like almost
midnight actually it was still open with
the smell of fresh baked goods that you
could smell from
Miles Away really
that's one of the reasons we were able
to find our way back
oh it smells so good so we decided to go
there the next day for breakfast
that's how they get you yeah also at 11
PM we also passed by an open gelato
place
this was one of the things that blew my
mind that you know I like ice cream in
the winter maybe once
but I I
here in Austria in the winter time
already by the time of Autumn until the
summer starts all ice cream places are
closed
and it's Unthinkable for them to be open
because no one would really make use of
it no one wants to eat ice cream gelato
in the winter
[Music]
of November where it's cold as [\h__\h]
I saw open gelato places everywhere
and people were actually making use of
it and they were even open until late in
the night
foreign
I am fascinated by Italians
maybe it's just Rome but uh Gelato at
night very popular apparently
your stairs just built different they
really love their gelato
um
[Music]
in Spain too same in Argentina wow
wow all those beautiful
summer image countries
[Music]
God
wow you guys have a different culture I
guess
oh
wow what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
what it's not like it's warm in the
winter it was cold there too
oh those like Southern countries say
they do the same apparently
it's not even that much South though
it's not tropical
fascinated anyway anyway
uh so yeah we smelled that so we decided
to go there for breakfast the next day
[Music]
we wake up to
a lot of rain
and
I was at this point so hopeful that it
wouldn't be the whole day
but yes it was the whole [\h__\h] day
and it was not even weak rain there were
maybe some hours where the rain was
weaker
but there was also always
a lot of stronger rain
and cold winds
throughout the day
and
we were sitting in the cafe
[Music]
and waiting for the rain to stop a
little bit
obviously
without oh yeah I did not work
So eventually we just had to go when it
was pouring down in buckets
and I we both had an umbrella
and mistake was we both were wearing
um sneakers trainers hiking style
trainers
because we thought we would be walking a
lot which we were
but the problem is they have this really
thin Airy fabric on the top with low-key
holes
where the air comes through right
so the moment I step outside
and walk
10 meters
I already noticed my feet are getting
drenched
[Music]
a few moments ago when I was still
sitting in the cafe looking outside the
window seeing a dude selling to tourists
a raincoat and also a shoe plastic bag
cover
I was
joking with my mom about how that looks
stupid
mostly the the boot cup the shoe covers
because they're like literally big
um plastic bags on top of the shoes
and then I was thinking in hindsight yes
we should have gotten those because our
shoes never had a chance
Deva
oh my gosh
well you know uh in Rome on a rainy day
literally everywhere you go there will
be people selling
actually only men never saw a woman
selling anything at all ever there will
be men selling you or trying to sell you
raincoats
and umbrellas
mostly raincoats though
uh randomly on the side of the street
uh and when we saw them you know we
didn't need the raincoat I really only
and even though it looks fit I wanted to
run and roam to his rooms but those are
anyway
um I I asked like one dude if he had
those little shoe covers and he didn't
have them and I never saw anyone selling
those shoe covers ever again only the
raincoats but no not the shoe covers
which is the one thing that I needed but
it was too late at that point anyway I
was already drenched hmm
um
women are not allowed by law to sell
wrinkles
sure that's definitely it
oh yeah anyway yeah it sounds like a
local gym business yeah and during
during the not rainy day they were not
selling raincoats they were selling
bracelets
and other [\h__\h]
yeah which I have another whole story as
well
[Music]
so uh yeah we were um from you know you
have to imagine for the Italians who
know Rome or the non-italians who also
know around we were staying at a place
really close to the main train station
and from there on we basically walked
all the way through a garden to the
Colosseum for a big Park
um which
was nice if it was not raining but with
a big Park the big Park you know it had
like already
fascinating stuff like like really old
little buildings like this this was um
apparently an old building where
um
old people
uh pencil and like uh what a pension
building for old people retired a
retired home or something like that I
think I translated what it said I think
this was it
it was behind the fence though I I
smartly photographed through it but yeah
it had like stuff like this this whole
big Park
and yeah we walked to the Colosseum
another thing I saw on the way to it was
um
this
there's like stuff like this you just
see randomly
like just
[\h__\h] dare
[Music]
oh
wow
that is cool
foreign
s
um
[Music]
full of ancient rooms yeah hell yeah
so much history
[Music]
so that was actually already at the end
of the park and then we walked a bit
more and we finally
um arrived at
the kind of the back side of the
Colosseum
um you know the famous
see how [\h__\h] shitty the weather was
but yeah
it would have been so much better if it
was nice rather but oh well so here you
see the Colosseum first the first view
we kind of had
we were on like a pretty high level uh
and we had to like get around get down
and then walk all the way around
um because first we tried to go to the
right side
and the right side was kind of just like
we looked down and we saw it was a dead
end and we couldn't go down but this
kind of like this construction side was
uh from this side it was kind of
disturbing like the view and the
atmosphere I would say
um but that was only from this side if
you look at it from the other sides it
was not bothering
um
and but here you see here you see it
says ticket
um office and ticket for the Colosseum
Palatine Hill Roman forum
uh uh thin Euro okay
and I think that's the ticket you need
for entering the Colosseum and the The
Forum woman no no no no no
like
I my mom was not planning on entering
she did not really want to enter
and so I was just like okay I guess
we're not entering also because the
tickets were I mean we did not even
check but we just I guess assumed that
they would be online only and sold out
in advance which seems to be true though
um
so we just walked all the way around it
and on the way
I already found
cute seagull
and I started taking pictures of cute
seagulls already
at this point
the statue in the back is actually just
a picture by the way
but isn't this a good picture
I I took it on purpose like this with
the statue in the back
[Music]
cute even got like got it when it was
cleaning itself cute
so now we walked around it and then oh
we we reached
this point
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] them
[Music]
here we go okay we move we reached this
part
where you can see
on the right side that wall is the
remaining outer wall
and on the left side you know it did not
have that wall anymore it was destroyed
but yeah so this is the the actually
basically the back
aside from what you do not enter
normally you enter from the front but
you know we walked all the way around it
um
so I tried to zoom in
and look at this
and
then
so
this is you know some nice Latin written
on it
spectacles
insignities
statistics
[Music]
I learned Lots in before in school yeah
but I cannot translate this because it's
been too long and basically Latin was
the reason why I left that school
[Music]
but cool stuff Benedictus the 14th
um yes
Benedict who's the 14th and
that is a pope was a poop
[Music]
so the snack
and then oh you know when we were
walking around it
we were noticing
some flaws
holes
these bigger holes
I didn't know
you have these all around the Colosseum
and
we actually eventually found out what
those were
and it was a very surprising interesting
reason because like we were like what
makes these holes like it's at weird
spots so it's not like they could just
fall out there right because you look at
the placement of the holes
um and then I was wondering maybe like
it was shot with like small Bombs all
over but no so a tour guide ended up
telling us
that in all those holes
that was originally
um
I think bronze
I think it was bronze or gold no it was
probably bronze
or Woods or wait there was there were
several materials that were mentioned
in a connection to a lot of
holds in the Colosseum and other places
basically there was something in their
material that many many many many
hundreds years uh thousands years ago
um people went there took it out stole
it brought it back to their own country
yeah and in some places it was bronze in
some places it was gold in some places
it was I run in some places it was um
wood even
[Music]
they were just lacking so many materials
in other places
um of all places
take it from there which
is so like
I can't
like even back then you must have looked
at this and understood that this is like
this this is history how can you take it
yeah
oh man
yeah so that happened a lot apparently
yeah a lot of uh I forgot the countries
they mentioned some countries who did
that
uh but also originally in order to even
build this
I think she also mentioned that they
took
materials from elsewhere so you know it
was all just a big exchange and you know
you know giving and taking taking and
giving receiving and stealing
it's a thing it's a thing yeah
and you know Rome wasn't built in a day
but this thing this Colosseum which by
the way actually is not even called
Colosseum and uh the official name I
already forgot it
let me look it up
the Colosseum
Aya flavian I'm I'm free field trip
uh I'm I'm I'm free feature is the
actual uh
uh name yeah
and it was built in eight years
I think
really fast because
um you know it looks it's obviously huge
yeah
and looks like it would take ages to
build
but
the thing is that it's like very let me
go back to I guess like this picture
the thing is it's very repetitive
you have the same arches all over again
so
um the people who were building it
didn't even have to be specifically
skilled you teach them how to make an
arch and you're done
so we were told that yeah just a lot of
unskilled people built the same thing
over and over and over and over again
yeah a lot of people and that's why they
were able to build it in such a short
time
[Music]
yeah
yeah well it's like just like a million
arches it looks so cool though
okay so so that was like you know we
were walking around and then we we uh
kind of reached the front side
eventually
and at the front side
I photographed
[Music]
um
this thing
um this was also an arch right next to
the Colosseum
I forgot the name surely in Italian can
tell me what it's called again
but like here's some close-up
uh
uh turn your heads everybody look at the
details
look at the details
ah
I'll call the costantino really well
that might be it then it's right next to
the Coliseum you can see it in the
background
um
see look this is cool
it's just somewhere at the top of the
arch
Arc Arch Arch
some oh yeah
over here this is another example all of
these letters originally had like bronze
or gold or something on it
and you see it's gone they took it off
you didn't see the holes probably where
it was like nailed hammered in
[Laughter]
funny
it's so funny
it's ridiculous
here's some more details that I took
uh what's going on here there's some
dudes uh in armor looking up to two
dudes standing on a podest
uh with like fashionable drapes
around their body and then on the right
side we have like more dudes with some
sheeps and a pig and uh
a cowl animal
and I have no idea what's going on here
no idea
[Music]
[Laughter]
no yeah but it looks cool
I hear another detail
uh
uh took a lot of detailed shots here
because there was a lot going on
so here we look uh-huh or some broken
side thingies but it looks so cool so
detailed look at all those details y'all
wow
wow see they all Walking In One
Direction here
where are they going
uh here it says Clementi the the 12th
font Max
Etc
exactly what it says
yeah you can't walk through it there was
a fence around it but it was pretty big
and you could get like literally right
in front of it
um
at this stage I was like freezing and uh
cold
and then we were just like I was taking
photos and we were gonna walk towards
some Palatine hell thing I guess but
then a lady
walks up to us and asks if we're
planning to go inside if we have a
ticket or so and we were like no I guess
not
but then she explains that she's a tour
guide and if we want we can join her
tour
if we join the tour then it will cost
more but if we just want to go inside
that's possible too and it will cost a
little bit less but we will enter as
part of the tour
and there were a lot of these people
around okay
and these are so from from my
understanding
tour guides at least ever since the
pandemic happens the the tickets for
these sites were mostly available online
I guess so anyway tour guys bye
tickets for tours a long time in advance
even without having the people to enter
the tour already so they just deserve it
in advance and then at the spot they
Scouts the tourists and obviously
there's a lot of tourists who don't have
a ticket and this is at the moment the
only way to get in because then on the
day the tickets will not be available
because they're sold out so they have to
rely on the tourist guides which is a
bit more expensive than normally as we
saw before tickets 16 Euro and I paid
much more
but so
I kind of did want to go in my mom
didn't really feel like going in and I
understand also because there's like
stairs and all that and my mom has like
some weakness and all that but I kind of
I was like you know I'm here I should
see the inside I should
I'm sure it will be worth it so she
offered us to you know going with the
tour and I was like you know what I
actually I do want to listen to your
explanations it's a one hour tour and I
actually do want to listen to it because
I do want some information I just I
don't want to just look at things and
you know be like okay that looks cool
but I have no idea what the history
behind it is
and
um yeah so I I convinced my mom to do it
so when we when we did go and
head yeah we had to wait quite a long
time and the freezing cold until the
whole group was ready to go in
had to wait like half an hour or so it
was freezing
but yeah we made it in and in hindsight
I have to say it was so worth it
oh I wish I was your tour guide
you're an archaeologist oh cool wow
that's so cool is it scalping though I
don't know
I wouldn't I don't know I don't know if
it is but in that moment it's kind of
the only way and a lot of people do it
that way
um so if you if you plan on going to
Rome ever
well you can even go on the spontaneous
tour like that or if you really want to
go inside on your own then you should
book The Ticket way in advance
so
yeah
um there was a a tour guide lady she was
like really fancy she looked like a like
a fancy lady I could barely understand
her Italian accent though in the first
20 minutes
because she was also we were all walking
in while she was talking and it was
really distracting and I had no idea
what she was saying in the first 20
minutes or 15 minutes
um but she was nice and we all had like
ear pieces with like a walkie-talkie
kind of thing receiver thing so we would
hear her even if we were 20 meters away
that was actually pretty good pretty
helpful
yeah but I had a hard time understanding
her English the first time so I was like
oh this is gonna be [\h__\h] I'm not gonna
understand the word but then later I was
actually able to understand her quite
well and that's where I got all those
informations about how fast it was built
and by what kind of people it was built
while it was so fast and and about the
the stolen bronze and whatever and all
that so it was pretty interesting it was
pretty cool and uh I I even got to ask
some questions and she answered those as
well
um so we entered and I mean the tourists
all do it differently there's so much to
show so we did not look at every single
detail
but we would look at like this thing I
already forgot what that was though
um but yeah that was the first look
inside after a security check by the way
but no problem with that
um
we were a group of like 20 people maybe
or 15 or so
um
yeah I don't know what that is what is
that I don't remember
and and she told us to look at the
ceiling so I took a picture of the
ceiling she was saying something about
that ceiling uh something about I think
I think she just said that the ceiling
you know parts of the Colosseum are uh
restored and and supported and all that
but you know original stuff that is not
renovated is
I think she said
30 or 40 percent or so
no there was something with the ceiling
but I forgot what it was this was still
in the beginning where I could not
understand her so well
um
and then we walked by a lot of stuff
here there were a lot of these like
places in between the arches
and basically
this was where the stairs were so all
the normal stairs that go up to the
seats all the stairs and the seats are
destroyed so those don't do you know
this is just left over
but you have to imagine here was the
stairs to go up and basically see I also
learned this let me show you actually
um on this occasion to explain this I'll
show you a picture
because I took so many pictures
[Music]
um so there were like several rows of
saints
um on the more or less bottom
because it's close whereas then the rich
people
the middle was middle class and up very
high was the the lower class because
they had to walk up so many stairs to
get up there and she also said something
about there was only so little time to
enter she said like a certain amount of
time maybe 20 minutes or so uh she
really emphasized that that you have to
enter and leave in 20 minutes or
something like that I don't know what
happens if you don't but she emphasized
that
um and then there was like um if you
look at
duh how do I show you this
I think it was
I mean I could be wrong
but I think
how do I point it out there's nothing
really to
nothing that points it out specifically
there was a seat for special like
Emperor or whatever
um
I would say it's like in the almost the
middle almost The Middle on the right
side
I think it was there
yeah I mean now it doesn't there's not
much remaining and then
um basically you see this big open hole
in the middle of course there was a
floor on top of that so they restored
part of the floor in the very back as
you can see but they left the rest open
just because I guess it's cool to look
inside which I agree it's kind of cool
so I I asked like okay what what is
inside like what was inside there under
the floor and she said yeah well people
were like um just I guess like
you know working down there preparing
stuff and whatever
but yeah there was some stuff going on
inside there and also we didn't go
didn't go down there but you can see
there's a path down there in the
underground
so some tours they go on the ground we
didn't though we didn't
um
[Music]
yeah cool isn't that so cool it's so
cool
I I took a video
but it's basically the same as the
picture so I'm not focused on
and then while we were walking inside
there were like a lot of things like
this
um in like museum style they were
showing stuff like this
stuff for games
yeah
oh sure
she's just half a body
a lot of stuff like that and then inside
you know we would walk through
these hallways which I thought looked
really cool
you know for the Arches and on the sides
it was always open
very cooling yo
um
[Music]
yeah I think that was basically all I
had of the color sale oh there was way
more like I was listening to her talk a
lot and she was showing a lot of like
things cool things
even told us about
then with my a little model inside the
clothes see I'm a little model of
um a call of Sam
that was built by a certain dictator
um starting with the letter M uh she
told us a story how he
um he really liked he really likes the
the Colosseum
um so much that he wanted to build his
own and there's a Mario
and it's you can look it up I think if
you type in his name and call a sandwich
though maybe it will come up
it has its own name though but
um there's just this Square Coliseum
basically it's a square version of the
Colosseum it has all these arches
uh and it's Square [\h__\h] block and
it's also in Rome but a little bit like
outside
[Music]
or maybe that
maybe that sounds familiar
it's kind of weird the fact that it's so
Square it makes it look like a really
weird building yeah it's a cube
um
and uh
it's kind of on the way to the airport
if you ever go buy a car then you might
see it she said and the thing is that it
for many years recently in the recent
years this place
has been used as an office for a fashion
brand called Fendi for like 11 years the
main office was in that weird [\h__\h]
Colosseum which is so
to me it felt like such a flex as a
fashion brand you could like get just a
random office good looking modern office
but you choose you choose the cool Sam
Cube that was built
by the wishes of a certain
Mr M
H okay
that's weird I don't think they use it
anymore so now I don't I don't know
what's inside now but uh
weird
look it up look it up guys have you
looked it up have you looked it up
[Music]
history do be weird
oh
oh wow what a roast
[Music]
looks wacky right
I don't know it looks like
hmm
I don't know how to describe it because
it gives me weird feelings though
ah Palazzo de las a
yeah that's the name then okay okay so
after that uh this was not uh with a
guide but we got the entrance through
the tour we went to Affordable for one
more months
[Music]
in Italian
which is right next to the Colosseum
basically a big open-air Museum
of all kinds of cool ruins
um
and I'll show you a [\h__\h] ton of pictures
because I took so many pictures
first thing you see one of the one of
the first things you see is this cool
Arch that I had to take a picture of the
inside because holy macaroni look at
that
would you say this
look at that
all the details
I know
[Music]
so cool so it had a lot of these kind of
things standing around let me try to
give you a vibe
so this is a vibe
you've seen the back behind the fence a
lot of ruins yeah yeah
let me just let me just walk you through
it
what do we have here
you know are you getting into the
atmosphere are you feeling it
this is you know I used my my zoom but
what do you say now here you have we
here we have the Colosseum in our box we
walk through the photo romano and in the
front
in the very back do you see
those angels
[Music]
oh
that's what we were heading to
that is also very very big famous big
big big site that you have to check out
if you're in Rome
um
so what I what I saw a lot in Rome that
really fascinated me with this these
layers
there's so there's like so many layers
like a cake or like an onion I said uh
ogres have uh
ogres and onions have layers and also
Rome has layers
you know what I mean
he's so cool
[Music]
so crazy so it was this was a huge Park
I totally recommend the floral Romano
and what do I have here
okay you know there were a lot of people
walking around basically okay you have
these little little paths to walk around
and everybody will also
um uh like little little signs with
um explanations what everything was and
it was really interesting
a lot of cool interesting things here's
more more layers
I was really into the layers here
I took so many photos and my mom was
like why do you take like five photos of
the same thing and I said because of
like I'm like trying to wait for the
people to walk by and I'm waiting I'm
trying to figure out the right angle and
the right
um you know landscape or porch red Etc
like so many things to think about
yeah but look at this
so much in one picture so much oh oh oh
here here I was
I was being really artistic
let me see which one is the best here
perhaps that one
[Music]
oh
uh in the front
made it blurry with the focus
and uh yeah you know to have more layers
and more depth in the picture wow I'm
such a photographer wow
no filters by the way it was shitty
weather so without filters it looks kind
of shitty though
um
oh then there was this this cute
something the way you could walk through
like some cute influencer girls were
trying to take pictures in there it was
really dark though like I don't know how
you take a picture in there
just one of the many things it was
really small though we have you can't be
tall if you want to walk through here
[Music]
we have a disa
a lot of broken sculpture thingies
broken buildings ruins
[Music]
yeah
more of that
there's a lot of people like up there at
the top of something you see it I don't
know we didn't go there
maybe another time I can go there looks
cool
oh my God like this will take ages
telling you about all of this
[Music]
and they actually saw these pictures I I
hmm
I will still upload later on Twitter
because I wanted to do something with
them
but let me show you
anyway
this was another cool thing I love these
kind of things I don't know how to call
them but you know they have this big big
[Music]
tall things
yes
yeah so cool
not so many of them and oh my God so
cool this one was still quite intact
and then here we go I took a lot of
pictures of burps
burp pictures
yeah
[Music]
they're so big look verb and layers and
depth
long boys it has long boys but this is
this is chunky boy
big fluffy bellies mmm so cute this is
one oh oh oh oh oh this this this one is
[\h__\h] gorgeous I must say look at that
holy macaroni I think I uploaded this
one on Twitter
look how the front is in focus
and the back is in a little bit blurry
oh
I'm doing [\h__\h] magic with these
seagulls they're my models
Top Model
and then I have this one
I like that one even though there's no
ruins in the background and then we have
the the seagulls who are done talking
with each other
so babies often which makes so much
sense to me now that in Japanese the
name for seagulls is umineko which means
ocean cat
made so much sense to me now now that I
realized they sound like cats quite
often
and I think I uploaded this one too but
in in in portrait mode this is the
landscape version
little burp on a pillar
and then we have
[Music]
um
another verb in front of the Basilica
Emilia
he's so cute look at it look at the
Flappy Bird
and then we have uh two burps being
fluffy
on their own pillars
and then I think this one's a bit darker
that one's better maybe
cute so cute
uh oh
oh I took a video that was really good
let me see
okay are you ready for a picture a video
it might be loud I don't know
[Music]
hmm
okay
I I might I'm you know what I'm gonna
mute it okay
wait
let's look at it here
so we have Sea Gal
you approach your your thing looks good
your pillar I'm gonna approach there
I'm gonna drink good rain water now sit
how do I sit if I sit side fits or if
it's I said oh shake that water
it's so cute
oh my God freaking adorable
[Music]
being adorable
s
[Music]
[Applause]
oh this was a nice view
this was when we already pretty much
reached the absolute back of it
and you see like a big view of
everything that you left behind
that thing gives you a good good feeling
of want
what it looks like overall
yeah it's a really big place we didn't
even see all of it because we got really
like we needed an idol meeting and we
were hungry and we were freezing
[Music]
uh some pages I uploaded on Twitter that
you must see you have to check it out
because you know this one was a flying
bird
it's like a story in a couple of
pictures
and then we have another another bird
[Applause]
and then we have
another one
um
I don't know why they come in flipped
when in the actual Windows preview they
are already in the right direction oh
well
here there you go burp burp
and then we have
oh so adorable so cute ah
[Music]
burbs my mom and so at this point she
was like can you stop taking pictures of
these birds and I'm like um no
I have to it's my calling like this is
literally the reason why I came to Rome
and I just didn't know it beforehand
well
sharing one pillar
adorable and you see the layers again
the layers of Rome
beautiful
that's walking and taking pictures
because there was no tour guide so you
know
okay here we have another burp surprise
I always have to resize these [\h__\h]
and this one unfortunately I guess it
wasn't so much in Focus but
I like this one very much too
isn't this art what a model and this
without makeup even
okay okay here
I think we left oh yeah
uh I left
I left the
um
let me look at this video what did I
film
ah
[Music]
is this
oh
no no that's just I guess an overall
view I can show you this one too
maybe that I don't know what you hear I
can't hear it but this is just
some of you
I'll hear from layers of Rome
[Music]
looking around
for Romano palatino
yeah lots of tourists and we have those
beautiful pillows
yeah that was what it was like but I
took one video
that was so funny with the birds maybe
I'll find it another time
well okay so we left for romano and we
were looking for a cafe we kind of
failed
and looking for it but like even if
do this you find stuff like this you
just walk through it like Rome also see
on the top right all those burps
[Music]
things
everywhere and you see the holes again
where they stole the materials
funny
yeah you just walk through it like in
the middle of the city
like this was a normal freaking path
around for a Romano with traffic but
even there the buildings look like this
insanity
like I I come from Austria where we I
was you know I I said this to my mom
after looking at all of this
I was very proud of the beauty of
Austrian cities older buildings
and architecture uh and castles and [\h__\h]
you know but then I walk through Rome
and I'm like how can
never recommend Austria
to someone who wants to visit a city in
Europe
ever again
I can never ever recommend anything else
again besides Rome
because I've seen a lot of places and I
I say okay Paris was beautiful too
and and and we have a lot of beautiful
places
in Europe but Rome it's it's no nothing
is a [\h__\h] match to Rome
Rome is next level especially because
you have all these things so closely
knit in one city close to another there
are many many others like Greece for
example as well have uh cool [\h__\h] like
this too but in Greece the problem is
it's so spread apart right and on
different Islands as well and so on but
in Rome or in Italy especially in Rome
you have it all right there
if you walk five meters not even five
meters you don't even have to walk you
look around turn around and 360 degrees
you see look
I can't
and I got to this point
when I saw
possibly it was when I saw this
and it was only the side view
it was only the side view
this was only the [\h__\h] side view in
the middle of the traffic
[Music]
hi hi
I don't know what to say
i i i
this was
[Music]
in reality it looks actually much
smaller on this photo but it was insane
reality
there it is huge it is [\h__\h] huge yeah
and it has like a big fountain on the
side on the sides yeah and in front of
it there's a big like big big big road
where oh yeah everyone drives around
every [\h__\h] bus goes through there
every time we were on a bus ride we
passed by this big thing again and again
just look it you can go inside but I we
didn't because we were like looking
desperately for a cafe
um so eat something and we were freezing
like I was freezing like [\h__\h] my feet
felt like ice cubes
like literally ice blocks I felt like
they were surrounded by ice blocks and I
was just walking with my feet caught in
ice blocks but
it's
insane
wow
wow what the [\h__\h]
oh oh and this looks like Fogo Romano
but when you walk we were basically we
basically circled this building I just
showed you
um but when you walk around it then you
walk past this which again looks like
fojo Romana but it's not it's just a
random random ancient ruins in the
Center guys how can I how can I not
recommend wrong to you
just like everyone
I'm having like a [\h__\h] mind break
mental breakdown openness stuff
I can never recommend Austria again and
they have the
SE girls so cute somebody wrote their ad
there let's not advertise them
well that's a good picture yo
look at those knees look at their knees
at their knees
oh
The Burbs
[Music]
so good
oh man
yeah Rome is next level like it's a
different world like it felt like I was
in a different century
I was like feeling like I was 2 000
years in a bag almost fell through the
brims of history and every nooks and
cranny yeah willing to pay the visit you
have to oh
you [\h__\h] have to yes okay so after
this
um we escaped to a really [\h__\h]
expensive restaurant at the corner of
the street uh with a view to the big
white building that I showed you I
forgot the name even though it's a
really important building
um
I forgot but yeah you saw it and uh
Romans know what I'm talking about
and yeah so we escaped and I just wanted
to you know even though it was already
so close to dinner because our dinner
was reserved my mom was here for dinner
at 6 00 PM
but it was like 4 P.M or so and we were
starving so we needed something small so
I really wanted to eat
I really wanted to eat it because I love
it you know it's basically just toasted
baguette
why is it like this yeah and with some
tomatoes and olive oil and some
yummy yummy
mozzarella kind of cheese but Buffalo
and then I also ordered uh
this on the right side is yes Tomatoes
but also underneath
um it was buata because I also really
wanted some burrata I love
I love bugatta
yes yes so we ate this together and it
already
it wasn't saying this this one [\h__\h]
starter one [\h__\h] starter would cost
like 22 dollars or so
as much as like a main course normally
I cannot explain we my mom got a glass
of apple Spritz and I got an iced tea
and this we ate these two plates
together and I paid
60 [\h__\h] dollars
or so
that was the most expensive place we
went to
but one thing that was cool that I did
not take a picture of but I saw in a lot
like basically every restaurant in Rome
had
um
uh like outside sitting area and you
know because it was cold they put up
these flaming
things right next to the table I mean
the flame is contained into something
but the heaters they all have these like
flaming heaters like a big flame like
the Emoji
and it was so cool I really like that
because
um you know
in like compared to normal heaters this
one really gives off like an open flame
kind of atmosphere
honestly the problem was though that it
only heated the left side of my body and
the right side of my body was freezing
because it was only on the left side
um
[Music]
so that was a problem that they did not
consider I guess
um
yeah I was I was like
um I have to say it's really sad that it
rained so much the first day because
we were suffering and that kind of also
brought down my mood at times a little
bit I tried to I tried my best but I was
in pain I was in pain my mom was in pain
we were both in pain and I was freezing
my mom doesn't freeze so easily but I
definitely didn't
it was tough but I wanted to look at as
many things as possible
[Music]
um
and I wanted it to be worth the the
visit and worth the money so I wanted to
make the most out of it
um
anyway after this we pretty much
immediately
went into I grabbed I grabbed the tax
day and we went to traced
and is
like Rome is divided by one River
and all of these sites were on the on
the right side of the river East Side I
guess and we went to the the other side
with the
um with the taxi because
um my mom actually for both nights chose
a restaurant uh in that area because
they have a lot of nice cool restaurants
over there the bridge over the tea Bell
yeah yeah there's many bridges that go
over it but yeah we went to the other
side of that
um
so my mom chose a really nice restaurant
I really liked this one
it was kind of narrow
um in like terms of size but it was
comfy and we went all we got a table all
the way in the back and it was not
crowded at all because we had such an
early reservation and so it was really
calm and quiet and cozy
um I think maybe maybe this picture
captures the
style and atmosphere
relatively well
so this was the view from the back where
we were all the way to the front
see it's kind of cozy and drastically
rustical look with lights hanging and
and some weird like wool balls hanging
in the ceiling as decoration
yeah yeah I think it looked better in
reality than this photo it's hard to
capture though than the atmosphere of it
[Music]
um but they were really nice the
waitress was really really nice looks
kind of cramped yeah this path was kind
of cramped but in the back where we were
it was uh you know a lot of space
um that was good that we went to the
back
yeah and then
[Music]
so this picture maybe that
looks good
[Music]
foreign
walls with some wooden
um cover and then the menu is
oh we actually ordered that one
huh
cute
cute and then my mom I didn't take a
photo of the starter but that was the
start of the poem it was like
green tomato slices
uh fried
like you know like onion rings yeah
um with some uh Tata sauce that's really
good but when they when they arrived
they look like
um fried apple rings like a popular
um dessert from Austria and looked like
that to me so I was like oh Mommy
I need so we shared that it was really
good I
have not really been that Italian but uh
yeah it was really good
and then my mommy uh got this fancy
thing
she got octopus
to put with uh the green stuff and some
really yummy mashed potatoes
she really enjoyed that one
aesthetically like I feel like it looks
so cool but you know I I went for a safe
choice but the waitress says it's a
really good choice because it was a one
of the daily specials
um they had
and uh oxtail uh Ragu
with a
homemade thick pasta noodles they had
their own name but I don't know what to
call them but so it's basically like a
really strong Bolognese I could imagine
like describe it like that
the meat of the oxtail as grinded minced
meat
um it was very very ah it was so yummy
it's really rich in flavor I loved this
one
portion looks small no it was really big
especially because the the noodles were
really thick you you cannot really tell
from this photo but it was a big portion
don't worry it was very big
okay that was our dinner and then after
that you know we went back with a bus
actually
um
uh which was fun that's where we started
to realize okay the number one traveling
uh Transportation method in Rome is
buses
it's a deep plate yeah exactly
yeah uh so from then on we only went
with bus
um also because we were [\h__\h] sick and
tired of the rain yeah bus was fun and
then basically next day we got breakfast
and then we went straight dot two
two drum roll
[Music]
does this look familiar to you
Fontana
I think what's it called
baby
very famous big ass fountain with
turquoise looking water down there and
uh a big big statues of horses
being
fought by manly men
trying to be controlled or not trying to
resist to be controlled by the manly men
and inside I guess it's probably being
used as like a official
Country official office space or
whatever no did not throw a coin I don't
think anyone really does that here
because the water was mostly without
coins and people were besides you know
instead of throwing coins they were
focused on taking Instagram worthy
influencer pictures
it was funny too like me and my mom we
were just sitting there because there's
some some rails to sit on in front of it
and I was like looking at them
you know some some influencers like
posing really like fashionable in front
of it with her legs crossed and like
her her upper body really like put in
nice position
[Laughter]
yeah and I did not do this I was just
enjoying the view it was really sunny
this is the second day and it was really
sunny we had good weather it was really
pretty it was good weather so we were
very motivated and happy
hmm
what similar photos I'm not on this
photo I'm behind where I'm not in front
of it
but it was really crowded it was really
crowded indeed
but it was nice I enjoyed looking at
this for a while and then I went
to get some juice
even though normally I don't eat ice
cream in the winter very often but it
was sunny and there were a [\h__\h] ton of
gelato places around here
and that looks so good I cannot show you
a picture of the gelato but I had
um
what did I get I got amarena with cocoa
I love amarena ice cream
and on top of it I had like
not mango
something that's also kind of orange I
forgot
well it was so good and I asked my mom
if she wants one too but she said no and
then
I was like are you sure and she said
yeah I'm sure I don't wanna I don't want
ice cream I don't like ice cream I don't
want the ice cream I don't want ice
cream I asked her so often
and she just said no no no no no and
then I give her a taste of my ice cream
and then five minutes later when we
walked back to this thing to look at it
while I was eating my ice cream he was
like okay can I get an ice cream after
all and I'm like
gotcha
so
I I
bought an ice cream
[Laughter]
I think I got a little taste it seemed
to be like milk flavor but specifically
that kind of milk flavor that you have
inside the Kinder chocolate oh
amazing I made Joyce
blah blah blah blah blah
um
so good so we were enjoying ice cream in
the sunny weather in front of a very
touristic fountain that looked really
nice
king of buses by the way because on this
day we were like using bus
transportation all the time I saw
Hood look at it
[Music]
it's so adorable but why is it so tiny
it's so small
[Music]
so small but we didn't get into one of
those we went into normal buses
never seen those now there are a couple
of them I saw a couple of them around
so cute I wanted to go inside they were
even not even that crowded for being so
small I guess they're like unpopular
lines that just exist because I guess
there's a need for it but not that big
of a need so they're small
oh
[Music]
so cute minibus baby bubble bubble
bubble bubble Buzz
bubble bubbles
cute
okay what is this
ah okay our next goal after taking a bus
was another big amazing thing something
called Uh there's something something a
castle of Michelangelo or something like
that
so when we arrived we we kind of uh got
off a station that was like five minutes
walk or so away from it and we had to
cross a bridge that was also like
directly connected to it and
Michelangelo Bridge or something like
that
this was The View
absolutely beautiful
[Music]
it's so cool so pretty the thing I used
to go back the round thing is the thing
that we were going for
oh
[Music]
let me look at it first before I show it
to you guys
oh yeah that's I think that's safe to
show
[Music]
sorry so loud I'm muting it so this is
the little bit of a panorama brought to
you by okay one one this is the left
side with a big famous bridge on the
left side
um but we didn't walk over that
it looks you see here this is this thing
and this is oh actually
trees are drowning in water this was
because I told you there was a [\h__\h] ton
of rain the day before
so the water was higher than usual but
yeah this is the thing
huh
and then we walked towards it
[Music]
uh-huh
this was when we were on the bridge
look at that blue sky
girl blue sky
so
this is it
this is this
and Michelangelo or something something
with the angel or Michelangelo or
something like that I don't remember all
the names of the things that we looked
at I'm so sorry but yeah you see uh the
whole Bridge was like
um on the side decorated with some cool
angel statues as you see they all have
wings
yeah and they also had uh names and
explanations I think of what they wear
underneath and then you know you see
this big building I think inside is a
museum we did not go inside because it's
not free and we just started the day and
I guess we were not in the mood
uh
but maybe one
will go inside so yeah I'm leaving
myself some reasons to go back someday
because there's a lot of things that I
did not enter this time
um but at the very top you see there's
some people there as well and at the
very top you have this Michelangelo
angel or whatever
really cool it's a really round building
yeah it stands out so much because it's
so round like the Colosseum and this
thing them being so round makes it stand
out so much it's gonna look cool I don't
know how to how to explain my feelings
towards these things but they're so cool
[Laughter]
sophisticated words
I know Michelangelo is No Angel but he
made some kind of angel statue
Pokemons
but I'm not that deep into art so I
don't know [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[Music]
some Angel yeah please please tilt your
head because I'm sick of like changing
this all the time everybody tilt your
head you give your chickens you can do
it you have a flexible neck
angel
here's another one
[Music]
wow they were so big
wow now she was missing or he she he was
missing some fingers you see they broke
off now it looks like she's giving you
she's flipping you off
the middle finger is straight up into
the air
um
I feel I was a little bit rude but okay
and then we have this one also very cool
really curly hair
really pretty nice wings
and then
I don't know why but
I have a cute dog
that is that
that's all not my shadow
and so not my mom's Channel
but it's a cute fluffy dog but it had
lots of hair
oh it looked back to me
look at this
it was like like it was like a walking
um cleaning mop
and from here if it were if you've been
to Rome before you know that if you walk
here if you walk to the left side from
there where we just were you go to
Vatican City so we were aiming for that
um but before that
[Music]
here's a burp
[Laughter]
between the Michelangelo Castle thingy
and Vatican City no
that's a burp it's not a statue it's a
real one
yeah burnt cute very cute burp I took a
really good picture of my mom and the
bird as well but I will not show you
that one
here's a another view a kind of of the
side
you can see like maybe you can see it
the people peeking through through the
like Windows at the top almost like kind
of the middle of the top level you know
you know so one day I want to go inside
and look for that it's
thick building
so cool also the brakes off a lot of
these buildings were really really like
small tiny thin bricks I find that's
really interesting because it gives a
nice look
and then that means also they've used
some bigger ones but you know most of
the the this lower lower main wall they
use like these fin bricks
[Music]
ah but it's so cool
and oh I took a close-up with my zoom of
the big blue statue on top I has a sword
but only the the blade of the sword
seems to be a different material maybe
it broke off at some point
foreign
it looks so brown but it doesn't look
like wood I don't know
that was my 10 times Zoom I'll fight him
you want to fight him why are we finding
finding him
I don't need to find him
and then we looked over
and uh uh what we would see
from
not so far
was the border to Vatican City if you
don't know what that is it's
um officially not part of Italy but it's
in the middle of Rome not in the middle
it's on the side of Rome no I'm gonna
sell the middle that's in Rome but it's
not Italy it's uh you know where the
pope lives the pope and his people
they chill in there there's um 800
people who live in Vatican City but I
guess they also they all kind of just
those 800 people are not normal
residents I'm pretty sure about that
and it's very small if you look it up in
on Google Maps you see it's really small
um yeah it's like its own country right
yeah kind of like that but
um
so there's no like passport control or
anything but officially like you know
it's a different place Once you walk
over the line there's no real line
though uh usually you can just walk in
there and still feels like you're in
Rome basically you yeah
um so uh
that was a lot of people and we also did
not go inside this one but I looked at
it from outside for a while
I observed it for a while and oh
there's this this big
big ass Square
and people go like to the very front and
line up to go inside there's like
something something inside probably also
like something like a museum as well
and like a church and stuff yeah
obviously yeah yeah and I liked the
pillars so I wanted to walk through some
of the pillars and then we just ended up
sitting down somewhere but
um
let me let me show you the pillars
because you know we like some pillars
here
yeah I'll size this one down for you
otherwise a little lamp is cool
so this is like the side path
look oh big
big pillows
wow so we walked through there and then
we sat down kind of on the low-key
pavement
and if you I wanna I wanted to look a
little bit at the details so oh oh oh oh
oh I guess that's a video oopsie
so better yo
what the [\h__\h]
that's a video
you mean that's a video
do I have a picture
I mean I guess the video is okay too let
me see
[Music]
ah
do you hear this
do you hear anything by the way
no okay
[Music]
okay that's good I'll mute it here we go
so uh from the start here look there's
some statues all over decorated all
what's up
one for each pillar
don't know who those people are though
there's some weird screens are in the
fountain and the verb and many statues
and hola well well ceiling well cool
lots of people
wow what's a pavement wow people oh
curious boobs crane tree Christmas tree
oh lots of lots of those birds yes
that was really cute uh here this one
it was a white kind of pigeon like a
look like a a a snow Leo part pigeon
just wanted to show you that and then I
have another funny video
[Applause]
it's but basically there were mostly
there were pigeons here
um
but sometimes you know some people were
feeding the pigeons yeah and so a lot of
pigeons were around us but then
sometimes seagulls would fly in uh and
they would like
three times the size of those pigeons
basically and they would try to get some
of the bread which didn't even even so
easy for them because the pigeons were
like usually like
five to ten pigeons in one place and
then the seagulls were also all over
always only solo and so I caught this
pigeon
just right after it stole some bread at
this pigeon this seagull just right
after it stole some bread from the
pigeons
successfully
look at that again
wait oh sorry I think that had some loud
sound Maybe
[Music]
and then
it flies off and I follow I follow oh
I'm still kind of following it wow
wow legendary
[Music]
oh did you hear my love
don't listen it was funny though
everyone was laughing around us
oh
okay Escape
so no pigeons can catch me
blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah
successfully escaped
not too low
[Music]
you had when it stole the food from the
pigeons
after
um updating my social media on the day
before
some Italians
answered my tweet and one I think Roman
person
told me to eat this one thing that is
basically Roman Street food and said eat
souply please eat souply and I looked it
up and it was actually something that
looks delicious and easy to eat for me
so I told my mommy that for lunch we're
gonna have a super snack
souply yeah Roman Street food I thought
we have to eat that you know
so
right next to
um like really close to this Vatican
City
we found or I found a pretty well rated
uh Roman Street food place and it had so
please
and one of them uh you know they don't
only have it in Rome but the Roman
typical version I've heard is the one
with tomato
and mozzarella inside so this is
basically rice inside
with you know you know for in this case
for example tomato and mozzarella cheese
and tomato sauce and mozzarella cheese
rice and uncovered fried in this
breading
there was another choice of flavor which
was carbonara so I got two of each and
we shared those and those were
incredibly filling on its own like
really
we were actually struggling eating all
of it
they're really small they're like you
can hold them in the palm of your hand
and we both ate two but they were so
filling
but they were really good
I like them I think it's a good good uh
choice you know if you in Rome and you
want to try some Roman Street Food go
eat
there's a lot of supply places
um
really yummy so after that we felt a bit
stronger but it was still so early
you know at this point we saw the the uh
the Fontana de Trevi we went to Vatican
City and the Michelangelo place
and we went to have this stuff and at
this point it was only 1pm
we did all of that in and breakfast
in three hours
so at this point I was like
Mommy
what are we gonna do because
this was all that mommy planned for this
day these three things the Fontana de
Trevi the Vatican City and the
Michelangelo place to look at it only
from outside
and it was 1pm and I'm like Mommy what
are we gonna do until our dinner at 7 pm
[Laughter]
so I looked through Google Maps to
whatever looked interesting to me
we got into a bus and the next place we
went to
was
[Music]
the famous Pantheon
again you see holes do you see the holes
do you see the [\h__\h] holes
here as well
look at those tiny holes like okay there
was like bronze or whatever in there but
what like I can't even imagine because
the holes are not even like
systematically placed they're just
randomly all over
so I wonder how it looked like before
but the cool thing about the pantheon
are not only the pillars because I'm a
lover I'm a sucker for pillars it's also
that you can go in for free surprisingly
one of the few things that you can enter
for free oh thanks for
[Music]
the most like you got shot at clay
yeah so you can go inside for free and
it's pretty big and um there's also
audio guides in there but we didn't use
those
um
let me show you
[Music]
did I not take a video inside I guess I
did not
what did I
I did
okay
um
okay so this is the round view of inside
wow
it's very crowded of course
[Music]
there's like statues all there oh and
the ceiling is incredible
me and my mom were like obviously
there's no way it's open up there right
there must be a window there but no it's
constantly open and people people taking
selfies and [\h__\h] oh yeah well
but now it's open that's
what we were lucky that we didn't go the
day before when it was [\h__\h] raining
all day
because then but there's actually a
draining mechanism there's some holes on
the ground that you don't really see
unless you look for them but there's
there are holes on the ground some here
and there
um
glass would have been very expensive no
but I imagine that maybe you know later
on they would like added some kind of
kind of closing mechanism in modern
times a glass or something that closes
when it's raining or on something oh
yeah
so let's look at it again
actually this place
houses
the graves
if I don't remember incorrectly it
houses the graves of the two and only
Kings
of Italia right right Italian friends
as well as I think like maybe one of one
or two of the wives probably I don't
know but uh yeah the statues of those
kings are there too
and I think I took like a peak jaw
yeah here there it is
this was one of the grapes
of and this was Umberto
Umberto the first from the king of Italy
a really fancy uh grave with like a
crown statue thing on top that's on the
real crown the pillow never I would say
that's just like a statue kind of thing
um
wow
yeah so oh there were things like this
all around inside
the pantheon and then in the very front
we actually sat down for a while
uh and just
stared at this
Altar and looked at it
it was so big
and the ceiling and everything was
really fascinating the marble floors
everything
really fascinating
hmm
yes
yeah so we just chilled a little while
in there and whereas some more like
statues I don't know if you want to see
them if yes then turn your head right
now
oh I did it too and it cracked very nice
yeah
[Music]
okay
that was a cool thing to see
and after that we I think we walked
yeah uh close close to the pantheon
there was a square that I forgot what it
was called
um but I had video let me check
huh
let me check
yes maybe you guys can tell me what it
was called
some of you guys me
no some kind of Piazza
yes it is
foreign
[Music]
Square I'll show you again with this
another fountain with muscular manly man
doing some cool poses like some tropical
tree also part of that and a big pillar
with oh I saw these
want to have that too I saw these
pillars in a couple of places and they
had uh hieroglyphs I think
engraved in them which was interesting
but this is just a chill place where
there's some people trying to sell you
[\h__\h] like children's toys out of all
things and bracelets and whatever
um but
um one thing that
uh I actually was interested in was
there was um there was some art
some people
were selling oh they were brought up
from Egypt oh that's why cool
it was quite surprised to see
hieroglyphs um but yeah then what was I
saying oh yeah I saw some people you
know were doing portraits live portraits
but also always just selling art that
they did before like some old Italian
men
uh yeah and I was like looking at it and
thinking maybe I should buy some because
I want some art for my apartment that's
like actually drawn and not printed on
so I bought a two actually
quite expensive but
it was pretty good I did not take a
picture maybe I'll take a picture on
like once I put it into a frame
but yeah
two cool hand drawn pictures from an
Italian artist
just trying to get by
yeah
oh oh if you walk uh outside like if you
try to leave this Piazza then on the
side there is another like little
fountain
and I had to photograph this because the
statue on this fountain
this dude
he was oh dear oh dear well don't look
at that but he was trying to kill
[Music]
and Alex
out of the person's bottom can I show
this
art right was the water flowing into the
fountain
this looked really funny to me
I wonder what the story behind this is
I guess this is him just hunting food
for the for the daily Fish Market oh
also there were ladies if you look at
the back this lady has like a little
hairy tail on her butt and they were on
top of um horses with fish tails
so
that was interesting
yeah that girl on the left she has a
tail and they were all like sitting on
horses with fishtails
hmm
well
yeah is this okay to show YouTube
I did not even
not even realized there was a peepee on
there I thought I was focusing on the
octopus I didn't realize until now
is that Poseidon
it is 3 ton really
shut up
guys
anyway from there on uh it was
you know what we we got to get a cafe a
coffee my mom got a coffee I got a hot
chocolate and it was it was
3 P.M
so
we still had so much time it's like
Mommy where should we go next we have so
much time and then uh
[Music]
I was just scouting through Google Maps
again
to look what looked interesting to me
and then one thing
that I thought might be interesting
was a hill
in home that had some cool stuff up
there and I forgot what the hell was
called but it was so worth going there
um a hill but it had also Medici
something something and
[Music]
blah blah
and castle
yeah stuff like that
um
no it's not the Palatine Hill
available
[Music]
area around it on top of the hill so we
we went there
and uh basically in front of it on the
bottom there's a big Square
in the white talk like this
there's a big Square
everybody tilt your heads
so this is layers [\h__\h] layers again I
love layers
um
this is on the bottom
and then you see this is a fountain
again on that side and and then there's
like some layers and then on the top you
see the viewing platform up there yeah
cool cool cool but you can't go like
straight up there directly you kind of
have to log like in slopes like left and
right around and then you finally reach
up there so that was the goal getting up
there
foreign
and there was another one of those
hieroglyphs
um
uh pillars
look do you see the hieroglyphs if you
have a big screen in high quality I
think you will see it
[Music]
so cool to see that here and you see
slowly the sun was setting but it was
still only uh
3 3 50 P.M
so from there we walked up and I made
sure with my mom that she's okay with
growing up because it was going to be a
challenge
but it was also going to be so worth it
and uh the first picture I just showed
you before the pillar
and I we actually got to look at the
back of it and I thought it looked
really cool
the only thing that's kind of ruining it
is the iPhone advertisement so let me
cut that
there we go that's better
like normally you don't really get like
a good look of the backs of like statues
like that sculptures but I thought it
looked really cool like the The Backs
were really detailed as well
the drapes of the the clothes the folds
were so soft looking
and the spines wow humans spawns
you saved the with the pillow in the
background I felt like I was really
getting so artistic as a photographer
during this trip like next level [\h__\h]
man
yeah layers Again by the way the sun
peeking through and the sunset low-key
starting
[Music]
the song
yeah and then we walked up and up and up
and up and up and up and eventually
[Music]
we made it
here this is a low top on the left side
you see someone making music that dude
was making some really good music he was
like
um playing all kinds of instruments at
the same time
like he would play like um machine and
the piano and saying he had a good
singing voice and if you go all the way
to the front then there is the uh
viewing platform that we saw from the
bottom what is that dude doing the one
in the card yeah they were you see
there's a couple of them in the cards
they were like 20 20 I swear grown ass
dudes like around 20 19 years old uh in
[\h__\h] cards [\h__\h] around there
and then I don't know I don't speak
Italian so we didn't really understand
what was going on but all the cards all
these dudes they gathered around the guy
who was making music
and uh there was this one dude the like
an older don't who seemed to belong to
the card people probably like like
renting them the cards and he was
starting to discuss with the musician
what seemed like a discussion kind of
like yo uh stop playing music get out of
the way so that my card people can drive
around because they were talking and
talking and talking and the instrument
guy he kept on it seemed like he kept on
saying like no no no like I'm gonna do
my thing here you can't tell me to go
away
and uh the cards the dudes and the cards
they were like literally camping parking
right around him interrupting him and
bothering him so I'm like what the [\h__\h]
is your problem this place is huge like
why does he have to go anywhere maybe
that was not what they talked about but
that's the only thing that really made
sense to us because they were waiting
there waiting and waiting and waiting
and had quite a loud argument now it was
weird anyway I tried to get a good view
in the at the viewing platform was
really crowded
and
but
this is what I got
ah I think the time when we went there
was perfect because the sun was setting
and there was this big Panorama View
with some trees in the front that gives
you some layers
and wow
wow and this was uh not even the only
good view if we walked somewhere else
later on uh for even more Scenic
beautiful views but I think that was so
worth it the trouble of getting up here
um
the view is not the only thing that they
offer there let me see this one
foreign
[Music]
oh yes
I think I captured
this was right before the dude
um stopped him from from playing music
wait a second
uh otherwise it uh here
okay I don't hear the sound but I think
you hear it and it's fine but I sure
it's just a little
you do you hear him
he was playing the doodle machine then
puts it down and play and play other
thingy again
it was really cool
no there's those [\h__\h] teenage adults
[Music]
yeah I'm trying to walk over there to
get like a good shot
[Music]
oh but it's so crowded but look
hey cute girl oh well
yes so that's kind of a view
oh [\h__\h] what was he playing will I get a
copyright strike
I don't know I didn't hear what was he
playing
it was something you knew
yeah it was a nice PGM for a scenic view
I really thought so too so when he
stopped playing we were kind of sad
um
but it was so melodic really nice
anyway
back to Italy bgm
so I took some more photos of the view
that were
really cool to me
look at this
I'm such a photograph like oh my God
look at those layers
look at the Orange and the sky
[Music]
and then I took this one let me turn it
by you
I think this one's one's a wool
because for sure you see it how the
pillow
is so straight just like that road with
the traffic on the ground is also so
straight
I am such a photographer
[Music]
yes
have a good photo sense thank you I
agree
I was really feeling it
[Laughter]
yeah
yes I'm good at thank you I'm having fun
with my phone uh some for some reason
you know this one was so orange but then
the photo that comes after that
this is not so old Ranger I guess yeah
that's the left side
I kind of liked the left side because on
the very left you see on the very very
very left you see the the big thing yeah
the the angels on the top you know
um the horses
but it was so far away from the main
view with the sun setting that here it
didn't look so good
um the other picture was right where the
sun was setting and this is on the very
left side so the the sky doesn't look
that special here
um even though the buildings would look
cool
interesting happened we walked around
the park area
[Music]
um
yeah it shows how big the building is
that's right we walked around the park
area and
um
something
interesting happened that was kind of
disturbing but also added to the Italian
experience I would say
thank you thank you that's it so there
was you know because of the rain I guess
there was a cool photo spot I think
that's why they were all graveling
around it there was another like kind of
viewing platform with a nice view
and there was a
puddle of water that I noticed made for
a really good photo actually because of
the reflection but anyway so when we
arrived there uh you know a lot of
people were standing there trying to
take pictures
um and there was like one dude
trying to take a picture with his
girlfriend I guess uh
right at the fence and I I own we only
arrived when they started fighting so I
don't quite understand what was going on
but the dude starts yelling in Italian
really loudly
um he was like holding his girlfriend
um you know like lifting her up with his
arms crossed around her butt can you
imagine
uh and he was like I guess why they was
screaming angrily at another man he was
trying not to drop her in the middle of
the puddle I guess that was funny so he
was like kind of like tip-topping Towing
around the puddle uh dropping off his
girlfriend going back to the dude and
like yelling at him and several times
throwing his arms around him actually
smacking him with his fists several
times while the other dude was like with
I a little bit of a cheeky smile saying
stuff like in Italian like it's okay
chill dude kind of stuff like that I
imagine like trying to call him down not
punching back at all but the other guy
would just not let loose and while this
was happening at the same time there was
like why they were fighting so loudly I
was like really worried and kind of
scared like right next to them in front
of the puddle was a musician playing and
singing some really beautiful music
he thought it was a really romantic
place there with so many couples like
[\h__\h] that they just
they're just fighting this huge fight
making a huge fuss in drama and this
dude was like trying to like smack him
was actually smaller uh than the tall
guy who was just chilling so I imagine
like he was maybe sneaking into the
picture or something like that and and
the dude just did not like that at all
it was so much like oh [\h__\h] you you
little [\h__\h] smack smack smack what the
[\h__\h] are you doing that and he's just
like it's okay it's okay chill not even
not stop and this guy who was making
music just did not stop making music and
all the other people there were just
standing there staring at the situation
like what is going on
unfortunately I did not take a video of
that because I was too focused on taking
some cool pictures but
um
so to give you a little bit of a um an
image
of how this looked I I I did not have
like you know
someone to take this perfect beautiful
picture of me but I was like yo yo yo
mommy wait now I understand why
everyone's taking a picture here it's
because of this
look
let me let me get the princess because
[Music]
of this
because of this reflection that looks so
cool I made some better pictures but you
see too much of their faces so I'm just
gonna leave it at that yeah but they
still he doesn't understand
look at this camera oh I mean that looks
cool to what he's taking but he does not
have the [\h__\h] puddle reflection that
looks so good because of all the rain it
looks like they're standing
even capturing that with a [\h__\h] idiot
he doesn't want to know what he's doing
at all that was not the couple by the
way they came right after the fight
started taking pictures so it was not
dumb but
look at all the potential I took a
really good one actually you know a lot
I'll show you because there's the the
light
let me let me throw it into Photoshop
actually
because I want to flex this was just I
took this in one second
and I think
that's [\h__\h] marvelous
uh wait a second
and the gaussian blur
[Music]
Ry
okay
okay perfect
um
I should send this to the couple because
it's such a good couple photos so
romantic you don't always have to see it
faces perfectly because because
this this is it man this this is all you
need on it
[Music]
look
even like partially on this like kind of
like slightly on the side
because I guess I was just standing
there you could also move it a little
bit more to the middle sure but look at
that
romantic that reflection on the ground
so clean and so clear
[Music]
um
in the sunset Mamma Mia by the way
I did hear an Italian person saying Mama
Mamma Mia pretty loudly at some point
which at that point I felt
it was okay to say mama B I didn't
I did it at all
don't use it I hold my health back
[Music]
but this
is so proud
I felt like such a photographer then we
walked on around because this area is
pretty big we walked by a lot of like
[Music]
head
that statues statues like literally just
Stone heads
on like hundreds of stone heads just the
heads not the busts just the heads
but I guess maybe a little bit of the
bust but mostly just heads all over
the park on on like podests scattered
all over
uh
there was even one what was it called
I was even on the funny name
but I forgot damn it
some noodle name some name that sounded
exactly like the noodle with the same
almost the same name
[Music]
yes pedestals
yeah yeah so that was actually kind of
spooky because it was getting dark and
we were walking through kind of like
almost a forest and there were so many
hits and some of the heads had like
because of the rain and the dirt I guess
they had like
um
it looked like you know the top
part of the head was like darker and the
the remains of like
um moisture uh was visible on the heads
in the form of like like drips you know
like dripping from the top downwards
their heads and if it was red it would
look look so spooky because it looked
like blood dripping down their heads
but anyway that's just me feeling spooky
um
and then we met we went to this this
place
that
that I found on Google that was also in
the park which was another one of these
things but I was just at this point I
did not care for what was in the back I
cared so much more for these ducks and
geese and everything
I uploaded a video on my Twitter that
you may have seen because
so many of them and I looked at them for
ages and mommy was like let's go Kiwa
and I'm like no
with a look at the fluffy parts of the
cute box and the watch you watching
watch kind of movement
and they were like
that was so cute
but also there were like some couples uh
in the boat
um driving around the the water that was
cool too if you if you want to do that
but I was more interested in the Ducks
and there were some people feeding them
um the geese and the Ducks
so I was watching that and we're so cute
some of them you know here like your
names
oh cute
none here but
very cute fluffy butt
um
yes
[Music]
okay and then after that
we felt like going down again down the
hill and towards maybe our restaurant
thinking that maybe maybe we've seen
enough
we're kind of tired from walking so much
even though we took the bus quite a lot
but let me tell you we were still so
much too early
at this point it was
super
so we walked very slowly
and at the bottom when we walked down I
saw this this was really cool
[Music]
it was already pretty dark so the light
is not good anymore
but this looks so cool
uh the leaves in the water
made looks
looks green stuff growing all around it
the fountain thingy where the the water
was just like flowing down
dripping making the dripping sound it
looks so cool it was really wide and big
right like on the street by the way on a
big Street
um
okay so then we made our way with a bus
to trusted
I don't know
um and walked around and we arrived like
one hour early
at the restaurant that we were supposed
to have dinner at
in the hopes that they you know later
might be a problem
because later well
they might be more busy but before will
be early so
wouldn't they maybe let us in
you know
because they're not busy but then we
were there and there was a guy working
there putting everything in place and we
asked if we can go in and he said no
we're opening at City
which is seven which was exactly when
our reservation was at so we could not
get earlier in even a minute
but I was freezing and freezing
so we walked around the area trying to
check out some shops but I was
surprising and at some point we just sat
down in a nice
um restaurant that had
um this View
uh actually a big big a big Square
um in front of I don't know what this
building is but it was lit up nicely
and yeah it was a nice view when we just
drank like I drank an
anti-alcoholic cocktail and my mom drank
some kind of cocktail
but yeah it was this big Square
and I had a I had a I had a blanket on
my on my feet hoping to warm up
yeah
anti-alcoholic yeah yeah no alcohol a
mocktail
why are you not why are you lulling
oh no no okay
don't make such a big bail out of it
all right then finally at some point
after suffering like I was we were we
were trying to kill time so much like we
were so desperate I was like Mommy I'm
so cold I need to get into one building
I can't wait outside any longer so we
went into a pharmacy I made up a reason
to get into a pharmacy to buy something
I bought some like um warming uh
shoulder pad thingies to use in the
night time because I was having a lot of
shoulder pain as well
and just to be in a warm environment for
even a few minutes uh then we went into
a random ass store that sold like
blankets and decorations and [\h__\h] we
were acting as if we were interested
just to be in the warm
and I went into a vintage store that was
cool because I never go into winter
stores but I always kind of am
interested into them but I don't know
where the cool ones are
so yeah we kept on trying to find places
to enter and then finally finally we
made it it was set there it was 7 P.M so
we went back to the restaurant and we
were the only ones and it was really
quiet it was kind of awkward because I
felt like the waiters were looking at us
it was so quiet uh we started with uh
starter of uh carpacho beef carpacio
which had a really good marinade I
normally don't like eating um
uh yeah raw meat or fish or whatever
well it was pretty good had some baby
spinach on the bottom lots of cheese on
the top and we ate it with some bread
some baguette as well that was our
starter we shared that one and then you
know
I I wanted to order something more
interesting but I was too scared that I
didn't like it and then I could not
finish it I'm always scared of that so I
went for a really basic Choice I'm so
sorry I'm waiting for such a basic
choice
I went for a couple dollars
[Music]
Original Italian proper carbonara
because I always make carbonara with
cream and normally you're supposed to
eat it you may you're supposed to make
it only with the egg yolk right yeah
um I have to say though the pasta and I
ate on the day before was better this
one was it was good but it was getting
very Bland and boring after a while
so I regretted choosing this pasta to be
honest I love carbonara though but it
wasn't bad but it's just after a few
bites it got so Bland it was also a huge
portion it looks small maybe because
it's like like a mountain here
but it was actually so much I could like
really not finish it but I tried my best
even my mom was like how I don't know
how you're gonna finish this
it only looks a little bit small but it
really wasn't
maybe this way you can see it a bit
better
I mean it looks small I know but it was
really a lot and those were again really
fake noodles
but something interesting
oh don't look at her hand
this one has no hand
and it's turned around but it's some
kind of fish I see Barb see brass or
something like that with some potatoes
uh fin thin roasted
potatoes underneath
and cherry tomatoes around it and stuff
and some green stuff and all that she
said was really good but she also agreed
that the restaurant before that the
night before was better
I
stealing a lot of cherry tomatoes from
her because the taste of my carbonara
was so boring after a while I needed
something fresh in my mouth
yeah but anyway
um we ate that
and then we were tired so we went back
to our apartments with a bus
[Music]
all in all that was a much better day
than the first one because of the sunny
weather and we were quite happy
and we said
and then honestly on the following day
it was really only like going back home
um we woke up we got some quick
breakfast
we got into a train we got to the
airport we went inside the airport we
waited a [\h__\h] long time to board the
plane because they were freaking late
with starting the boarding my mom was
like really annoyed by it because she's
not used to it I was just like oh
whatever
it's the usual [\h__\h]
um but yeah it took ages until we could
take a seat also because I chose the
very last row in the back of the plane
so obviously we were the last ones to
take a [\h__\h] seat almost
um and then I have to make a confession
[Music]
in the plane
I was bored
and I had my switch with me
so I played some Pokemon
and don't worry I did not like Advance
crazily I just
um you know you just will not be able to
see the scene of when they
um announced the fact that you are on
the treasure hunt
that you can see in all the other
Pokemon streams anyway and then they say
uh you know then there's this thing
between the NPCs are telling you oh you
should go with me no you should go with
me and do my thing blah blah blah and
then they let you go so I just skipped
that basically you will not be able to
see that and then I just um uh explored
the whole area around the grass no the
bug the bug Arena
so at least we can skip the exploration
of that and then we can go straight into
the bug Arena
sounds good
I'm only watching you play Fruit but
really I did not give anything important
it's really it's just like it was a
scene where
this uh yeah the owner of the school was
like oh yes now you got the trash
at all and then yeah the other
characters were like oh you should go
with me and go check out the Arenas and
the other guy was like no you should go
with me and check out
the the big Pokemon that
um make trouble or so the mysterious
Pokemon and then the mysterious voice on
your phone says oh you should you should
go with me who would not really with me
but you should go do this thing that I
wanted to do
um
yeah it's nothing important please
forgive yeah I did not do anything
important important I I did not go into
the arena I did not even go into that
City I I only walked around it
yeah anyway
this is all the photos I have from my
Italian trip yeah
after that you know we arrived home at
my place and I said hi to my brother and
uh he uh reported some things to me that
what he has been up to for the past
months and we cooked or Mommy cooked for
us
uh and then everybody slept over at my
place one more night and then early in
the morning everybody left today
um
so that was it that was my trip around
it was so cool so cool
it was fascinating and as I said I don't
know how to ever recommend any other
place in Europe ever again over Rome
like Rome will always be now the number
one thing that I have to recommend in
Europe because that was the most
stunning
and mind-blowing
architecture and I call archeology that
I've seen in my whole life especially so
close together so compact so so much the
the amount of it like insane I've been
to a lot of places and if you want to go
sightseeing in Europe then I'm sorry but
Rome has to be on the number one of your
priorities
it has to be and if you go in the summer
I think I recommend
um going in
early summer when it's not too hot yet
because in the in the High season summer
then it will be probably really really
[\h__\h] exhausting with the heat
but if you go in the early summer it
might not be so bad yet and at the same
time you can go
to the ocean because Rome is so close to
the ocean that's why there's so many
seagulls
and you can go for a swim on one day and
you can go sightseeing on the other day
and then go for a swim again and then go
sightseeing again and so on
I think it's the perfect combination of
doing things for me it was freezing and
cold it's a bit suffering but still
amazing hmm
yay
grandma was the most beautiful city
yeah well I mean beautiful
yes beautiful too but more than
beautiful I would say just uh so
interesting so rich of history and
insane
like ruins of buildings and and also
intact buildings and all that
you have to say
today like for example when we would buy
bus tickets she would
um ask for them in Italian
and stuff like that so she
she a bit of Italian
as good as mine just kidding
but yeah it was um
[Music]
did you mention any desserts oh well the
gelato
but besides that after dinner we never
really had dessert yeah
because we were so I was so full I think
my Mommy too yeah
my throat hurts
let me take a fruit candy I'm back to
normal everything's back to normal my
throat hurts
my face hurts
I can't face my face when I love you
oh you don't you need to give me the
right mind I know but thank you
110 minutes
110 yeah two hours almost
all right screen
go bye bye
bye-bye bye-bye
bye-bye
okay and now we're gonna read some some
super chats because I need to catch up
and then I'll see you on Callie's
Channel but I'm gonna take a little
break in between but still I'm gonna
read some super chats now
and then tomorrow we're gonna play
Pokemon by the way and then next week
you can also expect I will play so much
Pokemon because I need to catch up
and I am like I can't [\h__\h] hold back
I need to play as much as possible
um also odena forgot to put it in her
schedule but we are doing
supposedly
uh classroom in Indonesian on her
channel on Sunday
closely
if we can squeeze it in
[Music]
tomorrow on my channel the thing is
premiering for the YouTube music weekend
but it's only 15 minutes so you know
that is at 7 30 PM I think
[Music]
um did you see the shirt I made
yeah I was um offered to be part of
YouTube music weekend this year
I only got 15 minutes which is so short
so like there's barely anything I can do
in 15 minutes and originally this was
the thing where I was stressing out so
much about getting my motion capture
suit to work
because I wanted it to be special so I
tried to make it work and do it in 3D
but when I was trying to set it up you
know there was a deadline and it was
just so scuffed and I couldn't get it to
work like I got it to work for the
karaoke
wasn't it 45 it might be 45 yeah
so yeah that's that
well I will go to an Isle meeting for a
moment and then we will go read some
super chatos okay
[Music]
um and just one thing I want to say at
the end
thank you guys for waiting for me
um the Italy trip was a lot of fun yeah
I hope my mom had fun too because this
was basically for her
um to enjoy herself and she was like
really fangirling so much about room so
I think she had a good time even though
it was exhausting
but uh yeah hope you guys enjoyed
looking at the photos as well
[Music]
thank you soon for waiting for me and
Italy room is [\h__\h] amazing everybody
needs to go yeah
you have to at least once in your
lifetime your mind will be blown
okay see you in a second
hold the line please hold the line
Hold the Line
just hold the line
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm
at the castle
[Music]
where am I
okay
[Music]
koala's back
oh God
[Laughter]
no no
I was good I'm good I'm okay I was just
a little bit surprised by the bottom
left
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
it's okay I'm okay
[Music]
uh anybody who can tell me where
where I need to start
[Music]
um
I left a button on the screen Oh you
mean that thing oh wow good eye
[Music]
the OG pretty karaoke okay okay
mm-hmm
huh start from debuty kids time to rise
would you recommend roam over Maldives
uh it depends on what you are like
looking for if you want to relax then
the Maldives if you want to see
something cool then go to Rome
it's a completely different kind of
vacation
do you want to do side thing or do you
want to have a beach vacation
actually I've been thinking a lot about
the Maldives these past days because
um
uh K-pop solo artist
uh called uh sunmi she I've been like
seeing on her Instagram that she's been
at the Maldives recently in a resort
that I know which one it is because I
was looking at it when we were looking
for
um places to stay at
and um
[Music]
she's been like posting videos and
photos and I'm like the first time I saw
the photo a photo it was not really like
100 clear that it was the Maldives but
like she didn't write it anywhere but I
knew immediately that was the Maldives
because that water that is Maldives
water
that is Maldives water
I I instantly knew
I love the Maldives I'm gonna go back
I want to go back yeah next time prefer
probably not in the monsoon season 6
uh yeah
but that place she stayed at even had a
slide like for their own Villa
that's so cool
[Music]
shut up that's not why
yeah I want to go to a lot of places
that's a problem I would have to be like
one of those travel influencers and be
on a vacation every freaking month
s
[Music]
I'm scrolling maybe I should just go for
hololizer this time because
it's everything is so far away
oh but will ah ah wait how do I get to
the unarchived once again
no there should be one but it's like um
like hidden I have to like go around it
[Music]
wait is that on
oh
[Music]
wait that's it
did I have the super chats off do you
need a link I mean y'all
because the one I'm looking at right now
has no super jump that's the right
broadcast
really
[Music]
if you want to give me a link you can
send it to me on Twitter
mm-hmm
[Music]
but be fast
be fast make it fast
[Music]
the spaghetti chats
oh there um
thank you
thank you so much
okay I got the super chatos
um
this one gonna read the projects from
here
[Music]
also I was watching the archive of
Amazon
um
Thanksgiving stream what the hell she
was like shooting stuff
I'm cooking
but the shooting stuff really got
because I'm like what
hahaha
so funny
so America
ah
yeah she had her own shooting range at
home
[Music]
um
what's the word
she hit the things pretty accurately
[Music]
yeah I should watch it it's archived
but what the hell was the target damn
what the hell was she cooking she was
throwing in like some Cheetos or
something
[Laughter]
that kind of shocked me as a chef with
SH
but overall cute and funny
yams and green beans but what the [\h__\h]
did she say she speak on it
Funyuns
I don't really understand that
oh yeah she's showed up during the
collab yeah yeah
substitute for fried onions
[Music]
you need to put fried onions on green
bean casserole ah pretty son of a green
bean casserole in this thing what
you guys make it too easy for yourself
you lazy [\h__\h]
like for a joke like those
um hot Cheeto mozzarella sticks for
example okay I understand for a joke for
like a tick tock uh yeah okay it looks
cool because it's Hot Flaming red and
all that but
dinner
those aren't a joke in America
please don't use me as an ingredient
think about it
who should I use then
it's good stuff well okay I'll have I
may make it for me someday and we'll see
if it was good
okay let's go I need to get some
freaking super chats done before the
Cali collabo
and so we start with jackets monkey
thank you for the pinky yeah thank you I
want to say thanks for interviewing my
own
did I already read holotalk super
shuttles
she's such a sweet girl who works so
hard all the time I hope the chickens
will learn a lot about her today and
don't forget to talk about ah this is
still before but it sounded like it
already happened don't forget to talk
about all the great songs she's been
making thank you oh yeah I interviewed
your Oshi Kiara or I was interviewed I
guess I was interviewed by wealthy Kiara
yeah she was kind of weird
um but she did a good job I guess
because obviously I can't interview
myself so I had to get someone to do it
and I thought the most fitting one in
that situation was just wealthy Kiara
because
she understood me and she knew what um
what I was going through and yeah like
we've been together for a while and I
just thought you know since it's my show
I wanted this one not to have I mean I
thought about it to be honest I thought
about having someone else there
but um for me this episode
I think
it would be funny to have myself
interview myself you know and um just as
a jerk kind of but also I felt like it
made also sense and it would be funny
hmm
yeah
but it was quite difficult to make it
all work and edits and [\h__\h]
but this way like I had control over
everything and
I think it turned out really well
you clicked on my link why would you
say it really is
doing the wrong one I thought you were
gonna send me the right one
okay I only read one so we're going back
to the karaoke ones
you're sorry yeah you better be sorry
amateur
okay
you have a break for three four days and
you come back to your shift and you do
this
bamboozle me yeah I'm already in the
other link okay thank you
soon thank you for the pinky it says no
need to read aloud
okay so I'll read it quietly
[Music]
why not
hmm
yes you can have
if it's not taken yet
thank you Evangel you're so confused so
confident I love you
thank you thank you cup you too actually
don't I didn't mean I love you I meant I
love you
mwah wait why did I give to you even a
pinky
give it to someone else
anyway thank you
I appreciate it and happy new year
anniversary
check out 47 ounce I've had to be mod
gang for a lot of the later parts of
your more recent streams because of work
getting visible it's really nice to be
able to catch this one and fall can't
wait oh
you see on the honor capped one then
you're lucky because that's that's what
you should be catching
fully
otherwise will be hard to catch
thank you thank you for watching and for
supporting me I hope you enjoyed the
anarchat karaoke the the song Choice the
set list was not the best in my choice
but um
I don't know I just chose some random
ones that I felt like singing normally I
have more of a system
um but I got some songs down that I want
to sing for a while and some repeaters
that were pretty good
[Music]
um
hope you enjoyed it foreign
[Music]
I remembered something
let me try to show you
mm um
[Music]
actually wait
I choked um
[Music]
let's see
oh that's looking good
oh my God
[Music]
it's loading so long
oh yeah
oh yeah yeah
[Music]
yes yes
yes
hello it's a me free dikiwawa and
remember me
[Music]
no butt update yet but they're working
on it however I did request another
thing a while ago
[Music]
I know my hand is cut off but it's cut
off for a reason
there is a reason for everything
in this world
do you want to know why my head is cut
off
because they finally
answered my request
of
nuts like
uh I don't know like um
this one
or this one you know without in my other
hand disturbing it
oh but of course I can also put them on
just this one
how does it says
and not only that now I did not test
this out yet because they told me it
happened while I was gone
but let's test it out
let's see
oh
I can also know
put the chicken in my hands and in the
other hand
and do a shake shake shake shake
next time I do my 3d full body stream oh
this is also a first
ah
well maybe it should be like Turned but
okay that's better than nothing so if I
like move it around
I grip it if I have my my hands records
on I can grip it
here sword
sword look at it from here
and
whoa
ah it's there I mean so my sleeve is
poking through that's a problem I'll
I'll have them look into that I guess
the probably the sleeve is a little bit
too the arm is a little bit too close
[Music]
absolutely no options
yeah
full form
[Music]
[Laughter]
before I wasn't able to wear them in 3D
so I was like oh they're part of my
outfit so can you guys please add them
since there's already models of them so
it should not be an issue right
so there you go
that has been done and they are working
on the butt I don't think yeah no
yeah no no there's nothing there yet
but it's gonna happen soon I promise
okay of course but update is the most
important moment in history of her life
anyway let's go Baku
there we go
[Music]
I'm good
I just wanted to check that
back to normal
thank you
[Music]
no cake just pancake
but pancakes are yummy too
but you know for me I wanted to get the
hats removed so I can wear all those
like seasonal hats like Halloween witch
hat or Christmas Santa hat Etc stuff
like that um
and then if I do my full body 3D stream
again I want to like swing around my
sword enough
[Music]
okay
let's go where was I here Ty
[Music]
ing thank you for cheering for me always
and unconditionally
um
will they help for the official model to
be released sometime I think they will
eventually be released
perhaps after
um
a proper
[Music]
um
you know like the IDS did like a proper
showcase stream
yeah maybe after that yes
[Music]
never gonna give up your dancing boss
loving this content thank you thank you
I tried to recreate that Rick Roll dance
a little bit I don't know if it was
noticeable
he just has such simple Rick Roll iconic
moves I wanted to do them I could I
could do better though it was kind of
spontaneous you notice oh yeah oh yeah
that's good
Rick Roll right off the bat as the first
song kind of risky I know but it had to
be done a nice skin color yeah yeah I
just found King never mind it was not
Rickroll it was King
[Music]
hmm
again
oh yeah
maybe maybe if I ever
if I ever do proper 3D in the whole life
Studio maybe yeah that will be one day
possible
I'm glad you enjoyed it and you didn't
feel insulted by the Rick Roll
Ultimo MK
20037 now thank you thank you for the
pinky lovely
thank you if you write that during the
Rickroll nah that was way after thank
you I'm glad you enjoyed it thank you so
much I I tried so hard to put everything
together properly
and also let me tell you singing while
dancing is [\h__\h] exhausting
especially when you have asthma
um some kind of joke
awesome
can you listen to it too I'm happy to
hear that dragon is
thank you thank you
I wanted to learn that dance anyway yeah
let's do it let's do it
[Music]
honestly unless you're like a
professional who does it all the time
um singing while dancing without
losing your [\h__\h] breath
even if it's just a simple dance it's
impossible
if you're an amateur
so yeah
don't expect too much from us
at least like life it's not possible for
amateurs even if you don't have asthma
it looks so easy
but it's not like you go to karaoke and
you try to sing while dancing like
properly
dance around while singing you will
notice you lose your breath
um
it's so difficult
[Music]
anyway one time
um
happy birthday
it might be late but Happy Birthday
[Music]
I learned that from love life anime oh
really
ah because of their actual like concerts
I thought the anime but you learned it
from the concert
but they actually I'm pretty sure they
go for a lot of training before doing
those concerts so it's not too
too much of a [\h__\h] show
yeah I can imagine they must have
practiced a lot
[Music]
and if it's a really big stage you know
you have to also run a lot when you
change formations and when you switch
from like if it has like a like a
catwalk stage then you have to run quite
a lot if it's like a Budokan kind of
size venue
then yeah you have to run a lot too
and also the air inside of these places
is really [\h__\h] too for singers
it can be extremely dry and
yeah your throat will dry up like crazy
which will make it even more difficult
and then if you're nervous then just by
being nervous you lose your breath as
well
it's just all
inhuman for an amateur
need a lot of practice a lot a lot a lot
a lot a lot a lot of practice on cardio
[Music]
oxygen tanks
that would be helpful I guess
hmm spicy chicken
[Music]
um
I'm too high and
I know that's too high
but I like it it's a pretty song I'll
sing it again sometime
oh this is where when I was singing My
Humps and you guys were spending she's
got me spending oh spending all your
money on me shocking
shocking that koala danced to that in 3D
let me tell you if I was not being
watched by you guys
I would have danced way harder to that
that was just then I saw you guys in the
chat line oh my God
that's like her moves her hips how
scandalous yeah so I was like holding
back
so I was doing less spicy stuff
should be more spicy
more spice more spice more spice
I haven't write nothing that next time
you should write
[Music]
something yeah did you like the money
throwing move
and yeah
uh happy belated birthday Henry
I am watching thank you Dominique Jones
yo the Food you've been posting on
Twitter is so good Kelly asked me to go
through the hashtag and find some some
pictures of foods that uh speak to me
and damn it was he was yours looked so
good you oh yo yo yo that Leia that is
brain frying to Kiana so cute and
amazing
[Music]
but I wasn't supposed to fry your brain
because we don't sell brain at kfp I was
supposed to fry your legs or your wings
or whatever
[Music]
can we undo is there an undo button
that's not good brain fried brain
doesn't sound very tasty
but maybe we can sell it to someone else
and people will not know this
um don't tell anyone guys don't tell
them
we'll tell them it's um
what could it be soft
um
um chicken tongue tongue is maybe so
acceptable people eat cows tongues
um
oh thank you naked chicken that comments
really sweet
foreign
[Music]
choo choo
is way better than you implied I
absolutely love your moves it's so cool
and considering this is only like five
percent of your power level makes you
makes me respect you even more I hope
one day we can see your super Talent OR
she our super talented or stay without
limiters
[Music]
okay thank you
no I don't think it was one of my best
but you know I just wanted to test out
the
the 3D emotion caption at home I'm glad
it went decently well thank you for
watching and enjoying it thank you
it was so much fun
thank you it was a lot of fun thank you
I saw Cali did one too like
last Monday or so
but hers was actually archived huh
I saw a lot of a lot of boobies close up
a lot of close-ups of the booba
interesting Cali interesting anything to
say about that
and I just watched the beginning of it
oh I forgot I have to watch it she did
ask me for the instrumental and I sent
it to her though
thanks for reminding me
I have to do it I have to do you it
watch it
[Music]
meanwhile we saw a lot of cake
no it's the miners cake cake
hopefully we will get plus cake you know
you know they sent me those pictures
right and then I said give me just a
straight standing pose so I can see it
better than I saw it and then I said
please a little bit more because this is
not enough yet
but then you think you know it will get
super big but no no no no it will still
be very it might be normal size in my
opinion
but I think now it
um is as much as I can ask for
uh
otherwise I will end up like Kim
Kardashian
um
[Music]
no dumpy but yes we will get dumpy
thank you
I think that's nape let me check
yes babe
don't be pending
okay as long as it's accurate if you
could hook it Papa's reflection well I
mean I
I feel like you know when you look at me
from the front you would the hips imply
that there there is a dumpy you expect
it but then you look to the side and
there's just nothing there
and it was just completely like a
straight line which was I would say too
much slimness I understand that you know
slimness is a thing
be slim but uh that was just that didn't
look good
now
I had to add some some curves that match
to the front curves that you see with my
Silhouette
yeah yes Phantom
[Music]
yeah having less on eofi makes no sense
also just kind of partially because of
the the pants that she wears and I'll
fluffy and make it look like that anyway
today was my day off but thanks to you I
was able to have a good done thank you
it was great for Deca though again oh
[Music]
you didn't mean
thank you
[Music]
thank you for waiting up early for me
that is
Young
[Music]
boy
there's also a blue team thank you for
the pinky I'm so proud of you why
wow I don't deserve that what did you
say that what made you so proud of me in
that pretty stream maybe because I was
able to figure out the stupid setup okay
I was quite proud of myself as well for
that
yeah
yeah yeah thank you so much
is that girl though what girl
oh it must have been some song lyrics
I wonder what it was
I forgot
you looked really cool you did all
yourself thing you got very strong on
you oh no yeah I did I tried to both on
Hollow talk and on the Rococo
I tried to hold back on asking for too
much help
actually
not enough the camera was um done by
amazed manager
yeah
Anna was supposed to
um play one thing one one
in the first time you know when I wrote
that we tried but things didn't work out
because like technical difficulties and
all that stuff and we needed to fix some
things instead
but then we had to reschedule really
fast because I had to record it like
within the coming 24 hours and there was
no time so actually well fiano is
someone else and
um the camera was by I'm a manager who
was so nice because I have to tell you
I'm his manager was
um busy the whole [\h__\h] weekend
constantly I'm controlling all the VR
stuff for anime NYC
and um helping us set it up and then get
in and blah blah blah
yeah
the whole time and uh in between
henna was so nice to squeeze some time
in there uh for my recording yeah and
help me with all of it all all the takes
I had I had to do
um
yeah sacrificed quite a lot of sleep I
think
no no no no no no all right henma was
not there in person so I don't think
I think who you saw was someone else
um
but uh yeah
it was great big help
but I'm it did end up offering doing the
camera next time because she really
wanted to control the camera she says
she wants to do it so like us next time
I do a pretty uh hold a talk
I will hit her up
[Music]
um
yeah thank you hanma I borrowed hanma
for the camera room work
[Music]
thank you soon
uh anyway was I
think
you're welcome
um new rock too rock and roll baby
thank you for watching my karaoke's
theme thank you see you on the next one
too hopefully hope you're not sick of me
singing yet
thank you for the recipe
moves are too strong even at 10 of her
power love to see you finally being able
to do 3D without needing to travel
Halfway Around the World also even at
batona well if I wanted to do something
proper I still need to travel Halfway
Around the World
so that's sad especially when you know
even if I were to travel
I asked to like record something
beforehand
um next time in I'm in Japan
and of course it doesn't seem possible
because of lack of scheduled space on
Studio side
so
hmm
uzukashi I really want to do some stuff
[Music]
but yeah
we are way in advance AKA like seven or
eight months in advance and
you went to Studio in Tokyo um it's not
a normal Studio it's a motion camera
studio and that's
I if I don't use the one from my company
then it will be endlessly expensive
not quite worth it
[Music]
but maybe in the future
things will improve in terms of
scheduling
I've heard some things so hopefully that
is true we will see
just have to always think way ahead in
advance but
I mean
snap that
easy
oh well
and what was I I thank you fried screw I
kissed my
kids face would you like one
served on a plate
with some whipped cream on the side
[Music]
reading comments
amazing deduction
s first of all thanks for the pinky this
is pretty undercut piano it was
everything that I could have ever hoped
for thank you thank you
thank you I was like you know a bit
worried because a lot of people in the
chat were saying oh it's scuffed and so
on and yeah I know it was like Loki
stuff but this was still like so much
better than I expected it so I'm glad
you guys enjoyed it and you say that
makes me happy thank you
um I think it was so like
pretty good for home free
considering that
you know it's in my home in my room
set up alone
[Music]
you can't expect like highest level
motion capture there
the arm movements yeah just just the arm
movements already add so much I agree
with that it is not one of them before
the collab okay chill chill chill that's
more than enough time
[Music]
I wish I wish chunky monkey Was Not
Invisible but you can't imagine when I
was holding her up over my shoulder
that she was right there
right so cute
[Music]
um
uh by the way I woke up like early today
because I also slept early but then I
remembered that today's stream
the Coronado is kind of late so
I figured I probably should sleep a bit
longer so I did sleep in a lot
I slept way more than I needed to
to be ready for the collab to have some
energy
but oh yeah in Italy the past couple
days I always woke up like before 10
and yeah
was quite healthy I guess
I got one more hour
some reason I thought it would start at
11 PM or so
okay so 10 pm
and I have so much time
[Music]
thank you thank you this is great
attention not too scums at all and this
is only a fraction of your power because
they're in a room you're currently in
any chance of 3D Santa Clara this year
Oh you mean like the Japanese members
had pretty outfits in like Santa Style
last year yeah I don't think so
and tell this that we got those I have
not heard anything
at all about that so
don't get your hopes up
sorry I wish I could just um slap
something onto my 3D model but
I I can't
it would be nice like we don't even have
to have individual ones on but I was
also saying it would be nice to have
like just like a matching sentence
really simple Santa outfits even just
the same as
these ones you can just slap it onto US
I would be so happy with that but yeah
best I can do is just Santa hat exactly
I can slap the Santa hat on my head
it's okay at least we have the kind of
little video yeah
yes
uh Santa well fiata maybe we'll get
another VR Christmas stream or something
like that
this year and maybe I'll maybe worst
case like the least I can do is maybe a
3D Christmas karaoke or so
uh VR with wall fiata again like last
year hmm
I mean I will spend Christmas with my
family so it will have to be either a
day or before or day after herself but
yes
Mariah Carey reference is great by the
way thank you I'm like
shocked that so many of you guys didn't
get it
normally you always like she doesn't get
the memes but then this time it's
actually quite like a common well-known
thing and you guys did not get it
foreign
one
yeah
but she sings even higher she sings like
that
she really goes up that high
crazy
yeah
it actually should have happened like
according to Mariah Carey on the 1st of
November but I wanted to wait a bit
longer because for me it was not time
yet
not really big on the music well me
neither but this is a meme
she sang it at the Thanksgiving Parade
wow
for Christmas there is just one thing I
need and I don't care about
us
[Music]
come true
foreign
[Music]
cuteness is so powerful I love you my
Oshi thank you I'm sorry I cannot offer
to you something of higher quality but I
hope this is good enough thank you Skye
for supporting
[Music]
thank you Sean you're the best
foreign
thank you for the pinky
Chihuahua you're the best I know in the
world you're in way better shape than
froggy voila
well why did you have to say that why
did you have to mention that what why
did we need that comparison
what do you mean froggy level was in bad
shape
[Music]
fact
s in
she's not chunky she was just in a cozy
onesie
why'd you imagine her is that all you
think about her huh anyway you rock yeah
okay attend your best setlist best moves
and adorable scarf
action I'm a bit confused about the
froggy wobble part but
um I guess I guess Theo complimenting me
but I I don't think we should be body
shaming froggy Wawa
why are you getting on fentanyl nervous
because body spray is not good
I know I know I know I know you guys are
confused why I'm defending her but after
something about the principle of you
know froggy Wawa being insulted for her
size just doesn't sit right with me
[Laughter]
you're doing so good it's like a small
concert more relaxing and fun thank you
love lava ah thank you
I'm glad you saw it like a small concert
yeah I feel like adding the body
movements to it
gets it in that direction I want to do
more like that
I want to do more concerts there's so
many ideas I have
um well thank you very muchacho
[Music]
thank you love you too
glad you enjoyed it thank you for
supporting me
where's the potato I was going going to
wait for my upcoming birthday and my
third birthday December read but this
feels more important you've always had
such a fun Dynamic personality home
pretty just feels so right
thanks for the amazing stream and
another great year as your fan
[Music]
ready
who's upcoming but maybe by now you
already had it
in case that is true then happy birthday
thank you for spending it with me again
also Leonardo and no problem you gotta
watch the archive though
Rome was amazing absolutely stunning
but
brain overload was so much incredible
stuff that I would stop functioning here
and there
hmm
anyway thank you thank you chicken
let's do more home for the shall we even
though it's kind of hot and tight and
blur a bit annoying but I want to do
more
stuff like that
yeah happy birth happy birth Happy
Birthday the verb
um
way too cute your singing always is so
incredibly beautiful thank you for this
amazing Channel potential I will never
ever get tired of your voice you truly
are the absolute best love you forever
weight watching thank you thank you
I'm glad you don't get tired of my voice
sometimes sometimes I do too
sometimes only rarely
oh
yes yes
I feel like I've been to Venice when I
was small but I don't really remember
maybe I might be wrong
but yeah Venice would be amazing
anyway I think I'm known glad you like
pretty cute mama just as much as 2dq on
one thank you soon for your support for
excellent deduction Cruise
thank you so much for 3D song
broadcasting can I please sing You Ain't
Seen Nothing Yet by Avril Lavigne is
that a new song because I don't know
that one
I guess she's still making music hall
that's pretty pretty impressive
wow
is that good
I don't know it have you guys listened
to it
oh I went to a concert two months ago
wow
no clue no
she was on first take oh yeah right
I don't know I don't know it's from
2013. oh that's actually pretty old
hmm
I feel like she recently released a new
song though that was quite like original
or younger Avril
I liked that one my great Junior and
Duncan shouldn't mess with the first
time because on TV table trading crusty
thanks mate for the rest of the Chateau
thank you so much for the stream kiwama
I know you've been struggling with the
setup but even with the Scuff the
results were 100 lower hoping for more
3D Studio streams in the future even if
it's only once in a while yes I think
I'm planning one for next week actually
um so look forward to the schedule
trying to squeeze one in there you know
between the Pokemon streams there will
be a lot of Pokemon streams
yeah so look forward to that thank you
Christine for the support that's mate
I appreciate it very much and here's a
choo-choo
[Music]
appreciate it
Patrick foreign
this was really fun your hands are so
expressive well I mean of course I also
like use them more than usually I would
say
like if I just like sit there and play a
game I don't use my hands because my
hands are busy using the keyboard and
the mouse or the controller
um but yeah
I think the head movements
make it
so refreshing so I want to use it a lot
which means you do use your hands yeah
I don't use my hands then but just you
don't really see much movement then
you're just always in the same place
even right now I'm not using them even
though I'm just talking and I don't have
my hands on the keyboard or the mouse I
just have them wrapped around my leg
I don't I don't use it like when I just
talk to you guys
[Music]
on the PC
but um
I guess maybe when I talk to someone
one-on-one normally in real life then I
might be using my hands more but now
during my doing my stream so I just you
know since there are a long time and you
don't see my arms anyway
I just chill
and relax and save energy
like why would I move my hands when you
don't see them
I saw Kelly using them though
when I was like swimming together with
her
I saw her using them even though it
would not be visible
quite active
exposed
that's a long time ago though
maybe it changed now
and oh yeah thank you
thank you for the wonderful singing and
handful events foundations and naive for
an unexpected trip down memory lane your
British accent is funny oh thank you
I'm glad you mentioned foundations and
naive out of all the songs because a
while ago I remembered them and put them
in my in my karaoke planned songs
setlist a long time ago like way before
that karaoke and I was like whatever my
next karaoke is themed ass I will sing
these songs
they are maybe not the most hype
mainstream songs but I found them to be
very nice
foundations I knew from the radio was
running a lot oh I didn't know it from
the radio but Naruto
[Music]
reduction thanks for finally seeing
vexil from the moment you sign a little
bit in the entropy Center I knew it
would be heavenly
yeah it was nice to sing that
thank you
and Jim Tracy thank you for all the pink
Super Chat last but not least that was
so awesome you totally rocked all the
singing and it was so cool to see you
dancing to the songs and getting to do
all kinds of 3D interactions we even got
bonus chocolate interactions thanks for
such a fantastic stream
thank you very much for enjoying it and
even the chunkers interactions
they are very special
well soon again sometime and I mean it
might be it might continue to be scuffed
in the next
future streams but I'm hoping that I can
you know with some help with the motion
capture suit maker make some
improvements
to the general setup by
um
trying some things out but it will take
a long time so don't expect anything in
the next
two or three months I don't know how
long it will take but I wanna I wanna
experiment a little bit it won't even
then it will not be as good as you know
cover studio quality of course
but I'll see what I can do
[Music]
something before oh yeah yeah I was
thinking so too I'll get so hungry if I
watch all if I look at all those photos
yeah um well we're done with those super
chats so I guess I could take a break
now and go eat something hmm
maybe I will
uh
[Music]
I already scrolled for a lot of the
foods in the in the hashtag and that was
already making me feel hungry
[Music]
though
now the magic turtle
good Japanese word meshitero remember it
because everything you'll be seeing is
machetero unless Kelly chooses a lot of
joke pictures I mostly chose like
serious pictures that I think are
seriously good looking
and impressed me
[Music]
see you in 40 minutes yeah I guess so I
guess we'll we'll leave it at that and
then tomorrow
um let's see Jazz team let's see let's
let me see let me see let me see let me
see my calendar
at 7 45 uh jst which is
11 45 my time
is that right
a 11 11 40 I think it's 11 45.
11.
45 and it's just uh 15 minutes if you
can't catch it that's okay because it is
archived it's a video
for sure
okay then Pokemon I would probably start
at
3 P.M or 4 P.M my time
maybe maybe 3 P.M gonna start a bit
early because there's so much
I saw a Pokemon
foreign
[Music]
for me
I don't stream at 2 am
don't worry
I'm gonna be in a tournament uh can I
talk about oh um
Mandy
uh I think I said I might be interested
but I don't know I don't remember
it depends
yes
depends on
um yes
on time and on here
when is it
I'm not
Pokemon once I need to catch up
oh yeah Co-op She also asked me about
call up um I don't know how when and so
on but uh maybe we can do it next week I
don't know
I'm probably going to be when you're in
Japan
no I don't think so
yeah probably like around uh
one month after release
for no particular reason probably right
before
or exactly on one month after release
[Laughter]
any later than that
just because of no particular reason
just because we feel like doing it that
way
yes
if it happens then it happens
see you later than one month after
release
yeah okay uh
so
I guess I'll warm up my food from last
night
until February not ah nah ah have you
not noticed
how everyone every time we play Pokemon
games we only play it for one month
what a coincidence
what happened with shining Pearl
happened with Pokemon Snap even even
though I didn't play it happened with
our our what was it our
our
you know the the medieval one
our chaos yeah
um possibly also was like that with
sword and shield but I don't think I was
in Holo yet at the point of sword and
shield
but I think it was the same
hmm
stop noticing things yeah yeah they are
gonna they're gonna cut my tongue and
tongue at the point and blind me
like in [\h__\h] admins Taylor so I need
to start watching I will start watching
the most recent season soon
uh
silence me I'll be silenced I will never
be sorry
I will learn I will learn
um hand Language sign language if I must
and until they cut my Ubi ubis and then
I learn foot language until they cut my
foot you'll be ubis then I'll learn
whatever [\h__\h] language I need to
learn
I'm proud language
[Music]
yes
[Laughter]
oh no
oh that's terrifying
all right guys I'll see you on Kelly's
Channel and then tomorrow on the YouTube
music weekend and then at Pokemon so
have a nice day thank you guys for
watching
[Music]
and thanks for welcoming me back
he was back
should we go today
[Music]
my side gonna eat some food
oh
[Music]
my mom says
it was iron
that they stole iron
[Music]
saw that message
I
but in other places they may have also
stolen bronze and other [\h__\h]
well it was iron in that case
I run yes iron
[Laughter]
I think one reason why I might be saying
iron is because Japanese iron
is
maybe not rotiness I Ron but
[Music]
I need and
whatever let's just I
run
[Music]
foreign
don't you think there's a whole [\h__\h]
conspiracy there anyway
[Music]
don't you dare bring up Iris about that
topic
[Music]
foreign