[Music]
thank you
you said it all I'm literally life okay
fine
oh as in you're on your opening
[Laughter]
hey
okay I'm live okay fine I'm gonna I'm
gonna move to I was talking and then
like wait wait
oh yeah let's greet everybody oh hi Audi
hello good morning
good morning
oh my God oh my God
Mission Stato
why hello everyone
good morning
yeah it's only the ID team right now for
those who are wondering where the Ians
are um I think
um they will be doing promotion first on
their stream and since we already did
our promotion yesterday so we're just
gonna chit chat right now I guess yeah
oh my God
more promotions
are still on the description by the way
yeah if any of you guys are wondering um
it's on our description it is on my
description yeah and everyone's
description oh oh I kind of wanna wanna
see
yeah so apparently uh I did an oopsie I
said that oh my God yeah pre-order is
closing an inner sloth and a hollow life
website no it's actually only closing
yeah that's only for the whole life
website yeah for the inner sloth
merchandisers you should still be able
to get them yeah you get enough even
after today yeah yeah for the whole life
one you can get it until 11 59 PM GST
today today
[Music]
me today November 28th that's your day
slot it's just still going so you guys
can chill
um
[Laughter]
oh okay
yeah okay
oh
yeah there's only Kiara and crony inside
for the Ian's right now yeah
yeah but yeah in the game
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
guys happy
[Applause]
oh yeah yeah
um yeah
oh but here's the question for you guys
from all of the merchandise that hollow
life and Among Us is having right now
which one do you guys are most
interested in
oh
um I like the keychain with all the IDS
and Ians oh like the cute keychain what
was it called again the emergency
meeting oh I like that one yeah the
emergency kitchen yeah the immersion the
key holders
[Music]
I love them what about you
there's a lot of you in here there's a
lot of you a same same emergency kit um
you know
I'm very much interested like you guys
said I like all of the key holders
Miyabi senpai's especially already put
an order in that one
yeah remember you guys you guys you guys
can get any OC from hollow life
production yeah down to ID Ian even
Stars ain't that cool
I actually haven't seen the Stars One
the Stars merchandises oh it's cute
charm yeah yeah
um I need to check them out
I think if if we're talking about merch
I like the plushy [\h__\h] ah the plushies
[Music]
take care of it and they just like oh my
God the real picture it's so good right
I wonder if they can get like the
Airship if you buy the whole thing
like you know in the picture they're
like an all-in-one Airship that's so
cute the whole thing
[Music]
that will be spicy yeah
yeah get them all before
wait
uh-huh before what before tomorrow right
no it will be gone by today if you're
talking about like Indonesian time
all right
11 59 p.m GST today
[Music]
I kind of want it but they don't ship to
Indonesia unfortunately you know what
you gotta do you need tip hello
[Music]
oh my God oh my God I love that sound
effect
[Applause]
like me
hi
[Music]
oh hi
hi hello
uh okay should we just play the the
basic the most basic one for for the
first one oh yeah sure
basic it is
already had a Omega stream like this
right like four hours ago or so yeah
yeah yeah
I got it yesterday
let's go
um
so fast
inside before me oh they're in the room
oh there's a room oh gosh
the other because the other room closed
okay okay I made a new one one second I
don't trust streamer mode
come on
stream remote works
[Music]
wow everybody's really tired huh
[Applause]
the titles yeah
do we want to do like uh you know a
classic introduction of everyone yeah it
can also be a soundtrack
let's start by the top
hello everyone hello it's on your mouth
is second generation how's my voice
all thank you congrats
I
really love that it's still fancy
okay available next what what's up it's
me the red I'm tired um
the red I'm gonna Channel my sleepiness
to being the best sauce rat that I can
hello
oh no you silly
just told me
is in the room yet I don't see her in
the room no I'm not isn't it
yeah
[Music]
we are hiding why are you hiding coconut
I'm shy do you want to hide it yeah
see this
Christmas
dog
yeah
kind of make it compared to everyone
else oh you know what beauty beauty is
is you're just beautiful fauna you know
yeah
I'll join you've convinced me
she's been returning to nature
I don't have any clothes yeah I don't I
don't have a whole life clothes we'll
work on that we'll work on that okay
crony next door
hello it's me
Tony
the
sound effect is sending me Acron they
say crony's low but I have her on Max I
can't do anything else
it's just her voice maybe her voice
yeah
speak from the stomach crony speak
higher let the world
higher they said you're too low
yeah
well I think that needed a bottoms but
then nothing happened I was really
expecting uh yeah thank you thank you
all right
all right okay oh my god oh say again
crony
you know yeah
okay yeah
thank you you should be fine me
I did it
it's having fun promoting Instagram
everybody
wow ready
amazing
thank you for bringing the energy that
we need Yeah
[Applause]
by your energy I felt that in my
eyeballs I know I've so did I wow
get better at feeling in your eyeballs
who's panties
[Laughter]
a lot of panting yeah it's still a
mystery yeah bye uh next
intro
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
thank you for waking up so early
[Music]
hello oh hi I'm not moving from Whole
Life English I have a stuffy nose to go
men
you didn't register to me that you're
saying oh hi I thought you were saying
Ohio but then you just cut it halfway
because you could be bothered to say
I got shy
I also heard nashimum instead of Nana
she's just saving letters I am saving
time here come on
maybe take too long the room is gonna
dispense
[Music]
excuse me
[Laughter]
thank you
and so the game starts kind of close to
chat real quick oh wait that's
a very small amount of tasks
I wonder if Kara sitting by kinda LED
you set the settings
and
if you haven't then then that's also
okay
where are we supposed to go again oh we
need to go to weapons all right okay
that'll be honest with you guys didn't
really sleep last night it was a
I was planning some stuff
forget what if we get my drift
let's go to admin
all right this thing don't open unless
it opens can't do anything about it
there we go it only it can only open if
we go to if we're in like polis or if
you're like in a in an airship
other than that uh doesn't really do
much
let's just finish the long task first
then
we go over the fun ones
nope nope nope okay
I trust you do not pull anything when a
senpai but deliver you're taking quite a
while
oh well I guess she's okay I think
Harrison might forgot to set it up
but that's all good that's all okay
it was a little bit last minute
I should help I should help her later
get us anyway so responsible
may I do a little bit of a confession
big fat crush on her
it's it's not really it's not
it's not a secret but
cronies the freaking impossible
chroni you little snitch somebody
yeah
how do you do ah damn
here we go I think you've been hi I miss
you buddy hello I missed you guys hello
hello hello
where's the buddy yeah
[Music]
I just arrived on the shield
oh sorry
oh yeah
it should be muted never mind
I have discovered the body I need
I was in storage
was a hallway to the left you know the
hallway that leads to electrical
and doesn't do that yeah yeah yeah that
is where I discovered the body and I
actually saw a
go in that direction right before I
discovered the body who was it oh
thank you
oh no but it wasn't moving wait oh but
like I've been traveling like everywhere
else like I've been traveling the right
side oh she said crony I thought she
said mummy okay
years does not work when I found the
body
you cannot report the body if you were
there
um
[Applause]
since we've already lost two crew
members
everybody
[Music]
oh yeah
yeah
you're on the right side
onwards but my ghostly duties
oh
[Applause]
I I should have used
right
um
I see you're a very diligent doing the
Warriors but maybe you should do
something
yo
okay
[Music]
where are you guys
foreign
[Music]
wait can I undo mine well you know
what yes I am the Imposter but guess
what oh my God
I'm gonna give this the Innocence the
win so
um
all right bye
[Music]
really
what a great turn of events
this child is an orphan
foreign
let it cry
[Applause]
maybe it was destined to be
you are also
parentless right now I'm sorry my child
no
hey
guys
what what
[Applause]
else
again
totally calculated so embarrassing
guys
in case someone doesn't know
if someone is someone is being choosing
as imposer and the Imposter said that
the next imposter is someone don't
believe it
which means that they're gonna be
innocent the only two people around me
were Kiara
between the two
I thank you Ollie like when I was about
to walk over and Anya was there and I
was like crony you just got me in so
much trouble
it worked out though I'm also sorry to
everyone in advance but hey that's the
game
man I
I went when you guys were in the
discussion and Courtney was like no it
was like people were there and then
everyone else seemed not convinced and
I'm like she killed man front of you
guys
full of my eyes that was so funny
yeah
I couldn't see it because I was doing
like tasks
were the ones in the room yeah and like
I was like I was hoping I was hoping
that Zeta would say something so that
people would obsess me I didn't yeah she
was doing tasks
the funny thing is that I was like I was
about to go out from that room so if
only you had waited for like a few more
seconds I probably wouldn't have thought
that
learned her lesson for next round right
yeah
[Music]
twice
I can't believe that
you know one thing that I've realized I
just love how mume's name is literally
mom mom
um
her name's mom
is Mom Mom and father
you know what Fafa I guess if you say
far far fast enough it'll sound like
Papa so we have Mom and Papa
I'm sorry I'm breaking dead right now
I I gotta I got a half hour nap and
that's about it
are you say anything bad I'm blaming it
on my brain
maybe I'm not a good person
oh no
running
it's very dangerous
[Applause]
trying to turn it on but people kept
turning it off
I just kind of like stopped and watched
it I was like okay honestly I I was at
there at the scene too but if you
wouldn't have just admitted immediately
that it was you then I wouldn't have
known because there was so much going on
[Music]
I was in there I was in there because
electrical was out and everyone else was
right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah how
can we know it was her we don't know if
it was her
there were so many people there
yeah
the animation of chronic killing it okay
too much
yeah I don't know because like I saw it
by the way I saw a movie like I don't
know I just arrived no no it's not mummy
I suck run in front of my eyes killing
it really
unfortunate
[Applause]
what Luna said crony just incriminated
herself right away anyway
best of luck
everything Tony thank you
[Music]
it's you who exactly who knows
a lovely turn of events I would say I'm
just going to upload stuff you guys
better handle the reactor leave the
tours to me I can't do your chores but I
want to do my chores
starting to sound like a jerk right now
I wonder what
caffeine tastes like
I don't like I don't like coffee
but I'm contemplating on actually
getting it
I
well yes we're stuck
I guess I'll just wait for my inevitable
Doom
I
still I don't think it's Sonya
she seems to be doing well for her task
okay we don't want to lose there's
anybody go on that one
I'll go on this one
all right uh five four seven eight five
I did it I did it guys
hi Mom how you doing mom doing wires I
see yeah the same we we have the same uh
fast
cool
last one last one
boom
guess I'll die
I'm so bored hey papa
I'm gonna stalk her and make her scared
or I can do this you guys want to do a
promotion
I'll do a promotion
she's dead
okay
chasing me and then she went off to the
right side of the map okay can I saw you
two running around yeah
I thought that she was the Imposter
because she was chasing me but she sorry
it sounds so suspicious right now I know
I do but it's used to me who made
chasing me around the table but I almost
called a meeting because I was like
that's kind of susp and I was like oh
it's movie so it's just probably just
being normal yeah it's probably
yeah
why did Ollie called a meeting just to
check actually I want to do a little
promotion did you guys know that the
whole life production and Among Us
um
um what if you go to the electrical for
like one second and then you went out
immediately
oh I was just checking to see what's
inside
why won't you check who's inside why
can't I check who's inside I can be like
oh something I don't know man that was
kind of sauce yeah yeah if you don't
have any tasks like inside the
electrical then why won't you go inside
and see if I could stick to anyone
I mean Ollie and me were like going out
of the room why why didn't you like go
with us instead you definitely where is
this intense
and like me and Ollie were like going
out
but like you you like you you were like
going inside for like one second and
then you came out immediately
why didn't you go with us
well because I don't want to get killed
there
last time last time we were all in
electrical we got somebody got killed
[Music]
um
okay somebody stick with me then
[Music]
laughs
for that
so let's go Google I'm I'm bored I don't
have anything to do anymore
I'm out of chores
hey I don't care if the comms are a
sabotage
well maybe the others haven't really
done their task but I did I did
okay for
oh that was fast oh Harrison Bible's ear
since she was alone I don't think it'd
be her
I'll keep a normal distance from her
make sure she doesn't just swoop and Ill
hello hello
I remember
oh
[Music]
I wonder if that sounds like Marines and
by a little bit
da da
da da da nope nope yeah
you go to that one I go to the no no no
you go to that one
okay
okay all good
now let's see what hmm
push
time to look for physicists who want to
be accompanied
but she's not here she's not here guys
she disappeared
then where is she
oh Pizza
delicious
all right I'll hold this one somebody
hold the other one
bless
we only have 13 seconds thank you
since she's looking at cameras
uh
what up
what up hello I was watching the admit
thing when we were all in the admin room
and then I saw someone teleporting from
storage to the to the main lobby
it wasn't the three of us who were in
the admin room and it wasn't yeah it
wasn't me phone and Kiana you know what
what's interesting is that Zeta came
after that
I came from yeah but I wasn't I was like
it came from the other side King I was
walking I don't know I didn't see anyone
teleporting though but that uh Zeta was
like yeah I said I came to admin
I think
yeah and we were doing stuff
interesting
I'm I'm suspicious interesting
so can you describe the the how many you
took to arrive at your destination
um I'm just gonna say I finished my
tasks
the wiring okay so so it could be a task
one yeah let's let's pick up for those
who finished
with those who haven't who haven't
finished the task
[Music]
uh I'll go with you guys too I can't
are we voting Anya we need Daniel to
vote oh yeah I'm sorry you guys follow
me just skipping I I voted
I hope you like my face
foreign
let's see what happens
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
yeah cause that was so sad I didn't
teleport by the way
can I just mention that in the
in the ghost chat babe is trying to sing
a Taylor Swift song
did you not actually get it I thought
you were just ignoring me on purpose I
have no idea how that song goes I didn't
even know that was a song until later on
oh my God
I'm standing there and you're right jump
is it
do you want to try a different map or
stay in the same map girls
um
I sure hope I don't get imposter because
I don't know these
yeah okay
[Music]
let's try let's try paulus I guess I
don't like it that much might be fun
okay
cold there you go
thank you thank you
y'all see nothing one second
oh my God
excuse that they don't know the map well
so they didn't know where to go no women
exactly but I'm telling the truth I
never know where to go
um
so like I'm gonna get lost a lot yeah oh
yeah
bye everyone
[Music]
just to throw them off
I haven't been getting any of them
lately
oh oh I gotta go here
fauna has a same one
gonna make sure nobody's dead
do not kill me
I made sure you were alive
please accept my gestures lovingly are
you following me on purpose fava I love
you I love the nature you give but I
don't think that he should be stalking
me
this isn't the full High Senpai
relationship if you get my drift that I
want
okay over here because no one should be
able to see me here
[\h__\h]
oh dang it
Speedy don't cry me again well she's not
the Imposter unless
yeah
oh office office oh um
why didn't you report
oh yeah you say you saw it but you
didn't report it
by the way yeah that was also nearby I
think
no I was from the office and then it was
on the left room right left room of the
outfits I think so I was in the office
and no no you would go to the right room
you were in the right room Anya yeah
so it was like it was dark so like I
didn't see this thing like I said I was
right behind you you seemed a bit sus
I was right behind her oh she was like
acting a bit sus in that hallway right
before she entered the right office so
I don't know
yeah but I was behind you
so I was wondering actually Bae was
actually on the left left-ish side of
the office I saw her I was in the office
I was in the office and then I also
started going away
I saw you I went I didn't go in the
office
I saw you I think go towards the office
I passed by you and said I think yeah I
think mommy is near Communications or
something yeah
Senpai was like around there but I don't
know why she didn't report the body
report I didn't see it first yeah they
and Anya are kind of teaming up against
Muna
oh
my God head are we folding well I don't
I don't know I don't know if there's
enough information or anything
[Music]
close
here interesting oh
yeah
Hannah said nothing in this meeting
poor girl no he's gonna do this
she was with me the whole time so I
would know that it was probably not her
I heard I I saw I saw a clipped that
that worked
why does it not work when it's my turn
so let's go down there
I'll fix the lights don't worry guys
a crazy Ollie hollow life Indonesia
second generation on the case
foreign
I'll fix it for you guys
to such a great person
uh you're
whenever I needed
oh yeah sorry
whose voice was that
ah dang it now I gotta start remover
foreign
and
the laboratory
which should be somewhere around just
checking noted bodies okay
what's this
boom boom
okay
I'll go this way
because this thing's far
foreign
good job
wait how many imposters too there's nine
of us
all right
this thing
one two three
four
nope a one two three four five six seven
eight nine ten
I'm done with my task
no at this point I think
I think we should be able we I think
it's it's very
possible for us to get another one oh
hey father here I'll stay with you guys
yeah follow you
listen I'll I'll even give you some
space
you do whatever
here here look see see
I'm giving you some space I'm just going
to be here like bodyguard
and yeah
I want to go together
she's downloading we'll wait for her and
then
because usually when Anya starts sussing
people that's when Nino she's innocent
when she when she starts playing
Detective
usually she's a lot
quiet she doesn't such people that much
when she's the Imposter at least that's
what I realized I know if that's her
meta though
I've been sucking off on your on your
wires haven't you fauna I'm done
oh that's convenient
so that's one two three she already did
three wires and the bar went up so
maybe it's a coincidence maybe it's not
I don't know but one thing for sure if
she does another wire then uh she saw us
just gonna tail her from behind
I'll go this way
oh it has a lot of dead bodies
where where's the body
where I wait where am I I'm here uh
security electrical
yeah I didn't go there
fauna and Ollie yeah we were from the
whole time yeah yeah we were from the
specimen oh
yeah yep on the way to the Bay was
suspicious of Muna and I didn't see her
the whole round no I was with Mommy
before but I go with Mommy before yeah I
didn't see nothing but not at all I was
in a boiler room still doing my task I
also didn't see mume but hmm
yeah I didn't see mermaid too but wait
what side are you guys on
um
I was in the in the with Walnut before
fauna only and Zeta we made right
and we're just like standing there yeah
in the emergency room
yeah right
yeah we did oh yeah the office and then
final went to the specimen room and then
we met up with Anya and then we went to
the laboratory and met up with Zetta
yeah I was mostly on the right side of
the map the whole time yeah me too so I
can't be on the left side of the map
um are you I thought I saw you oh yeah I
guess I just wait you said right side
right
yeah never mind I guess that is
I think I think we don't have any
imposters voted out yet right that's
kind of bad yeah yeah that's kind of bad
I mean there's a lot of people after
editing tasks I don't know man I'm gonna
laugh Luna Senpai peace yes
and and I mean if you die you can do
your task faster so it's a win-win if
you're not right yeah
I'm already done with my test so I'll
just follow people around
um I have like one more I have one more
I have like one more
okay
okay uh what do we do now yeah
hello where are you going
hello Rosetta where are you going
mom
I see you
social distance social distance
see I'm giving you a little distance but
I'm also following you now don't kill me
don't
do that
[Music]
no may you scary
who is it
was moomy she was chasing me at the end
I was thinking wait or can we not kill
again do I have to report before we can
kill the kids
heavy fire excuse me
yeah it's a new mode haven't you it's
there to explain why did you miss it you
should have prepared then you wouldn't
have you wouldn't have missed it uh-huh
oh yes right gaslighting is the victim's
fault okay I got you
I'm missing one person
oh who gave up
uh get in here
I'm sorry oh that's okay I am learning
the game okay I don't know the straps
here
I think we can at least squeeze in one
more round yeah maybe we can do one more
and then we can play hide and seek
all right
this one is
okay
yet another cool mate guys
gonna watch over before I go in there
all right
excuse me
locked
no one's dead right
it'll make sure no one's dead I'm gonna
gonna watch over you guys some names
they'd be like respawn kills Anya's
there no one said over here somebody
would be probably doing that so we will
be going to the laboratory
specimen room
that was fast
and then we just go down
and take a little shower
hey
one
two three four five six seven eight nine
ten I did it I can count to ten I'm a
genius
let's go
cute
whoa okay
it's not crony guys
[Music]
why did you not record it then no I was
on the security cameras I saw it it was
it what what how could you again
your body
well I saw on the security cameras it
was mermaid standing over crony's dead
body and also walking away
no no I was knocking crony earlier to
creep her house
right then when she died why didn't you
report her right then and there right
what wait but that was her natural state
[Laughter]
no I wasn't
[Music]
so I don't know I have no idea um also
keep an eye out on Muna because she was
running she was like there and then she
went the opposite direction so I don't
know if she really didn't see it or she
said
keep it you know I didn't see Pony die
so I I say honestly but okay
then we can just yeah
it'll be it'll be all okay
wait oh should I vote
um um
oh dear oh dear me
stuff
so uh
real cool
swag wait how do you okay wait wait
there's a lot of Stack people
there's a lot I'm going to watch over
give off us gone
okay thank you
[Music]
I was thinking parents
no one's dead right okay cool
I'm gonna do my last task
yourself which is over there no not here
oh this is
I saw someone here
senpai
huh
hmm interesting
I didn't see
I don't know kirstenby might have forgot
to uh I mean I mean she did do the
settings but what if she forgot to like
undo the visual task one
because there's supposed to be some
peoples
do what I'm saying
all right I'm done
I'm done
bye
look at my face it's like
yay we're all done party oh party I'ma
come
yeah party it's the three of us again
it's the over oh shoot
they they
oh oh those
they are smart whoever is the Imposter
they are very smart
oh
it's done
very smart of them to do that
because like everyone was going to this
specific room kind of
I'm just going to stand by here if
anything ever happens to the seismic
again
no no do your task
do you ask
yo
I like that Meme a lot
Vine was a golden age
I like Thomas Sanders and most
uh somebody else Story Time the story
times are fun and all those are here oh
fun party
so the thing is I kind of don't want to
go with you guys
oh
ah
okay she's not here
now all we need to do is wait for
victory
someone just needs to do their attacks
oh be careful of sad kills everyone
they can't do another emergency in like
10 more seconds so we should who's not
doing their tasks do your freaking task
I did mine oh what you guys doing
good job
again
I didn't kill anybody
after moving uh get out it was like this
is so hard to kill everyone yeah
and I was like bro this can't be real
that's cool you can see people's names
when they're watching somebody that's no
I just saw your your character your
colors
yeah yeah oh yeah oh yeah I think you
should be able to like see the colors
[Music]
um
well why are you looking at a camera
babe that's creepy
yeah
but but you guys instead not in like one
step would have like a different style
so I just like oh this is hard even
though I do it
it is hard I think everybody should be
off on their own and isolated at all
times honestly
yeah maybe because
except for me
monsters
oh there's always one can we just maybe
do one more round and in case someone
gets important monster who already got
impossible before we restart or just
yeah I wanna try but it feels like bugs
yourself yeah
I'm going to kill all of you
okay
okay yeah if someone gets it like okay
oh yeah oh yeah that was yeah do you
want to play one more round doesn't
matter who imposter is if I get it again
I'm gonna throw it
we could just do the emergency meeting
and cast okay yeah if I'm imposter I'll
be throwing it
oh [\h__\h]
well
emergency meeting everyone
anyone
I don't think anyone's going to
emergency meeting
I think
oh is that little curse at the end
though wait I'm not supposed to be here
wait where am I supposed to be
here I didn't know they had these
you know they had this here
oh
tourists
Nani
wait are we going to happen
what I I saw someone but I don't know
who it was because I wasn't looking at
the screen but there was someone running
Rockets right
oh yeah yeah by the Rockets me me me me
me
I I was stalking fauna and then it got
dark and I lost sight of her but then I
saw crony come from the opposite
direction
and I started stalking her wait where's
the body again I think yeah
where's the rocket uh it's nearby the
laboratory
oh no that's so far
I've just been in weapons all I'm saying
is that like on the left side of the map
it's fun did whoever was did they cross
paths with you or did you see them
escape to the left
interesting left
from the right to the left interesting
oh I did see crony run however I don't
know I I don't know I just wanted to
play It's funny then she might have
um
so okay I will fuss up
I I did get it again what but like
should you cast me out now
but I didn't kill anyone so I don't know
what happened
I don't need a hat of imposter and we'll
just continue like that
I'm an imaginary kill people I will just
act as if I did it
so like if I'm impossible again should I
just out myself
we have too many people doing like it
narrows it down too much so I'm not sure
we can really do that I mean we can just
keep Pony around
I'll just not kill anyone I'll just do
sabotage
oh oh that was close oh man oh close
but at least she's honest she's very
honest she's honestly yeah
so I don't know if it's my imagination
however
was was Zetta behind me when I was
running to the uh what is it called
telescope thingy
like I passed by Moon as in by now I
felt like someone was behind me and then
suddenly there wait am I supposed to be
here
I'm not supposed to be here
um okay
I'm just taking the long way out
uh okay
and then oh wait where where am I
supposed to go
am I supposed to go to the rocket
I felt like I did
be fine me and I bet they were the ones
who actually killed munas and by
I just didn't remember who maybe it was
moomy or Zeta but I don't know they just
sound similar
that has nothing to do with what I
actually saw it's not Zetta okay
we have to go she was in the hallway on
the left side of the map like but she
was like like a tree
on the path of the seismic thingy
she's in like the middle left okay in a
hallway wait who was with someone was
with me at stabilizer so they're also
safe
um
I I was walking up with you but then I
went to the left and I met she was
coming from that area but I guess she
didn't she didn't touch it yeah
was it every time I see crony I won't
lie
it's okay
yeah anything can happen it must be the
other imposter
fish are friends not food God I I have
no idea you go skipping
who to choose
[Music]
honestly I'd choose spawner at this
point what
have you been waiting for the every
single round you just said that and
amuted herself immediately
[Laughter]
[Music]
but since but now that you think of it
since mummy didn't report herself as an
imposter no she got an imposter twice I
mean currently reported so I don't think
it's her
it has to be someone else
but it's not dead that I was actually
very sure that it was it that actually
oh it looks so cute
[Music]
I was very very sure it was Zeta
but now that mummy didn't she didn't
come out as an imposter so that makes
her not imposter
no
he came out there's no way that movie
wouldn't come out too
hello
I kissed her and she ran away that could
be like a title song for something
ah she's accompanying me sweet sweet
crony
it's easy slime baby
[Music]
I ate well no crumbs left
foreign
good job child now social distancing
cookies
so cute she's just running around
causing havoc in the
in the crisis
and the seismic meters
that's cute
she's adorable
oh
she's also doing wires so it's not Anya
because why would she go in by herself
to gain my trust no she wouldn't do that
and I'm pretty much done
so it
so it's if it's not mummy it has to be
either fauna or Chiara senpai
I'm feeling like it's fun a little bit
but I don't know
Anya's here oh
yeah I'm guessing my friends can we be
friends
I love crony's characters so much it's
like it's me it's me
you can kill me if you want oh
I have one I have I have a theory
like Romeo and Juliet wait what what
romantic I have I have a very big Theory
so I was okay uh
ume and fauna at the very start because
they were the nearest people uh after I
saw Muna senpai
and since Connie came out I felt like oh
oh it has to be someone that didn't came
out after meeting Anya
um Anna isn't the type that would be
um going on herself doing duties just to
get in anyone's stress if she's an
imposter so it couldn't be heard it
couldn't be me so it's either KR Senpai
or bae
was not done yet
I don't know I feel like I I really
because we're kind of dwindling to the
final people so if you waste a if you
waste the thing we're gonna we're gonna
lose by the way the body was that
um beside the weapons is that weapons
like you better choose someone yeah like
between weapons and admin
why is Courtney still here
left
is
no okay yeah I mean I don't know why I'm
still here to be honest because it's
very nice and not killing anyone I
appreciate the jester thank you
but like really big props to like the
other imposter doing a very nice job
Let's Stay Together and finish tasks I'm
done by the way yeah
I'm done with my pony
if girls have been any Senpai or let's
say uh oh we gotta stay to get we gotta
stay together
let me see
Allah
don't worry I see you
and I see
Kiara this won't get copyrighted right
no one's doing the lights everyone you
know what I'ma Do the lights
[Music]
I'm sorry
in the Back Bay you stopped me where in
the back
yeah my outfit in my spine when you did
it respect to the ones who stayed alive
and finished the tasks yeah oh honestly
I was dead and had to finish the tasks I
think it was me I'm sorry but I did it
mattered
you thought it was someone red but I
wasn't looking at my screen I was like
what are they someone in bed no
oh yeah but is it possible to do one
more since like that that one round it
was just pretty much one imposter
oh do you guys just want to do hide and
seek I don't think
we should remake the room down
um you've got one in pasta and the
killing time is like 10 like the lowest
10 seconds and pretty much they have to
try and kill every everyone before they
finish the talk you know who the do you
know who the Seeker is yeah yeah so you
have to you have to say that you're the
Imposter when you get it
um and you've set the the running speed
to the fastest whoever's making the room
and then yeah you count to ten if you're
the Imposter and then yeah okay I have
the player speed on Max oh my God that
is so fast wow
10 seconds
10 seconds it doesn't get any lower do
we have okay we have to do task yeah
yeah yeah so the point is to finish all
the tasks before you get here
we can increase it though yeah yeah
increase the top task was too little
yeah
so wait so how many should I do
okay
no recording though no reporting um
which oil do you want to do
you want to do the normal one for now
let's glad okay oh and also lower
imposter Vision as well oh we're not
gonna mean ourselves by the way right
yeah
the lowest okay oh you can hear each
other's screaming
macaroni
who is it who is it
okay
oh wait oh wait I'm sorry
[Music]
wait you're are you faster
uh it's impossible I'm meant to die in
this
I have no idea
oh okay yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
die
it's even more scary
you guys the division
I got an achievement a lot is everywhere
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
slider elevator music oh my God oh my
God oh my god let's go
oh gosh
what do you mean I haven't killed anyone
in a while
um
[Music]
[Applause]
wait is it only is it now
dude
um
[Music]
I don't think so we can haunt her oh
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
no no I was gonna I was gonna click the
use button everything
yeah
give us another 10 seconds so close oh
no it's actually gonna happen I thought
oh no
I don't know I'm sorry we got five
seconds give them five seconds good five
seconds I think it's good I think it's
well balanced but it's a challenge
hide again
wait no you can't do it
[Applause]
okay possible
wow amazing I think it would work so
that we would win what what good time
[Music]
okay
but I'll change should I change
something any Improvement advice was
actually okay
if I hadn't messed up I would have won
so it's okay yes I think okay
play well if you want to win it's
possible
who's it I don't actually don't I don't
actually want to be it so please know
wait we should restart it okay
this game is so broken well we could
just do an emergency oh yeah yeah but
yeah you can kick her out okay oh
why would one thing why don't we just
you know doing the marketing
[Applause]
one you only have a couple of hours left
so if you wanted to get it but didn't do
it yet then go do it do it do it yeah
let's do it
just
do it do it
do it
the contest of all the including saying
do it is incredible
me me
[Music]
all right will it be fun again
we weren't easy wow
[Music]
wait what
is the tasks somebody died already
killed me already
okay you guys they were doing tasks you
guys are confusing me yeah
okay
I'm gonna die anyway probably so
it started
man I think
no idea what should I do
oh my God
you said what is happening
the Keystone that is broken
no more
careful now well this is pizza
I'm definitely not gonna be exterior
right now you don't need to go looking
for me
[Music]
I can't do the card
God damn it
no
ah she's ignoring me
at all
every time
one more time and boom
oh my God
[Music]
my hands are shaking but we lose it's my
fault
Daniela
oh
this gets hard when
there's only a few people left okay I
already mentally gave up on that one
[Music]
um
you are scary wow
you've got petrified
hey love everybody
[Music]
I'm so sorry
that was fun
did anyone besides me never get imposter
I didn't me I never I never got one only
an onion me we are cursed yeah I know
right it's not fair
I'm going to sue someone I don't know
who but I'm going to school probably
yeah
or hello
in Indonesia
how do I say please give me
how do I say please give me uh it
depends that you can at least give uh
you can at least just say it's kind of
cool uh something dong
like he does
oh my God
only I'm surprised it didn't bake me
um I will marry you or something like
that
it's like
anyway guys go purchase some holidays oh
yeah that's it right now it's gonna end
soon I'm gonna show you yeah in like 12
hours I think so maybe we can grab the
merch guys
acrylic stand yeah t-shirts
yeah really nice
[Music]
that was fun
so spontaneously especially members who
already did their homework
[Music]
and thank you
hope it was fun for you guys too thank
you yeah it was really fun thank you
I'll show you something
[Music]
with that everyone
ends today's Among Us stream we've had
two Mama's dreams back to back I hope
you guys enjoyed it and I hope you guys
will be buying our Among Us merch
um last Among Us merch for the holiday
fun as do the ones that you're seeing
right now the plush the diorama the the
keychain the sticker these things you
can only get in a few more hours because
after that the pre-order is like closed
the inner flat one is still going on
together
in 26 hours we're going to be closing it
so be sure to get yours soon hey yeah
always love IBN clubs yeah it was a
spontaneous clap but kirstenba actually
did a good job uh
what is it called being the leader and
uh
uh organizing the whole thing even
though she was not too organized she is
just so cool
I wanna
I wanna do stuff with her
the thing is that I cannot see on stream
or else I'll get canceled again because
apparently I get canceled for everything
ah anyways thanks so much everyone for
coming
this has been crazily and I am signing
up
or two
three bye bye
[Music]
foreign