[Music]
hello she's
hiding come on from I'm not here I'm not
here where where are you then if you're
not here I'm I'm behind
you I I can't see
then oh I must be
invisible everybody's saying that you're
very
shy no
K I'm not shy I like I love you're kiky
did you know that in Spanish Kik key is
what a rooster says too oh oh well I
mean I think all over the world the like
morning sound of a rooster is like
pretty similar
is like it's supposed to be the Japanese
way of saying
it yeah well uh hello sorry I did that
because that's what um like I always
make my guests do in my talk show in the
beginning I make them hide under the
table
oh oh I should I should have hid behind
my table
then no the host doesn't do that you
know why I do that cuz I like I I
explain what the talk show is about in
the the beginning before bringing in the
guest finally yeah I just like explain
it because usually I think there's
always new people watching so explain
you do this every single time yeah you
know got to have a pattern and you know
be like a professional talk show host
you're so professional what I need to
take
notes I brought food but you know do I
don't know if you want some turkey leg I
would love some turkey leg just a little
bite can can I have some now yeah take
take some oh oh you're kind of naked
there I I'm I'm not naked what wait wait
wait wait wait wait I'm I'm wearing a
bodysuit it's sometime I love that
outfit though oh thank I love your
outfit thank you just casual just casual
well wait a minute wait a minute wait a
minute you need to introduce yourself to
everybody even though everybody already
knows who you are nah I don't think so I
mean on Twitch I I feel you said the
different things but I feel like I'm I
people don't know me on Twitch because
I'm not on Twitch everyone knows you and
everyone loves
you you're just
exaggerating I'm not exaggerating people
are obsessed with you now introduce
yourself now okay
okay I am
Taki Phoenix H even though I have cat
ears on right now I thought maybe I
could seduce some people with my cat
ears today um well I'm a phoenix people
call me a chicken but I'm a phoenix um
I'm from H live English first generation
myth uh you know same as K
II yeah I I I speak German because I
live in Austria I've been raised in
Austria and but I also speak Japanese
and English English is not my first
language so please excuse me if I say
something weird or pronounce something
weird and uh I don't know I do some
music but mainly I stream like games and
stuff I am um I I often do very long
series but also I have like in between
games you know where anybody can come by
and I want to say
[Music]
uhas
qule
qule you say it so well
too I love me a fellow quo enjoyer I
don't know much about the quo can you
tell me about the quo
meme you don't know it
a yeah it's like a a nice lady says
today I wanted to eat
a and then you
[Music]
say yeah and then you know she keeps on
talking like ah so I went to the store
to buy a
quo I'm going to tell you the only
reason the only reason why I know the is
because I saw a clip of you teaching
coron to
say oh that's very recent yeah oh my God
she did such a good qu wait what what
people say I'm like late on memes don't
know memes what sometimes I'm late on
memes too you know you seem like someone
who would be very well versed in memes I
think I'm I'm well versed in other
memes oh like what what's your favorite
meme currently my favorite meme right
now no I can't say it say it my favorite
meme right now is and you did it at my
birthday
dinner what it's old it's it's it's old
but it's it's coming back it's coming
back you know oh oh what is it
about like the chat seems a bit like oh
the ones who know are like oh god oh
no most are like huh it was a it was
from a video from a beauty influencer
that she was having a serious talk and
she said she said uh some stuff that
was uh bad and then she was like and you
did it at my birthday
dinner I'm so sorry I can't like laugh
about it
cuz funny yet
don't worry my humor's broken the maybe
I look at the actual reference to it
then fun I can't tell her I can't talk
to her about that that's
x-rated oh he said sensitive yes it's
sensitive information and you're my
guest o well well yeah yeah I I must be
protected and shielded from such things
because I am Sayo yes you're you're a
pure say so Idol I can't do that to
you all right then so we only talk about
say so things
today I mean I I just don't want to get
in trouble I I don't want to get in
trouble oh it'll be fine it'll be fine
are you saying we're going to get crazy
up in here talk about crazy x-rated
topics no probably not thank
God I'm sorry to disappoint yeah I am
the purest whole life member yeah yeah
that's right I know I know you are I
know you are no but like I um I think if
if maybe there's some people who only
know know me like
very has a negative sound to it but like
shallowly like uh don't know much about
me but maybe only things about me from
like the beginning of my whole lifetimes
where people always called me like
bottom left and all
that you know that was like a big Meme
and well okay bottom left is a meme that
we created so you maybe you don't know
about it but it they're basically saying
that I am uh like horny and stupid um as
a meme as a meme but I uh that that's
long gone since um but I think maybe a
lot of people still have that impression
of me but I really like honestly
seriously I never could maybe I could
agree with the fact that I might be
stupid a little bit but not with the
horny part like people always say I am
but I I really am not I I am very say so
yeah well I know you're not stupid
you're really smart oh thank you I don't
know about the other part though well I
I am I am maybe only smart in
very
certain categories because recently I
played this game Q do you know it oh is
that the one with the drawing
yeah the little physics riddles I guess
and I was so bad at it I mean there was
one that I first tried
but it made me feel very stupid oh no I
I've seen people play it but I'm like I
can't play that
game there's no way I'm way too dumb
there's no way there I think the funny
thing about streamers playing that game
if they are too dumb for it that's the
funny thing but then the viewers will
also rage at you like why don't you do
it like this it should be like this why
don't it's true it's true they back seat
especially here but I don't mind I don't
mind the back seating for me someone
someone uh said I beat portal one and
two yes I did
but string no no I was also tring with
that what wait you're smart I I'm I'm
way too dumb to play that G I tried
finishing Portal 1 and two makes someone
Smart in your opinion too yes wow wow so
Portal 1 and two is like a test of IQ
for people for gamers I feel like you're
judging my intelligence right
now no no I you're like wow you're
really dumb no no I mean I I Al also
really often rely on like the chat's
advice I am like actually encouraging
back seating in my
yeah me too I always encourage back
seating I love back seating yeah like
Community participation you
know part of the stream yeah together
and then it feels like even more
satisfying when you when you finish
something and then everybody's like I
was part of this I'm part of the reason
she made this for real for real yeah and
then they started spamming I was here in
the chat and everybody's
happy yeah isn't that nice it's very
nice it makes me smile the only time
back seating made me rage and like
really upset uh is for example Elden
ring
oh that's but Elden ring is like um in
at least in in whole life uh the one
game that broke a lot of members in
terms of backseating like that's the
first time I ever saw so many members
like being like like
F you guys I'm gonna turn off the chat
or so oh I'm gonna just not look at the
chat anymore at all like I hate this you
guys suck stop
backing a lot of upset members yeah I
didn't even finish
it I didn't finish it cuz I was just
like oh my God everybody's yelling at me
it's really difficult it is it's so
tough it's it's Souls like games please
have mercy on me I need help with Souls
like games they're very scary uh I like
Elder ring cuz like you could do a magic
build because I just I'm just not good
oh Magic huh y' magic I heard magic
build
helps but I didn't
even I heard it was like uh basically
like cheesing it right is it
yeah that's why you hiding well your
mouse of course you cheese
why not yeah sure do it for the cheese
it's baby
mode oh no it's a valid Strat oh oh
they're they're protecting you
oh your Strat is valid your cheese is
valid I thank you I'm glad I'm glad you
uh agree with my
cheese I try to find ways to Cheese
games any anytime any any way I
can yeah because I'm bad
well me too me too iron Mouse wait too
what kind of game are you good
at
SIMS no but like I play a lot of Jes but
I I don't know if I would if I'm good at
that I was I think I was like decent at
like tails off rise and I'm decent at
Fire Emblem I guess after a lot of
practice oh yeah you like you play a lot
of Fire Emblem don't you
yeah I mean well I played two games on
my channel so far because like after I
debuted uh two have released since uh
free houses and uh engaged the the
Dental One recently um I know nothing of
fire em I I haven't played one Fire
Emblem game oh well they're like
strategic and they're turn based so at
least it gives me time to think about
everything yeah I think it's it's it's
helpful but yeah I guess I'm only good
at them because I spent a [\h__\h] ton of
time on them and they took up hours and
hours it took up 80 hours the engage one
I think it took up 80 hours of stream
time on my channel yeah oh my God
freaking
long oh my God that's so long that's way
too long for
me what's like do you not play like
longer games I I I I have but it just
takes me so long because okay I'm going
to tell you one I have a terrible sense
of direction I'm very bad like I will
get lost I was trying to play Resident
Evil the other day and I kept running
around in circles for like 20 30
minutes I never played Resident Evil so
I'm not sure if that's like a really
hard thing to do like getting lost like
running in circles like that no no it's
it shouldn't happen
no so you were NE really really
game yeah I like games that hold my
hand yeah so you cannot play
GTA well I played it one time you can
drive around endlessly I know I don't
think I'd ever get the game done I'd
just be driving around I finished GTA 5
on my channel you did I did I feel like
I'm one of the I'm I'm the only one in
whole life English who ever finished GTA
5 that's so determined to finish games I
have to finish games when I start them
then usually with the intention of
finishing them oh you're a
completionist it was so good it was so
worth it it was so fun now I want to
play it but then I'll probably start it
and never end it I wish I could still
play it you know I wish I wish I didn't
finish it are you guys allowed to like
play like GTA online no no right yeah I
can play GTA online I should I guess
yeah it's another I want to go back to
the days before I finished GTA 5 man and
like a lot of games that I
finished you know you know I really I
really love tunic does anyone know tunic
man oh is that the game with the sand
like it's like a a sand game and there's
like sand game is it a sand game no not
a sand game Sorry like it's it's kind of
like a Zelda game yeah but with a fox
and it was one of the nominees for an
indie game of the year but this stupid
cat game um uh killed it are you talking
about straight yeah which I also
completed um but junic is so good it was
robbed it was absolutely
robbed tunic Justice for
tunic are you you don't like the cat
game I love the cat game too play it but
but like I say from a objective
objective but or like I don't know as a
person who played both games I say tunic
is
better it is true I I'll I'll check I'll
look into it so that I can play it so
myself oh subjective well you probably
you will not be able to play tunic Iron
Man probably not from what I've learned
about you now that you're like kind of
bad games I'm terrible at games I'm so
bad lost and yeah tunic's not for you
no games are for
[Music]
me did you play stray I did I did play
St it was cute but the thingies like
they scared me I played I played on on
stream and then I never played it on
stream again I played a little bit off
stream and I was like uh I didn't I I
haven't finished the game I'm I'm I'm
pretty bad when it comes to finishing
games uh I have like a short attention
span
uh I feel like you well you would get
lost in in stray too so I did
yeah it's also a little bit on the
difficult side I would say I had some a
little bit problems here and there
sometimes
sometimes but no any game about cats is
a good game I love cats me too you're a
cat right now ah well well yeah kind of
it's just a cat
disguise yeah I'm trying to get a little
bit closer to my
cats so cute I love my cat oh I wish I
could have cats I wish I could have pets
I've always wanted a cat maybe you can
in the future maybe I would love a a cat
the ones that look like the gremlin with
the big floppy
ears do you mean the naked one not not
the naked one there's another one that
they're
theying when you say floppy ears there's
just like Scottish fos and Solon like
those are not Gremlins though no no
they're called or uh Oriental short
hair oh let me look that up
Ori
G or you're going to be like
what a yeah yeah seen
those yeah I
mean they look funky don't they
yeah they do they deserve love too yeah
they look fine I mean some of them look
a little bit more weird than others
you're so honest I appreciate it you got
to keep it real oh god oh you always
keep it real oh [\h__\h] how what they sound
like elephant
ears yeah they're like really floppy and
cute and they honk they don't they don't
meow they honk they
go really yeah
[Music]
weird cat well but I'm sure it would be
very appreciative if you gave it some
love Yeah I want to I want to love a
weird cat no well I like the naked cats
too yeah okay I think what if you get
both the Oriental short hair and one of
those naked cats I will be so happy o
you're you're making those unpopular
cats very very happy and if somebody
comes by and visits you and sees those
two cats they're going to be
like something's weird what what what
what are those what's wrong with this
woman what are those fish oh like leave
my rats
alone ah don't call them rats beautiful
cats I don't know I just like weird
things I I love things that are not uh
the
ordinary that's nice I know like Ving is
also not so ordinary that's true that's
true that's very
true when I tell people what I do and
I'm like yeah I I do some streaming
we're kind of streaming and I'm like
well uh anime streaming anime streaming
I'm um I'm an animate girl on the
internet perfect next nailed it and then
like your your loan has been
denied oh yeah okay mhm I didn't
even last time I got an like apartment I
don't think I even had to tell them what
my job is they didn't ask for your job
no
no because I guess also didn't need a
loan but was it's just renting I guess
if I were to buy one they would ask in
chire what are you doing what makes you
able to pay for this are you able to pay
for this yeah probably then they would
ask well in the United States they ask
you even if you're renting or not they
they straight up ask you what you
[Music]
do yeah I mean maybe sometimes they do
here too but I guess I mean when you're
able to pay for the for freaking
stupidly EXP ensive security dep
sometimes they're like insane here like
what you sometimes it's two times the
rent sometimes it's three times
sometimes it's four times the rent and
then when you're able to pay that I
guess then you're probably uh able to
yeah pay the rent hopefully they would
assume so you see it's so different over
here cuz even if you can pay it like
they ask you huh how come you can pay it
huh why are you questioning it none of
your business they're just really nosy
yeah but I guess they have the power to
like you know just turn you down if you
don't tell them you don't have to tell
them but if you don't tell them they
might just say F you go somewhere else
then they ask you everything they want
to know everything about you they want
to know everything about how you make
your money and where about your social
security number you'll never have my
social security number please tell me
your Social Security number no no no the
thing is we don't have social security
numbers in Austria I only like heard of
it you know like from streams that it's
you shouldn't tell people but it's like
kind of a joke please tell me your
Social Security number it is kind of
number I think yeah the credit card
number that's important I mean the
social is important too but I don't
think you can get too far with somebody
else's social or what can you what can
you do with a social security
number well you can open up a credit C
oh that's not that
useful why do people hide it so much ah
you can steal their identity yeah
identity theft how well you can take the
identity of the person and open up a
credit
card again that doesn't seem like so
overpowered it's bad because if if
somebody opens a credit card in your
name and spends a bunch of money on a
credit card they ruin your credit score
and then they ruin your life
h ah you could buy a house yeah they
could buy stuff in your name and
basically ruin your credit name oh no I
see I see yeah I don't think we have
something like that we don't we don't
have a we don't even have I don't know
do we have credit score someone just
said Oher probably doesn't have a credit
score what is a credit
score I don't have a credit card I wish
get a credit c a credit score is like
something that they use in the United
States to measure your worth
oh and but then it does it have to do
with a credit
card uh yeah well yes and no because
your credit can be affected by things
that are even not a credit
card oh it's weird oh o like if you had
like crimes before maybe uh it could be
like crime but it could also be like uh
let's say like a student loan like you
got you you got you owe school money
that can affect your credit score or
like so does everybody have a credit
score yeah everyone what's your credit
score it's I don't
know my credit score my credit score I
think my credit score might
be bad because I have not opened up a
credit in a long
time or maybe it's good I don't know
open up a credit to know to know did I
tell you there well no I don't know
maybe my maybe maybe my credit score is
okay now but I don't know it's probably
bad it's like what's your credit score
is maybe it should be my my new opening
or like get to know question that's an
American that's like a m yeah that's
like a meme question that you ask when
you're going to date somebody oh they're
like hey what's your credit score that's
like the joke don't care about your IQ I
want to know your credit score
no hold I wonder what mine would be
yours would be very very high because
you're
incredible I don't think that and you
seem pretty
responsible well at least I don't owe
anyone money see your credit score will
be wonderful W let's go then I would be
such a desired object of Love wouldn't I
very much
so I should become like one of the like
a main main actress of like a bachelor
show like but I I'm the bachelor oh like
The
Bachelorette yes would you ever what if
there was like a bachelorette but for
like
vtubers well I feel like something like
that has probably been done before Oh
that's true maybe even like
neuros oh that's right you you did a
stream with neuros I did how was that it
was difficult cuz she she's slow and I'm
really bad with s uh awkward silences
like really F I understand I understand
yeah cuz she needs she needs time like
you need to like talk to her and then
give her time to respond yeah but at the
same time like she was responding to me
but at the same time I I had to like
throw in uh images of like fridges
because we did a fridge reveal and I
would throw it into like Discord and
then she would react to the image but
then I I wasn't allowed to interrupt her
while she's thinking about the fridge so
that gave even even more longer awkward
silences it was difficult but yeah I
also I've been told that she like at
that in that collapse she took even more
time than
usual apparently and yeah so it was a
like it was fun so you had to you had to
physic like she would see the picture
and she would like process the P that is
crazy yeah see I almost we're going to
get replaced she's really popular people
won't need like real vtubers anymore
like we're not we're the ones who maybe
are like somewhat partially replacing
like real life vtubers but next we're
going to be replaced by by AI vtubers oh
no the replacing ones are being replaced
oh no she's taking our jobs she is
taking our
jobs
singlehandedly God of course because an
AI was like perfect like she doesn't
really have like a yeah she doesn't
really have
much except for being an AI she will
always come up with endless funny
tangents and the thing is like even if
she says something bad no one can be mad
at her because she's an AI like oh my
God you can't cancel her she's an AI
she's living life on easy mode yeah it's
too easy I can't believe she's the
winner she's adorable though she's
cheesing be tubing that's true
basically well you know what that means
what we need to make AI versions of
ourselves I tried that you did wait like
for the stream before the collab of her
was basically her controlling me and
giving me things to say oh but it was
awkward too my my be was like saw
through me really fast they're like
something's off here you're too
human well no normally you're too human
and now you're talking like sh the
weirdest [\h__\h] is coming out of your
mouth what's going on I talked to uh AI
chat out of me and I broke
it oh how did you break yourself I kept
saying that I wasn't real I was like
you're not real you're not really iron
Mouse you're not the real me and I was
like really mean to it and it broke and
it didn't want to talk to me
a well that's so sad poor iron Mouse I
feel kind of bad now iron Mouse AI is
broken like for everybody or just for
you just for me oh okay well you're not
you're not meant to talk to yourself
anyway that's true that's true that's
like ruining that is wrong that's
like that's bad it's like seeing
yourself going back in time talk to
yourself creep it's creepy but did she
talk like you I don't think she did but
people say that she
does I bet there's an AI tap on of you
you know I used to love when I was
younger I used to love those God uh
chatbots oh yeah know what I mean yeah I
know there was like a god chat bot
online like I don't know 15 years ago or
so and I had fun chatting with them I
used to chat with the chat bot
too we're so
lonely that is so
sad look at my life well as a child I I
I mean I was I wouldn't say I was lonely
I I was just you know uh I don't know I
thought it was funny cuz you know
technology
technology technology fting yeah yeah
yeah it was just the product of the time
we we we just wanted to like find
interesting things online to
do definitely not because no one wanted
to talk to
me no no no no no no no no it's just
interesting has nothing to do with us
being lonely no no me lonely no course
not well I mean maybe now but not back
in the
day sad it's okay it's okay you're not
lonely you have all these people that's
true at least we have real yeah you have
kfp and I have my my little demon people
a
demons yeah my demons they're demons
yeah we're all demons oh no oh no I have
to Vanquish them with with my book of
The Charmed Ones what what The Charmed
Ones do you know charm I do know
charm I'm like rewatching it right now
you know the original one or the new one
the OG baby oh my God the OG one is so
good of course yeah and you know that's
why I react to Demons like that now have
to Vanquish you
oh my God the power free will set us
free the power free will set us free the
power free will set us free how do you
feel about like the CH okay there was
this one part okay I think towards like
the end of the show it got like crazy
cuz then like they started doing like
other stuff like they became mermaids
and like all this other stuff happened
and I'm like the show went crazy at the
end it's been so long I don't remember
that to be honest I'm like at season 3
three right now after they like switched
the other sister yeah that's okay yeah
I'm I'm still with PR right now but
should be gone season four is where they
switched them out yeah yeah yeah that's
when the show starts getting unhinged I
think I I do remember them getting
becoming mermaids yeah yeah I remember
that I remember the mermaid
episode did you not like it I did I did
I like I like the show a lot it's just
uh I feel like uh I barely like I
remember it here and there but I was
more of like a I I like to watch uh
Buffy
oh that was uh a little bit after like
Charmed at least a little bit after it
started right I feel like yeah Buffy I
never watched Buffy but I heard of it
yeah it's on I think well I don't know
if it's still on Netflix it was on
Netflix before oh really yeah I liked it
it's about vampires yeah vampires
vampires
oh well you you were young when you were
watching that right yeah yeah yeah I
feel like as a I'm not allowed to watch
those things vampires are the coolest
things ever it's true when I was a kid I
always wish that a vampire would come
and bite me so I could become a vampire
so I would go to sleep I would go to
sleep with the covers down and like have
my neck out like this so I can be like
oh come on bite me so dramatic
please but they never came oh
man I didn't watch Buffy but I watched
vampire Knights the
anime my animes yeah that's one of my
first ones and I don't know there's
something about you know the whole
vampire
drama you just want to become the the
main girl you just want to be her maybe
maybe and courted by vire like who did
you like more in vampire in Vampire
Knight what did you like guys yeah God
do I remember let me see Vampire Knight
do you do you know their names Vampire
Knight kame characters I think one was
kame and the other one was
Zero H yeah that was this the the the
silver-haired guy and the blackhaired
guy right yeah H I think I probably
prefer the blackhaired guy the silver
one was probably
too it was kind ofan he was mean yeah
but yeah what was the silverad one like
the silverad one was kind of mean but he
was like he was like the type where was
like no I can't I can't bite you oh
never mind I'm going to bite you oh no I
can't bite you oh never mind no that's
so stupid I would never watch this kind
of stuff now cuz it's so cring
me I used to love cringe now I hate
cringe oh man me to me
too oh man cringy the Edward type yeah
he was like an Edward type I think ah
Twilight Twilight did you watch Twilight
I did but I didn't like I didn't like
like it it was I I feel like it was a
little bit too much for me cuz there
were in teenage years there were evil
the teenage girls who were absolutely
fascinated by Twilight and the other
group that was not and I was the one
that was not yeah I was like I was like
the one that like vocally like in front
of everybody I was not but then like I
would watch it like when nobody was
watching and I'd be like
H not so bad making your vampire
fantasies come back
again H you can't hide it I there's no
need to hide it you're you're a
Twilight groupy no no no I wasn't a
groupy I
swear iron Mouse so edgy teenager iron
Mouse so edgy I was just always that
that that girl that wanted to be
different you know I was like I'm not
like the other girls I'm so different oh
I wonder if that would make you
different though cuz like everybody was
watching Twilight I feel like that's
true probably you know I was one of
those those kids that thought I'm so
cool and I'm so well I didn't think it
was cool I didn't think it was cool at
all I wanted to be
cool me too who doesn't everybody want
to be cool yeah it's true and what kind
of what kind of girl where you in in
school well I would so I don't know if
you when you went to school were you
able to wear anything you wanted or did
you have to wear
un anything I was wearing I was already
such a we so I was wearing like M short
skirts with over KNE socks and everybody
was always like uh oh I I wear Gothic
Lolita outfit I was L style
o for real like all the time all the
time Shee she was such a weave I
know I'm such a freaking weave I'm so
embarrassing you must have I'm sorry but
you must have been quite like The
Outsider right
uh yeah pretty much everybody else was
like stuff can I imagine them treating
you so well like cuz you know kids are
shallow and it was a little different
cuz like I went to like schools where it
was like a lot of like performing stuff
and like people were like artists and
like musicians so everybody was weird
okay yeah then then they're more
understanding for me too like once I
switched to art school that's where
people were like more accepting of me
being different and actually like found
it maybe a little bit interesting
partially and before that I was like
always the the freak the outside the the
nerd the weirdo no you're not a freak
what I would have been your friend thank
you I I think all of us like vtubers
like if we went to the same school back
in the day you know I feel like we would
have been friends cuz we we all seem to
have like most YouTubers seem to have
like an a similar school life
past an outsider I feel like a lot of
YouTubers are like either into like
theater or like something with like
performing or something yeah me too me
too singing true
true a I almost I wanted to ask you
about Kpop
yeah I love kpop I love kpop I love K so
you mentioned that you uh only like like
older groups like whom o some of my
favorite older groups okay so I I love
the Big Bang uh that was pre-
Scandal why Scandal oh there was a
scandal with one of the members but that
that's okay they're not they're not a
part of the group anymore so it's fine
oh okay is Big Bang the one with the big
tall one yeah with t o p yeah he's
handsome he is really handsome and he's
very he he's very artistic my ooshi from
Big Bang Yeah t
o oh yeah okay I also like Day song a
lot too so they're both my favorites
uhuh all right do you like any girl
groups uh I I liked Girls
Generation uh I loved I
know I loved okay my favorite alltime
girl group of all time forever all time
was to
anyone oh
and I Mean Girls Generation too I I used
to
listen songs it's the only group that I
actually own like physical merchandise
from they were the only ones that I ever
like I went all out and I bought like
the the the the CD thing and everything
and I was
like oh I like the taxi taxi
[Music]
taxi you better run r
they have so many bangers they do oh I
like mister
[Music]
mister
M cute do you like AOA oh I know AOA
they did the Elvis song you they did
yeah other
songs no the the one that goes la
la do you remember that song Or No wait
now I don't recognize it
oh it's like their first song a lot of
AA I listen to a lot of AA though it's
like one of their first songs that came
out yeah the first song that came that
that that I think it was it was it their
debut song Hold on let me check I got to
Google Now now I have to
Google oh oh what about if you like
older ones then you probably also like
Miss A I love Miss A yeah that was good
I love Miss A I know a lot of lot of
older ribs too you know uh what was it
Orange Caramel Orange Caramel was my
favorite sub group of all time right I
love yes they're so cute their concerts
are so cute yeah so bouncy and sweet and
cute and popping yeah I still oh my God
they did a they did a commercial for uh
for this ice cream company and I still
to this day remember that commercial the
bingu the bingu song that they did and I
love that song so much it's so
cute
no actually I only like female Idols
like in terms of Jpop and K-pop both of
them I somehow I only girl groups can
spark an interest in me I don't know why
it's because so cute and talented yeah I
love the Aesthetics
and I don't know like I prefer listening
to female voices most of the time I
guess I like I I used to be I used to be
a huge J-pop Idol fan like when I was
very very young I started getting into
Jpop through an idle group called
Betty's Co bow Betty's Co bow wait hold
on did they do the song uh
chaa yes I love that
[Music]
song that was a cover though yeah I love
that song I love it so I'm surprised you
know I thought you would come up with
like one of their they did some like
anime endings for some some
Shen anime like
some say
boy yeah I don't know why it was like
that was one of the first songs that I
ever saw of theirs that like I connected
with for some
reason 11 which I didn't watch but you
know I through V coob I got so deep into
the whole J-pop Idol culture and became
a huge otak I I went to so many concerts
in Japan from them I got so much
merchandise and I went to many handshake
events and you know I thought I want to
become part of hello project that's the
like the company that all these ID
groups were under unlike AKB AKB is
separate but I was I was on the Hello
project camp and I I was so passionate
about it and I wanted to make music like
them I wanted to dance like them and I
kind of aspired to be you know one of
them and I I auditioned for them but I
never made it cuz they like they usually
don't let in
foreigners the only foreigners I've ever
seen are uh in morning
musim uh like some you know and Asians
there's no like you know other you know
foreigners ever so they didn't it
doesn't really even seem like there's
foreigners um so it just didn't feel
like there was ever a chance I tried
anyway but it didn't work out and I
eventually you're an idol now yeah I
guess not really the type of idol that I
originally aspired to be bit different
but I'm yeah but you're still a
wonderful Idol what do you want to know
a fun story tell me your fun story so
I'm sorry for everybody in the chat who
Maybe likes AKB but I did not really
like them cuz I was just you know on the
HP camp and you must understand so yes
um I the reason why I prefer an HP was
because like you know I don't I didn't
really like the whole huge rivalry
concept that AKB had of their voting
those big voting contests where if you
don't get number one number two number
three or so you're absolutely devastated
oh my God the drama the drama
and then if you fall off from place two
out of like over 100 to place three the
next year then it's like your life is
over and like your whole your whole
confidence is like torn away from you
Stripped Away from you and you're
nothing that's what you what they make
it feel like but so this and like also
their songs I didn't like them so much
and the way they didn't sing life most
of the time HP was like really
impressive in that field like singing
life and doing really hardcore Ros at
the same time I thought that was really
cool so so um I I was I was big HP fan
and then I I could never get in but
eventually at some point I saw
AKB made uh like a kind of like a like a
rival group uh of for their for
themselves called noi zaka
46 uh that's the first time when they
branched out and you know didn't use the
48 I guess
and I don't know if you ever heard of
noi zaka 46 did you uh I wasn't well
vered in in the whole like I'm going to
be honest I was more into hello project
as
well what what I love Maki goto and what
the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] I didn't expect
that now what I thought I was just
talking
about talking
about what you know what I'm talking
about yes I know you're talking about
I'm freaking just talking into a voice
I'm an idle freak the [\h__\h]
what oh go oh that
is she is she is a special one she's
very
special okay let's talk about that in a
second but but so so nois Saka 46 you
know they did uh auditions for that and
I thought you know they're kind of like
promoting it as a as a rival group for
themselves so I thought well I don't
really like AKB but I will use this as a
reason to audition
now so I I wrote this in my audition
form that I I'm I I prefer HP much more
I don't really like you guys but I think
that's exactly the reason why I would be
good for this group because you're
saying basically roasting them my God I
don't like you guys but that's why you
should me cuz I think I will be a good
rival and improve this by not liking you
guys and they let me through
I pass [\h__\h] pass with that attitude
isn't that
ridiculous what the heck that's insane
what the [\h__\h] I passed and then I didn't
come to the second round because I
didn't care enough I prefer for an HP
out oh my God you that that's hilarious
what the [\h__\h] that's
crazy well in hindsight it was funny
because I ended up meeting the group
randomly at a convention in France when
I was just chilling and hanging and I
knew that they were like like
performance guests there but I wasn't
going to see their performance or
anything wasn't interesting I was there
for other reasons you know but I saw
them like vlog in uh while walking
through the venue and I was just like
sitting on the ground somewhere alone
and they walk like by they're about to
walk by me and I look at them and I'm
like oh interesting I I know them so I
look at them and our eyes basically meet
and that's when when the eyes meet you
know that's when my Entertainer switch
turns on and I'm like oh hi guys I know
you
and they're like oh interesting and then
so they come up to me and they start
interviewing me and I tell them that you
know I audition for them and I could
have been one of them cuz they passed
one round and they're like oh it was so
cool what tell us more tell us more oh
my God look at you flexing all up in
there yeah I was flexing but I did not
tell them that I I I don't you know
really like them I did not tell them
that can you imagine if you would have
what the heck that been so Savage been
funny oh my God but but I I just want to
say you know
um I listen to some of their songs uh
over the over the years and you know
there's some there some good stuff and
they're cute you know they're cute I'm
not like hating on them I I just prefer
hell project you get me iron Mouse I get
you for me like I wasn't really like
into their stuff that much and then they
made an anime and the anime made me like
them a little bit more more but I was
never really like as into that as I was
to yeah it was and it's all because of
I'm I'm just such a [\h__\h]
wee it's okay we all are it's okay I'm
just such a freaking wee what can I say
I was like oh there's an anime cool
okay he what's your favorite HP song oh
my God I have to think uh it's been so
oh my God I'm so I'm so removed
I don't know if you've had this happen
to you but since you started retubing
you don't keep up with all that stuff as
much as you used to so it's like a lot
of the stuff that I used to be into like
I I'm not really like that's why when
you were naming like current like K-pop
groups I'm just
like ah well with K-pop groups I still
keep up but I got to be really honest I
don't keep up with HP anymore because
all the groups that I was like
supporting are gone now like Betty's
Global cute smiling it's turned into
something else it's cuz we're old
yeah no no I mean I can't blame them
Ben's coobo was like doing their Idol
thing for over 10 years cute as well and
smileage just fell apart too early for
like their own good but do you know
smileage I don't I don't know smileage
that well I'm kind of like have you
heard of them I'm very old school you
don't understand oh but smileage was
like you know the the the newcomer that
everyone was placing their hopes in and
p and they were doing so well but like
immediately after the debut one of their
only four members left and then they
started crumbling and falling apart and
that's where yeah it was already over at
that point somebody was like cing ussd
oh my God don't get me started with
K-pop stuff at Le they came back aren't
you happy they came back I'm happy that
they came back I I'm very very happy I
think they've withstand the test of time
y'all know about the the seven-year
curse over there in Kpop land
oh twice is uh longer than seven is it
are they are they wait how old is twice
oh my God no wait don't hold on I love
twice please wait they they broke the
curse and they're doing really well oh
from 2015
so oh 8 years that's good they broke it
and I mean if any girl group is going to
break it I'm sorry but
twice they're the best what can I say
they're amazing I love them so much I
love too what's your favorite tce
song every
song
yeah but recently I I love all of their
recent releases too but ah I like I like
alcohol free that one was fun because it
was so tropical you know the tropical
song but no I love them all and I'm
thinking if I should go to their concert
cuz right now they have a Europe tour
upcoming what of course you should go
what are you talking about I've never
been to a K-pop concert before and it
kind of scares me oh why why why why why
why I've been to a million HP concerts
and there I just felt like comfortable
because I knew all the coral I knew how
to cheer cheers especially it's
different yeah like it's like so the fan
CH stuff is different think yeah and
they're really easy for HP but I don't
know how to chant for K-pop like no idea
and I feel like I mean okay I can just
watch quietly I guess but then are you
really enjoy I'm sure there has to be
some guides on on the internet somewhere
that have don't have time to learn like
the whole discography of
songs no that's true that's true that's
why you have to go with somebody so that
you don't feel Soo weird you know you go
with a nice group and it's like it's not
that bad if you don't do the
fan well I'm I'm I'm thinking about it I
mean they're always I guess reselling
tickets for people who don't want to go
girl if I was over there I'd go with you
but I can't so oh well yeah and I I'll
find someone maybe and then maybe I'll
go unfortunately they're not coming to
Austria cuz no one ever comes to Austria
no one cares about Austria [\h__\h] everyone
should care about Austria well
especially you with like your Opa
singing skills you must know about the
the the country of classic music Austria
moart yeah I'm I'm besties with moart
you know oh are you yeah I mean he's
dead now but um I used to
be I can't anymore I can't but I I lived
for many thousands of years so I I he
was my best
yeah he's dead that's true you've been
alive a very long time possibly even
longer than
me oh Pro I mean the thing is it's it's
a bit of a shinger cat kind of thing
maybe because I'm a phoenix so my
lifespan isn't even that long often cuz
I die but then I revive so that's true I
haven't been living continuously for
that long I remember but I come back I
remember one time you did your red debut
stream and you yeah you were reborn on
stream I was there in hindsight I'm
happy that happened because um like okay
so for people who don't know this
happened probably like two years ago
pretty much in the beginning and my
channel got just randomly just YouTube
things it just got randomly banned and
it was just gone like not just one video
was gone no the whole channel was gone
and I was remember everybody was
freaking out yeah but uh I I wasn't
freaking out much cuz I I knew I didn't
do anything but so I thought you know
what I'm going to make this into a a
funny thing so once my channel was back
which was soon after I did a redut
stream um I just acted as if it's my
first time and and I made you know a
whole comedian skit about it and I think
yeah everybody said I handled it so well
and and made it into a really enjoyable
Arc and then it hasn't happened in a
long time but after that something like
that did happen
again and I repeated it so I had a
couple debuts by
now just like a phoenix should that's
true every time you
renew yeah and you're reborn I keep on
coming back you can't get me down I'll
keep on coming back I say that I say
that I'm like a cockroach you can't get
rid of me ever I always come back that
disgusting that is disgusting I am
pretty disg I'm so glad we don't have
cockroaches in Austria wait what you
don't how is that possible the climate
the the climate is just different we
don't I mean there might be some hidden
somewhere but I've never seen a
cockroach in Austria
before what they probably exist but they
they don't really you know they're not
really around
they're maybe outside but they don't go
inside Apartments do they have spiders
God spiders yeah I mean no dangerous
spiders we don't have dangerous spiders
oh I hate spiders oh well no problem
don't worry no speeda no speed Exodus to
Austria yeah they're just not uh
cockroaches are not common I remember
like when I lived in Japan M it was
shocking to me when seeing a cockroach
in inside my apartment but even more
shocking was when I had a rat living in
my
house or several I don't even know rats
or mice I don't know in the end what it
was there yeah there's someone called
Casper um it's like a character from the
time when I lived in Japan uh when I
started out in whole life he's this
whole character like I ah okay okay okay
let me tell the story cuz this is you
interviewing me right I should be
telling the story of course sorry to
make that's why you're
here it's about
you yeah it's a bit awkward cuz you're
you're Mouse um but but so um I uh lived
in Japan for like a working holiday at
the time when I joined her life MH and I
I was living in this really really small
uh f walls cheap one room apartment at
the time I joined cuz no money but then
I joined and I realized I can't stream
like this because even when I whisper
the neighbors heard me even when I was
whispering they were banging against the
wall so I was like okay [\h__\h] I have to
move out as soon as I can and for some
connections I was able to pretty quickly
uh secure uh a house for myself which I
thought would be great for streaming cuz
well it's it's it's not connected to any
other houses they're close but they're
not connected and um it was cheap but it
was cheap because it was really ran down
and it was through a connection
but yeah I thought well whatever even if
it's run down like I I won't get
anything better than this right now
because I still don't really have the
funds for it so I moved there pretty
soon after I debuted and first the first
night already I noticed some tap tap tap
tap tap sounds in the
ceiling and it was freaking me out cuz
it wouldn't stop and I I wasn't sure
first what it was and I told my landlord
and uh they sent like some professionals
over I guess and like for months they
would try to get rid of my mice friends
but they never managed to do it
successfully it's seems like they would
open up the ceiling um and put like all
kinds of you know poison traps and all
that up there I'm sorry I'm sorry iron M
but it's okay the worry they tried and
apparently like one of the poisons was
like kind of poison that blinds them uh
and then through that I guess they
somewhat die I guess oh nothing personal
yeah
um I was feeling don't worry you're not
killing me it's fine yeah but your like
not distant family my distant relatives
they deserved it
no but the thing is like no matter what
they did it never ended it never stopped
and they even told me like they wouldn't
even find dead bodies like of them um it
was definitely more than one I think but
they were like somehow immune and what
the heck yeah it was making me cry
was freaking me out and then at some
point I even saw them like running past
me that was freaking me out even more
when I saw them and they ate my
chocolate even though chocolate is
supposed to be poisonous for them but
they ate my German chocolate that I
imported cuz I was missing German and
Austrian like European chocolate they
ate fr the plastic the bubble wrap and
the plastic and the chocolate they ate
all that [\h__\h] they didn't die M
ridiculous
but it was this whole Arc so I
eventually first I I I felt embarrassed
uh about the fact that I had an
infestation of rats or mice in my house
I felt embarrassed about it so I was
talking about them as if they were
ghosts first on stream so that's why I
called them Casper um cuz there's this
ghost called Casper right yeah some star
yeah yeah and eventually I couldn't hide
it anymore and I said you know they're
mice rats or so and they I don't know we
we made it into a funny thing again on
stream and uh I never ended up killing
them eventually I gave up and I just
accepted it and then the funny thing is
when I moved out away from them I felt
sad I felt sorry for all the things I
did to them and I felt sad to not have
them around me anymore
their presence was with you they were
like you had to leave them behind yeah
it was somehow sad you're invisible pets
yeah but yeah that was so sad this whole
character disappeared from my stream
that was part of me and my streams for a
long time especially during a time where
I was struggling a lot cuz my first half
year in whole life was full of struggles
and self-doubt and
problems technical problems and other
problems I don't know yeah so that
really like shaped the Casper was one of
the things that shaped my Beginnings I
would say oh my God that's so sweet it's
so weird though Casper was there for you
yeah during the tough time yeah helping
me out thanks Casper I miss you Casper
if you're out there I hope you regained
your eyesight and made many family
members yeah I'm sure I'm sure they're
in a better place now maybe they
reincarnated as some other
creature who knows so hopefully
something better I mean Sor sorry I must
I mean you know something that I just
not that there's something better than a
mouse um there's a lot of things better
than a
mouse okay okay okay you you you you
admit it okay then then of course I'm
not well technically I'm not really a
mouse it's just my name because where
are your mouse ears anyway oh I have
them hold on
uh [\h__\h]
cute wait I never saw this outfit with
the mouse ears before yeah that's cute a
maybe you make me you make me feel like
I want to poison you you want to poison
me
or maybe I should just eat you cuz right
now I'm a cat if you're if you're going
to poison me put it in the turkey leg so
it tastes good oh yeah okay okay you
won't know yeah yeah yeah let me live
unaware I don't know why I even have
turkey legs cuz I don't even like them
that much I
realized you're not a turkey leg fan no
I thought chicken is way better I like
chicken
too I miss chicken I want to eat chicken
nuggets
nuggies Yum Yum Yum yeah I love
nuggies what's your favorite fast
food
O Okay so from Burger King I love with
my life I have this one two go Burger
it's the uh crispy chicken oh I love but
I noticed it's different in some
countries uh in Japan the crispy chicken
was called crispy chicken but it wasn't
the crispy chicken it was completely
different than what they have in Europe
um the crispy chicken is a long one
right no that's a long
chicken the crispy chicken is pretty
small but the thing is the the breading
is like with I think something like corn
flakes or
so which makes really
crispy oh tempora batter no not really
no oh not quite what kind of crispy then
it's a really good crispie I think I
think it might be in America got to they
might they should I think they have I
think so bro I love long
chicken yeah long chicken was my first
lover and then after a while the crispy
chicken appeared and that was my my true
love Yeah but uh like if we if
we talk about
non like not specifically like a company
like a
brand terms of fast
generally I think I eat a lot of pizza
though I love
pizza pizza yeah Pizza did you say pizza
yes I said
Pizza Pizza yeah Pizza yeah that's
exactly how you pronounce it yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah that is how I
pronounce English isn't my first
language well mine NE but piz English
Spanish is my first language we
pronounce it pizza oh really yeah oh
pizza oh okay well then that makes sense
yeah oh vamos vamos
Pizza
Pizza you're cute when you speak Spanish
you like it I like it people say it
sound
funny no cuz I I talk like a different
like so I'm from Puerto Rico so like my
Spanish is like I in Spanish Puerto Rico
Puerto Rico that's so cool you speak
German right yes
Al in Spanish German is
Alan German the word German is Alan yeah
oh Al
Al
men I know I
what did you
say I love you too yeah
yeah I think you said something bad but
[Laughter]
okay no why would
[Music]
I well that's so cool I sounds so cool
man I I I was hoping oping to learn
Spanish eventually that was like my plan
at some point but and I never had like
the the proper like Drive someone needs
to push me to do it now I'm learning
Korean Korean is going better cuz I I
have like more motivation to do it but
Spanish is so cool you can do dual
lingual no [\h__\h] dual lingo I hate dual
linga yeah dinga sucks you can't learn
the language of dualingo you know that
sucks balls only maybe guess it's like a
support mechanism or so but I I'll help
you learn Spanish
slowly but it won't be good Spanish you
say that but you know everybody always
makes empty promises and I'm sick of
them I'm sick of them oh my god do you
get empty promises too me too all the
time yeah everybody this it's just life
is society is filled of empty promises
it's true people promise things to you
all the time they say they're going to
do XYZ and it never happens
yeah you know so many uh whole life
members promis me tell me that they are
going to come to visit me in Austria and
they never [\h__\h] do what except Callie
you know Callie is the only one who has
visited me here cuz she is the real
homie she is a real one that's true mhm
that's very true yeah if I could travel
I would come and see you because I've
always wanted to go to Austria uh-huh
really really really yeah but I can't
travel on on your top one country it's
not my top one country but I've always
wanted to go there because of the
musical history thank
you you would you would enjoy it we have
like there's like big classic music
festivals every year in Easter and and
in summer and so on all because of my
love of Opera that's that's what drives
me to want to go there you should
perform here I would love to perform
there one day no aora aora concert aora
you should no you should just come up to
the mountains I I'll bring you the
mountain yeah and then sing about ad in
Opera version I've always wanted to
learn how to
Yodo what Yodo yeah you Yodo I don't
know I want to learn so bad somebody
offered to teach me and I want to learn
who offered you oh there's there's a
there's a wonderful Korean uh singer and
streamer named Charming Joe and he knows
how to Yodo and he said that he'll teach
me how to Yodo I don't know but he does
it so
good I think it goes you know
like something like that I don't know
you sound pretty good what the heck
you say you don't know but you sound
pretty good I just you know just the
Vibes just just picking up the Vibes I I
like I like The Vibes you know what if I
learn I'll I'll I'll show you what I
learned okay and it won't be an empty
promise I swear okay it better not be
swear on Mouse
ears okay you don't seem to care much
for them cuz you take them off so
much I like how honest you are it's so
wonderful it's very refreshing
thank you what mousi on that
note you need to bring up the questions
now otherwise we don't have time for the
questions oh my God wait we've been
talking oh my
God a a good talk show host should keep
track of the time you know what you need
to teach me because I've watched your
talk show and it's so good it's like
very professional but I'm very
unprofessional I'm not organized I'm
scatterbrained and I I know that I'm
scatter brain and I know that I'm very
unorganized it's part of my charm okay
it's okay and I also see this kind of as
like a twitch style to take things you
know slow yeah yeah we're like really
laid back over here you know I really
need somebody like you in my life to get
my [\h__\h]
together first
question well okay what country has the
best bread and why is it
Germany what this is insulting what
no I I don't know why it says
specifically Germany I think we in
Europe have great bread uh and Austria
very much too did you know that uh
croissant qu come from Austria is that
where Quant are from apparently yeah I
thought you know people think probably
it's from France but no turns out
they're from Austria I thought they were
from France yeah I thought so too
wow so that that tells you we know a
thing or two about bread we have good
bread oh my God that means your bread is
awesome yeah one thing I really missed
in when I lived in Japan was like uh
European or Austrian style bread because
like there's this thing for example
called shat which is like the darker
bread shat it's yeah it's kind of like
healthy bread I guess I don't eat it
that much but sometimes I felt like
eating it and in in Japan if you want to
get that kind of bread you have to go to
like really expensive stores and you get
like three tiny slices of that bread for
like 10 bucks or so oh oh my God which
is insane it's like what what because
normally they don't do this kind of
bread in
Japan bread I mean yeah here you could
get a you could get 10 loaves for that
money well Japan is good bread too but
like different bread I've only had like
my favorite kind of bread is Cuban Bread
have you ever eaten Cuban
bread Cuban yeah Cuban bread
Cuban you need to you need to you need
to have some Cuban bread wait c u b a n
yes oh from Cuba yeah from Cuba what's
Cuban bread like it's so good it's like
M how can I explain it it's very soft in
the middle and nice and crunchy on the
outside oh I just Googled it it looks
like a buet yeah but it's super soft on
the inside well baguettes are also super
stuff and need
some it's just a
bagette it's different though cuz it's
made out of like it's made out of um
it's made out of
lard
lard okay it's it's a little different I
don't know I know it it
it you might be a little apprehensive an
idian but I promise you it tastes really
good no I would definitely 100% eat it
but it's not something that you should
eat all the time since it's all
lard oh L lard yeah like Lord is
like fat
yummy
what'ss L how the [\h__\h] do you make bread
out of Schmitz I thought Schmitz was
something you put on the bread like we
literally have bread uh like topped with
with lard I don't know I'm not really
sure uh how that works how How It's Made
oh
God are we lagging am I lagging no it's
it's me it's me my internet is going
crazy oh God I'm so sorry oh it's okay
and I I noticed like you cutting off a
little bit voice I told you my my uh
yournet [\h__\h] it's bad it's so bad I'm I
I well I moved it's just I'm I'm I'm uh
I'm getting my Internet fixed who so Z
internet is what they called it wait
what but are we live now yeah we are we
are we are we are now okay we are we are
let's go next question M we got to get
oh God next question
sorry oh what is your favorite part
about anime
convention for me and I think austri or
like European conventions are very
different from American conventions I
saw a lot of American conventions
they're like at in in hotels and like a
lot of it just happens inside uh for us
I feel like we have a lot of conventions
that are like right next to huge parks
and Gardens and we all like to chill
outside most of the time um so for me
it's like just meeting friends but I
think okay that is probably same for
most people just meeting friends cuz my
closest friend Circle they're all
convention people and we don't meet up
much outside of conventions cuz no time
time passes by so fast and then another
convention comes up but it's so fun I
love also like road trips to conventions
in the car really long trips really fun
you can sing K-pop in the
car no we would probably do J-pop yeah
Jpop in the car to fit the mood like
anime songs to to Get Hype for the
convention yeah who I always want I've
never been to a convention well in
person in person oh yeah yeah you've
been like driving around on an iPad
right yeah only on the iPad like as a
tour I've never been like in one like
right there oh yeah it's it's probably
definitely
different I want to visit an American
convention I've never been to one that
would be interesting yeah you totally
should someday like a big big big one
like uh ComicCon or
a ComicCon scary I want to go to ax but
ax also scary ax too big it's really big
it's really big so intimidating and over
whelming I heard last year there was so
many people that like the air was like
bad yeah and and because that was in the
middle of the sea thing I think like I
know people who went to uh it and then
came back sick so maybe especially
because the air is bad and probably you
know so many people oh my God I had to I
was like the sea thing and then I was
like oh the sea thing the sea thing the
sea thing the sea thing next question
next question oh aside from wait
SAS sash s s s Saha cake can you
recommend some nice Austrian
desserts I just like two days ago had a
dream about one that's how much I'm
craving it uh or actually one day ago
maybe um it's called kaisar
Ka translated to the emperor's mess as
I've just learned thanks to a fire
emblem um kaash is basically easily
described uh as like you know scrambled
pancakes but it's not just that it's
more special than that it tastes more
special than that it's like huge you
make you have this this huge frying pan
right you fill it up with the the the
liquid for the for the being and then
you wait a bit until it's becoming you
know uh not liquid and then you start
scrambling it and there's like you I
think you throw I never made it myself
but I think you throw in a lot of sugar
and then you know it becomes really
yummy and then it's really simple in
theory but then you eat it with either
Roa or apple MSE and it's so yummy so
good good dessert oh man I want to I
want to eat it ta yeah and you know we
have a lot of other desserts too I think
Austria you know we we have our own
Foods um but mostly because we're in the
middle of Europe Central Europe
surrounded by a lot of countries like
Hungary Germany Etc Italy we like adopt
a lot of their cooking but when it comes
to desserts I think Austria comes up
with a lot of desserts like Saka cake
and then app Str uh stuff like that Ka
are a lot of your desserts like tastries
and stuff yeah I think I think so like
apple strle apple strle apple strle
apple
strle
yeah oh gam nood gam that's not the past
but we also have this called gam noodle
which is oh oh let me it's better if I
Google English
uh English explanation jamp noodle is a
is a fluffy yeast dough dumpling filled
with spiced plum jam and served with
melted butter and a mix of poppy seeds
and sugar on top and usually it's like
swimming in the hot vanilla
sauce that sounds so good what this [\h__\h]
is incredible especially if you go
skiing which we austrians like to do
very much when we go skiing you know up
on the mountains we have like all these
uh like like huts with yummy food that
serve food that you should eat on a
mountain such as this gam Noodle and
it's like it it gets like a million
times better when you eat it in the
[\h__\h] cold outside and your skiing
clothes on the mountain outside it's so
nice I've never been skiing in my life
uh it's it's it's dangerous I me and
Cali went skiing in Japan together in
Hokkaido and I [\h__\h] crashed and
almost broke something oh no that fun oh
is it hard to ski is it hard to learn
how to ski or
no I I guess it's not that hard but
somehow as even though I'm Austrian I
struggle with it I shouldn't struggle
with it cuz it should be in my blood but
yeah I want to learn one day it's it's
scary but also it's fun I like winter
sports I've seen people do a lot of
skiing and I've watched people ski uh on
TV and like on streams and it always
looks so much fun I wish I could I've
never been in snow ever I've never even
seen it in front of my face M what wait
wa you say you're from Puerto Rico yeah
there's no snow there but right now
you're in America I'm in I'm in uh you
can't say yeah I'm in I'm in hell okay
okay okay okay okay but I guess there's
no snow there there is no snow here
ooh that's sad w we have uh always snow
we have four seasons and winter comes
usually with snow I mean not So Much
Anymore these years but there is snow
definitely on the mountains and like
Austria is known for being [\h__\h] at like
sports like soccer and so on but the one
thing that we usually in like Olympic
Games and so on win something is winter
sports that's the one thing that we can
get something
with oh because you guys are so
acclimated to snow yeah we grew up with
it and so we have a lot of pros at it in
Austria oh do you know how to ice
skate oh yeah yeah I know I know I mean
I can't do fancy tricks but I
can normally move around yeah is the one
into ice skate it's so beautiful it is
oh man I I don't don't worry like I
can't do those fancy trucker but I
understand like looking at them looking
at people do it makes you wish you could
do it right I I wish I could do it too I
wish I could do it too I always wanted
to learn but uh I just you know uh my
mom told me it was too
dangerous too dangerous she said it was
too dangerous for me to to learn and
that I would hurt
myself well you would probably indeed
hurt yourself if you tried I I probably
would because I'm not very uh I'm not
I'm not that good at being coordinated
in
[Music]
movement well no pain no gain that's
true gamer
words next question next question ah I'm
learning if either of you have seen
clips of each other what was one that
you think
about oh I feel like you know since
you're on Twitch um I don't see so much
of you yeah but I do like something see
like some clips of you and Connor and
then you doing opera singing and then I
always see like you keep on changing
your outfits and your designs and all
that I'm like what she's got another one
what she's got another one what she's
got another one what what what what D
crazy crazy you don't only change
outfits you change your whole like like
uh like style of like art style and
that's so cool like I like the current
one there very much oh thank you I'm GL
I'm GL like it very cute
a the the one that sticks in my mind was
the one that I recently saw was the one
with you and
[Music]
coron are you do you check stuff on TW
uh on on on YouTube I go I go on YouTube
from time to time not as much as I would
like because you know the whole uh work
and stuff but
oh Nar well if you want some digestible
content I may have a lot of long streams
but I also try to upload some shorts and
and like like some of my own clips and
so on on my channel not many but there
are some so also for people who are
like maybe I'll give Ki a chance I saw
you know what I did see I so for me like
I don't really like watch sometimes okay
so
don't I I I I I lur in people's streams
okay cuz sometimes I'll be in my room
just be like I just want to watch a
vtuber and I'll just like look so I've
seen I've seen a couple of your streams
I saw your uh your new outfit debut when
you did the German debut stream that you
did okay I mean that's um over half a
year ago I know I want that one and
then it's hard
nowadays I feel like the more time that
passes the less time I have oh that's
that's sad I hope you can make more free
time for yourself I would love to I
think now that I'm that uh I have moved
I think that uh I'll have more time oh
okay um but one thing I wanted to say is
like for people who are like just
getting into me and they're maybe a
little bit intimidated by like memes and
so on or things that I mentioned that
they don't know what the [\h__\h] I'm
talking about I have this series called
kfp 101 um where we explain uh in like
like maximum 10 minute videos uh
whatever the thing is so we have one on
Casper we have one on the usual room Etc
yeah so I think it's good to get an
understanding of kiaha and our culture
and and don't be intimidated uh because
people people always say KF is a very
welcoming um community and and very
sweet and very open to help anyone
so11 on my channel you're so Prof you're
so professional and organized and you
really know how to like Market
yourself thank you I do I these are very
good
qualities thank you you also Market
yourself very well no I'm not I'm not
organized I don't I'm a train
wreck you're you're Prof you're
absolutely professional it's it's very
inspiring I know you too no no you no
you no I mean I mean yeah I think I
think from what I've seen you seem
professional to
me next question
we're entertainers you know so being a
train wreck is entertaining on its own
that's true that's true everybody loves
a train wreck I don't like to watch
people who are like I don't know
suffering I
guess maybe they feel you like to watch
me suffer thank
you like suffering in games and all that
you know especially when you you're
acting kind of stupid and then you feel
like you're more intelligent than the
streamer so that makes you feel better
about yourself maybe who knows you know
what I think that's the experience I
offer to everybody everybody that
watches me they're way smarter than me
and when they watch me play a game
they're like ah yes I'm not as dumb as
her thank goodness Jesus isn't that a
relief yeah yeah that's a service that
not everybody can
provide but I can I I got some of that
too yeah don't worry it's fine we all
stupid no no no you're not stupid oh my
God long one W this is very long hi
Mousie hi kiaha you've both been doing
Ving for a while now I wanted to ask you
both if you could share a positive
experience or moment from your time as
vtubers so far something that you will
still remember and makes you happy when
you look back on it happy you are
finally doing this thank you for
everything girl sending you both a lot
of love
oh positive experience
all right I'll start for me oh man of
course there's many but uh if I had to
think of one now I think it would
be like having finally after a long time
uh in the internet doing stuff you know
uh finally having an audience for it for
what I do and being appreciated for it
uh like you know for singing and
entertaining and all that kind of stuff
for existing in the first place yeah cuz
I I felt like I was always working
towards something in my life uh and and
and I mean I'm very
tenacious but I've I've been struggling
I've been thinking oh this is never
going to get go somewhere because it's
just I just don't see anything coming
back from how much I put into it the
success that I would hope to get is
never
coming I don't see it so I was
struggling a lot with that but now I
finally see the reward for struggling
for so long having a an audience that
listens to me gladly and will come to
see me in conventions and events to
support me will cheer for me will listen
to my music and listen to my talking and
watch my streams endlessly and that's
just
finally yeah I feel appreciated and like
I have a purpose and I don't feel like a
failure anymore oh my God no you're not
bro you were making me tear up I'm not
kidding I'm I felt like a failure so
many times in life and now finally I've
I guess to understand I made it to a
decent point I completely understand
you're not a failure though but I I
completely understand because I I know
what it's like to feel like a failure
and I know what it's like to uh try
really hard to work towards something
you just feel like you're not getting
anywhere and you feel like nothing's
ever going to happen or nothing's going
to come of something and I can I ask
like how long did it take you to like
kind of I guess what would you say break
out like break make the break to become
like you know somewhat popular it's a
weird question to ask but like how long
did it take you as iron M oh I started
streaming in
2017 and I didn't start growing until
after the pandemic started so in 2020 oh
yeah it took time it took quite a while
but like when I started like I didn't
really like I didn't really think about
getting like famous or anything like I
wouldn't be honest I just started
streaming because I was really
lonely uh and I didn't really have
anybody to talk to because
uh so in real life I have a uh medical
condition uh that uh is an immune system
disease so I can't really be around
people a lot I can't really be around
too many people and uh because of the
fact that I was struggling uh and uh I'm
I'm living with my parents uh it was
hard for me to get proper medical
attention and um I was very very sick
before I became a vtuber like it it got
very bad where it was just like I just
thought um I'm never going to work again
I'm never going to do anything I'm never
going to do anything in my life and I
just thought you know hopefully I could
make friends online and maybe talk to
somebody and uh maybe just you know
enjoy what I can here in my house and
then uh I started really liking the
streaming and I really started liking V
tubing a lot and I I I had like 5 to 10
people watching me I think the maximum
amount that I ever got was 2020 in
January for my birthday was like 50
people watching me so it wasn't until
like the
summer the summer of like the pandemic
to like September of the pandemic in
2020 that I started growing like a lot
and that's when I was like made what
happened there uh was it just the
pandemic or did you then start V tubing
like cuz before you probably weren't
like moving like this right no no before
it was like really small and uh I I I
would just come on I would also I was
like really sick so I could only stream
for like one to two hours I couldn't
stream for long hours because I was like
not well and then I met uh my friend
Melody and I met a couple of other
streamers I met uh silver Veil and I met
uh uh Zen and I met the people that
became vjo and we all started streaming
together and started growing I guess it
was like half of like uh the pandemic
and everybody being home or I don't
really know I just know that I just all
of a sudden people just started watching
me and I think also because like I made
friends in the community and like we all
just started supporting each other a lot
so we all grew and then I think what
made the growth even more like impactful
was when the show Joo started and like
everything just started picking up like
a lot and yeah I think I could feel that
yeah and then like I started making
money which I never made money before
and then I was like oh I could pay for
this and that and I could do this and
and now I'm here now I'm a little bit
healthier still going through some stuff
but it's it's much better now and uh
it's crazy for me to think that like a
few years ago I was just not I was just
a girl just talking to avoid you
know yeah
I I know how difficult that can be when
you're just trying for a long time and
nobody's really
[Music]
watching but finally finally all the
like struggling and and working hard has
been rewarded yeah cuz like it was hard
for me because so before I did the you
know I told you like I got sick and
stuff but like before that like I was
trying to become an opera singer and
that was like my dream like I wanted to
sing opera I wanted to do to be on stage
that was my dream and then I got ill and
I had to just stop everything and I had
to stop going to school and it was just
like I was like oh my God my life is
over and then V tubing happened I was
like well um I'll just enjoy whatever
and now it's like I'm living my life
again nice I hope it helps you I hope
that you get like the fun and and
satisfaction a great and I'm happy that
I can meet incredible people like
you and your story is inspiring too you
know well I can't tell you all the
details about it unfortunately cuz a lot
happened before my life but you know
that's okay that's okay you
know but yeah whole life definitely
rescued me from a situation where I felt
like it was over like ah maybe I should
give up and nothing's going to happen
but yeah here here I am and things have
improved greatly and turned out for the
better for
me thank you Hol life thank I'm really
grateful for hollow life for doing that
for
you me too me too you deserve
happiness you deserve goodness and
happiness you know that right oh thank
you you too you too favorite red hair
wfu well I'm talking red hair as like
you know what we see in real life as red
hair like which is actually orange or do
we talk about red red hair H I don't
know they didn't specify so we could say
either one okay well if it's orange then
it's obviously
me yes no but I guess I think one of the
most popular answer would be uh ASA Lang
oh ASA yeah she's cool she she's
redhaired yeah I guess redhaired in the
orange way
and then uh for me like red red
hair one I can think of is for Tang Yoko
oh she's cool big
lady and not an anime but from Ark
Knights okay I guess they have an anime
now but from Ark Knights Su is such a
hot red hair chick oh yes oh my God I
haven't played or nights in so long
oh me NE but I I still follow it which
one is your Wu right is urza Scarlet
from fairy tale oh I see it yeah she's
she's amazing well I'm surpris I'm
surprised people know s people know what
of course everybody's a wee here wow
yeah but like Ares
wow
nice well I have a favorite red-haired
husband
oh oh he's he's a Aya from UT no
Prince I don't know that one either it's
like a uh a idol anime
game I see Idol idol
stuff I see okay I have the husbands
only Wes yeah yeah yeah only wife sorry
I'm sorry I brought up that subject my
bad no no problem no
problem okay next one next one next one
oh Kara how does it feel to be living in
the country of Europe
lasta no but seriously though what is it
like living in Austria and does it
differ from other countries you visited
SL other members of Hall life reside
in yeah Europe is a continent and
Austria is a country the middle of it
with the capital of Vienna just to bring
it out there for people who don't know
if there are
any um
well how is how does it feel to live
here I feel like it's very nice I mean I
couldn't really imagine living in most
other places outside of Europe uh except
for maybe Japan because I've lived there
before and I know the language and it
feels very convenient cuz many things
are very convenient in Japan but at the
same time the reason I chose to not live
there anymore is just because I I never
felt like truly like I
truly feel comfortable there uh I don't
know there's like many factors like that
make it difficult to live in Japan as a
foreigner so I chose to go back to
Austria also because of my cats and all
that but oh just you know in your own
country in the end you feel most
comfortable because you know how to do
things you know how to adult how to
function as an adult in your own country
and I think our our laws and all that
are pretty
decent I mean currently our gas prices
and [\h__\h] like that is apparently really
expensive and our red prices are also
[\h__\h] expensive um and I pay a [\h__\h]
ton of taxes to Austria cuz we are one
of the highest ones I think in in in
Europe um so that's not so nice
um it's not perfect but I'm pretty
decently happy here I think I don't
think I could imagine living in America
for example I'm sorry guys it's it's
it's a different experience I think I
think it takes some getting used to if
you're not used to probably I mean I'll
gladly visit because at least I can
speak the language but living sounds
very difficult I don't even want to like
realistically speaking moving to a
continent that's so far away that's the
reason why I didn't bring my cats to
Japan for that one year
cuz that's rough and O sounds very
challenging I have so much Furniture
here and all that it's just unrealistic
but I don't know if I want to live in
Austria forever though because it's it
might get boring but I don't know I
don't know where would you where would
you
go that's a good question I don't know
but I think think the good thing is
about living in Europe is that you can
so quickly and so cheaply visit nearby
like any other European country here
there's like really cheap flights you
can like fly over to Greece to beach a
nice Beach really fast you can go to
Spain Italy uh everywhere so quickly so
I think if I just live in Austria
forever I'll be happy because whenever I
feel like leaving and seeing a different
different place I just I'll just jump
into a plane and immediately it will
take me to another nice place so that's
a really good thing about Europe yeah I
mean I can even go to Italy by car or or
Hungary or Switzerland for that no it
doesn't matter I could go anywhere by a
car and fury if I had a license but um
everything's so close by you know oh you
also do not have a
license yay I do not have one either
that's fine you don't we don't need a
license let's be driven around instead
yeah yeah yeah yeah we don't need to
learn how to drive e oh yeah Croatia too
H there's just lot of great places in
Europe well so one more question yeah hi
ki do you exercise to stay healthy you
are an incredible singer love you from
Argentina Argentina thank you m
H I do not
exercise I should because it's making me
probably very unhealthy I should
[Music]
though thanks for the
reminder I don't want to be reminded
though I mean next question yeah yeah
yeah let's just move on to the next
question oh you traveled and visited
many countries Nations during your time
in hollow life such as mald
South Korea Indonesia and Italy do you
have any deciding factors when
determining the places you plan on
visiting um I feel like all of these I
went for different reasons uh
but I just um currently I'm trying to
make many dreams come true like mold for
was for example a dream come true cuz
it's such a it's an expensive
destination
that yeah I would have probably never
been able to go to if it wasn't for
whole life uh but yeah making my dreams
come true and then for Indonesia for
example I just wanted to meet all the ID
Girls and Italy Italy I went to like
recently because I wanted to um see Rome
for the first time cuz I never saw Rome
what the [\h__\h] and I wanted to bring my
mom cuz she has been on a trip for many
many years and so I invited her to come
with me because she loves Italy Rome was
possibly out of all the countries and
places I've visited so far the most
impressive Place have ever seen mousy so
did you go to that Rome thingy the
Coliseum yeah the Coliseum and then
there's like these these ruins and [\h__\h]
oh my God it's like insane everywhere
you look it's incredible everywhere you
look there's something fancy
old and whatever it's really cool all
the structures I love old
buildings it's incredible I mean in
australa we have a lot of old buildings
too but Rome is like next level it's
crazy that must have been so beautiful
to see in
person you can someday I'm sure one day
I hope to don't give up dreaming I will
never stop
dreaming I stopped dreaming one time
I'll never do it again okay that's good
good like I mean I don't know you're
real you're act I don't you know I don't
I don't know what
what I don't know you're age I don't
know how long you're expecting to live
and all that but you know I think you
know you got time don't give up I'm
pretty old I'm 6,000 something years old
you know yeah but I mean like 6,000 out
of out of what that's maybe just a small
number 6,000 may just be a small number
that's true that's true for mice
I'm an ancient
Mouse you're going to become more
ancient I'm sure so I'll be I'll be an
old grandma
vtuber Yeah you you'll come over to
Europe and I I'll you know cuz that's
the good thing about having every
country bordering another we can do a
road trip for all the countries yeah
that would be so cool yeah and the
mountains the Mountain I love the
mountains I hate them cuz climbing up is
a pain in the ass oh do you not like the
the the altitude of mountains with the
ears and
climbing
um I I I don't think I've ever
experienced that anyway cuz I have I
ever I don't think I've been high enough
to experience that I mean I've been
skiing and all that but I never
experienced like the altitude being a
problem there before my ears are so we
have mountains in Puerto
Rico but I don't think they're as tall
as the mountains over there I don't know
I could be
wrong maybe not I don't I don't know
either I don't want to underestimate
your
mountains could be good mountains
there's there's some pretty good
mountains we have a special we have a
special
Mountain it's it's very
unique and there are two mountains that
are really tall and they're side by side
to each other and people call them
boobies
next question I was listening seriously
to you m no I'm serious that's the name
of them oh you're not talking about your
own no I'm I'm 100% serious they're
Callas like or
something or
something see people know what I'm
talking about it's true they're two
booby shaped mountains side visit Puerto
Rico one day Mousie yeah I think you
like it it's really nice is do is there
a nice Beach there's a beautiful beach
all around and there's a rainforest it's
a Caribbean Island
yeah holy macaroni let's go there's a
rainforest and there's like this big
waterfall and you can jump off of it and
everything oh she and there's a lake I
would be scared to do that but it looks
pretty there's a lake that like when the
sun I was going to say when the Sun
turns
off when the Sun goes down when the Sun
goes down the lake glows cuz there's
bioluminescent uh creatures in the water
oh
fancy wow got some fancy [\h__\h] there
damn I'm going to put it on my bucket
list yeah
definitely I'll be I'll be in Puerto
Rico one day wait for me I will wait for
[Music]
youto
Rico oh you really your are is good
thank you you're really good cuz I'm a
cat I know question mous do you want do
you want to answer one or two more
before you leave yes speed speed round
okay speed
round oh you receive a lot of fan art in
projects is there any form of fan art
you want to see more
of uh just more art please we always
love more art more art I need more art
more more more I'm going to be honest
like it definitely slowed down since
like the beginning of uh you know when
everything was hype hype hype so more
art please more more yeah more please
now next
question oh hello there from the land
down under Kiara as a fan and as a
content creator myself I feel like this
question should be asked more often but
I absolutely must know how have you been
lately anything funny or cool happened
to you recently how is life well mousey
since when a speed run round I I can't I
can't tell the whole story but like a
couple days ago police came to my
apartment while I was gone uh it was
freaking me out but if you want to know
more look up the kiar police clip on
YouTube oh my God I'm going to Google it
I'm gonna go on YouTube and I'm gon to
look for it definitely clipped yeah
oh my God they called me like I was gone
and they called me from my apartment and
like where are you so if you want to
know more um
yeah oh God that sounds terrifying
what okay well I'll I'll ask you like
two more and then and then your viewers
and fans call you nicknames such as the
gamer of Ian the game finisher of Ian
how did you change as a gamer since
becoming a
vtuber oh I think I I am a better gamer
now than I was in the beginning I would
say I mean I'm still not that good at
least not in the beginning when I
started a new game but I think I'm
generally like better at gaming now um
um yeah like many games that I tackled
before a whole life in the past like
near
utata oh my God I wasn't did you play it
before I gave up at the beginning cuz I
got so frustrated me too me too I never
got past the tutorial because it's so
mean like when you die at that boss that
lets you go past the tutorial then you
have to start from the very beginning
again from the tutorial it's pretty long
and there's like no checkpoint or so
that's so mean and so I never did it and
then I started streaming and I I played
Neato on stream and then I I was fine
and I finished it the whole game as well
oh my God so yeah I got over hurdles the
one hurdle I will never overcome is
Super Mario 64 oh
is it is Super Mario
[Music]
64 the one thing that scares me is Super
Mario 64 why why is it
scary it's just so rage inducing you
know it's
hard I hate it no I love it but I also
hate it I love it I wish I could play it
well I see I see rage inducing
it's next question okay okay next
question next
question for you what is the hardest
most difficult part of being a
[Music]
vtuber interesting I think a lot of
things are made easier thanks to being a
vtuber cuz I don't have to do my makeup
and stuff for streaming stuff like that
you know but what what's more difficult
Maybe I mean
[Music]
generally I feel like what makes me wish
I wasn't sometimes is like when we uh
perform in in a concert or at
conventions or do meet and greets and
stuff like that I wish I could like
actually be there oh yeah and see it
with my own eyes and I mean you can TR
most likely relate to that yeah I can
not only because of your like spe
specific reasons but I think generally
that's a vtuber thing too yeah to a
certain extent um and it it's just like
certain things that I wish I could
experience like real really really
really in real life in real real real
life for real for real
to me too yeah that's so that's kind of
sad because it gives it it it takes
something away from how special things
should be
yeah you know it's hard because
especially I feel like lately uh a lot
of conventions have been happening and
I've seen a lot of like um Indie vtubers
go to the convention and go in person
and meet them and I I feel like I'm like
man they're so lucky that they could do
that I wish I could do that too yeah
yeah like okay you you can't do it for
your own reasons and then whole life
well we can't do it cuz we're Coro and
there's certain I can't just go there
and say hi I am Ki I can't do that so
yeah it's hard some some rules have to
be there in place and and be protected
to yeah to have a system yeah I I
understand fine I get the system it's
fine yeah I I accept it but you know
it's just a one thing that it's a little
bit sad but it's okay I totally get it I
totally get it I feel like I'm also kind
of like a a oldfashioned type vtuber
because to me like I this is the type of
youtubing that like I'm used to and like
I'm good with I I I feel like uh the
Indies Indie people like it's it's great
for them and I think that's amazing but
like to me uh as much as I wish I could
and and I can't but it's like it's I
don't know it's it's like different
styles you know what I mean yeah yeah I
see apprciate differ yeah there's
different types of
YouTubers that's for sure yeah and then
sometimes you know I envy the Indies
sometimes but then other times I'm like
I'm glad I'm in Holo you know there's
good time good sides and bad sides or so
I guess like you know yeah there's pros
and cons
everything yeah so that's okay next one
maybe last one yes last one last
one oh how do you think you've improved
compared to your early Hol live days
that might be a good question to end it
on
nice um yeah so people know I struggled
a lot in the beginning had like bad
microphone had lots of technical issues
cuz I was like moving and then I had no
internet for a month and had to stream
and live from my manager's place for a
month uh yeah and then I was um always
like behind on my gender mates and made
me doubt myself and um doubt my like the
way I do things and all that but at the
same time I I wanted to believe in the
way I do things like uh in the beginning
I thought that you know my language
skills are maybe the one thing that set
me apart so I wanted to use those um to
my advantage and I got criticized a lot
for it for speaking Japanese a little
bit uh every once in a while on my
stream um and I I still want to do
something with that though so that's how
I eventually came up with Holo talk um
and I may not talk as much Japanese in
my streams anymore as I did in the
beginning um but I still use it for
stuff like whole talk and I think I'm
doing something good for whole life with
that and I found my place in whole life
that's for sure like I I I feel think
have come to settle down and and it's
just more comfortable now I don't feel
so stressed about every single thing
anymore I don't have so many technical
issues anymore and I think I'm settled
you know I don't know it's hard to say
why how but time has passed it's been
two and a half years more than that
and that's
like everything's chill now and I think
I guess m maybe maybe I've improved a
little bit in terms of like how
I stream in general but I think I've
always been a good Entertainer like I've
always been good at Tangen thing and all
that um so I never doubted myself about
that
but no you're also very consistent all
the time oh yeah I try to be I try to be
that's like I I feel like I always there
there's part of me that feels like I
always need to catch up and and I feel
keep on consistently bringing content
because I don't want to lag behind I
don't want to fall
behind uh so like I'm always running a
marathon you know that's why I I stream
so much and stream so long and
consistently yeah and and take very good
care of my community because I cherish
them I value them I love them and I
thank them every day for being there for
me and believing in me giving me a
chance
when many others didn't
so yeah and I I definitely got more
confidence there was like the first year
was rough for me in terms of confidence
I was uh crying a lot and struggling a
lot but now now I'm pretty uh like
stable I would say you're so strong holy
moly thank you there's still some stuff
happening behind the scenes that is
really rough to deal with um um yeah
especially oh like one thing I think I
wanted to say as uh that was difficult
as a vtuber is like because you're
like kind of um not really hiding but
like you're you're not showing a lot of
yourself right and that makes
people like want to try even harder to
find out the things that you're not
saying and not showing so they will
invade your privacy even more yeah and
and that's like really difficult to deal
with for vtubers I think um many issues
arise from that and yeah and that's
that's a struggle too but besides that
um I think I've I've I've come to a
place where I really can confidently
enjoy my job and and be stable and uh
cherish every day yes every day is a
gift every day yeah it's so fun and I'm
so happy that I got this job um because
it as I said it saved me from a really
difficult position situation and I don't
want to give it up ever I want to
continue I still have like many many
goals right now I'm working on an album
uh to be released in the summer yeah
aome yeah I want to make I I want to do
more 3D performances cuz like one
problem we had we may have gotten a
boost from debuting during the pandemic
but on the other side that kept us from
doing a frd deut for a long long long
time uh and I feel like that kind of
stunted some things so um now that we
finally had our frd debut in February I
hope that we can do much much more
things in 3D uh in from now on and
that's what I'll be working on and
trying to uh improve and and yeah and
more songs like fever Knight cuz 80s
Vibes oh you like fever KN it was so
good I love that thank you fite is very
unappreciated song of mine I like it but
then again I really like that old like
all the Retro Style songs and yeah yeah
I actually that makes sense yeah I know
you
do fite is uh close to 1 million by the
way on YouTube if you guys want to give
it a listen I think you guys can stream
it she's super super
close you so close to 1 million wow
please oh I'm so happy that you came to
talk to me I don't want to take up too
much more of your time cuz I know you're
busy I know it's late I would love to
talk more but yeah maybe we should have
started earlier
cuz known we should have known that
we're going to talk long don't worry we
we could maybe we could play a game
sometime soon and we can talk more oh
yeah sure we can play GTA online
oh I wonder how that would turn out to
be I would totally do that I swear oh my
God I'll download it and I'll install it
just for you let's
gos fun than you so much for having me
usually I'm the the interviewer so it's
nice to be on the on the couch for once
yeah you got to take a break sometime
you know you work so
hard I mean I don't I don't consider
this as a break cuz I'm still working
right now that's
true I'm working right now but it was
fun thank you you're very easy to talk
to oh no thank you you're easy to talk
to too I was so nervous when I was going
to talk to you cuz I was like oh my
God what do I even
say it just flows naturally doesn't it
it's fine yeah it does I think I think
it also helps because it's like you I
feel like you're also extroverted so
it's very it it's just easy that's what
people think I'm just a good talker I'm
just uh very good in Social
situ n I'm not extroverted I just hate I
just hate awkward situations so I I I
try to save it but I I hate actually I I
I don't like being around people my
social battery drains really fast I I do
it to not be rude and all that an
introvert and extrovert interesting
yeah social introvert yeah yeah that
makes a lot of sense oh thank thank you
for coming on my show please everyone
follow k please uh shout out anything
you would like to shout out if you'd
like well uh yeah well just uh stream
favorite night I
guess and feel free to check me out on
YouTube I may not be on Twitch but it's
very comfy in my in my streams too and
uh there's some clips maybe if you want
to you know have some appetite
appetizers some starter uh to figure out
what I'm about uh it was an honor to be
here thank you very much M I'm honored
to have you K thank you I can't wait to
play with
you yeah have to be GTA 4 yeah it could
be anything you know one day could be
anything okay bye everybody oh sudden
Ending by this is how we do things
around here we just end oh that's so sad
suddenly such a cliffhanger what the
hell you have a special ending don't you
oh yeah I say and in German we say Al Z
AL Z yeah that was
perfect
[Music]
what byebye bye-bye