[Music]
me
foreign
[Music]
do
you
[Music]
i'm still making tea i'll be there in a
moment
one moment
[Music]
you
me
[Music]
do
[Laughter]
sorry i was fixing something uh
i'm making tea
wait a second
there we go
hello
i sure
got my ball
how are you doing
i'm a little bit uh stressed out i went
to buy uh
honey and breakfast and now here i am
[Music]
just a moment before the stream i was
still eating breakfast so
i need a moment to
chill
it's 4 p.m woman what what so what
it's not like i woke up at 4 pm i woke
up
when did i wake up woke up like
uh
two
two hours ago or so or more a bit
earlier than that i was actually
i was having some uh
trouble sleeping until
uh well wait a second
oh i was having some trouble to sleep
until the time i wanted to sleep because
my [\h__\h] neighbors they were drilling
and drilling and drilling and drilling
and drilling and then they would stop
for like 20 minutes so you would think
oh i can go back to sleep now
you would think and then bamboozle
uh 20 minutes later they start drilling
again for like 10 minutes and then they
stop again and i'm like okay okay okay
okay now i can go back to sleep
and 20 minutes later they start again
[Laughter]
[Music]
but i don't know which neighbors it's
very hard to pinpoint
it's okay though um it forced me to wake
up so that's okay it was an okay time it
was
i was already
waking up um i was about to wake up
forcefully whether i wanted or not
yeah i'm very into construction i mean
it's i think like
um
the the pacing of how often that happens
it's not even that often it's not that
often it's not that unusual
and i think the you know that time when
i told inna about banging and drilling i
think wasn't that in my old apartment
i think that was in my old apartment
so that does not count i live somewhere
else now
yeah yeah
you guys know what's up
[Music]
that was in japan was it in japan it
might have been in japan oh
well that's even even more uh
even further
far
further in the past
okay guys we're playing pokemon again
today
mata pokemon
i prepared like two tracks for
for adventuring if there is no bgm i
might play that on my own but yeah
and i got tea i got honey i also bought
pineapple juice
because i i
i always i keep on thinking about what
uh i think it was soda senpai right what
she told me about pineapple juice that
it's good for
good for the throat in theory i have
snacks too yes but they're not with me
right now
sounds as if they're dead or something
snacks are somewhere else
uh
what pizza juice what
welcome to the membership thank you
yes
so
so i am uh more or less prepared for
another
chill day of pokemon
uh
we left off yesterday
at the point where we were introduced to
the diamond dude and the pearl girl
pearl girl
and they had a conversation here they
were like [\h__\h] you and he was like no
[\h__\h] you and then they were like okay
let's go in so now we're going in as
well
yeah
yeah it's cute right the the pokeball
pokeball cute i'm always ready to catch
someone maybe i'll catch some chimpkins
as well
while i'm at it
[Music]
top tier dialogue exactly quick story
yup yup yup i know exactly what happened
yesterday i remember everything
perfectly i have a photographic memory
oh here there's some detail there's some
detail this stone's sticking out wow
that is that is some detail
oh wow i can go behind you
look look
detail oh look detail
detail
i'm actually not joking i'm serious
well i mean the the tree is floating but
that's okay
[Music]
let's go into the
building
let's go
okay what's up i i want to get to know
that cute girl let's see over there
oh no
oh wow what a tree that's a pretty tree
why don't all trees look like this
[Music]
is he gonna make a fire for you in that
fireplace and i suppose it's a fireplace
it's eating berries and this is a time
machine or what it's hard to guess what
this is supposed to do but it certainly
does look impressive
well honestly
it might really be a time machine so my
theory is like obviously he's not from
this timeline even let's be real um i
have i don't really know i don't know
the story i have yet to spoil myself
but there's no [\h__\h] way that he's not
also from a different timeline and he
might have used this to travel around
but
i'm not sure he's just british
[Laughter]
yeah but like how [\h__\h] no
but then why
why is uh like their clothes so
old-fashioned and old
oh my god is she the ancestor of the
poke center lady
holy [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
oh is that a seeing test
oh that's funny
we can try it we can try how well i see
nurse joy ancestor what the [\h__\h] yeah i
was saying why do they look so
old like as in uh they look like they're
from 300 years ago
and yet he looks like look at his
clothes they're not so far off from the
clothes that i started out with that
doesn't look like
i don't know
that nah that that looks pretty modern
to me
um
anyway doesn't matter
you know i expect great things of you
crazy on the good fight on it yeah i
guess i was supposed to look at this huh
the blackboard ah
requests
ah playing with dirk oh [\h__\h] it's the
thrift long quest it seems several
people have spotted a dripline playing
with one of the village children
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
mickey from the security corps can tell
you more speak with her and get to the
bottom of this
oh
that kid did
i can't be good onyo yavin
uh i'll check the other one too bother
zombie doof they're always bothersome
yeah yeah butter it seems a band of
butter some video that's really hard to
say it's like a tongue twister by the
sambadoof brother somebody's buddhism
keep sneaking into the village and
causing trouble talk to some of you from
the security corps and see if you can
help set things in order
there are no other requests okay
how is this my main quest
ah no there's another thing up there
that must be those two
fighting people no oh wait that's a side
quest isn't that
looks cute
oh splendid you came along at a good
time i'm looking for a pickling stone
you see would you mind lending me a hand
it needs to be the right size to fit a
top on one on
a top one of my pickle pots and heavy
enough to put a nice firm pressure on
the pickles while they're fermenting
but i suppose it will be hard for me to
lift such a heavy thing from the pot the
best thing would be for the stone to
lift itself up actually
yeah i was just about to say are you
gonna use a pokemon i have a rather good
idea there's a pokemon called geodude
dude that lives in the deer track heads
oh wait he's gonna lift it i thought he
was gonna become the lid
the pickle lid
i think i have one i think i have one
where did she go where [\h__\h] did you go
what she disappeared
hey
i already have one
did she go upstairs
why did she leave
she's just poof ah yeah this is the
other thing that i wanted to see this is
what i expected when going in here
huh um i'll find her eventually
are there the
the the ones where i can give back a
quest also marked i wonder
they should be right like on the like
outside when i run around
what do you intend to do about that
cleaver commander commodore
he may be descended from a warrior of
almighty signal but look at the mess
he's causing
we can't sit back and let him reach on
you know right to the point ottoman
time wasted is lost
well tell me what would you have us do
cleaver is a precious lord of the pearl
clan is he not
that's the point my clan can't intervene
directly where lord of the pearl clans
concerned if my people were to do
something our two clans might end up
back at each other's throats just like
we used to be
on you we don't want that
but even folk of the girl let the girl
speak for one's head
i wanna hear the girl speak
even the folk of the galaxy team have
been wounded haven't say seems someone's
got to do something here
let her talk
there we go
who then what the diamond clan have the
pearl crown bring down one of its own
honest nobles
i don't believe i said that fought it
maybe
you might as well have said it your fool
look we don't even know what drove load
lord cleaver into such a violent frenzy
i'd like to know that myself this is a
first as far as my clown knows too
i say you've arrived
it is me yeah yes have you not noticed
me i've been standing here for a while
actually
and this is
a new spammer for service corps
i hear from my uran's weird ears favor
good to finally meet you stranger from
the rift
i'm adamant leader of the diamond clan
if you want to be formal i don't care
but that's just that's a mouthful just
call me adam
he's got really uh fuzzy eyebrows
they're even like they're not just like
flat on the face they look like they are
like kind of sticking out you know what
i mean
really puffy eyebrows
if you came from beyond the space-time
rift could you be from the space where
almighty signal is set to receive
resigned
i'm irida leader of the pearl clan
and foresight on my watch words which is
why i have trouble believing such a tale
could you really have passed for that
rift
i have a proposition why not send this
one to study cleaver before deciding
what must be done
what
me
okay of course me who else
it sent this stranger who supposedly
fell from the rift to study cleaver is
that a pokemon like what the hell are
they talking about all this time is that
a pokemon
this newcomer with no experience
says the leader with almost no
experience hey shut up shut
up a pokemon okay okay okay
being a good leader isn't a matter of
time it's a matter of embracing his
vastness without fear
well then there you have it if how new
you are doesn't matter then let's give
the kid a chance
i'm sold commander let's try this your
way
this should be fun i'll get to see how
good you galaxy folk really are with all
your weird ways putting meow pokemon in
those strange balls and well what have
you sorry and cat is meowing in the
distance always have to communicate with
her otherwise she thinks that i don't
like her
they've been very um
very talkative today
that whole practice bothers me
almighty sinnoh made history vast so
pokemon could live freely for out we're
meant to stand alongside pokemon not
count ourselves above them
we do not use pokeballs from our desire
to control our pokemon oh only so that
we can live together
for me it's not like that i just want to
control them but okay
[Music]
i think it's smooth no no it might be
choker okay
[Music]
yes you're going crazy i looked at her
like
she was at the other other side of the
like living room i looked at her and she
looked at me and then she zoomed over to
my side
and then smoothie attacked her
okay so i always get very excited about
everything my cats do
[Music]
junk is cute
hi junkers oh i see her she's she has uh
taken a sit in the shelf hi
hi
i'm waving i'm waving in here
oh this movie is at the top of my shelf
she hasn't been
up there for a while nice movie
hi
[Music]
show us what you can do
this is your mission alcheala
i order you to study cleaver and help us
find the truth of this situation
i accept
of course i do
real life pokemon more important yes yes
yes yes yes yes uh it's just uh
i i wish i wish i could put them in a
pokeball and and uh bring them to like a
vet or like travel wherever
with them like that it would be so so
much easier
ah they would probably also feel much
more comfortable in the pokeball
if a pokeball is really as comfy as they
say
than they feel uh in a transporter box
and they would be so much smaller and so
much lighter hmm
that's not cruel and pokemon games
always say pokeballs are like comfy and
super spacey inside
um
they'd be lonely well is there has there
ever been like a lore on pokeballs that
you can get two pokemon in one pokeball
maybe aren't i mean there are pokemon
that look like there is more than just
one creature right like for example the
the ones that
peek out of the ground the victory
uh
yeah so in theory you could count them
as a free pokemon for example
uh and i could say doctoreons
i could say that
my two cats count this one pokemon and
put them in one pokeball anyway this all
doesn't matter because it's not
happening
remember
wait who's talking commodore
remember that you're a stranger who
to one day out of the very sky above us
people are naturally suspicious of your
presence here if you wish to be fully
accepted and trusted you must work hard
work yourself to the very bone
that's that's it that's that's the
mentality
that i like to hear
let's go
fancy of the woods
well that's settled and there's no time
like the present
lord of the woods cleaver is descended
from a pokemon that was blessed with
almighty sinnoh's own power
no other pokemon you've yet encountered
can compare to his strength be warned
i am
i am warned yes thank you
don't know how much that will help me
but thank you listen to me
the galaxy expedition team has come to
the history region as a group of
outsiders
some might
even call us interlopers
libraries we mustn't do anything to
threaten our relations with diamond and
pearl clans understand
[Music]
that's a very threatening
uh
views
join me downstairs kiawah we'll cover
the details of this new mission okay
[Music]
now where is that where is it sidequest
lady man i guess she went outside hmm
all right then i could have given it to
you immediately but you said nope
[Music]
oh god you're already here
from
professor lavinton the briefing if you
please
yes let's get right into it so come on i
oops [\h__\h] but as you aware by now
cleaver is your mighty thing night night
night invincible even what
the security corps strike throwing
pokeballs at cleaver when they were
attacked but i'm afraid they didn't even
come close to catching him it seems he's
a far trickier opponent than even those
aggressive species of pokemon that
cannot be caught outside of battle once
they're right
he's british
our lock to be perfectly clear on this
point this mission will put you in
extreme danger do you believe you can
handle it
of course it's a
child's game
let me well then let us go over to
particulars
[\h__\h] trailing again
the diamond and pearl class revered the
nobles because they believe this pokemon
served their own mighty sinnoh
they leave offerings to express their
gratitude to these pokemon in locations
they call the noble seats
[Music]
so perhaps a good starting point for our
research could be to find out what sorts
of offerings they normally leave for
this cleaver
we sound scottish today
why did this sound scary it sounded like
it was happening in real
life it sounded like asmr like really
realistic to me in my headphones
oh
jump scared by a tiny sound effect
kiara we need to speak with you
listen not a rift in space time seems
like it connects this world to a whole
other world the
surprising
the world might be where almighty still
know itself resides the true almighty
sinnoh that is the one that rules over
time
it's literally a continent but okay
so if you fell through the space-time
rift that might mean you traveled
through time by almighty sinnoh's power
think of it you must have been just
swimming in its divine might wow
treat me like a [\h__\h] god let's go
yes that's how you're supposed to treat
me i'm god am god become as god
mokami
i saw this
in
[Laughter]
well i've got a favor to ask of you oh
amazing
wait i he's like
he's completely changed his attitude
towards me
oh amazing time travel is that irony is
he being sarcastic no he's being real
right
don't just study cleaver quell his
frenzy
well you certainly caught us in a good
time young ottoman we were just
discussing our next steps with regard to
this whole cleaver situation
oh
you must be that galaxy team scholar
i've heard about good to meet you mr
professor
i'm really cool now yeah
coming in
uh share some of that knowledge with me
sometime
now let me elaborate a little
holy [\h__\h] those textures
those proclaim types have a lot of
respect for cleaver you heard his title
lord of the woods
it sounds like a lot of the rings
i'm sure they'd rather get his this
under control too but it's hard for them
to come right out and ask those of the
galaxy team of all people for help
[Music]
and the truth is we in the diamond clan
have a similar problem on our hands a
pokemon dear to us often off in the
mountains has flown into the same type
of frenzy as cleaver
now there is certainly bad blood between
us and the pearl clan but still we've
all got to share history and that means
we ought to tackle or promise to give a
wink tackle you know if your pikachu
that you don't have
but there aren't many capable of
standing up to such powerful pokemon
you're the best hope we've got
you'll find cleaver at grand tree arena
that's it that's in the very heart of
heartwood his warden is a boy named leon
or lion only orion
bound down to your new god kill you i
have been a god all along didn't you
know
you guys knew when you were praying to
me before
leon is a brilliant child but also a bit
stupid sometimes brilliance can't be
blinding you know
he'll tell you all about his beloved
cleaver whether you wish him to or not
anyway i'm sure you're up to the
challenge so we'll be counting on you
see you later
i wasn't probably not well now you are
thank you
uh
wait who the [\h__\h] was they again the boy
in the back
wow he just said his piece and then
vanished he must just value this his
time that much i guess
adam and i weren't young wrong you know
if you were to study perhaps even quell
cleaver you'd best start by visiting his
abode
okay no it's okay i'm going there
i am already on my way
now that we've got the heights camp it
should come in handy for getting to
grand tree arena and don't forget to
visit the pastures choosing your pokemon
team carefully makes a difference
[Music]
yes yes yes yes okay we want to go to a
new area
huh pick up the materials you come
across satchel always seeming full look
at her face
if that sounds like you would be wise to
lend me your ear a moment and hear what
i have to say okay
i'm a hormone
oh okay who wouldn't like more space in
your satchel
that sounds like
the way you say that to me
in while i'm passing by
makes you look very suspicious
who wouldn't like more space in your
sancho
and that sounds very sus
sounds like you're
dealing me with something
something sus man
you can get around even more than
satchel of yours if you learn the trick
of packing things in i can teach you if
you'd like what do you say oh
hacking things in my teaching fee is 100
bucks okay
then lend me your ear
don't don't take it i still need my ear
one more kind of item
[Music]
and that's all there is to it you see
how much more you can fit in packing in
by packing things rightly if you want to
be able to carry even more things
there's more i could teach you what do
you say no no no
what do you mean like one one extra item
slot or was it like a whole
category
[Music]
what just one
that one huh
ah
well it is pretty cheap but
at the moment i don't really need it
although look at my inventory being full
i don't know
um i've seen there's a chest and i will
i will put some things back that i don't
need or i also need to sell something
price increases it oh well that's lame
that's lame that's kind of lame
okay let's see i know i can sell the
stardust right
um
[Music]
i'm not 100 sure what i can
sell here but these these seem pretty
useless
um i need to craft as well what is that
black temple i have heavy bowl
mmm
chesterberry
peppa plant spicy pokemon restore ppm
let me craft as much as i can
oh [\h__\h]
oh okay uh
i
i think
uh does someone know how to dash by now
because i'm pretty sure there is a dash
button that i'm just not aware of
oh wait
was is that it yeah that's it okay i
figured it out pressing the skip stick
okay okay
why did the game not tell me man
oh wait why am i talking to you
no i don't need to
need your help
i'd be very grateful if you try to craft
something using this special recipe oh
okay
a new recipe
here's the recipe huh
pokey dolls oh
three locks of wood
what what are they what are they good
for just uh for decoration or what
[Music]
cute
there's like japanese dolls that are
called cookishi dolls i think and this
is a like a a pun
pun intended
yeah
old version of polka dots i suppose so
um okay anyway i want to use what i have
use it all up if i can um do i need app
i need i pick one here too
okay we have a few heavy balls
stop rolling you [\h__\h]
i guess i'll use it all up
um
use this up too i suppose should i i
don't know if i oh maybe i should keep
it i don't know
i'll definitely make all of these
and let's see how much space i have in
my inventory now okay it's looking
looking better
so can i equip this to someone
no
wait what is that sign here can you
evolve
[Music]
what else are you going to use also
maybe i don't know i don't know what all
the recipes i'm going to get like maybe
an improved potion
[Music]
got the idea for a new move okay go
ahead do what you want
wow we already have one final evolution
in our team
oh
that one evolves so fast doesn't it
yeah i do have i i do have a chest yeah
yeah yeah i can put some stuff in there
number you've evolved
two out of two
how
about it
that's not true happened to both two of
them
bugs evolve quickly yeah
they have early evolutions it seems
hyena
okay let's put some berries in i guess
uh item storage
oh
i'm storage
and
donate this right now
move
a ball of mud
don't need that
tumble stone
move this
one stats can we use to raise effort
levels only out uh-huh
okay
that's all i'm gonna move
and yes
then i think i'm ready to explore
[Music]
x but shortcut oh i didn't see that
thank you
who are you i have a
feeling you're going to give me a side
quest
hmm
i'll play an orange oh you do you want
an oranberry i literally just put them
in my storage
uh
yes yes how many do you want
yeah yeah
um
five orange berries no problem
don't forget to craft more i i did
no did i not i crafted some heavy ones
did i not craft any normal ones oopsie
oh wait i have 62 what do you mean craft
more
um
move the satchel
five
i did i did i did
there's a box right by the gate oh
oh oopsie
heavy ones would be nice i'll try i made
i made a bunch i don't think i was able
to make more
[Music]
oh it doesn't it doesn't show any marker
above him that i can give the quest back
so like
what if i like this guy i remember what
about the others
and i don't remember
uh
happy to help
thank you tumble stones
i have to set the mark of myself
[Music]
oh man
was it who was it was it he no
[Music]
wait why do i why do i do
that where do i do that
minus
y
uh-huh
are these ones i can give back
oh no
no requests
[Music]
show
only complete polka dots
so this one i can give back ah
i can only do one at a time
oh man okay
so
oh is it that one over there
why are you so far away
they're in their own house now
why did you go so far away but yo you
have a bigger version of my place nice
huh the mirror is covered so
that you don't see your your own
reflection why not are you scared of
your own reflection
i got what you want
or do i yes i do
here is my one and only
geodude
[Music]
would you look at that yeah it's a rock
a floating rock amazing
fascinating
dude
[Laughter]
just be careful that he doesn't ground
pound you or smash you with his rock
fists oh god oh god oh god
oh god i love it
[Laughter]
it just kind of just kind of happened it
just kind of happened
uh
we shall
dude
dude okay
[Music]
speak to them where are they
ramble
wanna do this one worm for wormpole
where is this person
what
inside
ah are you is that you
does he really say that the pokemon dude
i do i do i do
i will give you this one
[Music]
have fun with it
cute
[Music]
uh you want me to name it
yeah
i don't give a [\h__\h] what you're gonna
name it
yes beautycon
whipple can evolve dazzling honey
okay
and
uh
what about these
where's how fast can i use where's
sumogee
right at the gate okay
i hear you caught three different
species of pokemon in your trial that's
no mean feat i have a job that's perfect
for a high achiever like you see i need
help researching ah it's so special doof
again
how are they bothersome they're so
adorable
i look away for one second and the
little scoundrels waltz right into the
village oh this is awful i'm a complete
failure as a member of the security
corps how can i face captain caesar like
this
now get a hold of yourself to monkey
just catch the bidoof and everything
will be fine
but still freeze a lot mm-hmm i will
help you
task it
[Music]
leave it to me
uh wait are they like scattered all over
ugh
are they hiding now
oh dear it's a bidoof hide and seek
game
oh i feel like i heard or maybe that was
just my pokemon over there
and the
pasture
bit off
but radoof
where are they
[Music]
is everyone here
sorry for running over your field
oh hello you have a sad quest
listen here cereal cupcake i saw the
darnest thing i was scoring the hardwood
for crops we could grow in the fields
here when i saw this pokemon called
cherium isn't that the berry pokemon
changed its appearance before my very
eyes ah
it wasn't the evening the light was
getting dim all of a sudden sharon's
petals closed right up so it looked like
nothing but a little flower but
let me guess you want to have one of
those pokemon
it was in full bloom but why would it
bloom just to close back up is that how
evolution works was that to change i saw
something different it was indeed
something different yeah
um when you finish sharon's pokedex
entry let me have a look ah okay
okay
okay but do you know of a [\h__\h] bidoof
i just heard a pokemon noise i think
what
what am i hearing
can i run up here
oh not really
hello
[Music]
but that's weird
they're actually hiding pretty well
um
we're going crazy
grandma have you seen them a fluffy
the doof almost looks like a cat
[Music]
one is near a big building potential
why are they such a pain to find we hope
let's see there maybe ah
i see you do have to use my own balls
doof
oh wait i don't have to ah
found one
okay wait so what we have two i only i
thought i only found one
great going
remaining bit of two
was that her own bidoof
okay if one was there i feel like the
others would be further away
i feel like i just heard one again
really really really tiny sound though i
doubt that you guys hear it
that was my own badoo
[Music]
when you love badoof so much that you
hear them everywhere
[Music]
i think i feel like this song is this
bgm is so repetitive
the melody
that that guitar sound
da da da
yeah jump jump
a sailor theme would be nice hell yeah
it's it is a very short loop at least
[Music]
it is relaxing but it's so repetitive
man
okay one more one more
how come there was no bee doof over here
it sounds like there should be one here
did i miss one
have you seen a badoof
sir please
you want me to help you with your quest
you help me with mine please
one more badoo
on the other side of the map
one at a
fence
i'll look over here again
oh that's cool i never looked up the
inside of your shop but it looks pretty
cool when i can go inside almost
it's holding me up longer than i thought
it would
maybe
someone said fence maybe here
no
nothing took me so long it was
embarrassing really defense of the
pasture
oh okay okay okay i'm gonna go to the
pasture thank you for the hint
wait is the
the dashing does it stop after a little
while or
because she has no stamina or
stops after like two seconds of dashing
i think
but there's no no no like stamina
uh
being shown to me
ah for dude you want to play with the
other pitots understandable
kawaii
oh it's so cute chomp chomp chomp let me
try to drink my tea
honey honey honey
[Music]
oh
dodging i i didn't feel like spamming
dodge really made me fast at all
cute
let's put all the little travel makers
safely in our custody now to give them
the old hippo you're gonna throw them
out
hold on
it'll be a shame to just send those bits
back into the wild no my construction
clubs could find the use for them
well you want to keep them
but these knowledge nibblers have caused
so much trouble for the construction
crips
they're just pokemon being pokemon how
are they supposed to know our village is
a strict no chewing zone
shows good taste on their part to come
all the way here tonight on our wardrobe
too
but if they're gonna stay here they'll
have to help with our work
they're listening they're looking at her
you're cute
naughty nipplers just like my kitty cats
they've got the guts to keep trying to
get into the village plus the teeth to
ganash roof trees and rocks just with
our corpse needs how about it little
ones meals taste better after a day's
work you know
yes i see
just what i wanted to hear
oh
this is how it starts
a relationship between pokemon and
humans
a world of
just pokemons and humans having
friendships and
and uh working together
this is how it all starts
mm-hmm
wonderful take it
rare candy
so we do the other the the the driftloom
quest right away as well
oops
our thing's my good friend abuelo
i certainly hope you're putting that
secret back strike technique uh i taught
you two good use
sometimes
either way i have some super potions
here just for you oh i i think nothing
of it having the survey corpse out and
about studying pokemon is great for
business you know supporting you now is
actually an investment in my own
fortunes
i like i like what you're saying sounds
good to me super potions
now i must depart there are ruins that
are just calling to me
okay um i think i want to do the
driftwood quest do you guys want to see
that rifling quest
spoopy spoopy quest
uh
it's over there
apparently
what is that it's about the pokemon
balloon balloon pokemon what is this one
doing here now oh
uh balloon pokemon eating children i
think
something like that
is it you
so you've accepted my request to look
into the driftwood i can't tell you what
a big help that is
let me fill you in we'd heard reports
that drifloon was playing with one of
the village children over on prelude
beach in the evenings this seemed like
odd behavior for pokemon so all of us in
the security corps worried its true
intentions were to harm the child in
some way
thankfully all the blitz children were
safe and accounted for when we went to
check on them and that would have been
too dark if they disappeared but there
was one curious thing none of them seem
to know anything about adrenaline
but while so many people from the
village have reported seeing the pokemon
we can't simply pretend there isn't an
issue here can we pretend
since this calls for some investigation
i thought the survey clubs would be our
best bet
we need you to find out the truth behind
the driftline that the child has been
playing with
okay at the prelude breach in the
evening okay i mean it's getting dark
now
i have a quest too
um
let me drink tea
lined up side by side
oh okay
uh i don't know if i have a
different sized one
no no no no
okay yeah yeah bigger than yours how big
is yours
ah apparently i have one
apparent
apparently no
ah my own one
wait is he gonna take it away from me
or does he just look at it and then give
it back to me
happy birthday
[Music]
no my number comes on he takes it
do i i mean i can catch a new one
i can catch a new one i guess
yeah but now maybe later i'll i'll catch
another one and bring it to you
because uh otherwise i have no water
pokemon
wait what where
oh this is where we caught them the
babies
okay
right now i also hear like really soft
pokemon
voices in the
area but i don't see any pokemon
the hell
is this too early
prelude beach
yeah i think we're yeah obviously toilet
it has to get dark i guess
i should have pokemon here too
i had to get 12 before i found one being
since i am able to give him one is the
one i have already beat
or is that just he's gonna look at it
and be like yo that's not big enough
perhaps
by sleeping yeah but i will have to go
somewhere right to sleep
fast travel oh
uh wait uh
x where do you want to go
[Music]
farm
no
not really but
i guess i'll sleep in my apartment
yeah they made fast travel available
quite early huh i don't think it was
always that early in other pokemon games
i think you had to wait quite long
though
2.8
two okay i don't know how big that is in
centimeters but okay
until evening
yeah i need it like you need to fly yeah
[Music]
let's see
can we
find that driftwood now it's fast travel
can i oh
yes
i wonder what will happen something
scary
okay
jerry flown
balloon pokemon
oh
that's so [\h__\h] scary what the [\h__\h]
what are you doing there
let's try to go for triathlon
server cops lady over here
oh [\h__\h] hey um i wanna go home now but
trifloon won't let me go what the [\h__\h]
he just wants to play probably
it's it's
i can't imagine it's being evil
can you help me please
sure
i'll fight it if i have to rip it apart
i'll pop it with a nail
oh there we go
ichata
yay now i can finally go home but hey
drifloon didn't mean to be bad it always
played together with me it's real
friendly so i kept it a secret from
everyone
okay my name's tacky see you around
i know i know i know the pokedex entries
but maybe that's just you know um
maybe
maybe that's just
what do you call it again um
[Music]
um
uh uh i forgot the word for it
rumors no just more like a
purposefully
propaganda i suppose misunderstanding
no it's uh maybe yeah slander slander
that's what i wanted to say maybe they
want to slander that's a cute
cute
pokemon
because it's too cute to be true
a misconception it could be anything
honestly
or maybe just someone fought you know
maybe they reused it like a burn book
they made up things and wrote it in
there like a burn book that's not fetch
at all man
that's just not fetch
oh
it's a [\h__\h] burn book the pokedex is
a burn book
[Laughter]
what did the balloon do to you
i guess probably some kid's mom didn't
buy them a balloon
um and then they
they saw a drift loon and they were like
okay if my mom won't buy me a balloon
and i'm gonna get a drift loon and they
came home with with the driftwood and
the mom said like what the [\h__\h] no so
the mom wrote in the pokedex that drift
loons are scary so that the child would
be scared by that and believe it
and then be like no i don't want you
anymore you're [\h__\h] scary and then it
let go
that's that's the lure that's the lord
it's all just a mom making up a story in
order to scare its child so that it
won't bring home a balloon
yeah yeah yeah yeah
sounds legit makes sense
pokemons
[Music]
have you found out i have found out this
but it's all a lie
i see it's a little tacky was trying to
keep uh
drifloon from getting in trouble
all the same he was in considerable
danger
without your help goodness knows where
driftlin would have taken him by now
stop
i'd be remiss if i didn't follow up on
this traveling incident i'll urge
captain sister to post extra security
clips guards are out on the prelude
beach at once
i'm sure that pokemon doesn't want to
harm the children
oh man
mom can i have a balloon no
balloon balloon
and what's that super cute super old
idol song from betty's kobo where they
were singing uh
something about balloons i think
i need to look it up again it was so
cute
okay let's go back to the main quest
although can i sell the stardust really
quickly
quick quickie to click
oh oh here it is
sell it oh what is done
ah exp candy
honey cake come on
kikity quick
no no not this not that one
99 drift balloons keep on stealing
children we don't know what they do with
them
[\h__\h] it's so scary men
heading outside the village yes uh we're
going like here
heights camp i think
[Music]
maybe one day i write a full version for
that
[Music]
yeah i think i'm good with my
lineup of pokemon
um
wait where the hell we should uh
aim to go that way right
is that where it came from yeah
okay
how do you spam that i feel like i'm
slower than just
when i'm running
someone said they spam that and then
feel pretty fast
hi boobs
okay
uh time to play some bgm
whoa that's loud
you hear that i have two tracks we can
figure out which one we want
uh what's strong against stone again man
i don't remember
well no now i don't need it because it's
a battle
uh
oh is it gonna be a battle who knows
maybe i'll just try to catch it he
forgot about me
[\h__\h]
still didn't notice
water grass fighting around okay
huh
let's see if that's a one-hit kill
oh it's not okay we can i guess we can
um
catch it we probably need
a bit more for some points
dude
[Applause]
you for real men
wasting my time
[Music]
oh flying is weak against rock [\h__\h]
come on come on get down
that is one cheese
[Music]
i saw by the way in the area that we are
that we were roaming around yesterday
um
that you can catch a pichu there it's
pretty rare as well apparently
oh can i just uh
no i wanna
look at you ah
i'm
[Music]
oh we can uh
try to catch some more
i don't know what i have that's
effective but i caught one
never seen a single pichu you can find
monsters as well oh
hopefully we'll find uh
which way should i use this bike work
yeah but works
[Music]
hey pretty strong
feel it
okay okay then
was actually a good choice
okay we still didn't see it use uh
the skill that we wanted to use but
that's okay
oh these are zubats down
there of several ones
but we've seen one before
[Music]
okay ah
we gotta go this way i suppose
another child safe from driftload yeah
let's go
indeed indeed we are heroes
[Music]
you wanna fight
the the seamlessness of the fights is
really really really awesome
like
i i mind
going into battles much less than i did
um in previous pokemon games
it's so fast
[Music]
so
that's that's pretty dope
and yeah i'm catching pokemon as well
really fast
[Music]
you gotta praise them where you gonna
praise them
gonna be honest
get me those bears oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
i don't even remember seeing that
pokemon
a diamond pearl is it only in diamond
parasect
you don't know you don't know
probably too strong for me yeah
i suppose so
i know should i go down this way ah well
i guess i am going down this way
[Music]
oh that's a small boy too we can catch
that small boy
[Music]
he's so small baby
oh
is that a water pokemon or what is that
oh [\h__\h]
that was by accident
[Music]
uh
oh it's so fast
speedy boy grass bug oh he's so cute
am i getting it am i getting it
i got it
maybe catch it two about two
or
if it wants
oh that was way too far [\h__\h] oh no
hey did you see me really
ah
okay i don't know what pokemon to use
but how about this one
keep it away from firefly it doesn't
like that oh
what did you just do
no
[Music]
i was still able to attack nice good
choice okay it's just me being lucky to
be honest
just being lucky here
you have no idea what i'm doing
oh there's a person over there
[Music]
music kind of spoopy right now
i'm gonna catch or maybe i should fight
one
ah the eyes look so funny the eyes look
like those goggly sticky eyes you know
what i mean
the ones that you can stick on anything
the ones that wiggle wiggle
[Music]
fire
[\h__\h]
oh well we got to attack three times in
a row so it's all good
you know things happen so fast uh
i don't have i don't have that much time
to think about
uh
think about what i wanna
use
are you kidding me
not enough space
can i like
raise the level
let's use it on a rowlet
island master one of its moves nice
grab a single pokemon small amount of
experience points
uh which one are we gonna keep i don't
know the only one that i know we're
gonna keep is my starter pokemon i don't
know about the rest of this
i'll give it to you for now
[Music]
okay
crack something oh you're right i can
craft while i'm outside too now right
i forgot
i forgot about that
really
hello uh bermy nice to see you
uh
i don't know where are you going
i don't know what's effective
[Music]
you know whenever i switch pokemon in
the battles like last stream people were
like were like uh switching is the worst
thing you can do
so i want to not switch too often if
it's just a tiny battle
yum yum yum listen to orders unless you
get your star rank up ah
you need to fill the dexila
catch yes i will try to catch more
pokemon
have you ever come across a tree shaking
yes yes yes i know i know i know i know
i wanna i wanna focus on you
what do we have number defeated oh i
have not defeated it yet times you've
given it food what
you can give it food
interesting um you are a bug do i have a
fire pokemon i don't think so oh
no don't
don't run away
boy
you gotta do this smart
hmm
wait how about i don't try this one
you don't have enough space again
ah
let me try to craft something
is this a one time use only
[Music]
it's not okay cool
oh [\h__\h]
what what who's attacking me
ah yeah
[Music]
wow
really aggressive aren't you
ok
but do be looking around let's see
yes by now i know that it's effective
against you
number of defeated 556
a wolf burb can evolve
let's go then
evolve fuel
oh
staravia
gorgeous
unfortunately as i said we have we had
star ravia we had shanks on our team so
those two are a no-no for our team in
the future just for now when we don't
have much else to choose from
we're keeping them
oh it's daytime
wow good morning
ohio
okay that stupid ass beetle
you think it already noticed me
wait i wanna i wanna kill one though
oh don't i dare you if you run away
again
uh oh [\h__\h] no no
fight
um
is there anything here effective
bite
nothing okay
oh yes we killed it before it was able
to run away
[Music]
well that's all i wanted to do
oh
a big boy
uh
no i don't want to fight no don't attack
me
no no no no i'm good i'm good i'm good
i'm good
here's the evolution of bidoof
so
i wonder if there's completely
separate entries of like um tasks
for the evolutions as well
[Music]
there are
we do what's strong against the doof
what do i have that's strong
it really doesn't care
electric
okay
uh
oh people are real
okay
well let's try to defeat it
i can't unaware
it seems like it's still unaware
of style
oh
where are you here you are
tomorrow
[Music]
you can check the right side if if
there's a concentric circle which means
i know that i know that but sometimes
when i haven't fought the pokemon yet it
won't tell me
and i don't know the effective stuff by
heart
so i need everybody's help sometimes
okay i guess we're crossing the
the river oh you see that detail over
there
no not you
okay i'm i'm good i don't care about
them
i almost would feel sorry about
attacking that one
oh
it's just chilling
oh we learned a new one thunder fang
time to try it out ooh
paralyzed nice he contemplates life
uh now we try to catch it oopsie
pouring people around yeah he was just
chilling
i feel sorry too
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
although i could also try to catch one
of those big boobs
i have to catch those too right
oh what's effective
what's effective guys
i don't know
uh
two can evolve okay wait one second
electric
route uh
man shinx has a lot to do here
nice
did i catch it unaware it should be
unaware
oh [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
go go go strong
oh thank god level 17. wait i wanted to
[\h__\h] i wanted to catch it but i forgot
about it
oopsie
spoiled apricorn okay whatever
uh
what
is that
alpha pokemon oh why is that so big or
is that the last oh [\h__\h]
you have to run around that
oh wait um holy [\h__\h]
well first of all evolve
do it
around 10 evolve too
whoa
wow oh
[Music]
good boy i love this pokemon i love the
design it's one of my
favorite pokemon designs i think
from the first one to the last one
it's very very um
stable it doesn't get worse
verb evolution number one
oh
and this one i've seen it before it
doesn't look so bad either
it has a nice hairstyle very slick
[Laughter]
okay
uh wait um now let's heal everybody
oh heel
okay
uh heel
it's fancy yes it's in its teenage years
it's trying out some hairstyles
what else can we do compatible
um let's try to craft something again i
guess
zero
[Music]
minecraft for
okay well my inventory is still looking
pretty [\h__\h] full oh my god
uh
is there something i don't need
blackboard maybe i don't know
well okay well just
no don't attack him just take that run
run run run
oh it doesn't really it's pretty easy
going
i thought it would be freaking out a bit
more what the hell is that there's a
pokemon there
inside the materials i wonder what that
is but
i think we're just gonna focus for now
on
[Music]
yeah even if it's alpha it's still a
beaver right that's so in character
very easy going
it's level 16 only you think i could
kill it
if you guys think so i can try
i could likely kill it okay
oh god what effective pokemon do i have
help me
what's effective here
should i catch it should i catch the
alpha but when i catch it it turns back
into a normal one no
electric okay
oh [\h__\h] don't look at me don't look at
me take it easy
it stays it stays big
what is it stronger then oh [\h__\h]
it just hopped away
man it looks like jonkers
on your butt
it has better stats it gets moves at
normal one zone should i
um replace my own one with this one
maybe i hope i don't kill it
junk
whoa okay
the good thing is
we didn't have this pokemon in my
original play through it's kind of a
boring type right it's only normal i
think so
not sure if i'll keep it forever but
wait do i have to use a heavy ball
oh my border normal water oh no water
[Music]
okay heavy barley let's see
dual tab okay i didn't know i thought it
was only normal okay okay
oh oh it didn't like it it didn't like
it
but it's still two stumps to do [\h__\h]
trying again
how high is the percentage here that i
can get it i wonder
how how good is that ball
not that good apparently
oh
should we try to no
[\h__\h] look still down full swipe yeah
yeah yeah yeah
uh
okay i mean water is not gonna hurt me
much so
far swipe
there it is actually really coming in
handy now
critical hit
i see oh [\h__\h] oh do you have an ice
attack
oh boy
[Music]
oh
holy [\h__\h]
come on come on come on
[Music]
he's gonna wipe my [\h__\h] team
[Applause]
holy [\h__\h]
it's pretty bad oh my god what if i run
out of heavy balls [\h__\h]
you won't kill one of your own brethren
will you
oh no
oh man
oh man come on oh boy yay
see he did not he was not able to kill
one of his own brethren
you become
he was intimidated he was like okay you
have one of my own people then i will
become one of your people
oh wait but b doof can evolve now
uh wait can i uh
switch out the team now or do i need to
go to one of those farm thingies
[Music]
attacks i can switch anytime right but
not my team right
i have to go to the camp okay well for
now um
i'm finally gonna use for my items
hooray
okay that's
come on
okay at the camp
okay
we'll switch it out then we'll have a
huge ass bidoof we'll be barrel actually
this is exciting um but i guess we could
evolve this one anyway
uh
just to look at it
even you can find them by going east
from north feeling
they are spawned with pedos
okay let's field lance count to the
crescent shape thing
[Music]
for the test yeah
are we
sorry move my microphone
a frightening b-bar l
welcome to the team
okay uh craft
handcraft [\h__\h]
yeah okay
no space in my inventory and can't craft
anything this is
a problem but i gotta go to the next
waypoint
i have to
gotta ignore what's around me then
um
[Music]
running around
it looks very peaceful doesn't seem like
it wants to fight
oh
[Applause]
what about you
oh [\h__\h]
oh
okay it's coming close so that's good
nice nice bro
would it
work it did
bunny earry let's go
uh let's try this one as well
the more the mario right
[Music]
hell yeah those are easy to catch
apparently
can i get those do i already have them
in my inventory
oh my god it's so cute
that's it can i already catch it or do i
have to fight along
it's so cute honey pokemon i doesn't
want to be caught
enraged
oh
angry
understandable
understandable i have a disturb you oh
[\h__\h]
um
[Music]
skip its mail only female b what
but oh [\h__\h]
i only really want to catch it for the
sake of the cask you know
um
i don't want to kill it i guess we can
also kill it anyway
in case we kill it we kill it that's
okay
[Music]
would you be dropping honey
oh no not very uh
all right
[Music]
honestly
it's pretty fun pretty fun
this game
oh
i need to revive again
do you guys when you're playing this
game are you pokemon also dying a lot
i feel like the the difficulty like the
level
the levels of the pokemon are pretty
high which is a good thing
yes no yes yes
oh thank you for being honest
[Music]
am i going i'm going that way we're
getting closer
and done
yeah the pokemon are pretty strong
okay
actually never mind
uh
let me see
number of heavys i need a heavy specimen
and i need to defeat one uh and electric
top move okay defeat let's defeat one
with uh
luxio
but i might have to um
uh battle with both of them thank you
for renewing your membership oh no i
don't have to okay
that is also something i think is pretty
cool that if there's like other pokemon
around
you um
often end up fighting
both of them
or even three of them
as we've had yesterday
yeah
pretty cool
also challenging as well
very challenging
what about you
i want to see
your entry
oh [\h__\h]
wait hey
uh
baby doll ice
pn
it has a attack that's like pn
and defeated we need to defeat them
it's running away
there it goes
all right i'll remember it
piano attack i can do that too
last time i attacked you guys with pn i
got like a lot of new memberships
uh what's effective what's effective i
wonder
uh
it's a bunny oh [\h__\h] it noticed me nah
don't go away
[Music]
tell me your credit card number
fighting another fighting
sheesh
no don't run away
you can tell now well i guess that's
very bunny bunny-ish of them to run away
like that oh
[Music]
[\h__\h]
nice nice nice nice fruit
[Music]
what's the best here
maybe flying
two sentiments that's pretty good
[Music]
look at that oh now you're in the mood
to find okay
[Music]
you think it's shiny no way it's chinese
no way why would it be shiny
oh god it's actually pretty scary to
kill a shiny one huh
but um
one good thing i've heard that you uh
can see on the field if a pokemon is
shiny you can see it already so for
shiny hunters like fubuki samba
it's gonna be
actually pretty easy huh
yeah
seeing it before running into it
very very helpful all right baby
[Music]
oh that's really really not strong
oh okay you can run away i only wanted
to see the pn
okay
[Music]
stop
yes sir three other three
oh
i want to explore but with a full
inventory it's pretty tough
hello aren't you a child well i guess i
am too
i'm leon of the pearl clan the warning
to cleaver lord of the woods
mm-hmm
and you i've already deduced that you'll
come here to meet cleaver i'm right
aren't i
of course i am i can see it so clearly
after all the powerful awesome cleaver
has become even more awesomely powerful
perhaps that strange lightning the other
day was almighty sinnoh's divine power
but whatever it was it struck my lord
and left him imbued with an awesome
might
so i must turn you away even if it pains
me it's too dangerous for you to meet
that's that then
no
let me in
the [\h__\h] surprised faces of the
characters man
oh such an earnest desire to meet mighty
cleaver i have to admit i'm struck by
your passion
but well i'm afraid your passion is not
the real issue here
i've been told in no uncertain terms by
erita that i am to let no one near
cleaver
huh i've been sent to meet cleveland
you'll fight me okay fight me
i'll take you on
your little child
go goomy
goomy
[Music]
i don't know what's effective this is
embarrassing
uh it's a dragon
bite
[Music]
decided so do you let me go to cleaver
now after i one hated your pokemon buddy
what do you think
uh how can this be well i'm strong dude
i may have been defeated but my point
still stands it's too dangerous
the only welcome you'll get if you
approach him is a flurry of devastating
blows
normally i'd simply try making him an
offering a nice helping help heaped
helping of his two favorite foods served
up with respect by his loyal warden
that's me of course is usually enough to
please him and soon the prickliest of
moods but even i cleaver's loyal warden
can't get close enough to give any
offerings now not with the way cleaver
is rampaging and running on milk
there's nothing that an outsider like
you can do
oh kitty
the ancestor of clever we're dear and
their cohort drew and almighty sinnoh's
own power to protect pokemon and people
alike so it's said it's spider grace
that our clan than any of us still lives
in vast history today
hey rita what are you doing here
[Music]
as you say clever has grown even
stronger but i'm afraid the strength
poses a problem for us if he was indeed
struck by that lightning could the boots
have been sent by the force you know
that the diamond clan bows too
clever means so much to her clan i hoped
we could bring the situation under
control ourselves not for our hands up
and ask some outsiders for help
but we must save cleaver from this
frenzy
every moment it continues the danger
grows if more people and pokemon are
attacked it will lead to conflict with
both the diamond clan and the galaxy
team
[Music]
you stranger from beyond the sky tell me
could you galaxy people actually fix
this
could an outsider actually find a way to
quell our lord's frenzy
figure it out
very well
leon and i will gather foods that please
cleaver in hopes that we might be able
to get close to or close enough to make
him a proper offering
a human offering you actually
as for you find a way to call his
friends even if you must search every
corner of vast history
i thought i could meet him today
man
my arc phone
i can return to base camps in an instant
okay
press the x button while consulting the
platform a little easier to travel okay
head to the base camp yeah i need to go
there
uh
all the way over there okay
if we go to field lance camp we could
look for the eevee again
it might take a while though
maybe we'll even find a pizza
good to see your kiawah
and serving his favorite foods
need to mow this over back at the
laboratory you should come along too
oh i didn't really catch that much
you're done
but i caught an alpha pokemon yeah
that's right i did that
i did do that
so that's all that
next rank
i don't did that yeah
[Music]
now maybe i'll take up some more if i
was able to catch that one then i'll try
some others as well
so according to the information you were
able to learn from me rita and leon of
the pearl clan
where this the normal course of events
that
that francis cleaver would be called by
a nice serving of his two favorite foods
which are potato machine by any chance
is it possible that the aromas or some
other coconut components of these foods
might combine in a way that could not
only calm cleaver but draw him back from
his frenzy
but by your own report even cleaver's
warden who looks after cleaver and knows
him well cannot approach him in his
current state
it would be a fool's gambit to get close
enough to offer him food
um give me a moment if you would i need
some time to ponder on this there's
ought to be something in my research
notes that can help us
[Music]
i think i wouldn't mind replacing my my
luxio
with pichu slash pikachu slash right to
and having that is my electric pokemon
who says that
we'll simply have to throw the food
really that's the idea
you have quite the i'm for throwing
things haven't you
[Music]
wow are you roasting me yo
yo
is one of the kfp people involved in
making this game
by the suggest you take cleaver's
favorite foods and throw them at the
pokemon yeah which ones are they
[Music]
crafting to shave clevis beloved foods
into balls
and throw them to achieve the same
calming effect but from afar like a food
ball
[Music]
tea time balls
[Laughter]
okay yes
why not call them lavinton balls uh-huh
i don't want lebanton's balls though
i don't want to touch his balls with
that name i just sound like i'm the one
being launched exactly
exactly
[Music]
then you should hurry back to the grand
touring arena and tell the pearl clan
about our brilliant plan okay
okay
but before that
oh hello what is what it's been
imprisoned
what's your name again people up
they imprisoned it what the [\h__\h] let it
out
oh it's open
above okay
never mind then
never mind
not my business what's that what oh
oh wait is the german name maybe hip hop
i think it might have been or that was a
different similar pokemon
uh talk to the captain to rank up oh
[Music]
indeed
yo boss
captain my captain
oh captain my captain
where are you
what wasn't she usually here
[Music]
you're not the one who helps me to rank
up
[Music]
one floor below
oh
attention my tank
yes what is this
what can i do for you today i hear she
as well
[Music]
look at it
what do you think
what do you think do i deserve another
badge
[Music]
me a raise yeah
she actually approves raises i can use
federal balls
[Music]
oh thank you recipes feta balls
super potions yay
nice
okay
um
i think i'll buy the rest of the
slots for the inventory
i kind of have to
inventory
where was that dude again was it it
wasn't here wasn't he inside
it was inside
thank you
[Music]
inventory becoming bigger
can i afford all of them i think i can
[Music]
imagine getting a salary am i right
camping
what do you mean
there is a salary involved it's just you
paying me
[Music]
but how many can you give me
huh
you know what i was doing last night
i
designed
um outfits
for
the amatori song cover music video
that's right
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] that's expensive
yeah i did it this time
it's nothing crazy it's just uh
it's pretty simple what i did but that's
all you can do oh wait you can even do
more but okay this is getting expensive
cut
uh
okay that's quite a lot more space
that's pretty good
um
[Music]
yes yes
it isn't a little late for the outfits
what do you mean
i'm i'm getting um
something
special
done for the music video
actually getting uh special
models done it's
it's
putting a lot of
thought into this actually
um
yeah
it's gonna be um
special models for the music video for
the song cover
yes
[Music]
um
spoilers spoilers
spoilers
a little bit it's coming soon anyway
not much more time left it's it's coming
it's happening guys
uh
dust
[Music]
you can open you with two cents i get
new hairstyles and [\h__\h] really
i want to take a look
the thing is you already have to pay
before even
um looking at the hairstyles right that
kind of sucks
yeah
ammo is gonna be in the amateur cupboard
what
yes yes yes let's make uh oh you need
potions for the super portions ah
and the pep up plant
[Music]
okay did i only make one whoopsie
uh
wait what do i have in my storage
i had to go wild when they didn't have
green you didn't
wait that's a bit drastic you don't have
to go
bald just because they don't have green
hair
well that's her fault if she thinks she
gotta
if she thinks bald is better than going
green
well that's her problem
sounds like a
sounds like a hero pro her problem
let's move on this again because
i don't know what i need for
crafting except for this one this one i
probably don't need
necessary sacrifice
i want to take a look i want to take a
look but it's so expensive and i don't
have that much money right now
oh i can't craft anything from that
anyway
oh okay
[\h__\h]
[Music]
uh
hmm
but i will use
all right i wanted to uh
wait uh i need to go to
let's go
here
what are you doing
can you tell me how we're going to make
themselves so tiny yeah i can tell you
but apparently as a protagonist i'm not
allowed to speak to you
okay so where's my big badoof
ah this one this one um this one is a
big one
it has
better attacks definitely icy wind
damn
and
this one has a higher level but this one
still has more hp
ah but attack is actually only 80.
attack 66 special attack pretty strong
defense as well
is that good
[Music]
okay and then we'll also i want to
switch out
um
no but we already have grass
i want to have a bug only
i could ah we could put a fire pokemon
but was only level four
[Music]
scientific bun eerie
but it would be fun to have a ghost
pokemon wouldn't it
ghost and flying
we'll just have to level it a little bit
just to get rid of the pokemon that um
we had in our previous playthrough and
we don't want it want anymore
okay those are really low levels so
let's try to
um use them um even if
maybe we'll find some stronger ones
replace dust ducts why
my mind at galaxy hall is one fine
building even from from the outside
the galaxy team certainly got themselves
the grand headquarters i'll give them
that
um
it seems like they're still working on
it
oh yes i came because i had some news
that i thought you might be interested
in
better you actually see
what's going on though let's head to
what did you end up calling it the
heights camp
oh uh hey hey no
i wanted to go catch an eevee
oh hello
uh okay
look
what do you mean i forget circles i have
i have the the
the horse with me
spoke to me about what's been going on
told him how you've been trekking all
over the field and seeking a way to
quell cleveland's frenzy thank you i
guess all this from someone who's not
even part of our clan of brooklyn just
some wanderer who fell through a rift
into this world and hearing that well
you can see how he responded he wants to
help i suppose
wait can i write it down
you found me wolfie which means you'll
need a flute like we have
mine demonstrating oh
very important listen well okay
oh
i thought you were gonna go ocarina of
time on me now
i was watching a little bit of noida
stem by playing ocarina of time today
it's really cool she's playing ocarina
of time
at the moment
not right now but like in general hmm
celestica flute that might just plant
hmm it's a precious tool that can be
used to call on weirder so you can ride
upon him let's go tessel
we have a mouth now
it said that the celestial flutes were
gifts from almighty sinnoh itself and
now this one's yours
whoa
[Music]
a flute that can be used to call a
special pokemon that are willing to bury
you around the region is timber is eerie
and mysterious
in the end indeed
indirect kiss with them
it's not that kind of gesture really i
can't play the flute for the life of me
how much it makes you what makes you
think i can
see if you can play the melody okay
i'm gonna be uh a natural at it
obviously wow
first try
and i'm getting an indirect kiss with
mine let's go
okay he liked it
okay
i think this is uh only i'm only winning
right now kfb we're winning
a mind played oh just don't have any
the question is can i use this
mount as a pokemon as well to fight with
me or is it just a mount
um thank you guys wow
tata
press the plus button to summon a
pokemon to ride on
a pokemon implies that there will be
others
circles majestic circles wow the throne
that i'm sitting on
look at that sit sitting sit city cities
sit hmm
what is with balloons what what balloons
you want a driftloom
balloons balloon race
just need to burst as many of my
adorable balloons
oh come on that's breath of the wild man
okay
17 balloons
find me here anytime let me know okay
i guess we can try
balloon race [\h__\h] is that difficult
how do i pop them is it difficult
burst them all
yeah i want to do it
i'll i'll give it a try
no no nine six no following there total
fruity
okay 45 seconds
should get
that is easy it's easy okay
oh dreamlands i can't dash though all
right i tried dashing hold feet
oh i can't dash
oh what about the pokemon [\h__\h] don't get
damaged oh it's really easy indeed
oh i'm gonna jump
ah [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] camera
look
when i'm holding b i can't move the
camera
oh what
well definitely um that's enough but for
sure
are we done
oh that's it
wait how do you
how do you jump
but apparently you must jump because uh
leave be pressed for constant blues and
jumper fly okay
20 balloons
should i do it again will i get
something if i get all of them probably
huh probably a heart container
[Laughter]
you beat my attack of versing 17
i get oh it's complete though
hmm
i guess i can try again
controlling the camera though while uh
zooming
is a tough one
maybe i get rupees the fans will get
older you must now return the food no no
but do i get anything better i wonder
if i get them all i get a red candy aha
okay i'll try i'll try again
[Music]
come here
go go go
[Music]
[Laughter]
adjusting the camera is [\h__\h] annoying
though
ah
oh i got something though
orcina let's see
let me try again then
i don't want to give up here we're so
close
to
[Music]
a certain purpose what the [\h__\h]
i wanted to be there
[Music]
oh come on
oh man
oh
oh that shitty camera
[\h__\h] that [\h__\h]
i got honey
well great oh man
let me put some items here man
um actually
oh man
man
[Music]
it's making me mad
it's not costing me money though is it
at least that's something
okay
what the [\h__\h] is that camera dude what
the [\h__\h] is that
press x
uh
see the camera swear to god
[Music]
oh backwards
it was a close one
maybe maybe maybe that's good enough
[Music]
those two if i if the camera would
adjust itself i wouldn't have to
miss those last two
i have to learn to do it
like without adjusting the camera like i
don't know man
there is no time to adjust the camera
but like how the how the [\h__\h] will i
know where i'm going
[Music]
okay now it's moving pretty nicely
but there's some corners that
where it looks like [\h__\h]
okay okay pretty good
oh that was good that was smooth that
was pretty smooth
come on
[\h__\h] where the [\h__\h]
is going so well
oh it's going so well
[Music]
maybe maybe maybe maybe
hallelujah
[Music]
i popped every single one it was pretty
difficult man
nugget
rare candy oh
not only a chimken nugget
whoa
oh no i don't want to rant actually
sorry uh i like to do some shopping
oh ten thousand
hell to the yeah
oh yeah
that is worth it yeah ten thousand i
didn't know you only said rare candy now
we're talking
let's see i didn't what is that
i i'm stupid
i still have problems with this uh
inventory
um
let's use this
i don't know i might just
get like higher level versions of those
two
i'm gonna use it on you for now
nice that was fun that was fun
a bit frustrating but still fun
okay uh can i go on an idol meeting
really quickly guys
eh
i can check the new house that's true
but i would have to go back to the city
huh
uh
or i can just look online
uh do i check hairstyles first
let me quickly uh where is it
where the [\h__\h] is it again
where is home
prosperity's lost satchel
how do i get home again
oh
wait is that a side quest
meeting first okay brb uh
lost status are a good mechanic wait do
i get more space in my own satchel if i
pick those up with
you can help them get their items back
oh
oh oh how i'm professional
okay see you in the moment see you in a
moment
you
i brought a cat with me
guess who
he's junkies
hello junkies
hello oh
do you hear that
soft
soft pearl
and when i hear too and my headphones
sound so nice in the headphones
[Music]
who's
[Applause]
hmm
[Music]
okay
i'm turning into a cat
[Laughter]
yum yum yum yum
there's so much to do i don't know what
to do i want to get an eevee i wanna i
wanna i wanna do so much let's go let's
go to uh
where was it what did you say
crescent shaped something
was it then uh where did they say was it
somewhere here probably no
let's go oops now let's go to field
lance camp
i want that ev
yes sir
i need it
when you want mushroom recipe
oh
you know girl yeah yep listen emma i
need to tell you about a great cake or
recipe huh
mushroom cake ew disgusting
and teach me the recipe
and i spray the good wood by using it
okay
thank you
uh give more of the item ah it's pretty
much room do i have it with me
no i apparently i don't but i know i i
think i have one in there
yes i do
uh
i forgot how many he wanted i think two
i just got an eevee what are you gonna
turn it into
what you're gonna do with it
mushroom mushroom cake that sounds so
disgusting
for a one in a while pokemon and if it's
partial to a nice mushroom snack you can
bet your bottom toadstool it will go
after the cake alert
you can use that opening to make your
getaway or of course try to catch the
pokemon
oh okay
that's interesting we haven't tried that
yet throwing food at
ah
throwing food at the pokemon we haven't
tried that yet but okay
not a hotel thank you mushroom cake
marketing
hmm
you wanted something
is that how it goes
that's how it goes
you want to learn about it okay i can
teach you
you call it shiny if you [\h__\h] no way
i'll show you the completed pokedex ew
maybe in my free time
uh
i think during my
skiing trip like
when i'm bored when i have some time
like while while i'm traveling
i might
i might play pokemon i'll bring my
switch with me i wonder if um
rmt yeah
i wonder if rmt is playing it too
because she
played um
the other one the pikachu and ebe one
uh
i think she yeah she also played certain
shield i remember we both played it at
the same time i remember that actually
so
she might just not have gotten it yet
but i think if i show it to her
she would totally play this one as well
so you can
play it at the same time hey oh wait i
have a mouse
oh wait can i pick up stuff while i'm
riding
yes
hallelujah
okay so where is my beautiful evie don't
attack me you will regret it
[Music]
what about this can i get these two
nah
that would be nice
if i could uh
collect those as well
[Music]
oh nice jump
but the the evie was here what it was
here man
but someone said something about kristen
shape that looks like crescent shaped to
me but i don't know
they all do
look like that to me
let's look around a bit more this is
where i found it yesterday exactly and
there's a nice punita
a rapid dash i guess
not ponyta
oh it's raining
oh
[Music]
evie
i saw one earlier i got away [\h__\h]
i wonder if electro pokemon are not
gonna come out when it's raining
because that would mean that we're not
gonna see pichu either
pichu was somewhere
here as well what what is that what did
they mean with crescent shape do you
think they meant this one
wonder if we can get over there
let's try
uh wait which way is that wrong way
someone's property
my junior's there again guys
what junior
oh god what should we do did that one
just run away immediately should i try
to catch it
uh without having it notice me
what you need
what what are the the feather balls
again by the way
there is a feather ball
it runs when i try to attack him so i
have to throw a ball huh
all right let me
that that warm
warm pokemon is freaking out over this
dancing
okay it's sleep it's sleeping i think
red bulls and flies ah okay
it's sleeping
it's still there oh no
[\h__\h]
safety ah
damn
but i'm pretty lucky with finding this
pokemon
okay well um
that was that was i wonder if last time
we also found it here or somewhere else
i think it was somewhere else
um
anyone
and how do i
i need to get up there
is that possible
fly
fly you fools
maybe
without
no
oh get up there
how else
how else do i ah wait no there's a cut
off here
how do i how do i get there
hmm
well i get there
when i get there gonna go around i'm
trying i'm trying okay i guess i need to
put
where is it accessible and what is not
accessible hmm
all right
just gonna roam around if we're lucky
we're gonna find something interesting
just by roaming around
at
[Music]
how are you
i'm looking for special pokemon and
you're not special
maybe we find an alpha on the way as
well
[Music]
that scream out of happiness by the way
when i won the race and hurt my throat
again
but i was so excited
i can't hold it fast
and alpha evie is that is that even
possible i wonder
birds
but until then i was uh doing pretty
well today i must stay
until the scream i was feeling
better than yesterday
um
so that's that's a good thing
are there any stats that then evie is
more
uh likely to show up during the evening
time or night time
i can't quite imagine but
[Music]
alpha even came up in the morning
you can find hordes of evie where where
where where where where where where
where
morning time you sent i got a shiny evie
what the [\h__\h]
what did you just did she just stumble
across it randomly
i found more in the morning than at
night okay let me turn into morning time
maybe the rain will stop as well maybe
it doesn't want to come out because of
the rain
[Music]
spawn in the same place if there would
be dupes kill them sleep and try again
do we have to kill them can we not just
go to sleep
um
i like to rest
until morning
senpai
it's not hard to find a shiny tree but
um
well how likely is it to find the shiny
without having one of those shiny chains
or does that is that not a thing
in this game
shiny chains
farming eevees there's a video about it
shiny raids are higher
that's nice of them
wait now now would be a good time to
turn on some bgm
i hope this is okay
[Music]
we're also partially looking for pizza
by the way
maybe managed to look somewhere else not
here but that's where i found the eevee
originally
[Music]
so loud
okay
um well
[Music]
you leave me no choice but to uh
catch
is you
i guess the equivalent of killing you
[Music]
okay
oh it's a heavy specimen for the purina
so
um
now i sleep again
this should have been a real bgm it's
pretty good right right i was looking
for some bgms
before the stream
[Music]
foreign
oh is that just uh people trying to
impress me with their information but
she did not actually get a shiny
would have impressed me uh but
apparently football game senpai is once
again doing a shiny only run by the way
i think she's playing right now
too i watched a bit beforehand uh but
without a shiny starter i suppose
oh interesting spots
[Music]
who's that
is that one of those satchels
oh i found it by accident
yeah she wants another shiny magikarp
but i have a feeling that it's not gonna
take her as long as it did uh previously
um in in the other game
yeah
wait so what happens with the last
satchel
wait where is
off
what is that lost and found oh
[Music]
if you're black
oh you might lose some of your i'm not
oh
if you find a satchel someone else was
lost be sure to pick it up to settle
your tree it will be returned to its own
and you can receive merit points oh
that's cute
ah that's
that's what that lady is for mp can be
exchanged for items at the training
pleasure and pick up stuff
you may be able to get your hands on
some very special items
[Music]
contain 19 types wait if you black out
do you lose all of your items
unless someone returns it to you
what
[Music]
all right so this counts as you received
a i received the bank you give
[Music]
oh
and what about these these are i i i
they are on my map but i haven't found
them
[Music]
or i found them and they didn't thank me
yet
yes okay so i haven't found them yet
they are my map
that's pretty cute
that's another cute function
that
was not necessary but
wow
alpha uh alpha boy
one looks strong though
so you saw i wonder what level
um
electricity do we even have something
that's effective against him
focus to check the level okay we try
[Music]
feature in that area
safe
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
wait how do i say it again here
let me see i want to see where i am okay
here
[Music]
you're saying pichu might be somewhere
here
that is worth checking out
[Music]
oh
puppy oops stop running poppy nella
is that you
[Music]
a [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
why'd you have to move
really bad at aiming right now
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
ah
beautiful
i think in germany was papinella
[Music]
our first one number cut during daylight
hours and yes yes oh there's more
there's so many
are they having a great time here
[Music]
my daughter attacking me they're
attacking me ah
okay we can fight uh i don't know what i
have that's good uh
a level even are you here take this
[Applause]
might be too low level oh no
no we're fine we're fine
wait if i use hypnosis it counts as me
seeing the pokemon using hypnosis right
[Music]
oh wait now we can now i need to stop
the music
listen
[Music]
okay well we have now seen it use
hypnosis
um nice
i turned off the pgm
[Music]
that barely did any damage
it's astonishing
is that two damage
power 30 that's [\h__\h] weak
and so weak
uh man
oh man i don't have any electric pokemon
left
oh [\h__\h] uh
it's stabbed oh
[Music]
a phoenix must always go strong style
maybe this owl can learn from
phoenix's power and oh why am i not
moving there we go
let me take off road candy it's time for
fruit candy
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
take a [\h__\h] chill pill
you want to fight really you sure
fine with me
are you not naming your pokemon
ah
i fight for girls
i guess i could
uh only the ones that i am actually
using though
[Music]
we just um we're not even doing any
quests right now we're just looking for
pokemon i hope that's not boring to you
guys
but i find it pretty chill right now
okay maybe you guys need a tangent um
today i went to the supermarket
and i found uh wait why am i not moving
i found the the thing that you guys
previously recommended to me
uh what was it called again something to
sleep easier mella was it fella tony
melatonin
not pop their idea
[Music]
yeah i found it i thought you have to
buy it in a pharmacy but
wait they're already so high level no
yeah you guys told me that it would help
um
to sleep
fall asleep easier i might try it
tonight even
does anyone have the experience with
using that
oh
[\h__\h] is clutch it's not strong enough to
warm that it does help oh
ah it's not strong enough to warrant
being sold at a pharmacy
[Music]
i did buy it yeah be careful not to
overtake it
yeah yeah yeah
of course
one hour before sleeping one hour before
bedtime oh a lot of you guys seem to
have experience with it
doing your normal sleeping always
oh
i usually only take a
wait wait wait this is interesting i use
it regularly it's great it's a hit and
miss based on the person not directly
melting when you study them
just give yourself a solid 10 hours or
so with it
uh-huh
naturally oh that reducing your body i
guess so
i need to go in and get really sleepy
within an hour wow
just take two mg reduces chemicals that
make you sleepy that your body naturally
just hit
allows the help for your body naturally
yeah i i don't have a problem with
sleeping
like falling asleep in general and
sleeping a lot that's i'm i'm good with
that it's just my problem is that i need
to force myself to sleep earlier in
order to fix my sleep schedule which it
has been [\h__\h] up for so long that
honestly i don't really care that much
anymore but
i could give it a try with that um
now
with melatonin what am i doing why did i
go into my inventory ah in order to heal
[Music]
uh
yeah
i wanted to heal
melatonin will help with that
interesting
i will give it a try then
and i will report back to you guys if it
worked
no sure
[Music]
wanted i really wanted
[\h__\h] something's attacking me what is
that
wait whose attention have i grabbed
you
i want the pizza
oh my god oh my god uh safe oh [\h__\h]
i don't know why but i like to press uh
plus in order to get into a menu but
it's not [\h__\h] plus
save
pizza
uh what should i attack it with
something that doesn't kill it um
what does what will not kill it
ah wait we have a verb we have to burp
or should i should i first try to ah
should i just try to use a pokeball
it's so far away though
how's my
accent creature's keeping his guard up
[\h__\h] um
pro pokemon
please please
i'll be so good to you i'll be so good
to you
ah
don't run away
it's keeping his guard up okay maybe it
doesn't really want
[Music]
safe's coming for pichu well it's
[\h__\h] cute
it's [\h__\h] cute man is it still there
does this really work
oh
this grass is pretty close
yes
throw food first
[\h__\h]
i didn't notice me what kind of food
what kind of food i only have
[\h__\h]
berry
wobble wobble oh
[Music]
i don't know why i keep on doing that
oh i want to switch it up but i can't
right now
can't take it into the team right now
but we'll change it up later
okay the only one i want now is an eevee
an eevee would be nice
hoshina
not gonna fight that boy though i'm
scared
i'm pretty scared i should however i
don't think i've ever uh
i thought that was a the the cocoon
pokemon but it's not
hello
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] i'm not here
uh
i think
i need to fight these number of defeat
at zero
number i caught zero
i don't need to catch it i already had
one but okay
why
ah we're finals on i'm fine fine
okay okay okay
did you know there's a requested gift
that gives the shiny ponyta what
ah this is a different one oh okay okay
okay
uh okay
saved
okay
uh
only killed that one successfully
maybe let's catch that one over there
is it sleeping
i think it's sleeping
come join my team
or my pastor oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
now you want to fight okay
should i kill it
kill it
please imagine you need to just
a little bit because your body produces
its own but if you're insane
it's important in the brain uh-huh yeah
i am inside a lot
does it
is that the one that gets produced when
you go outside
thank you for the membership welcome
thank you thank you thank you
welcome
[Music]
i want my [\h__\h] evie man is that too
much to ask
oh
don't mind me boys
sun controls my sleep circle i don't
feel very controlled by it to be honest
i feel like i'm in full control
17 months when you say it like that it
sounds so long again
should i catch more drift loons
[\h__\h] there's so many
[Music]
number you're defeated oh i can defeat
it with my own driftwood now and then
get that one
uh
let's do it ghost effective against
ghost
let's go
if i went full control i wouldn't be
having this problem
it's not like
like if i really need to wake up at a
specific time if i have a reason for it
then
i am able to do it
i just when i don't have a reason for it
then i'm also my body is like why why
are we doing this let's just continue
watching netflix
like for hours and hours knows
you know
[Music]
time to look for
evie
you feel that thank you
i feel that too
[Music]
what is that in the grass
a little beetle okay
yeah there's maybe there is nothing
wrong with that
there's no problem with that
all the same pokemon you know what i'm
gonna go towards the
request
the main quest now
we'll find an eevee eventually
worst case i'll i'll get it off screen
but i think i'm sure there will be other
areas where suddenly i'll be overwhelmed
by the sheer amount of
eevees running at me
right thank you for the super chat you
found a shiny gee dude as you were
watching
what the [\h__\h] how like were you looking
for it or did it just randomly
stumble across you
what the hell
they're very fast i know yeah i need to
switch and teacher
okay uh
oh
switching pichu
i want to see my pokemon
look at that cutie pie okay so that
might actually be
one of the members that we're actually
keeping pony don't know
because we had her before
um
my peach is female
and my triple is a girl too and my bible
really is a girl too
so many girls man
now i shall
uh why do you name them
uh change name
you guys were asking for it now you
finally get it what shall i name pichu
um help me out here
um
[Music]
sparks
oh yes beethoven is cute too but it
looks very sparky it has the beast box
so that's all that's so that sparkle
[Music]
don't stop don't stop i'm thinking about
keeping drifloon
is there flow strong uh or i guess we
can probably get stronger girls pokemon
later on but the thing is we we didn't
use a ghost pokemon ghost type at all in
the last run so i'm thinking of at least
uh bringing in a ghost
pokemon this time
please no different
this one is tanky driftling is good okay
then at least for now i want to keep
drifloon
um
okay
let's let's uh find something that's not
too obvious
um
what do we call it no no we're not gonna
call it 99 no no that's boring
[Music]
casper is a ghost true nana
[Applause]
i said nothing that's too obvious
[Music]
gum
it does look like bubble gum it does
look like it's bubblegum somehow
don't you agree
helium airhead
that's cute
holo balloon
boing boing
why
because it makes me sleepy
because it can use hypno hypno
hypnotosis
i don't understand some of you guys's
name ideas because i don't get the
references for some of them floaty boy
spookers
spookers that's cute
ah
no toast
what did you say
inflation but no we call it inflame
inflate tune
inflate non-inflation inflation if i
shoot
yes
okay it's a stupid name i'm not quite
happy with it but
and we named bibarel
oh
chunk
because he's alpha and his big oops
big boy
the rest i don't want to keep them so
i'm not keeping them
okay we got some names finally
anything else i wanted to do can i craft
something
yes i can
[Music]
what craft 11 of those
all of those oh i can only do two okay
i'm gonna make all of those and
all of those
why the hell
not okay
looking good how's my inventory looking
i'm looking pretty empty
okay
are we ready to go
when was the last time she used dusters
i don't even remember ever using it
where are we going where are we going
that way
on our way to
our destiny
while also collecting some stuff on the
way it's pretty far away man
they could have given me like a
a checkpoint over there that would have
been nice
[Music]
don't mind me dude
do you dude
sorry no one wants to play with you
sorry you're not one of the cutest
pokemon
use candy on pizza i think it will
level up just fine
[Music]
oh wait
you know what i just thought what that
was
i thought it was that um
sword and shield version of that one
pokemon with the leak the duck pokemon
with the leak
for some reason
because of the the gray
bird body
that would have been fun
[Music]
see how it's flying but the animation is
like a
freaking picture show
i was gonna be like yo it's flying but
oh okay now it's flying normally
hold up
did you see that
two frames per second
but it's flying that's cool
wait a second let me get out my
tangent
[Music]
ah
the other day
you know how
uh
uh probably you guys have the same issue
probably also get recommended uh a lot
of polls on youtube don't you
defeated number i've called let's catch
it
uh
i know what to use
yeah yeah the v2 bubbles which member
and whole live e and blah blah blah
which member of holland blah blah blah
now um there was this one poll the other
day
and it was asking
which member
i think it was in hollow myth
which member in the holland
swears the most
and
i'm i'm self-aware i voted for myself i
know what's up
but then maybe you saw it
kelly was by far number one in that pool
um
which is just
just not accurate
oh do you dude
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
right i think we can all say that and i
think even even
uh deadbeats would know
that i swear more way more than callie
but the pole
callie was like so far ahead of everyone
else
yeah it's a matter of public image
exactly so those polls honestly they're
absolute crap because the people who
vote in those polls they have no idea
what they're talking about
and i feel like you know when when i
collab with the other myth girls just by
watching those collabs you should
you should know you should realize you
should see it you should have actual
proof
very immediate obvious proof that i
swear a ton
i mean i guess maybe it's good that i
didn't win and oh the alpha is back
maybe it's good that i didn't win in
that poll but um
i don't know
it's just those balls are so
inaccurate the the
the results of them are mostly
so inaccurate it's ridiculous
public perception yeah i was reading the
comments and a lot of people were
writing in the comments of that poll
that the result is ridiculous people
have no idea they they are probably the
people who voted for callie
probably don't even watch kelly
because if they watch kelly they would
probably know she doesn't she maybe she
swears like a bit but by far not as much
as i do
[Music]
they probably don't even watch her
they just they probably
um
watch yourself maybe i don't know gouda
and they're like yo uh probably callie
probably callie swears a lot
it must be kelly
[Applause]
[Music]
i'll try to catch it
oh you want to be called anyway don't
you
right in front of me
callie's ashamed of it
[Music]
you're not gonna stick small in people's
minds what
they might only watch clips but even in
clips don't i swear a lot
not that i like really really wanna be
number one but
oh heavy specimen
i just feel like the that is a that is
proof good proof
that the polls are
stupid
it's so stupid
i mean i think i know why those channels
are doing it because it really works
well in the algorithm i mean i'm not i'm
not subscribed to those channels and yet
i have those polls in my
um algorithm all the [\h__\h] time
[Music]
so i i understand that's probably why
they're doing the polls
if you ask
hollow fans
a question
about
um holo ian for example
people want to prove that they know
their holo members that they know their
stuff
and in order to prove it
what can one do but share their
knowledge in a poll which is very
important
very important knowledge
oh i know who swears the most in
halloween i'm sure it's cali
diana runs around full series yeah it is
fun to click the button like i whenever
i see a ball
most of the time i i vote in it too just
because i want
i i probably know um myth members better
than most of the people who are voting
so i want to share
um the truth you know
i want to share the truth
[Music]
get rid of that misconception man
actually let
no not you what do you want
you look so happy
i need to give it food huh
sometimes you've seen this confusion but
i'll give you food um
[Music]
that's [\h__\h] pokemon
any food
[Music]
he took that as a threat you don't want
to eat it
[Music]
he took that personally
[\h__\h]
okay
uh
what is called mind these are quiet
it doesn't like the berries i suppose
wait does it really not like the berries
what what food does it want to be fed
um
yes i agree yeah there should be a poll
that asks who is the most bottom left
and it should be me winning by far
yes i agree that is so so true
[Music]
so true bestie
make a poll oh maybe i should imitate
those polls maybe i should act like i'm
one of them put out some polls on my
community page
who is that who is the cutest of hollow
myth and then give give only kiwa choice
kind of um
just just trying to
sabotage
get into everyone's minds
mind control guys
propaganda
there's only one answer what the [\h__\h]
can i not get up there
don't understand what the hell that
that anton
psyduck wanted from me
man
what do you want
i still haven't caught one okay
um
[\h__\h] it's looking at me
i'll throw it anyway
yes finally we got a silkoon
it's about time
who's the best way to win the world is
there a pokemon down there
no
i wonder if later we can ride on a
pokemon uh to to be able to surf in
water
thank you for renewing your membership
a bear polar bear
um hello
i'm back
i know it took me some time
yeah it also makes me think of lonely
island when i say man
so you saying that gal uh you galaxy
people came up with a method to try to
quell lord cleveland's frenzy
i guess so food i forgot which one
though
you'll mash up clear his favorite foods
into balls so you can throw offerings at
him well that's quite an unorthodox
approach your galaxy people your
inventiveness just blows me away i mean
now you can make offerings to lord
cleaver from a safe distance
i'll land you my aid if it means we
might provide cleaver with his offering
let's begin at once
yeah
i wanna i need to i need to make an
umbrella for her i need to craft an
umbrella for her she's getting wet maybe
that's maybe it's good
whatever the plan is you'll need
cleaver's favorite plump beans i've
brought them as promised thank you
god that's right my apologies erida i'd
forgotten all about you
i admit as we haven't been able to solve
this ourselves we seem to have a little
choice but to turn to the galaxy team
but even i still have my doubts about
whether we should entrust such a thing
to an outsider these galaxy team people
don't share our customs or our values
so prove to me you're willing you stand
in the press oh
[\h__\h] i have my pichu out right now
[\h__\h] she wants to fight me
glass in
uh oh wait hold on
glass soon
no it's not too much for me i just uh
wait glaston is an ice pokemon right i
don't have a fire pokemon what else
should i definitely not my planned
pokemon
brass pokemon what should i go with
uh ice man [\h__\h]
rock i don't have a rock do i but i have
chunk should i do chunk okay
at least my chunk is alpha
hell yeah
oh cute
looks like smoothies
look how chunky he is
[Music]
well i have eyes too
okay but we're gonna do a roll out
strong start
yeah we gotta do strong stuff
i think
actually let's do normal
normally
good good
good damage he do be chunky
look at him look at his glorious
chunkiness
she got to attack twice man
is it because my chunky boy is so chunky
that he's so slow
well no problem though no problem
battle has been decided anyway
big boy
he do be chunky
yes yes
i see now poke balls are simply your
tools of choice not powers of disregard
for pokemon oh yes
you still understand the pokemon that
you've caught and treat them as partners
i feel better putting my trust in you
now i think
let me see your pokemon's wounds
i want wounds
now explain the galaxy team's plan what
do you mean to do with these foods
i throw him at them
so because you have to keep your
distance you'll mash clive's food
favorite foods together
roll them up and try to crawl his frenzy
by throwing them on him
interesting so you've developed soothing
bombs of sorts to calm our lord
very well if it will help soothe
cleavage frenzy let's make these bombs
with our very hearts themselves
and throw it on the ground
looking good there a very devil mountain
of worms this should please cleaver if
anything can
now then ready yourself and i will
summon our mighty cleaver lord of the
woods
i'm ready i think [\h__\h] i think i am
i only have to throw stuff right
it goes off
will it be the legendary what pokemon
are we talking about
though it isn't yet the time of the
ceremony we've prepared an offering of
your favorite things
benevolent lord who works his might
between the heavens and earth we offer
our gratitude i beseech you reveal to
our eyes
listen well kiawah keep your focus on
cleaver
dodging will be vital oh okay try to
avoid these moves as you're throwing the
bombs okay okay okay that's fun that
sounds like fun
what is it
what's it look like
big tree
deku tree
give me your nuts
what is that
completely new pokemon right oh [\h__\h] or
is it history version of that
cypher yeah yeah yeah that's what i was
thinking
it looks a little bit like it to climb
victory against the normal pokemon noble
pokemon
nobles
and quella's frenzy you'll have to throw
bombs in it until its frenzy gloss
reaches zero
if you manage to create an opening
in the noble's defenses you'll be able
to send out your pokemon to battle
against it oh [\h__\h] that didn't save
if you win the pokemon battle and the
noble's guard will stay down for a brief
time
uh during
win the pokemon battle and the nobles
gone we're staying down for brief time
during that window bombs will be more
effective than usual so throw as many as
you can
well okay uh oopsie oh god
[Applause]
[Music]
throwing
pokemon okay uh which one which one
shit's over lately delay it's late too
late
ah
which one a water one [\h__\h]
[Music]
double hit okay
cleaver down to the stance
it's okay
oh okay
[Music]
oh that's a lot of damage
are we gonna kill it
he said that we have to like defeat it
in battle and then yeah continue uh to
grow
[Music]
i need keyboard and mouse yeah
controller isn't working well this
in this situation trunks don't die don't
die jump
[Music]
should i heal
i better heal
heal that chunky boy
[Music]
him to be honest
yes
indeed
[Music]
oh guess when you make him bunk against
the tree
you will immediately be able to do a
battle
ah
i can one hit
him how many times i have to do it
i slice you up
yeah
[Music]
uh one question can i heal right now
sorry we're in the middle of running
away but chunky boy
since uh that noble pokemon always seems
to get the first hit i need to heal you
ow
ow oh oh
oh
this is the last one
almost done
show cleaver you power yes uh should i
uh catch it this time or still kill it
i guess
we're still we're still killing it right
[Music]
we're still killing it
can't catch okay
yes fishing
good boy
calm down eat this food
that's what we do at kfp
magic
oh you look very different now
not very charming but
yeah
nice dodges thank you
not noble anymore
hole
he really doesn't look much like his
original form huh
an insect plate stone tablet imbued of
the essence of bugs when used on a
certain pokemon it allows that pokemon
to gain the power of the bug time
oh is this a stone book
stone bug type
it's an evolved what
is it the pokemon i'm thinking of let me
let me see um
cypher
cypher yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
wait did that one never have an
evolution
but what is that red cipher
that comes up
that's shiny or what
sci-fi
it did but it has a new one is the red
one the evolution
um
ah
and now
and now this is the other evolution
[Laughter]
what what happened
some kind of light erupted from clara's
body
has lord clever's frenzied mind truly
been put at ease now
does this confirm that the strange
lightning was to blame for cleaver's
unnatural power
the other evil solution is still is
one's rocket
[Music]
cleaver is new for this game
yeah i think i see it in the trailer
baby
i think so
well this is what i think after all
we've seen
we know strange lightning came from out
of the space-time rift the other night
those boats must have struck cleaver and
driven him into his frenzy after all can
we stop using that word i really don't
like it
the lightning came from the space-time
rift
but if almighty signal really does dwell
beyond the space-timer of denver state
strange lightning and indeed was
almighty sinners power
then were we even right to try to
interfere
i happily went along with this plan to
create some bombs as if i knew what i
was doing like some kind of thoughtless
fool outrageous inconceivable
calm yourself lion
liam remember that the lord of the words
has long been our protector keeping the
pearl clown safe from dangerous pokemon
that might harm us
would power sent by the true almighty
signal have driven cleaver to turn on us
and attack people on pokemon
indiscriminately i doubt it what quinoa
accomplished just now it needed to be
done
the gaki is enraged throw bombs at him
yeah
or give him a snickers
i'm glad we could settle this without
further strive with the diamond clan or
the galaxy team if you come across other
pokemon in the grip of this painful
frenzy please help them
i'm apologizing sorry not sorry please
take these on behalf of the pro clan
consider it my apology for having spoken
rudely to you earlier and the token of
my thanks
i love you
yes we can marry yes
ah berries look
i thought it was a ring
let me care for your pokemon as well in
appreciation for fighting on our health
hmm
i think i finally come to believe that
you truly did fall out of the sky though
i still cannot imagine the reasons that
play
and it seems like settled uh scenes of
saddle things here
i wouldn't mind seeing lord cleaver in
such a frenzy again he was faithfully
strong after all
yeah that was actually a very fun battle
i must say
i like it i enjoyed it it was um
again pretty
stressful
but that made it challenging so i think
that's good where are we where does the
game want us to go
he wants us to go home
uh well no it wants us to go
yeah wants us to go home
wait do i need to go to the fairlands
camp in order to go home
but i want to check out a bit more in
this area before i go home
[Music]
scyther is nearby
really could i catch it
hello big boy
[Music]
come on
oh [\h__\h]
oh he didn't notice come on right in its
big mouth
hook
[Music]
[\h__\h]
there we go
i want to see alpha wylor that would be
epic we got him
[Music]
that was easy
what is this place here
[Music]
oh the honey honeybees honeycomb
thingies
there's honey on the ground are you guys
gonna attack me if i take it
[Music]
did they notice me
i'm gonna catch a few combi
such a cute pokemon
[Music]
number cut oh that's the first one
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] don't go away
that helps lock on for aiming i guess so
oh it does not want to fight
look at that that's the the the before
the evolution the original form
whoa
uh wait so that is uh
bug flying
what's effective wait let me see
what's effective against the
bug flying
catch it yeah we'll try i guess but i
feel like we should first
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] no already noticed me uh rock oh
god wait not two at once
uh
[Music]
well even if we're killed by accident
we can still catch the other one
hopefully
oh i one hit him
oops totally not on purpose
[Music]
we have that special move that keeps
cypher alive
uh although you scared me with your eyes
was that an ice attacker what the [\h__\h]
swipe
my froze have been pretty bad yeah
adopted a hard hitting stance that's
okay
it do be okay go swipe again
oh sheesh
don't kill me
it's a bug move okay don't kill me
got it
oh oh okay
uh
[Music]
i try
uh oopsie i try
[Music]
roost heals
heals half of the hp oh
thank you i didn't know i didn't realize
[Music]
yeah
can i get up here no
[Music]
yes i can
is there no climbing option
that is dodging the only way you can try
to get up uh that place
[Music]
mount yes yes
i think we got what we wanted here
let me steal some more of your honey
what are you doing here
oh so many of you
what about evie's though
are there some eevee scraps there's a
tunnel i wonder if i have to go through
that for the story
[Music]
evie close to the village
evie is evie only in the start area
oh
i'm guessing i'm guessing we're gonna be
here
later anyway only spawns in one location
but there are okay well then okay i'm
going um
uh
for sure
i'm gonna go there again
last last try i'm gonna try for the last
time to find that stupid evie
god damn it
i'm probably gonna find it and then lose
it again
only three spots well i know of one spot
[Music]
horseshoe
go by foot
uh well i'm here now
in this area
um
[Music]
maybe i should save
i can't oh because someone's attacking
me right
now you said so
oh
save it
big deer ain't sally yeah keep on
pressing it by accident
there's no evie here
[Music]
someone give me an evie
maybe one of you wants to send me an
evie
bambi
[Music]
you wanted to find evie but i see you
said starting area only yeah well that's
my problem
that's my problem you got your attention
that's cheating that's not cheating
trading pokemon is a culture
women's pokemon that's absolutely normal
[Music]
oh holy [\h__\h] it's so aggressive shall we
try to kill it
[Music]
or
catch it
oh [\h__\h] be careful
[Music]
how [\h__\h] big are you rambling
a little [\h__\h]
run
[Music]
sorry for disturbing you i did not
expect you to be level 40.
[Music]
too strong too strong
run
hmm yeah it is very pretty though
a huge horseman
i want that horse
[Music]
what are you doing you want to fight
no you just want to play
i'm not here to play
i don't think there is an eevee here at
the moment
i'm also kind of off the track now
[Music]
oh it's called horseshoe planes because
the huge rabbit dash is there huh
it's around that spot really where it
was just now yeah okay okay
do i need to catch everything here in
order to make it spawn
[Music]
near the water
i didn't need to sleep or reset sleep to
reset spawns
okay
shock is fixated on use rollout
chicks you feel like crying now you feel
like running away now perhaps
i defeated chinks good job donkey boy
i am going to
go
back
although i'm really close thankfully at
least it's very close
sleepy time
[Music]
morning
midday
it doesn't really matter right but let's
do a morning time
focus on one spot where you already saw
an eevee if there's another pokemon
there kill cats to rest
don't just rest past time huh isn't that
what i'm doing
all right
[Music]
maybe i'll be lucky and find a shiny one
wishful thinking i know i know i know
[Music]
by the way
very random
but
i've been thinking about um
you know how
marine senpai and football is senpai
where the whoopsie of the ball were the
first uh whole life member
[Music]
members to appear on hold attack
um
[Music]
and i couldn't ask them the speed
questions right
[Music]
so
i was thinking
[Music]
i have to say i know i know i know i
know
um i don't really wanna i was thinking
instead of bringing them back on
holotalk again i was thinking of just
organizing
either solo collabs with each one of
them or
um a big collab with like maybe a four
person collab like mario party with
marian senpai fubuki senpai and another
en girl or so maybe and then at the end
of the stream i'll just bamboozle them
and i'll be like yo speed round hold up
speedrun out of nowhere and uh challenge
them
to a speed round
and that way we'll get the speed round
but i've been wondering if i do
one-on-one collabs what should i
anita especially for madden senpai i
feel like i need a good idea that really
gets her
interested in a one-on-one collab
because she's a busy woman
she's a busy woman
and she um
i think she
um
she's like
the type who
will definitely say yes if it's an
interesting collab but if it doesn't
tickle her fancy then it's like
[Music]
maybe not
oh [\h__\h] and there she goes
yeah okay okay
um
beauty novel reading
getting a permission to read a novel is
very difficult
drawing collab that doesn't sound that
interesting i think
i think the easiest would be
where i think they would both say yes if
i invite them to mario party with
another ian member
it is a weird combination and they might
be wondering
why did kiwawa invite us this is a weird
combination
oh but
oh phasmophobia i feel like he likes
spasmophobia but i don't like
flasmophobia so no thank you
um
[Music]
amy where the [\h__\h] are you
oh
[Music]
hey
hey listen
okay wait it it's still
it's still here let's uh go around for
the grass
for a berry
[Music]
uh
yeah but i thought that it would
probably be more like mostly um
um
a japanese
a mainly japanese co-op maybe not even
on my channel but it would be great if
it was not on my channel and that i
would suddenly do the speed
speed uh
hold hog speed round are you interested
in that barry oh badoo seems to be
interested too oh [\h__\h] don't run away
vadoof is so [\h__\h] chunky screaming in
the earthquake around it
oh [\h__\h]
and evie is scared of beethoven
boy
[Music]
come to me
oh
well i am an idiot
[Music]
asserting dominance
asserting dominance like
[Music]
come on come back
[\h__\h] helmet
stupid evie playing games with me
we're gonna be best friends
trust me
how high do i have to go beside
no
come on
an english or german learning collab um
i want something more entertaining
[Music]
okay
oh we have apparently not been spotted
either
yoka
my my own my very own kusuogaki evie
we i feel like we spent a lot of time
today just wandering around
time goes by actually much faster than
yesterday i feel like
um i will go back to the main quest now
now that i have my eb
it goes on
i'll stay up i want to see my pokemon
but i still don't know what i want to
evolve it into we'll have to think about
it and also have to find the
a fitting item i suppose so
wait wait if it's normal right
[Music]
oh
i guess we got rid of dust ducks
we'll have to
check the stats okay i have to figure
out what to do uh a fire pokemon would
indeed be nice because we currently
don't have one in our team and if this
is like the fourth gen like diamond
pearl then we're gonna have a problem
finding fire pokemon anyway
and we're not using ponita because uh
rapidash because we used it last time
yeah yeah yeah safe safe okay okay
[Music]
which one was the the fire one vaporeon
or something like that oopsie i wanna uh
name it
[Music]
how dare you
but i'm so happy to have you now
i must
i must quickly
level you up a little bit
by
[Applause]
letting you maybe mind some things
of course
have you attacked some of these boys
evie versus bob
starly come on
you're a good match no
sally has been intimidated by the
silgaki
understandable
do you want to fight yes of course you
want to buy
what's up
[Music]
you can get chimchar i forgot what that
was was that a fire pokemon
[Music]
oh
it's pretty weak
[Music]
but wasn't that a startup pokemon
why can't i get it
here are you for
real are you kidding me
are you kidding me
it's not a start yeah it's a starter
because it's not a starter here well
that's cool but they oh wait was
chimchar originally of gen for starter
and that's why it's
since it was gen 4 but not a starter
that's what's here do i understand
correctly
[Music]
let's fight
okay well anyway now you uh back to
topic now you have my now you know of my
plans to
collab sometime soon with fubuki senpai
and mariam
just i mean
i mean it's a it's i would always love
to collab with them but it's a good
reason to
um ask them for a collab because i need
the speed dating and speeding i need to
speed quiz
questions answered for future references
looking forward to it
me too
we could also try to somehow
um maybe i was also thinking maybe maybe
uno with the rule that it's english only
um
which will make it difficult for them
but maybe a different world for myself
then
and if they speak japanese then we'll
have a battle game or something like
that
oh and then oh my god wait listen so i
say if you if you if you don't speak
english then you'll have a batsu game
and at the end i revealed about the game
and it is the speed quiz
[Laughter]
because uh i definitely want them to do
the batsu gamer and i think
i think it will be inevitable
that sounds genius what if they don't
fail they will trust me they will
oh they will wait
um
they definitely will
know
how
[Music]
that
what are you thinking about huh stupid
boob
chimpkins are better
even even eh even if they manage to go
for the whole game with english only
i'll say well you managed to
successfully speak english only but i
will
i shall challenge you anyway to a speed
quiz they'll do it gladly i'm sure of it
yeah
i think it is a genius idea
no stupid [\h__\h] cricket man
these pokemon that just don't have the
balls to fight me
fight me
come on
now i caught it unaware
either way kiara wins exactly
the game is ringed from the sky exactly
[Music]
but the question is which other ian
member should be my partner in crime
maybe someone that they would feel happy
about excited about collabing with
which will give them even more reason to
accept the collab
guru
yeah martin and fubuki definitely would
love to collab with buddha
both of them as well so actually yeah
i think that would make all parties
happy everyone would be happy
why am i doing why am i
i'm leveling evie right now
i suppose i'm feeling i feel like i'm
doing all of this very brain empty stuff
right now
no thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm not catching it
stream whatever sounds like just stream
whatever i don't care but no we are
telling people to stream
brain empty style
and soon it will be
stream
with amitori
oh oh
what could it be what could it be
i said it did you not hear it i'll
repeat it uh stream
with amy tori
did you hear it this time
[Music]
how obvious you have to make it stream
oh [\h__\h]
i saw that coming
stream
[Applause]
[Music]
anyway
uh
i have no more space in my satchel cool
good to know uh
so like he did that is sad
but we will now
go back
although this this satchel is really
close i want to try getting it
andy satchel
where is that
can i uh mark it
is that now
oh it doesn't show me the distance
um
i guess it's on the
hill somewhere ah there it is there it
is
this is really like breath of the day
they took a lot of
what the [\h__\h] are you
you look like my mount
is that rare is that a rare find
the normal version the pre-evolution
[\h__\h] did it disappear
it disappeared
that evolves to my mount but if i evolve
it then at least oh there it is
i could actually fight with it is that
what you're saying
oily oh
scary you're scaring me
have you never seen a stand up oh
[Music]
maybe not in 3d
oh no
not sure
they're standing there menacingly and
also i've never been scared before of a
zubat but when it's like
when it's coming at me like that
attacking me
holy [\h__\h] that actually really makes
these lame-ass pokemon scary for once
isn't that fascinating
[\h__\h]
[Music]
stupid pokemon
uh is it still here did it disappear
it's still there it really wants me to
catch it
nice dodge yeah good job
well yeah
oh i go up i'll go up i'll go up
oh oh oh oh it's also coming up
oh [\h__\h] i'm not here i'm not here i'm
not here
uh
um
come on come on come on
yo we got it
cool what's what type is that
boom headshot
[Laughter]
360 no scope
oh there's so many more oh i thought it
was special
oops
oh that is so
pretty
yeah hi
oh it's running away
just like
the animal that you're based on
[\h__\h] it fauna ah
i might if i use it
normal and then sign
they won't attack me huh
you're too scared of me anyway it's very
close now is it up there
yeah
come on
come on come on
yes i gotta go around
thank you
evie
baby i might change your name eventually
[Music]
threatening but ah that's why they died
i think i know now
okay i got the satchel
my quina
sunicorning
okay oopsie i'm out of here
finally sorry for the weight guys
and alpha sampler
one day we'll get this boy's satchel as
well
one day oops no that's not that's not
really what i wanted no no no
[Music]
no
oh
part of the game it feels like i'm
playing breath of the wild yo now no
more need to play breath of the wild
because i'm playing this game
i
guess maybe i'll do some shopping do i
have something to sell
no
maybe not i have something to craft
and
a craft
a lot of the heavy boys
breath of the signal
but they did that definitely on purpose
i mean come on oopsie
to make it so
similar it's not a bad thing it's very
good this is like
this is something that pokemon always
had the potential for
but they never used it
they never used the potential they had
like this
uh but now they did and it's really cool
it's really cool
[Music]
okay the crafting system i like as well
i mean it's obviously nothing
complicated
still it's still a children
uh a game aimed at children so that's
that
uh
what do you say how much do i get for
this i did a lot man
caught using back strike for the first
time
four thousand six hundred
[Music]
yeah we're we are big children yeah big
bubble bubble
doesn't need to be complicated yeah i
think i would like it less
if it was any more complicated anyway
i want it to be easy and simple and
quick i know a lot of people like very
complicated crafting system as well in
certain games but i think for pokemon
it's best to not over
over complicate it
[Music]
oh it seems you've made some new
observations let's have a look done oh
and most illuminating i'll update your
pokedex
thank you
do i get another rank now
still a little bit far from that but yes
i have quelled clever
yeah well report to the commander
thankfully not a commander like in
handmaid's tale
oh
holy [\h__\h] why is that joke so heavy
uh i saw the light fading into the sky
you must have quelled the lord pokemon
yes i did everyone everyone always knows
what i'm doing it's like everyone's
watching me i feel so stoked
what do you have there could it be
my mount no uh two of the fabled plates
of old oh i thought you were gonna say
something about my mount
where all creation was born that is the
being's place of origin or origin
oranges
it seems to be a phrase from a very old
myth hold on how did you come across
these
i don't know i just explored everything
i
guess i see so you were given the plates
when you impressed were deer and cleaver
i suppose so yeah
i forgot to be honest
that is quite something indeed my heart
is practically racing with excitement
it is my guess that you will find more
plates like these scattered across
history
if we were to gather them all and
decipher the scripts on them we may
uncover something absolute absolutely
amazing the mysteries of the past oh how
they take on my curiosity what a joy to
be alive in such times
when i must be on my brain until next
time bye-bye bye-bye
nice talking to you
wait let's check out the new hairstyles
i guess i hope i don't regret it
uh
500 is okay
thank you for the membership come send
me down welcome welcome
[Music]
mama
what's your name look i don't know what
you got
a braids
no wait that's old
we had that before what do you mean new
are you kidding me was i bamboozled the
the colors are old as well
[\h__\h] you
it's
they'll tell you when they have new ones
oh my god okay
um well i guess i'll change my hair
color
i guess we're going gold now
but hell no the the gold on the eyebrows
i don't like it
i don't like any of this
uh
all right i'll go with this
i'm not going bald like fauna hell no
i'm bleaching my hair
wow what a beautiful blonde hair color
actually it does look a little bit like
the yellow on the tips of my twin tails
i guess
thank you um
yeah
i look like a lime
[Laughter]
but in this slide it works and this
lighter looks okay come back any time
dear mm-hmm i'll come back when you got
new hairstyles
oh sure
lime joe
that's me
grandma what are you doing now
hmm you good
wait what is that what is that what is
that blackboard
nothing okay
uh to the commander we go
i think
yo i feel like i made barely any
progress today but i kind of hmm
it's already four hours yo
yo
lauren has received the reports of your
exploits you successfully quelled
clever's frenzy restoring peace of mind
to jesus people you are stranger to us
one who fell out of the very sky yet you
have served the galaxy team admirably i
admit you have earned yourself some
degree of recognition but things are not
settled yet now i wanna play more though
i've received word that there are other
pokemon nobles falling prey to such
frenzies elsewhere in you sweet
so carry on with your research and serve
your duties and prove that you truly are
an asset to us that is all you're
dismissed your fellow cervicorps members
are likely at the wallflower go and join
them
waffles potato mochi time
and help you catch up ah
i guess so are you guys playing the game
as well on the side who's playing on the
side
cute
yeah yeah yeah oh there's gossiping
about up a storm about our young friend
they love gossip me me so many of you
i have way further along than i am
guilty as charge still waiting for copy
oh
can't get it until much oh that's okay
and you're getting yourself spoiled now
i guess but you're gonna get spoiled
anyway and when you play it yourself so
at the fourth noble oh there are more i
kind of
didn't realize
only focusing on kiaba ah
[Music]
probably going to i was playing dark
souls 3 oh
mount corona
don't have a switch what
i dare say i was well prepared she was a
quick study of how clever moved in
battle from what i heard
all in all it was a very good show
victory well earned
going to work in the field lands should
feel a lot safer now thanks to ukiyawa
and if you want to feel even safer try
making some of these benny taught me how
to make them i wrote out his directions
into a recipe
smoke bombs
[Music]
what do they do
lovely
now that we need not to worry about
being mauled by cleaver either
let's take our chance to study all the
pokemon that call the obsidian field
lance their home
hey
hell yeah
why was that so [\h__\h] scary that sound
bit
why are you [\h__\h] scaring me
i've been waiting for you kiawa my name
is vesa
there's something really important i
need to tell you would you come with me
she looks dead inside and she talks as
if she's dead
thanks for the membership welcome
um this is kind of a secret but
something terrible has happened he saw
us in a whole lot of danger
hundreds of years ago a being that
brought the calamity to this region was
sealed away by someone using the power
of a strange magic why are you telling
me this
what
but now for summary unknown reason the
magic has come undone and the seal is
broken
pouring energy
she's just so broken you have to repair
her tomorrow i hate to think what might
happen at this rate so please kiawah
hear me out i need you to restore the
broken seal
tell me what to do
we have a collab tomorrow so all good oh
thank you i'm so happy you believe me i
just knew you'd be willing to
help this odd keystone is for you keep
it safe
oh
odd keystone
skyward sword all over again
yeah for real though [\h__\h]
it's following me everywhere it looks
like a face
doesn't it
mysterious stone that can be used to
collect wisps that glow of an eerie
purple light
spiritum huh
after the seal was broken a whole bunch
of wisps scattered across history
a hundred
and seven of them in total huh you
counted them
with the odd keystone i gave you you'll
be able to gather them all
see the whisper normally invisible but
not to the holder of the keys odd
keystone
i know it's a huge task but please you
just have to gather all the wisps for me
there's one real close to where we are
now is this a side quest
how about you start with that one
it kind of sounds like a side quest oh
see that flame hovering over there try
touching it
uh
skyward sword hello
this reminds me of that um
you know that part where you don't have
your weapons
[Applause]
wow
impressive
20 ish per zone
the wisp has been absorbed into the old
keystone just as it should have been
thank goodness i picked you to help me
with this
come talk to me if you ever need help
finding the remaining wisps and one last
thing as you gather more and more wisp
i'll give you some rewards as thanks
i'll wait here for you while you carry
out your search good luck
106 to go
that is a challenge but i'll take it up
the next day
stretch stretch stretch stretch
[Music]
perfect workout
hey
you're you're telling me they have new
hairstyles now no no way no way
wow the galaxy team hairdresser really
is dare i say cutting edge oh my god
she also looks familiar oh hey yokiyawa
the girl who caught clever aren't ya
there's me
best girl
mars aha
i knew it you've got quite a reputation
you know
i mean you called one of almighty
sinnoh's chosen ones some people are
actually kind of scared of you for doing
something so bold
she is cute holy [\h__\h]
i'm attitude by the way i'm a warden of
the diamond clan my special skill is
giving haircut
what
you give haircuts too
oh snap but i came here to talk to you
uh to your mr camera to see you around
oh
those clubs you were wearing when you
first came to the village i can't
describe you the shock they gave me it's
as if i got a glimpse of the future
there's no mistaking it you're
passionate about fashion aren't you
yes
i see well i have the duty of making
this village more fashionable too
let us study fashion together you're
part of the survey club semi right
please i ask you that you lent me your
talents
i've been told that hippopotamus which
can be found around the crimson islands
have different appearances based on
their gender i feel like if i were able
to see and compare them uh it would
inspire me to create new designs for my
clothing
okay
male and female okay i have not seen one
yet but i will well there's a lot of new
cyclists
i will do my best what do you want
whenever i have more wares when yes yes
yes yes yes what do you want
getting a hold of new wares
try to sweeten up hearty greens
when do i get hearty greens is that
something i can gather in the next area
maybe
what do you want
hey sport in you and some tarp are you
the guy
with the horse game with yeah balloons
more balloons
oh
thousand points
awesome points
well i'll get a square final on the
target practice game hosted in the
practice field outside july village okay
maybe not now
is that difficult
uh
i fetch a plant maybe i have it what do
you need
bitter leaves
[Music]
ask anise
is she in the is she one of those nurses
holy [\h__\h] that's a lot of questions you
know what i'll that's all i'll take for
now
are those mighty carbs up there
yo
wait today
good day
add some because weren't there like um
construction things here
did they add something to this building
did they finish
yo and this dude wasn't here before
they weren't chilling here before
including items you won't find at a
general store oh
berries ah and plants
i see
special product scatter bank set
what the [\h__\h] is that
that's for you to find out after you buy
it is it worth it guys
scatter bang set
town grows as you pro progress that is
pretty cool that's worth it okay we'll
take it then
whoa ho ho scatterbrain when thrown at
the ground these balls produce a loud
noise and scare off weak pokemon in the
area sending them running
ah will that reset the spawn like it
will send them
running as in it will send them into a
void
is that what that is
[Music]
oh oh like not only the ones that i
throw with that but like everything
around me
[Music]
um
are you the lady i need to talk to no
pacell
yo where the hell is that other lady
thomas
my father was one of the nurses
[Music]
hello
oh
ponita
it's a lot of quests is there anything
else here yes
highlight cycles yeah
you should do that automatically
i would prefer that but okay oh there's
one more floor higher
[Music]
ah
the cute red haired girl is here oh this
game has a lot of cute girls
i like it
oh it's always come towards luna as well
this suggests that even pokemon that are
not nobles can't become friends each
i've received no word for madame or
arita but this is not something we can
simply ignore
in any case you have my thanks you did
well to inform yourself it was a lunar
situation
no problem adamant's got his hands full
running our clan all and where's the
luna's warden wouldn't even give me the
time of day
so the galaxy team are the only ones i
could turn to about this
unlearner's warden is mistress collabo
for the pearl clan is it not
of all the wardens she is the most
narrow minded
bound by tradition
she likely does not take kindly to
outsiders meddling in her affairs
i have a new mission
order you to study with luna in the
crimson islands
okay new area let's go
i wonder if they're like dressed
differently and if their village looks
different
yes yes you'll the pokemon over there to
be more fearsome okay
uh your color you should be able to
handle crimson marlins on your own okay
here's what you need to know your
destination is a place within the
mirrorlands known as the solacion ruins
hall
this is where you'll find ursulina's
warden
[Music]
all righty
let's do that let's uh
eh shiny ponyta oh that's the quest of
the shiny ponytail
i mean it's not that special when you
can literally get it from a quest though
i don't know that kind of kills
specialness about it for me
um um
you just unlocked the balloon race
mind helping me train sure
uh don't i have a
evie out right now folk
let's see what happens
great what's bathrooms
oh you got the map junior and i keep on
trying to
uh catch
and like it keeps on oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] yeah
yeah use your hypnosis cuz i gotta be
avoided wow
um
can i look at it like this okay
effective
super effective
but it's not really as strong
we'll try
let's give it a try
[Music]
i shall try in strong style
strong balloon
just be careful that the mime doesn't
pop you
the faint of mime junior
sneaking up i tried i tried sneaking
i got his pizza
ow
i'm paralyzed
and fond of
right after
yo
uh
uh water is
all very sweet to like
oh one
um
there we go again i forgot
wait i don't ask
uh
what
water is very weak to electric okay
they're not a good choice
we're back to it
i don't know who to use um
how about chunk uh oopsie
[Applause]
okay
let's go you're so chalky
uh water no
how about this
[Applause]
chunk is weak to electric well [\h__\h]
ah
do something chunk
come on
[Music]
that's some alpha you got there hey
don't make fun of my donkey boy
[Music]
stupid mouse
stupid electro mouseman
yeah half of my team weak to electric
pretty bad situation but
[Music]
yeah
you move
move mastered
recipe
stealth spray
not that i need it but okay
more ways to use all the items i have
can i make it right now let's try it out
also did he heal my pokemon
yes he did okay
good
catch a hippodome there's so much to do
guys there's so much to do
oh i can't craft anything
um
i have a [\h__\h] ton of items though
let me sell
my stardust
anything else we don't need i need
everything
that's the problem
ah but i can use that
real candy raises the level
i will use it on
me
[Music]
okay
where are we going should we do main
quests or side quests
i think i'm gonna just keep some side
quests for
private time
with pokemon
i also don't know how often i'm gonna
play it next week but
yeah i am i'm kind of hooked i think
i think i'm pretty hooked
[Music]
well what should i move
there's another rare candy in there
[Music]
is your vacation not next week
most of most of next week i'll still be
around i'm gonna make my schedule
tomorrow so you guys will see it then
uh but yeah
most of the time i'll be around
it's more like the week after
[Music]
okay so now oh we're going over there yo
it's so far away
made success
oh
crimson milan's hmm
looks okay
here we are my girl the crimson islands
an area team with reports and wielding
pokemon poison
and plenty of others besides folk poison
seems like hearing a tough aim for a
tough mission i'm sure you can handle it
though that's right you're heading to
solancia and ruins aren't ya they're off
that way if you need a pointer see the
entrance way over there
huh
yeah yeah i see that i've noticed that
oh my god
the trees man
you know i wish we could tell where or
when one of the space-time distortions
was going to erupt i wonder if checking
your map would help
i wonder i wonder
space-time distortions wow
that looks crazy
are dangerous places where powerful
pokemon appear however if you are brave
enough to enter them you might be able
to find rare pokemon and items inside
but can you
escape if you enter
i'm counting on both for you to carry
out your survey work as best as you can
sure blah
okay new camp new pokemon
oh that one looks familiar
that's a flower that becomes a flower
doesn't it
[Music]
i don't know what to say
okay
um
all right uh
what what is that
what is that
castor fern well moment i thought it was
a pokemon oh you're attacking me
oh
i'm not sure if that is a good oh choice
wait chunkers okay
of course that is a good choice
oh oh you're still alive
that hit me as well
should i catch it
now we're already in a fight
let's end it
i defeated it
wonderful and it leaves me with a ball
of mud
not sure if i wanted that
okay that looks kind of
cool that looks decent yeah i don't know
i mean the wheat is kind of weird but i
like the the the ruins and the
a lot of uh
pawns here and there
kind of muddy area
it's definitely not mud you think it's
it's poop no no no no no i'm not
touching poop
[Applause]
come on come on give me something is
that is that too
low
yes it is
what it didn't notice me i think it's
sleeping
yeah
[Applause]
because
i got it
oh wait is that isn't that something i
need for
harley quinn yeah i need that for side
quests i think one of my many many side
quests
stupid anton
stupid psyduck
ah
join us
[Music]
this
this pokemon is just
such a mood though
[Music]
i need to catch you for my pokedex
cute badoo
about you
nice
another one perhaps
the more the merrier oh no
it didn't notice me though i think all
right
not quite
oh
oh yes it did
okay
let's turn on the bgm again nice
i like that
you look strong are you strong
you look threatening oh [\h__\h] you notice
me it did
oh
uh uh
you look like a ghost plant pokemon but
i don't know to be honest i don't know
what to fight you with um well ghost
versus ghost is good if you're really a
ghost
it's just grass is it
i don't know what to use
flying dive okay i don't know use
confusion maybe it helps
pretty weak
[Music]
oh holy [\h__\h]
uh grass grass
i don't really have anything
i'll try
what about electro electro versus grass
probably not gonna do much
[Applause]
[Music]
grass resists electric
yeah i thought so that sounds like it
makes a lot of sense wait no no not that
one
[Music]
if i
stand in front of my pokemon's
attack
will i get damaged then two
or does friendly fire not work
good question has anyone ever tried
get it
yes you will
wow
okay
good to know
what do you have over here
what do you want
large specimen
uh defeat with fire type don't have that
you've seen use absorb okay i'll try to
catch it then maybe it will be a large
one
large boy come on
come on
give me a big boy
come on come on come on come on come on
come on come on
you said you wanted to
but
it was not a big boy okay
oh
oh [\h__\h]
uh you wanna fight um
what if i run away
uh okay
i will take up
a new challenge
oh guys before i forget i finally
remembered i had a crazy dream okay not
that crazy but a fun dream kind of fun
uh part of my dream
last night
what killed it
was um
about elena about reigning
i barely remember
it but one the one big important thing
that i do remember
uh
oh [\h__\h] wait i'm forgetting [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
no i think i think
so today it was uh lena was uh releasing
an album
uh with um like featuring artists
and one of them was
senpai
one of them was a holostar a lot of old
people i don't know why
and another one was me
so for some reason um yeah i was gonna
make some music with velena um i was one
of the featuring artists in her album
oh
yeah and i even remember like the
promotional poster that they made it
looked really cool like me and elena
and the others were posing in some
really cool fetch outfits
[Music]
like kind of um
kind of
kind of uh
uh what was the second makarasu frontier
style outfits
super fetch
so
gorgeous yeah
but
that does seem like it's a
maybe a vision for the future
it could totally happen one day that i'd
be making a song with reina together i
can see it i can see that future i'm up
for it
so fast oh my god
oh my god
[Music]
oh no no no no no no no
would be a song of each girl and then
whole stars
no after ahmed i do have um
some ideas for some collabs but also for
um also for original i want to work on
my original song that i've been working
on for a while
um
[Music]
i've been working on an original song
for quite some time yeah
[Music]
it's kind of
not
nothing much happening with it recently
but
i'm gonna try focusing on that again
what the [\h__\h] what if i die
wait wait wait hey hey
i didn't see where the [\h__\h] i was going
oh but the battle finished properly
i drowned during my battle man
you're drowned during it
oh man
[\h__\h] wait wait wait wait wait
ah
oh man
uh here here's a berry
eat that [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
can i collect it again
look at that
i think my humidifier is telling me it's
got no water left in it
yeah i think i need to put in water
again
otherwise it's going to continue beeping
let me just turn it off right now shut
up
are you turning yourself off
oh shut up shut up
are you shutting up
okay it's shutting up
no stop beating me
okay is it turned off now
i guess
do you talk with your humidifier often
no i never do
i never do
[Music]
i need you
number caught zero
number caught without being spotted okay
here we go this is my moment
unless i accidentally throw something
else here we go
oh it's my moment this is my moment
hell yeah
headshot
don't go
it's panicking
but still here
and don't know and don't know bad duck
bad duck
i've given it full that was a gold tuna
stupid duck
we got it yes
and we i think we completed like free
free
tasks yeah not being spotted giving it
food all of that
[Music]
did you guys happen to see a clip
oh
what you want to fight
okay
do you guys happen to see a clip of um
so what is senpai talking about the
message that i sent her yeah
she saw it a
couple days after i sent it to her
actually i sent it right after that
stream i think
right after the
the
um shrine stream that we had
yeah i am
oh nice great dust
uh
yeah
[Laughter]
but she finally saw it and i kind of
when i was riding into her i i kind of
had a feeling that she would use it for
her stream
she uses any material she can get and
makes
she tells it in such a funny way
entertaining way that any story
can be super entertaining as long as she
tells it
so what a senpai to name
very
[Music]
watching the clip right now
there we go
she's a master at spinning yarn
that's when you how you want to say it
certified comedians
yeah she's amazing man
birds of a feather right yes
i'm checking the clip oh you didn't see
it it's pretty new
i saw like two clips of it from
different people
hello galaxy member dodging is
everything everything when a wild
pokemon is lashing out at you
it's moves you judge right out of the
way while you're dodging your moves will
whizz right by you and not hit you yeah
that's right
that's right it's time for me to save by
the way i think
and oh yeah
lost and found
uh
i would like to claim it yes thank you
52 married points candy hell yeah
okay
save my progress is this this is like a
dungeon now
oh
who is that
not it
is that the cute girl no wait who's that
is that someone new looks like a new
person
oh
to you
huh no would you look at that you have a
salistica flute celestica
you must be the one they say fell out of
the space-time rift
yeah
that's it
i see i see
i've already heard about you that you
quelled cleaver in his frenzy
i'm sure many people were saved by
erections but i wonder if there wasn't
some other way to handle the situation
shut up
what you did is hardly different from
bullying a pokemon into submission
excuse me
i mean
you run about catching pokemon up in
those little balls you carry
did she just call my balls little
i don't need any help from your sword or
the diamond clan for that [\h__\h] you
that young lady others who offered to
help but associating with the diamond
clan
that's just what
okay boomer
this is really what the game is about
boomers versus [\h__\h] zoomers i am the
protagonist is the zoomer cause i came
from the zooming future and all of the
other people in this game are boomers
oh
be on your way huh
there is much i must do and i prefer not
to be distracted any further you are
[\h__\h] boomer [\h__\h]
how about you show me the strength that
you could quell or even a frenzied lloyd
ah i guess
uh now we're gonna fight in front of her
and she's gonna be impressed because i'm
so strong or what but that's really
random that volo is coming here to help
me achieve that
okay
which pokemon am i
standing out
i don't remember
cute
okay perfect
um
let's do a step move because i don't
know
uh what else
[Music]
two in a row yeah it happens
if you look to the right side you will
see the action order
and then you know how often they will
attack
[Applause]
oh wait oh [\h__\h]
i ran into my pokemon well then i have
proved now that uh my own pokemon
attacks will hurt me
oh [\h__\h] you have that boy
uh
no stop
[\h__\h] killed my mommy
with two attacks in a row after
switching in holy [\h__\h] that's one thing
i realized the game didn't ask me about
the switching thingy can you change that
in the settings i mean i wouldn't really
want to
be asked if i want to switch my pokemon
since we did it this way last time
anyway
um but i just realized
okay
chunk time
man we have a strong ice attack
to deal with this stupid dragon pokemon
i think it's a dragon right
oh yeah is he making a [\h__\h] scent for
your team
[Music]
such a prodigious strength now let me
just heal up yeah yeah
[Music]
so
did the lady care for that oh what i
must ask your help in retrieving the
stolen wall fragment with your skill it
should be a cinch
wait stolen
yes exactly somebody's pillaged the
celestial ruins and made off of a
fragment of the wall engravings if i
bring that back the lady will
maybe cooperate with me don't you think
have we not heard of the notorious
misfortunes there are three of bandits
that have even hit us ginkgo guild
merchants more than a few times not the
kind of regulars i like to have let me
tell you
oh mr scala is doing everything she can
to regain the fragment but at 99 years
old well that explains why she's such a
[\h__\h]
it's a bit hard for her to chase leads
all over the place ah that boomer she
needs help from consumer
well if you would ask me nicely i would
have done anything for you
lady
so when you say kind madame why not help
find the fragment for the one he's
pretty charming isn't he
naturally i'll be happy to land your
hand mm-hmm those sisters sweat my wares
too and i'm no ginkgo guild merchant if
i take that line down and far be it from
me to let them just get away with
vandalizing the precious ruins of this
region
you know i did see the remains of a camp
i did see that too
okay i'll go back
task
okay i'll be on my way
naruto i'm on my right now
i'll be okay
i see
ghost pokemon i'm scared
wow look how shiny my
mouth looks um
[Music]
it looks like plastic now
it looks like it's made out of plastic
oh my god
it's plastic
that's fantastic
you can brush my hair
oh that's far
oh
man what
what
that's still not far enough okay i'm
coming down i'm coming down i'm coming
down
i don't want to fight you ghost pokemon
scary
[Music]
i have barely any pokeballs left
oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] okay okay okay okay
come on come on come on
okay but uh
the thing was on the other side i think
the water
and not
the fire fireplace was over here
oh
yes yes yes
coconut
time to investigate
it's a burnout campfire no somebody must
have been here yeah i know
now who might you be not some straight
traveler from the look of you
oh
hello
um
they look like a beach over
there is only one reason people go
poking around out here in the middle of
nowhere your raptors free aren't ya
sisters we should introduce ourselves
properly
before we show this poor fool how wrong
she was to assume she could ever beat us
[Music]
i bring good luck to my sisters wherever
i go and i love to anyone who crosses
her
sorry i'm a little bit
scary to catch
pikachu style the dawn the dawn it's the
dawn
and the elder smell be your unlucky
charm
but you spotted a four leaf clover well
i'll soon have you sing double
i'm the middle sister now one clover you
can't pick
you can't pick
heads i win and tails you lose you've
got no chance in this game of fortunes
oh
[\h__\h] she's rap battling me
i'm the youngest coin but i'm definitely
not your good luck piece
i like these three girls they're cute
pose
strike a pose
we're the in famous bandit trail the
misfortune sisters and your lux just run
out so this is like the
team rocket of the past which is so much
cuter than what we have now holy [\h__\h]
how am i in this kiddo
koi's child
okay
let me handle this sisters i'll only
hurt her a little
come on toxic croak let's doze this fool
and poison
fine with me um what's effective against
poison health chat
the band coin challenged you to battle
sidekick oh maybe ghost or ground
when i have my my boob out right now
you little piece of [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay perfect
oh okay not very effective still does a
lot of damage positions and level 23 the
levels are okay here
oh
strong style
go go go go go
super effective
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
i'll need it i guess
easy peasy
[Music]
unless you have another one though okay
battle decided what do you say
cute girl we could be friends now
i'm not fond of this outcome but at
least it's still better than plowing
fields for the galaxy team
plowing probably
the galaxy team continues to spoil
things for me even after i've left
take the blasted fragment and go just
leave us alone
oh you're giving it to me
i like how angry the the left girl looks
she's like
with the gritted teeth there's an emoji
that looks like her face right now
well fragment
a fragment that was once part of a stone
panel in the celestion runes it has
markings carved on it that appear to be
some kind of writing
yeah that one that one exactly that's
her
name
the weird the weird thing the word
writing on it made us think the stupid
thing was some kind of treasure but it
turned out to be a worthless flop of
junk
all that effort for nothing
tell me why why are you even seeking us
out what set you on this path
oh
i wanna help us luna
goodness how selfless of you to go so
far out of your way for the sake of
another
not all of us have the luxury of
offering such unthinking kindness to
strangers is she talking sarcastically
for some of us simply surviving another
day takes all that we have
understandable
maybe i can help you too
and i'm going to score the saddle of the
galaxy team which now includes you
well fight me then find me
remember what those ancient verses tell
us
why is it in days of spring beneath the
soft carousel of the sun the blossom
tremble and fall
spirits last by uncertainty your days
are also numbered galaxy
full bye-bye i like them
i like them
oh
okay look at that
i'll try to get there um i don't know
mama
wait i need to i can't get there without
uh a mob that a a mount that can swim
can i
yes so many moms everywhere
wait i missed i missed the
i missed the bridge
but maybe i should mark it um
it's uh i guess here
oh mark it as
star
i suppose ah
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
careful not to fall thank you black
friction thank you
you foreshadowed it
uh holy [\h__\h] man here take this
ah
fight me
where's the sleepy time for you huh
oh man
that is the second time
[Music]
now i can pick it up oh yeah i wanted to
craft some
pokeballs uh
let me try
craft
i can make some
i only have four
oh [\h__\h] i only have four apricorns
what
thank you lovely bug thank you
i need more apricorns
wait are they always only just like
uh
okay what what do the trees look like
that have apricorn
that's already
farmed i guess
i need africa oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] i'm not going down here
that sounds like a [\h__\h] uh flag but
i am not indeed not going down to the
space distortion
[Music]
i know you got the fragment back safe
and sound yeah i'm well aware of caleb's
reputation they say she's stubborn too
old-fashioned
she's a boomer we call that boomer
zoomer is called that boomer boomers
don't call that boomer but zoomers call
that boomers
but she's given a pro clan all she has
ever since she was young she lived her
prime years here in the history region
trusting in the guidance of almighty
sinnoh i don't think it's that she hates
the diamond clan or the galaxy team
rather i think she simply loves the pro
clan very very much me too
anyway i do hope you're able to come
organ luna's frenzy of course
i will leave it to me
and i will get her on my side now by
bringing back the plate
korea will kaise did
oh so you've come to bother me again
well come as often as you'd like but it
won't change my mind
look at this
thank you good night dog
what you went and retrieved the fragment
from those bandits shut the wait a
second by the way
uh
why go out of your way like that for a
complete stranger like me i didn't
exactly do it for you i did it for the
nice boy
volo i guess you're that eager to call
mr luna
that's right
i'll admit it i didn't expect anybody
else to truly care for luna
well then let's see that wall fragment
can you read that though
and there we go good as new
oh
incognito
are dosed up
uh
can't read
don't know what it says
oh you call them
huh you call them you known
in english
we call them in german we call them
incognito
pokemon
let me read what it says oh you can read
it okay
all lips touch
all lives touch other lives to create
something a new and alive
huh
you're unknown you know and pronounced
like unknown
and
[Music]
i see yeah
i suppose it means people helping each
other like how you helped me retrieve
the fragment
i've read this passage passage
many many times but this is the first
time i've truly understood what it means
maybe this is almighty sinnoh's guidance
what is your name then girl
i see
kiawah
please lend me your strength so that we
may help ursa luna
it's true that wizard luna has become
enraged but he doesn't seem to be in an
utter frenzy i think he will return to
his normal state if we can just give him
some medicine yeah i will throw it at in
his face
i could never bring myself to engage
pokemon in a battle but that's something
i can rely on you for am i right
where's that luna prefers to stay on
sludge mound please join me there when
you're ready
okay we got her she's on our side now
[Music]
all right should we head there right
away i guess on the way we'll probably
be distracted anyway
oh yeah oh
nice balancing
like a ballerina
oh whoa
that's still the thing over there
oh there's a big boy
go go swim
okay i wanted a shortcut
what i lost why did i lose
if i kill those pokemon
no not the best attacks here
[Music]
it stopped me from getting poisoned
ah like once it did it once and then
once it happened once it just it's
normal for it to disappear
[Music]
oh
okay
well
well then
that was the wrong way huh shabbato
doing a swim
there we go
oh come on
but
[Music]
bridge water scares me now
water is hella scary isn't it
bridges
wait is that shiny
why does that look shiny or is it just
the way it looks always wasn't it green
not shiny okay
[Music]
thank you aggressive sneeze was super
effective on my chat
i need to heal my team man
thank you
okay never mind
[Music]
all righty
oh
don't even think about it
ask me to heal
em
and for inflation
fast travel to camp no we're going
somewhere else we're not going to the
camp right now
we could but
i don't wanna what
time
alpha [\h__\h] shoe is that really what
tangela looked like i don't quite recall
it looking like that
wow it's crazy
that's tangrowth and both form of
tangiela wait is also tangela and in
english
it's a wolf pool wow
wow well you're scaring the [\h__\h] out of
me i'm not gonna fight you
that's for sure that's tiny katakana
where are your small boys then where are
your where'd it get oh there's one oh
cute
[Music]
what type is that oh yeah who's who's
looking at me
[Music]
grass poison grass grass okay
grass not adults
[Music]
not very effective
okay i didn't really want to fight you
but you came at me so what can i do
is that the sound of the alpha pokemon
close to me
yeah yeah
come on
we got it new pokemon in my pokedex
that's what i like to see
[Music]
kusogaki is getting stronger
i need to look up how to evolve uh
eevees in this game particularly like
where to get like
the
unnecessary
what
you want to find
the same way as before yeah but like
where the hell are they you know
[Music]
how would you how do you catch the fish
and how would you
um
[Music]
how would you sorry my question my brain
is empty
how would you make um
an eevee into a
fairy evie
in this game
what
[\h__\h] oh you wanna fight how do i fight
[\h__\h] face man
i dodged but i i am
i thought the wrong thing
oh wait i already did that
okay
well this is uh pretty funny i've been
having a lot of deaths here because of
all the [\h__\h] water here
interesting pokemon sighted
must catch
this won't work
[Music]
did you notice me yes you did ah
i guess evie let's go home
thanks for the pinkie
three strikes you're out yes i am yes i
am i take it
ah i accept uh my defeat oh god baby
doll eyes
i don't know what attack what to attack
you live
quick
it was rousey to move goddammit
oh holy [\h__\h]
um i'm out of here
fire or flying okay
you guys should know that by now
[Music]
we don't have fire yeah
super effective
well
that
was a lovely
frog
i have sighted a frog
oh i want to heal
[Music]
and i wanna heal
there we go
wonderful
is that a pineapple what the [\h__\h] is
that
what is that is that a pokemon
it's a pineapple what is it
what is it
i can't touch it i can't take it
it's mysterious
[Music]
for a pokemon edit
really is that gonna work really
[Music]
whoa
cool thank you for telling me i knew it
had to be something
although hmm we got so many items again
it would be good for us to go to uh oh
bargain
what
can barely move here
to go to a camp that would be smart um
hello oh oh god oh god
uh okay let's find
[Laughter]
okay we're fighting against two pokemon
strong style
zone
i don't know about this one though can i
walk in this water i will not test it
out during a battle but uh it would be
interesting to know
no effect on me nice
no events
[Music]
for once a smart choice of pokemon made
by yours truly takanasi kyoto
it worked on both of them
i'm a genius i think i wanna catch this
one though
[Music]
it is not deep okay
let's go
come on come on
be mine be my valentine
[Music]
wonderful
i'm running out of pokeballs
[\h__\h]
sorry i wish it's my vulcan balls again
and let's fight you're in my way
i will craft them yeah i think now i got
some um of those berries and they're not
really berries but i think i got what it
takes now
i was i ran out of materials before
because i i think i didn't loot enough
trees for a while
oops here everyday a key items crap come
on give me some
okay i can make quite a lot
i have a [\h__\h] set of tumble stones man
oh
i can make the
smoke bombs now okay i shall make a copy
a couple
what is this stealth spray
i guess we'll make it since we can
and we'll make these
would also be cool to have like a
crafting level
um and then learn you know
learn some recipes by
some maybe some opt
[\h__\h] so learning some optional recipes
by oh god is it coming for me
learning some optional recipes
[Music]
by upping your
upping your level
yeah that would be cool anyway look
did you notice me
[Music]
not really they seem really easy going
it's like they're the the bidoofs of the
water or the mud
okay hippo hippopotas we need a couple
of them
uh
right we didn't oh wait we need a female
one and a male or what was that quest
the distortion is gone well i wasn't
really ready for it anyway what is who
is who is challenging me
uh
what what to fight you with you're cute
you're
cute to find it liv um um
i need a mail can you see like the
difference
with grass
[Music]
oh hello uh hey
now we can fight
so i got a mail and this one is mail too
okay okay okay
they make it so easy to fall down
so dangerous
ah
ah did you miss
oh it ran away from hook's shake oh god
it's turning night again
i'm gonna catch some more
i don't see this ah wait the one that
one over there looks different than that
one so is this male female
i guess we'll find out
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h]
brown's notice me oh okay
this one is female
[Music]
come on
we got it i'm gonna get another one
though for the task
for the mission
[Music]
slap that booty
um i want to know uh
what do i need to do with you guys
number you've caught without being
spotted they did not spot me
number defeated number you defeated with
grass huh
i did did i not
did i not
wait
before we go into that battle
we have to heal again
oh it ran away wow okay no more running
away now no more anymore now
i dare you to run away
super strongly that's my fault
wait i must have learned new skills by
now right but i just uh since it's
already four
i didn't realize and
i didn't realize probably
i need to switch out some skills
let me take a look at it now actually
that's very important
and i can do it now right change moves
oh my god
aerial ace
probably better than
one of my flying scales
uh a magical leaf probably too oh this
is uh
[Music]
what do you think get rid of gust
okay
but we can always change it anyway
what did i change yeah okay one two and
tada
magical leaf never misses
replace gust and
uh leavage
okay magical leaf instead of leafage
what about air slash 75.95
um
i guess we're good for now
is not good okay
okay what about the others let's take a
look
[Music]
oops
do you have anything that i've been
missing out on
aqua tail crunch rest and bite
i need your opinion everybody
happy birthday
to libya fun time leave your time leave
your fun
love you fun leave you a ton
aqua tail and crunch crunch at least
crunch
instead of taco
for now
and then
uh
aqua tail has 85 19.
oh
should i do aqua tail instead of water
pulse
okay okay okay
and
and rest we don't really need
okay
confirm
thank you
for your help
no
chunk can use crunch and aqua tail
what about you
we got a fire attack
i want that
um
and hex 6500
that's that's looks that looks stronger
to me than astonish
can i put that in
hex op no astonish okay good what about
mystical fire can i put that into
learn both maybe instead of call mind
i would do that
basically over here no
hex has got a paragraph hypnosis
oh
ah
yeah on fire today
confusion really
put out coal mine swap coal mine yeah i
don't use it okay wait then uh
no
miss not mystic what
uh
keep confusion
do this
what do you mean i enjoyed the game
yesterday a lot as well
uh but today i feel like also because my
throat doesn't hurt as much as it did
yesterday
um i feel like i can go on longer and it
doesn't feel as
i guess it doesn't feel as slow anymore
even though i'm not really doing much i
feel like i'm doing way less progress
than yesterday but i'm just doing my own
thing at least
uh
next up when can sparks evolve what
level does a pichu evolve
what level does a pichu evolve do you
guys know
but we'll end it soon anyway
i need to sleep early and make food and
then collab with nanaki tomorrow
evolves with friendship
oh how do i make it like me
there's no petting in this game is there
or do i just oh
i did notice that you can just throw it
out there and then talk to it like that
is that what they want me to do feed it
food can i give you food
you take that
you want to eat that [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] that's not good
uh pizza doesn't seem interested in the
berry i'll just use it a lot okay okay
okay if that's good enough well then
come with me
yeah
you're gonna follow me right
come come come
come my little child we're getting oh
very close oh oh i see it
[Music]
i see what's going on
me dick donna
oh
i wonder what's gonna happen uh wait i
wanna save i think
[Music]
what do you want
hello there so you're the servant corpse
child who call out the lord of the woods
are you think you could help with
setting up on you yes
i need it
setting up what do you mean
go to help set up the bug boom bound cap
where the hole
[Music]
where did you go
wait how did they do that again with the
side quest uh
shoes no
[Music]
wait how did that work again
ah here missions
where is it
hear that one
[Music]
go to help okay
huh over there okay we'll do it first
we'll do that one first
ah nice nice spot you got there oh no
you're using those pokemons
i have a dislike for them
oh yeah i keep i'd keep your distance if
i were you yeah cause they're stinky oh
you want me to fight them
leave it to me
they look a little bit like jumpers
[Music]
yo
the tail really remain reminds me of
junker's tail
oh [\h__\h] my my pizza oh no
pizza pizza
now
put your feet
bad for a friendship wait a second wait
a second wait a second i literally just
saved right before that so
i'm gonna use that as an opportunity
[Music]
i've heard it lauren's friendship so
yeah
okay okay okay now i'm prepared i didn't
expect uh that i had to fight
these pokemon
nothing happened you saw nothing no no
uh so
how come i sent a picture
[Music]
yes yes yes
uh what should i
what should i fight them with though i
actually don't know
um help help me
anybody help i need somebody help
they're fluent
really
okay oh wait
that's not how it works
i'm here now second hack i know it feels
like a deja vu
hey
[Music]
nikai
i will i will do it properly now
[Music]
go in platoon
um
not sure what to attack with though
it's just effective on it
why
they're immediate
was that bamboozled
confusion what it has no effect
[Music]
a bunch of people said in platoon but
that doesn't seem like a good choice
[Music]
don't kill it
switching
[Music]
one about chunks
don't hurt junk
he will sit on you and you will regret
what you have done
okay at least
one is dead now
[Music]
yeah three of them ganging up against
one is only fair if my one is as big as
this
then we can talk oh my god
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] um
well
i don't know i haven't used boyzell in a
million years
[Applause]
[Music]
i don't know what to do
i should replace blizzell
true
um
let's see
[Music]
let's see what we can do
oh my god
why are these [\h__\h] stocky so strong
[Music]
oh no
maybe swift is better
wait but it's raining now shouldn't i be
also a staff so let's that's a lot of
pools
it's raining and i have stabbed if i'm
not strong enough now
what the hell
all my pokemon are dying
it's raining man
hallelujah
[Music]
i can catch them too oh
oh
i didn't think of that
i tried to catch this one then
[Music]
[\h__\h]
i have mercy on you by using false swipe
and planning on catching you and this is
how
you repay me you little stinky piece of
[\h__\h]
i should kill it at this point
because if i throw a pokeball and it's
not going to enter
then it's going to kill movement but
okay i'm going to try it i'm going to
try i'm going to try it i'm going to try
it
[Music]
[Applause]
are they really like
doing this right now
are they really
my weakest pokemon are left right now
[Laughter]
um yeah we're gonna kill it um
it doesn't matter with what
we want um sparks should not die
but yeah um
what's my strongest attack here
kill it
no more dead pokemon
allowed
championed that
mukatsuka
okay
uh-huh yeah i can't believe it either
well at least we got a camp out of it
worth it
um yeah
[\h__\h] stunkies that's why i hate them
that's why no one likes them
do i get a heel please oh hi there
did i get a heel they didn't [\h__\h]
heal me
well uh sleeping gives me a heal right
i could
use a rest
until
midday
a good night's sleep man
wow
good morning we're all happy
yes we are
wonderful
do i have
no i'm just gonna ask if i have the
those
berries for the pokeballs nope i don't
wow i'm really lacking pokeballs you
have some
um i'd like to do some shopping
100 that's pretty cheap i'll buy a
couple
okay
um
[Music]
okay let's do this
store i need good morning from korea
annyeong
good morning to you too
store unneeded what do i not need
this
um
well that's a lot
oh
i never need those
no flying pokemon in sight
this may be
um
nature's wrapping paper
remove it i don't have a recipe for that
um
you need to think about who to use this
on we have nine of them now
oh
don't just don't forget you have those
remember
probably
i'll try not to forget
[Music]
okay i made a little bit of space okay
[Laughter]
over here
or luna is enraged yes but he must still
recall his long relationship with the
pearl clan he never fails to show up the
moment i play my celestia flute
amazing
whoa
it's a bear
look kind of cute it looks um kind of
worried
wait that the sign on its head head on
the forehead looks like a sun that's
covered by clouds
apparently that's an ursa ring
apparently
[Music]
new evolution
now show your metal to ursa luna but
remember that ursa luna is a pokemon
very dear to the pearl clan i will not
permit you to catch him
okay
well i will kill him then that's the
only other option
what do you want me to do
oh it's just a normal battle
i guess it's not a shiny either like
that
what what type is this excuse me level
26 holy [\h__\h] um can i find it with me
i don't want everyone to die again
[Music]
well okay i will at least attack once
oh wait ice might be good
[Music]
super effective holy [\h__\h]
okay okay uh i get another hit actually
this might be stronger
aqua
[Music]
is ow that was a
strong slap man that you served there
but that's okay
my pokemon are
pretty
strong in terms of attacks against this
one was i really not allowed to catch it
what if i tried to was it not possible
you said luna my poor darling you must
be exhausted from running around like
that
let me call make you all better thank
you
i have a special medicine of the parole
clan it will clear out any poison in a
book pokemon's body not allowed okay if
poison's what's causing where's luna's
rage this is sure to calm him down we
call it toxic gone
simple name
oh it does not like it
yeah so
it's so potent that we can only use it
on tough resilient pokemon like where's
the luna they're there derozan luna
you've calmed down now haven't you
his claws i don't want to get too close
to them
it's all very strange though
yeah he wasn't glowing or frenzied
it's just a normal stupid pokemon very
astute of you galaxy team recruit you're
exactly right when you quelled cleaver's
frenzy i could see the strange light
rising into the sky all the way from
here but no such strange light erupted
from ursa luna after you defeated him
nor was he glowing
and what is this clinging towards luna's
coat
seems like some kind of powder
that girl from diamond clan
now why did she of all people find the
need to come and tell me
is it
a distraction
wait
tell me about ursula i wonder
oh but i almost forgot something
important
play your celestia flute for me won't
you
wait can i ride him too huh
and that's why i can't catch him wait a
second
can he swim though i need a swimmer
yeah
he's opened his heart and learned well
the sound of you playing
wow okay but i don't need him i have
another mount what the [\h__\h] but he gave
me a stone tablet
oh
very good at finding things that are
buried in the ground uh-huh
we say that he's digging for treasure
even if these treasures might not always
glitch her own gleam
oh
he looks cute he looks so depressed
uh if you look at the those clouds as
his eyebrows then it's like he's always
questioning something
now go and let your commander know of
what transpired here child of galaxy
team
whoa
oh this is how you get the evolution
stones for evie
where's the luna will rush toward any
treasure he senses in front of him
press the y button to dig for treasure
when ursulina finds a spot that makes
him react particularly strong you might
find something nice
oh
uh okay but like how do i
how do i choose it wait [\h__\h] what have i
ah
[Music]
wow
so [\h__\h] fast i didn't even dash what
the hell it's like constantly dashing
hey what
what what
it's sensing something oh
what
why is this throwing me up though
pikachu also needs a stone
old very snow and part of a series of
old poems that have been unearthed
around the history
what do i need those for
no not now
[Music]
well that sounds like another fun thing
to do all the time
digging for treasure
the way he moves is so cute i guess he
dashes when he senses something huh
covering
he's big enough to take it out with that
alpha to be honest but
oh
he found something
where where where where
where when i'm getting attacked by all
sides i kind of want to get out of here
found it
oh okay i thought it would be something
more special
i can dig holes that reminds me of
aguilera riser
[Music]
we should go back though actually i
think that's why i'm gonna end it today
maybe after talking to the commander
get that progress going
nothing nothing here really
a little bit
you are definitely too fat to walk over
that i gotta be careful
excuse get it
oh he's kind of leading me there
he can walk off pretty well
no he doesn't want to jump though
what are you doing
huh
where are we going where are we going
where are we going buddy
[Music]
where where where where
where where where i keep on losing it
[Music]
ah
whatever
well there's our mission oh i know i
know i've heard i've heard i've heard
but you know if it's a if it's like a
side quest as i said i don't find it
quite that special
up here no
here here here i don't find it quite
that special it makes the shininess of
it like very unshiny
it makes it look rather gray to me but
yeah
um
i think uh like i gotta call
i gotta go with the professors right
ball of mods i thought he can find more
special things but okay
shiny and shiny
are you an
ah did it just at me
is that a pokemon oh come to franco but
reloaded mentioned that there were
carvings resembling white things on the
walls of the celestial ruins
but supposing that the pokemon were just
so uh we just saw is a species with
multiple forms perhaps the carvings are
actually likenesses of this very pokemon
i'm going to add a section specifically
for that species to your pokedex okay
are you telling me i have to find all of
those as well the whole [\h__\h] abc
the whole alphabet
according to me
what's this now letter like markings
seem to have appeared in this section
i've just added oh
and was that your arc phone i just heard
if your mysterious device is reacting to
this new species i wonder what that
could mean
the y button while viewing the cover of
your pokedex to jump to your
unknown
unknown research notes by deciphering
the cryptic symbols you found in these
notes you can try to find all the
unknown hiding throughout the region aha
this unknown possess a mysterious power
that repels pokeballs containing pokemon
so you won't be able to battle them but
drag them down and catch them all if you
can aha
now
i'm reporting
i should get a rank i think i think i'm
getting a rank up
freestyle member let's go
what's illuminating mm-hmm
yes
another reason to go to the commander
uh to the captain i guess
i will return to the village
i actually was thinking of doing a super
chat rating after the energy stream like
uh like immediately after
in the same stream
so
i think actually today i'll excuse
myself without reading them
yeah yeah yeah
uh sorry i didn't read what he said at
all
yeah um just so that the people
know
uh who are not planning to go there
because it will be a mostly japanese
only stream
maybe
maybe you can spread the word that i'm
doing our super chat rating anyway
yeah would another stream frame be
better i don't know i'll do it in the
same i think
freestyle let's go
[Music]
hey you have officially attained the
raga first star in the galaxy expedition
team
i cannot use great balls
pokemon of up to level 40 will obey me
recipe
great boss
wow
[Music]
thank you
milady
well i'm here
i'll get a few slots
somebody for tomorrow but thank you it's
probably not that bad
uh
yeah
my tweet about when i start
reading i don't know
oh oh yeah tonight i gotta catch a
different
formula
[\h__\h] yeah that's what's going to keep me
up tonight ah i can't sleep early
tonight i have to watch that
okay
we're going on six hours let's read
let's hear what they have to say and
then i will end it for today
yeah well we have a situation here what
no more potato more tea
did you run out of potatoes
let me explain
lilligant our clown's lady of rich of
the riches in the frenzy and that is
annoyingly kept us from me ha
yes so it was a distraction was it
assassin or was it that it was
yes there are only a female elegant is
it a pokemon which makes us honored one
our lady of the rich but this isn't the
time for cultural lessons they wait
there the way they say like king of blah
blah blah
and then the lady makes it sound like
they're talking about humans
i'd like to find out just what aliza was
thinking but she's nowhere in jubilant
village
last i saw she was at the wallflower
polishing off a big old point of potato
mochi
now that i blame him my cooking is
simply irresistible
if what is what the diamond clan was
somehow involved in that situation with
the raging ursa luna of the pearl clan
it could lead to the two clans going at
each other's throats again
tell me commander if we do end up in a
struggle with the parole clan what will
your people do
[Music]
we would be forced to remain neutral
meaning what
if we were to show support for one side
it would put us at odds with it with the
other we came here to create a home for
ourselves not to take part in tearing
the land apart
after all the work you put in to get us
to treat one another as equals and keep
us from fighting i suppose it's no
surprise you'd refuse to intervene with
trouble where to break out again
yeah well perhaps you have some idea how
to how might address this situation i
don't want to read male people anymore
it's a difficult voice to do
i could call ursa luna i don't know
does that help
please don't help
[Music]
luna should be able to sniff out at a
zoo at wherever she's gone
if you're strong enough that luna deemed
you worthy then you should be ready to
qualify as well go ahead to lilliganten
brava arena is home you'll excuse me
excuse me
okay ladies
and gentlemen you must swell any pokemon
that could cause harm to the people of
history always remember we came here to
make a new home where we could live
without war or strife
take it
everything sounds so much sweeter this
way
so much happier
okay
thank you everybody for a marvelous time
today
[Music]
what a massive mushroom
uh-huh parasite uh-huh okay
maybe i might uh
do it in a separate stream on the same
day i'll think about it um for now i
wish you all a lovely night uh
wait don't forget to save your progress
i wish live had safe slots but it
doesn't
um
yeah i had fun i hope you guys had some
fun too did you did you did you did you
who had fun raise your pokemon hands
your pokeball carrying hands bye
bye
you did really okay
it was uh kind of chill today
um
but i enjoyed that
i'm a chicken have no hands and raise
your wings
raise your wings up to the sky that bad
like a butterfly
we are chickens but we can fly like
everyone else
[Music]
chickens ahoy
yes i'll see you tomorrow we're playing
um a horror game that is made by a whole
life by cover a whole live themed
horror game
uh with nancy's mental support on my
side so it will be
mostly japanese but yeah and it won't be
a long stream either because it's a
short game apparently
but yeah
if you wanna see teen energy together
tomorrow then you might wanna check it
out yeah
it shouldn't be that scary i don't think
it's
from what i've seen it's not like any
zombies or so are chasing you it's just
like
a scary atmosphere with uh some
i guess a stereo scary story
and that's about it um it's just a demo
i guess so
yeah it's for free of charge by the way
uh you can get it from the home page
[Music]
any loud noise or pop-up will scare you
as we've seen today yes
try not to scream too much of course not
of course not
i won't even i won't even talk that much
probably you know what i have a good
idea i can make ninji read those texts
or part of those texts texts
to help me with some kanji and also um
help me understand and help me not
strain my voice too much yeah i'll make
it i'll make energy read everything
inside
it's inside
[Music]
so i'm really hungry now i gotta gotta
grab some food now good night everyone
thank you for watching today
thank you guys sorry for not reading
super chats i'll read them tomorrow it
might might even be a separate stream
we'll see
oh bye bye and enjoy
[Music]
thank you
it's food time
[Music]
da da
you know what what's a cool pose
this
not really is it cool maybe if i look
like this
do i look cool
[Music]
seek thanks okay bye
everyone take care of yourselves okay
[Music]
i just opened uh
just opened twitter and i saw i don't
know simple i got a new hairstyle
by the looks of it cute
i saw that she was getting some kind of
update
oh that's cute
she's got a hood
[Music]
oh cute
wait she's also releasing her
what is that
she's relating to her religion releasing
her first original song as it seems
to say
[Music]
okay i'm so hungry i'm out of here
so hungry
what