[Music]
n
a
[Music]
s
hello can you guys hear
us yo K Kitty key I'm a w k Kitty
Dad Dad Dad I I I feel so bad like I
feel so rude towards cie because I can't
see her just move your
head her her camera is right in front of
her face what do you mean you totally
see her she's right beside
you talking about what are you talking
about when I look frontal I can't I
can't look at her I'm going to make
funny faces at you and you won't be able
to see me and you're looking at her
something that's for
sure sorry
do you uh remember these
microphones remember them oh yeah yeah
why is mine upside down again because
back then you started out with an upside
down microphone and hook thought oh she
she wants an upside down mic a hook was
so silly I appreciate it though back in
the day they're so old I haven't had it
during my during my yes I know I was so
happy to see it that was so cute
actually that thing was that thing the
mic was ready for the three on it but I
didn't have like a place to use it so I
was like please I must use it for the
birthday live so I used it it was nice
to see I didn't know that you were going
to do that the microphone into 3D wow
and for people who don't know uh these
mics are like really old around our
debut time my artist hooka Papa made us
some you know simple cute Koka
microphones so here they are yeah cute
sorry sorry if hear mouth noises I'm
chewing gum like a Yankee right
now I'm feeling fresh yummy yummy so
we're here for a nice C out OCH
session we're going to yeah we're going
to wak wak we're going to Hype up for
the
hor which is this
weekend we'll all be there yeah every
single every single one of myth will be
there we will indeed Maybe not maybe not
all on the same day but uh yeah yeah
different different days we all be there
so you guys better cheer for us okay
yeah any of you guys can't be there in
person there's of course is always a
online streaming option so watch us
please and to get into the spirit of
this hyped up event we're going to sing
whole life songs only yeah yeah wow
wowow so I asked each member which H
life songs they can sing so that I can
like you know choose only those
obviously and and you girls have given
me some choices and then I like for
everything that like overlap for example
if am said she knows a song and K says
she knows a song then I put them
together so there will be nice shuffling
units yeah I may have overestimated how
many songs I know I you gave me the
biggest list I did I vaguely know no I
really appreciate you want to be helpful
my list is quite sure was two songs
Jesus I'll move my hand I'm sorry I I
didn't include like the group songs I
know so I thought oh surely she can sing
the group songs so I put I listened to a
lot of them but I never like took time
to learn them I know the Melodies I'm
just like the lyrics go just say w over
and over again H wouldn't that W or yeah
and it'll be fine but uh yeah all the
lyrics are on we have them already and
um they're romanized for easy
understanding just just as a side note
isn't that what happens when you you
guys also go to karaoke here it's like
everyone just pulls out their phones for
the ROI cuz the
screen you can speak Monga you can only
speak yeah but I I imagine yeah for like
people who are not who Al especially
because like if you sing something you
have to be able to read it really fast
yeah exactly like I can read like and
stuff but like I can't read fast enough
for the song yeah so I'm just like well
take my
phone I I can't even do that because
usually the connection is so bad in like
K places for me has English lyrics
though for English songs cuz I went to
one yesterday by myself yeah so when in
da just go for English songs yeah they
got everything they do have a whole lot
of English songs like world yes yes yeah
I get to scared to sing them though they
have all of a solo songs too chikaku
too Ino Japanese K play
yeah so we're all together it's an off
collab let's go we're going to have fun
I'm not coping a feel on Amit stop where
do you guys want me to put my hand cuz
here it's Kiara and here it'sit what do
you want me to do F holding hands or
it's in my pocket no I can't do anything
it's it's bad every way sorry it's okay
all right F A sorry anyway yes we're
going to sing songs y so let's start
with journey like a thousand years yeah
that's you been a thousand years already
fly do you feel old
yet well I've been alive for more than a
thousand years so this is just like baby
baby years yeah some people that like
started off like finding out about myth
when they were freshmen in high school
are getting ready to graduate person
from high school isn't that crazy what
even is a freshman first year first year
it's so cute we don't say that in
Austria wow so cute okay J stop stop
everyone says stop they don't want to
know the truth stop what stop the a what
we all die one day guys everyone dies
everyone okay girls please I'm the proof
let's go to go fly Echo the longer we oh
you start
Reverb you get ready to click and sing
click I why is there so many songs that
start off right away we're singing I
mean really need
the quick three two
one
longer we stronger it makes us as we
fight every F hold on finally defeat
this journey thousand years to
[Music]
meet Yeah Yeah Yeah
hyp Song and now Enchanted by R painted
and wishes granded by time our longest
dos connect yours ech of Ages
by made a spash but found I'm not free a
fish out of water bound to the
Sea brought you right
by I bet this moment away we can ride
yeah connecting songs of
the
sky take off and fight the longer we
wait the stronger it makes us as we
fight every F strength to finally defeat
this journey thousand years
to witness to fire in our minds burning
inside Rising again From the Ashes every
bruis scratches makes us feel more alive
we never give up never give in no matter
what say instead will
crush
us'll make it ourselves and make
memories there ain't a mystery our
brains cannot solve we just shine
brighter
tiol connecting songs across the
wall the longer we wait the stronger it
makes us as we fight everything streng
to the fin the this journey a thousand
years to me let's get very extra here we
go at the end of this world there's
there's our Fighting Chance sorry
nothing changing it's always the same
story staged with a different
dance seek out a happy end for me my
friends and those who've loved us up
till
now I want to see
smile I wait you somehow and fly was
that right we wait it
makes strength to finally defeat
Journey let's go let's TR it can't Beed
the wish in my heart is you right here
by my side strength is all that will me
I won
wait to
[Music]
me I can't sing seriously when all of
you are like right here that just
sounded to me like the ending sounded to
me like cats in the night in the in the
like in an alley outside
Yow sorry it's just all of you guys'
faces are right here so when I sing
seriously I'm like oh my God they're
looking at least in like karaoke rooms
it's dark so you can't see the
facea look at your phone don't don't
look at anything else just look at your
phone but they're all looking at me what
do I do we're not we're not I'm not
looking at you cuz the freaking camera
was blocking your face rude you can't
see me stick my tongue out in you B I
wish I could see it
clap clap
clap let's go you got to sing louder or
get closer to the
microphone okay okay rapping is fine too
you know if you're worried about like
the sound of the melody just rap it you
know that's that's what I'm going to do
that's what I'm going to do for some of
these that I don't
know that was our was that our first
song or our second one that was the
first one that we did the I mean the
first as in like the first that we ever
released I mean together yeah that was
our first one
ever we were kind of like what about
Country Road no that I mean I mean
Originals we don't talk about country Ro
that's our original song what do you
mean that's our original what treat
though treat say my or treat was the
first one true yeah yeah it is kind of
our first original yeah Halloween stream
we did that was so fun really happy with
that one is that the one where we played
that that uh that game with the
neighbor oh was that a different
Halloween the neighbor game where we
were like it was like a scuffed game I
thought it was we had like um I think
the council joined in at that time and
they all had they all had like councilor
joined and they had like their our first
Halloween would have been like right
after debut yeah yeah the first was I
think it was the the collab was that the
neighbor one was star together or what
did we do T star whatever I don't
remember that was for Halloween yeah the
cursed frog and shark ones shark frog
shark was neighb was 2020 they said yeah
yeah yeah not squashy so
[Music]
nostalg even the Scuf games are fun when
it's love you it's true yeah those some
good times honestly the maze though was
my favorite Halloween thing
that yeah everyone had their Halloween
yeah you could be like a frog or a shark
yeah oh twerk twerking was I a frog I
was a frog right I think so those are
the beginnings of froggy waa I still go
watch that sometimes just cuz it's so
funny I miss the shark
Bros oh yeah really really funny good
times good
times cool I am by the way planning a a
big VR event for all of us for Easter
again so April April yeah Easter is
apparently on officially this year on
the 1st of April but I think I'm going
to do it on the 31st of March yeah
because I a lot of you girls probably
want to do an April Fool stream so I
won't do it on the first of April So the
plan currently is like 31st of March and
I hope it will make it a time Easter
second year in the RO cross fingers
crossed this time it will be hopefully
less scuff so um please look forward to
it yeah just on the topic of are you
know yeah all right all right all right
let's um let's sing like a a duet duet
how about we we'll get
C together
with how
[Music]
about I'm I'm going I'm the orchestrator
the puppet master god she's so
scary cie signed up for a lot you know
no I just gave a bunch of songs I can
sing these big Tas how about M7 M oh God
the one the one that I don't know very
well we'll get it out of the way we'll
get it out of the way now okay if you
need help I I think I know it a little
bit get ready for the best rendition of
Mumu yummy you've ever heard in your
life you just got to like envision your
inner Oka you s by and just sing like
chill okay yeah I feel I was like in a
classroom where the teacher's looking
for someone to read and you were like
please don't call please don't please
don't choose MOA yummy please ey contact
well you put Mami as a song so you can
sing so I'll have you I made a mistake
andj M yummy by Calli and honor all
right oh is it loud enough I can hear it
all right am you're first go oh wait can
we
restart you can't hear it hold on you
can't hear it oh that will just turning
it up yes okay
okay oh man ruin this I'm going to ruin
[Music]
it
me man go
[Music]
man
you got
it
[Music]
sorry
you got
it a
legend I don't know
this
Sando okay
[Music]
okay
sorry
[Music]
yeah
mag
magic
sorry
yummy
sorry um
there it was cute it was cute I pulled
out a bunch of different little
characters there too you know share with
you guys my acting skills was actually M
on the side the real version the real
Mumu was uh Ena all
along because she's muggle
muggling the cover of all time
why is there a Mor like this I know you
chose a special of those of you who did
choose wait did I write it down yes I
did okay that was beautiful that was
thanks hey how about you how about you
sing a song now easy Grand Puppet Master
okay how about you sing a song how about
you and me sing a song oh my God why do
you do this to me yeah all right let's
do it how about you and me sing do you
it's a M10 spark me like a flame you
know I'll never be the same oh but you
know what I have a problem here cuz like
on my phone the orange and the pink
looks the
same you can borrow mine oh thank
you m I have
your back up thank you okay got me
breathless oh yeah I'm by you night and
day how can something so wrong be making
me feel so right I don't know the melody
for that part what uh is it wait is that
the bridge yeah got me breathless so
yeah got got but now I'm kind of lost oh
guys get a room bread so yeah that's the
bread that's pretty much it though and
by you night and day I'm going to turn
it into a r all right let's
go do you do you I don't want to stop it
yet do you rocket rap version S as a
preference to in my previous stream a
lot do you yeah mhm I do got me
breathless so yeah okay then what do you
Reverb
ooh okay do you by
takamori
go one of the best
songs
yeah I don't want
to
down about you when I see you I know
it's true oh yeah now got to get you oh
now now now if it ain't you baby then
I'm done girl you know it I just can't
resist you your eyes are like a spell
that I can break through and that should
scare me but I don't know baby you're
captivating me and in the end you let me
go what we do love hate all the same if
you know play the game I'm up up I fight
theing and I won't try he all the same
if
play the
[Music]
game the same do you do you say you feel
that same me like a flame I know never
same do do you
the game don't ever let yourself fall in
you got it cuz Love's just like a toxin
the way pain is so common your problem I
can't go I'm just in love know that SM
not Crush save me I'm in too deep and I
love the rush yeah I just can't resist
you like SP I can't break and that scare
me but I don't know baby you captivating
me and in the end you let me go that's
just what we do love all the same if you
know play the game I'm locked up up side
now I can't F the feeling and I won't
try the same if you know play the game
baby you decide if you want me shout it
out it's just a game I can't complain I
do the same do you do you say you do
feel the same me like a flame I know
I'll never be the same do do
the
game got me breathless oh yeah I'm by
you night and
day be making me feel so right
yeah just like you do I'm always coming
back to you you that was really good
thanks I did my best let's go is just
game I can't complain I do the same do
you do you
you me like aame I know I'll never be
the same oh do you do you in the end let
just
is just a game we play
hat you
say just game play love hate TR and
[Music]
betray
game
hey
uhuh that was fire yeah that was really
good that was so
smooth
the that was pretty smooth I love how
Ena was dancing the whole time I saw you
like boogieing down yeah she was vibing
side of my eyes my eyeballs I feel like
the way you were vibing you like you
could probably even sing the
song probably not bust a move please
continue to bust believe in yourself
yeah believe believe thank you k for
singing do you with me no problem hey
teacher can I sit down now you're
sitting can I can I stop can I stop my
report please and let another kid have a
chance yes yes yes all right I'll
orchestrate something big UPS teach
thanks see what do we uh uh a song with
Ena perhaps she just don't blame me guys
by the way for not assigning Ina to too
many songs I would have I totally would
have she didn't give me many songs I
just don't don't
have learn for next time but okay Ena
gave me a really really amazing one
though oh sorry Kell you have to sing
with
her can you please stop doing this to me
why am I at all of them we're going to
do M2 that's cool I want to sing it's
fine I'm not I'm not shy or anything I'm
I'm looking forward to this one
ghost I feel like I have to try if I'm
going to sing I don't even know if my
horse is warmed up enough for
this it's fine don't worry I won't bust
out Gilbert I'll keep him you ready oh I
think you sippy sippy sippy sippy I mean
there's intro so it's fun okay okay here
we go enjoy
yay I'm not a coward I'm not a coward
yeah she's Callie you're my Joker Callie
stop I'm not a coward you're Joker my
Joker stop you're my the ass the ass up
my sleeve fo what what is that what
that's recited in German sh with the the
the you know the the TR the tra
card say ass the ass of all right take
it away Ena bring us
[Music]
[Applause]
home
fore the
dark
[Music]
[Applause]
fore nice than
this
[Music]
[Applause]
money to do
it
[Music]
foree
[Applause]
amazing guitar so
[Music]
low
[Applause]
for need to get your
[Music]
foree
W
yo
amazing
wow thank you for the punch punch punch
that was beautiful thank you that was
fun that was a fun song to sing that's
one I've
singing yeah you didn't need a warm up
Ina I always do otherwise my voice
cracks cat like oh was cracking this
time you did not release your Kraken
yeah if your voice cracks once you got
to make it crack over and over again to
make it seem like you did it on purpose
Ena Ena Ena likes that joke I didn't
even realize that you made a joke there
hold on that was cracking her up that
was good stop yeah thank you I I'm a
comedi
hen stop
it I want to die get it cuz I'm the Grim
Reaper cooking today day okay that was
beautiful enough enough
enough I can't party without some
pun I'm yeah I Choose You W wait let me
turn off Echo just for a moment uh the
next one
is Sparks okay light the
flame yeah this one okay Sparks is with
am and
kiaha woo so many songs are just
capitalized sorry we're so edgy yeah the
Capal I'm like glitch the real Edge is
when we have both I want to fix
something too all capitals and lowercase
letters all mixed
up if everyone's changing their stuff I
want to change my stuff too a my
hat throw away the gum what what's the
code H oh 1 2 3 4 you know the code know
the code
wow I want to like is this I don't know
how I have to memorize but I do one one
one one it's like they all know this is
better this is better okay okay okay are
you ready am okay you're starting off
with the first line right all right it
and I want to I want to hear you loud
and clear not just me I'm saying it for
them okay where's where's Sparks
uh
okay
Sparks yeah Sparks like the flame yeah
my throat hurts so Dan I'm going to
dance Too you tell me when it start I
forgot okay okay I think you'll feel it
here it comes it will start in 3 2 1
zero down on the floor late night you
don't know don't know don't know what to
do
hard to tell what's wrong what's right
if yes or no don't know don't know what
to do it's hard and you're losing the
way take a chance and dance the r you
got the king never throw it away don't
forget don't forget what
I out of your head only once you make it
you're going to be
okay going head and do it do it if you
want it let's get to it everybody's
going to know your name SP like the flam
the Dark of the night don't stop don't
stop just go your own way so don't be
afraid just your heart keep your head in
the
G never be afraid got to make it hot
like a volcano a match burn it up keep
your feet against the table to the Beet
of
your like the flame so don't wait start
a fire today stop stop just go your own
way we and looking back take the fast
lane now the drive seat they just gas
out
loud so fast that should be that's how
we like it you heard what I
said of your head is only what you make
it you're going to be
okay take a step and move it move it try
you won't get through it everybody's
going to know your
name the of the night today don't stop
don't stop just go your own way so don't
be afraid just your heart keep your head
in the game keep up keep up and never be
afraid let go off the past tonight just
the future only you define
Kiara
and I'm I'm
aor
go don't stop don't stop just go your
own way so d be afraid trust your heart
keep your head in the game keep up but
never be afraid got to make it hot like
a
volan
[Music]
Up Wait start a fire today don't stop
don't stop just go your
[Applause]
[Music]
own go Kara go yeah
[Applause]
flame they did we're setting the studio
on fire wow oh myud is kind of expensive
Idol barbecue except it's not Idols
barbecuing it's idols on fire being oh
barbecued sniff American style barbecue
yeah wait I think I'm no never mind
there are a couple Americans in here
never
mind or it uh I mean Japanese Japanese
Korean stule they are kind of different
aren't they so many different barbecues
Yakiniku Yakiniku Yakiniku is the best
that's my own personal opinion yeah
Barbe barbecue barbecue what's your
favorite uh in in Japanese Yakiniku
what's your do you have any like
favorite piece of meat
that I mean do you remember one no I
don't know yeah you like the th the thin
one not the tongue I don't like the tong
yeah cuz like I think you like the same
things as me I think I remember yeah so
like just like yeah just like maybe like
um brisket brisket like akami like red
meat and nothing else so like no horon
right like you're not noon no horon no
tongue yeah I think you also like Ros
though Ros okay sure yeah yeah it's the
yummy red meat that's not anything
strange of course
w I'm going to sneeze oh yeah hor yeah
it's not my thing either oh yeah sh sh
my favorite yeah bless you you
sorry you mean with like the golden
Flakes and I mean it doesn't always
come with golden flakes it comes with
golden flakes where you go all right
well I've just seen it have flakes on it
that's but it do be usually like a fancy
piece of meat to order sh sometimes they
bring out the certificate is that French
yeah but said Japanese Japanese
pronunciation
it just means
like hat right I don't know I don't know
you know
[Music]
French we're not like we're talking like
uh not to each other but like against
sideways sideways yeah like parallel
we're in a parallel universe talking
French to each other we're not
communicating next I don't eat gold
flakes by the way chat stop you don't
eat them but you can eat them right no I
did look I only took people to do that
because I wanted to show them hey look
I'm getting you an expensive State cuz I
love you I don't eat that alone okay no
no yeah that's fine I think I went with
Kelly once or twice why I went to an a
rice place and they had um goldplated
potato salad it was like covered
completely in Gold PL okay that sounds
kind of
yummy house every night no I don't know
why just wanted to be shiny yeah yeah
shiny Kelly you don't have to feel like
like weird or so cuz like nowadays I
think gold flakes are like in a lot of
things it doesn't mean that the that
expensive I don't waste my money on
Golden steak please believe me that's
not where your AA SPS are going for it's
to make coobo smile please imagine
imagine imagine cie like one day showing
up with the golden
teeth gr yeah C of Grill that's tacky as
I wouldn't do that doesn't suit her
it doesn't suit her I wouldn't do that
but if anybody you know it's got to be
the rapper no no Grill please you don't
like grills no that would not suit me at
all I'm not like cute the bling
bling I like cute grills that's what
about rose gold grills okay rose gold I
still think that's kind of tacky I love
rose gold does everybody have like a
favorite kind of like you know rose gold
I like rose gold like silver or rose
gold or gold I don't like jewry you
don't like jewry I don't wear jewelry
either they have purple gold now purple
gold yeah I video making purple gold I
was like there's purple gold like a 40
minute long video of a guy playing with
gold I'm looking it up purple gold I
mean okay looks nice W yeah looks like
never takachi purple yeah it is it is
it's like a muted purple T purple I mean
isn't it just like an
amethist it's it's like an alloy of gold
like you mix it with a certain other
metal in gold and then it turns that
shade when it so can they not make that
with all
colors I don't think so cuz it has it
needs a chemical reaction to pull that
color yeah well you and me certainly
have a chemical reaction
on just like I'm still in my previous
stream
girl it's just me it's one-sided
Amy
I like you all down it's a good thing I
have across the table from you gor
scor okay let's do let's do another
group song oh okay uh let's do we did
Journey let's do
nonfiction spreadshot yeah that one I
can't wait to Screech and have my voice
higher high notes sorry sorry this
song's so high don't die me first
listening to the demo I'm just like yeah
this is do I get to my part uh oh I did
tell I did tell the producer we could
sing higher than I think we actually can
surprisingly I can sing lower than what
I'm usually
given um I might I might look up the
lyrics here cuz I can't really see it
what is this C Gilbert
returns anyone have a helium balloon
asking for
f oh uh you start you go from some some
until song You and I okay okay H then
you start from do okay okay see okay
okay sorry if I like uh mistakenly sing
yours cuz I think it's my color I just
got to channel my inner opera
singer I can't I can't do what narissa
can do though I guess got Nissa in here
yeah okay get her to do some oper
belting for us guys let's go
nonfiction
enjoy I still remember the
the song's so chuny but I love
[Music]
it
belongs F lines of words and rhy is a
hidden
though fractur deeply worn by Sorrows
from time and time again take my hand
and
ENT
[Music]
it yeah
yeah it's so fun to
say no one can top the way bua sings
that
hard
fact
by
St
anding
ining soul to hear a song when string
don't stri SP of Life stay on the now
for behave we St
instead all
together reach out the ever we page we
ignite come alive like a starv night
with the fire no doubts can take away
got no very Fe love pril so painful now
we Mo endlessly On By the Light Spar and
Bre into the
dark sorry this is C right the next yeah
this
[Music]
one's some RS upon a time not where a
voice gets heard will the gred lines of
speeding time make us f l when then is
running dry a soul on fire is driven to
react and when burning flames attack we
will never fade to black no fake not a
dream or a trick
of always fake and see take a see it's
our story side a World's brought to life
their vo is VI and is real they say p
sword we choose in FA we can never lose
our way by star SK and
theing ining along muscl who hear our
song when go the
[Music]
stret stay on the fre now forces say
behave we
[Music]
stay
oh God this o oh def Until the End stay
killing to
[Applause]
singing and Me
Wings remember the good times
we
all set every final pie in motion now R
let's go woo in a sh Souls Reach Out
theage night come alive like a star
night with a fire no doubt can take away
a fairy
tale sh may we joyfully On By the
Light days are just the part of being
free we V it all by
heart and smile side by side
[Music]
among I definitely felt my Grandma
coming out there in
my they're telling me turn am's mic up
but we only have one microphone and it's
the mid in the middle of us maybe I'm in
a weird spot cuz I'm I did try when you
were singing I don't know if you guys
noticed I I lowered at at one point I
lowered the instrumental a little bit I
did see you doing that so we can hear
AIT but I can't do that all the time
yeah sorry it's it's enough can I see
something I just want to see what shape
the microphone is on Square maybe that's
why cuz I'm at a corner oh true a you
are at a corner it does have the the
circle setting in the back on right now
yeah yeah but if I were see if I were
right here compared to being like right
here I don't know if you can hear a
little bit sounds the same this sounds
the same you can like lean a bit more
forward like this but then your D gets
obstructed but it's it sounds muted
compared to like when I'm right here
compared to like when I'm right here it
oh we're doing ASMR now let's go slight
slightly better they say they hear the
difference yeah yeah okay sounds better
okay I'll scoot over then
yeah big difference all right all right
K by the way you said one and a half
hours you have time right for this oh
yeah okay then we got to hurry up and do
more songs yeah it's cool don't need no
need to rush or anything but it's it's
exciting yeah yeah okay then let's see
let's do uh we did
this we did ah ooh Let's test out the
new acoustic settings that am has
provided us with by doing
M8 what's that one it's the end of a
life end of end of a life I signed up
for end of a life I'm curious about I
didn't sign up you just ask what song
you you said you know that one all right
let's just we can we can do this one
full together if you no separation just
just follow my lead girl just follow my
lead you'll be fine okay I I
mean okay unison's fun hey you know what
Unison singing is fun okay but but but
you belt so hard that we might not hear
am so I'll I'll make I'm closer to the
mic I'll be
[Music]
okay right right through hold on a
second I sorry i i r oh it's nice I'll
never find my
I'll toide this Labyrinth of Lights
there was Madness in the meaning
neverless we were screaming at the top
of our lungs to num City never
died I'll
fly
no those hides I'll never find another
chance to say thanks for saving my life
I was hopeless it was singing running
roadless we were singing at the top of
our LS to ninous this city never
beautiful yeah let's go what what's the
root of it all huh I couldn't say used
to jumping and fall R clich we rug it
off without complaint not a sound you
I'm trying to find friends cuz in the
end nobody sticks around when you
yourself a crowded place that you turned
around and found yourself in loveing
outer space c The Reckless nights no
strengths laughing at own dreams just
what the hell was so fun the tree
stumble used to fall in the concrete
jungle singing CU it's all right we mix
the on and trou R our discontent and
though it's history I can't forget the
time that we spent convin that this
could be another end exist between
pretend Twisted alter fiction where I
miss my disapp into the is the that I
can never befriend Let It Go fade in
Fade Out this crazy dream without a
direction floting
aimlessly there's nothing left back
there for me Brea in but it won't stop
the rain from pouring
run right
through those nights I'll be find my way
back to you inside this La the light
there was Madness in the meaning never l
screaming at the top of
our city
never was there a inside fireflies
between theing highrise left a trail
behind to find and Wasted Time Of Our
Lives silencing are overworked and under
thinks in offices a cofin until office
where you late yet aist an optimist who
to be nothing wrong you're right songs
behind the lonely shade the world s
place without the words that you convey
when the ladder fell and shattered every
bar that we play does it matter in the
end the mened and DEC and your friends
retired of fantasy or wishing they State
you don't get to say I miss you you
watch your hero until the rear view
mirror of the villain you portray stop
the pity party listen you don't get to
be dismay you don't get to be emotional
feel blessed you got it made these the
best of years of life because you chose
to make a tra Rec the days and hope you
pray for this what is that this fade in
Fade Out this ha dream without your
direction
aimlessly there's nothing left back
there for me pretend the end of a made
up story
fly
noof those I never find chance to say
thanks for saving my life I was hopeless
it singing
dness were singing at the top of our
L this died say goodbye
toow there was Rance in self we've got
no
chance but the hands Through The Night
We R so fast till the school Chimes till
the train runs we know it's
time waking up now to the real life let
dayam till the next night I'll keep
waiting the saxes Jack keep waiting for
you
[Music]
oh let's go tax let's go Mr
sex
W yeah oh piano give it to
me
yeah to
[Music]
myam the next flight driv so long I got
older now the crowd's gone is it over is
it over this is it's over over y it
feels like it's back to 2021 I was
looking at amma's lips and she really
was keeping up there yeah the the rap I
was looking at
me the death rap of the verse two maybe
next am solo song is a rap song yeah
give us some bars let's go yo
MC that was beautiful that was really
nice and you you girls had like a good
un Harmony yeah we Blended pretty well I
beautiful thank you so much for singing
so beautifully for all that was fun your
you guys turn yeah now you guys sing
together no there's nothing there I
think because in only gave me two songs
oh we can do another group song uh yeah
yeah yeah wa wait let me see which ones
do we do we did we do the ah okay okay
okay we can do another group song We Can
Do Re okay which is so fun
okay continuing this
Odyssey
refrain
[Music]
memories okay I found
it uh why what numberers is this all
this is all you right cuz I made you uh
the whole g r is covered by cie I didn't
think I didn't think anybody of us could
do good us rap uh so
suddenly speak so fast guys I'm sure
Callie can do it cuz you wrote it I I
did yeah G's in my head she's in there
do your best girl impression yeah like a
cutesy WAP yeah
reun reunion in
Japan
which one is here ready set
stream continue the harmony confuses
me Contin this I'm singing with the
harmony
yeah M and when the cloud Skies become
bright let's
reunite
he hey
he can you guys believe we're actually
Idols no way we did it has been set
stream is Showtime baby I would say
today's broadcast on sight delay rubbing
out the stuff is it really enough so
buffering endlessly why to it easy what
have we learn start of fire in their
hearts on the PC Burns optimistic focus
on a quick fix teach still go stronger
but never and never saying die and I'm
aware it's ironic but where's the
freaking lie dreamers to streamers to
entain is to S I'm not losing to you
young people ignore her
dead bring mystery toing out astion
dancing in Flight we
ignite crating in the my that we're
creating there's another story waiting
through this world and beyond our
distant dreams have brought us here a
strong unyielding Bond guiding us and
the sleep will bring us
that we hold dear Time Rushes on and
these winds may scatter us we'll keep
this promise when the moment finally F
we'll always find a way to
re cute
yeah
oh
yeah I'm diving in again now it's time
Sinker let's try the deeper end we could
to hold my f with everyone
Andy and have fun nobody escapes death
and I know that it's morbid your coming
go I'll still pretend I've got this
killing disorted listen I want to look
cool but end up tripping and falling gu
I'll keep playing the fo to hold on Thea
or
calling moment let us do this day
triumphant sorrow hope for tomorrow
we'll always find
[Applause]
say
something yeah go
here wait can go sing this next part but
can she hear it oh
my where are we where are we in every
Universe we were always meant to meet
sing sing in every
Universe in every Universe we were
always meant to
[Applause]
sear that'll
never
know we will theth
throughing dra us together I can sense
another wish is coming true each we
Str me and you all together
sing out again wait sing out again I
forget the cloud SK C start this F
briming with memories another story
starting right here we'll keep forging
ahead to make a saga all our own
whichever we treadly journeying we know
we're never really alone if we believe
wherever F may find
our love will us every epic chapter we
ride will set us on the back
to hey hey hey hey hey oh my
God oh my God
perfectly the timing yo wow what timing
hey that's a
surprise while I was singing and looking
at my lyrics on my phone I got a message
from gura and was
like and then she came
in
Goa Kaa Goa say something hi hi hello
she's so small okay you talk and I move
[Applause]
this it works technology what song are
you guys on uh reunion which is 1 2 3 4
5 6 7even eight song was that oh my
goodness it sounded like a crazy person
rapping to myself it was funny it was
pretty good would you be willing to sing
with us a little bit or are you leaving
soon I can
say we could like let's see what songs
do we have left we
have oh my God there's
two freak the real one wait I'll make
space I'll make space how' she get so
big um
oops wow so she really sprouted up huh a
it's all of the
N like this oh no let me put where are
we gdy gdy oh
yeah here she
is let's go here my God there's a shark
in the water we scooched we scooched
okay this one can go
Evacuate the ocean byebye do we want to
add like I don't know something into it
or do we want to like how about can you
sing
chuu CH or can you sing Violet cuz like
those are songs we have already planned
and I you could like replace someone
else how should I know if you want no no
no go with your plan go with your plan
no I need to add just I just came out of
how about we I'm a bit I'm a bit
mentally poooo right
now
she could just join in the chorus yeah
she can join we still have the another
group song join in that one oh we can
sing the uh wait another gr oh but
that's not our we can how about we do a
like journey of a thousand years or so
again but this time with the original
lyric split Engish
English okay it's not in there but um do
we know the original lur split I mean
the lurks are in there but the lyrics
plate is different it's time for a pop
quiz ladies we know it I don't remember
I mean I remember don't
to the on that because yeah bring closer
the shape of the
microphone Country Roads is always
waiting for you no no no I cannot yeah
that then we'll have to
unar oh we totally know this one we're
one take me home it should be good right
to the place yes sir what a nice
surprise we good journey of a thousand
years again okay
[Music]
yeah okay you you can hear the music and
all all right there is a knob for you to
change if you there's only four knobs
though this is mine yeah yeah mine is uh
uh over here this are these are all
yours one of the cables yeah this oh
this one should be I could hear it okay
okay okay I think so I can't hear it
anymore but we'll see yeah I I stole
your headphones these were those were
broken kind of wait sharing one huh can
share one sharing is those weren't
working before they're working okay
they're like cutting out for me okay
that's why we just have manag nice oh
they also say myth or treat Bo but the
thing is I have instrumentals prepared
cuz it's not my own PC OB you look it up
on YouTube I'm pretty sure this treat
instrumental okay all right then let's
do reunion one more time not reun like a
fast take off and fly fly F fly the
stronger it makes us I'm not scrolled to
the song one second
Str Fe this journey a thousand years to
me let's
[Music]
[Applause]
go yeah take it away you know song and
stuff
Enchanted by rhyme painted in wishes
grounded by time our longest hopes
connect a fish out of water bound to the
Sea a reckless High di by my side I bet
this moment away we can
ride connecting songs cross the
sky take off and fly the longer we wait
the stronger it makes us as we fight
every F strength to finally defeat this
journey a thousand years to
me witness the fire in the minds burning
inside Rising again From the Ashes every
bruis and scratches makes us feel more
alive we never give up never give in no
matter what's ahead and stad will crush
your's
us see we'll make it ourselves and make
memories there ain't a mystery our
brains cannot solve we just shine
brighter gr
tiol connecting songs across the
wall take off and fly the longer we wait
the stronger it makes us as fight every
F strength to finally defeat this
journey a thousand years to
meet at the end of this world where
Fighting
Chance nothing changing always the Stag
with
dance seek out a Happ for me my friends
and those who loved us up till
now I want to see
smile find my way to you somehow take
off and
fly wait long us as we
F the she's
[Music]
back
let's in my heart is you right here by
my side strength is all that we need
[Music]
[Applause]
years I'm moving her you're a PNG it
works the future sure is amazing
I love
technology these are good as real
movements what what happened to her hand
she's fished so she swimming around
sorry I tried to adjust this so that it
would it was like Turned but
accidentally
it's fix it
orod oh okay maybe you can probably
reenter it should be fine yeah one 2
three
four nice how lovely how
lovely
this one I
think ass so we're going to do as next
song how
about back okay we're seeing hopefully
she's here to stay this time I'm not
going to touch it this
time I'll put small here how about
violence with Ena and
am what a special
collaboration
Violet okay are you ready to sing if GA
feels like chiming in she can always
chime in you got to you got to let us
hear your voices if you want whenever
you want whenever you feel like
it no pressure though no
pressure
Violet you
ready you
ready okay yeah you didn't sound so
comtable always hear help
[Music]
sorry
for
[Music]
foree
fore
[Music]
[Applause]
foree
[Music]
beautiful
speak speak speak it speak the language
of the
gods they sound like
[Music]
that
y beautiful music you too you two should
sing more together cuz your voices
together are very sweet I'm cute when
she sings like
ballads in the beginning I was like
who nice what do we have left VI done
the last hey also I'm realizing you made
me sing all the ones that I was in like
first why' you do that to me I don't
know it just kind of happens no it
didn't no it didn't to take one for the
team thank you all right yeah no Pro
you're welcome
guess girl your
lashes my God
myti I felt the Bri over here when you
were
blinking that's what the wind was K's
looking very on flake sorry I
specifically did it before you guys all
got here cuz I wanted to look
onom oh it even matches I didn't notice
your nail yeah my nails magnetic shiny
magnetic yeah yeah it's like magnet nail
polish yeah yes so it's like a magnet
nail polish thing see look oh I love
that design too it's wait so if I put a
magnet on there it's going to stick C
cute cute maybe thank you take them off
if you ever go into like a what's it
like a MRI
machine like my hands
like ow ouch
ouch that probably doesn't feel so
comfortable is it time for
CH how should I know how should I
know M9 it's kaha here with me the clock
won't stop spinning waku Wu
wuu it's time
again's
[Music]
go you're here with me that's right I'm
not just
a coming she's right next to me is that
an
imposter
[Music]
when we first
met I wonder to what you think of me
the it was aect narrative but time went
by I forgot to hide the laughs that came
so naturally to lows and high I wonder
why
I ever thought you would leave now no
matter where or when we are I know it's
you I can count
on nothing can stop us
now time
go how should I know why it seem when
you're here with me the clock will stop
spinning W wa W doy doy hi spe faster
all night you R forever
clear to see that this mystery was soled
immediately know you got
[Music]
me I'm a
dance oh
[Music]
yeah it's been so
long since I laugh so hard I cry you
came
along it happens almost every time that
I hear your voice I'm left no choice but
to let you know what you mean to me
spying time skipping protur memories now
no matter where or when from our
friendship's elementary case Clos now
you know nothing can stop us
now time
go how should I know seem when you're
here with me the CL will stop
spinning doy doy SP
faster forever C to see that mystery was
immediately chicken me each day we're
older what the future holds is not not
not for us to know yet it's gone gone
gone before we know it so let St a
question
we can make each second
tile
forever now
[Applause]
or how I know why it seems when you're
here with me the clock w't stop
spinning faster don't D you friends
forever
to see this mystery was Sol
immediately I'm not just I'm
a look at
[Music]
this
I'm are you
[Applause]
I'm not small am I know I'm a detective
I I will arrest
you
wow wow
wowow what a
banger that was fun aming oh oh there's
someone with you and me oh there is
that's right the most edgy one of them
all God the edgiest song and then
there's uh a grip song yeah Y
which but if you remember how to sing
that last group song you're welcome to
join in that last group song but we'll
sing
after oh that's the best one
yeah okay okay uh so retrospective when
we think of Edy songs we think of
present let's go stuck in an endless
loop I will deny the truth don't deny it
asking why deny it how do you how retos
it's really
deep in
retrospective have we sang this before
together no together no oh I guess we
haven't but you sang it in a I did a
couple
times let's be oh Loney is here to lyri
ride just
emotional you wouldn't understand unless
you know you looked at the lyrics really
deeply yes yes be sure to let out your
emotions I will lot of grows I am blind
oh here it is
okay here we go here we
go enjoy the edge the first cord when it
hits Oh wait I can't really see can
I borrow someone's uhoh thank you it's
all right I start
[Music]
Yeahs you the same I guess that's life
if you couldn't tell by now I'm
hopelessly waiting begging all night to
break
through second and last l b deny the
truth asking
why
let's go I can't
redo the past and present calls me to
truth and every part of my being doubts
the best feeling so tell me what am I to
you I can't
renew the part of me I lost in The View
hooked up on all the waving eyes leaves
me
pared taking to steps back but I keep
moving
[Music]
on are you feeling the Evanescence yeah
I am I
do I feel 15
again concern is filling up your lies
once again I am all broken I'll save me
if I can I let it go let it go we again
down by now I'm hopelessly wasting I way
to the core
inside it keeps
eating at me every day asking
[Applause]
why I can't
redo the past and present call me to
truth and every part of my being J the
best feeling so tell me what am I to
you I can
renew the part of me I lost it the view
hooked up on the wering eyes lead me
paral taking two St back but I keep
moving
on and I tried to change me but my mind
can't just erase me anym than I have
already done and looking back I'm ready
to admit that it was all me who
destroyed everything
oh caught up in my D caught up in my
can't
ignite puts out my
light I can't be sure of who I am or
when I'm a
li I can't
redo the past and present calls me to tr
and every part of my
beings the best feel
so tell me what am I to
[Music]
you
oh
am
turning
[Music]
back yeah
[Applause]
than my soul ising I can't R the past
and
present the truth we have let all our
edgy emo emotions out feel very very
refreshed it's perfect time because
Kelly has to leave very soon oh I mean I
can I can push it's really it's okay we
have one song left in Fe one
more we don't get to do very often so
they can
wait I think it did we did uh like an
off collab uh on K before a long time
ago remember unarchived no it was UN
archived was it when we were all sharing
the same house yes that was a while ago
now H so sleeping on the
couch I thought off collab you know what
can we do I thought kind okay cuz we
rarely get the chance to sing together
like this true true yeah in a in a
casual not in a live setting right yeah
so got to make use of it group song anle
yeah the last one is a group song but
doio like
uh how about how about goodna sing sing
all of my solo Parts the orange yeah
I'll just I'll just join in like the two
together parts are you sure or I don't
know you can sing all of the blue blue
Parts I mind that all the blue parts are
our about the blue verse Parts yes
please those okay and then we all sing
the the chor we sing together Clump
together sounds good that that actually
works out pretty well but can you also
please sing the opening alone I want to
hear you sing it oh Ure tired but okay
my
best so oh yeah I need to type in the
last one guess what it is guys forgive
me if I flub it I mean all day we've
been fling so don't worry about it you
should have
heard
disaster M was real rough yummy oh yeah
you would have totally nail it you would
have nailed it but we had a hard
time okay okay uh our bread
[Applause]
forade
by got this goob you got this
[Music]
how blind am I here it
is I remember when this starts yeah it's
like right away yeah no no it has a
build up I'm no because she was in the
city I'm say this song the toot okay
here we go wait for the
[Music]
Tooty partyy
yeah yes Orchestra
we're Idols let's
go
yeah why mine's the high
part
[Music]
for
foree
[Music]
Fore
come
[Music]
on
this
foree
[Music]
spee
[Applause]
for
[Music]
[Applause]
our I'm sorry there may have been some
mistakes in thei was incorrect because I
wrote it in one minute there were no
ragi lyrics so and then Jemma left the
room cuz she had to you know pick up on
it and then I was like okay I'll do it
and I really quickly wrote down the Romi
on my own so there may have been like a
few mistakes there wow much
[Applause]
quicker it was mostly mostly correct
yeah that was
so yay that was fun so happy like this
song is perfect for last song right I
think so too it has like this big ending
Orchestra I mean f is almost you know
here yeah I'm so
excited I'm excited for everyone else's
performances too wait to see I hope all
of you will be watching us once
again or will you be there yeah yeah
will you be there I heard about like
compared to last year I heard about so
many more like foreign friends from
overseas coming friends fans coming into
Japan this time like way more than last
year K I know you guys are they're
chilling in Japan some of you mhm yeah
they like offline meetings too and like
they're going to like for me for example
there's a place that I always go to or
like used to go to it's called enoshima
I saw like my fans are like going there
to check out the places I went to and
taking the same pictures and so cute
cute my oh she stood right
here
the I used to do that for bands that I
liked so like I can kind of used to do
that for
fun people go like anime locations in
Japan
right I hope you guys are having in
Japan when you're in Japan and if you're
not in Japan well then I hope you're
having fun wherever you
are watching our streams for example
that is
fun I want to see that Cave the Cave
yeah the cave cave there's a cave there
where you go in with a candle but um
it's it's it's fine it's nice kind of
damp and you know but did you go before
yeah I I love them I've been five times
yeah I brought there with hat remember
yes yes that's anima know there's an
anime that I like that takes place there
so I want yeah I think
[Music]
there's I don't know though the cave
incident wait was there a cave incident
I don't remember a cave
incident
yeah
konima not osima
enima yo you got to be careful and you
say that we're stupid foreigners please
understand so yeah um I don't prepare
any
an should redo
M please please wait who wants to think
I think she's the only one who knows you
want to give us a solo people would cry
we'll we'll chime in We join in the in
the course
okay I'll join in in the places I know
that I won't mess up and
sound yeah okay Anu Anu good version by
someone that knows the song well yes I
thought for will be happy I sure hope so
we need Redemption no pressure no
pressure no pressure pressure Senai are
you listening to this it could not be
worse it could not be worse we can redo
the yummy yeah yeah we can yeah well
first we have to make the chat chat
Uncle Uncle Ray is also fun we can't
hear you Uncle Uncle
Uncle Uncle is it Uncle r or is it Uncle
Ray UN in Japan they say really no shows
I've been there're
like Uncle Uncle R it's Uncle R yeah
what I've been lied to this whole time
keep going is it English is it is it
French in in uh us concerts they usually
do one more song One More
song One More song One More Uncle r
uncle R Uncle Ray is dead I guess
it's Uncle
no alol
alcohol alcohol alcohol alcohol yeah Oh
I thought we were family friendly yes
family friendly that's why I haven't I
only drink mocktails okay mocktails do
be yummy I love mocktails it'll be good
you did order one when you came
over are you ready ever be
okay we got your back wait can boost my
volume we got your back yeah yeah yeah
yeah only like the monitor can be BL oh
okay should I
restart I'll sing really low I'll back
up and no no no
just for
CH
[Music]
number
for
[Music]
yum
okay
[Music]
y
yumy
yummy
[Music]
ymy
yumy
W not
cursed this song brainwashes me it's so
good it doesn't sound like Mumu to me it
sounds like gumo goo you might be the
only one really I seeum
it's like when people say like like
taian over and over and over
again said it's
friendly the meaning of isese is
different
okay maybe I am a little no I'm not Dum
what I'm not D finish you're
smart
oh gura what H do you have that file on
your head I don't you don't I don't cuz
you guys could have prepared uh like
even since Valentine's Day right you had
like all the pickup lines there yes okay
we'll do a collab when when we're back
to our usual homes the usual rooms and
it's it will be a normal collab but you
will throw those pickup lines at me cuz
they cannot go to waste yeah check your
own pulse diara you got to check your
own pulse okay okay heart rate we can do
we can do a horror game stream like uh
Outlast no I have to send you a video of
it for reasons that I'm not going to
tell you but then I'm going to be there
when you listen to it don't make collab
but you have to watch the video it has
to be a video you don't want me to play
another horror game with you no no no we
do the horor G I would already have like
the heart uh thingy on we do the horror
game then I send you the video you watch
it on stream while I'm sitting with you
how about I heard this new game poppy
play time is
popular poy you played it Kelly yeah
they even got it in the claw machines
like in the crane games they got popy
yeah it's so popular pop
poy I don't know what it's about but if
G's there I'll do it especially if my
reward if my reward is pick L from G
I'll do it yeah she won't she won't send
you the video until you complete the
game let's go okay okay okay so was that
lovely or was it not that was fun that
was
fun hold
[Music]
on now I can I I would say I can change
the thumbnail again yeah I do have a
five people version
[Laughter]
so what guess what everybody we have
nothing to announce oh
yeah we have nothing to announce at all
just watch the we just want to announce
that we don't have an announcement have
an announce yeah you thought you thought
we surely are going to advertise some
merchandise to you st no no there is
nothing to buy just enjoy the Fest yeah
well I I mean this is like not company
mandated I just want to say please yeah
watch us at the Fest if you want to it
was going to can we say that we were
going to yeah yeah we had like we kind
of were supposed to do something uh
together but then that got cancelled so
so we did this instead oh right right
right we decided we do it anyway body
pillow no no body pillows no don't you
haven't announced later yeah that's
something different though don't worry
right now it's my time yeah my time but
my time is over
yeah fun though thank you
guys thank you
everybody thank you for
joining you guys are still going yeah
I'm glad you made it I would go on
forever but we got to end it thank you
for watching Everybody
enj Take care it's a myth on on on zero
on on free one two three is 3 1 Z is 321
3 one 3 2 one and then on the Zero we
say timate okay got it are you guys
ready to chat ready three two
one you miss bye
bye bye bye
[Music]
byebye