[Music]
I've switched the
screen yeah oh you did Oh I thought that
was what that
meant sing
[Laughter]
mine let's go
yay
mails pom is having
hallucinations no no is no I okay Kiara
was like who's making that sound and Kar
was like Moon walking in place and then
a started Moon walking in place and it's
you guys it's you it's standing still
she was standing still I was also
standing still
My My My Stream will be on my side I
believe it but it's too late stream is
never on your side you're alone Pomo
you're
alone no
no you'll be on my side
right who me no
[Laughter]
what uh OHA was H what's going on here
hi what's going on
stop it and introduce yourself stop it
stop it at
once this game has TGG go Crouch I
thought it was old this whole
time p
p yeah introduce yourself
oh
okay oh can't see your face up there
hell
everybody yeah it's a little
intimidating right it's kind of
creepy
yeah hello yeah yeah yeah I'm
puu no you're
R I'm one of the worldwide what was it
what were we worldwide wife web we are
the worldwide wife
web I'm I'm Wu of the worldwide
wide we it's not that hard to
say why are you having so many trouble
saying
that
I just woke up okay oh oh yeah can you
give them like uh the story of your your
your current issues that maybe issues
arise because of your current location
oh yes I might stop pointing at me I
feel who's making that noise
what wait who's making that noise no
it's so noise there's no
sound she's hallucinating
again my chat hears
it okay then there also I'm currently
sorry I'm currently in a hotel in Japan
so I might poof out of existence may be
a sound from the hotel
room from next door it's kind of
spooky
spooky all right all right heard enough
of that wife yeah next next one
who oh this wife the we we i i w what no
she's Moon walking she's
not she's
not I W no
you you you we I thought we were all Wu
no only she's
Wu oh then I'm po
no hi I'm wewa from the world W it's our
first I'm
first I'm WEA from the worldwide wife
lab
Ying I'm so
happy I'm so happy we're finally
collabing we even met IRL before but we
never so happy finally wait didn't you
wait in when we met IRL didn't you like
pay for like my whole
dinner no no yes you did yes you did a
stop pointing don't
answer
no that was that was pretty cool and
handsome of you oh then yes I
do nice thank you so much maybe this
time maybe today I can thank you for all
of that maybe I can keep something back
I'm looking forward to
it we what do you what do you know about
this wife
there she got some great assets oh yeah
oh
[Laughter]
yeah I'm embarrassed
stop what's
happening I mean
yeah I even got fan art of myself drawn
in aa's outfit it looks pretty sexy I
saw it did you see it good yeah I saw
it I love the PO thing saw wait I saw
yeah okay
Weis Go on the stage the wife stage
yeah hi Darlings I'm oisa of the
worldwide Wu web
yay beautiful life this is this is my
wife because I'm literally going on a
honeymoon with
her yeah that's so fun stealing kiaha
for
myself I don't really know if that's
really applicable because I invited you
I don't know how you're stealing me you
don't need help
[Laughter]
that I'm so excited I'll have her on
Tuesdays
Tuesday yeah yeah we just switch
off okay okay I guess all right oh my
gosh she's moonwalking nobody's
moonwalking who's Moon
walking maybe maybe we don't know about
our moonwalking skills no I'm not do it
again p
crazy do it again I I don't know what
you're talking about do it do it again
do the moon
again
oh that's not Moon
walking Moon
[Laughter]
walking yeah wait that's so smooth oh my
God she's actually so smooth with
it she's a smooth
criminal
it's great how people can get so excited
over the most scuffed and simple
features of a
[Music]
game so easy to entertain
okaya hello I am The Mastermind behind
the worldwide wife web I am the wife of
everybody if they make me a wife I will
be everybody's wife let me wife you uh
today I came here to go to the wife
convention this is the wife convention
right yeah yeah yeah of course we just
need to pick up a few things first oh
okay then call me wa your wife let's go
let's go
wa wa my wife
yay wife wife wife you guys have a
lethal company wife uh no you you girls
no maybe I think I like the I would pick
the Bracken the Bracken oh the Bracken
it's like The
Nutcracker what it always play since
that existed oh is it a
Monster yeah
yeah okay okay I don't know them yet uh
well shall we set up and start our first
mission then should wait we have to
explain to to okay okay am I the only
one who didn't play it yet was first
play yeah okay have you ever played fmop
phobia yes and I do not like it oh well
it's like the exact same thing except
different yeah yeah point at me point at
me okay so basically kiaha we're going
to be going to moons okay and on these
moons it is our responsibility to go
into these uh long abandoned buildings
and collect materials that at the end of
three days we are going to be selling um
There Are Rules so you're going to
actually want to come over here since
it's your first time and go ahead and
read this
manual uh that's on this table there's a
manual why does it say it's so hard to
read though dominated by a few species
fauna is dominated by a few
species
she's that's what I thought the first
time I saw that too I was
like okay can I man I thought I'm
reading the manual
P oh there it is
sorry never
so we can also just explain to you as we
go but basically we're just looking for
things to pick up bring back to the ship
if all of us wipe we lose all of our
items um so if everyone's dead it's best
to just leave oh okay there will moning
place on the counter and buck D ding
ding the Bell until the company answers
the door and remain what what what is
this about what when selling scrap the
company yeah so Day Day Zero technically
or the last day we go to the company to
sell all the stuff that we found um and
we have to place it on a desk and then
ring a bell for them to come get it how
do I oh there oh oh
uh I can't I can't read and dance I
can't read and
dance what did you expect what did you
do did you do
something oh did you just answer
question oh there we go uh yeah I answer
question but I also don't know how to
use the terminal I don't think we have
use the terminal for the first one I
think we just on right
inter
yeah
need in order to R risk of damage the
autopilot pilot ship will not stay on
the moon surface past midnight please
time your careful get keep the crew mate
at home to Prov we need to keep a crew
mate at home can I stay at home worry no
no no no
no you can't just type the code for
example you know how do I know the the
broadcast code oh whatever Girls you'll
tell me right you'll tell me all of this
ah um yeah of course jeez yeah oh that's
a lot okay let's go let's go all
rightone sh how do I punch someone how
do we start the ship you can't well you
can you get if you pick up like there's
like stop signs inside if you pick it up
you can hit people yeah you can hit
people or you can hit monsters team yeah
so when a monster attacks me I I should
try to attack them back um well some of
them you can and some of them you can
okay walk some of
them they see
you that's a crab wolf I feel like oh
we're moving oh we started
go let's
go kill just like
let run okay I will run I will run wait
did it start run r no one started I
thought the game started Why didn't it
start I thought so too I'm going to
press I sound it sounded like
it I'm going to
start oh Waiting For
Crew
[Laughter]
beep okay please hold my hand
[Music]
when all I have to do is building pick
up
stuff okay F threatens other life forms
okay okay I see good morning this way
right wow uh I don't know is this the
moon are we on the moon it's this way
yeah we're on the moon there's no way
that this you come here there's no way
IED one flashlight no
okay wait can I run oh you don't need a
flashlight that's
fine wait I have nothing you girls have
items no okay this way now we don't have
anything yet we got to make some money
honey oh it's [\h__\h] oh my God
it's
[Music]
wao I haven't played since before
Christmas so I'm like where are we where
is it okay where the [\h__\h] is she going
should be
time for
ice time for ice cream I was just
following you I'm trying to find the
building I hate the audio in this game
oh my God the
Acoustics there where is the
building why are we already separating
where are the
others it's okay they'll find us
eventually hopefully where the [\h__\h] did
they go new creature creature there's a
your la
go not that don't okay don't go in the
water or you will
die okay here's a
bridge new creature what creature am I
seeing there's like one in there's like
little birds that fly but they're not
harmful
okays oh don't go in the water oh oh oh
there's the water there's a fire exit
yeah we're upstairs I think the ex
where's the entrance oh it's right
beside me so we go in from
here the way she
runs hey that's the way you run
too so you just hold e and go inside
okay but where the [\h__\h] is everybody
else
yay hi hi is it just me who finds the
Acoustics so so
upsetting find the what the Acoustics
are so
upsetting so hard to hear one one little
de who made this game all alone yeah
we're in the
toilet it's so awesome it's like 2010
Xbox mic
yeah nothing here Xbox nothing here
okay there's nothing so far everything's
still normal but I'm like I'm getting
nervous when is the Weir [\h__\h] happening
don't go don't go without me don't go
without oh my
God what what what what what what do you
mean there's a Bracken what is this ex
where are he I lost him I lost where are
where are you where are
you what don't scream don't
scream are you okay no ah stay with me
stay with me come here is he gone come
upstairs okay okay she got a gun oh a
why why are we going out [\h__\h]
man why did he go out he heard me
because there's a
Bracken there's a bra p p is bringing
stuff back to the ship oh my God what a
queen I don't just dropped something off
um we could go down here and go in the
fire exit and see if there's anything
different Mountain okay this so weird I
don't understand
anything there's like a monster in this
game that I think if you look at it for
too long then it can like start chasing
you and then it kills you yeah he gets
mad and then I looked at him and then he
was not happy oh
okay oh oh oh I like the I like the
audio in here it's better the P's over
there uh what the bracket yeah where
where no way I saw
something too I don't see it I looked
down the hallway you can go see him if
you want okay yeah go go ahead
K the Bracken is my choice of waifu for
in-game
characters I don't see I'm too
scared I don't see it oh do I have to
scan
no you'll you'll know when you
see I I see it I
[Music]
see
by oh what was that it looked like a fat
slug know it was a really big guy
yeah guy where's Pom is she dead she's
the ship I think okay or that's her
[Music]
hi why are you laughing
she's enjoying life where you going oh
well there's a v I think and
a oh right inside well when we were
going through the main entrance the
Bracken was there and then we went
through the fire exit just now and then
there was a thumb
FM no way and the braen yeah you
wouldn't believe watch check this [\h__\h]
out I you wouldn't
believe holy [\h__\h] is a lock
right oh he was just um he just
chilling
on come here
[\h__\h] oh you
wouldn't we're going to lose day
one are you stuck no I got aying glass
do something kill it you going to burn
him with the sun Le the way
pom I stayed back I think
he's he's
not great good job good job wait do we
all live I think he found us yeah we
live we're all
good go back yeah
yeah
oh you're joking
me
a what the
[\h__\h] what why am I alone why am I alone
why am I why am I alone why they did not
tell me what to do why am I alone why am
I alone did I
die I'm
alone well I can't lose this alone
what's
happening
wa oh it's scared of
[Laughter]
me what was that
what like oh [\h__\h] not her oh no
terrifying
woman a oh I wonder since there's voice
chat in the game do the monsters like
react get out okay what
the my hurt my shin
ow wait what are you doing here a moment
ago you weren't
here I I came in because the guy came
after me what are you
doing what are you
doing oh don't don't oh God the back oh
god um I guess he can't come here I
think we're in trouble wait I was in in
this room like for 2 minutes and I
didn't see you where have you
been oh I was outside I just came inside
oh okay
I think I think we're in trouble kiaha I
think um I think we're in trouble kiaha
I think we're in trouble kiaha she say
was a cute
voice somebody died so I don't I don't
know who why are they such
amateurs so true okay I'm going to check
outside maybe we'll be fine it's still
there
yeah how dare she leave me alone she
just going to going to
[Laughter]
die okay hello sh sh don't make noise
don't make noise Crouch walk Crouch walk
okay okay yeah yeah hi I'll try his
best
hi let's go
okay
okay we're crouching shut down we're
walking shut up oh
sorry oh my God you told me to shut
up [\h__\h] if I die because of
you nice follow me okay
okay I see the ship
Fu what the [\h__\h] I
just why are we screaming why are we
screaming wait there's light there's
light
oh a the pad shape we'll leave at minut
then hi hi hi I made
it I made it is that a dog what wait sh
sh sh is there a dog no dog I'm I'm a
human yes there's a dog yes there's a
dog I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm
sorry
what was there actually a dog I think so
I saw something running oh it was a worm
there was a worm oh I couldn't tell that
sound was a dog like she like I'm fed
she I'm
like no my wife is dead who will go to
the m mes with me the most paranoid the
most yeah I mean yeah I am the most
paranoid still going to the males with
you
a how did you come back
to it's worth 50 no one no one got
anything else no we couldn't cuz the
Bracken tried to kill me the second we
walked in is this the only thing we've
got you got to do is yeah I grabbed that
I haven't played this game since we last
played
it oh yeah it's been a while thank you
for 20
memberships thank you for
[Laughter]
20 nice wow nice so was that that was
pretty bad wasn't it we didn't really I
didn't see anything pretty bad situation
yeah that was a pretty
bad pretty good I mean yeah we did good
you got we just got unlucky is our quota
out of
130 nice yeah yeah yeah yeah pretty good
huh oh oh let's go okay let's
go who wo
wo this the same map three times in a
row so you won't get lost okay remember
it yeah yeah there's a beehive beehive
careful
beehive run run can I take
[Music]
this what the [\h__\h] those are actually
worth a lot of money so if we can get
them it's really good but you got to be
tricky about it and basically uh close
they're both close though I think we'll
be good yeah we could try to get them at
the end and then just have everyone else
on the ship okay so let's go okay get
them at the end get them at the
end
yeah we're on
March cute no it's December uh no the
Moon is called March
wow sometimes they
are what was that sound is there one
way is there a oh I forgot to tell you
so when you right click you scan and
that's how you can like find items and
stuff okay nothing down here always be
okay okay ABS always be scanning always
be scanning okay like this okay okay
chat am I doing there's nothing
here oh I got a
ke oh you keep
gun oh careful for
turrets I thought oh there's a
turret I think I heard a chunky
wony what word chunky wonky has come to
assassinate my sock
puppets BL you um why am I alone and why
is it dark don't leave me alone y who's
who's squeaking oh
nice oh my God you scared me so bad what
there really nothing down there I scared
you yeah I turned around and you're
standing on the stairs I'm just there I
don't want to be
alone so dark
we okay there's nothing downstairs
anymore
okay people I think we got to find oh I
can't see where the jump is should I
just should I do it no no no no no no
it's you can walk around
literally you don't have to moonwalk
your way way
over why is we so gone again is she dead
again no I think she was I think she had
something oh oh hey my OBS died where
she F what I don't know just for a
moment though oh you don't think she you
don't think she died to the bees right
there's no way that she died
again I will kicked her out of the
collab I'll take these take these to the
ship I'll go back with
you you okay yeah the graphic scared me
and they're so
bad the bees the bees no those are
little flies the bees are like in a
circle they're like oh if you scan it'll
come up with their little name it's like
the something name I don't remember I
hear them Don't Go Near them how do I
take them hear the
be
run run
runit what are we doing oh I'm like
dead I'm I'm kind of dead but I think I
got scratched instead nura is fine but I
don't know where she is she's
whing where are you guys am I I'm in the
ship oh no I'm good oh hi oh wait that
was my
stamina that's what's just my stamina
who this p rain
why
does up what up hi because they'll
follow they'll follow us into the ship
that's why okay do you want me to we
have to go at the end though oh I was
looking for an an entrance in a fire
exit trying to find find
one don't be such a loner stay with
us I'm
sorry so cute is
[Laughter]
this where I don't wait isn't this the
way we just came from or I see a a
door oh over here is this where we came
in before any any chickens emergency
want to be eaten by me oh it's here it's
here oh there's bees oh oh oh wait
me oh want the
window oh we can just go inside oh
really but very slowly
slowly what the we just go very fast
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go hi
yay oh where are you guys I hear you we
went in through the
emergency oh oh where is it it's on the
floor it's like a
little my game just lagged is there a
mob it's a little what
sorry the second I was saying something
my game lagged and I'm like oh is that a
mob
SP it's like a little down the hill I
don't know what else to call
it okay I I'll go look for
it
we
where do I
go
where oh
[\h__\h] I'm
[Music]
scared why don't they come to rescue me
isn't the other
side it's a cockroach oh
item wait I want to bring this
there wait how do
I go
down
you think it's better to go
down what
oh
no
we you left me you left me uh but it
looks like
something's I even found a
teapot I know I was watching you I felt
so bad um
oh she got
bracked y I saw a cockroach and then I
think what killed me was a was a
different mob though I
think was it really dark no uh not
somewhat oh God why is Rissa just
hanging out and chilling
here she's scared she's not moving so
I'm inclined to think that she is dead a
Bracken okay was a Bracken pom's still
moving I think P might be coming
back p p she made
it P get in here she made it I think I
saw a dog oh yeah be quiet that wasn't a
okay um I think the other two are dead I
think it's just us no way can you see
that in there yeah so your assumption is
correct um I also a little creature by
yeah yeah um well those I think are the
beads so what I'm going to do is I need
you when I say so to hit the start ship
I'm going to grab the bees okay and then
I'm going to bring them back Nissa
you're so
brave
ready yep hit the button I'm ready
[Music]
ma'am go get the
be get the be hit the button she died so
fast
therea oh
oh hit the button get the Beehive and
run not the
Discord hit the
button oh was that the right order just
the Beehive yeah yeah yeah okay get the
Beehive go go
[Music]
go okay I think I did
it oh hell oh
yeah where'd she go nice the lazy if we
were
laziest
most hey but we got more stuff this
time the is in love with me or something
m is 60% oh
[\h__\h] where's the Beehive I I brought it
in I brought it in oh they knew that we
did it for Discord so they don't count
it oh my
god oh we were reported or the St the
the the game developers are watching the
stream right now and they're like all
these [\h__\h] well we have di for no
reason of
stuff he scared
me no
you know you know one good thing about
living alone I just realized is that
nobody can like turn off the lights in
the room I'm in randomly by
accident oh my God that is so
annoying do people do that to you that's
so mean I mean when I when I used to
live in my family I mean it just happens
doesn't it like when you in the toilet
Idol meeting and then
somebody what what I mean not on purpose
just by accident
this is a k only exclusive experience
maybe it's maybe Americans have the
light switches on the other side of the
room on the inside yeah yeah it's
usually on the inside on the inside your
bathroom light switch is on the inside
in the
bathroom yeah yeah yeah oh wait is this
a cultural
thing probably maybe I think so oh
interesting I have some light switches
uh uh for example my guest room has a
light switch on the inside but my
bathroom has a light switch on the
outside I see him
why interesting now I know what to do
when you're on the toilet I see no wait
now reisa knows now rea's going to turn
the light off when I'm with there you're
right no you have the
opportunity you will not dare
make oh what is that there's a monster
there's a monster or an animal he kissed
me what is that he kissed you I'm not
sure I'm scared animal it's
zooming did you see it where oh the bird
look at the bird W that's a huge [\h__\h]
bird why is it on the
ground he's walking around yeah just a
bird what that's not how birds move what
the
[\h__\h] why are they on the ground
too where's the oh I see a beehive but I
don't think we'll be able to get this
Birds [\h__\h] Birds oh my god
lital oh what the [\h__\h] is with these
bird I need to make up for my failure
run leave me go to the building you go
at the very
end I need to get it closer failed
construction it is okay why don't they
fly anymore why are they only what the
[\h__\h] what
they I oh I found the
entrance entrance is
[Music]
here we're on bow again so it's be the
same the first
time oh my God oh my God who are you oh
you scared me why are you scared you
scared
me I'm just a
girl I'm just a
girl let's follow p
you following me
okay
w
wow dead end
w w w you were so cute you were so cute
in the nin Sanji festival
thing no thank
you very I'm
embarrassed no um actually yeah actually
it was wasu wasn't it yeah it was pretty
Nong oh my God and very
UT
no just uh you know where is everything
M the light is on down there should we
go
down you could try no you could
try oh I found an egg beater what let's
go Waba cooking stream is
happening it's happening oh my gosh I
want to try your cookie so bad what the
[\h__\h] are you talking
about you have a problem you have a
problem yeah yeah are you guys flaring
without me yeah totally we're talking
[\h__\h] about you what the [\h__\h] where where
where why is there what's wrong where is
she where is she um I can't see anything
it's too dark it's too dark
what's that oh oh there's a key key I
want to take I want to take I want to
take can I
take no hopefully we don't
die wait what's that
sound them
walking it's probably Nissa should we go
out I don't know what that sound is
should we
leave oh I think we should go yeah we
should go
as long as I have how do you have a good
such a good directional
sense uh I think it's
because there was nowhere else to
go Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy
Mommy it's okay it's okay where Pomo
wait pom I can't see I can't see other
way come on wait I can see where are you
I'm like stuck in on the wall [\h__\h] oh I
see you I see you come here come come
here okay this way I love you I love
you
pum
internet
[\h__\h] what
what where am
I what's
the oh that's
nice that's not
nice turn turn the lights on rubber
ducky collect oh somebody else is
bringing it what the [\h__\h] is
this
go
away go away go
away
did did you not like me switching things
around why will no one come pick me
up pom's stream got turned oh did she
actually cuz it seemed like she had lag
going
on I can't click this button I think I
disconnected cuz I lost internet you can
keep playing until I'll I'll join at
when next game okay okay we were ki's
going to die
so shook of
me well I mean if I'm going to die I
might as well you know die with
bravery
what
um so cuz he's not going to move
right oh he's like making yummy
noises
uh don't leave without
me okay that just kill me then
okay what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
this thought I could see
[Laughter]
[Music]
him is it good if I just don't look at
him I mean I can't make it past
[Music]
him wait what if a
jump let's
go door should I go up or
down wait it's surely there sh I should
up up or
down oh my God I was I was desperate I
was desper
but you your best I thought maybe
there's a path there but there
wasn't was a nice ending though my go
that was so silly was that a scream or
was that a mob uh maybe no idea maybe
Scream
Wait
yay yay someone want to reinvite P yeah
please bring P yeah can you can you
reinvite in in this game chat or does it
have to remake yeah when you when you
hit um I think we might need to drop off
the items real
quick days to meet the um I think I have
to remake the lobby because you can't
invite people that's okay yeah yeah but
I I think what I'm saying is I think we
can drop off the items get the money and
then try to revite okay let's let's try
that real quick genius I don't know how
to go to the someone please reinvite me
whenever you have the chance yeah thank
you
um and we're
sa we're going to reinvite
you thank you I miss
you I think go to the company we just
press e here right no use a terminal to
rout to the
company on our way let's go yay I have
no idea aren't you proud of me that I
actually did kind of escape the Bracken
first yeah good I was watching you thank
you somebody's watching me and not
helping
me okay I can't help you I don't we have
should have come back you should have
come back oh you were dead okay
right CU
yeah what's you what is you doing with
it okay just drop everything off here oh
okay can we be killed during this
process no no of course not of course
not
she sayle so confidently yeah I don't
believe after we drop all these items
off uh can you come hit the Bell until
the guy shows up we don't have
toell hit the Bell you might as well
yeah just hit the Bell the guy will show
up you can just sit there and just
there's oh we got
it yay oh
okay I feel like I heard some noises
from Monsters out there
so we work for
Monsters okay so now let's start the
ship and see if we can reinvite Pomo
otherwise we'll remake the lobby okay
okay oh wait ringing the bell would that
do something like
no I would never I would never K be
careful or I'll turn off the lights when
you're
pooping
mhm
not yes yes that's exactly when I'll do
it
reached
really what no way I thought that was we
no I can reinvite
now will I let you no okay uh would you
mind making a new room at WEA okay I'll
do I just yeah wait killed
PCO hello thank you for the raid
wow a okay I wait
for that was quite
funny my first my first my first
experiences with this game that's quite
funny let's go another round I hope pomu
won't won't like you know lose
connection again Pomo Pomo hello she's
alive
M yo we were together and suddenly you
were gone and I was like what the
[\h__\h] yeah um my internet decided to just
I know it I know it yeah yeah so but now
you're back can can you tell us to not
do that again
please yeah I think it maybe got really
flustered it was like so nervous around
you like I mean we were just by our
so no if you're so if your connection is
so unstable then I think I'll I'd rather
stay with one of the other girls for
next
time holy sh I can't rely on you I can't
rely holy [\h__\h] God damn call an
ambulance but not for me not for me
people we
we D her just got thrown away she looks
so serious on the computer I love you
pomu like she's actually doing hold on I
can't
hear what is she doing what is WEA doing
on the
terminal wait what did you say my my
headphones came
[Laughter]
out only stream will
no over for me guys
doing how do we start the game Oh I
thought you you knew what you were doing
you looked like you knew what you were
doing I picked the moon and I ordered
some stuff but the no just hold
e hold e on this like the thing on the
here if you hold e then it'll be
like wait no it's not giving the prompt
though yeah I didn't get the prompt for
start game oh it's because I'm the host
though okay yeah
youc okay sorry
Oh yay is this new map oh I almost
jumped yeah it's a new map
pumpkins yum yum I like the pump okay I
stay with you WIA don't die okay I order
flashlight so I'm going to watch for
themer why is it why is it echoing we're
not in a
room this Moon
acoustics
he what are you looking for what are you
doing I'm looking to the sky for the
items I ordered ah they come from from
the sky yeah there it is what the [\h__\h] I
thought it was a
dragon okay grab a
[Music]
flashlight that's all you ordered oh
wait another one oh my god let's go okay
I think they already left right so I'm
going to go put this extra flashlight in
the ship okay
okay and a Happy New
Year we wish you Merry Christmas we wish
you I oh I have battery oh [\h__\h]
okay y I thought we were suddenly
getting attacked by a
dragon Piana hi okay let's go okay
okay so are you having fun with lethal
company yeah it's quite quite a lot yeah
I mean yeah I feel like I I barely see
what's inside uh but maybe that's really
just all there is
inside yeah there's not like it's not
crazy you
know okay we got to go deeper deeper
deeper and I got to get in I want to
actually manage to bring an item back to
the ship that that would be cool we'll
get you there cool I don't think oh look
here they've left this giant item out so
why don't you take that and bring it
back to the ship that I don't know if
that really counts as such an
accomplishment no so whenever you find
you'll get big items that when you hold
them will say hand full and whenever you
get them just drop them out at the
entrance so oh she's gone I'll I'll but
what are you going to follow me yeah
yeah yeah I'll stay with
you oh hi hi wait do you have another
big item M away for me oh wow here wants
to bring something back to the ship so
that actually makes sense that you're
coming with me now cuz you also have
something yeah okay oh you lead the way
I think it was that
way this way oh down
okay mhm WEA have you packed yet
no no I'm waiting for my thing to get
here cuz she said WEA said that she like
usually packs so early I packed the day
before or the night before I pack a
month early well it's because it's my
first time in a really long time
traveling uh from hell you
know but I don't know a month in advance
is kind of
crazy it's cuz I get anxious no it's not
because you get excited and want to you
know get ready for what if I miss
something okay here we
go I just drop it on the floor yep just
drop it right on the
floor okay and
then okay let's see how the others are
doing before we go in they better not be
dead they're moving W yeah they're
moving but it looks like that red thing
they're being chased by something yeah
oh they're aware I think they're
aware yeah I think they're scared
interesting should should we
go um yes okay have you been using a
flashlight oh there's like oh no never
mind I thought there's more I was going
to say yeah you can charge your
flashlight here oh so whenever the
battery runs out
slow oh it's the same effect as with the
bees scary
don't worry oh my God they're staring it
down oh oh trying to run
oh oh okay ladies ladies should we
should we not be oh I think they're out
okay right should we go to the
left um oh P went back
in there maybe there's an item that she
really wants to
get yeah oh oh no oh oh they left right
when they was charging at them look at
them
go let's go sweet they're so smart you
think the day is much
longer um I don't know what time it
is where do we see it's 30:3 so we
basically want to be back by 5 oh we
should go maybe we've wasted you chicken
we should
go I am a chicken let's go h no they're
still oh no look oh there's a
monster disappeared now into the
darkness but uh uh-huh are you sure is
it under your bed H
Nissa come on chicken come on chicken
how oh there are two dogs on them
they're staring down a dog you chicken
you chicken okay go get that go bring
them back yeah if you
though no one of us has to
live good luck oh I'm probably running
in the wrong direction or wait is it
this way is it this
way
[Music]
pom
that that didn't last very long help oh
come back I heard a dog drop your
flashlight
okay are they dead Al is still moving I
think she's on her way back but I think
pomu disconnected again oh no no
panian not again p no oh I feel
bad me too restart game for Pomeranian
yep yep we'll wait for a WEA to get back
and then we'll remake the room stupid
Hotel
internet did you
[Music]
DC oh
man do you know do you know that pomu
has a company in
Japan e no and they do they do um what's
it
called uh yeah really yeah
p pom noi it's called pomu
No pom noi
mhm yeah for real though every time I go
there I think of pomu cuz it literally
says pomu I would I would think of pomu
too
yeah pomu was going to die why the [\h__\h]
did I not think of that
P
we
we oh wait it was a sound sensitive
wasn't it yeah the dogs will hear us
how close I mean we're going to have to
restart so I guess it doesn't matter if
we die true so let's just start the ship
and leave her uh
wow sorry AA
P
we we no how can you just leave we
bye bye you think she can hear
me she actually did I'm missing
wow oh no no it calls Pomo lazy don't do
her dirty like that oh my God I was so
scared I'm lost um pom disconnected
again we need to disconnected right
beside me a m maybe she should be alone
maybe being next to somebody like does
something to her connection
yeah so should I remake again well she
didn't she didn't seem to I don't think
she's back cuz she didn't write anything
after I wait let me see
p was that it
[Music]
yes like are you okay you want to come
back I want to come back yeah I'm My
Stream so I'm going to play okay okay
okay less pressure on the inter web wait
someone said it auto saves when you go
into orbit so are you guys saying if we
pick a moon and then re start the room
it will let's give it a try save I just
don't know if they mean
like now
or yeah and now it's fine right because
it save it probably saves after it shows
the report of all the players right yeah
right I don't
know um it already saved it said it's
saved now it's safe to leave okay all
right we will make a new room please
save the progress thank you okay reming
[Music]
nice okay wow so we'll still have those
items so what home is with us in spirit
she's in my heart yeah she'll be there
she'll be their next
game there we
go play a game oh P raed me P raided me
she loves me the
most back did you here I'm back pmu
raided me so she loves me the
most wow the worst she can do is say
no can you hear
me
okay you're like I don't know where to
go I'm like it's okay follow
me
a hopefully you survive this time a
little bit
longer let's go let's go let's not waste
time we yeah let's go you guys see
there's some there's some flashlights on
the ground for you guys so please pick
them up thank you
[Music]
yeah
after you oh yes I will start the
[Music]
game oh my God yeah take it uh remember
to charge follow you Nissa okay are you
sure about
that uh we were did you grab yours I'm
grabbing I have thank you okay yep I'm
going to buy
some more stuff good morning did you
guys die to dogs or no they didn't I
didn't die oh wow Pro
Gamer wait is this the first map this is
yeah it's the first one is this tangle
wood you looks
yeah this one's easy to
remember I was singing flashlight guys
did you not notice wait H go up wait for
me guys I'm too stupid
clim oh there we go they're just
laughing about
me hello hello hello hello hello hello
hello hello hello oh hi
[Music]
hello happy New Year it's no sour sugar
Mommy
okay what are we getting pick up this
walkie talkie
walk how many are there um only two so
if we travel in PS okay I got one um I'm
dropping the other one right here okay
so I said I I I I won't go with pomu
anymore um
so where's the flashlight I
bought who wants the walkie you we the
walk oh okay someone take it how do I
use wait we should do we should do we
should do little um exchange wife
exchange I go with a we pomu goes with
Wisa okay okay okay oh my God Wife Swap
yeah Wife Swap oh my god do you guys
know in in Germany there's a a TV show
maybe maybe America has it too where
they swap wives it's it's called f toou
and so
stupid hello say so
stupid okay we go this way
okay let's go hello down we and wa
sitting on it wow oh no no the
backs in there the backs there's a
bracket on the map why why
[Music]
are oh Jesus there's a slime at the
entrance slim oh you guys are here oh no
slime it's coming towards us slowly
slowly is this my wife no the Slime is
no joke but it's so slow what are you
gonna we can walk around
[Laughter]
it SL is in love with me oh there's and
then there's
H oh it's God this isn't the fun kind
you guys face up like that but so far
it's not doing [\h__\h] I'm not impressed
yeah
okay
bye no wait where's
we I'm here she already went oh
okay I check that room there's nothing
in
there
here we so what do you like to do in
your free
[Laughter]
time I like
to I like look up random facts about you
on the
internet what
there sounds key there
sounds what the
[\h__\h] smoke
Smokey what the [\h__\h] the flashlight is
not
helping that's because there's a steam
Le yeah I can't find the valve you got
to find the valve oh my gosh my
eyes
that's dang
oh oh it's
you
I think I'm alone scared me no we
here of my voice we're in the G guys my
flashl the
fck
P I did
it yay Yi Y where hello hello oh
hello hi okay we're all here together y
we're all in here
together a steering
wheel oh yes take it I can finally have
Direction in my
[Laughter]
[Music]
life no one would [\h__\h] noce no one
[\h__\h] know
this and maybe they think I died cuz of
a monster or so but no nowhere I just
fell I just walked casually no
too
G oh I walk in here and I
die I just so casually walked in
there why can't I pull the
valve what's Bulma doing oh she's
outside no no it's not outside we are
you there
over yes I'm here over over there so
many little guys everywhere you know p
would be way better at this game if she
had a box I hear with hello she just
needs a box
hello I can't find a single
thing how about finding my body oh can
you recover people's bodies cuz I feel
like I saw die to my death here over
something like that why would you be
dying
over I'm going to jump to the other side
over you are a crazy SC over insane just
going to die just like
me no F [\h__\h] [\h__\h] F
fucku know don't do it pom don't do it P
what was it oh she didn't die a little
sound like a
little iy see p doesn't P doesn't stream
right now but you guys can see her see
anything POV from my POV oh wa oh but I
can see you my body is hard to get yeah
like wait how would you get my
body
I know why are we together here I'm
going to jump here I'm going try and get
to the other side because there's no
other way to the other side go outside
walk around no no pom you're stupid no
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] wow okay I'm impressed I'm
impressed and now she's going to die
alone on that side wait there's an exit
I found the fire exit nice oh I'm going
to jump over too
that's pretty sick and a fish oh we
outside going back and
died I think the ship's this way I can
listen to what she's saying on Stam that
way yep oh she got something the [\h__\h] a
fish
y'all oh what pom don't overdo it don't
did you find
anything yeah I found some stuff it's 6
let let's
[Music]
go leave now or you will regret it God I
hate going down here cuz it's
so if you got motion sickness Look Away
guys look
away that's you it's dark outside we got
to be
careful
[Music]
fine this tangle wood can't wait to tell
them how I
died oh I I do think they noticed yeah
they definitely noticed pretty soon
actually I don't know if you can hear me
still po but I believe there's a worm
there's a worm hello oh a worm who said
that oh we w uhoh a worm
uhoh yes hello okay let's go just the
narrator Kiara where's Kiara what she
didn't
dead I've been dead for
ages my body has already decomposed get
out of
here where's W cuz the dogs are coming
out the do back you get back
inut okay
good might be really funny if you didn't
here I
am I'm the only one who died I'm fine
with that o lazy
oce see sustain the most injuries um my
the Slime was in love with me hello what
happened girly what happened you all
noticed I don't know about the others
but pom you just said it in the ship why
did you notice so late what the hell
that I was dead took you a while
um it's a pretty big place okay you know
basically I was just walking like so
close to you girls and I was walking
normally casually and suddenly I walk
over a ledge and just fall and die it
just me or it really laggy you
what what what it was lagging sometimes
because the game is like a indie game
like the microphone gets really like
pixelated and when you were explaining
it just got really but did you
understand I B they just walked off and
fell and died really not not an exciting
death it was funny
though that happens yeah that's like the
lethal company experience not going lie
it really is now did I lose the the
flashlight yeah oh
[\h__\h] I'm sorry it's okay I'm sorry bu
one it's okay did you order something
again yeah for me me this
[Music]
timey I'm going in yeah you and po leave
leave a walkie-talkie for kiaha okay oh
yeah here you go thank you I take okay
I'll pick it
up what did you
order I ordered a pro flashlight the
strong
flashlight okay I follow Lisa I follow
Lisa yeah we party
hardy party
hardy I'm staring at someone's
butt
my guys relax my butt is quite
famous my
oh my butt is on the Hollywood sidewalk
whatever it's called walk of f it should
be
mhm oh hi guys
hello WEA you're in charge of the
light of course where are you I'm not
the start I picked two things up so I'm
going to put them outside K yeah I'm
behind oh where wait where are you wait
here okay I'm back welcome back which
way you want to go I was going this way
oh oh we can go this way go this way
anything here if you're happy and you
know it clap your butt cheeks if you're
happy and you know it clap your butt
chicks if you're happy and you know it
then you really want to show it if
you're happy and you know it clap your
butt cheeks yeah clench them really fast
oh my
[Music]
[Applause]
goding
shut the door on
me Rel
okay
well
pom she was just there
pom it took a while that was
freaky don't scar us for
real I don't
know if you're scared then cleans your
butt butt cheek
I think we could go through the fire
exit yeah let's go get the fire exit you
just ignore the fish okay is it on
purpose pick it up okay okay okay I took
it I think we clapped our butt cheeks a
little too loud I think so SP spider the
spider was jealous because the spider
has no butd cheeks it's like
w don't cheeks it just has one hole one
big wait wait wait tell me more about
that one
hole what do you mean the SP
but that a boom box bring that back to
the ship oh no
it's wait why did she pick up a giant uh
engine thing oh good I thought it
was wait what I haven't played since
where the
[\h__\h] oh the spider's up here
the door MK wait is the mask a mod or is
it actually a part of the game what I
think it's a part of the gate because I
think someone used it
yesterday rainbow put on a mask actually
oh God yeah that's scary okay I'm
leaving what such a
chicken I am a
chicken I'm literally kfp what do you
mean okay you have an
excuse good
excuse weisa did you pack your undies
don't forget your undies no I haven't
packed yet I I what if I did forget them
kiata then I guess if you can have mine
I you your ass would probably not fill
him out but but excuse me I'm also quite
gifted in the ass Department what do you
mean well I don't know if your has your
ass ever ripped apart jeans like
subconsciously I ripped apart not jeans
but I also don't wear jeans what have
you ripped apart then lady um leggings
well leggings are like leggings are
weaker material than jeans uh fabric I
don't wear
jeans you talking about jeggings no
we're talking about ripping uh
undergarments with your butt and and I
said I ripped jeans before and she has
only ripped Lin before so I would say my
butt is stronger but I'm saying I don't
wear jeans yeah but like how
about it
me I have Fe wait how pointy you're like
a polygone like Tomb Raider how pointy
is your butt that you have excuse me no
no no no no no no it ripped it like you
have to imagine like when when someone
really strong like a bodybuilder flexes
their muscles and then their their shirt
just like wow
you
know shirt you know so like that I did
that with my jeans I
guess well what hi have you ever ripped
a pants with your butt yeah no
noely story but I mean okay now I am now
I am proudly flexing as if it was my
butt but before I actually said it's the
moths and I still believe it's the moths
okay was my before you told everybody it
was moths but now you're you're taking
that story back well yeah I'm taking
credit now because my butt could do it
if my butt wanted to but it was the
mths yeah oh like the mths like chew
through it I think so how dare they
right yeah how could they do have been
me that's so rude should have been
you why does it look like we're
incriminating each
other you're the one who killed TI uh
what did they say
objection
objection who's getting eated off the
[Music]
ship wait we got so much Lo what happen
to you [\h__\h]
idiots [\h__\h] idiots those [\h__\h]
idiots now we're going to get
miners [\h__\h]
idiots those donkeys you [\h__\h] dony
you idiot
sandwiches you
donys did I drop the
walkie-talkie you everything you were
holding such a
donkey guys we
made yay
building oh my God I thought maybe if I
had jumped it would have like back the
ship
no mean I thought it would happen I
thought we would be saved I guess it was
that it was for
science
yeah all right let's go drop everything
off shall we okay okay do we have
enough we'll find out real
quick I think we have more than enough I
[Music]
think K did you learn about
this about the what what
K you have to after we drop off the last
yeah no all right click the button
anything else which button the Bell that
just went off just keep clicking it till
it shows up which one okay oh
um yo she's played this game so many
times what you wanted that to happen to
me
yeah cuz I love you you know you know
the males then there's sharks and stuff
you
know sharks don't really like to eat
humans though well I have a good
relationship with sharks so I will tell
them to do that why would you do that
they won't like me I'm not
tasty do we have enough I know
you
400 let's get pom back oh man why why
did that happen why for what what was
the
purpose I didn't think it would happen
so fast
pomu did pomu know did she know yeah she
knew it was going to happen I think she
didn't think it was going to P I didn't
think it was going to happen so
fast
$92 we got fin for your death what the
heck oh but where
is okay let's see so Pomo died
unnecessarily
twice yeah
great but it's okay cuz every time that
you disconnected it didn't count as a
dead so we didn't get charge so it's
just making up for it making up logic
okay yeah yeah logic checks out girl M
it's girl math for real if you died if
you died two times for free and then you
had to pay two times for death it's free
yeah it's just even out now okay okay
okay sure I won't die anymore on purpose
I didn't die on purpose before but you
know I won't really die on purpose okay
um where you taking us this time
mommy somewhere is fine somewhere
somewhere okay oh thank you for being
our Navigator thank you thank God yeah I
don't want to touch that keyboard
okay let's go
TI we can't we can't afford to go
to yeah we're
poor too poor to there's more wait
before you guys jump there's going to be
more flashlights coming for
you
you we wish you a Merry
Christmas I've never had a sugar mommy
before I'm so excited and yeah now don't
let the plane land on you or you will
die oh oh [\h__\h] oh don't worry pomu knows
all about that yeah I knew that
happen oh where is it where is it where
does it is it because we didn't put out
milk and
cookies maybe where is
it
okay a oh thank you yeah oh strong Flash
oh big flashlight all right don't lose
them this
time Whoever has the other Walky if you
want to leave it in the in the thing
since we don't have one so that way if
you die you don't use a walkie-talkie
okay wait I'll come with you so
smart so
[Music]
smart okay let's go let's go Happ being
the bread winner I'm happy to find loot
and provide for this family yes I will
continue to just buy stuff I didn't
think you guys could hear that from that
[Music]
distance
smoke be here hello what does the smoke
do what is this it's the it's the the
smoke it's the stuff with okay watch out
because you can fall and die here how do
you find the valve oh
hello hello hi oh there's a of stuff in
here I found a big
loot
yeah a key I can't
see
uhoh there's a loot Bo there's a loot Bo
you
guys the vent is open the vent is
open Oh
no I got the
key where the hell is it what the [\h__\h]
why are we in a
sauna we need to we need to find the
valve okay I'll find it again I'm the
wall finder the ball
finder
oh my God I can't see
[Music]
anything you found it no I found it I'm
going to leave I am literally the
[Applause]
[Music]
Wilder I'm getting out of here what it
doesn't
kill uh it killing her yeah
H
oh um I think I'm in trouble ouch oh
God Liv oh my God you both lived yay
where
where's I seen the ship um I hear her
walking around out here talking yeah oh
okay but I don't know where she is
oh I think I see her in the ship maybe
maybe maybe she went through the fire
exit
yeah okay should we go by
exit wait what what this way what where
is this way I don't see
you follow the voices follow the voices
I
hear good tidings we
bring you are
youring hello she is the bread winner is
there more steam or am I going crazy no
I don't think
so
okay what is this place oh there's
nothing else
here well I guess we should go back to
the ship and leave then she's such a
chicken oh wait this way just
kidding oh this thing is this guy is
also harmless where is
[Applause]
he uh
um hi what's harmless oh my God WIA
there's a monster there and I'm going to
die
there's a monster where behind
me not anymore no there's
not um
okay I think what the we need to get out
of here okay run uh okay exit exit exit
exit did you just exit the radiation
where's the exit I don't know he here
follow me I don't think it's here follow
the sound of my voice oh let's go
okay let's
go we got this let's get out of here y
oh
extion let's
go so good that you were
there yeah thank
you
nice when my wife wife saves the
day we you know we we are we are all
connected with our wiess so you don't
have to call her your wife's wife she
can also be your wife there was a sign
hello if you have don't go back in's
wife oh I did I almost died
oh wait how do well I have to walk
around I didn't no you can jump down oh
okay woo
nice all four surviving and bringing
back loot incredible no way yeah the
circle of life lights really saved the
game I didn't bring anything but I was
here for support oh yeah I brought a key
but I I didn't use it again like I never
used the key you can save it we can we
can use it mhm okay yeah we can save it
for next time yay we have so much
stuff
y adop the ID wife sharing system yes we
have a wife sharing system yes yes sh a
wife all right shall we depart you
indeed access file
secret secr from Fire
Emblem what's this posted
girls it what's this posted what you can
grab it I think you can type it into the
oh yeah the computer it just tells you
stuff I think it's post it M oh oh
oh no nothing said
about oh my God
intern I'm the CEO I'm not the intern
what the
[Laughter]
hell okay um you know someone has
everybody starts somewhere kiar okay
yeah but is this
real is it
what what's real what's wrong someone in
my chat said type boobies on the
computer
what did you do it what happened I don't
think you need to type in on the
computer they're on the screen aren't
they nothing
happened they're they're
trolling what what no no no no it's a
it's
80085 oh yeah lead code it's a code
gamer talk code
boobs oh I don't know about that one oh
is it not boobes so should there be be
eight
O8 uh one three five for
boobies oh three nothing
happened yeah
135 type
135 something happened but when I typed
boobies it asked if I wanted to buy the
boom
box oh
wait maybe how kind of no I didn't it
said do you want to spend I just that is
what I call customer
service
store
box on the menu it'll just automatically
or we could save up for the jetpack no
or we could save up to go to
Titan Titan okay let's go save up the
Titan Titan okay so we need need uh
about I think it was about 400 to pass
wow so currently our stuff is worth
about uh uh
157 so we still need to get quite a bit
of stuff so we got it yeah we got it we
got this how little when we didn't even
die land the
ship do you guys want to try going to
March sure again okay can you wear this
not eclipse
or I'm not I'm not I'm not going to
chance
it
okay I'm going to switch five we're
going to wipe for this no just for this
run
oh just for this one I'm going to switch
w sing W I
choose wait wait wait eeny meenie huh
eeny meeny miny mo catch the tiger by
his toe een Meen anymore I don't know
how it continues go here we are
okay didn't even consider me no because
I I was with you last last
run
[Music]
yeah okay I think we're witnessing a
lover's
quarrel no no no
no the birds the birds and the beans and
the
bees wait is that why there's birds and
bees oh you Mak a good point
P spicy Leal company
spicy spicy
[Music]
spicy hey we need go this way let's go
this way okay I you're right you're my
wife for this one okay let's go I hope
will not be a burden to you never I have
a key by the way oh awesome let's find a
lock door God I hate the
smoke smoke where is
smoke no I don't know I oh I can hear a
land mine though watch out yeah I think
I saw it that thing oh yeah wouldn't it
be funny if um you
know don't let the intrusive thoughts
win
would be kind of funny it would be funny
if I stumbled into it accidentally oh
another
key what's that over there wait what oh
there's a turret that's a turret that's
a turret that's a turret oh portal
portal oh what the [\h__\h] there's so many
land mins and turrets and stuff oh my
god there are there's so
many oh I don't think the landmines will
kill us I think it will be that friend
um um this place is kind of dangerous
there's so many
Landes well as long as we don't step on
them
oh oh go back the way we came y i got
this worry I'll protect
you
um maybe oh does it react to us
talking um I honestly I I don't know
what it reacts
to guys what does the braen react to
chat that's company players I think
that's a door lethal company players in
the chat Oh wrong
door it was a
door exit
Doo exit
Doo Oh interesting
room oh there bottles here
hello I heard someone wait is there
another I heard someone hello hello
there
a yeah there's
a nothing
if I can hear a land mine
though oh what the
[\h__\h] that sound is a land mine
oh
there's so much happening I'm
scared why is this game so scary oh wait
there's something there oh there's a
door here we can leave ah oh you got
pick it
up oh exit oh my god let's
go yay I found the most important item
in the
game where are we I don't know how to
get back from here I feel like we're in
the back side of the whole
thing that's what my women's intuition
tells me all right Le just the
way e me okay yeah you got it okay maybe
I shouldn't be tooting the horn maybe
that will call the dog
[Music]
over no you scan to find your ship oh
how do I know where it is with the scan
you have to be in like a specific oh is
this water okay don't go in the water
[Music]
okay
I oh I hear
bees what about this path this is a nice
path
okay
oh oh what why are we so lost or maybe
what
[Music]
about okay you're still here sorry yeah
I have no stamina oh got to work out
girl uhoh that just means they took the
core but even outside radiation
ya I don't
know oh I think it's just inside the
building I don't think it's that way
where is the ship oh it's right here
right here
what right here just walked around
it how did I miss it you found the way
back oh oh my God you're so good at this
game yeah we only found landmines that's
all we found and this I found some stuff
pomu is on her way back too oh no
there's a monster guys guys guys guys
stop there might be
[Laughter]
[Music]
dogs okay
P I don't I'm not sure where she
is yeah but
sh people people oh no no pom no I to
save her where is that can we zoom out
it's like
no uh oh she went inside
dodged okay she's at the entrance anyone
want to attempt to meet her there save
her a wewa save your real wife okay
byebye drop wait drop your
flashlight oh well oh she's outside
again right that's outside yeah yeah
yeah and there's no
monster she very careful oh oh they
found they met oh love story Love Story
TI the ship is here the ship is
here
we we're
here she's a
gamer over there she was
already you [\h__\h] made it wait right
get they attack you they attack
you over here okay hurry and get on and
let's run
y I almost died to the Bracken too that
guy came up on me and I turned around at
the last second we kind of saw we saw
him so many times we are we are ladies
of competence holy moly yeah he was so
cute and like look at all that wow I
think we're pretty pretty close to our
quota I think we need 3.99 we're at like
368 so if we just get a few more items
count everything sometimes like the game
glitches a
little I think it's not that I think the
the buying place is different being part
based off of how much oh we're at 396 if
you stand over here it scans them all
better yeah is that how it works in the
game like the
company items at different rates every
time
I I'm not sure don't forget to charge
your flashlights ah thank you
yeah okay was that enough is one charge
enough oh yeah it is yeah top left just
one scanner only scans a set
Limit Oh you're trying to SC kind of
random it's percent based on what day
you go different rates based off of days
left oh I
see
oh
okay
okay oh it is different depending on
where you stand it really is
different oh oh let's go cool
let this is this the last
one yeah this is the last day so we just
need to not WIP so if everyone's dying
just whoever is left leave
I go with pomu
now okay me yes and that's probably
going to result in you
seeing I was going to say you're going
to jinx it by coming with
me W so fast I used all my
stamina okay the ship is underneath okay
yeah we just keep basically hugging this
way yeah you got to like yeah
never remember where the ship is on this
map yeah this one's more
tricky here we
are all righty my show
girl all
right let's go this way where's which
one is
this that's okay too
Pomerania there's a
remote what how do I grab oh I can't
grab the remote oh can you get it wait I
got it I got it oh nice nice she she's
gaming she's yeah I'm jumping and I'm
taking what's for what's mine what shall
be mine what's yours what's rightfully
yours H yes P I told I told the other
girls that you have a company in Japan
that what I told the other girls that
you have a company in Japan that's that
makes yeah it's a restaurant chain that
you know you know they make Pomo
rice what the [\h__\h] is going
on that was they're trying to exit
something's what was there just a guy
it's just a robot yeah he's just
loud oh that's the sound they want to
take the robot to the ship right away
apparently so I'll be back so you three
travel together may maybe he brings a
lot of
points maybe I don't know the remote is
good yeah the remote's good can I leave
it here turn off
turrets it can no way no I don't know
somebody said nice or remote that can
turn off a turret no way for
Real Palm will come with
me she so bright she a new Phoenix one
guy let's go oh there's some there's
spider over there there's a spider over
there oh it's
coming at least I thought it was coming
is
it oh they're staying
inside oh you're not scared of the of
the
speeda scared of what you're not scared
of the
spider not really oh there's a there's a
thing down here not really she says
wa that will bite her in the
ass got it
oh no remember the spider doesn't have
an ass I know but it will bite into your
ass cuz you do have
one oh you think out of jealousy
yeah basically you want to leave that
outside or carry uhoh uh-oh there oh or
I'll leave it as where are
you
a oh I think she's oh come back come
back up here I'll help
you I'll help you I'll show you how to
get back oh hell yeah okay so yeah go
where P just going so you always go
under this do we leave you're going to
get any scrap no I'm not finding
anything under this thing I'm just
mental
support and then go straight through
and then you hop right basically so you
go right and then you go right again
and by these basically anything that
pomu collects means I collected it
too why you laughing also I got the
remote control
so she did I mean I found it but she
grabbed it oh my God I went the other
[Music]
way this map confuses me so bad mhm I
know this one's
weird
yay okay we have so much
stuff our place is crowded we we
definitely make the quota so do we want
to keep looking for a little bit or do
we want to go what is it
scan 12 objects outside the ship
totaling an approximate value of
1265 1200
I want to go back
in be quiet be
quiet is there a
dog yo I was you were closing the door
right when I was about to leave again
dangerous oh did you just start yeah
there's a dog right
outside I could
take that's not a dog that is not a dog
I'll open it up so you can see it
okay damn it oh he's
gone really motivated I want to go back
inside gets eaten by dog yeah n I'd
win I'd win so loudly I was just like
shut shut up shut
up oh it's
over damn
it no okay it's okay we can go to the
next map no we got go to the company do
not after we sell everything do not unal
life yourself at the ping pong machine
again okay
yeah p
p okay let's see how much money did we
make a lot
Grand
take what we're going to Titan baby what
is it chat just because I did a little
ping pong doesn't
mean
anything what do you mean you
know like
pink
we what are you
doing going to say
F we can sell multiple times oh I sold
something I don't think I can't tell if
it's open oh it's open it's open it's
open open
what oh the ping pong is
selling oh
yeah oh so if you stand there when
you're selling it it will eat you oh
yeah
500 wait do we want to sell everything
or do we want to keep it yeah we want to
sell it all let's should sell everything
almost we need to go to Titan do we sell
Keys oh no keep the keys keep the keys
we play this game are sweaty and like
save things for later
quotas oh be careful be
careful stand back
hey hey get back here is not opening the
door okay we're maybe he has no more
money to
buy it did open it wasn't opening okay
now we wait Mr
Man got it vamos vamos
chica
vamos
okay how much money how much did we make
wa W how much money
muchos w
see who don't watch this
stream oh oh I'm inside okay well that
scared me should we go to Titan or the
other one first like we're lacking
someone we need to go into first pom
wait she you're outside come back in no
she's right here no I'm right
here oh oh oh okay I thought maybe I
thought you were just some hanging suit
like this one
oh I'm just I'm a mannequin yeah yeah I
don't know that was
weird you guys see her I don't see her
should we go to the house one or should
we go to Titan we're going to Titan I'm
sorry I already said it yeah I like
Titan the difficult map it's a difficult
map you're a professional
now we're going to die now because it's
foggy on Titan and we have haven't died
in a while it's kind of boring maybe I
should do a a a die for entertainment
it's the perfect
time for the sake of content whoa
lag lag
yeah BBY BBY hey wait I'm going to buy
some items before we leave okay
[Music]
okay wait for it to come down
yes there's
snow snow snow what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h] oh it's foggy is this Titan
it's foggy so it's here yeah why is it
why why is it why why why is it doing
this is it's fogy extra foggy holy
cow my my I think I have a
bug what's wrong do you see my
hand
what about it what about it your hand
doing that I don't
know drop it
[Laughter]
oh guys where is it oh it fixed it I
don't know it fixed it
uhoh is this way
oh found it hey hit it hit it I was
cheering it's like the it's like the
cheering animation we have in our app
where I can't find you guys where are
you
I'm okay I can't follow my Bo this is a
great start oh ni I have my light on I'm
yelling okay are they all here circles I
think oh I'm at the
sh where are the rest of the shovels on
the ground where wait did you not pick
one up no oh we can hit things with this
now oh let's go our weapons there wait
there was three on the ground and now
there I took one two of
them it's time to go but where the [\h__\h]
are we
going where are you wait no idea I think
I'm just going to go up I'm just going
wait I'm right behind
you are you near the ship he's at the
entrance yeah I'm at the entrance now I
couldn't find you guys by never finding
the
entrance right
here but I think oh behind you behind
you behind me behind me yeah here here
and then we go up here oh my God okay
where's P we're up here climbing yeah
they're
climbing Moon there's a about you a
shovel yeah
oh oh it's
not yeah yeah she's bringing it to you
oh okay oh my God my already 12
sh maybe we should just leave thank you
the quot we have to do it for the
company yeah we got to do it for the
company let's go in it go oh hey how
many hits does it take
guys
abs oh there's a bell and
nice uh that I have a a a teeth in a cup
biting fast in a cup yeah do you hear
the sound of it
biting there's also
a oh a picture I hear the sound hear
Town should we bring it back already
because I'm already full
inventory yeah me too and this is really
rare this is expensive all right not
rare but all
right
nice we're out
fast nice nice it's my holot talk show
cup hold talk talk show cup almost I
almost just died
why are they screaming thing on the wall
there was something on the wall what
who's talking where is
Pomo I'm downstairs
okay Visa was like panicking I heard her
Panic me too me too wonder what's going
on let's just go we'll go home oh yeah
let's just go whatever I mean doesn't
matter
yeah I think you know sometimes time
every man for themselves wait where are
you
uh the ship ah here oh hello hello hello
look look at my
hand those are Dentures I don't know
they're not
mine these are good ass
dentur Grandma
W and this okay value yay wow that was
worth 60 that's crazy yeah the T4
80 the painting is 64 oh the teeth for
the most worth let's go I know that's
crazy nice morning morning morning shall
we return again round two yes round two
baby
okay could have charged the flashlight
but oh
well it's fine I should I'm going to go
charge it real quick actually
okay I
forgot then I'll do it to really quickly
just for
security here we go these are your
footsteps right yeah keep an eye on the
time they say p oh doesn't it close at
five no it just gets dangerous around
five
a wait uh but Titan is dangerous all the
time a
yeah coming up didn't really seem
dangerous yeah I'll carry it thank
you oh yeah you can take that one oh
okay I'll drop the other one someone
should stay
behind no we should all leave it's
almost 5
wow but nothing call me a coward I only
I was inside for like 2 seconds found
five items and and then left I saw like
an an one square meter of the
inside I killed the bug and then I
killed
theg yeah it was really scary damn it I
didn't use the shovel at
all I that was my first time killing
anything in this game
damn how will I ever become the
ship
somewhere somewhere oh way isn't the sh
like right okay or is this
way what does that even mean this way
over here over here what does over here
mean found it yeah yeah yeah right
right not very we're safe oh okay okay
let's
go oh sorry okay I think we should
leave I heard screaming okay oh
screaming that scared
me
who screamed you I don't know maybe this
mask screamed uh we have
$466 worth of this you have the mask oh
my God yeah no don't let po no no no PO
put it
down down why what does it do it going
do it it'll turn you
into it'll kill you yo I saw that clip
when when Millie teleported you into the
ship with the mask on I I saw what
happened I know you are capable of doing
I've changed my
way yeah interesting I didn't do
[\h__\h] back to just but I'm like way more
productive in this game than in uh
what's it called cosmophobia this is fun
yeah don't fun the only part yeah this
is just like fast phobia um control wise
everything else is very
different yeah yeah yeah it's just fun
yeah
yeah this time this time I'll go inside
and do
something yeah didn't you pick stuff up
though I did but it was like immediately
after we entered I didn't see anything
from inside oh my D yeah do you like my
denters I do I love them I picked those
up I'm surprised are we going
yeah let's
go what was
that what was that sound
effect when you pulled the lever pull
the lever wow back beaches is this is
this not the
Titan no I thought we now that we bought
it we have it permanently so we can go
or I think AO will on this until we die
die
I thought you to pay for it every time
nope oh there he
goes who are you Lisa did you buy
something
again no sorry I I'm just I zoned out
for a second I was letting my cat out of
the room a
baby yeah baby are you going to miss C
when you go oh they're saying apparently
no we do pay for it every time oh but
last time
that's what you have it till you
leave Raa you know what you should
do what you should cut off some fur from
your
cat just a little bit take a Polaroid
and then tape the fur on the back of the
Polaroid and then take it with you in a
wallet you're so crazy that's what I did
sorry apparently I lied I'm sorry I
didn't realize that we had to stay in
the orbit of it so we can't go back
no it's okay
oopsie no we that was that was a real
natural
old
wait
yeah hey somebody hit me don't hit
me my flashlight Friendly
Fire why did it do that when I killed
it
that was so nasty so gross M [\h__\h] youu
is there something cool
here oh I don't want to fall down
anything
around yeah don't jump be
careful nothing I
hear you sure I am so not scared anymore
now that I have a shovel yeah
right the shovel has has freed
you it's going to take me like 20
seconds to scroll over to my shovel when
I see an
enemy you'll see a Bracken and then you
won't be so brave anymore well he's
different
he's he makes me nervous he's tall dark
and
handsome oh sorry
sorry what's happening over there come
here come
here what what is that
sound
nice nice the way I killed it was epic
murder a present for me I have a present
for you yeah open it oh my God wait I
brought you can I open it mer you can
open it
how oh wa how that how did you do that
that's what you always wanted romantic a
stop like
oh want to kill you this is the I guess
I'll try to bring this out if I find
yeah if I find the
exit you guys hear that
I think someone
died um I'm alone no it must be the wind
drop off yeah let's I don't know it's
not worth it if I'm alone I'm going to
die oh oh I saw
[Music]
someone let's go there oh somebody where
is everybody hi I'm
here I'm scared do you want to leave I
think there's a bad gu yeah I don't know
how to get home oh let's go we we came
from somewhere over there and I dropped
the wall B right cuz I uh didn't want to
go I think there was a monster close to
where I was before okay well from here I
don't know where we go I think this way
I don't know either may this way uh was
it this way okay maybe no there's no
door oh I can't
oh you have to kill it my hands are full
it's it's down there now where did they
go he's just
chilling he's on the other
side don't other side where they over
there but leave leave him leave him we
should oh I see him I see him I see him
I don't think we have to go I think we
go this he took something he took
something he can take
something yeah that's what they they're
obsessed with taking loot oh what is
this path is this the right path bug I
don't know oh I think you're right I
think you're right
all and then from
here uh from here I have no
idea
we didn't go that deep
in no I think I don't remember that
though oh oh I remember remember we
killed this guy right here
yeah did we go
up no it's right here oh you got that
yay oh they were probably worrying about
us I if they were so worried they would
have come and gotten us
they're probably about to leave us
behind I know right look at this look at
this K
oh w a laser are they actually there you
girls hi A's dead oh what no how did
that happen what did you
sure but there's a monster nearby
somewhere what you all get oh 400 ooh
there's lots of loot here I I only
brought a big valve and we we were like
almost
lost and couldn't find our way
back oh there's so much loot by where
lra
died no way I think it's the loot bugs I
think it's the the loot
Master leave the we'll have to buy
another flashlight for yeah we
survived we we'll miss you bye we'll
miss you
byebye
sayala
sayala oh nice
Sky wait AA took the
mask oh what no why would she do that
it's on the floor it's on the ground
okay good sustain the most
Chang
thrilled was it a loot bug no it was the
things that like hang on the
what how did you that drop down onto
your face and like Eat You Alive what I
was like yelling I was in the room
beside where you guys were and I was
like guys help me I I heard someone
scream yeah but that was me I didn't
hear anything I'm so
sorry oh oh man Kiara you left her to
die me I was I was alone already at that
point you left me
okay for
you wait why did it only give me one
item wait I'm going to buy you another
Pro flashlight yay
yay
[Music]
oh okay I guess I can only buy one at a
time just ate me
alive then if it ate you alive everyone
like yeah pomu she
heard I didn't he what what do you mean
have no idea she doesn't have a stream
open how can they
know I have no stream I have no
stream she 100%
hurt a we watch for the thing thank you
and everyone charge your flashlights
yeah thank you Mommy mmy she's so
[Music]
responsible you'll get it all for
yourself
tonight is this freestyle or are there
real lyrics
the tree no it's made it's freestyle oh
okay good good
freestyle
thanks oh
[Music]
somewhere find it a we I'm here they're
already there out they started Christmas
without us woohoo good okay you got both
of them yes thank
you let's
go oh my God wait I've never
seen goodbye I didn't know you could go
up there if this works then I'm sorry
it's for the content oh my god oh no it
didn't work it didn't take
me slid right off oh
man all alone I wanted to go where Santa
lives I thought it would bring me to the
North
Pole I thought so too I thought you
would go for sure yeah
um that been so
funny what wait here's pmo who this who
this El
where I think
she yeah I think she left us wow she so
Speedy she's responsible and plays the
game
correctly she's also chicken though
all righty Bring It On is
the all the
M what is it I hear
it you
are oh
it oh what the [\h__\h] thank you for saving
me I oh it took my items I I gave it one
hit but but you saved me yeah on the
ground
ground without you I think I would have
died
possibly wait why because it was already
on my
face you think you're going to like turn
into a
bug what oh
was what the [\h__\h] oh there's another one
no what thank you oh my God you're so ah
ah ah help me oh Pomo you saved me twice
what the [\h__\h] I said cure you this can't
keep
happening I'm scared fom they've got it
out for me what the [\h__\h] I think it's
like you have a sweet blood or something
you know like they think you're wait I'm
going to put this
outside oh maybe not here should I not
put it
here well there's two fire eggs
exits
oh the
gravy W
grav oh okay the gravy P stay close to
me stay close to me P wonder if they try
to eat me
again I know I got
you what a hero where the what a
freaking hero I
think I think I should be your body this
see this is why you should have stayed
with me from the beginning I see shiple
I see shiple or the main
entrance I oh I see the ship over here
oh
oh I'm
coming
P
Pama is it that thing that's oh it's
that thing
okay hopefully
not looks like she walking around okay
so pomu in case I die we have the
Beehive it's very close it's not in here
because the bees will get angry okay
right yeah after we put the shift to
take off someone needs to go grab it hi
okay it will not be volunteer yeah it
will not just drop it on the floor in
here no
will die get the bees will get stuck on
the cuz I'm almost dead too but yeah can
we not just take the Beehive of the
shovel um they'll electrocute you
because the the shovel is metal so they
will kill you instantly oh damn okay oh
oh don't don't drop it hold the Beehive
apparently hold it in the ship hold it
in the ship so yeah once you grab it uh
after the ship takes off immediately go
grab it and hold it don't drop it okay
okay okay I'll do it now just needs to
know it looks like she's coming back so
we can tell her
too oh she
we oh I was fighting for my life wait
there's something really big in front of
the door I have to grab still oh wait
okay should I come with oh you got it's
just one
thing you want to okay I stay
with hi I'm almost dead from beas
thingss oh you know what happened to me
me and Pomo are walking around and then
this thing that that sucks your face was
going to attack me and before it
attacked me I punched it once but it
still got to my face and I thought I was
going to die cuz it was it was already
sucking but then pomu pomu hits my head
with the shovel and kills the the bug
let's go but then literally 10 seconds
later the same thing happens
again yeah that'll happen
that will happen save me twice saved me
twice how many times did you save me
whistle I'll save you in the Mal divs
you won't drown I'll I'll save you but
aren't you you're not an efficient
swimmer
either yeah but I've got big bobies so
they'll make me float uhuh okay won't
sink we should we should got combine
your big bobies with my big booty I've
got a big butt too we'd be perfect oh
what did they do oh they went back
in they can't help it they just they
wanted to get the thing but they made it
outside wo now they just need to make it
in
here oh oh no there's something
there shh it's okay just be quiet just
in case you think it's
dog it might be a dog I'm not sure bow
bow how about [\h__\h] how how were the
dogs doing you played Lethal company
right with them yeah they did really
well did they let the dogs
out no no
good good
okay they're both there
oh come on come on are they even oh oh
it's right there
yay
yay you made they were new it looks like
a reskin of an older mob yeah
we
yay maybe it's like a all right I'm
going to get
it wait wait wait we have to take off
first we have to take off
first are you ready let's go
giant let's go wait no hold on I don't
know where it is where is it there's a
giant there's a giant there's a
giant
wait did you start it why yeah why why
why why wasn't me I
didn't let
go I'm not letting go I never let go
collateral
Dage what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] I was C in
between I but you recovered my body
so
by just you died in the ship it's so
squishy yeah right okay keep holding on
to it and let's go to the company e
maconi e how much is that
worth a
[Music]
lot still doesn't say how much it's
worth good oh beehive
19 19 that's it oh 90 90 no it's got to
be way more no it said
yeah oh is it okay if it's just in front
I thought it was worth at least 200 yeah
I thought so too is that okay
oh be high value 90 apparently they vary
from 6 to 7 to 100 plus that's only 90
for us even though we're this cute I
know right and it's kill EAS not worth
it not worth it oh Jesus not that
guy I think it's full I can't yeah uhoh
oh god oh watch out watch
out I terrifying he doesn't like the
teeth
professionals professionals
professionals
[Music]
baby we saw more remember when you heard
the screaming before it was from the
phone
oh
yeah oh this is a wait he's taking it
right now don't sell the
mask why not we got to we got to use it
no it's evil what do you mean I want to
see what
happens okay I'll bring it
back
no wait so we're not selling the M ah we
still we still have a one thing up here
though we do watch a YouTube
video come on Chad you literally watch
the clip you know you see yeah but like
I W us have experience it together I'll
be right back in 2 seconds okay okay
okay now put on the mask no no let's
surround no can surround her
no I'm scared will she kill us all
nothing
happening wait who's going to wear the
mask not
me is that sound oh God what is she
opening
we have to protect her P your mik's
[Music]
not what's what's happening I don't know
your mic wasn't muted so I needed to
protect whatever was going on oh I just
got my French
toast from
7even yes oh my God yes oh my God I know
exactly which one it's so good never had
it before
it's so good the one from 7eleven oh my
God Japanese 7eleven we got to make it
clear I heard I heard American 7eleven
is not
good I've never been hey we made so much
[Music]
money oh God our clot is going up higher
and higher okay so we have
$1,227 can we go to the mansion one what
one is the mansion Ren or
Dine um which one is okay wait there's
two of them but one of them the cheaper
one is the more worth it I think oh oh
um yeah what one
sucks oh what one dine dine is better
dine is but is that one the Mansion
yeah okay yo will this one be the last
one because remember when you girl said
off stream going to do 2 hours it's been
2 and a half yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah we can do three more days haven't
noticed yeah this we're going to have to
die anyway because if this is the last
one so um we could just go here explore
it and then do the mask yeah oh my God
I'm so
oh oh a little love
bite a little love tap let's go love tap
yeah charge your flashlights
everybody oh no it's raining uhoh is
there electric is there lightning oh God
I think it's okay pomu take the mask
it's all yours and leave your flashlight
and your shovel oh no okay she it but
then you're not going to be useful sh
ready ladies you're going to die
right let's go in first though right
yeah let's go in first okay let's go in
first okay okay you lead the way p
this way shitty
weather
where's we
we we we we we we
we
we we I'm coming don't worry okay okay I
bought something Wow Let's wait for it
yeah let's wait I'm excited I don't know
what it is is it the
jetpack is it the zap gun you
buy what I'll see you soon oh it's
already in the ship oh I don't have to
wait for it do you get the teleporter is
it the toil it's here it's the toilet
what the
wa nice wa off try going privacy please
some
privacy okay let's go where we
going sorry guys that was we're going to
kill pomu when she puts on the
mask okay look whatever we do like a
hide and seek we'll do like a I'll go
hide and you guys find me no what if the
co finds us first yeah I love the coil
head they're my number two Oshi after
the
Bracken
pretty he's pretty
cool got a good thing going where is the
entrance I'm in water this is water
don't go in don't go in [\h__\h] you water I
hate Water
[Music]
Rising hey where where's the building
how do we get in I think we have to go
this way we were baited by this light
thing I don't no the light's right it's
cuz there's raining and the water like
piles up really fast uhoh I don't know
how to get in I don't know how to get in
either why don't we leave and see if the
weather is better tomorrow okay that's a
b idea can do that we tried our best
yeah we tried we came we saw we DED it's
fine it's fine yeah we
dedh
oh cuz the Moon is called Dy you're so
[Music]
silly [\h__\h] weather nah defeated by the
UK
yeah you want to use the mouse M move or
do you want to wait until it's
clear I want to wait we got to look yeah
we got to go inside the building gotar
this is my favorite man okay
everybody
in average British
Beach I flushed
before we left did you wash your hands
we don't have a
sink oh that that is it's conundrum
isn't it it's okay I put my gloves
on Can we is this okay that we didn't
get
anything yeah because we're not trying
to win cuz either way we're going to
start stop playing after after this
yeah okay moons let's see dying is
eclipsed so now we'll get to see an
eclipsed oh no what in thecse you can
you don't have to go to a new place or
you can just oh oh yeah can we I think
you can just land yeah okay yeah let's
do it yeah you just land again Eclipse
weather eclipsed what do that
mean there's toilet oh
skib ski toilet let's go
no okay I think this place is always
eclipsed no it's not always it's not
it's not Eclipse right now right it
didn't say so it is it is it is well
then we're about to die probably right
now
oh we're going the same
way I think I hear a giant why did they
call you the
nisler um because biu called me
nisler oh because
is G
mhm my little bi boo
Zoomer it's okay we also have a
Zoomer in our wave our third
is well in your wave fin yeah our third
is the zomer yeah
has
a I can tell we're we're in oh my
God can we play
chess oh never mine oh I make my
move okay Ron calm
down waa what is this cool place finally
something else what is that I think it's
pe oh it
is oh there's a spider in there oh hello
oh I found gold oh
[Music]
really since this is the last round I'm
just going to risk it for the
biscuit and just go to places
alone what are these
sounds the Holy Grail yeah I don't know
what happens like we're going to Reen
Harry
Potter okay there's a Holy Grail right
right in Harry
Potter am I going in
circles look I might be I definitely
have no sense of direction
now no oh the Goblet same thing same
thing
no hello hi there's a bug in there
oh oh hi come here come here oh come
here oh yeah
a f who hit me she hit me I didn't mean
to I'm sorry I'm trying to hit the
B no you hit me no I didn't
no if anything I'm hitting on
you there I don't think there's anything
though
yeah we're so powerful now nothing can
ever get
us
[\h__\h] oh no what the
[\h__\h] what is
that yeah keep on hitting it yeah it
will die
eventually what oh
that's it's
possible
what the [\h__\h] is going on hi dead
girls hi how's it going I love how we
even connected in death not even death
World Part this relationship was so much
so many things Nutcracker there was
theil yeah there was me with the mask
on waa the first thing we started
hitting was that I thought it was an
enemy uh I don't know what that person
thing was but apparently it it only mov
if we're not looking at it the coil
head was confusing yeah that's the coil
head this has been fun we're not going
to meet our
quota that's okay we can just go in and
do our
best yeah we're still we're still at we
we have one more day right yeah yeah so
we can go in and do our best how much
money do we have left oh and then we
won't make the quota and then Kiara can
see what happens when you don't make the
qu oh yeah cuz I guess we never saw that
before true M no so you find out today
find out
today oh there it
is let's go let's go I'm honestly
surprised that we haven't even water
we're Pros Pro for real what the hell
kind of amazing I thought at least the
first round we would
lose yeah no we're just we're
winning you know why we're winning cuz
we're the worldwide Wu
web yeah the world
wide worldwide w we can add another
W the winning worldwide
we hey even more W's where is the door
where is the door right here one here
oh hi oh we're here again let's go I
want to go upstairs bye-bye where did
you where did you I found something oh
there's a robot but I don't want to pick
it up cuz it's loud I found going to
make
anyway ball might as well just have
flooring oh
[\h__\h] it's still
dark I'm hungry guys I need to
cook you poor thing hi hello oh you
heard
me yeah you're hungry oh what the [\h__\h]
is that yeah I'm
hungry what is this that looks kind of
crazy what is this really fast and like
float over and I'm like whoa oh what a
weird dead end everything look normal
yeah
[Music]
we oh I found a
key a
key never have I ever used a
key oh that
oh funny
sound what is oh
yeah what is this
sound is it a fire maybe a
fireplace that's the land mine saying
hello well now without a flashlight I'm
way more likely to
oh let's go I used the
key
uh oh come there we go I found something
nice the mask is
B if I'll ever make it
out use it oh okay they won't they won't
expect it what
happens nothing happened oh ah I dropped
it not
us
how do I oh yeah let's
[Music]
go what how do I use
[Laughter]
it but I I don't see
anything and I found why did I die Oh I
thought I would be the Menace to
Society found a mug that says number one
mug and God damn it nice shall we try to
bring these back to the ship even though
we're not going to make quot yeah I
thought it was going to do something
else I think I'm going to keep exploring
yeah me too see there oh it turns me
into a zombie so maybe my my zombie body
is able to haunt them I feel like I
don't think they're proposed to K that's
a good idea propos be quite a good use
K
yeah she's definitely
alive you sure oh no don't don't try to
find
me I know you want drive on to the Mind
chat there's my intrusive
thoughts they have no
idea
K hi
sound what's that sound please find I'm
not sure okay I'm just going to follow
you okay please find me dead
end find the
[Music]
wa mom doesn't say
anything rea's
world they're so cute she's downstairs I
love these girls no I think I'm upstairs
did she leave what do that sound oh oh
God I'm being haunted by the little girl
no oh God why is it
you if I I hear her breathing she's
like oh my God she's right here oh she's
gone now oh my God I'm going to die to
the little girl my head's going to get
exploded guys it's okay just come here
come here that's what happens I'll get
you out yeah no don't leave no don't
leave did she know I think she put on
the oh I think so too
you found yeah I found I guess so put it
on don't get
killed um M just wants a hug say oh my
God
you you kill
me you are Creator the wife web the
world web am I about to get cupon yes
oh that's
me you got C on for real oh my you
standing on
[Laughter]
stairs painting in the ring hi we you
you what there's so many voices also
dead oh let let's death yeah
sorry I hope I don't die to the little
girl though if I die it's all on it's to
you why would we that to the little girl
she'll come out here she'll explode my
head what God pomu is getting
haunted oh what the [\h__\h]
oh oh my God
no
[Music]
no it wasn't even it was the dog yeah I
actually I found the mask and I I I
actually didn't know what exactly would
happen even though we already
experienced it so they told me to put it
on and I thought I could freely haunt
you guys when I put it on but I didn't
realize that I would die and then not
have control over
it so
funny no you that was so good you just
got quiet all of a sudden I turned
around in here but it was just because I
went on my own to find some stuff so it
was natural that I became quiet but it
was fun watching you girls looking for
me yeah we were looking for you he's so
sleet so um because we have uh because
we have we have
nothing we have nothing we don't have to
go to the company meaning we can just
explore di one more time
oh fun yeah and then uh once we end this
day we don't have to worry about
collecting anything because it's Day
Zero it'll just uh we'll experience the
loser thing so say you we paid good
money to be here we just go again or
what I say you oh now we don't even have
shovels anymore we have
nothing at all go to a moon on day Zero
I thought you have to go to the company
no if you're going to lose
anyway what the hell is this what is
water oh Quantum Rock he okay everyone
Look Away not water look back look
back what the hell going on wa just
climb around it yeah we're getting
baited wait can we go to this go to this
side I'm already I'm already over me too
I am s of it e
hi so over
H where are you I already lost you we we
I'm just following I'm following it's
okay
hi hi we lost the other
two they they'll make their way surely
[Music]
okay oh there it
is okay it's the Mansion
again yeah but I think here it's always
the Mansion okay
nice
WEA yeah
hi hi always got to make sure you're
still close by cuz it can change so
quickly in an
instant that's true well now we can't
protect ourselves what can we make it
step step on the land mine
somehow be careful be
careful h k yeah look behind
you
behind me there's a little girl no
there's no girl she's gone now there was
a bug I was looking at the bug you were
looking at a girl what about me I
thought you only have eyes for me the
[\h__\h] oh my God I'm
upstairs oh
[Laughter]
no oh my God I'm
sorry oh oh we are oh [\h__\h] me oh my God
oh God oh I'm gonna die oh this is so
bad oh my God I'm going to die oh
there's a
nutcracker no oh no oh my god oh
no P blow him up step on the land mine P
him up P him up blow him all up
together why does she oh my god oh why
does the land m not work on him where
are you little girl just kill me
now the [\h__\h] Pomo can you step one one
step forward
my oh my god did you guys see the little
girl from my POV no we can't my own it's
in your head oh my God it's in my head
take your pills pom that was so evil how
wait which one did you guys die to uh
the yeah the nom nom nom nom yeah they
Di to the coil oh the coil head it was
funny wait WEA did you die before us um
I died outside cuz a dog ate me that a
dog should have climbed the rock with us
should have climbed it with us as you
have not met the performance has
been you welcome to our disciplinary
hide with you the corner get in the
corner get in the
corner coaster W you're
fired well [\h__\h] you too oh Discord hello
hello
wives hello hello hello oh wait we here
should we switch to Discord yeah Discord
bye-bye
game I closed game okay that was fun
actually yeah see you were so worried
that it was going to be not fun and then
look at you well yeah well I I think I
would say bra it's quite repetitive
though it is a little repetitive but
that's why like uh the the worst levels
get like the the more things that are
kind of introduced but it felt like we
kind of had really bad things right off
the bat you know yeah we were a great
team of
wives M and it was really nice with this
group I like this group me too w web
we're all so pretty we're so beautiful
like oh my God slave
to thank you for wait wasn't it Pomo who
invited yeah thank you Pomo yeah thank
you P yeah I'm glad that we could play
I'm glad that after you ended your
stream you were able to play for real
for real yeah thank God sorry I keep you
seeing no that's fine as long as you you
didn't have to leave completely I'm
happy yeah no I have fun had a lot of
fun thank
you thank you girls I love you girls oh
my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God worldwide wi web winning worldwide
wi web win winning w web girls
Ys yes oh why did you change your
picture a w because you're not playing
the game anymore but it's
weird it's cute that's my Discord icon
how could you say it yeah let her cook
oh okay I I'll consider it she's gaming
she's gaming yeah this is
gaming what was I going to say I was
going to say something but I
forgot remember
[Music]
uh uh I'm remembering
uh [\h__\h] subscribe to the worldwide yeah
subscribe subscribe and leave a like and
S yes everybody type type into your
search bar on your browser worldwide Wu
web winning.com
ww I'm going to buy that domain right
now worldwide oh my God actually
winning no I don't think that what
happens if I put it in connection failed
connection failed what does that mean
we're not
real uh we're real we're real we're real
to me we just need to establish it you
know yeah yeah I think with this collap
we have established it yeah
[Music]
yeah that was fun thing you girls I I I
wish you a a happy happy New Year soon
and Merry Christmas yeah and and I wish
you much love and um don't forget about
the fun times we had together the love
that we shared it's happening it's
happening I don't know like don't don't
don't divorce me okay I could never I
wouldn't even dream about
it ever
ever we're the
wwww now
W yeah wad w w
w so many WS I'm going to make food now
okay thank you guys that was so much
fun thank
you some
[Music]
time oh yeah to everybody wife making
out e e now I'm freaking out
e why you say e you're the one who
started this too much Kies bye
bye bye everyone thank
you
[Music]
byee
I in German we say oh I
[Music]
forgot byebye byebye too much too much
Les I got a really really funny uh fake
Super Chat the other day and it's it's
become a meme too much lesbian please be
careful I have to show
[Music]
you