[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
let's not make it loud
okay guys so
uh so we we we are doing the
halloweenity metronome battle finally is
uh yeah it's the D-Day you guys can tell
how nervous I am yes uh
and uh this is attention I'm probably
reading from whole life ID generation 2
and we have our co-host here please
introduce yourself
[Music]
so if you guys looked at the thumbnail
earlier we have eight participants well
including us so six people there are no
hosting and plus us two eight people
fighting for the
Yago trophy
today
but don't worry even though even though
you have to fight for this everybody
gets a participation prize which is this
plushie you can you can hold it if you
want ah I wonder the plastic okay thank
you yeah
[Laughter]
plushie yeah everybody gets one so they
can you know they can they can take home
after the competition or maybe during
the competition if somebody wants well
uh to start off what is a metronome
battle wow what is that what is that
girl I don't know oh my God I'm confused
please explain
oh okay metronome battle is basically
it's just like a Pokemon battle it's but
it's different because the only move
that you're allowed to use is metronome
only selected Pokemons can learn the
move and you teach the metronome through
TM and then uh you pray for the RNG
because what metronome does it it's it
pulls moves from like a a decided pool
of moves and then you just pray that you
get a good move some summaries sometimes
you get uh not so lucky moves remember
our demo battle last time
yeah it's RNG It's So Random oh gosh we
need luck yeah you need luck um she got
destroyed because she was so unlucky but
I'm really scared from the for the D-Day
because well because I don't know I
don't want to run out of luck well okay
yeah we don't know so before we start I
want to explain to you guys the rules of
this fight so
[Music]
so the rules is two versus two singles
formats so it's not a double battle so
it's like single format but like you
give two Pokemon okay and then prepare
two Pokemon with only metronome is
moveless and no changing until the end
that means you have to stick to the
roster until the end like because people
will reveal their Pokemons and stuff
right so it's okay you have to stick to
your choice yeah and then
you read the next one the next one is uh
which one is
the rice can turn your Pokemon uh uh
more bling bling more prettier and
that's a good thing and the next one any
health items okay so if you want to hold
my hand I mean hot hot berries is okay
all right yeah because I don't know uh I
don't know guys I'm consider I think
like I was thinking with like oh maybe
we should restrict this restrict that
but I feel like Terra still lies is like
the gimmick of the game anyways and we
like a little bit of chaos if not a lot
of chaos so I guess surprise let's go
surprise we need gimmick yeah YouTuber
okay okay and then any health items also
okay yeah guys so yeah uh for real guys
any hailed items okay for real and no
but no abilities that affect the
opponent BP negatively you wouldn't want
your PP to be affected negatively right
so PP is like uh your metronome you only
have limited amounts of uses and then
once your PP Runs Out you will start to
use struggle which is a move that hurts
your opponent Pokemon a little bit but
also endures you quiet you know so it's
like yeah no pressure no pressure guys
this is a no pressured tournament and
then maybe it's enough yeah people
enough and then you can use items to
raise your PP at your Pokemon when
preparing and you can use PP up but from
my experience with the demo battle yeah
we don't really need it I think but you
can anyways yeah yeah
and then we can do Max one Paradox no
mythical legendary well why because it's
up to you whether you want to use
Paradox or not even though no mythical
legendary but I feel like the Paradox
Pokemon is like the you know the main
thing of this Pokemon and I think it
would be a shame it's like you still not
used but I think it's just nice if we
have the choice too okay
[Music]
yeah yeah like that like that like that
yeah
and okay yeah you guys already know what
Paradox Pokemon can use metronome there
are actually three three Pokemons three
Pokemon that can use uh metronome in the
Paradox I was actually considering uh
using it but you'll see what I end up
with later you guys uh probably if you
watch the demo battle last time you will
be spoiled but I just want to have fun I
think like my team has like a very nice
uh you know dynamic not Dynamic see just
like cute and then what about you Kobo
what are you using the same or what are
you using I'm using the same uh the same
okay okay so for those of you who watch
the preparation stream you have already
uh been spoiled with what our poke what
what our Pokemon is here guys okay yeah
then
so uh next is I'm gonna uh show you the
brackets
yeah she's so tall guys it's okay so
this is what the bracket looks like and
by the way don't forget to tweet using
enxid metronome
yeah and then for the first one we have
Anya melfisa and Sarah's fauna and we
have Kalia pimori and kobokanaru and
yeah and then the first battle is
actually Pavilion Rene and takanashi
Kiara yes and then crazy Ollie and Muna
hoshinofa yeah guys so they will we will
advance shoes
you until whoever wins the Yago trophy
that versus yeah interesting right
interesting fights well guys uh we don't
wanna I don't know we don't wanna uh
talk for too long right so we're just
gonna start with the first one I know uh
this says like we're not going
alphabetical and I think for a little
bit of demonstration I think uh me and
takanase
Kiara has decided that she would want to
demonstrate a little bit with me first
you know okay
so we can go to the main game screen
okay OMG
okay
yo main game
hello
[Music]
you can be here because your co-host
yeah yeah okay so
yeah so
um let's go
no not cheat not cheat guys
okay so you guys hear the Pokemon music
right and participating battle team I
will be using these Pokemon I don't know
what Pokemon uh Kiara will be using uh I
think so and then I want to choose the
current party so this is not no
restriction so see this is the normal
rules number of Pokemon is one two six
but we're only using two anyways Pokemon
level set to level 50. everything is
allowed except when it's outside the
rules yeah and then
participating okay yes
it's fine guys it's censoring my first
Pokemon but believe me it's intentional
no it's not cool yeah preparations
complete
and then uh oh she's using uh in a cute
Pokemon like me
I don't know do you think I should enter
this first yeah I think so I don't know
that
okay and then we're standing by okay
Kiara
yeah everybody is like everybody is in
the other voice yeah I think they're
just like chilling
well yeah
I
don't know
bgm loud okay okay okay now it's okay
right I think
Kira is not in VC no but if he I'm here
yeah yeah sure you want to come here
they're asking you if you don't have
items I have items
don't worry okay
oh my God good day but yeah no don't
bombed their Roti I will bunk so that it
will fall apart no no wait I will
terrestrialize I will become ghosty do
you want to terasolize Kiara no
okay fine I won't rationalize them well
that doesn't help anyway I hope I hope
not okay so she has tinkathon and I have
royalty which is a synasty well let's
pray let's pray for the best
oh gosh she's faster
yeah she's faster than me what the hell
is hyper voice
hypervoice is a voice verbs hyper you
know what I joked about re like studying
I didn't joke about studying oh let's go
what the heck okay but it's not very
effective but it hits anyways it's a
critical
it's a critical anyways let's go
what the hell it's so unfair that you're
using Ghost Pokemon
why then why aren't you using Ghost
Pokemon
Ghost Pokemon
oh shoot oh okay welcome to fighting oh
my God
[Music]
magic powder is powder but Magic
oh my God you're now psychic type for
some reason
[Laughter]
KKK
um
what the hell is power split oh no huh
shared its power of the target what do
you mean what do you mean shampoo with
the target I don't even know what that
is
sleepy sleepy Mommy okay let's see how
long do you sleep when you sleep uh
yesterday I slept for uh
45678 like oh my six hours
[Music]
until you wake up wait what no okay
whatever I don't know what happened
concentrate on commentating I think yeah
okay you're still sleeping I think you
should wake up in in like a few turns oh
yeah
I'm so lucky oh
what are you French I've seen that
before but how does it work I lost HP
too yeah but like you have a substitute
oh
[Music]
my god
when the substitute dies I come back
yeah when the substitute dies you come
back as a substitute can use metronome
too okay no I come back you come back
okay oh my goodness
[Music]
let's go
oh
yeah I keep on switching back and forth
they're still back in the substitute I
don't understand how many HP does a
substitute have
oh let's go you know I'm trying to get
worried that we ran out of pp because I
I expected this to be faster oh my
goodness yeah
oh
well the substitute is really is saving
wow
oh no it sounds like an attack okay two
times water hit
okay I think the sun is very tight but
not anymore
oh man now I'm confused because
I have
now I'm confused because of outrage side
effects man if only you didn't have
substitute you're so lucky
[Music]
can't see health bar oh no so sad
mama
[Music]
what oh my God
that's ridiculous Focus
oh I'm crying because you're so mean
you're so stupid
when people say cannot see the thingy so
I can move
okay thank you
oh
no no no no no it's okay
okay
[Music]
no confused okay okay
okay guys wait I will I will set up a
little bit oh no
shape
let's go come back let's go come back
what is it with all these attacks
what is that oh it failed I don't know
what failed now there we go it failed
guys there guys I can use metronome
three more times there we go
there's a battle it's communicating for
me is it oh no no sorry okay
okay
oh my God
oh my God is a buff attack I mean not
buff attack is a buff move that improved
the thingy the stats of My Pokemon
um are you able to use metronome oh
what's life days oh shoot
what is nice oh
nice we're already gonna finish this
let's go finish it Mom can you hit
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
it's not over yet true
it's not over yet close so I would say
yeah
I'm close though I will like
what side
um will up the site
that you copied there's no stat changes
yet so
why are preparing for me oh okay oh wow
now
too bad for you and now you're faster
and then doesn't affect but you're so
faster so
um next to you
oh
low damage yellow damage so sad rip all
the stat Buffs that I got
what attacks do I need to to not miss
you
okay nice okay okay super effective nice
move
you have to cheer for your mommy yeah
yeah yeah
opportunity
[Music]
yeah I have an eye I see you oh my God
so beautiful
and won't help you
okay
come on come on and Spore
man
besideshield Bash
what is that let's go
no
oh my God
I'm trying I'm praying for real
oh yeah oh it's so cute
there's no way there's absolutely no way
first one
why flying I told him I want to fly why
you die the only way for me to survive
is if I have an attack that makes me go
away or you miss but um
[Music]
I don't know
[Applause]
oh
hey
that's crazy
[Music]
let's go
oh my God
[Applause]
that was crazy
yeah like the subtle things that happen
like the substitute and and yeah
and now this with them you fly I dive
what what's going on what's going on
indeed oh my gosh
all right but the fun fun fighting with
you
I will carry the hollow bird name yes
please do to be honest when I saw that
we have to fight against each other I
was kind of sad and I kind of didn't
want to do it because I don't want to
fight against you so at least now it's
over and you won so hopefully just like
in the Japanese metronome battle
hopefully you as the host are gonna
bring the cup home
go go
[Music]
okay but it's just uh it's just a unique
warm-up warm up right
that was the real deal oh this is a real
real one yeah real one no mommy mommy
I want to fight you
Mommy
why are you diving huh why are you
diving no diving was good I think the
Highlight on that match was um basically
me going to fly and then thinking oh man
it's over oh
in the last people who didn't support me
no
bro no no why you blame me now I what
the hell Mommy I want to fight you now
but yeah that fly counter with dive was
amazing oh my goodness
that was epic
live yeah wow wow wow
yeah okay
me I Advanced to the next and then next
and then next we have uh next we will be
having uh can you ask who's ready who's
ready who's ready well
I'm ready though
you ready
um okay uh did you prepare the room
I'm with I'm with Daddy now in the room
okay
no because I will train you how to
commentate so next week
okay crazy
you ready are you ready
yeah I think she's ready okay yeah yeah
we think yeah they're they're oh they're
from right now they're preparing right
now I think okay okay okay crazy only
crazy crazy crazy crazy
okay okay okay
they're searching for opponent to battle
oh
okay okay we'll wait for them we'll wait
for them we'll wait for them
[Music]
maybe we can oh
is fauna and Anya really we can do
we can do fauna and Anya
oh sure sure let's go now
okay yes then
let us move
let us move to the without it guys this
is
[Applause]
just wait be patient just wait patient
[Music]
I'll try my best to comment comment the
moves the the Pokemon the moves
yeah Pokemon the moves yeah yeah
okay
okay I think this is okay
participating battle team we can't even
see but it's okay
I think it's okay well yeah we are so
ready for this
you're very ready
okay sorry guys I'm just so nervous I
thought you don't be nervous
yeah okay okay okay okay can you tell
Kobo to sit down no
well okay next one we have uh we have
uh fauna and Anya
nanya please come in please come in
please
if you guys want to come in then sure if
you guys don't want to come in that's
fine too but now please come in
you just don't want to work
oh yeah
it's okay if you don't want to come in
yeah hello hello
hello
I'm so nervous right now
you're not the one battling
I know
I know I know okay it's fun and Anya now
um
let's go oh God okay waiting for all the
preparations to be completo
yes see
and then
Darjeeling sorry you can't see the name
but because we're covering and cupcake
from fauna right this is fauna POV by
the way
hmm
interesting interesting interesting
interesting yeah I'm gonna use the same
Pokemon like like Mommy before mommy
yeah yeah yeah also same Pokemon as me
just like the evolution oh my God
I see what you are using for your polti
guys you come prepared
I would have Googled what are the best
items
he paired yeah so prepared okay
just gonna pray exactly it's that's the
mindset you know that's the mindset
and Anya here has a slow bro as well as
the Gardevoir so may the best combo win
let's go you got this
both of you got this
still communicating wait are you guys
all ready
[Music]
okay phone already and you're ready or
not I'm not good oh okay okay okay sorry
sorry I shall be good the video is
okay okay sorry sorry the bgm is mixing
no no no no no no no no
oh I turned mine off
oh intense bgm oh gold stars
[Music]
don't worry about it oh this bgm though
oh my God okay
oh my god
let's go okay
I'm HP not visible yeah guys
so I will read it out to you
Thunder Punch is it effective
defense fail oh no
it actually is visible never mind
share this guard with the target spicy
okay interesting interesting yeah what
now double hit okay okay your phone is
using the same Pokemon as me pretty much
I don't know if the ability is the same
because um
yeah cause like the ability is a weak
armor right so if we need armor if they
get physical attack then the speed will
race or something uh like the defense
goes down but
the speed goes up
fire fan
they're dealing the fence fell defense
going down everything yeah yeah that's
it that's it that's it
oh no it's burnt I'm still yeah wait and
this Pokemon got burned I don't know
until when yeah
excuse me oh huh
Dragon Rush
got so much damage onions got I don't
know I don't know
[Music]
the thing was burned is that it kind of
it's also gives your you know attack in
half it reduces your attack oh okay oh
my God
my Darjeeling oh my God
nice game
is still sounding strong with more than
half HP what's gonna happen
let's go okay this is gonna be a little
art yeah yeah yeah oh my God it's fire
fire it's fire elements
yeah basically with terrestrialized you
can basically do any element you want oh
do it again oh come on let's go
fire Gardevoir is kind of metal though
that's cool I know I know drill run oh
my God uh no is the substitute guys oh
substitute gone let's go
gone in just one move let's see if
they're dealing
can pour some tea
whatever
oh but because yeah wood Hammer is a
grass move with a recoil but because
Gardevoir is fire man yeah
that was like 20 D chests yeah
oh poison Sail
but well they're just oh
Darjeeling finally got refereeled and
then now photo will have to finally get
the Tinker tone out what is this
oh God sorry delayed I'm just my
daughter
okay well there's still a chance for
Anya I think
I think it Tan's very cute
kitty same time
oh Fairy Oh fairy type yeah
beautiful
yes this is gonna be really close unless
somebody gets incredibly lucky or
unlucky
we're easy that's me right now I'm so
worried
so
gardevoir's ability it can't have
synchronized so what synchronized does
is if say he gets paralyzed then the
other person oh no no no yeah yeah yeah
yeah
but not because it has insomnia now it
cannot sleep you know there are some
moves that take advantage of sleeping so
if you have insomnia then you cannot
sleep you cannot yeah
oh my goodness
confusing
[Applause]
oh my goodness cupcake okay come on
cupcake
oh God
my shot my shot oh shoot I hear the
super effective noise okay oh my God oh
my God Metro no Metro no metronome
low sweep
ouch
okay
Poco actually has more HP now so yeah
it's so close
cuckoo is actually leading oh my
goodness wait so it could be anybody's
game wait what
okay okay what is this oh my God
oh my God
[Laughter]
I don't know what happens now what is
that what was that yeah
explosion
oh my God that's so hard what can happen
huh
it's my first time saying that skill
s
that's crazy oh my God so so so so what
uh so we have to rematch oh yeah uh
because
oh my God
yes yeah
cause you fainted first
that because cupcake Fanny last so
technically uh the game uh picks Upon Us
win that's so handy though oh my God
everything can happen in a metronome
battle well crazy you guys were asking
for like self-destruct and something
like that well
this is um
anime ending though
yeah I think guys yeah yeah I think yeah
oh
yeah that was epic though thank you so
much for playing I think it would it
would not be fair if we did a rematch
from an explosive move yeah thank you so
much though that was really epic thank
you Father and Anya oh thank you thank
you
everyone thank you yeah
[Music]
oh my goodness what name what was that
skill
that was crazy that was explosion
explore
indeed well that's crazy like I would be
a really I would be salty I would be so
salty about that you know don't jinx it
don't jinx it
[Music]
um
but it's still Fair yeah it's like
that's what metronome battles are I
guess okay and then so we have Sarah's
phone advancing
oh my goodness okay nice ready for onion
milk Pizza nice try nice try yeah yeah
yeah very unexpected move very very
unexpected yes yes yes
okay well uh the next one we will have
crazy Ollie and Muna hoshinova are you
guys ready
okay they seem to be ready they seem to
be ready so we can set up what did you
think about the previous game though of
course like the ending was like really
yeah yeah something but oh my God that
it was so close though I think the the
fire Gardevoir was like wait what yeah
I was expecting something more
straightforward you know like uh maybe
uh what's Gardevoir psychic is it yeah
yeah yeah I don't expect that cuckoo
will also fainted yeah well
that was epic see this is the art of
metronome battle guys yeah out of
metronome and next up uh next up we have
uh Muna hoshinova and crazy Ali so we
can move here yes game let's go
um there we go because this is my first
time yeah why my current Mark they have
like
lots of oh because yes uh
ah I have to edit it first and I
um maybe you can like pick yeah okay you
can edit I think wait I'll I'll just
like
okay I'll I'm showing your screen
anyways
let's look at muna's Pokemon
but but but it was on my party and boxes
and I cannot wait
um wait let's uh let's try if you use
the same party but just like select two
oh can I I think maybe you can
okay
versus crazy Oli
oh yeah yeah and then you can choose I
think ooh Ollie's using scream tail and
please see someone's taking advantage of
the Paradox okay roll here
many Pokemons I can learn metronome so I
just took whatever okay okay okay me too
me too me too me too
yeah I just ended up
um basically looking for the Pokemon I
already have I think when I click first
and second I think my my other Pokemon
oh there is only two okay nice nice nice
nice oh my God all these photo is so
funny
wow it's a bunch of oh my God deadline
you're terrorizing me with this kind of
name that's right
oh my God it must be that guys Paradox
Pokemon is allowed but Max one it's up
to them if they want to use or not me
personally I choose not to use but
Ollie's using exercising her right to
use Paradox Pokemon
hello BJ I'm sorry guys I just realized
the level is not 50 50.
[Music]
upside upside
I do remember three minutes
pretty much
yeah
[Music]
uh battle again but with different rules
yeah
yeah yeah
single wait which one single battle
normal rules
shingle battle it's single better
Memorial
thank you okay
okay we're ready we're ready
okay okay ready ready okay
sorry guys my mistake I also didn't pay
attention to the rules on the right
um
okay it should be good right special
level 50.
yeah
okay all right
okay
standing by
wow very nice so Gardevoir and Gengar
versus Blissey and screamtail yeah round
and pink just like my
buns nice one
is this Muna POV yes this is muna POV
yeah
so the POV always belongs to the person
on the left
oh wow Stone axis
pointed Stones that's like a hazard
that's like a hazard setup so whenever
uh
it's like a hazard setup so whenever
muna's next Pokemon comes in it will be
like
okay
it's a paradox yeah
soft boiled yum eating man don't what if
that would have been so good if it was
like if it happened in the middle of the
game though
attack order yummy oh damn so bulky I
just have the spell metronome yes yes
yes
yeah yeah yeah vacuum WAVE clean up
away yeah not very effective
wow yes nice oh fire spin okay oh
trapped in the fiery Vortex it will hurt
nice
nice with it with fire Gardevoir in this
tournament oh my gosh well let's see
what's cream tail is going to use cream
tail is going to be using a drill effect
hopefully she will be fine I mean he
okay okay what about Gardevoir yeah
muna's Gardevoir is male so sleepy sleep
sleep
time sleep time and got a fire spin yeah
it doesn't wake up from the fire spin oh
my God it's sleeping
oh I think Muna is reading yeah at this
rate like if it goes I don't know
anything can happen though yeah
oh my God what is this what what is this
crazy
that's crazy oh my God okay only still
can come back we don't know she's
setting up for real oh my goodness she's
rationalizing
[Music]
oh
my God
nice move
yeah
um okay
buff let's go Forest Palms
she'll be able to finish scream tail but
let's see what what scream till can do
to retaliate please deadline please
make a move
[Applause]
[Music]
come on come on come on
okay different spell
it's not effective but fire spin will
still I don't know the fire oh the fire
is a little
annoying annoying okay okay okay higher
attack and she has lower defense okay
let's
pray to the metronome Gods what will
happen
so
for you
let's go
okay okay
how long oh the fire spin is gone
because maybe
oh is there setting up as well oh my
goodness okay scary scary scary scary
scary scary scary okay what got buff
the thing is cream till is really scary
what does it do oh my God
you know okay let's go oh my god let's
see the thing is see the thing is if
Ollie if Ollie
oh
my God
okay
okay the duck life
oh my god
wow that was wow damn
that guy had the first time but guess
what
ah man it could have been anybody's game
but yeah at the beginning the fire spin
thing if only god of Warhead hold on a
little bit longer then yeah that was so
hype hold on all right thank you so much
thank you
that was great Gigi that that was epic
battle epic epic epic okay
only advances
Echo ball perfect
yeah
okay wait
oh yeah yeah yeah
guys we don't know what will happen even
though we find that like the the feeling
went okay this time Muna will win but no
you cannot think like that yes I can
happen in the metronome battle well next
up we do have
yeah I wanted to fast okay next we have
the last
um the last thingy of the thingy we have
Maori Calliope
I'm hungry
who will win OMG you win I don't know
oh my God I don't know how this is gonna
go
Pokemon they could learn metronome
before I came here okay well to be fair
nobody knows so you know
about RNG exactly okay give me a sec let
me just put you put your name and stuff
and Kobo because it's okay yeah you
don't move you're already moving here
anyways it's fine okay okay one move
okay okay
well
we are gonna move here then
Young
okay normal rules we're checking the
rules again for the level set to 50.
that's nice okay
Mori are you ready
ready preparation complex it's as ready
as I'll ever be to okay
let's go child enter
and the guys
[Music]
hobo is using the same team
um
and chancy let's go
another team what kind of normal sort of
normal I just caught the chansy let's
see how they do let's see well Chelsea
is a pretty bulky Pokemon at least in
terms of um special so we're just gonna
pray I'm gonna make you work for it
I'm confused you cannot do that wait why
is that why what as she sprayed I
deleted all my moves wait where where's
the Metro
[Laughter]
I taught my Pokemon metronome and that
was it
okay okay
[Applause]
hold on
okay we stopped we if we stop for a
little bit okay okay so why is this
happening okay okay
so why why is this going on why is this
okay
can I ask you what item you are using
a salt vest
[Music]
okay so oh my gosh all right let me cool
all right real quick okay okay okay okay
okay
um quit quit quit quit yeah so what's so
fast is um raising the holder special
defense but also prevents the holder
from selecting status moves and it kind
of interferes with metronome I think
Daddy
hey at least we figured
for the first part okay okay okay okay
and then we
go
[Music]
slow it's okay let me go ahead and
change
okay what shall I eat
let's
um let's see oh goodness it's okay it's
okay we're setting up setting up
[Music]
I wonder who's gonna add Vans let's play
them whoever advances don't have
metronome and I don't know he has you
know he she has metronome but she's
using an item that prevents her to use
the move properly oh
my God
it's okay it's okay now I'm good to go
you're good to go okay we'll be fine now
okay I guess about items huh it's okay
open your code really quick okay I'm on
my way okay okay
shut up
never missed another little massage
it's fun it's fine okay and and now
back and this time I'll be able to use
my move
this is such an interesting concept for
a for a tournament because it really
there's not a lot of skill involved
yeah
only one skill 71 skill let's see what
happens exactly I thought I wanted to
like make a fun game that you know
people don't really need to stress about
that much you know I like that yeah
competitive gambling they're saying
um
[Music]
all right and I'm the luckiest you're
the lucky now for an opponent to battle
okay all right all right
the Battle of who has the best luck
today yes may the luckiest Advance all
right wait why am I in offline mode who
do that to me hold on a second he was
online before I guess well online go
online right I'm going online
competitive gotcha all right well I'm
really scared though because Ollie is
bringing a paradox Pokemon and I'll have
to go against her if um after this
[Laughter]
oh but it's all right oh yeah thanks
this is smart hey smart
we did not Outlaw Paradox Pokemon so I
did not like you yeah it's like her
right to use it I just wanted to
Showcase you know like
I feel like it would be a shame to
disable to rationalize and Paradox
Pokemon considering like is the
highlight of the game you know
um yeah it's kind of this this deal
thing I guess I'm on my way I entered
okay okay okay
we're in we're in the same room now you
have beautiful eyes called
I know you
opponent has been found okay that's
great
okay okay fingers crossed it works this
time okay fingers crossed it works
yeah surely yeah
[Music]
I wonder
uh nothing again she was like what rules
I said normal rules and she's like I
don't know which normal rules and
there's only one normal rules
yeah right his defending battle team
well I'm confusing the call
IA and Savoy for Cobalt
um
same party same party same team as
before for me okay
enter enter
Pokemon yeah
okay okay done have you seen it have you
choose
here we go okay let's choose
here we go here we go here we go here we
go here we go here we go finally back
yeah
yes okay okay see I'm ready finally yeah
let's set the Moose
maybe May the best metronome user and
the luckiest okay
I wish I'm lucky let's go
okay okay let's go okay more reverse
let's go
watching from the watching from her
switch she knows early and so she spoils
all of us my goodness
it's okay it's okay
all right come on Michael
[Music]
the latency Advantage oh Walter guys
let's go
Sheena use metronome what will she use
struggle bug
ouch it's not effective but still does
something special attack drop yeah
let's see okay yeah
reason why you're not using any items
I don't know what items to use
there you go there's their answer
my child tells me to whoop you teach you
a little lesson
from Uncle Mike
the Moose is loose this Pokemon is evil
inside she's such a tank
a scissors oh my God what the what
I mean hello
crazy yeah the Moose is loose he's a
crazy Pokemon
don't bite me I'm a good time bro
oh God
what is that I don't know Shadow Ball
what's Shadow Ball gonna do oh not so
bad
attention after this spoiler spoiler
henching after this handshin now
oh we're gonna terrestrialize into Ghost
type
oh wow pretty spooky yeah like this
Pokemon
[Applause]
ghosty ghosty ghost
that's that's the smart thing about
choosing a shadow type Pokemon is there
are quite a few don't worry about them
yeah uh so normal and fighting types
don't move uh don't don't work I mean I
think
yeah all right yeah I'll meet you on uh
on your playing field how about that no
join you yeah do a little magical build
transformation how about that sonny boy
[Music]
because I'm proud of you son
and I want to be cool and hip like the
kids nice
[Music]
let it
I can't I have to it's part of the
tournament
okay Metro no metronome Ice Beam how
much damage also you're getting a lot of
what getting a lot of good status yeah
still no damage setting up yeah you know
what would be heartbreaking if suddenly
somebody gets like oh revert all the
status or like just like me earlier like
I set up and then like I rolled a move
where I copy the other person's stats
Daddy stop
hello
that's kind of part of the tournament
though well
I guess
they're both on like half HP but the
problem is Cobra is already down to her
last Pokemon and
um well you know about to lose all my PP
what happens if I'm out of pp you're
gonna struggle
yeah okay am I allowed to struggle the
tail in Blue from behind your team
yeah
if you lose the pp you will be
struggling
yeah okay so am I allowed to you
struggle
um it's automatic yeah
okay gotcha just making sure yeah yeah
yeah because it is not to move
yep yep okay suicide
it's a huge amount of a huge amount of
HP you got okay okay the mother of yummy
support me oh my God support
yeah yeah cause they got the strips the
HP they're still home
there he goes there's still hope because
that place right now
oh my God oh my God you struggle
Oh shoot that's a lot of HP
oh my God
down
yeah it's supposed to be a Chance the
Rapper but I couldn't put the full name
in uh okay it's too long
[Music]
I only have three moves left what's
gonna happen
sorry
[Laughter]
thanks
uh how much PP I have now oh oh my God
teleport but it failed yeah it's for
escaping
which will happen first uh lose PP or oh
leftovers that's smart I actually wanted
to use leftovers but I didn't have
leftovers and I yeah I just I don't know
where to find leftovers so I just like
you know whatever
yeah
yeah yeah
oh
the same oh God
[Music]
I hate you I do hate hearing you in pain
I really do
I just brought really tanky Pokemon
one HP and a dream
Cobo was one expanded
[Music]
oh my God that's Overkill though I think
oh
[Music]
yeah
why did you have me fight Kobo
what wait Reddit why why did you
choose to it's messed up dude that's my
son listen I had to make some arranges
okay because I know some of you are not
streaming
[Applause]
well when you set the Moose loose that's
just how it goes this is a strong one
I'm scared of fun of those
yeah yeah fun is scary
[Music]
go fauna go fauna go Mori thank you for
playing Cali cool staying here because
she's the co-host yes yeah
later bye bye
I'm going to the other room now
[Music]
room
okay well I guess next up would be me
and Ollie I'm just gonna contact her a
little bit
uh BRB not BRB I guess I'll just set up
my stuff
uh
um
[Applause]
[Music]
I forgot my
I forgot what my room is what my room
number is
ah
okay take your time
okay next up uh we're gonna fight I'm
gonna be fighting Ollie
well let's go holla real fighting let's
see hello Ollie you'll be here with me
well so I don't know you you you don't
have to enter now we're just gonna um
summarize for a little bit you can be
here though if you wanna okay well to
summarize the people who advanced let me
um turn you up a little bit okay the
people who advanced uh the the I don't
know what phase this is called
semi-finals I guess oh is there a spauna
calliope Mori Pavilion Arena and crazy
Ollie well done
everyone reach this face damn so fauna
will be fighting Cali and then right now
uh Rainey me is gonna be fighting your
way Ollie
um do you have any uh last words you're
just kidding
oh my God so intimidating
you'll have to do the deadlines then I
guess
deadline no for real though I'm pretty
scared because like Paradox Pokemon
because they have high base stats so
yeah Paradox are basically like it's
kind of like uh not legendary but also
like good stats you know oh yeah that's
but the thing is I decided to allow it
anyways because I wanna
you wanna because I wanna I wanna allow
it because I want to see at least one
Paradox Pokemon in the tournament you
know hmm
so I'm glad Ollie's delivering with the
very very cute
[Music]
[Applause]
so what's your strategy do you have any
strategy
to win
I pray
that's a spirit
[Laughter]
that's the spirit that's the spirit well
I'm just like
yeah who are you rooting for Ollie or
rainy on my gosh I'm neutral oh
[Music]
okay okay
I trust you I trust you that you are
professional
and then yeah yeah I'm looking for Ollie
picture
professional professional yeah yeah
I found it it's just like it's just
oh okay there we go we find it okay I'm
gonna enter yeah okay
didn't
do it okay
[Music]
we have matched with each other
yeah you're a sushi and I'm a duck yeah
what the heck
Ollie's liking the belly rolls okay I'm
sushi sushi
and I guess the duck is not me even
though I'm the bird
let's go foreign
damn I did not consent to this
[Laughter]
but it's up to me to decide the battles
is yeah normal battle
normal rules and single back
win
[Music]
do we lose
okay preparation's complete
first I'm so scared
it's almost scary
battle battle to save your house being
loot by Cold
bullet see let's see
[Laughter]
yeah yes yes
we don't know who will win because
I don't know because I'm scared of her
Paradox Pokemon
is pretty scary no royalty royalty only
no deadline
yeah she's really fast
[Music]
nah man don't set up that's so unfair I
mean anything is there I guess
Bulldogs
[Music]
so Bucky how many HP do you even have
yeah really known
please
[Music]
okay
okay crystallized
you know what like the thing is
the thing is
I don't even have defense and she's like
oh oh you turn
thank you
but defense fell
okay
well I guess
I guess you'll be getting the other
Pokemon out
dang it I didn't want to introduce your
schedule and
you
thank you
what the coming now
well oh my God
[Music]
oh she's faster now
special attack harshly fell sad what
even am I gonna attack with
um
barely did anything now we'll break a
cup
okay okay okay okay okay
conflicted the royalty versus egg
oh you're using that you're using a
shell Bell yeah so Shelbyville like
gradually restores HP
throat chop oh yeah
nice damage
I hate this so much
guys this is yeah oh my God I hate sad
storms so much
please
did you remember something about
schedule okay let's see what move I will
go for
ha button pass up wow
nice whoops nice book
okay okay oh my gosh oh I already saw
thick oh my goodness
oh no
well we can see
[Music]
wow hey hey
this is not good that's why it needs to
come out soon
[Music]
come on come on come on come on
for belly jump you will need at least
less than I mean more than half HP or
else you will fail it so Billy drum is a
move that uh improves your attack but
you need but you have your HP kind of
you reduce the HP but only was failed
too okay
if belly drum succeeds though it could
be a sweep
but I don't know I don't think oh my God
Bruce for real
oh
my God yeah Ruth is a HP HP thing
that's a big amount of healing yeah nice
heal hopefully hopefully hopefully just
praying
playing here you go oh
yeah
that's what we've been okay
sounds excited oh thanks freaking God
[Music]
oh no please thank freaking God okay
okay
oh cover let's go let's go both got
recovered guys okay cool HP for arena
now
oh there you go thank goodness
oh that's wrong not very effective
oh
yeah schedule's going down I have no
hope for schedule let's go the thing is
there's limited PP with metronome so
not the baby dog
baby dog
what's after wing oh nice thank you okay
bro speed Rose
hmm
okay oh my God stop stalling embrace
your death
you're doing your schedule period
period
[Music]
yeah and only have four move
oh she's so bulky though that's a
problem yeah
[Music]
maybe right now can make it
underwater were you underwater were you
underwater hello I am underwater please
why are you underwater thinking
[Music]
um
why
[Music]
what
but I'm trying
I'm trying to stall
[Music]
so I don't waste
nice move from right now the improve
player Pokemon
a Pokemon oh man I'm just thinking if I
should turn off the lies or not
I think I will
just because
[Music]
look at me it's kind of like a tea you
know
it looks like the Apple yeah yeah it's
like a hot drink you know
[Music]
oh no oh my goodness
okay it's too bulky yeah
oh my goodness
[Music]
uh
when when will you be free
after the Apex tournament sure why not
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
you know I I want to go to spy you know
yeah oh I
yeah yeah
[Music]
you know we confirmed that I you will be
looting me so there will be no Spa well
I can loot your money
okay bye-bye thank you ollie that was an
epic fight yeah can I try only a nice
try good game good game
I'll carry the whole little name
yeah nice Anya
whoa
another selfies Rock oh okay
okay
oh my God that's amazing oh my God I'm
just gonna be honest with you I don't
know what I would have done if it keeps
going you know because screen time was
just like too bulky so man yeah you're
right like I mean like we all said
anything can happen in a metronome
battle
um
explosions nothing new now but yeah hold
on give me a sec
give me a second guys I think um weekend
the next person would be hello oh we see
somebody oh no the next one will be
serious fauna against someone has
disconnected
Calliope Mori oh my God
yes and the next one is fauna and Mori
uh let me just see the
the waiting room
wait wait wait live versus death live so
you guys will see even though a little
bit delay is okay yeah
but you guys will not be able to see
that it's delayed anyway because
because I don't know not because yeah
well okay let me set up oh hello are you
ready
yo self-destruct is just the worst for
this battle for this tournament man it's
like
you've got two in a row right like
yeah I guess so hold on guys so I'm just
gonna like set up first I'm not showing
the screen yet
uh Callie so Kelly yeah and yeah
[Music]
very automatic scary
wait I don't know why I found that okay
and found that name found a name I made
my patience please patience great job my
patience thank you
are you scared
they're both round
they are they're round and bulky
well Kelly where is Cali why is Cali
hidden oh it's because she's not I'm
here okay well I think we are ready
there we go hey let's do it let's do it
okay
wait is this allowed what is allowed the
commentators though how to cheer
foreign
so it doesn't affect
we'll bounce
another one of these movies
[Music]
after you I'm not allowed to interfere
with the uh you know decisions I learned
that from from watching you I just
learned foreign
[Music]
come on SmackDown
why Lord oh my god well guys you just
saw that second first move first move
well she got yeah she can only
tarantulas now
I didn't know you had a shiny one too
yeah or reflect nice oh that's gonna
help a little bit with tanking some
attacks
but reflect is only for physical I think
right if I'm not mistaken I can't read
[Music]
yeah but Michael moose is the best when
it comes to physical yeah it's okay
power through power through May the best
May the luckiest
when oh shift gear yeah
wow a nice that's kind of like the move
they use in the uh what the story ones
right
um okay okay okay Razor Leaf
you can do it weak armor yeah the same
ability
there he goes the Moose is not loose
anymore oh no no longer lose he's okay
oh confused
that's true
[Music]
Diamond Pokemon okay
metronome sorry guys lag Mega horn bro
what was that
um
[Applause]
wow the table's turned yeah and a
critical hit that was pretty nutty oh my
God crazy
well there
that's that's the game that was so fast
that was fast that was like maybe the
fastest battle damn following up well
congrats Fafa congrats
for us I will be watching from the
stands
thanks for inviting me yeah
excited I'm still supporting you that
love you
I'm sorry what was that he said at the
beginning
no no
someone's getting grounded
[Music]
all right
then thank you shoe well okay now now
what
it's gonna be a Santa's team party are
you serious
let's go oh my God this is Rick this is
well you know guys I think the sin is to
Evolution line is kind of good so maybe
Marty Mom that's crazy okay then
this is real well it's just you and me
now and Kobo too you're commentating I
guess
oh my goodness hold on let me just set
up my stuff a little bit uh
[Music]
I'll message you the room
okay
[Music]
wow I I really didn't think that the
finals would be
um
Sarah spauna and pavolia Rainey
has a t Pokemon darkness baby Royal
maybe soonest he is lucky yeah maybe
Sinister is just the best Pokemon to use
when it comes to metronome battles
oh my god let's go tea party
tea party yay okay fun I'm gonna send
you the thing you want to oops
[Laughter]
I'm gonna join the battle someone's
gonna be joining
[Music]
um
well okay I'm gonna join
wow this is
we're so close to the finals are you
gonna be winning the Yago trophy or am I
gonna win the Yago trophy we don't know
it all depends on luck who will win
will there be any stuff this rock again
this time
[Music]
it's okay guys so this rock doesn't mean
you lose yeah I think
oh yeah I think so I think so hold on
oh oops
I'm like trying I'm just like trying so
hard because both of us are on the left
both of us are on the left and I'm like
yeah
what's the most epic bgm battle bgm I
don't know I like using nimona just
because I like nimona hmm
yeah the Moon is pretty good yeah it's
good well
okay I think um
Penny ah
dad likes Cassiopeia
okay okay okay wait let me
[Music]
I think it's okay fine
yeah where are you oh behind me okay
well we can move
shoot let's go let's go move to the
final round and then move the fauna text
here
[Music]
professional so good right yeah I'm
professional Horse no professional host
you will be
[Music]
ready
no I thought you were neutral yeah I
mean I'm neutral I buff right now too
okay I got you both I support you guys
okay let's go let's go let's go let's go
is it the real good luck wrong wrong
press sorry sorry guys preparations
complete
[Music]
wait bgm you want to change the bgm oh
no whatever I think it's too late we can
do wait wait back back back can we back
can we back enter
um maybe not
uh oh well
it's fine
imagine this is a very epic final bgm
[Music]
what are you doing
well may the best cities blind win
good luck
let's go let's go let's go
[Music]
okay there we go
the baby and the mommy let's go yeah the
baby is the mommy
[Music]
what's round I want Square
oh no what's wrong what is wrong it's uh
I'm guessing it's like a physical move
or a fighting move I think it's a normal
move okay
matter
[Music]
oh flail no oh I love you unlucky is
real RNG is real
oh no she's faster
[Music]
hopes guys oh my God oh my God
oh my goodness oh
wait what what so faster wait
wait oh my God
oh my gosh
there's still hope
yeah it doesn't count the buff
oh oh
I'm just hoping I'm just hoping it's
close it's close
it's close oh I mean look oh no oh I'm
sweating I'm sweating so hard oh my God
you're so mean
together
okay
[Music]
that's a physical attack so there's
still hope
oh my God oh my God
um
oh but does it affect me oh my God
another explosion well I can I only have
had training to carry me to Victory if
Victory is yeah yeah
it's not IDF there is no explosion I'm
gonna to rationalize because that's
literally the only thing I can do
that's cool
hold on I'm so cursed
let's go come on
your metronome is cursed I think
well hopefully you will be so kind
[Music]
oh my goodness it's a trick oh my God
oh my God they're doing so oh goodness
[Music]
oh
good luck cupcake my daughter oh cupcake
let's go cupcake
let's go um I'm just praying really hard
you know
I'm just praying really hard oh all of
the stainless steel lines are down so I
really don't know what's gonna happen
tea party's over guys I'm praying for
self-destruct no no no not by me you
know not by me but by her all right
oh my God
super fun
thank you
no no you're puffy
oh come on but attacking Parish you
don't have time to waste the
um don't explode
[Music]
[Applause]
huh oh
man I guess I'm just unlucky my luck
ends here I guess yeah
oh my oh
he's been a dream
crazy
I think Arnold will be very good soon
[Music]
yeah now now oh my God that will make
the difference
yes
bye bye right now I
bye
I was lucky today
and there we have it the winner of the
fight today is
well there you have it two cities in the
finals but unfortunately the baby one
the baby one has to say bye bye
big
red not rig not rig that's the wheel one
fair and square with the Absurd rules of
the metronome but yeah wow
thank you so much fauna for playing
um
I want you to stay here for a little bit
can you um yeah can you come back in
five minutes
sure sure I want to interview you know I
want to interview I I don't know you
won't know just kidding well okay okay
we're looking at the brick and Sarah's
fauna is the winner the winner of
Halloween ID metronome battle and she
will have the Yago trophy we wanna
interview with Sarah spawner well
okay
uh I don't think it takes five minutes
but well
I don't know what do you how do you
wanna if you were to put it in words how
was the how was the final like
for me yeah for you for you for you oh
my God it was epic the tea fighting with
the tea the tea baby one yeah the baby
teeth fighting with like their mother
you know
baby cannot win fighting with their
mother right so
baby okay I guess so the baby cannot win
against the mother it is what it is
that's why guys uh if you're fighting uh
don't fight with your mom because you
know your mother have higher base stats
than you she will always hit you with
the sandal yeah
explosion thing explosion yeah I guess
we learned next time if we wanna do
another metronome battle we should use
uh instead of sinister we use policy
guys because it's the mother has more
you know has more power right yeah yeah
yeah yeah A Life Lesson for this
tournament so amazing right okay I think
we want to uh I think we want to call
fauna to the to the stand to the stand
yeah please wait I want to hello
I'll come back okay wait wait
[Music]
yes we have fauna okay
fauna
congratulations
okay we're just gonna be doing a light
interview today so I want to hear about
uh your preparation a little bit you
know did you uh prepare or how far did
you prepare and then prepare I'm worried
now then maybe I try hardened too much
but I thought I don't I don't know
Pokemon very well so I was like I have
to make every preparation possible yeah
excited Eevee train my mom's
nice nice nice nice nice well uh it's
not uh it is not in the rules that you
cannot even or IV train no Ivy train I
mean I mean I guess just like get born I
guess or bottle cap it's not in the
rules that you can you utilize your
Pokemons very well and the RNG gods were
blessing you
leading you to victory so and then you
chose cover code and what was your item
what was your other item
um good question
good question yeah what is it
what was it what was it it was the other
one the queer amulet aquarium yeah I
think like I saw that and I was like wow
this girl's prepared I just Google what
are the best hair amulets come on and
then I picked the ones that I already
had ah very nice very nice I think it's
kind of cute that we have matching
Pokemon though yeah I'm the baby the
baby party yeah a little tea party and
then halfway through the tea party was
over so we're like you know what let's
get this over with and
she defeated me anyways fauna
congratulations
please hold it with please hold it with
I don't know Happy Feelings yeah
I'm very grateful to have this trophy
yeah you can put it on your head you can
put it besides you have to uh what is
your your comment about this trophy
please
[Music]
a very cute best girl best girl best
girl indeed best girl for best metronome
user winner let's go yeah let's go
okay fauna congratulations you are the
winner of this tournament please uh keep
this Trophy and I don't know any last
words you want to say to the chat and
the last words I mean any message
[Music]
um Cobo is a very good good luck charm
ing
[Music]
she was a good luck charm you know we
had Pokemon items but the most important
item was there I guess
thank you so much fauna for thank you so
much
[Music]
is for everyone
oh oh we all got the plushie yeah the
plushie is for everyone
so you yeah so you get the plushie I get
the plushie and then everybody gets the
plushie
I have distributed it uh to everybody so
if you want to use it anywhere then it's
fine okay okay okay
thank you so much and big big big thanks
to the participants who have
join the tournament I know you know you
guys are very very busy but thank you so
much I'm very very grateful that uh I
could do this I couldn't you know I
couldn't what English I don't know I
can't do this without you guys possibly
thank you so much Kobo for willing to
become a co-host it was a refreshing
experience and I hope you guys enjoyed
the
tournament and I guess so that is it uh
for today uh anything else did we forget
anything hmm
oh yeah
guys yeah guys guys guys a little off
topic yeah guys but whole idea right now
is doing a hibana so it's kind of like a
simulation of like Japanese Festival
event and yesterday we did day one and
then after this we still have day two
okay so for those of you who are
interested please visit us you know um
is already day one but we still have
more people day two yeah yeah okay guys
thank you so much for watching thank you
so much
[Music]
battle please don't forget to tweet with
hashtag enxid metronome battle for what
you think and stuff like that okay I'm
very very glad I could have this
opportunity and thank you for everybody
who participated thank you for you guys
so much let's have something else like
this something thing fun you know
sometime sooner or later okay
and
um
[Music]
foreign