foreign
[Music]
thank you
Christmas
[Music]
thanks
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
oh
no
no Christmas although we can act as if
Sunday is Christmas because that's when
I'll do
Christmas karaoke
[Music]
hello hmm
ah
thank you for coming to uh
Super Chat reading stream yeah I didn't
tweet it out until now because I thought
oh well
Super Chat rating stream the people who
want to come to that kind of stream
they look at my schedule anyway and then
they'll be there they'll be there
whoever wants to be here we'll be there
[Music]
there's what's playing now in the
background sounds familiar to you um
[Music]
yeah they remixed Sparks the midnight
version
I really did I tell you that I didn't
know that that was happening no one told
me
so weird nothing told about it but I'm
happy I was like
always hoping that maybe someday they
remix a song of mine
and this one's um
very nice to use as a background music I
think so this is actually perfect it's
like a it's like a nice birthday present
even though it's not my birthday is
oh the swear it fades out huh that's how
it fades out
eh
I wonder if they don't have like a like
a loopable version
just realize now that it fades out like
this hmm
well it isn't there Loop eh I mean you
could probably if you know how to edit
stuff like this then you can probably
Loop it yourself
probably has some
some livable Point somewhere
but
be too impatient to do that myself
I might ask but yeah
I've been trying to not contact General
because I think she's uh on a very very
very very very very rare leaf
for like
two days so trying to not contact her
even though there's been things on my
mind
I don't wanna I don't wanna
I don't wanna like bother her right now
Leaf yeah l-e-a-f exactly that's what I
mean yes because she's on the leaf yeah
she's standing on the leaf right now
like a frog there yeah yeah yeah she
turned into a frog that's exactly what I
mean thank you for making it very clear
[Music]
yeah nature
nature called her and she was like I
have to return to Nature oh sure
the Frog version of genma
oh Lily patch but
also I'm sure that frogs don't only
exclusively sit on lily pads I'm sure
that frogs have set on other things than
lily pads before you lose [\h__\h]
oh man
what is this banter frogma
[Music]
actually frozen leaves yeah this is
shortly frogs and leaves
uh
how you guys doing hmm
if there's no Lily but they just
levitate exactly
why are you like walking around in front
of my office huh you're making me
nervous
YouTube
he's looking at me
you got something to say
to my face
doing pretty good doing great I'm sick
I'll get well soon trying to get ahead
of you and get engaged yeah go go
don't have much time
cold oh hi hi chunky is entering the
room chunky oh hi if she has jumped on
the table oh you want to take a sit
if you sits you fits or fits use it yeah
you can sit here there's space for you
smoothie was sitting here yesterday
you wanna keep me company really they're
so sweet I did lock the door oh she's
sitting exactly Which movie was sitting
yesterday
and between my monitor and my keyboard
hi cat how long are you gonna stay there
you're not as
as patient this movie is
hahaha
ah she's a sweetie potato
[Music]
yeah Final Fantasy even if I have
interest in playing it
doesn't mean I can play it on stream
so it's not not the problem of whether
or not I want to play it there's a new
one coming out in June
wow
new new game
unfortunately I don't think that will
happen
I would if I could
oh you're gonna do a sit or you could
YouTube
I had to cut so much hair out of her but
she's still like if you look at her you
wouldn't notice that anything's missing
even though I cut so much
Atlas happens where Square can too
that's interesting that Atlas happened
before Square happened
that interesting
even though I mean Japanese members have
been playing
Square Enix games
interesting situation
haircut yeah she's still fluffy
nuts didn't have huge impact well no I
mean
I I mean a lot on her looks yeah not on
that but I do think they have an impact
like
probably feels itchy when she has knots
a little bit painful
I still feel like a tiny one here on
your chin we're gonna cut that letter
okay
how many true crime videos did you
watched since yesterday not that many
I watched probably more
um
what's his name
I think Max fosh
you know I've been I've been I really I
really think
Max fosh yeah
he's so silly and so funny
you guys know his videos they're so good
just so sweet ah he made that one video
where
um it's like a prank where he like
um uh rents a piece of land that's
visible if you fly into uh Gatwick
Airport
yeah and then you look at the wind and
you see what he put there like huge huge
writing welcome to Luton Airport
which is a [\h__\h] airport the shittiest
airport in England yeah oh bye-bye
chunky monkey or that guy yeah that guy
and I watched that one I haven't seen it
until today
and then a bunch more with one of the
Elon videos no that's that's another
person but they're friends and they're
similar they're both like
British guys who make similar type of
videos they're like high quality and
really good and so funny it's like huh
best
YouTube videos
on YouTube
my watch is so cute yeah he he wanted to
become a member of the royal family just
for a moment
so he looked for her he looked for uh
any any ties any fans or ties to royal
family and then he found someone one of
his fans had Ty who like what had Royal
Blood in him
and so well he was a guy but they got
married anyway and it's so funny and so
cute they got married for like 43
minutes and and then and then he gave uh
like some random street food place the
Royal seal of approval or something like
that
and then they got an annulment because
apparently they couldn't get
um divorced which was a stressful moment
he realized that
that videos good video the him Max Flash
and Zach alsop are currently my favorite
YouTube channels
they both make those damn good videos
yeah
his taxes went up during those 40
minutes
ah well in hindsight they didn't go up
because he got an annulment right so all
good
I don't tend to put channels
yeah currently not watching them 10
though he's not he's not putting up
anything that's interesting to me
she's playing some weird ass horror game
or whatever I don't give a [\h__\h]
ah
oh yeah what do you know what
how I talked about me watching the
murder interrogation videos
now apparently that clip of
which that part was just a a filling a
filler
for the oh I talked to gouda and she's
okay clip
but that clip went into the recommended
videos of mummy when she watched and she
messaged me she was like look out of
nowhere she's like hey I saw that clip
do you know this channel
which one was it again uh which one did
she say
I didn't even know JCS stands for Jim
can't swim but apparently Muma is also
into those videos
but then I I actually didn't reply since
but I wrote her a big wall of text like
oh yeah I know that when I'm watching
that one and another one and this is
like the current way this is the most
shocking one to me like this and this
and this didn't have happened and what a
[\h__\h] idiot oh my God unbelievable
crazy [\h__\h] out there right
yeah I I unloaded my current obsession
textile
for
letting me know that she's interested in
it too I thought I need to share now
maybe instead of uh girls talk what I
should be doing is
crime murder
uh
interrogation inspection talk with Gouda
and lume me
so what's your favorite crime
but it's kind of
[Music]
um it's a difficult topic to talk about
because
somehow it's fascinating when it
shouldn't be and I don't really want to
obviously I don't think those kind of
people deserve a platform right
obviously so
um episode 2 murder
it's so weird to like even laugh about
something like that so let's stop
because that's like really weird but I
mean
yeah it's weird how something like that
turns into entertainment if it's
fictional like on Netflix or whatever
you know okay I guess that's
Entertainment but
the only one
who fights those things somewhat weirdly
entertaining
but like not entertaining in like a
hahaha so funny like um Family Guy or so
kind of late
it's more like
entertaining because
it's just crazy to know that something
like this really happens and it's not
just fiction
and then how how they get caught because
I think that is called schaden Florida
that plays into this is shot in Florida
uh was that in English
was that the word that only exists in
German I must be in English too
wait you guys understand what I'm saying
it's German though so uh wait that
there's really no word okay but you
understand so it's basically I'm just
like
happy for someone else's
humiliation and pain
[Laughter]
Urban right so I guess
I guess you know just as being served as
soon
satisfying
foreign
oh man what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] is
this
sadism I
[Music]
as the official translation of
schadenfreude no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no you can't get that one through
it's not sadism
anyway so apparently that's what I'm
bonding over with these days
but better than not bonding at all right
better than nothing
[Music]
is
but no it's not really I mean that's not
really the only thing it's just one
small thing that came up
um but
I'll talk more about
me and Kura
and India
soon
[Music]
they told me they wrote
something on members but I'm gonna wait
until the
say it publicly because I don't want to
be the first one to publicly say it
even though yeah probably already a lot
of people know but I'm not gonna say it
well if you're not really curious and
you don't know then you might want to
get their memberships
[Laughter]
no they no it's not about leaking
membership stuff they told me it's like
at least Ina told me oh it's okay you
can talk about it but that's kind of
weird thing only mentioned in the
membership so I'm not gonna say it
go get their River ships
also get my membership while you're at
it
[Music]
don't sell strategy what a deal you can
get free
because I'm not giving you any of them
free
way ahead of you
[Music]
such value thank you I mean I'm actually
gonna do a members member stream next
week too because obviously there were no
membership streams for like what three
weeks or so
so I want to make up for it by having
like two in a row
[Music]
um
although I guess
the next week one would already be next
month right
when when does the month end
student Tuesday so if I do it like on
Monday or Tuesday then it's still
technically in the same month
oh membership
thank you
thanks for the gift of memberships it's
not like there was the one thing that
you needed to see on my membership board
though but but you can get well since
you just became a member you can get
that free membership wallpaper for this
month
check out the community board
you kidding recently too oh
[Music]
oh my God
congratulations
[Music]
nice we want new kitty too but already
hands full with current kittens
always feel like I am need to cuddle
them as much as possible
I'm so busy with cuddling
so what we're doing today is reading
super chats and hopefully getting
somewhere with it tonight I even turned
off the super chats
I even turned them off no I didn't get
to meet Kelly's cat
and no time to visit or or like I was I
guess already gone when she got the cat
um but seems like she's got a
she listens to my tweet
I was like hey Kelly then you should get
a second cat so you have two cats one
plus one is two
on Twitter and uh yeah will you be
visiting her when you come back um I'm
not gonna let someone take the chance
from me too
visit her I might even sleep over just
in the hopes that the kitty cat does
well although when they're that young no
they should let me sleep but I hope that
maybe they will sleep on me
if I sleep in her
on her sofa
maybe they will bond with me and sleep
on on top of me
I'm not gonna let someone take that
chance from me
sleep over not with Cali sleep over with
the cats
that's a cat sleepover
I'm a style Cat take over
I remember when my kitties were like
kittens
they would sleep on top of me they would
like sit and sleep on top of me
whenever I was sitting or sleeping
and I missed that they stopped doing
that when they grew up
they still always are close to me and
they still sleep right next to my head
but they don't sleep on top of me
anymore
um
so sad
my old boy still does it every day yeah
I'm hoping that one of my cats get like
really old maybe they'll do it again
because when cats get older they get
mellow
and more even more cozy
maybe they'll do it again
or at least like you know they might be
a bit too big to sleep on me but maybe
maybe they would just like become lab
cats that I'm still not giving up on
that hope
um
still not giving up
[Music]
oh she sucks on your finger or that's
actually kind of I think a little bit
concerning my cats did that when they
were kittens
and I looked it up
and I mean as a as a kitten it's still
kind of normal but as an adult can
I don't know about that but who knows
I mean it's like just uh
although it's kind of weird it's kind of
weird
bye-bye
[Music]
don't King Shame the kitty
Kitty at heart
decided to enter the room again hello
hi walking up to me
hi
oh yeah you want to come up here again
you're welcome to do so
can't make up your mind
thanks for the gifted memberships to
every guy every guys
everyone
when you want to say guys and everyone
at the same time
oh no she's just sitting down there
just just you know
hi every guys
I actually doesn't sound that weird
sounds somewhat natural
dying
[Music]
it's very
okay she was just saying hi she wasn't
really trying to scratch it
she's just reached up to the armrest
tried to say hi
[Music]
you want to sleep on smoothies spot on
the Big Orange beanbag
can she take the stink
happy birthday mud arcade oh can't send
the Super Chat
happy birthday
congratulations
age is dooming upon you every day we get
older
and you will eventually
cease to exist but today is not the day
[Laughter]
what I'm just telling the truth
it is what it is
you're welcome
it's just what what I tell myself when I
get older another membership gifting
thank you
you good though right monarchy
[Laughter]
no no sadness
yeah you have to realize you're mortal
but it's good if you know that because
then you will cherish each day more
chill out
yeah yeah I'm chilling I'm back to tat
lasso
as well almost finished like maybe like
three four more episodes
of tallasso
it's really cute good show
what
and where's the rest of that story huh
I can you post the same thing like three
times when I'm I was scrolling all the
way no four times by now I was scrolling
all the way up to find the first part of
that story because I don't know what
you're talking about
but it's just always the same comment
I'm going to give last of us a try
um wasn't planning on it
or is that even from which publisher
[Music]
Sony oh I don't know how we stand with
Tony
oh your cat's sucking on your finger ah
ah cute
[Music]
I asked Lena for you both to play
medicine
kind of like Mortuary assistant I think
it would be a good time
no that sounds absolutely terrible
terrible idea
[Music]
Oh Oh you mean the show oh I never
watched the show
foreign
well I still don't want to do them I
don't want to play them
among them
you don't call it a chicken for no
reason [\h__\h] you frog you're not much
better
frog you like a chicken
you're slimy
Timmy and your green most of the time
thank you so much better than me
[Music]
oh
um
big cup of tea
right in front of me
I did that thing again by the way today
this is just a dancer stream so far
we need a warm up you know I'm just
trying to warm up
it's kind of like weird to just go
straight into the Super chats you know
what I mean
but I did that thing today again and uh
too good to go thing this time I didn't
do a supermarket I did a restaurant
enough for three bucks I got like a
full meal with a starter and a main
course
and I mean it wasn't like a fancy meal
at all but it was good it was good
yeah
three bucks
I mean free Euro
I'm about three bucks I think someone
around that
green arrows somewhat something like
that
why let me see though
I oil in USD
it's 3.27 bucks
hmm
it is a good deal
box how big a meal we talking about size
but
I ate it for lunch but I only ate half
because I I was thinking maybe
maybe half is enough
I could have probably eaten the whole
thing
but then I was considering maybe I'll
eat just half an hour and a half later
and now I'm not sure because I was also
planning on cooking hello fresh later
seems like I have forgotten to to Cho to
choose the recipes for this week
so
they sent me some stuff that I would not
really have chosen myself but oh well
oh well well something with mushrooms
I'm just gonna leave out the mushrooms
and something with avocado so I guess
I'm maybe I'm just gonna leave out the
avocados
and then another thing well that was I
think fine
overall
[Music]
nothing spicy I don't think it's spicy
I don't think so at least at least not
spicy
yeah I don't like mushrooms for avocados
I'm like
no why
why avocado why why has like no texture
it's just mushy and black
The Taste is
so Bland blah
blah
I know everybody loves avocados
[Music]
avocado on toast I never had that
thank God there's some people who don't
like avocados
I beg to differ
[Music]
my meow meow
what is it hmm mommy's streaming
[Music]
like a dog
chunky wonky
[Music]
before it's chunky monkey
today only chunky wonky is showing me
her face on stream
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] avocado shake what ew
yeah it was just a little bit maybe I'll
put it in it look it looked like it
wasn't like
that much avocado
the rest of this nation is exactly like
Yukio oh really
[Music]
I have to say that avocados are
delicious
I'm sorry I know you guys use it a lot
in your cooking right
sorry
avocados are bland exactly
now you're not a ghost you're a real cat
ah she's like what I'm a cat
what what do you mean I'm a cat what is
what even is that
[Music]
how far
sir are you aware you're a cat
oh yeah okay I guess I'll start
I don't wanna
get pretty far today
[Music]
do you guys
oh she's in reach she's in reach
Ed
just trying to escape I got there with
my feet
um
oh yeah where do I have to start reading
do you know
foreign
[Music]
can't escape
geographer
Geo part two
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
try to finish it
like me
why did you give up on it
I finished it
me guessing where the states were
it hit
wow wow wow
100 accurate
of course because I am also American
my map of America
yeah
I think that should be introduced in
geography classes in America
[Music]
now don't skip my finale until you play
yourself that means like you're never
gonna watch it
because you're gonna push it and like I
am gonna play in this sometime and
they're gonna push it endlessly and push
it and push it it's not gonna happen if
it didn't happen until now then is it
ever gonna happen probably not be honest
to yourself stop lying to yourself
oh no do you want to go
no it seems like she wants to go
no don't go
okay
uh with
[Music]
um
soon no cat in my lap
I will now start
reading doing the unthinkable reading
super chats
what on Earth
got you this
question
for the pinky Gilmore Girls episode 13.
how tough is it for you to throw out old
stuff or nice look Lord with the
girlfriend that study group snack plate
had 20 pop stars evil parents starting
to Mellow I hate those other Roots knobs
yes yes yes of course and then actually
I think there was like a karaoke uh
stream that I did
uh close to after me watching
re-watching the 13th episode of gamble
girls which is why I did end up putting
uh The Bangles song into that karaoke
because watching that episode reminded
me of that song's existence so that was
actually connected
yeah I've let chunkers go and she's now
free to roam my table
laughs
yeah I sang it I don't know which kind
of looking at once but it couldn't have
been that long ago
I'm gonna sit there okay
sitting on the side table free range
chunkers
okay
she threw my switch off the table
well you sweat when why is it on the
table
be somewhere more secure
you always have to make way for the cats
not the other way around
yeah not the other way around
yeah she wants to be near it's so cute
anyway about throwing out old stuff
um I think I'm way better at it now than
I was like five years ago or so
yeah
but like I think I kind of was forced to
um throw out a lot of things many times
because like moving from Japan to
Austria and the other way around many
many times and then within Austria
moving many times over the past I don't
know how many years
um
but especially the international moves
you know can't bring much
yeah
with you so
had to always get rid of many things
so I used to have like so much hello
project merchandise
and I don't know at what point it was
but at some point I
got rid of pretty much everything the
only thing I kept was like free and
t-shirts
that I use for pajamas
um
yeah all the merch that I accumulated I
had so much
but then I had to think about it like
well
I don't really
follow them properly anymore because my
favorite group is gone I guess I think
it was maybe after they were already
gone
and in the end whatever I mean t-shirts
I can use but it think about it what are
all the other things gonna be useful for
like pictures and photo books and all
that
and now most of it most of the hello
project merch was
just like collectible
photos they were by the way I think they
did like a gacha system a lot of the
time where you would buy one A4 size
um like photo
and and then it's like gotcha you don't
know which member you get
um
did you sell them I no I didn't I guess
I just
sadly threw it away
[Music]
don't say that Munda you you guys are
never allowed to throw away my Birds no
yeah you bought you you bought that with
your hard-earned money and there's
memories with that I mean we could say
the same thing about all the merchandise
that I had bought but along the hello
project merchandise I'm gonna be honest
was gifted to me
from other fans because I was younger I
didn't have that much money to buy all
that much myself
and then other friends would be like
super nice to me and be like hey take
this like this what about this one
um I didn't spend that much money on it
actually
no you can't you can't throw away the
qawwa merch
no
no Kiana No Good Sister Knight in there
what if I need to make more room for
more kiwawa merch well
that's another story but
why would you no you can't get rid of
from walking home that makes no sense
makes no sense
and she's cute chunky wonky cute
anyway so now I definitely
don't have those problems anymore with
getting rid of things
separating myself from things like I
also got rid of so many Plushies
when I I think it was when I left my old
roommates
apartment
I think that's when I made the decision
that I don't need all this [\h__\h]
plushies
I had a lot of them and I realized oh
this is gonna take up a lot of space in
my
in in all the boxes
I still have like maybe one big alpaca
when I say big I mean really big a
really big one
but besides that in terms of plushies I
have like nothing
um
[Music]
again here I was like what use is a
plushie to me
and now I have these cuddles that are
basically plushies too and they take up
a lot of space on my bed anyway so no
space for the plushies anymore the old
plushies
yeah who needs blushes when you have
cats
foreign
[Music]
kind of surprised
how many Plushies
so many of the whole life Japan members
had in their places accumulated
because like you know
I I I I mean
you know it's
I don't know it's I was really surprised
because we're all like
all old enough to get rid of plushies I
would say
but yeah like Martin had like a million
million different types of the same
character plushie all over her apartment
so big so so so many
and then I thought okay maybe my new
example is a special case but from there
on I visited a lot of other members
places and there are almost all of them
had like a lot of plushies around
I think there was only maybe one member
wait wait
yeah I think maybe Julie didn't have
that many
but her merchandise is like it doesn't
um she has like not plushies but she has
other
things that are in theory merchandise
but you don't even notice that it is a
merchandise of something like it just
Blends in so well
Cali Cali just has a lot of merchandise
everywhere
um no plushies though I think not not
many at least you guys let like a lot of
figures and acural stands and posters
and yeah
thanks for the gifted memberships
[Music]
oh
actually I think
um
maybe it doesn't have that many Plushies
around if I try to think back don't
think she had that many
hmm
and actually one more thing that I was
surprised about is that
I expected
um the members to have like a whole life
merchandise everywhere
but most of them didn't
which
I'm the same actually the only place
where I have some merchandise is
hidden in a Cupboard and some like wall
Scrolls like tapestries in my office
but only in the office yeah Callie
definitely has a lot of them but other
members mostly didn't so
yeah but I mean if you're in if you're
in honolife for like I don't know three
four years or so
imagine if he would put out the
merchandise in your room there would be
like so much of it
and I guess you just tried to try to
control it
um
[Music]
or just try maybe they're just trying to
have their places look like normal
places so that when they have maybe a
normal person a normal friend or so over
who doesn't know what their job is
you know
it wouldn't be so complicated otherwise
you would have to hide everything I mean
we'll have to hide you I guess you could
say you were a fan of whole life because
you don't have to say you are part of
whole life maybe you just have so much
merchandise because you're a fan of
whole life
could always say that
that's why I try to keep it in the
office
if I put out some
the Plushies are helping with
soundproofing I guess so yeah
if I have some merchandise that I want
to put out on display it's in my office
because then I'll just if I have someone
over who I don't want them to see you
something of it I'll just close the door
say this room you may not enter this
room you know
[Music]
hmm one fourth of my room is already
full of whole emerge
damn
myself one fourth is really a lot
don't open that door
[Music]
yeah yeah I can always say I'm just a
fan but yeah
but then I don't want to explain to
someone who doesn't know whole life I
don't really want to explain them what
it is
imagine me explaining it and them
looking it up and then you know it's
kind of awkward you just told them
you're a fan but
they might actually like watch some
videos and then uh
[\h__\h]
now they know maybe they find out
oh did I tell you guys by the way
speaking of found out
[Music]
that friend
did I tell you about a friend you know
who likes the Cali song that I did
by now knows
the oblivious deadbeat I wouldn't call
that person a deadbeat anymore because
they seem to try to stay away from whole
life for a long time now
[Music]
um
yeah it it wasn't really
through my own actions though I did not
tell him
I did not tell him
but eventually
and
[Music]
it happened
and I was like wait since when do you
know I didn't know that you know I would
have liked to know that you know by now
that's that's weird
I don't know we don't really talk I
don't really have a connection
we don't talk and uh
yeah so and it was just that one time
where I realized oh
you Naro hotel okay
good to know yeah it's more of a friend
of a friend
um
I don't really
converse much
with that person anyway I should read
super chats
yeah no I wasn't asked for an autograph
no no
never never
[Music]
it's not about being respectful we don't
even talk there's nothing
nothing no need to be respectful and we
don't talk
[Music]
um
hey thank you for the pinky finally
reached two years of membership thank
you for countless hours of entertainment
you give us I hope this proves that I
will never get bored of you
[Music]
I don't know if that's a proof the fact
that you did stay for two years means
that it could be any time now
that you leave
[Music]
you are definitely my one and only ocean
so I think you can let me out of the
YouTube room now
hey
no no no no if you if I am your own she
that would hopefully mean you respect my
wishes and my orders so when I say you
have to stay in the usual room then you
will serve your sentence as long as
it takes
so you will hopefully respect that right
and stay
thank you for two years
of supporting me dance
soon
I was waiting
for that thumbnail you're gonna make and
you never made it it's okay now I don't
need it anymore but I was weird I was
like kept on like checking uh did he
make something I didn't he said he was
gonna make something
[Music]
yeah I kept on checking
it was you were pushing for other kfp I
wanted to see your attempts though
and what was I gonna do Aya
[Music]
you need to make up for it
for the time
you have kept me waiting
but
I'm going back to your profile and
updating it and looking through the
optical uploaded images like did I miss
something oh yeah I found I thought he
was gonna make something
um
kept my hopes up there man
got a makeup for it
[Music]
no not structure
I was waiting
no not not stock job
at least obsessed
there's nothing to do with that
[Music]
thank you
she's just sitting on my side table the
whole time so cute
I saw a clip I like
yesterday or so that you made I was like
ah it's actually a good Clipper why does
he never make clips of me
I'm not trying to pressure you or
anything
not at all but yeah a nice nice clip see
you make
um
hmm
[Music]
yeah yeah
you've got nothing to clip right now
right
you ain't busy right now right
okay
no knife
and Matt's the machine thank you
[Music]
oh
oh I watched me on you meals New Years
the Divine Nation on tarot cards however
meal only did the Divine Divine Nation
for Japanese who knows too bad Ian and
ID were left without predictions we need
a fortune tell for Ian and ID right away
see I did this last year right I did the
fortune telling for everybody last year
whoever called in I didn't do it this
time because while I was I couldn't I
was busy anyway
but yeah no fortunes for us chunkers
just made us sound like
like an old man
are you good
hand reading stream oh yeah right I want
to do that this year too it will take me
some time though to learn uh the basics
again
of hand reading
um
do you know how many sports fans you
angered with your Massachusetts pick
it's a pretty huge rivalry between your
pick and the actual state
what where where I put Massachusetts is
a place that they uh
have a rivalry with
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's funny
oops oopsie actually
as a Texan I agree that we should get
Oklahoma far away from us
[Laughter]
interesting I don't understand these
issues you guys have but it's funny to
read
some internal issues
Murphy
passive Destroyer says are you renaming
the states renaming the states or are
you trying to get them right I'm so lost
here I was trying to get them right
thank you soon rough times thank you
soon absolutely
[Music]
connection
is that something that like is baiting
me to say something it almost sounds
like it's failing me to say something
because it doesn't make any sense like
this
me
[Music]
I'm not sure it doesn't sound like
anything though
right
say it in your head first oh it's too
late now
maybe like
[Music]
is that something
time for nothing
um
what are all these weird super chats
they're all testing something
why why
Dominican Cruise sanctions
did I just ask you guys if you were able
to Super Chat some reason
but there's so many
all of them were like tests yes yes
I didn't need that many tests one would
have sufficed
silent Nerf gun kitchen alcohol
up
uh
[Music]
Bob Dylan Daniel
thank you for the pinky
hmm
Happy New Year
[Music]
I can't believe it's a different year
now man
it's always so stressful the moment it
turns December it like wait a second
what the [\h__\h] one month left
kind of stressful is there anyone who
doesn't feel stressful whenever like a
year ends stressed out
to anyone who doesn't feel like that
[Music]
um
no okay okay then we all have the same
problem Hallelujah
thank God
seems like pretty much all of us
I'm relieved actually
um I've accepted my demise
foreign
[Music]
s before I can get stressed yeah but
then even afterwards you're like wait
what the [\h__\h] is fine
I wanted to do more things
[Music]
um
why stress about it well because
makes you realize
that time goes by so fast and you need
to make the most out of it but there's
only so much time you have
on Earth
think about it that's so stressful
we only got one life at least I know
unless you have like different ways of
beliefs but
usually
you only have one life and then
hmm
you want to make the most out of that
one life
oh
and you would think that right now
a job I have now I even more so I should
make the most out of it
[Music]
and wanna accomplish things
while I am in whole life and yeah
the problem is that streaming long hours
every day makes the time pass by so fast
too and there's not like much like I
like you know I wake up and start
streaming or I have breakfast and it
starts streaming
and then I'm done streaming and I'm
tired from streaming maybe I have some
energy to cook
much a little bit of Netflix and fall
asleep to you know
Netflix
trying to
like log out of work brain
it's called having a job well yeah
I know it is a job
[Music]
and then there's there's more that I
need to do though in order to accomplish
all the things that I want to accomplish
while I'm doing this
more than just streaming like streaming
is just like the surface the the top of
the the tip of the iceberg
[Music]
challenge you have a job that can bring
you Joy
it doesn't only bring me joy though
there's also times where it brings me
sadness
much sadness
and stress and pressure
no not only joy but I am thankful for
having a job that does bring me joy at
all because some people have jobs that
don't bring them any Joy or some people
don't even have a job well you know
that's also a problem
[Music]
speaking of
when I came home
to my brother was I so did you like do
anything while I was gone
in terms of like applying anywhere I'll
look for an apartment or something and
he said no no she's chilling and I was
like
um
[Music]
I'm a sister his youngest sister I don't
want to be like hey you should do this
and that
but this was
like what he was planning to do well I
was gone and I said well you have like
one more
period of time one more chance I guess
next time I'm gone
when you take care of my cats again
but
wow
[Music]
at least he was honest
I mean it's it is time sensitive issue
too because
well it's his business but in the end
it will become either mine or my mom's
business
you know
because he will need a place to stay and
he will need some
money to stay afloat
so you know
yeah it's hard to give an older sibling
life advice yeah or anyone like you know
that's older than yourself
who's related to you
can't
doesn't don't feel like I'm in the
position to tell them anything well like
I mean even when I feel like I I would
be in the position
then I still feel like
um if I say something they're gonna be
like what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] no
I'll mind my own business as long as as
long as your business doesn't become my
business though
oh well
[Music]
um
I can hire him as a maid
no no I don't think he would like
that job he has Michael
a certain
what's the word
specialized specialization
and that's what he's like
uh looking in
and I don't think that's that's like a
field where it's difficult to get a job
he said so too
it should be no problem to find a job
he'll quickly find a job
he said it's not like a field where one
struggles to find a job
but it seems like he did not apply
anywhere while I was going for a whole
month
[Music]
but hopefully next time
I will not tell you what he does
celebrate
DJ Spooky Fish Tank
[Music]
yeah I I wish him luck and I hope he
finds something he likes you know but
um as I just said you know I'm stressed
about time ticking
for other reasons but but that's the
thing normal time takes yeah
time is ticking
that's good
thank you
I think okay let's say that you wake up
to fight
I see you again
that's moving chunkers are cheetahs
you have been sent to a world where
house cats don't exist and people have
domesticated cheetahs instead
are you upset or can you accept these
changes
um
well I mean I have to accept it because
assuming I can't go back to my world
yeah very important and highly relevant
questions
this is the least weird one I've sent
yeah
I was worried he would say like you wake
up in a world where your cats don't
exist at all that would be a very
disturbing
world to think about
well
I mean if they're domesticated I guess
it works but
I will definitely miss their old
body I'll buy my chunky monkey
[Music]
yeah well thank you for this
deep question
cheetahs are pretty chill I've heard
even if they weren't it says here
domesticated cheetah so
they are they are made to be chill at
this point at least
um
[Applause]
decently cute but they're not fluffy
enough and they're too big they're like
you know I don't like like really really
I mean it's not like I don't like but I
feel like pets that are at least the
size of a cat are easy to cuddle with
and then as I've talked about before
like a hamster is so tiny and there's
like barely any surface to pet and even
if I pet I'd have to pet with a finger
not even my hand but my finger
but then a cat as big as a cheetah
is
or all ready too big
how do I
although never mind I guess when you
come when you can cuddle a human you can
also cuddle a cheetah I guess
big as cat though
I guess it works
you can use it as a dakimakura basically
size of a dakimakura
I beg to differ on the hamster Point
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Laughter]
I knew that you would find my statement
problematic
scared of saying what I think in terms
of hamsters
but they are hella cute man I really had
to consider getting one for myself
when I saw those hamsters of no other
senpai
[Music]
you recognize my connections
thank you for the pinky One Direction
please there you go thank you to you to
Nunez thanks for the painting
yeah it's a long time ago I hope you're
here to pick up your donation
sorry it took such a long time we had
many many orders
you know
better late than never
thank you
Patsy Duncan and ayama
[Music]
and I was able to beep it out again
yatta
um
[Music]
okay until guests are done
so
wasn't that bad
had some big tangents in between but
besides that
wasn't that bad next is this one
it's such a good thumbnail
ah
cute
well
I am hoping to do a whole talk with her
soon but
um
we'll see what happens
I I I am worried once again
that I'll have problems scheduling it
but
uh I'm not not gonna give up yet
don't go
um
[Music]
oh I I think I did tell you guys right
that um we were able to like find
another date before a leave to meet and
that's actually like when she got sick
so it didn't happen I didn't meet her in
the end it was very sad
bro
I'm very sad
maybe you saw it I think she posted
about it on Twitter
uh I was like a day when she wasn't
feeling well
um
[Music]
so I'll wait for her
for hollow talk I mean now she's feeling
better but you know that's why why that
last meeting didn't happen
[Music]
and so we're gonna read some chats from
that stream now
[Music]
um
for this one but your Japan trip has
been amazing so far angel I'm sure this
collab will be another Banger and that
money to sleep over certainly one for
the ages have fun
thank you very much
yeah oh the mining one was like a great
kickoff I feel like great kickoff too uh
the endless
of collabs
mudding is so fun too
collab with because she talks so much
but all that excitement you know all
these all these off colors are pretty
short but
not only the Malin one but all the off
collabs in general they were always like
so exciting
and I was always using so much energy
and laughing so much
and and screaming so much that after an
hour I always felt so drained I think
they maybe felt the same so all of them
were really short but yeah but gold they
were really good
I don't know I don't know we'll see what
I tangent about later
why does My Little Pony scare you when
did I say My Little Pony scares me
[Music]
hmm
they're ponies oh yeah My Little Pony
doesn't scare me but
[Music]
maybe some of the fans
foreign
such a weird ass coincidence because I
just watched
not an interrogation but just a like
crime video today
where
um
I don't even want to talk about it it's
so [\h__\h] creepy
oh you know which one
yeah where the guy was a huge My Little
Pony fan
that's all I'll say
huh
what
what no that's not no that's not it what
the [\h__\h]
I know what you're talking about
[Music]
don't know what you mean
yeah let's move on but it's not what you
guys are
some some of you guys are thinking about
no oh my God
what the [\h__\h]
no please let's move on
thank you cup episode
[Music]
oh
God
thank you for the pinky
[Music]
hmm
uh
so cursed so much suffering
Christopher's back but that's got a new
kid named Africa oh
every year my mom and I used to watch a
version of Alice in Wonderland where
Sally true first but bad
played the tiger tiger what's the tiger
lily
she looks so different in Gilmore Girls
yeah
Alice in Wonderland
uh what was it
Sally truth is Sally
first that flower
I haven't really remember that part
that's
oh that looks like it was a long long
time ago and she
yeah was much younger and
looked definitely very different back
then wow
can I see that
huh I guess
damn
it's so interesting
seeing some people like
who who are in the media for like
20 30 40 50 years
60 years maybe even see how they age you
can see them
and compare bam and you can only see how
they age you also see like how the
quality of movies
change and improve
and how fashion changes everything to
him
the time movement is documented
it's really cool
[Music]
cool
thanks for the pinky it's finally
happening god dog and Tanto together at
last I'm so happy oh that just mean
Conan gonna know I watched another bird
woman please don't read this to her
tangent oh don't worry it's so late I'm
so far away from her she will never know
she will never know
[\h__\h] Amazon
such a good time
it was like a really stressful couple of
days around that time
because I think
it was like
isn't it like the day after
was it immediately the day after my I
met money senpai
because I think I slept over
and then during the day I had to do some
stuff
maybe I was
Studio or something like that
was really busy and then
yeah then afterwards I went to Kona
place so
sleeping in a different place than
working and working working and then
going to Kona place for off collabs
very busy but I had such a good time
about that but because of that uh I was
so tired
so after the collab
um we
sat down
yeah to watch Netflix and Netflix and
chill on her couch and and
we were under one big blanket and then I
was like
cuddling and oh she was kind of like
more of like a in a boyfriend position
because she had her arm around me
and she was like you touching touching
my shoulder stroking petting my shoulder
my arm and all that
sinking more and more into the couch
which meant more and more my head was
going from like around her shoulder to
more like
the lower and the softer area
I had one problem though you know I
didn't you know about my
[Music]
when I
try to stay calm
you know that's why I don't want to like
sleep with someone in one bed at
sleepovers but
how I uh like get these
muscle I don't know muscle pains and all
that so I was feeling that the whole
time was like oh this position is so
uncomfortable I want to move I want to
move but I don't want to move too much
because then maybe she'll feel like oh
is she uncomfortable let me let me like
just
get rid of my arm and all that
so I was like laying there we were
enjoying
um Netflix but I was enjoying this time
so much but at the same time it was
suffering because my body was in so much
pain and eventually at some point I
couldn't take it anymore and I like
moved away from her
a little bit lifted my head and then
just went crack and cracking
changed my position a little bit laid
back there
um
yeah mental Bliss were physical anguish
yeah
but the whole time she was like petting
yeah it was like I was the dog
so you know at the end of the Stream
you know we were talking about uh I need
her to watch Lord of the Rings and she
needs me to watch Star Wars but
obviously that would have been like too
much of a commitment too long in that
evening so we were like thinking Hmm
what should we watch and I was like we
should watch something that you also
haven't seen yet and we were going
through her Netflix and she was like
I've seen all of this before
and then I asked her what what do you
like she said she likes like
um
dark and and creepy I don't know uh
maybe like horror kind of things
and I was like well I don't like that I
like funny and bright things
and then I followed something I was like
wait I have the perfect show that I
really liked recently that is both a mix
of dark and bright and funny
Wednesday I was like I think you will
love this
thank you I love it anyway I I've
already seen it recently like binge
watched recently but I was so up for
watching it another time
so we binge watched like two or three
episodes from Wednesday and they're they
are pretty long I think one is like an
hour or so
um and she really liked it she already
knew um The Adams Family
and told me she likes Adams Family but
she didn't know about this show yet and
she really liked it it was perfect yay
she really digged it
um
yeah it was a perfect match
I think we watched it in English with
Japanese subtitles yeah yeah yeah
because I don't think there's a Japanese
dub I don't think so
step now I'm pretty sure we watch it in
English
yeah it is creepy and then mysterious
spooky everything
she really likes the hand oh yeah when
when the hand appeared I was like oh
she's gonna love this she's gonna love
[Music]
so I think that was the perfect choice
and I'm hoping we can watch more
together
but she might just watch it on her own
who knows
because now I'm gone
I was hoping we could watch more of it
together
yeah
one thing I found was really funny oh
did you hear you have your corner
tangent by the way one thing that I
found was really funny uh
you know I was so shocked about sweater
using audacity now I was also shocked
but kind of like pleasantly surprised by
Corona using Firefox
[Laughter]
because I used to use Firefox for a long
long time too the only reason I switched
to Chrome is because of the extensions I
guess
and eventually it was just kind of like
Superior I guess but I used five [\h__\h]
for such a long time and so according to
using five books I'm like why'd you use
[Music]
Firefox in a long long long long long
long long long time but I do like the
browser
um
good browser yeah they did have
extensions too but Chrome just had I
guess many more
[Music]
Firefox on mobile is fantastic
there's still some people use Firefox
well you're using the same browser there
you go
yeah so yeah well
besides that you know
she gave me that t-shirt I have that
t-shirt now
yeah it's a cute
but kind of like a crop top T-shirt with
uh Disney Motif on it
cute
actually I just asked her for some
change of clothes because I was wearing
you know really warm clothes because it
was cold as [\h__\h] outside
but uh I knew that
you know since the room is obviously
heated and since we're gonna be
streaming and then it's gonna get hot I
knew I was gonna be sweating if I don't
change into some other clothes so I
asked her for a change of clothes but
she ended up giving it to me because she
was like looking for some change of
clothes and then eventually she came out
with this t-shirt and she was like hey I
got this before but I don't think it
suits me I can't wear this so if you
want it you can have it and then I was
like it shows the tummy yeah and all the
worried anyway though and I kept it
because it is kind of cute I guess
um
yeah I took it with me it's mine now she
wanted to give it to me she said she
wasn't gonna use it
hmm
midriff
yeah
exposed to me no I think I was wearing
like a high-waisted Jean so it wasn't
really exposed but
I think crop tops work really well with
high-waisted jeans anyway
especially if you're self-conscious
about your tummy
so
yeah something to remember her bye yay
indeed
um
no oh
so when we after we were done watching
Wednesday you know I was so tired I'm
such a long day and I didn't even sleep
that much you know at Martin's place
anyway because I had to leave her place
really early in the morning
and yeah so it was really tight I was
really struggling to stay awake and I'm
like uh cool now I guess I gotta go I'm
like really tired we're also like
considering me staying but
um well
after staying at someone else's place
already the night before I did feel like
I need to
go back to my hotel
so yeah I left and then we gave each
other like a million hugs again it's
like I don't know we just really
struggle saying goodbye to each other
I'm like Huck and then like oh
and then have never had
a hug
and yes
and she called me a taxi and I was like
I'm not a freaking taxi but she called
me a taxi anyway
so sweet and then I went back and I was
like you know what I'm still kind of
hungry so I went to the convenience
store and you know what I got
you know what I got
there was
there was a hot dog on the Shelf so I
got a hot dog
I took a photo I was like look Courtney
I got a hot dog hot dog it's us
I don't know why but somehow I had a
craving for a hot dog
that moment
yeah I've warmed it up you can warm it
up and tasted pretty decent
a decent convenience store hot dog
I wonder why I feel like I was like
brainwashed by the Illuminati or
something like that because I I can't
explain it otherwise it must have been
something like that
yeah and after that I just kept on like
messaging her hey hey I'm really busy
and I think you're really busy but can
we find another date where we can meet
and like the whole time when we're
trying to figure out something but it
looked so impossible and then finally we
we found one evening where it would work
out but then she ended up getting sick
and then we didn't meet that day
so
um sad
well hopefully next time
[Music]
I had a good time though yeah she's very
touchy she keeps on like
she would she would keep on
poking my
waist or so
and and like you know
and looky looky hey
out of all the off collapse this is the
one where I felt the most
like
um shine not not shy but like
embarrassed embarrassed but
um
red word
flushed flushed Maybe
blasters plaster that's the word that's
lost
because like during one two switch the
game even tells you to look at each
other so the whole time I was trying to
look at each other but at the same time
I would feel so cute
it was hard to look in there
because it's just oh we were sitting so
close to each other like shoulder to
shoulder butt to butt
looking at each other
[Music]
Panic moment every time
foreign
no I can't do that because
you know Noah foreign
[Music]
foreign
that's a difficult situation
it's like a
love triangle but then Cali is just like
she's not even part of the love triangle
instead of Cali
no
no no no no
Square
what is it no I don't I don't I don't
think we need a hookah Monica
I want a
dog collab
that's all I want
anyway
continuing
Patsy Duncan okay
I don't know how to say your name is
[Music]
thank you for the rest of the time
thank you very much
[Music]
thanks for the pink super
foreign
[Music]
thanks for the pinky great stream I
really had fun amazing band I hope you
two get to collab more I hope
well next up we should do hollow talk
right
I hope it will happen
I'm waiting
um
hopefully yeah it will happen will it
will it
no I don't want to do how to talk as an
off collab because
that would make me if
I think I would struggle to focus on the
translation and the whole camera of work
like changing things in OBS Etc
I need my personal space for that yeah
ideally my usual streaming environment
so you know just feel more comfortable
there to do that
um
thank you though thank you GD
[Music]
um for the pinky
thank you soon
[Music]
this Russian Works to make a real set in
a mock-up Studio like one day I didn't
want to do it in 3D animal cap Studio
yeah
[Music]
thank you
um
[Music]
for the red super chat this club has
been a blessing Corona best dog one of
the first I watched live in Hollow and
Chihuahua my favorite lovely doorkeeper
you were so cute together I love seeing
you have so much fun vlogging around
with her I want to see more hot Dogo
plus that was here thank you
thank you so much hours I don't think
I'll do look what
not being like we would need to do a lot
watch ones I don't know though maybe
maybe maybe only one or two but yeah
um
and supposedly she feels the same she
told me too every time when I was asking
her like can we do something again she
was like I feel the same way I want to
meet you too again
um
but maybe if I watch Star Wars
then I can I can alert her to me to
tangent with me about it I don't know or
or
we can still watch Star Wars together
I'm sure she would like every watch of
Star Wars
hmm
yeah she said episode one to three
um
what about episode two
and thank you tragedy
please
and with that these ones are finished as
well time
yo
even though those were pretty fast I
still managed to give you a tangent so
going well so far I would say
next up this shouldn't be
um too many
these ones
there we go
she's read ten times one and I predicted
oh
yeah yeah well well
we're getting there maybe
uh oh yeah this is really short Jacob's
monkey thinking Skye thank you for two
pinkies
one more year passed I still am glad to
meet you you're warm keep making me feel
comfy I love you bucking oh hi Kiana
for real time now I enjoy every moment
with your stream in the past two years
and I will support you continuously love
you my Oshi
oh you've been around for a long time
thank you so much it's really nice to
see a familiar name
donation makes me happy that you're
still here thank you for a wonderful
year let's go on to another wonderful
year
[Music]
for all the time you spend with kiwawa
even though
even though time zone is probably a big
big issue for you but you still are here
so often even live not even a VOD
thank you big thank you
a bucket was coffee right
and now you have to stand on your own
feces again
hybrid
no candy thank you soon
[Music]
yeah yeah I wonder if you played the
game did you try Valkyrie connect Tai
Chi
[Music]
if you did thank you very much
hope you're enjoying it hope you were
able to upgrade make us Ascend by now
19 1087 FBI unusual incidence unit
thank you
foreign
that's it
that's all of those
next up
this one also shouldn't take too long
[Music]
they're doing why are you aware collable
Huawei aware is another one of those
games that can only be played in an off
collab so that was a nice opportunity
hmm
[Music]
um just gonna say that if I don't read
your super chat then it doesn't
necessarily mean that I missed it
for the pinky Gilmore Girls episode 15
both Christopher and Dean like
motorcycles oh yeah nice bonding moment
there I guess
should I be worried for Rory is Dean
going to be the next the new Christopher
Christopher pulled out his cell phone at
Luke's sign says no cell phones
why there's five points I'm liking
Christopher no not because of that even
even Lorelei sometimes pulls out her
cell phone at Luke's right so
but it's fine
I mean he's got his flaws but I think
he's okay he's not that this dislikable
yeah here's a decent decent guy he's
just trying to
um
I mean
I I just have to imagine it might it
must be difficult when you're like what
like 16 or so
maybe he was a little bit older than
Lorelei but you know when you're that
young and you get married and then you
end up even oh you get married because
you accidentally
have a child
unplanned at such a young age and uh
well from there on life is a roller
coaster
I am
I mean he wasn't really part
of
you know
parenting that much but and and that's
obviously also disappointing for Rory
and Lorelei but
you know in the later years he tried to
make up for it so yeah
I don't even know what's been happening
in these shows but then usually you
should watch couple girls to understand
what we're talking about
hahaha
then you wouldn't be so confused
hmm
Cruise
shipment
what is this
you guys were trying to find like a
hashtag for us and you came up with
something but I personally felt like
it's fine
takataka
[Music]
to Tacos
no it's not Hall clock
no I'm gonna get what you mean but
Firehawk is cool yeah Firehawk is cool
too but takataka is funny
it's double takataka
so I think we will go with takataka
because I like it
how about taka from takane and Dashi
from takana
[Music]
or how about AKA from takanasi and never
from um
genius
no no that ain't gonna work nope
foreign
words can truly make a world of
difference and a very well made have
saved a life today
what what did I do so from all of us kfb
thank you so much for all your love and
care what did I do
why what
what did I do did I do something
specific
sounds like I really did something good
okay on Twitter
yeah I don't know
it breaks my heart to see something like
that and I know that
you know other people would just you
know I'll just look over it because too
busy or just don't want to interact too
much or so but I can't and it's also one
of my Vlogs in some situations
that I'm just
too
interactive with my fans my audience
my community
in some ways that can have that really
like stressful outcomes
[Music]
um
because then also some people like
expect
because I try to do so many interactions
with you guys
then when they're lacking people are
like well what the [\h__\h] we now now this
is what's happening she's not keeping up
with their interactions and what is she
doing lazy [\h__\h] or whatever
well no oh that must mean this and that
I'm trying to interpret tape things into
it which aren't even true
um
you know
I really
tried my best to keep it balanced and
all that uh
but for all the people who are really
really really like
um
needy and really wants to be liked on
Twitter that's okay okay I get it it
feels nice to get a like from your
Aussie I get it give let me give you one
tip like
um
one thing
that I've been always like looking out
for more is replies that have several
paragraphs not just a reply that just
consists of night stream
end or
killed and I just wanted short sentence
you know my finger like I will read all
of it but my finger will automatically
push the like button
uh easier
if the Tweet is longer because I don't
know it looks like you put more effort
into it you put more thought into it and
I thought I spent more time reading it
which one was more interesting so you
know hmm
hmm
yeah they're interesting to me
it's just my eyes spent more time with
it and then my finger just pushes the
like button doesn't mean that I didn't
read the other ones and it doesn't mean
that I didn't like the other
like really like the other replies but
you know
if I have to give every single reply a
like then it's never gonna end and you
guys I think maybe a little bit
underestimate how much time it takes for
me to go for social media every single
day I I spend so much time
trying to keep up all those interactions
every day
and you know looking for all the
feedback I get every day
I spent so much time with it
some people think it only takes like a
minute or so to go for all my replies
but no it takes my especially if I want
to read it properly
and ideally I don't want to just scroll
for everything blindly
ideally I do wanna
and create the things at least roughly
so it does take time you know so please
don't don't be sad or don't think too
much about it when
uh you maybe didn't get a like or so but
if you have really really really short
replies then that might be a reason why
you might not be getting so many
um likes
um
but generally I try to
really look at everything
um
[Music]
um please understand I I I'm not a
machine I can't
you know look at literally everything
and I can't reply to everything and you
know
not a machine
I required to call Piano thank you
thank you guys for understanding
thank you
uh
oh yeah where did it come from good
questions
ah from the game of creative yeah yeah
because we were talking about Twitter
and me interacting with
fans
um and that being important to them yeah
yeah but as I said you know it can also
lead to people being unhappy with me not
interacting enough
I try I try I do try my best
yeah
so and especially the link recently was
even more difficult because of Twitter I
don't even know if it's a bug or if
they're purposefully changed it because
I'm definitely not the only one who has
that issue
with the reply it's not showing up in
the reply section anymore unless it's
like a indirect reply which is so stupid
that cannot possibly be like
a future a feature that they
purposefully implemented
because that makes no sense why in my
reply section are there no replies why
are the only replies in my reply section
the ones that are indirect replies
like replies to another person's reply
to me hmm
like think about it logically I mean
Twitter has been doing some weird stuff
recently in the past months but that
doesn't even make any sense like why
would you do that I'm just it's not
logical is it
it doesn't make sense
so that made it difficult to keep up
with it
because even if I go to my actual tweet
and then directly look at the replies
there
not chronologically sorted and there's
no way to chronologically sort them
there so
I I can I would go there once after a
stream and go for everything that's
there at that point at the time but I
can't continuously keep on coming back
and look for new ones especially if
they're not even chronologically solid
but like mixed in between
um yeah and then I have to like look for
the new ones
in the middle of so many old ones
so that sucked and now I'm doing the the
hashtag thing
I'm looking sometimes at the hashtag and
sometimes directly at the direct uh
tweet replies
a little mix of everything
but in the end it's both like not really
helping my usual workflow you know what
I mean
not helping my usual workflow
it's disrupting my work workflow
it's annoying
keep forgetting to put the hashtag in a
direct reply but some people do and I
still I would say I still often catch it
anyway
um
but anyway if you didn't know about it
since a while ago Twitter has been weird
so if you want to reply to me and have
higher chances for me to see your reply
then please use hashtag talk Wawa
um somewhere in your Tweet so that I can
properly
foreign
[Music]
these normal replies without the tattoo
sadly
I even see
Tweed seller not even a reply to me and
not even tag yes I see it all
see it all
[Music]
yeah do you know if your tweets are
filtered by verified user uh I do have
um a column for that yeah
for verified users but
I completely
or almost stop almost completely stopped
using that one
because ever since literally anyone can
become a verified User it's been very um
unhelpful
it was helpful for me to filter out
um and see like any whole life members
replies and uh likes and interactions in
general
and now it's become pretty difficult
again like I can't see of any whole life
members interacted with me anymore
because now it's just everyone
[Music]
so difficult like I want to know
I want to know which member is looking
at my tweets and liking them and
replying
it's hard to find now it's a mess
oh
[Music]
I still like look sometimes
trying to find
some some of them the only ones that
usually stand out to me are Kelly Kelly
likes a lot of my tweets
thank you Cali
[Music]
reply to a tweet of the Vata melino
but is she even is she even verified
because not all whole albums are
verified
[Music]
did I see her replying
let me go to her profile and then look
for tweets and replies
and there it is
oh 11 hours ago oh yeah I think I think
I may have seen that one
the drinks really were very cute
oh yeah actually let me talk about it
can I talk about that for a moment
because
um
I'm kind of supposed to talk about it
and it's at some point in some stream
and I don't want to talk about it can I
talk about it now
okay
[Music]
I don't know where but yeah so I already
posted a tweet about it today early in
the morning I woke up so early what are
you guys not surprised no one no one
like tweeted at me no one did a tsukumi
and we're like okay well you're up so
early again
how long does the second one last oh I
don't know I don't know how long
but it just started so
I think it will go for a while
I'm still sleeping myself
well well well so
um I think how this happened is that I
asked what am I stand by if we can
collab
and then eventually she was like oh I
have this thing and he went do you want
to go there
I'm like oh a chance
to meet
a couple of whole life members all at
once some of them who I haven't ever met
before and eat yummy food well hell yeah
so that's how I made my way into that
group
um nice timing yeah it happened to be
within my stay so perfect pretty much at
the end of it though but yeah
now it's not a collab but this is the
one that I was talking about you know
the big group of people that I will have
food with but
um that wasn't a collab
just as
meeting and eating meeting and eating
the meat in
yeah so I arrived in azuki Senpai was
there already
and
it's so cute I bonded way more about
than I thought I would like out of all
the people there I think I bothered the
most of asuki senpai but that's probably
also just because we were on the same
table and we just got to talk so much
uh
well we talked so much
also my food has Empire so me and Mata
man and for now the same but we were all
on the same table because we were the
first to arrive so we just first sat
down on that table and then
um
[Music]
ironically came last
even though it's her thing
she came last but then yeah because of
that they were sitting on the table
right next to us which was really close
to our table it was really just like
and then like right next to us but they
the tables weren't like completely
attached to ours
so there was some space but it wasn't
like she was far away but still just
because of our tables being separated I
guess we both
like
we're kind of blink regrouped up and
then kept on having our own
conversations on each table you know
what I mean
so to be honest I barely talked with
vatamas Empire
[Laughter]
yeah but there will be other occasions
I'm sure so it's okay
um oh actually so since this one's
already at the end of my trip
um I already did this at
uh an occasion right before I think I
guess it was with um
[Music]
no I don't know whatever I did on like
one or two days before
that I got like extra souvenirs right
I already had to do that like many days
before and that Yakiniku
uh dinner with the team yellow I ran out
of souvenirs even though I brought so
many and then I had to buy new ones
um in Japan but they wear German
Austrian chocolates so
I think that makes up for it so I bought
so many souvenirs already for the team
yellow basically I everyone
that I met for the first time I gave a
souvenir but also some of the ones who I
met for the second time because um in
some groupings I thought it would be
awkward to only give certain people a
gift and then I have to explain why I
didn't give the others a gift so for
some groups I gave like everyone a gift
um hmm
no so
uh then for the for the Shabu Shabu the
Bata Merino I gave I had to go shopping
again because I was like damn it I ran
out of someone needed some kid
so before I went I tried to find that
store again close by
and I rushed over to buy another set of
souvenirs and had them gift wrapped and
all that and then yeah I brought them to
the place to the restaurant
I just wanted to make sure that everyone
gets a present because you know I wanted
to leave a good impression yeah
what did you give them
um uh after I had to like stock up on
souvenirs
I ended up buying everyone one great
dashboard chocolate
and um like a little ladybug
um chocolate uh package thingy then
there were lots of like small ladybugs
inside one package
why the ladybugs it's because I thought
it was cute first of all cute and small
and second of all because here
I don't know you probably do it in other
places too but
um here it's like on New Year's
we like to gift like ladybug chocolate
or whatever because they're supposed to
bring luck on the new year
um
[Music]
yeah
so I included them because it was just
it just turned 20 23 so it was like wow
this fits and then I can tell them about
the fact that this is a thing over in
Austria which will be an interesting
fact to talk about you know a Talking
Tom
big brain holy [\h__\h]
you're not minor waffle because I didn't
have those uh in those shops that I went
to
um
nice ice break up
I mean I didn't even need an icebreaker
I am the Icebreaker
don't need extra icebreakers
no no no
I actually like the ladybug really did
she say so
smug
Ice Ice Baby
yeah so um
[Music]
saw this now
so oh yeah
um
they served us everything because we
like we were able to test literally
everything all the drinks all the food
we didn't order all the food but like
everything important and like all of the
sauces all the drinks and so on so but
this is the main like important thing I
would say this is the lamp on top of it
is a big fluffy uh cotton candy ball
and then what in terms of meat another
thing we ordered because
Senpai really really likes guten this is
a huge plate of tongue look at this
wow
and yeah I can eat it you know I
actually I I think I liked
the guten
more in shabu-shabu form than at
Yakiniku
[Music]
yeah they're really thin sliced
I really have pretty colors
looks nice yeah and you throw them into
the
Hot Pot basically
often Shabu Shabu will have like two
different
like soup faces I guess that you boil
the stuff in but this one only had one
but before you throw all the stuff in
you first have to put the cotton candy
in that's the first thing you put in
when the water is boiling and I had the
honor to do that on our table
and then I I picked up the big cotton
candy ball and it was like bouncy and
fluffy and Light
and then I put it into the hot water I
just dropped it kind of I dropped it and
it immediately dissolved
immediately like the moment it touches
the water it immediately dissolves
logically but it was kind of fun to
watch
and the reason it goes in there I also
originally thought that it's just like a
[Music]
um
like a gimmick
because of her being a fluffy sheep you
know but no turns out
um it's because lamp is supposedly kind
of
stinky
both the
smell and I guess maybe also the flavor
often times
so
the cotton candy the sugar has the
effect of getting rid of that smell
stink hmm
I didn't really smell anything when it
was out there like this
but I guess when you would cook it
normally and eat it then maybe you would
notice
um
so that gets rid of it apparently yeah
it didn't like nothing tasted like super
sweet just because of the cotton candy
it was I didn't notice like if you would
have not told me I wouldn't have known
that someone put cotton candy in there
cold meat isn't easy to smell oh yeah
that might be it um
laughs
anyway this was a lot of meat and a lot
of vegetables I don't even know if this
looks like a lot to you on these photos
but it was a lot especially that plate
so much we were we were eating endlessly
yeah
and yeah we're also snacking on some
potato chips and some fries and all that
on the side
um
and then we dipped the meat and the
veggies and all that into whatever
whatever sauce we had at the time they
have a huge choice of sauces
and I ended up having Guma as my
favorite
I'm not surprised about because I really
like coma in general as a salad dressing
but Kuma uh uh sesame
also really fits well for shabu-shabu as
a dipping sauce so good yeah
[Music]
so much poof
spoof endless poof
we did end up finishing it and then oh
oh Freya said bye requested something at
the end I forgot what it was called
but after we were done with all of the
veggies and meat
she requested some type of like
rice dish
ES
[Music]
foreign
so basically what we served was a bowl
of rice and an egg yolk
[Music]
and
maybe some cheese
Maybe
so you pour the rice into the rest of
the soup
and then the egg all over it
oh yeah finishing the top of the fries
and udon exactly exactly exactly the
other table version
[Music]
and we had the rice version for this
Empire really liked it and I was like oh
[\h__\h] I'm already like pretty full but if
I can do this
surprise
there was a lot of food there
um
but yeah so you pour in the rice you
pour in the egg and maybe some
or something and then you mix it it
becomes a new dish basically
um
um I tried it
and
[Music]
I wasn't that impressed from the taste
but it's edible and like food yeah I ate
like almost the whole thing
thank God because I was like
I'm I'm out of here I'm done
so we finished eating
and the whole time and we were having
like really nice nice Chit Chats about
like um like exchanging
all kinds of like stories from the day
we're exchanging stories about Japan
uh and I was exchanging stories about
Austria and they were like really
fascinated for some reason
about the fact that I had
um that I used to work in
you know
and
h-o-t-e-l before
uh I don't know if I'd fascinated them
so much I told them most of which hotel
they were like oh wow so cool and I'm
like well
I don't really think it matters which
hotel though because it's um
it doesn't really matter
but they thought it was really cool I
don't know why
[Music]
we talked about all kinds of things and
then
and I think I got azuki Senpai really
interested into visiting Austria
really interested
she was really hooked on it
no
no showed her some pictures and so I
don't know if my travels as well
should have some Maldives travel
pictures too
yeah
she didn't know about Maldives but she
was also fascinated by the Maldives yeah
hey
yeah always welcome always welcome
and then after we were done eating and
talking
uh we
um we signed some uh like signing boards
thingies
um
and then and then and then when it was
kind of about time to leave oh before
y'all actually I think we had some
dessert too
not what it was though
oh what
I don't know if I I even ate the dessert
but oh let me show you
these were the drinks there were even
more but so I had that chocolate one
that was Valentine's themed I I said
like oh we should all try to order
different ones so I'm gonna go with the
chocolate one
and you girls try to get a different one
okay so we can take pictures because
we're gonna take pictures right I'm
talking about this right so we should
all have different ones so yeah we all
got different ones and then the the blue
one I tried that one has some gold
leaves on top whoa and some berries and
everything on the bottom has some jelly
and it tasted like I don't know what you
can describe it as but it's like a blue
soda
and then the other ones I didn't try and
I'm not sure what exactly they were but
I think they were all good oh I think
the left one is like some kind of milk
tea with rose petals or something like
that very cute drinks
these were not the only ones you know
they wanted to show us everything so
they also even though no one ordered it
they also brought out these ones
now that one's not neither of those is a
is a beer but I think they were alcohol
I don't think either of those were a
beer though
I think the the left one
you know with the pretzels kind of cute
and it was a float yeah but I don't
think it was a root beer float I think
it was more like Coca-Cola with some
alcohol and then the ice cream and the
right one I really don't know
no idea but those were all like special
time limited new drinks
yeah here you can see oh yeah wait it's
written here ah the one with the
pretzels is energy drink Coca-Cola uh uh
with some alcohol and
oh
is that the one that's the one right the
five number five that's it says Pana
[\h__\h]
I don't know what a Punisher is
is that telling you something guys
I don't know what that is
that wrong
that's so yeah because the other four
drinks are the ones on my right side
clap soda and beer ah ah there you go oh
beer and lemonade but it's something
like that I wouldn't know because I
don't drink alcohol but yeah this is the
menu there's like a special set
uh for 6 000 Yen which is like 50 bucks
you get all of this
which is not one person it's like for
several people you know this is a lot
this is what we had and we ended with
three people that was full but if you
maybe if you have a bigger stomach than
me then it might be enough for two
people
um
it comes with a lot of meat and then the
drinks here we have the uh the names are
cute too the first one is
number three is my soda number four is
uh milk tea that's colored like you
supposed to be a romantic thing
is
close closely not
I'm almost not red panation
don't know what that means maybe it's
supposed to be red normally
and then jingies
as well so reference to Genghis Khan
and then on the bottom you see all the
merchandise you can get which is some
new coasters that are different all of
this is different from the last collab
they had new coasters and uh the clear
files I got them too
yeah so many coasters they had some
other merchandise too like t-shirts and
I don't know a tapestry I think they had
a tapestry I don't know how you get
those if they're available for purchase
but they had them as decoration
hmm
yeah
very funny names yeah and here are some
of the
The Coasters
I got them for free to take home a one
each though not so many these were like
scattered on the table
yeah cute yeah look at that one two
three four next one you're the the
uh clear files but those they look like
A4 but they're actually smaller than A4
I think they were like A5 or so
um
cute I got those too both of them
yeah I want to do like a club like that
too but
you know outside of Japan it's kind of
difficult because
outside of Japan like in Europe or
America
these kind of anime related collabs
they're just not that realistic at least
not foreign decent
scattered chain
restaurants
it was like one local thing that's only
available in one city then it doesn't
even make sense to collab with it
because like how how how
are you guys gonna get there
um would have to be like a chain but the
chains are usually like Untouchable I
feel like
um
yeah they collab in Korea it's
I feel like stuff like this really is
only realistic in the Asian market
unfortunately
hmm
see this working in LA or New York with
a collab with another Cafe
yeah I don't know maybe like a pop-up
Cafe in one big ass City but pop-up Cafe
I don't ever see that happening either
um
I don't know
not giving up yet though but anyway this
was really cute really fun and a good
opportunity to talk to some members I
thought I would be meeting
for the first time but it ended up being
the second time
but uh yeah it was a great opportunity
thank you so much for having me for
inviting me
I bonded a lot with
Senpai and azuki saying bye yeah foreign
[Music]
Hawaii would also be a place to try
yeah but then again you know that's like
so specific like one one place hmm
would be difficult I think for most
people to go there
just just to visit a collab but I guess
you could also just go for the vacation
and then collaboration as well vacation
and collaboration
no oh well so that was a tangent let me
go back to the super chats that's what
we're here for
um
which one which window which tap
what am I reading WarioWare
oh found them okay okay
words of a chance thank you
[Music]
thank you and I appreciate it very much
hope you had a lovely
nobody New Year
and some days away from me because I
wasn't streaming that much did you miss
me you better have missed me
I hope so
is that me
[Music]
ant
um don't don't say you didn't miss me
thank you
of course
miss me or else
always miss the Wawa
miss having koala in my life
[Music]
nice that's what I like to hear thanks
guys
[Music]
very good new phone who this hey
it's me kiwawa
it's me Chihuahua new phone what is
Chihuahua
same kiwawa same old
[Music]
I'm not Chris Pratt
um
Federal Bureau of Investigations thank
you soon
uh Patsy duncast
[Music]
Louie's English is great and you two
have a fantastic chemistry
was totally looking forward to this and
it was awesome hope you guys can make
the whole Tony songs gold happen it
would be amazing it would be uh
why until now like
420 hasn't been pushed by
uh official side
maybe I have to push them to push us
um
this is perfect you have like an
international unit
hmm you can show all good sides of whole
life
with this one naturally created group
[Music]
I think it's uh
perfect
they're missing out
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
get me the all the most important people
of the cover management
um tell them I have a really really
really really really really really
really really really important
meeting that I need them to take part in
from dentists
they're all like taking time and they're
busy ass schedules
think that's something really important
is happening
I think I mean it's not even like
something that would normally happen
that the member does something like that
but yeah and then suddenly I I show up
with my PowerPoint presentation about
why holotoni is the best and needs to be
supported by them
[Music]
maybe I'm maybe you will
maybe I will
important ah thank you
well well thank you Jim Tracy I think
eventually
something surely must happen with
holotori but
give it some more time and I'm I would I
really want it to happen like I I like
horror story you know
and now that I've also finally bonded
Waverly
which took a long time but uh
now we have a connection that I did not
expect at all I think if I would have
known that since the beginning that our
interests in terms of Music overlap so
strongly then I would have probably hit
her up way sooner I didn't know why did
you guys not tell me
not tell me someone should have told me
[Music]
I had a desk photo I don't know about
that I liked her duck and okay I want to
cherish and treasure turducken and I'm
also too lazy to change the picture
maybe I want to have turducken on there
turducken is different from honotoli
tradakin was was one solo Tony now
turducken is just turducken and
turducking on his own to me you know
it's just not like
couple of my most cherished friends huh
I loved her dog and I think turducken is
a compact fun crazy group of silly boobs
um yeah the OG unit we have to see them
separately we're going with OG yeah the
OG
color code is Gen one yeah
yeah yeah maybe see it as that
I like both volatility and turducken but
right now I want turducken on my table
oh imagine suddenly waiters saving me
like a rigid legit food turducken on my
table like I ordered turducket
I don't want to eat them
[Music]
please no
please
thank you this is done
you should try to doctor why have you
had it before
you're talking is delicious are you for
real you had had it before who left her
Dunkin before
I don't believe you
foreign
no way
it's very filling I can imagine because
it's literally
Birds filled into other birds of course
they're filling
[Music]
one bird is enough okay
okay
and next is the super chats from a Super
Chat reading stream to no one's surprise
you know what in hindsight this super
this thumbnail wasn't that bad so I kept
it
you know I wanted to change it but it
wasn't that bad
oh my God this one actually has
a lot of Super Chips way more than all
the ones that I've read so far today
not combined though
but oh dear do you hear my throat
already like dying I was eating a fruit
candy and it's not helping and and hey
what's happening
oh man
next Road candy I'm already struggling
it's only been two hours 41 minutes
[Music]
oh
um maybe maybe the one with the airplane
yeah maybe maybe
okay here we go I'm gonna try my best
there's a lot of things
oh yeah there's a lot of Pinks and rats
in the beginning but it's actually a
number it's not that many it's just the
the total
okay
um
for the pinky game of girls episode 16.
can we put Tristan in the usual room
the dude's whole Playbook is be an
[\h__\h]
Rachel was so hyped as a goddess but
she's no Kiana
you're such a charmer Rory couldn't say
I love you to Dean oh that episode I
feel Dean is overreacting what did you
think
yeah Dean was definitely overreacting
but it was an awkward situation trying
to remember back but I remember
definitely was awkward like he gives her
a car
and they have this romantic moment in
the self-made car at night
sitting in the front seats and he's like
Rory I love you and she's like
what did she say did you say thank you
what did she say no she just left she
panicked and left
um
but I think
didn't she like realize like she does
kind of love him but oh no I don't know
I guess it was just like too much of uh
I don't know
the first time she's been
confessed to like that was so direct and
he was just like
yeah bye
-bye moment
um
yeah well while she was young
and uh Tristan by the way I'm not sure
like which
like scene you're talking about
[Music]
but there's just one scene where I've
really felt for Tristan it might have
been in a different episode but
um he
[Music]
he kind of like
the whole Tristan storyline I feel like
it kind of gives you like a view behind
the scenes of a douchebag why is that
person a douchebag and in Tristan's case
it's because of his douchebag dad who
puts a lot of pressure and stress on him
that's why he turns into a douchebag
himself
hmm
it's coming for sure oh you haven't seen
it yet or another in another Super Chat
in studio bro thank you for the rest of
the chat Angels try often return to
Nihon has fill me with such happiness
that my dark sad thoughts have been
squeezed out of my brain yet it's the
joy that I'm feeling pales in comparison
to the joy you must be feeling thank you
so much for sharing your journey yeah
I'm
I'm really happy with how it went it was
so stressful for me at some point like I
was
um
[Music]
um squeezing dance practice and all that
and a lot of recordings and so on in
between all those after lamps I was
powering through because I was like yo I
have a limited amount of time here
I want to make the most of it
but it was really stressful but at the
same time it was so much fun and yeah I
had so many bonding moments with the
Japanese members mostly but also with
Cali for example I feel like with Cali
I've been like reconnecting with her
recently I think she feels the same way
and that was really nice
yeah
the other day you know when I called her
about the cats I didn't only call her
about the cats I also wanted to like try
to be an outlet for her for the travel
situation that she had where it failed
and I thought oh she probably
would appreciate to have someone to talk
with it about and I
listens to her situation yeah
and then talked about cats
it's been nice reconnecting with myth
members in general recently
because I feel like we've all kind of
been drifting apart for a while but
um recently
um I've been
you know
trying to reconnect with them and it's
been it's been nice
[Music]
yes yes
and I think like it's okay though to
drift apart and just because we're a
generation doesn't mean that we have to
always do things together and be like
the bestest of the best friends but
um
yeah there's no need for it but uh
I I did
hope that we can do more things together
recently and I think that's happening
and nothing that's coming
[Music]
hmm
because maybe you know
if you read the members posts
yeah
I'll be going back soon too and then
[Music]
if you know you know you know you know
I think we'll be spending a lot of time
together in the near future
yeah
mom
um
I think we'll have some en
tasty action again
I need more Kiana it's hot dog
[Music]
our tickets were four first available to
buy it
[Music]
you may have just missed
the overseas
um like uh ticket uh
uh thingy
Lottery
I tried to
um
share it with as many of you guys as
possible I like talked about it several
times on Twitter
[Music]
no I don't know I don't know if there
will be another round but it may have
been the only round I'm not sure
yeah but oh stream tickets yes dream
tickets definitely I thought you meant
maybe
um
like real tickets
see it in reality
um if you're fine with
um
yeah it's important to me that you guys
know
well if you're fine with uh streaming
tickets and those are uh I guess
available for purchase
I think so but there's no like
stress with that I would say
just buy it whenever
I really want to see it online all right
I think you should I think
I think as a kfp
and this year will you you'll get your
money's worth
um
[Music]
thank you so much
thank you for you know like sharing the
joy with me I appreciate it very much
foreign
[Music]
I'll be asleep during the stream but
it's my first birthday
I've been so here's my bonus for you oh
no I missed it
you've been a joy in inspiration for me
if you told me then that I'd be in the
best spot I've ever been and prepping
for my own Japan trip I wouldn't believe
it thank you Kiana oh that sounds great
are you going for a four fast
foreign
like in in case you get a ticket but
I assume that you're going anyway even
if you don't get a ticket
I would say that area and that time is a
good time to go to Japan because I think
March
end of March
is
cherry blossom time until beginning of
April
so if you stay long enough then you
might see the cherry blossom is a
perfect season yeah
I hope you can see some cherry blossoms
go to a nice park lots of cherry blossom
trees
do a picnic maybe with some kfp members
yeah it's also not too cold and not to
hold hold hot you hot then you're cold
and yes then you're now you're in and
you're out you up and you're down
wrong and it's right
[Music]
but it's not too old and it's not too
cold it's not too
hmm
it's not too
God it is not too cold you're in and
you're around you're up and you're down
[Music]
yeah good season
um even now though in Winter I would say
it doesn't get that cold at least not
like around Tokyo
but I guess it depends on what you're
used to
but I most of the time
really didn't feel that cold
in Japan
this time
foreign
[Music]
but maybe you can have um like a tarp
underneath the koala blanket that would
be nice
during a
a
cherry blossom viewing season I think
they also have this in the
um convenience stores
I think they do sell tarps at
convenience stores but even if you don't
find it in a convenience store you can
find it in like a Don Quixote or so
um
got something like that
yeah
yeah it's for covering yourself yeah
yeah it's not an outside blanket not
really
will get way too dirty if you use that
as an outside blanket
blank inside
uh moving on thank you type and I wish
you lots of fun and oh yeah happy
belated birthday congratulations
[Music]
how did you celebrate
did you celebrate
yeah I kind of regret like
not like celebrating my birthdays that
much in the past years
um
but they should be they should be
celebrated
good time friends and cake
I'm glad
hope you had a good time and yeah uh I'm
assuming this is your first trip to
Japan so make the most out of it
and oh for everyone who goes to Japan
for the first time in a while things
have changed a little bit in terms of
arrival
um I recommend you doing this before you
arrive there's like a website where you
can upload your
um
uh certain certificates of
I forgot what it's called your your
shots your
uh seething shots certificates you can
upload them
the vaccines yes
and and then it will give me like QR
code that you can show to the
immigration upon arrival and it will
make everything smoother because they
didn't uh do this before like two years
ago or so they didn't used to do this
[Music]
um but nowadays they have like a website
now you don't have to do it but like
it's really recommended you do it now
they all ask you for QR code QR code at
the airport now hey John you're here
good thingy
[Music]
um
yeah visit Japan web oh let me see I
forgot what it was called visit Japan
one
oh yes
that looks like it
oh yeah yeah Google visit Japan web
that's it
then you can choose the airport you're
arriving and then you give like your
flight details and everything you fill
out everything online beforehand and
then gonna you get two QR codes and you
have to take a screenshot make sure you
have it when you arrive
yeah
[Music]
I did it too what's really easy
next time looking for the top foundation
thank you for the pinky I'm currently on
the hunt for the legendary phoenix
Burger I tried to order through online
services but it says she's not on the
menu
um excuse me why is it too spicy limited
edition minus the kfb menu sponsor
Phoenix Burger but don't give Phoenix
Burger
what is this are you talking about me
just not streaming much and that's why
the Phoenix Burger is not available is
that a like a
hint to that
yes I'm sorry I'm sorry for taking the
Phoenix Burger away from you
[Music]
sorry for disappointing you maybe you
should have gone to a different branch
maybe they would have had it in a
different branch
we should have more spicy food on the
menu no
no no no no no no no no no no
you can add hot sauce if you want but
burgers in other restaurants either
[Music]
that is normally not really a food that
is being made spicy
so you can make it spicy if you want to
but it's usually not spicy
Seafood good no spicy food bad
foreign
[Music]
they are where
normally like I have never seen a spicy
Burger on the menu of a McDonald's or
Burger King or so before
never
ever
[Music]
yeah no
maybe that's an American thing
[Music]
and even if then there's an I don't
think very common
in Austria
wrapping for the pinky well I've decided
I'm going to Japan in March oh you too I
was supposed to go for the Olympics in
2022 ah
then the same thing happened now you and
kfp have given me a reason to go again
I'll be in Tokyo any shopping
recommendations or food I have to try
shopping Lincoln
I don't know what you're looking for
clothes or if it was close I don't
really I can't help you because the
places where I go to they don't sell
male clothes
uh
I don't know what you're looking for but
in any case a Don Quixote is very
recommendable because you can literally
find anything in the donkey holder
however it is quite overwhelming
especially if you can't read Japanese I
feel like this is a generally a thing of
Japanese shops but with Don Quixote it's
like even worse
[Music]
um especially if you go to one in a
really popular location so I recommend
don't go to a Don Quixote in like
Shinjuku or so because it will be so
[\h__\h] exhausting to just walk through
the narrow Paths of the Don Quixote and
try to find what you're looking for
because it's so [\h__\h] crowded too
uh donkey holders are everywhere so just
go to one that's not in a super super
crowded place
then it will be a bit better but Don
Quixote has everything
feel narrow though no matter where you
go to Don Quixote that's very narrow and
it has everything
and several floors normally and then
yeah you can get clothes you can get
food you can get like electronic gadgets
or whatever
anything makeup
anything
yeah
even
even some
some more adult things
um
and they have a fun theme song playing
the whole time while you're in this goes
like
[Music]
it's so fun
it's so fun I love that song so much
oh
[Music]
ha
ha haha
[Music]
all right just uh that's also part of
the song
it's like girl yelling
oh damn it's like echoing and reverbing
from mountains
yeah it's a good song
it's not a torture it's a Bop
[Music]
how about food
oh
I think I've already talked about what I
recommend in terms of food in Japan
um
[Music]
I don't know if you're looking for
specific
Shop restaurant name you want a specific
restaurant name or or like names of
dishes that you should eat
let me just tell you I think most of the
time wherever you go it will be
delicious even if it's a cheap place but
you should eat and hit a katsu or
tonkatsu and you should eat donkatsudon
and you should eat there's very very
many different ways of eating tonkatsu
and you should eat different types of
ramen because there's so many
you should eat
those are nice like things to go to eat
with for your friends because it's kind
of like an activity at the same time
and I guess if you like sushi I guess
you should eat sushi the real deal
is some some seafood here and there like
um tempura
but
[Music]
so good
I love unakidon
well have fun I think you will have fun
for sure no matter what happens
it's not hard to have fun in Japan you
don't even have to try
copper absolutely for the pinky coffee
stores with koala is always a great time
thanks for being with us even during
your busy days I wish I could have been
streaming more if I had like
a streaming environment in my hotel
I would have definitely streamed more
but the fact that I had to reserve
Studios like ahead of time like a couple
days ahead of time
or stream like off collabs which don't
take that much time
um in terms of like actual streaming
time
and kept me from streaming a lot I would
have streamed more if I could have
streamed from the hotel though but next
time
and it's already like
already ready to go I already saw my
next streaming environment place
before I left
I got like a table and a gaming I don't
even have to bring my own laptop I can
use the provided gaming laptop and it
also has a microphone but I might bring
my own microphone because
apparently that one sounds a little bit
tin candy
um but they also have like a a mixer and
a second Monitor and
um everything a mouse a keyboard
uh a mic arm
ing
oh
that's a proper setup yeah
[Music]
yeah and
hopefully a decent internet connection I
wasn't able to test that but it should
be fine
so
next time therefore the only thing I
will bring is my switch I think and
maybe my microphone just in case the
other microphone is [\h__\h]
um
yeah bring my switch and and maybe my
capture card and so we can continue
playing Fire Emblem or whatever we're
playing at the time yeah
[Music]
PS5 controller
I guess maybe that would be helpful if
we play a game where we need a
controller on Steam but I mean I don't I
can I can
uh choose games that just work with
mouse or keyboard for the meantime but
yeah yeah potato chips now I really
think I will send them uh in a package
though
the potato chips because it makes no
sense to send them in
um my suitcase
so don't be worried next time
um we'll be more regular and
um since I already like ticked off so
many meetings in my last trip I will not
force so many meetings in the next trip
and yeah I've already got a lot of work
done too in the previous trip
like in terms of recordings and so on
so I don't know
it will not be like another drought
draft dropped drought kiwawa
are you using your steam that no I
didn't bring it to Japan so no recently
I haven't been using it didn't need to
use it
give yourself more time to relax in
between
yeah I think I'll get more time to relax
in between but also you know
[Music]
money
come on
[Music]
thank you also for pink shoes
TK you call me TK I don't really have
much to say about playing so I'm just
gonna wing it ah
I think I already read this one is so
funny did that feels familiar
I think the joke seems familiar
calling me TKO is also funny
it Rhymes reminds me of like JD from
Scrubs
hmm
oh
wow wow wow nice joke
I wish I could tell such smooth jokes
like you I'm really even German a bad
joker jokester Joker
[Music]
I can't think of any jokes if anyone
would ask me to tell a joke right now I
don't think I could think of a single
joke
yeah no
no
I can't think of a single joke
I thought I was supposed to be the
comedian
I guess I'm not
knock knock
who's there
um
[Music]
I don't know there's no one there
no one really can really I feel like a
lot of people have at least one joke
up in their sleeve
for whenever they need to tell a joke
you guys not have a joke ready at any
time
good one
wasn't a joke
no
no oh
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no
no we wouldn't get it
oh yeah I guess I could just say oh you
want to hear a joke well I would have
one but you wouldn't get it so I'm not
gonna waste my time I'm done
you all don't have I thought I thought
people would have at least one joke
ready
it
I got in a dying with a panda by the
ghost of the bar
[Laughter]
you guys are hot I have two
aha
I don't know if I want to hear them
are they just a bad
subscribe to Kiowa how funny and what a
joke
I get some booze
they think of that at the spot because
that's genius
I was probably very proud of that one
I did oh what a genius
[Music]
ah
what
it was a shih tzu
[Music]
watermelon what are you trying to say is
it because the do thinks it has more
more animals
oh [\h__\h] too I thought it was a joke
about [\h__\h] still so it says she's so
freenia Duke
who thinks they have a lot more than one
because they imagine they have more than
one animal but
oh it's a shih tzu
[Laughter]
well that's kind of better okay I get
that
man goes to a doctor says he's really
depressed doctor says he should go see
the famous clown Pagliacci that will
cheer him up
but doctor I am pogliochi
ah James are you even trying James
are you even trying
[Music]
[Laughter]
you made it really awkward for me here
[Music]
um
oh man I'm laughing because it's not
funny
it's because I'm I feel sorry for that
[\h__\h] joke
it's a reference
and I also just laugh because I like you
so
you really like it don't you know like
when you like someone you just laugh
about literally everything they say even
though it's just so not funny
[Music]
it's like Crush says oh so I ate
carbonara today and then the girl who's
crushing's it just like
laughs
yeah
oh my God you're like so funny
wow ah stop I can't
oh you're so silly
oh my God
oh God uh thank you so much I'm short
uh
I did laugh for you genuinely though I
thought that was funny
right now thank you for the pinky thanks
for sacrificing time away from genres in
this movie so give us so many amazing
collabs and of collabs they've been
super entertaining and amazing I'm gonna
be honest
you say sacrificing time away like that
is really accurate because like
away from my cats
especially for such a long time it was
just one week that's okay but like
everything over two weeks hurts my soul
and I get really worried too especially
because my cats have been so
um
how to say rebellious recently
you know the famous movie jumping over
the [\h__\h] balcony and then it's moving
recently learning how to open the door
to exit the apartment
I don't know it makes me worry that when
I'm gone like what if the person who
takes care of my cats opens the balcony
and she just tries to do another stand I
did tell my brother though about the
incident and I don't think he let them
out but
you know some some other people would
maybe underestimate how serious that is
and are like oh well it'll be fine we'll
just open for a minute and then cats ran
out and this movie goes crazy and she's
like yeah finally
finally
no that's scary
too scary so that has been worrying me
but just in general like my cats
for me are a huge mental support
way more than you can imagine I think
without my cats I
I would unleash all my
all my
problems in a bad way
yeah be very very very very very very
openly depressed
um so I really need my cats they're my
babies
I've been raising them and I wanna be
with them you know it hurts me to be
away from them
no no my bubble bubbles you make me so
happy they're so cute and I just feel
like you know since I can't see how
other people treat them when they take
care of them I worry that they don't get
enough love from whoever takes care of
them
because they're just used to being
like
24 7 babied by me
so when that's taken away from them
I don't want them to feel too like
ignored and lonely
by whoever takes care of them but I
think my brother did a good job I I can
imagine like he told me he cuddled a lot
with them and I I can imagine he did
because he loves kids kids cats Kitty
cattles
and yeah I trust him to
yeah
like when he talks about my cats and
looks at my cats I can see
I can see he wants to touch my candles
cuts
I saw in the supermarket they had
um a package of kitkats with uh rings of
power advertisement on it for some kind
of like
um
game where you can win something
so I was like
oh I love kitkats I did enjoy rings with
power
excuse me so I bought it and I need to
look up like
how to participate and maybe I can win
something I don't know what I would win
LOL you you're you
don't judge me for liking it okay I mean
I know it wasn't perfect but I also know
that
they were definitely enjoyable Parts
okay so let's not get into that again
[\h__\h] sake
we're going to kitkats are so nice oh
yeah that's one thing in Japan you can
get so many different flavored kitkats
but
you know I like the classic one very
much
[Music]
more power to you thank you
there was some kitkats in Japan that um
it says you should eat them when they're
warm like throw them in a in an oven and
they'll be even better or the other way
around throw them in the freezer and
then they'll be even better
yeah
interesting all the things you can do
with kitkats
yeah like um
let me see
oh yakikito
um there's
um oh it's let me show you you know what
that should be fine it's fine here look
this one is pudding taste and even on
the picture on the packaging it shows
you
tells you to put it into an oven toaster
you know usually in Japan
and unless you have a really really
really modern expensive apartment you
normally don't have a typical oven that
is like under the stove you know where
you cook like a big size one normally
you don't have it most of them
uh either come with one of these or you
buy one one of those small toaster ovens
where you can really not do much with it
but it works yeah so it tells you to put
those in there and they turn out like
that
and then it's like fresh hot pudding I
guess
no thanks I'm good no but I think it's
good I've I've had
um some of these
different flavors before
I don't think I've ever thrown one into
an oven though
give it a try
I wonder if it's good yeah
foreign
[Music]
how do they make frozen pizza well in
the oven toaster
it's just they can't be too big
or in a microwave I see a lot of people
just microwaving their pizzas in Japan
like Corona did that too we got like um
like a pizza from the supermarket but
not a frozen one just like a
refrigerated one
and I thought you would put it in an
oven toaster or something like that but
no she just microwaved it so it was like
really soft
hmm
yeah yeah well I think Japanese people
generally they wouldn't go for like
instant Pizza they would just order on
Pizza online even though it's really
expensive that's more common than frozen
pizza
frozen pizza really common in Austria
but not so much in Japan I've seen it
before but there's not like not that
much choice and I think it doesn't get
bought that much as much as
um they would just order a pizza from
from a service
or in a restaurant like size area
[Music]
frozen pizza is good just not microwave
yeah I would I would put a frozen pizza
in the microwave like that's not how you
do it
no no no no no
big mistake
[Music]
foreign
toaster ovens
like if you don't have a big kitchen
with an oven like that already built in
then I think it's worth getting like a
small toaster oven
mmm
very handy
they can do the thing but it's just like
they're not that big but at least you
can move it around
put it wherever you want
um
and it works like for toasting bread and
so on too
so you have a toaster in an oven in one
thing it's a toaster oven
mmm where was I
Aya Reyna thank you so much again it's
been a pleasure had a good time even
though it was so hard to be away from
the cats can see how we got to the
KitKat toaster oven tangent through my
cats
I call them kids
Jackson FB thank you for the pinky it's
3 40 am and I have class tomorrow so I
gotta go
but but I'm glad you got to go on the
strip and have fun with the others thank
you I'm glad to
um
I think if I have known that I would go
back
um very soon after I maybe wouldn't have
booked this trip
but I just couldn't wait anymore and I
saw you know everybody else was also
going to Japan around the same time so I
was like I can't miss out on it let's go
so yeah I had to go and
um
I think it was worth it it's just like
it's too close to the next trip it
really is there's like too little time
in between
for me to recharge my cat energy
yes I'm going back soon I won't say when
but it's very soon way sooner than you
may think
but at the same time I don't really mind
going back even right now because of
those member posts
from other members laughs
yeah oh
[Music]
sorry mumei wrote back to me
hmm
[Music]
talking about the crib stuff
say hi for us
no
and I'm I'm like talking about her own
stream
say it
no
[Music]
no I'm the best
no no you say hi for you why do I have
to say hi for you
oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
now she's telling me about Hell's
Kitchen
[Music]
remains not watching she's not watching
I should I should watch that's what I
said to her oh I should watch this
oh
[Music]
foreign
crimes
dear Lord
[Music]
should we be afraid no no
it's all normal everyday stuff you know
dear Lord also known the spot
dear lady
wish I could join the console oh you
like to talk about that kind of stuff
[Music]
um
oh
foreign
okay I'm gonna tell her
that I need to go Focus back on my
street she probably doesn't even know
that I'm just streaming
should I tell her
foreign
[Music]
I can't end the conversation yet we're
like like really like living it up right
now
[Music]
we're into it yeah
well let me read some Super Shots why
was that oh
um yeah
thank you
look forward to
more fun with other members soon yay
thank you soon Midnight Rider thank you
soon
[Music]
foreign
anyway I am actually streaming oh sorry
um don't worry I wasn't
reading it out loud so but I'm gonna go
back to focus on life
dream while they are saying hi
they're saying hi I told her
buy a lot of chickens with a knife
they told me to say hi
she's caps log apologizing
let's talk more about crime soon
[Music]
[Laughter]
dangerous crazy birds that look nice on
the outside but a little bit broken on
the inside let's talk more about crime
soon okay
okay okay okay
I am just the Observer I am not the one
who who does the deed
out context it's terrifying
no I I am I am an observer purely an
observer
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh I'm just watching from afar I can't
interact or intervene
of anything
[Music]
okay okay and here we go
sorry sorry guys I'm back uh focused on
the super
chatsana thank you for the words of my
dad hi again I'm moving to Germany from
New Zealand in a couple months of work
oh for how long I wonder I'm looking
forward to being able to watch your life
more often and go to document Disney
this year
what New Zealand
time in New Zealand
now
10 a.m oh yeah okay
GMT Plus 13.
so is that it's even ahead of
Japan
[Music]
is GMT plus nine
damn
oof
head of Australia and Japan
my father just like ended there
didn't know there was something even
further
oh wow
damn
New Zealand is the first time zone
well then I guess that's really good
that you're moving to Germany and it
will be way easier to watch me unless
I'm in Japan but
damn do you speak any German though I
think even if you don't you'll be fine
don't worry
in Europe most people speak at least two
languages
um most people speak English
either fluently or
a certain conversational level so
I don't think you'll be like
suffering because of that but
don't rely too much on it hope you can
learn some Germany some German while
you're there I can't speak English
and English in Germany for sure so maybe
they have a funny accent but
yeah they might have a funny accent but
they they have enough vocabulary I think
enjoy
your turning you'll definitely have a
lot of culture shock though I think
I think Germany is probably very
different from New Zealand
um
but
[Music]
you're going to but I think you'll have
a good time it's a good good country
um
yeah and then you can go to docomo even
though I will not be there but I think
I think dokum is a great convention to
go to in Germany the best one possibly
um
yeah yeah so good luck with moving and
and stay safe and it might be really
stressful but enjoy the time you have
there yeah
yeah
for the pinky sticker no text
[Music]
why you don't want me to read anything
you got nothing to say
sticker doesn't even really like tell me
anything it's just a blob riding on a
rocket
don't know what that means
thank you so much no much appreciated
logical Paradox thank you thank you for
the pinky thank you this Fortune talk
reminds me last year you drew fortunes
for my birthday yeah yeah you predicted
my or she would send me a card
and I would have an amazing year both
came true
sent you a card or is you or she someone
else both came true so I would like to
thank you for your amazing Fortune
drawing skills hey
where's your Hoshi I don't remember
sending you a card I got a card from you
oh
okay that's not really quite what I
would have thought of but I see how did
I did I predict that what the [\h__\h] did I
know you were going to
at that point no way that was at the
beginning of the year right how did I
know
it
that's so specific
just read your fortune
yeah but how did I know
the the fortune say you would get a card
from your Oshi
I don't remember that word at all
really specific and we'll get your hopes
up so high
and for most people I don't think it
will come true
wow fascinating
damn
can't believe that came true
you have to talk you also told me it
wouldn't come true but it did
I told you sorry dude that ain't
happening I'm not giving you a card but
then I did that's amazing
that's just because I want to protect
your hopes in case it wouldn't happen
one then once your hopes to get up that
high
didn't want you to be disappointed after
all
and then you were even happy and when it
did happen
nice
what a cool story thank you
Happy New Year to you
kind of thing is
thank you
happy
birthday 20 damn 20th
man you're in your 20s now
I think a lot of people say the 20s are
the best years
so I hope that will be accurate for you
oh a cat is entering the room it's
moving hi
fridge fridge I think she just woke up
just saying hi hi
you're welcome to come up here if you
want
oh scratch scratch the catch me yes do
you hear me
[Music]
scratch scratch
coach scratch hmm
[Music]
yeah she's just saying hi to Mommy so
sweet
and where was I
[Music]
uh right now
are there new YouTube hi this movie
jumped up the table I think she wants to
sit here okay there you go
are there new YouTube profanity rules
I don't know if um you little [\h__\h] has
been demonetized it might have been
although I think that you only lose it
you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] your
little [\h__\h] one was uh demonetized from
the beginning right
apparently
the first 16 seconds of the video
I don't know
well there's some weird like Zip in my
in my ears
hmm
they really started to correct download
even on all the weather videos wow oh
well it's okay
that's all right
I mean usually the first
16 seconds our waiting screen
loading screen and then the first 10
minutes
[Music]
yeah I may I may swear but I don't think
it gets that heated yet
in the beginning
ding dong thanks for the pinkies
that's that sounds like translated
German a little bit too stiff
I'm not sure what you're referencing to
maybe
maybe four Fest
about 3D and all that
oh no oh no it's about I think I was
talking about us waiting so long for 3D
and not being able to use it much even
now yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
but you will get more of kibaba pretty
I had four Fest so
yeah
something to look forward to
it
thank you for the pinky and the support
very generous thank you soon
[Music]
foreign
thank you for the pinky
no reason at all for writing this now
all of a sudden but we love you we
appreciate you we'll be here for a long
time you won't get rid of us anyways
you're amazing our amazing hard-working
Oshi Phoenix thank you for being the way
you are also really no particular reason
why
laughs
[Music]
no no nothing that inspired you to write
this some kind of desperation
oh it's moving
he's showing me belly again
[Music]
you're lucky for over right now my mood
is being
kept
in a very very
um calm soothing happy mood by this
movie right now
so I can't be angry at you
[Music]
this movie is your third Aussie uh
uh you know what I appreciate that my
cats if you guys can appreciate my cats
I would really appreciate that because
to me they play such a big part in my
life you know
I know some people can't relate if they
don't have pets but you know they really
mean so much to me
no she's just oh
she got so comfortable in such an
uncomfortable space
partially under my monitor
are you comfortable
anyway thank you profile very kind words
um
no matter what has prompted them
thank you very much for still supporting
me even even when you now have to share
the love that was once 100 committed to
me the love and the attention
I guess
it's still enough
for me
please just stop but thank you
oh oh you want the easy way out don't
you you think it's that easy just
think you can just cheat on me and then
get away with it so simply
it's not that easy
no
you will have to accept a certain amount
of peace and jealousy
um
I will call you out
[Music]
thank you counting chickens
foreign
[Music]
was I'm glad the trip worked out in the
end thank you for telling us about
attention and finally tomorrow all right
yay
yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh that was when I told the end of that
was really an old one a long one I'm so
sorry but I think I I had to tell it in
detail it was necessary it was worth it
there was so much that I wanted to show
you all those photos
um
I was really happy to go on a little
trip like it was more for Emma than it
was for me like I just wanted Ahmed to
see something and that was accomplished
successfully
um
I think she really had a good time
so I'm happy
maybe I can show around certain other
members at some point somewhere
oh
do more tourist guiding it's my new job
I'm a tourist guide now
not a streamer my main job is tourist
guide
that cave was so cool no it wasn't it
was so basic
it was funny hearing her side of the
story
I watched that and I do not agree with
her side of the story of how I invited
her
I don't agree with that
[Music]
let me look back on it
why don't we start talking about it
[Music]
when is this
um
I'm checking my ships
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
Okay so
on
the 9th of January
I asked
I meant are you free on the 14th
he asks what for
I say maybe collab with hachama if I can
get the studio reserved
she says
um she would be down for it
but
depending uh it would be good if it was
later in the day because she maybe would
do some sightseeing before okay okay
okay okay but at this point
she told me she doesn't have anything
like specific planned yet and she
decides it like on the day before or so
what she will do like spontaneously you
know nothing set in stone
and I asked actually
uh do you already know what sightseeing
you will be doing on that day because
I'm thinking of bringing you to uh
blah blah blah blah blah blah blah just
in case uh we can't stream
um because enoshima would take a whole
day so this is just in case the stream
won't happen and she said uh yeah no I
don't know yet what I'm gonna be doing
uh just going day by day
see so it sounds like to me that maybe
she would appreciate uh me throwing an
idea at her you know you know hmm
so I say okay so if we don't stream I
will bring you to enoshima if we do then
we can think of something smaller to do
and then I will show you a notion by
another day but yeah so she didn't say
anything about monkeys or anything about
going somewhere else at this point
um
nothing
then uh on the on the 12th I updated her
um said that we can stream on the day
and
blah blah blah blah
and then then she tells me
that she's maybe doing a day trip maybe
on the 14th but only probably uh
[Music]
because you know it was it was only for
mostly only for Ahmed and then for
hachama I told her okay how about we
just go eat something together so that's
where I kind of like uh changed my plans
and I talked to her and then
then
a couple hours later
she writes to me
um I would still like to meet up to meet
hachama
uh because I got the dates confused
uh but yeah I will have time
anyway okay so so yeah because she told
me I can't meet because I'm doing this
whole day thing uh which she missed
mixed up because actually that was
supposed to be with uh Bales which was
on the following day right they had a
collab on one day later right she mixed
something up there so I'm like oh okay
so I guess if you mix it up
and you have time on that day after all
then let me tell hatima again that you
have time after all and then Hatton was
like oh okay I'm at his time then let's
go to enoshima together after all and so
then a couple hours after this happened
I met uh ah manhattama directly at the
Yakiniku and you know Hanson was already
excited for it we already talked about
it uh Emma told me it was a
misunderstanding with the dates like she
got it wrong and so I thought okay
she until this point has never told me
anything about monkeys
so then we sit together there at the
team yellow dinner and I had somebody's
in front of me Amma is next to me and so
I look at Ahmed
and just I'm like
uh
tomorrow yeah yeah
yeah and then
so okay
in that situation maybe I pushed her a
little bit but it never was like ever
indicated that she was planning
something else I mean I mean it was only
always like a maybe but then even that
trip that she planned like immediately
after she tells me that was a mistake in
the date so I thought okay you're doing
that on the 15th then huh
so yeah you know you know you know
there you go
let me touch my version of this no
yeah I mean if Emma would have told me
that she really wants to see the monkeys
on that day then it would have been fine
I would have just you know let her do
her thing
um
[Music]
maybe I didn't get into the room
correctly
no
I think
well I'ma maybe should have said clearly
that she doesn't want to go to enoshima
but you know what that at some point she
was like oh never mind I have time after
all I do want to meet hachima
so then I was like okay I guess enoshima
is okay
because then I also told because this
was separately you know we were in
different chats I didn't make a group
until after that it was finally set in
stone so I was the communicator that I
was I was
back and forth back and forth
yeah I was like oh I mean I'm making
meat okay let's go to her Anderson okay
yeah I guess so
tomorrow on killer keemstar
yeah I think
I think she enjoyed and Oshima she found
a lot of moths there
and some wildlife
was a nice trip outside of Tokyo so I
think it worked out fine yeah and I just
want to say and you know
I I was it was never my intention on
forcing her to go to editor
I I I did not think that that was how it
came across to Mama
um
that's uh interesting
to see both sides huh
yeah
I am next time I'll ask is that really
what do you want to do
I've been
um
I've been doing that like
uh we're good at two like about
something I was like are you really sure
that's okay like is it really okay we're
checking just in case it's totally okay
say no or just making sure it's okay
yeah I mean so I'm gonna do that for
Emma too
are you sure are you sure that's is that
really what you want
so tell me what you want what you really
want I'm telling what you want when I
really want to hook I wanna I wanna I
wanna I wanna I wanna really really
really want to see the monkeys
okay that's fine then
that's okay I understand the monkeys are
surely very interesting too yeah I
wouldn't have gone with her though I
think
because then I would have I don't know
I would have needed a bit more planning
beforehand
[Music]
not just decide like a few hours before
going to sleep oh we're gonna go to a
different prefect Church see some
monkeys
another time would be fine though
I wanna go to more places outside of
Tokyo myself to be honest
and the place that I wanted to go to the
monkey place
I think that's the prefecture that I've
never been to before
so I would actually be very interested
in general
um
although I'm not sure if I would want to
walk 40 minutes up a mountain
I think that was what she was planning
on doing
aren't there monkeys
and I said I saw no monkeys
yeah no it doesn't to be perfectly
planned but if it's a trip that goes
so far with a shinkansen out of Tokyo
and I'm already like I've been planning
something with hatama
a couple days already
I don't want to like suddenly be like
five hours before going to sleep oh no
now we're going there
super far away for the whole day
exhausting trip I don't know
maybe like 24 hours before is okay
also depends just on what I'm what I've
already planned though
but in general
I think I can be very spontaneous too
hmm
she saw the monkeys in the end anyway
yeah yeah I've heard good for her
good
did she really walk 40 minutes
did she
I wonder
damn
monkeys
ah oh those were the monkeys in Kyoto
other monkeys oh then we can still go to
the Onsen monkeys if she wants with me
maybe she doesn't want to go with me
has to be communicated clearly are you
sure are you sure it's okay you can say
no
okay
[Music]
monkeys and Moss that's on this
uh all right next stream that needs to
be read
say we are making progress
next one is this one
actually kind of sweeping through aren't
we yeah
[Music]
girls episode reviews in a row nice
why would rowing do the dreaming tutu
Tristan
I don't think that's what she did
why I get my daughter Lorelei did oh
ring for the adventure with Max but Rory
how could she why what's going on what
I'm confused I think you're mixing up
some things here Doug Hood
have you ever made an Impulse decision
that you instantly regret later boss
oh yeah yeah for example my hotel
booking for Italy with my mom
that was
I didn't do enough research on
that hotel yeah besides that hmm
I don't think anything that I I can
really
um remember right now
like for example auditioning for
whole life was an Impulse decision but I
don't regret that one
[Music]
then more
now that I think about it I may have
been more yeah I think anyone has that
then I guess
um
sure hope you wouldn't regret that one
yeah we good on that front
that was one of my best decisions in
life
um
I actually what I did regret is like
after sending in my audition I was
thinking for a little bit like maybe I
should have spent more time with it but
then I ended up getting a reply like
immediately
I think I got an email back like after a
day or two
which is so fast
so fast I was like okay I guess it was
fine that I only spent like
two or three hours on my audition
I was so inspired and motivated in that
moment
yeah
they knew you were the one
I guess so yeah
it was a fast process yeah
I'm glad
because I don't know waiting for days
and days and weeks would have probably
killed me like oh I guess it didn't work
out all right
I would have already given up
[Music]
yeah it was really fast so I take that
as a compliment I I take it as
like they didn't have to think about it
much they didn't have to compare other
auditions they were just like all right
this girl
she's it
we need her
thank you Doug Hood and it's scary
skins I didn't end it I
see I see
I eat Canton is a prefecture in Japan
and it's written in Japanese no I said
igk
that doesn't sound
please
and there's not even an end between but
good try
[Music]
it's time in the wild and you almost got
me
[Music]
almost
I'm assuming it's the same person right
because I I think around that time maybe
I told you
that wasn't you but I told you you
should like try again you should try
harder because you were just chilling
with the same name for the longest time
are you sure that's not you
download happy
birthday thank you
[Music]
foreign
that doesn't even look like her trash
can
[Music]
foreign
oh my God
I only see
but they both
have
yeah quite a lot of super chats foreign
let me see
oh but there's not not that many Reds oh
no at the end holy [\h__\h] why ah all these
new year's Super Chat suddenly
Ah that's why it's so many okay not a
hotel
hi
for like two months or so we haven't
been
um caught up
but I see the light at the end of the
tunnel guys
I see it
[Music]
um
okay
here we go
here we go here we go
enjoy
mini diesel Duncan thanks for the pinky
you know what you said in the beginning
that I don't have to read them so this
one I will actually
not read maybe next time but thank you
soon Max all the first time jackets
[Music]
although I am I am curious about your
cable girls reviews
and it's been quite a while since I
could be here for a live stream and I
must say I've missed it a lot so fun
following you Japan Adventures oh
spending time why because of my
different streaming times while I was in
Japan or just because you were busy
I hope that now
you can catch my streams better again
I hope so
sorry about all the weird ass times you
know normally we would go for evening
times for the off collabs
yeah just because
kind of it's better for the for them too
because they don't get up early
they wouldn't get up early
I did have fun
they were good ones yeah and like little
um little bites
you know
it's easy to digest
even if you have to be vodkang there's
like not insane amounts of hours to
watch so I think it was manageable hmm
oh
[Music]
oh your sleep pattern was different
well you know I've been thinking about
next time when I'm in Japan
um about like what time to stream in I
think
um
I might
I might stream early in the day next
time I'm in Japan generally but you know
me you know me I'll mix it up
and have a sad stream time
I'll definitely not be streaming before
10 a.m jst doll
anything between 10 and or more like 11
A.M jst to
midnight jst
on that more like probably 11 p.m jst I
don't think I want to risk streaming
that late in Japan in case you know
maybe the neighbors also get mad who
knows
so just all day yeah
yeah it works for me nice
nice
that might be a pain to catch up well
you can't be helped but
[Music]
once I reach like
8 P.M jst or so
that's uh a time that I often
streaming
um
okay maybe like 9 pm jst
that's a somewhat usual kiwawa streaming
time though
okay okay okay
we'll figure it out
8 PM just is 5 a.m for me FM just is
doable for me well there you go you know
we have a mixed pack of chickens
um it'll always be ones that
you know
can't watch it so well so that's why
I'll mix it up again
so spanking time thank you
and welcome back maybe
from what gang back to life gang
hopefully
but even as vodkang thank you for
supporting me
you know I appreciate it hopefully next
time
you can follow my Japan Adventures as
well live maybe maybe just maybe but if
you can't that's okay too
I'll catch up too thank you
edpie and Jesse hits the right spot yeah
for you it does
um
I'll make time if I can yeah thank you
please thank you soon
and getting a newfounded version
appreciation for the board game while
you were in Japan appreciate being on
the live thing as well though thank you
[Music]
I can hand a kiss for you catch it
nice catch please
thank you
oh
art and nice soup
um
[Music]
Alexander babsky
thank you for the red super chat I don't
think I can really help you with this
because I don't feel comfortable with
like
saying that to her directly but I hope
you'll figure it out
okay maybe
make a new account or so I don't know
good luck though
kwj duncast
what's up blue
it's all right thank you oh you're here
sorry it's um difficult for me to you
know
help you with that issue
sorry
um blue
was that supposed to be a rainbow you're
interrupted oh yeah oh yeah they've been
interrupting you
laughs blue let me read the rainbow
message Happy Lunar New Year Chihuahua
made us here bring you and kfb more
happiness and opportunities
to do great things it's a blast to see
you have been having so much you've been
having
so much fun in Japan take care and stay
safe
[Music]
oh thank you
damn well
I didn't know you celebrate Lunar New
Year
I don't know
for you
[Music]
thank you for sharing that with me
it's an honor thank you you're so sweet
even though you're
supporting
a frog a lot of the time
um I guess deep in your heart you still
love me the most right
it's okay
thank you
what's that dot dot dot oh what's that
you're shocked that I know
you can see her tweets about you oh lie
why lie why why
what's how do I find oh there we go
[Music]
onion Chihuahua is too cute
but that doesn't these are normal tweets
these are good tweets
how deep do I have to go to find
the
dangerous sweets
yo the chickens are so cute
chickens you draw so cute
looking good so far
[Music]
what
I can't listen to that now but it feels
like it's a recording of you singing
one of my songs
oh fishies
[Music]
hmm
I see nothing bad
in the replies to someone
what just one tweet or so but overall
blue seems like an exemplary chicken so
I will not look any further
hmm
no it seems good to pass you passed the
test I've touched your bullet
got lucky
pass some space and yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
what
poor blue you guys like trying to get
blue on my bad side poor blue
hello it's just an innocent good chicken
okay
hi
cool
[Music]
stretch
I'm done soon's moving
and yeah thank you blue once again and
kind to fight their donkey soon
because
random collusion thank you for the pinky
quick query Queen
what
you are making a cute cute joke quick
query
wait
me not understand though
I don't understand though
hmm I think that was something that was
supposed to confuse me so you did a good
job at confusing me
thanks for the pinky Nini diesel Danke
Schoen Thai tea thank you for the rest
of the chat
[Music]
oh you're opening up the Red Envelope
wave thank you tidy Happy New Year to
you too
finally New Year on your side as well
when receiving red envelopes not me well
thank you
oh thank you foreign
[Music]
I hear you made it
over to my side of the globe
you getting coffee yet
I hope so
[Music]
thank you Mama
thank you for every type of chat as well
24 months with our favorite Dental oh
time is passing so fast since 10 just
debut and happy Luna New Year tenzo yeah
happy New Year first of all and yeah the
time passes by really fast it's crazy
for me to think that I've been in
whole life for over two years
it feels like a year but it's over two
years
so crazy
man
I hope that we can raise that number
thank you soon for supporting me for 24
months not giving up on me ever thank
you
Happy New Year
mmm
[Music]
like reaching dinosaurs
foreign
[Music]
straight from the Wawa
straight kiss delivery
Edward Villages that Asian kid dang soon
sir 956
that Asian kid Danke Schoen James
Jackson
foreign
[Music]
this is the one of the rare occasions
where you don't listen to what I'm
saying huh
thank you though
hydration check yeah thank you and I
really love my cat paw cup it's so worth
it one of the best purchases I've ever
made
it's a small cup but
it looks so fancy cute
more water throat is
dying
[Music]
cat pot cup yeah I posted it on my
Twitter the other day like two days ago
or so check it out you're really cute
sanctions
no it's um
it's a
veg chat
a vegetarian chat who's green
sanctions
back in time again for the bread Super
Chat thank you
are you sure you aren't starving
well right now I kind of I am
right now I am getting hungry
um
and too lazy to cook so I might just eat
whatever I have left from the lunch
and add some extra kitkats as dessert
but tomorrow maybe
maybe tomorrow
or the day after tomorrow
sometime this week I will definitely
cook at least twice maybe fries ideally
fries is that a word price
was that a word
twice fries rice
sounds so weird oh yeah
yeah okay good I don't think it's being
used much
price
old school but correct it and what's new
school
cooking it's been a while huh
haven't cooked my own meal for a while
three times a lot of people just say
three times right
a triple doesn't really work in that
way because
you know I can't say I can't say what
did I say well I can't use it the same
way
even though it means the same thing
[Music]
okay once twice Three Times a Lady
even though fries exists what the [\h__\h]
fries is just being ignored
at least you cooked a little bit of
chocolate Ah that's true yeah yeah yeah
I wanna make that oyakodon in Austria I
wonder if I can make it I gotta look in
Asian supermarket for all those
ingredients
[Music]
Magician Girl
you being here reminds me I need to
reply you
[Music]
hmm
need to reply sorry
it's one of those times where I see the
message
at a time where I'm not really able to
reply and then I forget about it later
on I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
they made a new clip for my German
Channel and I have yet to reply properly
German channel is real
though I thought about it don't worry I
was like oh maybe a new clip would be
good
and I asked for one but I haven't
checked it yet there's a German Channel
German Channel myoshi
and within this month I got the message
within this month
um
[Music]
I just saw it now again date is within
this month
[Music]
so spanking hand kissing
that Asian kid
[Music]
here you go thank your food money hey
nice and big
what what's nice and big
the Super Chat
thank you for the food money
I very much appreciated as I told you
guys I spent way too much money on my
Japan trip you don't even want to know
you don't even wanna know
but I spent so much money on the hotel
for nothing because
and would have totally been fine with
like a cheap ass Airbnb or whatever if I
would have known that I wouldn't be able
to stream in my hotel anyway
so
I was really salty about that but
um
haven't told you how much she spent
cool
how much did she spend she only stayed
for like a week or so though right
oh
[Music]
do you know
she's been like 300 bucks on gacha
I think that's a good investment though
somewhat good
huh thank you
oh my money went into Gaza pasta
pay for a lot but the internet is man
yeah I was expecting the internet to be
decent but um I spent a lot of money on
the hotel room because I
needed a room with thicker walls but
even that was kind of lacking
um
that is elgacha
in Japanese hotels too anyway Be Fashion
thank you
I appreciate it thank you soon it will
go into my hell fresh subscriptions
thanks for the pinky more love for my
Odyssey why thank you why is this like
mixed in weirdly at the time that
doesn't line up with all the other ones
[Music]
hmm well thank you so much once again
sir 956
[Music]
for the red super chat a delivery of our
hyper condensed love for utensils
hopefully it feeds you well
very yummy tastes like chicken
[Music]
needs a bit more spice though okay
but fills my tummy well thank you
[Music]
very good
this is what you get when you raise your
chickens free range baby
free range is the only way to go
Moon doctor soon
celebrities oh
[Music]
starting to lose it
uh
[Music]
but nobody can say that I have not
been reading my super chess diligently
or whatever that word is
I haven't been tangenting that much
I've been I've been doing my best
[Music]
yeah thank you nice vocabulary
um I won't have on the supers
where's the cheese I need to go ham and
cheese on them
[Music]
yeah this the stream million progress
has been made
your sleep schedule was too good in
Japan and not 100 I ended up eventually
just
waking up
at 11 or so again
um
[Music]
but it's just because like whenever I
have to wake up early I will wake up
early but if I don't have to wake up
early then I will sleep in
huh
[Music]
it's my life it's my life it's now or
never
I am gonna live forever
la la
It's My Life
[Music]
yeah when there's no reason to why the
[\h__\h] would I get up early
thank you for understanding
[Music]
oh don't mention that that was
that's not only on me because the
miracle the bad Miracle about that is
that I slept in and General slept and we
both slept then
for that
search and collab
what do you mean Ina is leaking members
content did she just write it on Twitter
publicly also
or in her stream it's just saying it no
I'm watching more than just me
then you can't pay proper attention to
me
foreign
anyway yeah so
the funny thing is
I was not able to meet her right I told
you the first time but then
she came back
pretty much
last minute
we were like kind of overlapping with
her coming and me leaving
and so I did meet her
for one evening before I left
but
I will not tell you about it yet
just one evening so there's not that
much to tell you about anyway
there will be more to tell you about
as you can too
[Music]
but I'm glad yeah
actually I gave her
um through jenma I gave her presents the
first time she was here
so I couldn't meet her but Gemma was
able to meet her so I gave Gemma the
presents and she gave it to
um
and then uh on that one evening actually
I had one more present for her because I
had to think of her when I was in a in a
convenience store and I saw something
I'll maybe take a picture and show you
later or another time but I saw
something I thought oh I think I think
he never liked this
but I also kind of wanted one for myself
so I bought two of these things
basically you know those like
sketchbooks that are like two colored on
the cover like one one color is like
like a yellow orange and the other one
is just black
and it's like triangles
you know what I mean
no sketchbooks
I think they're like
like the typical Japanese Sketchbook
also
yeah so I found that in miniature form
like a small one
um and but it was not only that it was
like
um a certain silly mascot
was
depicted on it as well and I thought she
would love that both of that that
combination
and then I gave it to her and she did
love it she was like oh I
love school I was like I had to think of
you
um
she liked it
it's like a weird car hamster
I think I mean some of you may have seen
it before it's like a car hamster
hamster car
[Music]
I found it
wait I can maybe even find please what
I'm talking about
foreign
[Music]
no it doesn't come up that easily I
might have to take a photo of it by
myself and show it to you guys
but it's basically
that character on top of the Sketchbook
and it's a small version of it cute
why is that so adorable
because it's silly
yeah they made a hamster into a car
you shouldn't be so surprised I haven't
made into a car before I've also been
made into a taxi before
because everyone calls me a taxi well
anyway I have a lot of super chat's
still ahead of me so let me focus on
those
um
thank you for the right Super Chat
wordless though appreciate that right
now very much mwah as if you knew I
would be suffering
I even got out of the bed just to send
you a super chat you better buy some
yummy food with it so you won't starve
were you watching me like on the TV or
phone or something
you got up just to send me a Super Chat
thank you I'm
yeah
that Asian kid Duncan clubs Louis sir
956 Francis
no and I will never doctor
foreign
[\h__\h]
oh the pinky
[Music]
can I say this it seems safe according
to Google
it doesn't uh
doesn't translate everything though only
the second part
[Music]
MIT is cold
um
did that sound okay
thank you thank you for the red super
chat an old pink one and I said it I
hope it sounded okay
they were they were requesting for me to
say Happy New Year to you close enough
close enough doesn't sound that close
well you guys are giving me a free pass
right yeah yeah
yeah 10 of the 10 for 10 fries let's go
blue cat thank you donkey Shin also for
the red envelope here this is where the
Red Envelope spam really starts
thank you blue cat then you're too cute
give you a nice number of Red Envelope
uh
[Music]
was also asking for me to say that I
already said that some mission
accomplished
Happy New Year
thanks for the pink Super Chat Skye
Duncan for the red super chat
early happy Lunar New Year yeah you were
like maybe one minute early chihuahua in
case if you would not stream tomorrow so
here's my red envelope
yeah I don't think I streamed the day
after so good guess
thank you soon thank you Skye happy New
Year again
congratulations
I hope you celebrate it well thank you
for sharing it with me
Lunar New Year always makes me think of
the times when we played ryza
[Music]
for the red super chat too I'm
officially reborn is
it happened as I couldn't catch your
life to say this properly so I'm late
but I want to thank you for two years of
awesome content that made me happy every
day continue to smile brightly and warm
our little drink inside love you
[Music]
I'll try my best thank you so much
it's really sweet
it's hard as a content creator to keep
up like
you know the content for two years and
try to stay like interesting and
original and
you know
keep everything regular and you know
it's difficult but I'm trying hope
you're still enjoying it as you did in
the early days
hmm
thank you so much for staying with me
[Music]
passing a flying colors thank you
doing awesome job thank you
your content has only gotten better oh
thank you really
[Music]
had to stay fresh but I still love it
here thank you and that's hard
Um Papa thanks for the pinky Red
Envelope
pink button in the correct lighting and
the right lighting it might look red so
I'll take it thank you Happy New Year
[Music]
thank you soon
again on Pinky thank you what the hell
so generous Yuko
wow tank is just way way too generals
thank you
Yuki silver cook
212 Tanki shoes a 2012
MVB thank you for the pinky happy late
New Year and yearly chat message
oh you only
chat with me once in a year
[Music]
see that made me so sad I had to sneeze
out all the tears at once through my
nose and mouth
those were tears
I was appalled
by that
was devastating
but I have no time to cry so I just let
it out and it sneeze really quickly
um
[Music]
so
ah
very efficient crying yeah everything I
do must be efficient
anyway thank you MVP and it may be late
for our new year but you're actually
perfectly in time for the Lunar New Year
so maybe that was on purpose
can't really say you're late then thank
you
moose thank you for the rest of the chat
happy Luna New Year 10 so here's my Red
Envelope by the way I love this mom's
members wallpaper so much thank you for
the amazing art you're welcome I really
like it too
um I couldn't make it public until this
week with this week's schedule but the
full version is even more stunning
there's a lot of stuff going on in the
background I think it's the most
detailed background we've had so far
the cool thing is the artist gave me
like so many choices of like kimono
designs and then also different choices
for the background and for the whole
like composition and all that so yeah
it was hard to choose actually because
everything was just so good
um
definitely one of my favorites really
good wallpaper material right
yeah
I'm glad you guys like it but actually
with that I kind of created
somewhat of my ideal kimono what I kind
of wanted
and because the kimono that I have
is is the only thing that really is
according to my wishes was the twin tail
hairstyle
and partially the straight hairstyle
but yeah
yeah some things kind of went wrong with
the kimono and it just kind of happened
it's good anyway but it's not what I
wanted at all
I don't know if I ever told you but I
actually was hoping to get something
more fantasy like
with like burnt sleeves and all that
and then I was
um within the deadline I was like
Gathering like ideas and references and
all that
and then before the deadline ended
I was sent
drafts
a pretty far ahead drafts of
uh the kimono even though my deadline
didn't even end yet
so early yeah and yeah I felt bad to say
like no redo the whole thing felt
disrespectful and like a lot of work
um and then didn't want to be like that
so
I accepted it
even though you know kimono is like a
once
once only
thing
yeah this thing is just like my idea was
completely different from that and it
would have had to be remade from scratch
but
it's not like I was late I was like on
time
[Music]
yeah
you probably wanted to get it out of the
way quickly because maybe he had some
other work lined up later on
um
and then I was like oh
oh we know I'm really happy to see this
and it looks nice but at the same time
what do I do that's not not what I
wanted oh well
um
I don't really like the twin Tails
though the twin tale turned out great
because the twin Tails actually are
according to my references one on one
hmm exactly how I wanted them
that's why I use them so much
because they're like basically the only
thing that's 100 when I want it
[Music]
yeah if loving and spiky
I'm cute thank you thank you thank you
oh well well how did I get to this
how did I get to this
ah the months the members wallpaper yeah
because there I was like all right all
right it's New Year's time to put on a
kimono but you know what let's make a
new one an original one
um
yeah that one was uh kind of closer to
what I
actually want it
but oh well
oh well well this one's fine too this
one's pretty it's just more classic and
more normal
you know
and thank you moose
happy New Year UK silver cook Duncan
breakfast
thank you for the pinky Chihuahua and
having a nice Luna New Year's break so
finally I can catch up or stream oh
hey how long have you
launching
hmm here's my pink envelope happy Luna
New Year by the way I might have a
chance to go to Japan to meet some kfp
Fox and also see you on stage in March I
hope I win the draw oh I wish you all of
the luck
I wish all of the kfb who applied would
get in but wait has it already
nah the overseas Lottery the results are
not in yet right
let's feel nervous
I hope
everyone who applied can get in but I
don't even know how big the pool is
yeah
but it's okay in the live stream last
year was really cool too so you may even
have a better view in the live stream
than if you get like a ticket for a seat
like really really far in the back at
the venue
you know but I hope that the people who
want to get in are able to experience it
because I think the it's just it's just
gonna be so hype
to watch it at the actual venue
um
[Music]
I hope to see a sea of orange in a crowd
I hope so too members color orange
[Music]
foreign
ERS you can easily see them yeah
actually today
I saw someone walking outside with um a
hoodie that had pretty much the same
vibrant orange as my merchandise the omo
cat sweater I was like
is that my mama cat sweater turns out it
wasn't but that kind of vibrant orange
on the hoodie is so rare that once you
see it it's like chances are pretty high
that's my sweater because like besides
that I never see
a bright orange sweater like that ever
ever
[Music]
as like the girl who was wearing it had
her pants so close to the like middle of
her
um like chest area where I saw there was
something going on there and I wasn't
sure if that was the capability or not
and then I was like staring and staring
and staring like ah and then finally she
moved her arms and then I saw it with
something else there
I'm like ah well actually I'm kind of
relieved
[Music]
kind of relieved I guess
whenever another member says they see it
merch in a while it's almost always kfp
yeah that one is just it just stands out
so much
live meat shirt to go outside at the
moment ah that one is also very vibrant
yeah
good t-shirt
anyway happy New Year demo
wish you the best of luck
let me know what the outcome is
and even if you don't make it I'm sure
you'll have fun anyway
time junkie Duncan
ITA and thank you for the pinky
Happy New Year to you too ding dong for
the pinky what's wrong with using the
[\h__\h]
if that's a serious question but I mean
there's nothing wrong with using [\h__\h]
it's just so funny to me especially when
someone you know like sweater I think
this was about the audacity thing when
someone who like works there with that
kind of stuff for a long time
professionally and then they use like
uh a well-known free program instead of
going for like the real deal like a dope
programs or whatever
from this with Photoshop or also with
some kind of random program the same
with good Ado yeah good doesn't use
games she uses a program that I've never
before fire alpaca and I tried it and it
just
I would not have the patience for it
there's barely anything you can do with
it
[Music]
hmm
the only good thing about it is the name
no oh it's it makes everything just so
much more difficult
but I guess once you get used to any of
these programs of course they do what
they need to do and they work and so on
it's just funny to me
I just like to tease
especially about fire alpaca
Jeremy
thank you
oh my God I see the end what the [\h__\h]
oh my goodness
thank you for the pinky your first
superchat reading stream was one of the
first I watched live so it's definitely
something I remember though it'll be a
while until you see this and you might
forget why I'm even sending it yeah I
think I did how far will you be in five
of them once he wishes hey
family one since then hmm
wouldn't have [\h__\h] would you
bamboozle
why the first Super Jazz stream was so
good why why
because I cried and you enjoy seeing
girls cry huh is that it
hmm
that was a long ass dream house that was
wow
once for eight hours yeah but I only got
to like chapter five
really thinking though if I should go
easy did I think Raina started started
the game right did she like do hard or
normal like the easy one or classic or
what should you do what did you do what
what did she do
normal
normal classic
so hers will die if they die when they
die they die
people die when they are killed this is
this is normally such a funny statement
but in this case
actually makes so much
sense
people die when they're killed
sure for fine Bloom classic
ah
[Music]
yeah if you can still rewind I guess
classic isn't that bad after all
there's a lot of rewinds too I rewind it
so much in the last fight we had
and I still had like a couple charges
left
two or three
if you're like more careful then you
don't even need to rewind that much
[Music]
it being me it actually makes sense in
the context as well people die when
they're killed as they should
no
no it's just such an obvious statement
like
the sky is blue
or
when you see when it's cold and you say
oh my God it's so cold yeah we know it's
cold
oh it's snowing yeah I guess it is
the floor is floor it is what it is
I'm on hard classic and I rewind more to
optimize your speed than anything else
oh
is it that's important
should I just try to keep everyone
around the same level
be that hard
pretty important in all the games
[Music]
um
I get replayable maps soon oh yeah for
grinding um
it shouldn't be too much of a worry
anymore
your birthday is a celebrate day is the
day you celebrate your birth
duh
huh anyway thank you for the pinky thank
you for the hard work it's always
excited to find them yay we're in the
five of them Arc now
I'm really happy but I can't wait to
play more tomorrow
maybe not the club thank you for the
recipe
[Music]
taxi funds potential CEOs don't ride
public transportation like common
peasant also we don't want to lose that
buff
[Music]
lose that buff
mean my butt
but how would my butt not be lost if I
go with taxes because then I don't even
move anymore and then and then
um
I think walking moving a bit more is
better for my butt than not moving at
all
hmm
because it needs to you know
gotta work out to make the butt tight
and not just soggy
anyway
you have another culture very very nice
of you
you give me taxi funds you're not
calling me a taxi
that is how it should be thank you very
much
Patsy Duncan happy new lunar year to
YouTube
and with that that was the last one
for the Japan tangent stream
[Music]
okay
okay next one is the last one I think I
can do it because it has less pinkies
and reds
foreign no I wish I want to sleep I want
to eat but no I'm not running away from
it now we're so close to the Finishing
Line we're Bitcoin to give up let's do
this
for the pinky
[Music]
that one is so good though
Jackson's annoying cousin that that
whole Arc is so funny
ever had a friend ask you for a favor
that was just way too big to say yes to
um
no I don't think so can't think of
anything
[Music]
my friends don't really ask me much for
favors at all
right attention no
just giving a pink Super Chat what it
deserves the attention it deserves
anyway I can't think of anything so
yeah I guess that's a good thing thank
you crows done kitchen for the recipe
chat welcome back you Wawa here's a late
Lunar New Year envelope are you
celebrated too
it was also my third birthday yesterday
skfp oh
[Music]
how is that possible
Oh I thought the third like anniversary
of us
uh but then I thought that why you you
don't have a third year batch yet though
[Music]
but we are in here for right now and
okay okay okay it's your real birthday
the first one okay okay I'm back on
track
oh
[Music]
happy belated birthday
yeah
congratulations how was it how was your
birthday
did you celebrate or were you sad about
getting older were you trying to forget
your birthday
I hope you were trying to celebrate
such an occasion is a happy one
just want to thank you for all the fun
times can I request a new little [\h__\h]
birthday message
and maybe an employee number
would you have one should have asked me
earlier love you and take care
well well well you have barbecue um
birthday barbecue
nice
employee number is
um
you sent this on the 23rd of January
which in numbers would be like one two
three but I'm guessing such a number is
already taken
laughs
Want to Have Fun done this before did I
give someone one two three before
it's like a number where you would think
she's not even trying but
can someone check it is taken okay then
how about 241 isn't that how uh people
in America would ride it anyway
because
no
no no no it doesn't that's how we would
ride it here maybe
two three one yeah small to big or the
other way around big too small
so either day month year or year month
day
anyway so
[Music]
is is is two frame one taken
okay
well your birthday could now be either
the 23rd of the January or
[Music]
the 31st of February
or maybe this number of course has
nothing to do with your birthday at all
hmm
[Music]
so we will never know that of course
as all of this will be censored after
the VOD is archived
happy birthday you little [\h__\h] my throat
is dying you little [\h__\h] how dare you
there you make me sing this now
Cruise you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
I want to have some barbecue I haven't
had like
western style barbecue in a long time
you're welcome don't worry about it
I'm dying but that's just my constant
state
um
[Music]
as we all are constantly dying
every day
after our birth we are getting closer to
death as such we are always on the way
to die
hmm
are you okay oh yes sorry sorry did I
not give you a kiss all right come here
[Music]
I don't even know how much of that you
saw
probably not that much
[Music]
[Laughter]
that was very Square
[Music]
okay box jaw
I'm gonna punch you
I was there though
anyway thank you
hi Heather thank you for the rise up
foreign
[Music]
in chef
or INF Jeff
and for the pinky yeah I'm excited for
another Fire Emblem game I hope you
don't mind if I hold off watching you
play through until I have to have a
chance to go for the story myself
well well as long as it's not
too long too many months later are you
planning on doing it soon
look forward to binging the boss later
enjoy the game yo it better be soon
don't don't don't wait a year or so
please please please please please
please
please please please please don't forget
about it you're gonna forget about it if
you wait too long
hoping you will
watch the Bots soon
for now we're not that far in just yet
so you can already start have you
started have you started yet
I hope
go go go play the game what are you
doing
love head all the same if you know play
the game
[Music]
right now
damn I can't complain
oh do you do you say you do feel the
same
[Music]
time
a Bossa Nova version of do you wow
cool
hmm
do you do you
Play Fire Emblem just yet
thank you Jeff
right
Daniel everybody and also by the way
thank you all for all the sweet messages
I see you I'm just not gonna read all of
them now
but it's nice that you all are so happy
about me playing Fire Emblem thank you
foreign
[Music]
back in 2020 but I was able to get
through it if I can't then so can he
fight on oh but I don't think he's that
like desperate about it just yet
as he said he was just chilling
I think once he tries to get a job he
will find one um quickly so I'm not
too worried about that
but yeah
thank you though and I'm glad that
you're out of that boat now
um
yeah it's rough when you really want to
find a job and get a job and just can't
find one I think I've never been in that
position because
yeah the although hmm
in some sense maybe I was but not in the
most normal sense
yeah because the jobs that I've done
before whole where
yeah mostly it's in yeah normal to get a
job easy to get a job
um
and I haven't been jabbing that much
anyway before
so I can't really relate that much
but yeah that sucks when you want to but
you can't
and you need the money I suppose
um
and you try and try try and just can't
wait
[Music]
don't don't you use that word I've heard
it before
thank you
chopping
is a professor of wrestling I've heard
since before though
I may have actually heard it in German
though
yeah
I'm surprised it's a wrestling dude what
the [\h__\h]
well you know what I mean
eh
definitely heard it being used in the
sense that I mean it
for
we don't really say jabbing but I've
heard it elsewhere
not that crazy
yeah it's kind of for job hunting I I
think or like
um
I don't know doing many jobs at the same
time I don't know
not a good username
May believe thank you for the red super
chat not every mythical Monarch is as
smart as our attention
um
before any thousand year power nap
should make sure she would have a harem
of 10 minimum and at least one kid
perhaps remember succession crisis will
be decided for idle battles as Internet
as its tradition
but idle battles would probably be
something like rock paper scissors
according to akb48
that's how dare Idols battle each other
for the center position
um
so it's really not that scary although I
guess it can be because like that's the
most intense rock paper scissors to
exist in the world
the most intense version of such a
simple Carefree childish game
[Music]
intense hand shapes
anyway thank you Maple Leaf I feel like
I already kind of saw this and chuckled
about it when it came in already
originally yeah yeah yeah yeah thousand
years and so I'm prepared unbelievable
unbelievable
it's like it's their first time in the
rodeo
um
Rebecca
it's like what is going on there these
are like free Canadian super chats in a
row
[Music]
it's like they were together in a room
and they were like okay we should all
send kiwawa
a maple leaf super chat right now
Canadian Bros I guess my first time ever
sending an AKA Spa I've always loved
your streams they always pick me up when
I'm having a bad day really
just stayed up all night playing this
game hope you enjoyed I'm really liking
it so far PS I Love You
[Music]
Rebecca oh I wish I
wish I stay up all night playing the
game but I have to keep the fun for the
stream last night after ending the
stream I really felt like playing more
but I couldn't
ah this was rough a little bit sometimes
when I want to play more of a certain
game and then I have to wait
yeah but tomorrow tomorrow it's 4 P.M my
time we're continuing
[Music]
oh it's almost midnight what
thank you Rebecca and I hope you can
catch up with me don't fall behind
because
ideally would be nice if you can watch
my stream's live right so yeah yeah
let's enjoy it together
mwah thank you for the support
foreign
[Music]
Bell who also sent a wordless red Super
Chat thank you very much
Sam you're welcome
to write something I would like to hear
something from you thank you doll for
the support
[Music]
they're excited to see you continue your
Fire Emblem Adventure you're playing
free houses convinced me to join kfp day
one oh
oh
you mean you joined on the day one where
we started playing free houses
thank you so much for all the smiles and
love stand so no thank you we've come
full circle now I haven't we playing
another five emblem game now
hey hey
back then after Fire Emblem free houses
ended I really was like man
it was nice I wished I would
release another Fire Emblem game like a
main big one
in within a reasonable time I didn't
think it would happen
within my time in Honolulu but hey there
it is
back then I underestimated how long I
would be here I guess
and how quick they release games
um
[Music]
hi this is the chemiston show here right
now
well the kimberson show please stand up
please stand up I don't see them
I love seeing them don't think they're
here
[Music]
anyway
thank you very
hope you're gonna enjoy this Fire Emblem
Arc while it lasts
let's get lots of fun out of it
currently
I can't wait to play more next week
probably also gonna play at least twice
a week maybe even three times who knows
um
again thank you oh I should really get
that DLC the big moth outside of the
front door
what is that name I love that that's
funny don't have a big mouth outside my
front door though
Steven either how am I reading those
names now
sorry thank you for the pinky
it's been a while I somehow avoided most
trailers me too so this should be a fun
stream series hope you enjoy it yeah I
don't think I watched anything except
one
one stream trailer a stream
game trailer I can't I'm broken
but I completely forgot the contents
anyway which is good
a game where you summon past Fire Emblem
here was like persona oh is that the
thing you do in Persona yeah that's
finally playing Tokyo Mirage says
that's where it ends
but also what you do in Tokyo Mirage
sessions
do you also
summon past Fire Emblem Heroes
or is that just a thing that you do in
any Fire Emblem game it's just free
houses was different
[Music]
okay but it seems to be the same for
Tokyo Mirage sessions
yeah but it's idols
yeah just those two ah okay okay
the summoning is new
well as I said it kind of makes it feel
to me like an
All-Stars film game but the whole
All-Stars part I guess is on purpose
because it's an anniversary game as
someone told me
but it seems like something that would
typically not be released as like a main
big title you know the fact the whole
like
idea the concept of bringing back all
the old characters but maybe that's just
me because they don't do that in tails
of for
main games they do that for side games
you know entails of there's been games
where they bring old characters but it's
all like sad games
not main releases
so to me it feels like it would be a
spin-off for like a smaller console or
phone or whatever
um
[Music]
but I mean why not make it a main title
I mean
you know wanna get those like old
characters get some appreciation again
right I mean this there's no need to
make it into a smaller spin-off game
if you think about it
hmm
like tales of the race yeah
pretty common fart
it's more like a gimmick idea that they
made into swimming yo that's what the
fat like to me but that's maybe just
because I've been brainwashed by tails
off and maybe other games that I can't
think of right now
[Music]
loves to celebrate their older titles
except for racing them to the West
I've heard I've heard
of the world's Fire Emblem oh yeah this
is the word rally and mythology that was
one of those I loved that I played it on
the PlayStation Portable
um
sir 956 Freak video game
all right Ellen thank you for the
rainbow and you filled out everything
[Music]
yay my throat is excited just kidding
you have a wonderful year 2022 Kiana
with your caring nature you always show
us chickens how much you care about us
by now kfp feels much more like a family
than anything else oh
with all the hard work you put into
everything you do you prove time and
time that even when luck gives you an
opportunity you still have to grab it
yourself mm-hmm
by watching your successful path I have
found enough motivation to change my
life last year I had a burnout and had
quit my job oh oh
but good for you for quitting it
yesterday I signed for a new one with
much better prospects I also lost 75
kilograms
[Music]
in the last year and I'm now completely
new chicken with finally a positive
outlook on the future oh wow
value streams which always uh put a
smile on my face and lift my spirits I
don't think I would have had the
strength to come out of the valley I
wasn't
away I look forward to many more years
in kfb and as I have no skills to offer
I'm very happy to be able to support you
in this way thank you our the heart and
um
I think that's supposed to be saying
heart
of Polo Indian and the key factor for
the success of the whole group thank you
[Music]
wow but
you give me the credit but I think you
would have been able to do that on your
own
think you have the strength to do it on
your own
but thank you for giving me some credit
I'm glad if I really could help
to push you towards that direction
a healthier direct Direction both
mentally and physically yeah
really really proud of you
congratulations
it's like a huge turnaround and
I think yeah your future looks really
bright and and and you're gonna be so
happy with all the changes yeah be proud
of yourself okay
damn respect
all of kfp
nice
[Music]
so now
just kind of get things rolling this
year
everything is in your hands now you've
got the
what do you call it I I think you maybe
understand German anyway because it was
a Nero
in the hand
the horse thingies that you control the
horse with
in German you say that
and auf wiedersehen I guess
the rains oh
not in English though you have the reins
in your hands
do you say that so saying in German
oh you do oh
I don't know sometimes our sayings
overlap
hmm
anyway you know it seems like I inspired
you but the way you tell me your story
you inspire me back too so
thank you for that and yeah
I wish you all the best thank you for
sharing the story with me
foreign
[Music]
usual time slot I'm proud to see you
adapting to hard mode Let's Go
gamerovian
I would like to like experiment a little
bit but once you change into easy the
fact that you can't change it back to
Heart makes it really difficult to make
this decision
um
Well for now tomorrow I'll continue with
hard
I think I'll be very proud afterwards if
I do the whole game in hard mode but
yeah
it's
really
kind of mean that you can't change it
back hey what happens if you do a safe
slot
and then you switch it to easy or so
and then you don't like it and you just
go back to the safe slot where it was
hard still then that works right
I assume
should be
but still
[Music]
man
but that still means that you would have
to go all the way back to depending on
how many how much progress you've made
at that point so just get the DLC that
will help you really
best place to win then what I spent 30
bucks extra after already spending 60
bucks
and it will be helpful to me
well that's pay to win that's called pay
to win
it will help a lot what
[Music]
it what what does it give me I text like
op weapons or
op characters too
[Music]
oh
no it doesn't apply in tails off because
I didn't pay for my DLCs
so it was never paid to win and also
those DLCs yeah
I don't know most of them were outfits
but I guess there were some items too
so but that's free to win because I
didn't pay for them
okay okay well I do want idle card that
was that would be the reason for me to
get the DLC not all the extras but bonus
XP skills
bonus stat growth skill
strong engage weapons
uh
uh anyway thank you Rosaline I'll
continue going with hard mode but please
don't be mad at me if I switch too
easily eventually maybe I don't know for
now I'm going hard
I forget
[Music]
for the pinky
play as you see fit okay
um but easy isn't even easy it's not
even called easy isn't it called normal
sorry I'm exhausted
[Laughter]
glad I could make it for at least some
portion of the stream the old free
houses are when I started watching my
Aussie looking forward to even more
maybe also one of those
who joined at the
free houses stream damn there's a lot of
you guys and you guys stayed so long I
feel like whoever joined in free houses
they were just there to stay
wow
[Music]
thank you Nathan cotton
you got a free kiss it was a pinky
oopsie
I'm getting sloppy
damn it
fluffy snail bird fantastic
[Music]
thank you though Hildegard Danke Schoen
giant mode thank you for the recipe chat
the attention light happy New Year wish
I could send this since new year but
time zone was not kind I was on board
during Japan trip
um as many were the tangent was
delicious though let's make even more
lovely memories this year and Beyond
lower to kfp Viva La Canada thank you
yeah I hope I won't run out of tangents
whenever I run out I'm gonna go make
some more gotta go on a trip or
something
thank you giant mod
very much appreciated Happy New Year to
you too
yeah hope you can watch my streams
normally again now maybe
hopefully
thank you for standing by and waiting
for me mwah
[Music]
no thank you for the red super chat
against your happy Luna New Year sorry
for being so slow to offer my best
wishes I wish you good health this year
oh don't worry about it I didn't stream
a couple days after that
um
so all good
I appreciate it thank you very much
are you guys still alive hello
wake up almost done almost done
no my chat actually died and you guys
died too
my chat died for real here we go hi
hi
ah
so thank you blue Chan happy Luna New
Year to you too
I hope you will continue supporting me
this year okay
[Music]
thank you for another recipe
how the first meeting would go if Kiara
had full control of the conversation
instead of writers yes the queen my
mother has passed away but Queen Eve if
I may take celine's hand I can call you
mommy oh
Celine
would prefer her as a sister as a little
sister in Addison wife but yeah maybe
she could just adopt me
the the queen Eve I mean though not not
Celine I don't want to be celine's
daughter Queen Eaves daughter though yes
I need a mommy figure
my character needs a mommy figure in her
life otherwise and I see
no good future ahead
need a mommy to leave me
um
unfortunately it's not looking very good
in that
direction
thank you Maple
leafer thank you for the recipe chat uh
Pink Super Chat I can't see colors
anymore it's over I'm dying
thank you for this dream today and
welcome back boss I didn't realize how
nostalgic I'd feel to be watching I
can't read anymore Fire Emblem again
excited to watch and also play along I
recently got
hahaha I read it differently bumped
too full time so hopefully I can stay
out of spoilers my eyes are seeing
things man
[Music]
you don't want to know what I saw oh man
ah
okay
[Music]
ah
have fun I'm so sorry
wait what
you got bumped against your will or did
you want to be full-time
if you were full-time now then you
generally can't watch me that much
anymore right oh no
I hope you can still make time
otherwise kiwama gonna cry okay kiwawa
gonna be very very sad
need to grab those health benefits
um yeah that's understandable
that's important
but you're here now
yay thank you all for
so full time and also you're trying to
play Fire Emblem while also watching me
that sounds tough ooh
ooh good luck with that you gotta you
gotta do like multitasking and play
while I'm streaming then you can do two
things at once at least
free full-time jobs I almost like free
houses
fell nicely into my shift oh at least
this week right that's good that's very
good hope it's like this all the time
well good luck with your full-time job
now and don't forget about King wow
thank you for still trying to watch me I
appreciate it really
[Music]
you're the last one can you believe it
you are the Finishing Line
let me step on you
thank you mentioned 14 then I use a
super chat you are in a once mentioned
your interest in the mirror I read this
one already
Hallelujah and well now you know what
I'll do you the favor and look it up
I know
well I know Fantasy
XIV near
uh-huh
ooh
noise
wait it looks exactly like to be
damn
there's like
you know a similar I guess Graphics
stuff and like
body
style or whatever I don't know how to
explain but
it just works those
fashion items
it just looks like two beers in the game
wow and then what's something about the
red what do you fight
I'm not sure what's happening there
you got some story too I wonder
[Music]
oh she is in the game but you can also
get her outfit right
she has black hair and a white dress in
this screenshot
and yo
that's an alternative to be that
I have never seen before
[Music]
2p wait what's 2p
is that something I came up with for
Final Fantasy 14 or
is that something that
is just part of the near automata
universe
from fighting games
oh
it shouldn't have been more like I don't
know
[Music]
two
see
hmm
oh Soul Calibur oh she looks good like
this too
but the OG is best
[Music]
second player I don't know it makes
sense
2B 2p
the second player got to play 2p
okay
nice thank you
sorry I can't even get my voice out
anymore
guys thank you guys we have done it
almost six hours of super surgery
engines in between
go rest I will
Oh I thought maybe it would take me four
hours I didn't think it would take me
six hours yeah
Kiana really is back
I'm also front
I'm also front I'm back and I'm front
and I'm up and I'm down
[Music]
yeah I will warm up my food now and then
I'll make my farm level tomorrow I guess
um
huh
I'll never let this happen again but
this was really just such a
difficult situation where I got sick and
then I got sick at a time where you know
super chats do flow in a little bit more
than usual supposedly unless I don't
stream but yeah and then I travel and
then I couldn't stream anyway that much
and then the streams that I could do
would be wasted if I would do Super Chat
ratings for it
hmm
[Music]
I have noticed
obs
OBS ended my stream early
hey I didn't say you'll be the same
that was open that's not a smoothie
don't worry
obs ghetto
[Music]
um yeah they saw the end of the Super
Chat they were like whoops finger
slipped
okay and in German we say happy doesn't
thank you for keeping me company while
doing this thank you for waiting for all
the super chats to be read I appreciate
it we won't have it happen again at
least not at this extent
foreign
[Music]
about that one that's uh I have no
stress about that one
oh
yeah I'm keeping them
on purpose
good night everybody
thank you oh
oh
man
[Music]
foreign