[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
hello
welcome
it is october
spooky spooky spooky october
welcome yes i have
been made aware it is october
[Music]
that means it's only like
two two months to go
um the year is ending so quickly
i'm not i'm not so much stressed about
halloween coming
up more about like the year ending
so quickly by the way i just woke up so
i i'm maybe not um fully energetic yet
oh yeah i guess it's three months
i mean i guess you some of you guys want
2020 to end
which i understand but uh
i don't i don't really want 2020 to end
because it's just too
[Music]
too fast
oh yeah i missed a good stream i was
sleeping
how was it guys i i saw lots of
excitement
in the discord that's all i saw
you all watched it of course you all
watched it
oh yeah i saw jago was there i saw a
screenshot of his message
yago when are you coming to my stream
why are you coming to my stream what did
she sing
because she didn't leave the archive
right what did she sing
does anyone know does anyone remember
oh i just listened to that song before i
started streaming oh my god
girl angel's faces huh
hey bloody stream what's bloody stream
gurenge huh
[Music]
it's one of my favorite [\h__\h] monogatari
songs
she sang that
what that's one of my favorite
monogatari songs
oh well
yeah i actually also to my
karaoke list for future songs i also
added um
flawful time
my arm is broken why is your arm broken
like for real
hope you get better soon hope it heals
quickly i never ever broke anything in
my life
you know what's weird i never my voice
is still so
wakey wake not so wakey wakey i just
wakey wakey
um i never
broke anything in my life and
like i always felt like i want to break
something
i always felt like kind of boring that i
never broke something before
i also want a cast so
i've been thinking this for many years
like i wish i would also break something
one time in my life i want people
to come to the hospital to see me i want
people to ride on my cast
that's the m speaking no i just
don't it hurts
[Music]
you broke my heart and i want to break
my
actually it would be really good if i
break my shoulder or something
because my shoulder is really [\h__\h] up
to begin with
uh so i was always thinking like i just
want to rip out my arm
and then throw it away and then get a
new arm
connected to my shoulder because yeah um
can i just break my shoulder i feel like
if i if i once
just completely break it it might um
be able to heal finally
yeah that's my logic i think that is
actually possible
yep no i also did not watch becca last
eight hours
i just catch something on twitter that
kind of implied that she didn't
make it or so and she streamed for eight
hours and she didn't make it or what
unbelievable
that's a lot a long time
but uh eh
no crowns in eight hours what
zero wins in eight hours what the hell
but that is because that is because of
the stream snipers if there were no
stream snipers
i'm sure she could have done it right
[Music]
welcome to the membership guys
yo so today thank you
thank you for the super chance in the
memberships thank you thank you
today i sprint both my arms and ankle
four weeks ago it was painful you don't
want to
i do want to break something i'm very um
used to pain
i'm very used to pain so i'm like
under constant pain so i'm using it
so today we are playing some more
minecraft
and then i am taking a little break over
the whole weekend
so thank you for coming today everyone
it's a very important day
it's the day before the disappearance of
takanashikiya
yeah i'll be gone
and i don't even know how much i can
stream next week
might also be not that much the
disappearance of takanashikiya
yeah so let's go
i prepared some things in minecraft
because i got addicted i couldn't stop
you hear the vgm right
wait did i move something here what is
that
whoa
[Music]
welcome so let's let's get into it shall
we
i have um done some
exploring and
of course uh
once i did not stream i was able to find
a village
and it looked so pretty okay i'm on the
other side of the village now here it
doesn't look so pretty
but
[Music]
i already checked out all the houses
there was nothing special here was it a
bit laggy
uh that was there was nothing special
here uh
but i didn't leave some wheat bundles
here you can see
i am harvesting but
this village is so pretty that i feel
like bad for
like destroying it so i didn't want to
destroy it
look at those houses they're so pretty
[Music]
they're so pretty where are all the
people by the way hello
hello oh there were so many people
previously
hello it all died
so i checked all the chests already ah i
got some
empty maps on paper and that's about ah
and the card
carter carter cartography table
so that's cool that's at least something
well where are all the people hello
hello there's the golem
some of you told me to hit the golem and
no i'm not stupid
so here's one guy hello
they have this huge weird waterfall
thing here
very dramatic hello and he i don't know
that's probably not so good
that's such a good deal i don't know
maybe it is was that a good deal guys
there's a child stupid child
no one likes children that's not true
actually i think i do like children
and there's a kitty cat jumping up the
mountain so cute
bad deal okay i don't know what's a good
deal you guys gotta help me with that
kind of stuff
wait did i check that house i did not
check out
maybe the good stuff is there yeah i
didn't even see that are you okay
are you okay excuse me
i'll just check out your house hopefully
you have something
no of course you don't make
it's a useless village but it's pretty i
was thinking like i wanna i want a house
like that i wanna copy
that kind of building so maybe one day
i'll just destroy one house completely
and take take everything they got
yeah and i even didn't didn't kill their
animals because i felt bad
for like if i would take their animals i
don't know i would feel like such a bad
person
i don't wanna i don't and see this is
probably also a bad deal right
is that a bad deal it feels like it
but yeah there was nothing here really
nothing that's bad oogie
what is a good deal i wonder so
uh that's actually like i don't know is
there anything else you can do in the
village here
because otherwise i'll bring you back to
my place
is there anything i can do here
yes oh yes
make a farm well i already made a farm i
want to show you
oh hello it's assembling huh
wait oh wait it's not you who are the
ones
do they look different the ones that are
trading something do they look different
no some no i don't maybe with the white
apron
i know you also have that
still some of the villagers how am i
gonna steal the villagers
i don't want those guys with me actually
i
already got someone else at my apartment
if he's still there
the bell you got
i already stole one bell
oh okay where's the bell again
you guys and the bell i hear this
always stealing those bells wow
where are you going ah you're going in
your houses they're all going in one
house
you don't all fit in there
that's cute that's so cozy well
but wait if i steal that bell are they
not gonna be alarmed when things happen
and they'll all die
i don't want that to happen
i don't want them to be in danger no yes
yes oh
well then i'm not gonna steal it i'm not
that mean
okay oh i see a tower for me
uh yeah the last time i played i
actually also used coordinates
and i found my way let's see if i find
my way without coordinates today
er let's try to get home and there
i have prepared a mine
a great tower that's uh there's nothing
around the tower but i think i came from
there
i'm just too lazy to open the screenshot
with the coordinates right now
but we'll find back i'm sure
i might think i'm sure is there any
sign from me coming here no
awesome awesome i guess i
i think i have to open up the screenshot
to find where i came from yep okay it's
turning night though oh my god
and where the screenshot second one is
icons
[Music]
this one yeah
okay in coordinates
are one five two seventeen
two three eight
let's go so that means
uh
this
for okay at least for that for the x
x x x this way you should be right
and then for the set x so
just give me some time let's go into one
direction first and then
find the other directions help it's
night i should have just slept no i
shouldn't actually wait did i sleep and
i won't i forgot if i slept in that
village before i wonder if i
died it was not that far right so
i think we'll get there quickly
i also uh killed
a billion of fish i told you guys
yesterday in the talking stream but i
killed so
many fishes leave me alone
oh wait i gotta eat oh don't explode me
don't stop oh my god
eat
i wish you could eat while running okay
wait wait um we already passed it okay
and then
two three eight two three eight ah wait
i need to
i need to find myself uh is that
that's the way that's the way just
hoping the other one doesn't change too
much
actually it goes down a bit that's maybe
good it
you go up
i'm only looking at accordion it's not
looking good at what's around me really
leave me alone i'm
busy
wait i can't pass that where am i
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
we gotta go over here
yes you can uh-uh i'm not gonna make oh
there's a block there's a block from me
wow
and another one wow smart me
and another one yay
oh i see my tower hey oh that's
that's such a good feeling when you
finally come home
such a good feeling when you find your
home
and now i will show you the improvements
i have made in my home
actually it's only around my home
and i have a fence and my wheat farm is
bigger
yay and there's a lot of torches around
so
that the enemies don't come too close
and the thing is though
the owner of the llamas kind of bugged
out he's still there but he's
still invisible like if i if i click on
wait actually the only problem is i
can't really get uh
in there unless i jump from here
he should be there he should be there
yeah see i can still train with him
i can eh he's meant to do that
oh at night oh really but i feel like he
was also invisible during the day
but well yeah i i managed to
what there's a did i just see a potion
what did you guys see that
that's buggy and he was there for a
second anyway i i
i managed leave me alone i managed to
capture them so they belong to me now
yay oh he
oh he's drinking invisible potions
yeah so smart wow the npcs in this game
are
low-key smart
right what do you think about my
improvements
it's bigger so we can have more bread
cans
i was too lazy to make a bread and make
a
gate yeah do i have a hole right now no
[Music]
okay
okay i think now now we got oh
oh yeah and
okay
[Music]
yeah i should oh i've been jumping on i
guess
oh could you please leave them alone
you're not gonna get in there okay
okay and then i've made some i made i
didn't make much improvement here but i
did make some stairs don't leave me
alone leave me alone
so see stairs and then here stairs
i stole them from and that
uh ender navigates that we found the
incomplete one and look i have so many
fishies
that i already cooked and i also got a
[\h__\h] ton of mushrooms
but then i realized only the red
mushrooms are not enough
so yeah that's that
but that's okay so with the cartography
table i guess we can just put it here
i'm i'm not sure how to use it
so now i couldn't make a map right but
i'm done
i don't want to do that right now right
so let's put that in here
and maybe make some more bread
and but how do i make bread again
how do i oh
yes okay and how do i use the hay bale
ah oh
very useful very useful indeed
nice i could have gotten more oh wait
there's much more here
i could have gotten way more that's so
much bread
oh yes but i
felt like not taking too much away yeah
it looks uh it makes the
the map bigger right um
yes wait oh
i can still make a little bit
so
that's a bit annoying but okay
bread for years yay so much bread
yeah yeah yeah i guess we can just go
with bread now
and leave the other stuff in here so i
have a food chest
and i have a chest with stuff and i have
a
chest with stuff
all right so we shall
start the exploration
of
the the the
mine shaft that i found i guess it's
called mine shaft
yeah but wait what am i doing what what
am i doing what am i doing
i want to
do i have do i have more iron
yeah i do yeah i also got some more iron
so that i can make more
where is it iron pickaxes
oh [\h__\h] i need sticks
okay i'm getting used to this actually i
haven't played for like what two days
huh is it two days or one day i think
two days now
so i already uh got a bit unused to it
but it's already getting back
to me i guess that's enough for
exploring is that enough
maybe one more stone
um yeah
and then leave that here
leave that here leave that here look
down here
torches torches do i have torches no
wait can i was i able to make torches
with redstone dust
oh wait i don't have oh wait i still
have some here
oh yeah armor and shield oh my god yes
you're right
oh oh i can make redstone torches
okay wait uh huh
[Music]
okay that's enough torches i hope
what the hell
yeah i gotta make weapons ah
no space
okay wait what do i need
i need iron
[Music]
yeah let's see what we can make is that
enough to make some stuff
actually look oops
oh hey i'm wearing i i'm wearing some
stuff so i only need the top
yeah nice nice nice nice
so you wear that and maybe a shield
would be nice
maybe a shield where is the shield
[Music]
and there i need some planks goddammit
can you just
take it out of my treasure chest
okay
oh i don't think when you call somebody
[Music]
weapon eh well i kinda do have weapons
you don't think it's enough
bucket bucket wait i still have a bucket
somewhere
i still have one because i made one yeah
there we go
i made one because if you decide on toy
that i had enderman
visit me in my home for some reason
don't know why he came what he was
trying to do
but yeah
[Music]
what sticks with it sticks oh whatever
let's just bring all of it
let's make one more iron sword
that should be enough
okay now i think we got it all
i think we got it all so bye bye
hello
okay let's go
i have found the thing oh do you know
he's yeah he's really there
i have found the thing that uh i've been
looking for
my whole life my whole minecraft life
let's go a shovel oh
i could i guess it could be useful no no
i don't need a map it's really close
it's really close
believe me it's really close i don't
need a map
it was somewhere here
this is uh you know the special thing we
found in the beginning and
the place should be
was it here
yes
that i tried to make some stairs here
but didn't really work out
wow nice stairs kiara
how the hell do you get down here kiara
how do i
well okay that's another way to get down
so i came here
i saw this and was like oh my god i want
to explore but then i was like
no i shouldn't i should just explore
with the others but i did put some
torches
here here here here so we could go that
way
or we could go that way
do we go that way or the other way
i think it's really big go that way okay
i think it's really big okay so now we
do the trick
oh god i hope i get out of here though
we do the trick
we put all the torches on the
left side okay we remember
we put them on the left side
yeah i'm scared
left side where is left here
okay let's let's get started with some
of this stuff
i hope you find something nice because i
have quite the expectations for this
place
moshimos i hope this
ah nothing dangerous awaiting me
hello hello you wanna fight come here
you don't see me
fight me oh they're not really
coming why are they all waiting here is
that a spawner
i heard a spider dumb the spawners but
is that a zombie spider
[Music]
i guess whatever that is good for
hey nice and there's no more coming is
it really a spawner
i see a chest maybe it was not not a
spawner
left side
do i have to kill the bad
melon seeds nice
bats don't do anything okay but it
scared me
somebody once told me that bads are
dangerous too and i should take care
i did not know that but
i believe in you okay so what's in there
now is that good also has more torches
nice
actually let's take all of that no no no
no
no but the rails we don't need right
okay thank you for that oops what am i
doing
ah why is it keep trying to type
why does my why
no no
whenever i press w it doesn't work
anymore it just tries to type
how do i make it stop wait i don't no
no no i can't move right now
yeah japanese input make it stop
press enter it doesn't work
how do i how do i chat
press escape i did already
i can't move it keeps typing w
press t no it just keeps typing t
oh wait wait wait wait
[Music]
foreign
wind and space really you're not telling
me weird things
what okay no it's not going to be what
the
[Music]
okay
that was a big panic moment
let's turn on the air conditioning
because that
stressed me out so much that i feel so
hot right now
okay so we're probably gonna get lost
here and
left hello
there's nothing here nothing here okay
stupid creeper almost killed me like for
real oh it goes down
hello
yeah replenish your life i always feel
like if it's not too low
i just don't do it oh
water should we keep on moving
wait there's nothing here okay okay
nothing here falls alive but up there
and i don't want to go here now
i will go there from another way i'm
sure we can get there
get rid of water and why
why i'm not gonna move forward anyway
but okay she does nothing
i i guess that's useful right the spider
webs can be useful
i'll get the chest use it at the
entrance and what what for
did i just get it yes to put some stuff
in
yeah let's get the spiderwebs
nice spiderwebs i love spiderwebs so
much
yay so much
storage wait where did i come from
it has to be on the right side right
there on the left side
ah here i came from here okay see it
breaks ha ha
it breaks i think
right side nice
[Music]
okay let's put
okay you can have the minecart oh we
have a minecart
yay that [\h__\h] that [\h__\h]
that [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] that [\h__\h]
oh wait i don't need that okay
let's go here i didn't finish that that
other side but oh well i want to see
this is like really suspicious
oh it goes down again
scary i hear
that take rails from minecart
i think i took some i mean i'm gonna
take
maybe the rest later
cap full of spider yeah
i'm scared
see how good i am at fighting now hey
left or right left or right chat
where do we go
left oh there's nothing here
wrong choice my friend's wrong choice
let's see oh there's so much water here
that kind of sucks
let's get some spider webs
well i shall make the water stop
oh where does this car uh it comes from
here
nice good job
[Music]
get the spiderwebs
and get that iron
oh it's actually so peaceful here
there's like nothing happening is there
more
no
oh it already stopped here huh
what's the best way to get those uh okay
well then let's take some of these with
us
[Music]
oh with this we can maybe we can make a
rail to that village and then we can
like
live there half half of the time
wait i did not put any torches oh i did
okay now we go that way
more water that's a lot of water
[Music]
oh found it
found the leak ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
what did i miss iron where did i miss
iron
this is where i came from okay
but it's so dark here oh my god
the bed scared the [\h__\h] out of me
oh iron
i'm not good with scary things
okay that was also not the exciting way
to go
okay now i will not be surprised by my
pickaxe breaking don't worry this time i
see it
i see that it's about to break so
it will not shock me this time
might still not breaking
it let's go that way
left left left
no nothing wow
[Music]
i'm sorry bad but you kind of got
yourself in there
on your arm
[Music]
i ran could i get some diamonds this
time it did not surprise me
did you guys see the video of me being
shook every time
the pickaxe breaks
genius
there's also nothing here enough
number nine there's nothing okay where
else did we not go here
okay nothing
nothing yeah
you mean spider i didn't come from here
right
okay right side came from here i think
no no no no
i it's something just disconnected
oh did i come from here yeah
i'll f4 to teleport shut up
you won't get me with that one again i
mean you didn't get me the first time i
mean i believed it but i didn't
uh touch that button you won't get me
with that one that's too easy
who do you think i am a beginner well i
am but
it's so big though nice hello
it's a bit dark here
[Music]
yay
nice kill
oh my god is that a spider spawner but
i'll stay away ah
dangerous but there's no spiders i have
yet to meet a spider here
spuda
interesting spot
all right let's use a stone pickaxe
do you guys like spiders when you have a
spider
in your apartment or whatever in your
room
do you kill it or do you let it live
or do you take it and let it out out of
your room
no don't like spiders yeah me neither
wait let's block that
set it free take it outside that's so
nice
catch and release wow nobody
kills the spider use fire and i see
spiders
i usually like sometimes i ignore it
and sometimes i i kill it
because thank you for the super chat
thank you i read them all after the
stream
let's see what's here oh we can kind of
oh
oh my god there's a crazy spider turning
around and round around
you spin my head right round round round
no no no no no what the hell is wrong
with you it's a disco spider
[Music]
sorry are you are you insulted
don't kill me don't kill me don't kill
me don't kill me don't give me thank you
oh my god
sorry disco spider i didn't mean it like
that
didn't mean i'm like that
papa
[Music]
that's enough okay hello ah
zombie my spike my sword
i'm a good warrior oh is that another
spider spawner oh my god
[Music]
ew i got stuck in the spider web how
disgusting is that actually a thing that
happened
is that actually a thing or was that a
bug
[Music]
there's like so much oh creeper
so much to explore but nothing
interesting until now
wow you really need a lot of torches huh
nothing here wow
what it's a feature not a bug
do i want to go there
how i have not really uh found
uh out how to kill a creeper without
dying i always just run away from them
i'll eat oh thank you
um do you wanna come here
use shield
hit and run
it's quite nice
all right do i hit it
oh nice it just keeps stopping there
explosion no yeah no explosion nice but
there's also nothing here
there's so many bats holy [\h__\h] don't
hurt me
okay that's it again from that side
where did i come from from here
oh
crazy disco spider part two right next
to the spawner
uh-oh do i just i just run and well it
will probably follow me but ah so many
ah
oh it didn't come you didn't follow me
actually did i miss something here
i know that's the that's the whole i dug
myself
wow wow wow
okay another spot we have
not checked out yet
yo
by the way i have yet to eat breakfast
breakfast break fast i have a next
tomato so when i get hungry i'm gonna
start eating oh water i see water
oh
nice why is there so much water is there
always so much water in these caves
mines
i should okay eat more ye
oh it's so big
nothing wow
except spider webs there's nothing
except spiderwebs was someone here
before i doubt it
i doubt it but there's nothing
eat breakfast while streaming nah i
can't multitask
i'm a really a bad multitasker if it's
like something i can snack on
yeah that works but
if it's like not something that's like
eatable with one bite that's difficult
breakfast asmr to be fair it's not
really breakfast time anymore
[Music]
come on give me something nice
also i wonder how long i should stream
today because actually
uh i have like so much to do
well i think i kinda
you guys already know i guess but i'm
moving
and um i'm moving tomorrow and
uh i have not packed a single thing yet
instead i'm just streaming
i i'm moving tomorrow
so i'm like yeah when i'm gonna when am
i gonna
i'll be fine i just need a day i just
need like maybe five hours that should
be enough
to pack up my whole apartment that's
that's enough the good thing is i don't
have to do the furniture
that's the good thing good luck
thank you there's nothing here again but
i'll just get
that stuff here uh yeah
i feel like i probably shouldn't be
streaming too much today
and just get my [\h__\h] done
but then again then again i feel like ah
i'll not be able to stream much during
packing asmr
i'll not be able to stream much like on
the weekends
maybe you know like i said yesterday
i might be doing a test stream members
only
on saturday and then there's a collab
on sunday but if my
uh i have like internet that i'll be
using
meanwhile because the the big one
will take a lot of time until it comes
stupid
so i'll be using like a portable
internet for the meantime
and you know those are not really
suitable for streaming i use them when i
go outside but
uh for streaming i've never tried to
stream it
i feel like uh i watched a lot of
netflix and stuff with it and it was
always very
reliable for netflix
uh but when it comes to streaming i
wonder it has at least it has no
no maximum usage so
there's not nothing like that
you're okay with potato wi-fi but i'm
not okay with that
more soul stirring yeah there's a high
possibility
there's a high possibility that on
sunday on the collab
i'll be a cardboard cut out again
i don't want that i don't want that to
happen
last time i don't don't think it was
because of my internet to be honest i
don't think it was that because i was
using my good internet
it should have been fine i will stare
into your soul again is there any spot
we haven't seen yet
oh my god leg
up in here
how long will you have potato wi-fi uh
probably like 10 days
quite a long time wait where the hell
i got stuck in that stupid spider web
again disgusting
eww right side right side right side
right side right side
right side yeah
dun dun dun
ah yeah yeah a lot of um
in collabs a lot of
people do the cardboard cutout thing
but if it's only me it's just um
lame i think
don't you think so
um procrastinating
streaming like this because i obviously
should be packing
and i'm just like i got a stream it's my
job now i have to stream i have no
choice oh my god you
wait is that is that a
what is that sorry sorry sorry sorry
break the spawner eh no
how i'm gonna die we all know i'm gonna
die if i try that
hello you have so many eyes
use torches
use torches i'm gonna dive
though probably
do i just put them there or
do i just put them on the spider webs or
cover the spawner and torches
i can't put more retreats
let's go somewhere else but was that
enough
oh oh that's interesting that's a
another weird i see lava
are you standing right next to lava
that's dangerous do you not know that's
dangerous
it's safe now go back hey really
hello no i don't want to
talk to you
go back but wait what's here
more lava
the last time i died
[Music]
that's what you get oh that's the
spawner right there
last time i was i died from
lava is because of all the jump not
because like i
actually wanted to jump into it
[Music]
that spider is
much more stupid than me
because that spider did not have all the
jump on but still
jumped into the lava
bagana kumarana
oh my god actually that's a really
dangerous spot for me to be
eat
oh my god
i saw gold i saw gold though i need to
go there
i want to see what's here too
oh my god how the hell did i survive
that i thought
and with that low hp and poisoned the
stupid
[\h__\h] spider was like oh my god this
is a dangerous place to be and hell yeah
it was really dangerous
oh my god
we have to get back up there i don't
have
wow i have so much iron i don't have so
many normal stones
hmm let's make stairs i guess
eat thank you i keep on forgetting that
keep on forgetting
i know i know don't dig upwards but i
don't know
i i guess at least i'm not digging
straight upwards
how do i do this how do i do this to
smartest shift on blocks and look
to the side to build horizontally yeah i
gotta figure that out
i gotta practice that
wait no
no no
okay
[Music]
hello
ah that's the cold that's where i want
to go
jump jump
we can do it they gotta get back up
there
oh because of that stupid spider
there's so much gold
give it to me eat oh yeah
keep on forgetting to eat
okay now be careful so how do we do that
right now i can't just do this yeah
oh god
[Music]
wow where are we by the way
we are on
where is it again
wait are we on 29 that's so high
isn't that super high
nice okay
check the lava okay how
oh it will be fine
you mean i should go to the
to the lava down there i don't want to
go down there anymore
it's a dangerous place
so that i don't fall down there ever
again
there might be diamonds
eh
but i wanna finish oh my god
i wanna finish uh this exploration
how do i it didn't work
i can't put that [\h__\h] there
maybe now
yeah okay
smart ah no yes
okay is that enough
break it what do you mean break it oh
wait is that gonna take a long time
a minute oh
oh there's some experience points there
give it to me thank you wait so is there
something up there
we broke it nice hello
oh my god oh my god
i still hear spider noises
kind of worrying ew that's so disgusting
block off the lava down there
good idea so i don't fall into it you
mean
that's so disgusting that's so
disgusting
get a water bucket i i brought one i
brought my name
second i want to get all of those
spiderwebs
the spiders are still there yeah but at
least i can't spawn anymore right oh my
god how many are there
walk into it no no no no
no no i'm gonna get stuck
i know that
okay okay we did that nice
okay wait where did we come from hello
no not again
okay do we do we follow the skeleton or
do we go to the lava
what do you think guys
there's another spider why
are you alive disco spider oh it fell
down
lava skeleton lava lava
wow why do you want to see me die or
why would you want me to go there
actually can i check out that place
there's nothing here right okay
but what if there's a treasure there
hello
come at me bro you got nothing on me
trying to sound cool in english
yay nice he didn't even hit me once oh
god spider
spiders are my worst enemy
are you bugged into that wall too bad
for you
too bad for you
iron yeah yeah but i already got so much
iron
i was here before
okay let's get back up there
again
is it because of the rails
what is that
ah an arrow i was like what what what
okay let's get the iron and then go to
the lava
shall we
floating tracks nice
[Music]
so lava hello
what exactly do you guys want me to do
here you want me to find
uh i want me to find diamonds
and block that [\h__\h] off
oh let's be careful
that should be enough
okay
bye bye spider is that the right one
hello zombie
hey nice
wait so we came from there so left side
left side here
yeah we were here before should we check
out that place we actually
have endless water here so that's cool
okay so throw the bucket of water at
that right
hmm okay
more water oh maybe some torches too
i mean that's a red set but forgive me
okay more water not directly on not on
top
if i have more water don't worry about
it
look at all that water take it
how do i take the water oh okay there we
go
but now it will all disappear right
above the lava
don't die don't die when
[Music]
is there more water a bit more water
yeah i don't know i don't get it what's
the difference
i don't get it
oh wait
[Music]
huh that works too that works fine
i think what no
no it doesn't like put it on yeah i
can't see
there's still so much ah no more blocks
no no no no no no no no
no no wait i don't see my brand where's
my bread i have to
i put how do i eat it i don't see my
bread where's my bread where's my bread
i don't see him
where's my my face
now
i can still make it i could
we can still make it
why the hell did i not sleep at home
once
oh my god where am i going
no no no no
five minutes but sometimes it's like
more than five minutes to ride i've seen
it take more than five minutes and to
stop still being there i've seen that
before
no no no no no
i hate this i hate this i see a block
oh god it's turning night
five minutes while the chunks are being
loaded if you're
if oh five minutes if i'm in the area
okay wait uh where am i going where am i
going where am i going where am i going
[Music]
no wait i don't get it i don't get it
leave me alone leave me alone please
leave me alone
oh spider i hate spiders
where's my tower where's my tower
where's my tower
[Music]
i think i'm going the right way though
it has to be
two three eight on on that
and one five two
well we already got the x almost
we can do it okay now this one uh wrong
when's the right direction uh oh no
no what if i die after i died does that
the stuff from the first time i die
disappear wait blocks did i
is that the right direction
it has to go down leave me alone
no i don't have food just leave me alone
where my blocks there's a block
please tell me that's the right way
i don't see [\h__\h]
i found it
okay one let's just get in here for a
second okay cat food
uh food was not here food was uh not
here food was here
and then you know and then
okay and now um
just in case should we bring a sword
wait do i have a sword
sleep but does that does it not
disappear it's like so close can i
really sleep is it five minutes does it
include
sleeping
okay okay okay okay let's go
i don't need a sword bye hey and the man
buddy
oh my god how am i gonna find that let
me move
him i gotta find it
one minute don't lie to me
it's once it starts loading so
i think here okay
is it yeah
okay well but
this is a maze this is a f in maze how
the hell am i gonna find it
hey i'm never gonna find it
i went like everywhere huh
that's probably not it
shut up it's not 30 seconds must be more
than that
[Music]
i mean if we find the spot where this
where the spider
spawner used to be
near the floating drought
[Music]
hello hello hello
i want my goals give me my gold was i
here before
did i check this
where did i go where do i go
i don't know i went to all these places
[Music]
already
no no never give up sometimes it's still
there even though it shouldn't be there
anymore
right is it here
wait it could be here that's like that
no that no i wasn't even
[Music]
ah
i don't know where to go i don't know
i don't know when to go
was i here it all looks the same
no no no no that's that's close
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
i really thought it would be gone and i
wouldn't find it because everything
looked the same to me
everything just looked the same
but oh my god if i i
oh i panicked so much that i clicked f1
and then the interface disappeared and i
didn't thank you guys for the super
chest
and then i thought i wanted to eat but i
couldn't eat and then i just died even
though i was not even in the lava i was
just burning when i
didn't need to die and um and then
and then i didn't even spawn at home i
spawned in the [\h__\h] village but now i
found
my way so quickly i would say i'm a
professional professional
minecraft streamer now but you know i
did have some
life crisis right now i was thinking
like if you're mine and you get so much
and and you're like yay and then and
then you just die
from the simplest things and then
everything you just mind disappeared
that's like what is the meaning in
mining
anymore everything just you keep on
losing it
i don't see it
it's so depressing and so depressing
how do i do that now put in it
thank you i don't know how i deserve
super jets for that
but thank you
oh my god either oh yeah yeah thank you
what
what you're not telling me have to find
that stupid spot again
are you kidding me stay calm
stay calm you [\h__\h] creeper
i will [\h__\h] kill you
why are you already dead
what if i don't find it now what if i
don't find it now okay wait stay calm
stay calm
stay calm well did we go down there and
then
go back up did we
stay calm stay calm
no no i don't think we went from here
honestly
but i don't know stay calm it's five
minutes it's more than
enough time stay calm
day
i don't remember anything
i i don't remember anything at all
did i just find it that easily what
is
that's it right
it's too much it's too much
what the hell was that creeper doing
there
what the hell
that's where did he come from
where did he go where did you
come from cotton eyed joe
unbelievable unbelievable where's my
shield is my shield broken
i don't see a shield
i
go to chest yeah before we move on
i don't want to die again so
we should maybe go to the chest
it fell into the lava oh my god i wonder
what else fell into the level
my iron is still here my gold is still
here that's the most important right
did i have anything else that was
important
i hit zombies let's go
ah the spider webs
oh yeah my million spider webs are gone
no
let's go up oh wait that's not it
it should be there right
oh thank you for the super chat thank
you i'll
read them all at the end of the stream
oh my god
oh yeah yeah go away
i've i've been through too much okay
right side
right side nice right side
right side i've been through too much
well the shield doesn't matter i can
make a new shield oh we're already there
hey
that's not that hard
gold iron coal
coal iron oops
rails but i don't have many torches left
maybe i shouldn't make new torches
oh
my bread no
my bread i see we didn't go to that side
yet by the way
oh there's so much to explore still
my brand give me my no then i actually i
need
probably okay i need more torches and
maybe more food
and uh maybe more pickaxes and stories
if we want to keep on going
kind of just take a little look at it
and see if it stops right there or
what's the matter here
what is that is that a mushroom
why is the mushroom in here
yo i stuck
oh is that a spawner that feels like a
spawner
there was a mushroom
[Music]
get a shield get torches
yes we need it to survive
okay i take stuff i guess i uh
i guess i could take it with me
no no i hope i don't die on the short
way home
melon seeds i can make melons now
can
there was a there was a chest near the
skeleton
go now or come right back
later okay okay okay okay okay thanks
for letting me know i didn't
see it's night
it's okay we're fine hello
shut up i hate you i hate all of you
oh creeper oh no no no no
no no
no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no
no i live right over there it's all good
you don't have a chance against me
the flowers are so pretty
i brought gold home
hey food oh look at my wheat farm
wow oh my god spider i
i will never forgive spiders
spiders are the worst okay
[Music]
hmm
i need more chests
thank you for the super chat thank you
actually we could we could already
make some of that
let's make more iron
burnt to death was blown up by a creeper
the toughest day of my life honestly
so much panic what so what are we making
we are making a new shield
but wait do i have iron
yeah yep
sticks okay new pants oh i don't have
pants either
i lost my paint pants paints the lava
burnt my pants
i've been running around without pants
how embarrassing
paint
make them full i don't know how to use
it though
[Music]
and why else are we making a shield
more pickaxes maybe no
we didn't even use them that much uh
maybe how do i repair a sword
how do i repair it did someone know
mel is a great food source i wanna make
melons then
anvil what what
what
what what
what build oh is that something i can
build
what is it
what
can i build that wait wait
wait
uh a smiffing table is knotted right
smoker
what what
click search ah anvil
ah can't find it
right now it's not worth it you need a
lot of iron oh
not worth it okay i guess we'll just
make an avenue shirt
oh what make an iron block
oh well i guess it's not worth it right
now in that case
i'll just leave those broken ports here
we can repair them someday maybe
and just goes here and this guy's here
this goes here
oh god no space
wait we make some more bread too
wait i still didn't make a door for this
yeah ignore the windows sounds they just
sometimes stay like
oh
i mean some of them are not done but
whatever it's like almost all of them
are done
nicer
wait where are my llamas
no where did they go
and did they die i wonder if they died
do the lavas need food
i wonder if they died
[Music]
that's so sad they spawned
no why
and they were my only friends here i'm
so alone here i'm like all alone
i'm all alone okay
i want them to come back
okay let me get my hole and my melon
seeds want to make melons too now
wait
wait no let's keep it in here
that's not so much oh my bread is gone
the left animal wants to spawn
yeah i could have named them and then
they would have stayed
i shifted and wait why did i put my
seeds
here melon seeds only have three but
we're gonna get more
right oh and the mushrooms
i don't need so many seats
okay oh wait i wanted a hole
let's take the golden hole shall we
i mean when else are we gonna use the
golden hole if not now
gate please nah i don't need a gate
i don't need a gate
oh i said right okay now let's
uh
scatter my seeds
let's put some wheat here somewhere here
yay i'm so happy about my farm
it's so big and so pretty
don't you think
melons need space eh how much space
like one style around it
two spaces one empty block
i need two two so if i put it
here it's fine one tile in any direction
so here is fine
and then
here
make a different farm yeah maybe not now
sometime soon okay and then
here okay cool
melons i don't think i've ever seen
melon so
from the other whole life girls
i mean of course i've seen some melons
from the other hollow life girls but not
that kind of melons
but no for real like i never saw any of
them making melons
bottom left bottom left bottom left
father i'm fine with that i don't even
care anymore
if you think that is suitable for me
then all right i'll take it
oops i jumped on it god damn it
no i can't go there oh yeah
[Music]
you
okay focus on my pants i'm not wearing
my pants
so much for not being bottom left
okay so uh wait who
am i supposed to do something else let
me put the wheat there
did i forget something should i bring
something
[Music]
no torches torches
that's right torches
that's right sticks
where are the sticks where am i wait i
saw them
sticks torches
[Music]
oh oh shift click
is the best mvp
okay but we don't need so much food
thank you for the super chat
[Music]
yeah i have my shield let's go
oh yeah don't care that it's night
thank you for the super dad
i'm like today i'm having a problem with
the controls sometimes
shield and torch i have a shield
and torches
here i am again i came
to take my treasure my rightful
treasure right treasure that's probably
i
probably said that wrong and yummy
okay so apparently there was a treasure
there
here
god
creeper he's still alive he's still
alive
eh where'd he go
hey boy
i forgot how to do it
are you stuck in this spiderman
okay everything's cool that didn't hurt
me
wait
okay but it's where did you guys see a
treasure
oh wait i saw it
why is there so
those mushrooms look so suspicious to me
nice
spyderco what they look like a trap to
me
bye-bye mushrooms thank you
okay
my first laugh is lazuli
wow more seeds beetroot seeds
not bad honestly for me it's not bad i
guess we can take all those rails too
hey i never saw lapis lazuli before i
know that probably eventually
you get like more than you need but
i'm happy about that how'd you
strategic retreat
fight me
yeah well bow and arrow is not so smart
when you're right in front of me huh
why did i just drop that
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum road is the
best
food food source really
i'm kind of making a trap for myself
here but
all right thank you for the super chat
i'll read them out at the end of the
stream
not again is there a spotter for
skeletons here or like
do skeletons even have spawners like
that does every enemy have a oops oh my
god
a spawner like that
they do oh god
uh this is really such a huge
mine shaft
crazy
wow
i wonder if there's more treasure though
i want more
treasure ah there's no creeper spawning
do not destroy spawners why not
spawns because of darkness ah
wow spawn is good
ah why don't you tell me to destroy the
spider farm
and spider spawning
are the spiders useless so we can kill
the spawners
actually like i hate spiders i'm glad we
killed them
oh they're not useful
spider spawn is bad for farms
why is there so much here
cave spiders are bad that's
discrimination but okay
i also hate cave spiders
go to y2 yeah where i want to wear out
right now
41. yeah i still didn't find any
diamonds
[Music]
die job
that's enough that's
enough where did that come from
is there another spider spawner
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait no
ah
i'm like i'm not i'm not good with like
um
eating running eating running like
that's like
okay it's not so far it's but not so far
amma panic
don't panic did i just hear an enderman
oh my god wait did it just try to hit me
no i didn't right
that was just me right hitting myself
just
i just heard oh she's really close
nice
i hate them where's my iron
got it
[Music]
they all come at me i'm really scared
oh so many boats spouses
do you say vows of both it's both right
sometimes i get unsure about that
god you must be like she can't even
speak english why is she in whole live
english
wait and voting both right
why the hell what is she doing in whole
live english can't even speak english
for god's sake
okay let's stop oh my god you again
i will kill you
yes
hello lava
oh wait that's the lava that i
it seems familiar because of those
blocks i mean they're always
that i think those were put by me or no
oh
did i put those blocks there
oh my god yo
nice go away
nice nice
good job good job good job uh
this is not gonna okay
cleaning up this mess
okay should we go straight or down what
the hell is that i see something weird
there
what is that
what what is that
and no that's not enderman
it looks like a cactus
what is that it's just grass
it's just grass oh my god
where the hell did you see enderman
tayanka it's just grass
well you guys were so scared of that
grass huh
not me i knew it was cactus or grass or
something like that
you were the ones who were scared
i kind of got like a a flashback of when
i was
drowned in sand right there
not a good flashback
where the hell is this
i didn't look at you there you get the
end
there there it is
[Music]
hello sorry that i
kicked you out of my room the other day
with water
coming nicole now that music
that's so scary wait did you guys
actually see him when you said enderman
is there did you
was he actually there for a second or
i only saw grass
oh you heard him ah
[Music]
i don't know where i'm going right now
this is not really where i wanted to go
but okay
i hear spiders again not happy about
that
gohan
[Music]
minecraft
could i get some diamonds now maybe
10 13.
[Music]
maybe my papa should join the whole ibn
server
when we make one i want to invite him
i want him to join i mean
he's already you know busy with work and
then
spending all his free time watching
whole life
why not waste even more time by joining
a whole live vm server
wait i feel like i mixed up the
um whatever
sounds like a good idea right
coralia
what a genius idea
then my papa can't help me i'm sure he
will not
try any tricks on me i'm sure he'll be
on my side on minecraft and help me
right right
scares me so much oh
oh
[Music]
okay how nice
do i want to go down there where are we
i mean maybe oops maybe it's time for us
to look for some diamonds
is it
oh this never ends shift
okay let's uh but uh
shift shift okay shift is the first time
i'm doing this
so i go like until here maybe
is that no how do i do it like
underneath
there
okay
[Music]
i don't see how chef is helping me with
that though
oh okay here everything is nice
[Music]
bye
wait one second
oh my god there's like so many messages
on this card
wow wow what's going
on you
find my lava
so scary
oh okay how do i get down
[Music]
i want to make it below can i ah okay
never mind
oh when the lights suddenly
disappear so scary
hello is something here
actually i want to see some diamonds
where are we now
19. what did you guys say 10 10 to 13
should we dig a bit deeper like here
okay
even one diamond would make me happy
one second okay
me a dime hello
what is this again
oh
[Music]
fancy red color hello
thanks for joining the membership
what's hurting me what is her what
what is that this skeleton
yeah fight each other you idiots
idiots i love that about like that's one
thing i love about minecraft the enemies
attacking each other that's like really
cool
wow fancy red stuff
oh thank you this is like in real life
people telling me to eat
because i don't remember
yo hello
can i have some diamonds please actually
i just wanted to dig but now
i found another space like this hello
wow we're going in so deep today oh blue
stuff
blue stuff yay yay yay
[Music]
what can i do with flappy statues
oh more lava go back
keep eating oh yeah keep forgetting
[Music]
for enchantments oh
i say that right gold
okay where does the lava come from
though i have a bucket
i have a bucket and i don't know how to
use it
how on the floor yeah okay wait wait you
gotta do this slowly with your
instructions here
no right it should shouldn't be way more
in the back
make a waterfall it like maybe here up
here
yes no yes oh okay
one second
[Music]
acquired the skill of using water
oh wait i can pick it back up right wait
pick it back up that is not so realistic
but
oh
wow i don't know why i'm so impressed
but i'm really impressed
oh that's i wanted to use the black belt
okay
that works too
oh so much gold do you have some
diamonds too by any chance
okay do we want to keep on like digging
here
where are we 12 12 is a good
good spot why should we dig should we
dig here
gold behind me eh oh
nice good eye my friend
good eye anything else no
[Music]
wait there's some more iron here nope
not where the lava was okay then maybe
here
can we just go straight
but keep a safe distance
we are at 12. this is a good spot right
just go straight just go straight just
go straight
just go straight dig
one two hole i mean like that
really so i don't lose my pickaxe so
quickly
oh wait i should maybe use torches ha ha
yo
nice going well
okay i wonder how much long i should
stream because i like i told you i got
some important stuff to do
[Music]
i just want to find some diamonds but
that can take ages right
can take hours what
i try to touch touch oh i win
hello
[Music]
are you scared of the dark
oh gold gold gold gold gold
gold we have found gold capped wait
oh not that one that one
balls but that's not a diamond but so
much gold
[Music]
why where is it where where are diamonds
don't waste let's go one down
oh wait that's two down
i have finally become an egg welcome egg
yo where are my eggs at
hello eggs hello
egg and egg what about you
i really don't quite understand how
membership works yet did you all get
charged did you all just get charged
at the moment you join
it should be that way right
so i wonder
i still i don't i don't understand the
system like
when does the month and for everyone who
joined
today
just really one month ever after
30 day cycle all right all right so it's
not like i
i need to be stressed because it's
already october oh red stuff
we find all kinds of fancy stuff besides
diamonds actually i'm quite satisfied
oh more red stuff why
not score
store your stuff you think i'm gonna die
oh no red stuff lava
lava is everywhere yeah
you'll find diamonds soon are you sure
what makes you think that is it a bad
sign that there's like normal like
earth here
put torch in your shield hand
here
oh
wow didn't know that that works
well so much red stuff neat
wow wow wow ah that's
that's not dirt
oh oh i thought it was
dirty
keep on digging keep on digging
keep on
anything you guys want to talk about
i have lots of actually that's not true
i don't have lots of time i hear lava
i know your skeletons
they're probably above me
be careful
or it's getting louder it's probably
above me
store the stuff probably would be better
huh but i would have to go all the way
back
i don't even know where my box is like
in the very beginning
press every make a chest do i have stuff
to make a chest i don't know i don't
think so
i don't have stuff to make a chest
unless there's a stone chest that you
can make
can you make a stone chest wouldn't that
be good
jump will make you faster here
here wow
speed
where where did that came from right
side right side
came from down there huh
i wonder what disappear wow the lag oh
my god the leg
or something just disconnected
yeah i wanna
never
[Music]
but where did it come from
ah here did that come from here
but there's no torches
but it's torches are here on the right
side
i guess yeah i did come from above right
there's a spider i saw that spider
oh no no no no
ah
don't know what just happened okay
i just wait a little bit
i just wanted to place a torch but i
think i have the bucket in
in my hand
why can't i place a torch now sweat
where's the spider
wrong way go back
use the shield
okay well
why did you say that's not eh
eat it
it did why did you guys say that's not
where i came from
it did come from here
stupid spiders
this is where i i think
no yes
maybe it's another way but eh
oh my god oh my god
oh my god
hey huh
what about you huh huh huh
stupid spider
[Music]
make it visible
very visible
maybe maybe maybe today we leave it at
that you know i gotta pack my [\h__\h]
i'm moving tomorrow and i didn't pack
anything where did i come from
right side right side remember
but what's here
oh well that works no that's left side
but we're close i just saw the chest huh
shouldn't it right side why is it on the
left side ah
ah wait here yay
let's bring that stuff home
yep yep okay
eat in real life yeah i didn't eat in
real life either
and pack and what what did you say what
was your last thing
we gotta do super chat reading though
i had fun that was like really chill and
we found
lots of things really cool
and i died several times but i did not
lose everything
lucky
nice stream overall thank you
yeah i enjoyed it
i think we did some progress with mining
at least
what do they look like when they're done
that's oops
they're not done right
they're done
wait how do i harvest them
do i just keep going
i can't take it i can't
why wait so
do i need new seats how does that work
why is that broken
huh the stem will grow more oh
leave it but what about that spot in
that spot
they grow infinitely hey no need for new
seeds
what oh i want to make a bigger farm
cool
oh i want to eat watermelon now but i
think the watermelon season is over
what am i doing is
[Music]
let's just put everything here
i run woohoo
endless iron yay
wait how about do i have more i have
gold but that's maybe from later
wow oops how did i throw that
oh it's cute oh
should i leave it here i need to make a
bigger and nicer house soon
because this is a [\h__\h]
okinawa
i think i think i think
i think we can leave that down come on
that
make a castle yay
all right i think i wanna stop it here
smoothie let me drink my smoothie
i forgot to drink my smoothie
how do you say [\h__\h] in japanese
foreign
[Laughter]
how do you say [\h__\h]
no no no no no not that [\h__\h]
oh god
[Music]
i'm a bit exhausted too
now let's get uh
the super chat checked i have to send it
to the
managers first
of all
[Music]
if anyone still wants to donate it would
be very useful if you would do it
[Music]
thank you thanks for joining the
membership to everyone
okay everyone who wants to leave now
since we're doing the super chat reading
thank you for coming today
thanks for coming i hope you enjoyed it
um for the weekend i'll probably not be
streaming
much or at all i don't know uh but
there's definitely a collab on sunday
i think at the same time as the last
collab probably
uh so i'll see you there i don't know if
it was announced yet on which channel
we're doing but there's only cali and
gouda left
so it's evil one of them
we already found already found the end
i scrolled too far here it is
okay copy copy copy
[Music]
thank you for everyone who always stays
for the super chat reading too i would
feel so lonely if you weren't here
[Music]
tonight
super chat reading time check
please thank you
wait no what am i doing i hear some
zombie noises but they're not coming
into
my house right
why is the link thing not working
okay i got it i got it don't come into
my house zombies please
you'll be hearing that all throughout
the the super chat reading
close minecraft no
kara says she's gonna pack after this
but she's just going to play minecraft
[Music]
definitely not i'm just keeping it open
so that the iron
oh yeah so that the iron can be
uh you know made
oh
doubt no i really can't
oh my god i haven't i wonder i hope
there's not it's not even 24 hours left
until
the movers come the good thing is i
don't have to do the furniture
it's not even 24 hours it's like
how many hours is it
uh how to how to map i think it's like
16 hours
16 hours i can totally do it in two
hours i can totally pack up my whole
apartment until i do
no problem
my
stupid google
foreign
i actually i have a lot of a lot of
stuff that
takes up a lot of space
it's okay it's okay oh my god all these
monsters can you shut up i'm gonna
go to sleep first i'm michael i'm sorry
did you hear that i'm so sorry my
microphone is still like on a water
bottle now
microphone currently all the water
bottle
not very stable i did buy a new mic arm
i did buy a new micron
okay i went to sleep and then woke back
up in
my gran
super child is quick so
zombies can break doors what
well but it looks fine it looks fine
everything's fine
i've been playing piccolo's music over
the stream since i've gotten here
perfect
well that fits well but you guys did
hear my own music too right
i only in hardcore ah okay okay okay
okay
damn zombies breaking doors it's like a
real horror movie
you left iron in the farm wow
did
welcome to the membership hey did i wait
wait let me check
oh the the melons are already back
oh that was fast holy [\h__\h] that's so
fast
but i don't see any iron that's all
right i had another iron
it
how are they so quick
what
yeah it was just cobblestone i'm pretty
sure
okay
[Music]
yes okay i'll go uh
again thank everyone who donated today
and joined the membership i'll read them
now everyone we say dan keshen
after every name let's go
[Music]
inside
we already talked about that but
yeah at least you have something nice to
watch while your arm is broken
what did you do to break it thank you
mad scientist
looking for the top package inspector
from baron thank you soon arch thank you
very stellar thank you brian b6 thank
you
sarah thank you i won't be able to catch
most of the stream so i figured i'll
show some support and i'll catch the
archive later
have you planned eternal sonata okay
usually when you guys ask me if i play
this
played a certain am rpg mostly the
answer is no
even though i say i'm a big rpg fame fan
and i can tell you
i did play eternal sonata
that is one that i played ages ago but i
did not finish it because i was really
bad back then at games
so thank you night walker thank you
a happy lump jacket and this is a bright
place no freaky phones
yeah thank you i will uh but i wanna
one day one day i wanna break my bones
thank you sixteen bit for us
i sprained both i already read
[Music]
happens quite often
logan anderson
here's to help with your medical bills
after breaking your arm intentionally
or otherwise thank you
by the way amelia seemed like she'd be
interested in playing minecraft with you
if you were ever up for doing it oh i
think we're all we're all planning to
play together at least at least a few
times
thank
[Music]
me company for work hours
the people who watch my streams during
work funny
don't get caught would be very
embarrassing if you get caught
[Music]
trust me the shoulder is so hard to heal
it took me a few months and it was
dreadful but
you broke your shoulder before i'm so
jealous i wish i could break my shoulder
[Music]
by the way thank you for advice
yesterday it helped me somewhat
didn't really know did it really
that was horrible advice i gave you
thank you
fabian
which you're the best in the moving and
that nothing breaks missing i think this
time i'll be fine it's the first time
i'm using like an actual moving service
because i'm just so sick like i moved so
many times in my life
and i'm so sick of like always begging
like
phoenix family members or other friends
who don't really want to do it
begging them to help me because i can't
do [\h__\h] alone
and then organizing someone's bigger car
blah blah and then always something
breaks so this time
i did for the first time in my life
organized a moving service but it's so
expensive that's why i didn't want to do
it like if
if i can get friends to do it for free
yeah but this time i just i didn't yeah
this time it's moving service yeah
uh yeah
don't wanna move so annoying i hate
moving
oh my god an anime please say hi anime
girl
oh my god are you
[Music]
oh a cartography table is probably one
of the best things you can find this
early yeah
gamer 311 hi kiana this might be honest
but i just wanted to be sure
you know that i'm 100 kidding about i i
i hope so i hope so
didn't actually expect you to i made it
as a joke thank you it's really cute i
like this um
the paint style
it's like it's um bad but in a good way
thank you shin alex crowl thank you shin
v gamer 311
[Music]
conga bongo thank you frankie anger
still dancing
just popping in to say good luck on your
minecraft stream today i hate that
i have to miss the stream due to work
but i do need to make more money in
order to swim
chase meister thank you i'm so proud to
see how much progress you've made in
minecraft hope you have a nice break
during the weekend
yeah thank you i don't know if you can
really call it the break but yeah
thank you dustin heidi
and v gamer 311
it's used for machinery hey what do you
mean
machinery redstone torches are used for
machinery
what machinery
is
[Music]
[\h__\h]
please make a kfc in minecraft and
chicken farm oh i want to do that
but i still gotta figure out how to
catch chicken i have done a fan out of
you on twitter
but i'm bad at drawing done my best but
i love you so much thank you so much i'm
always checking the art tags thank you
everyone
redstone is the electricity of minecraft
i see you see it oh seed
seed works with chicken gotta remember
that
dustin hardy dankeshen missing one
dankeshan seraph amaros thank you
and scarecrow eight five one five thank
you thank you
you're the first feature wrap donut to
donate it to because you're the absolute
best
please keep being yourself and being
happy elsa as an australian i love your
casual swearing
keep it up double also i hope you do a
full cover of 99 lift balloons one day
it's my favorite song it's your favorite
song really
yeah probably um what's most uh
likely is if i do a non-archived karaoke
stream then i can sing whatever i want
apparently so we can do that
since everyone wants me to sing that
song
yeah one day brian l bank of shame karen
dummy
i drive an hour in the middle of the
night to get back home from work
and tonight was feeling lonely and sad
so i listened to your last karaoke
stream during my drive oh
thank you oh thank
you brayden buzz dan kishan
try playing your touches mostly on the
left hand side yeah i did that
[Music]
no it's a small move it's just a small
move not a big move
aaron cover thank you hey kiara wants to
say it's awesome seeing your progress in
minecraft
watching your streams is one of my
highlights one of the house of my day
you quickly becoming one of my favorite
streamers
thank you thank you and i'm happy to
hear that
thanks for the stream we want you to
know we appreciate all that you do thank
you
your company is great you're sweet and
most of all we love being we love you
being you
do what you want stay confident got it
done thank you i'm trying
[Music]
diamond spawning your lava pulses and
myth cars haul
dustin hardy a tentacled kfb dead
beats in there gets caught up by
dankeshen
rip disco spider kyra el dan kishon then
red thank you
manga fits you really well i can feel
that you're enjoying yourself a lot this
should be one of your signature games
oh yeah i think it will be it's all it's
a good game to always get back
to every once in a while between other
games i think
thank you christopher door and thank you
and tenta called kfb deadbeat pangasin
could you see thank you and styrofoam
505 thank you looking for the top
packaging
this is enough as a spooky halloween
stream yeah that's sorry for challenging
that you play a spooky game last time no
problem
thank you sean captain pepper jackson
tanker rooney thank you
thank you purple dragon vancouver alex
crow thank you
jennifer gutierrez tankishan mano kyoya
thank you
skye experience kitchen
[Music]
this is where everyone congratulates me
for finding my stuff after getting a
response
in that stupid village
thank you definitely not fair flames
thank you
extinction super cute fire thank you
everyone's congratulating me we got so
many super chats at that
moment your luck was incredible i can't
believe it congrats and finding new
stuff again it was really hard to
figure out where i was in that cave
pakistan looking for the top packaging
thank you so much
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
congratulating me
thank
[Music]
mod i don't think that we are allowed to
use mods
i think a freaking skeleton on the cat's
dance shin
tactical donut thank you chris free
dankeshen
shifty barrel thank you just yuwi tanka
thank you shin mousty smells dangerous
[Music]
that beats dan kashin swagger last
pancashin
trophy reference put what an extra laven
yeah okay we learned that now
on top of it like actually like higher
than
yeah i tried to do it like on top before
but that was not the
on top that you guys meant
yeah i don't know i gotta ask what i can
do and what i cannot do i think pro we
cannot really use smarts i don't know if
that's allowed
big smoke thank
[Music]
i will definitely say your minecraft veg
after experiencing
the sheer padding of the five-minute
recovery rule then and then the creeper
killed you as i typed it
i was like really frustrated and really
angry at that moment
like so frustrated that was horrible i
gotta re-watch them
and snow was actually funny
are you watching my own streams
thank you thank you so much
[Music]
gabrielle cronus thank you alex crowley
not so deadpool 15 thank you bronx 819
for getting my stuff back again
aka headstand
the occasional swear from you places a
smile on my face it's that precious
thank you captain pepper jack's
dunkishin
kh tank shin the red cast dan kashan the
death berry danke shin
it's been a while since i've been so
invested in minecraft i'm so happy you
got
at least most of your stuff back yeah me
too but my bread
my bread and my spiderwebs no
but still i think we we got a lot of a
lot out of it anyway
otp you should close off the entryway of
areas you have already explored with
cobblestone or
dirt that way when you have to run back
to the place where you died
oh smart
smart smart smart guys are so smart
thank you
i'll keep that in mind for next time
kiwi thank you
you should check out the official
minecraft wiki it explains many things
for newbies like
you actually think i'm gonna read like a
whole wiki
i think it's a but thank you but i think
it's better to just learn it on stream
anyway
i don't have the time to read a wiki and
even if i do it won't stay
in my brain anyway i have to experience
it myself you know
thank you this super chat is for the
llamas that left you
i hope you can kidnap more lamb i didn't
even try to kidnap them they were just
there and i fenced them in
but they're gone now i'm so sad
i wish you the best while moving to your
new place thank you
i gotta pack after the stream
[Music]
i'm gonna have to thank
it's really amazing how much you've
learned in minecraft so quickly ooh
it's thanks to you guys you guys keep
teaching me we are all so proud of you
can't wait to see more streams i was
what were you watching your debut stream
and saw
monaca italia's favorite is a favorite
series of yours who's your favorite
character
she's crazy she's my favorite
and i also like oh i just
cracked my bones again without even
moving
i also like um and
soda origin
she's kind of uh not very well known
not so appreciated but i like
uh and sengoku
yay i really like her her story was like
actually really sad
uh well everyone's story is always kind
of sad yeah
i love how in baka monogatari
they it's like genuinely a funny cute
anime but they have like really deep
story
really deep lore and everything's like
connected
and every character has like there's no
unimportant character they all have a
really big role
and i really love baka monogatari so
much
[Music]
but isn't the worst games in pakistan
that the japanese only understand i mean
yeah i i get i think i
get more most of it and even if
okay sorry i had to do a big joke
and even if there's something in between
you don't really get it doesn't really
destroy the whole thing anyway you'll
get it anyway also
i think in the subtitled versions they
often have those
translator notes but like the thing is
that there's so much
so much dialogue in in pakistani that
you would have to stop so many times
because there's so many translators
notes
so many it's just way too much dialogue
[Music]
adventure of phoenix kiara and her
endeavors in minecraft shows
us to joy sorrow angel pride anger
anger no danger anger pride and
curiosity as she explores the unknown
treasure awaits but danger is always
around the corner oh yeah
[Music]
people thank you and captain pepper
jackson
moonlight
[Music]
now let me refresh
there we go
[Music]
oh yes keep on drawing whole ibn would
be very
[Music]
yeah yeah maybe next minecraft stream
could be me building
a house brc
another fun roller coaster stream i
might not be make good at making fanart
but that make
really good memes ooh thank you maybe
you made one already that i saw
thank you scala
tactical donut thank you thank you
[Music]
advice watching a number of redstone
tutorials before trying to use it
redstone can do a lot of cool things but
it's very complicated
always watching film work nice
shane i also used the moving service for
the first time
in my life earlier this year you're
gonna love the energy saved oh yeah oh
yeah definitely
oh yeah but this is
actually like honestly i i wouldn't be
able to use a
moving service if it wasn't for you guys
i mean obviously this
this money gonna take a while until it
comes in but still
thank you so much i would have done all
this [\h__\h]
by myself if it weren't for you guys
[Music]
moving on
last one today tomorrow is my birthday
ooh
happy birthday not yet
but yeah thank you for coming then
did i did i answer that pink one
i'm not sure russell what you have
fourteen vancasion
okay we're done guys
i think we're done
it's not it's not a blank red super chat
it's a pink one i see the color
but thank you for your support
also thanks for joining the membership
thank you i will do my duty now
and pack my [\h__\h] up
[Music]
but packing stuff
in is much easier and faster than
packing out stuff and putting it into
the places where it goes
you know when i travel and i come back
home with my filled suitcase
sometimes i just
leave it for like a week there and don't
unpack it for a whole week
will you play ganshin no unfortunately
not
no permission uh also the last stream i
talked about pokemon unfortunately we
also don't have permission for pokemon
we uh i know there were other whole life
members
that played pokemon before but those
streams do not exist anymore
for reasons so unfortunately
yeah sorry i thought i could play it
because i just played it before but no i
can't
yeah unfortunately maybe one day look
get permission for pokemon again who
knows
will you play atelier rizza too i'm
planning on it but i first want to play
atelier rise at one before i start two
but also kuwait take my sons please give
me permission to play atonia
[Music]
today
i hope i hope i get permission to play
riser one before i play raiza too
i wanted to i wanted to finish riser one
before raiza 2 comes out we gotta see
those ties
those fake ties
thank you for coming papa thank you for
coming everyone i shall stop
procrastinating now
mina
for packing give me some please i need
i need some need some energy from you
guys some power
thank you
[Music]
did you guys notice how cute my eyes are
by the way
did you see my cute eyes before
kawaii
my eyes are so cute
when i wink my head moves so much stop
procrastinating burp
stop stalling go pack up what
[Music]
do i really have to do it
eat oh yeah yeah yeah yeah oh yeah i'll
eat breakfast
maybe watch one episode of friends
on netflix
[Music]
okay what i can do is watch netflix
while i'm packing
i can do that i can just have it open
big
now
what that that works though i i
sometimes do that like i i play netflix
and i do something on the side
i can totally do that
okay i'm good i'm gonna go now and do it
i'm gonna go and do
[Music]
bye bye
also melancholy thank you
is there some other super chats i can
reach
okay at the end in german
we
[Music]
in
um
but wait this one
thank you
thank
[Music]
thank you love you all
so
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
papa nice
hi
[Music]
you