​​​ ​Lying down on the floor​ ​​
​​​ ​Late night and you don't know, don't know​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't know what to do-o​ ​​
​​​ ​Hard to tell what's wrong, what's right​ ​​
​​​ ​If yes or no, don't know​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't know what to do-o​ ​​
​​​ ​The storm hits hard and you're losing the way​ ​​
​​​ ​Just take a chance and dance in the rain​ ​​
​​​ ​'Cuz you got the key, never throw it away​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't forget, don't forget what I said​ ​​
​​​ ​Get out of your head!​ ​​
​​​ ​Life is only what you make it​ ​​
​​​ ​You're gonna be okay​ ​​
​​​ ​So go ahead and do it, do it​ ​​
​​​ ​If you want it let's get to it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Everybody's gonna know your name​ ​​
​​​ ​Cuz sparks light the flame​ ​​
​​​ ​Turn the dark of the night into day​ ​​
​​​ ​(Don't stop, don't stop​ ​​
​​​ ​Just go your own way!!)​ ​​
​​​ ​So don't be afraid​ ​​
​​​ ​Trust your heart, keep your head in the game​ ​​
​​​ ​(Keep up, keep up​ ​​
​​​ ​And never be afraid!!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Gotta make it hot like a volcano​ ​​
​​​ ​Strike a match and burn it up​ ​​
​​​ ​Kick your feet against the table​ ​​
​​​ ​To the beat of your own drum​ ​​
​​​ ​Sparks light the flame, so don't wait​ ​​
​​​ ​Start a fire today​ ​​
​​​ ​(Don't stop, don't stop​ ​​
​​​ ​Just go your own way!!)​ ​​
​​​ ​We ain't looking back​ ​​
​​​ ​Take the fast lane now​ ​​
​​​ ​In the driver's seat strapped​ ​​
​​​ ​They just gasp out loud​ ​​
​​​ ​We're going so fast that it shouldn't be allowed​ ​​
​​​ ​That's how we like it​ ​​
​​​ ​You heard what I said​ ​​
​​​ ​Get out of your head!​ ​​
​​​ ​Life is only what you make it​ ​​
​​​ ​You're gonna be okay (yeah)​ ​​
​​​ ​So take a step and move it, move it​ ​​
​​​ ​'Less you try you won't get through it​ ​​
​​​ ​Everybody's gonna know your name!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cuz sparks light the flame​ ​​
​​​ ​Turn the dark of the night into day​ ​​
​​​ ​(Don't stop, don't stop​ ​​
​​​ ​Just go your own way!!)​ ​​
​​​ ​So don't be afraid​ ​​
​​​ ​Trust your heart, keep your head in the game​ ​​
​​​ ​(Keep up, keep up​ ​​
​​​ ​And never be afraid!!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Let go of the past tonight​ ​​
​​​ ​Choose the future only you define​ ​​
​​​ ​Even when the flames burn too bright, you're alive​ ​​
​​​ ​From the ashes you rise​ ​​
​​​ ​Cuz sparks light the flame​ ​​
​​​ ​Turn the dark of the night into day​ ​​
​​​ ​(Don't stop, don't stop​ ​​
​​​ ​Just go your own way!!)​ ​​
​​​ ​So don't be afraid​ ​​
​​​ ​Trust your heart, keep your head in the game​ ​​
​​​ ​(Keep up, keep up​ ​​
​​​ ​And never be afraid!!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Gotta make it hot like a volcano​ ​​
​​​ ​Strike a match and burn it up​ ​​
​​​ ​Kick your feet against the table​ ​​
​​​ ​To the beat of your own drum​ ​​
​​​ ​Sparks light the flame, so don't wait​ ​​
​​​ ​Start a fire today​ ​​
​​​ ​(Don't stop, don't stop​ ​​
​​​ ​Just go your own way!!)​ ​​
​​​ ​(Ah yeah)​ ​​
​​​ ​Music, Lyrics: KIRA​ ​​
​​​ ​Vocals: Takanashi Kiara​ ​​
​​​ ​Illustrations: NeonBeat​ ​​
​​​ ​MV: riguruma​ ​​
​​​ ​Logo: Spiritsnare​ ​​
​​​ ​Takanashi Kiara - SPARKS​ ​​