thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
wow
time to time to go I'm gonna mute them
now
as you guys know oh wow this is the
second year of Holo ID Club 2023 and I
would like to say thank you to all of
you guys who've been accepting to play
with us
and trying all the games that's been
setting for this year
um and also
um I would like to say thank you to
ollie and rainy for being the MC today
[Music]
for do a lot of practice so yeah it's
really helpful for me too and well
that's all I just want you guys to have
fun for today
today
[Music]
yes so uh we'll be watching all of you
guys
[Music]
will be commenting on every one of your
moves
secretly
nervous and after this what do we have
after this rainy
well we're gonna be having a captain
speech from each of the team
so if we can get the leaders to come up
here please
[Music]
oh
okay okay
what if I shift shift I jump someone hit
me
[Music]
it will probably be chaos chaos
let's have fun tonight
[Music]
and
next we have risu
[Music]
oh that's right Reese is our leader okay
I forgot no I mean I got confused I
didn't forget
[Music]
I didn't forget it no wait
so yeah let's let's have fun today
[Applause]
yeah I love our team leader who is risu
our team leader thank you I love you too
I love you
yes
[Music]
we saw the leaders and then it's now
time for the full introduction of each
team we can start with srikandi
sikandichan please
[Music]
Amelia from Amelia senpai
hello everybody
let's go let's win
[Applause]
um
on your baby
up to you where do you want to go first
oh okay what's up it's it's me it's it's
Bae with red from uh yeah
[Applause]
are you good
[Music]
okay hello everyone I'm Anya let's have
fun today
foreign
[Music]
let's win
[Applause]
[Music]
who is hitting me
completed your service
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
yeah
nice
nice nice
[Applause]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you
and next it's time for a theme for TV to
introduce themselves
[Music]
[Applause]
we have team spirit okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
oh sorry
and next we have Kyla
oh hello hi everyone my name is
blacksmith from Polo ID gen3 song
[Music]
hey
[Applause]
let's do our best
number one let's party I'm energetic
Yankee let's go
yeah thanks I know
next next next we have Kira
I know
um it's currently 6 a.m
[Laughter]
and I am gonna be at badminton and
sucker
[Music]
it says fauna from hollow life English
Council thank you for not putting me on
the soccer team
it's fun though
what are you participating in for now I
will be in capture the fort and also the
potato sack race
potatoes
okay we have soda Senpai Dosa hey hello
uh
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
I'm fine
hi
hi everybody
my name is
today is a company
[Music]
and next last but not least we have
coyote
[Music]
um
[Applause]
wow
that's sports that's all for team
fertility right yeah
but you know other than like introducing
the members I kind of want to hear
something more don't you think
everybody come up with their own team
cheers
[Music]
yeah
thank you
I'm ready I'm ready
[Music]
so after me I'm gonna start okay okay
okay
three two one
birthday party
[Music]
oh huh
[Applause]
let's go
yeah
kill everyone
that was so good yeah
[Laughter]
three
[Music]
two one say candy
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
yeah
well then Ollie obviously what do we do
after this
is okay
ten wow
[Music]
so the even today
um we're gonna play a lot of games
starting from capture the fourth or we
call it bentengan and after that we move
to the puta de sacres and after that we
go tug of war and then after that we
have badminton uh from the a side and
then badminton from a b side and also
after that we have soccer and that's all
[Music]
is ending
two that's all I hope you guys having
fun
[Music]
now it's it's time for you guys to uh I
think it's back to the interview it's
really interesting huh yes right
okay okay okay
[Music]
games
[Applause]
games games
soccer
classic okay
please
okay
[Music]
we're watching and you have to win for
us but no pressure okay racial games
[Music]
okay
I can watch from here oh yeah we can
watch from right here where do you watch
it from
[Music]
so there's some seats over there but
this is a nice view actually okay
we can just walk around I guess
archers
okay okay
sorry sorry sorry
[Music]
oh God
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
yeah
yeah let's go
it's interviewing time okay
what are you what are you most afraid of
of the other team not nothing
I just believe you got this in the bag
yeah oh is there any special tactics
that you're you know secretly cooking
okay it seems like there's no ready for
this game a kairashim dozo
oh
what is your tactic kailashing we have
we're gonna win we have we have secret
tactics that we cannot tell here
yourselves right yeah audience the
audience
yeah yeah we'll see
seems like you guys have secret secret
tactics
I wish you guys the best of luck okay
thank you
yeah okay goodbye
yes okay
foreign
[Music]
okay let's go ready ready I wanna watch
pretty weird
[Music]
how do you zoom again in here I forgot Z
I want to see
okay
somebody
oh we start already
[Laughter]
go ladies
but it's okay
gamers
[Music]
zombies
that was quick
[Music]
uh eat Kokomo together
so they were like opening the doors
[Music]
oh I see their strategy there's strategy
like we thought they wouldn't really use
the middle yeah
already last night but yeah okay
so
yeah
oh you can actually you could actually
open that door I didn't know
you can actually offensively I actually
remembered the the the way to the Middle
with uh
[Music]
um
but we were like there's a lot of um
success
Hold On music changed
tactics
where do we go now do we go back we go
back I think we are interviewing the
winner first oh that's right yeah yeah
okay okay
I want to see what happens
oh we just have to win
oh it's getting crazy
Fight Club
no HP we can just hit him all right
don't hold back don't hold back we'll
hit him all right
[Music]
they're me in the action
right
I think the interview is taking longer
than the game itself
[Music]
oh whoopsies that's not what I wanted to
do
oh my God
potato race
[Music]
yeah much bigger
oh
let's get to the other side
[Music]
oh I went to the wrong place
oh I'm a bit of a dummy okay sorry I
don't get out okay
thank God for that that would have been
tough
let's go
crazy
so I accidentally fell into degrees
okay
[Music]
oh still okay
for now okay okay okay let's go let's go
let's go
okay
[Music]
don't give up
you guys are great
whoa
oh what's in here wow the trophy is
bigger oh my God
[Music]
the door is opening if you like press
and then
cool oh
oh
my God
[Applause]
believe in you
disconnected
[Music]
let's just run for now I think okay just
practice practice warm up warming up
warming up yes
[Music]
stop
in the pot right
now
she's in her elements
oh a phone is very fast
[Music]
Sunday no problem
anymore
guys
so sorry we have to restart this okay
yeah but you guys were doing really
great
yeah yeah we were watching and we were
in uh we'll be back to you guys soon
okay okay
[Music]
no problem
it's doing really great I'll try to keep
it up no pressure no you're doing great
too
and then at least as they're like first
and second our team
what did you do
ready ready
[Music]
from above
oh yeah I'm gonna go for I'm gonna go
above too yeah
[Music]
let's go
around while watching
yeah we're watching from the top of the
trophies
foreign foreign
[Music]
because we did really make it clear
beforehand but after this after this
race in the other competitions if there
are connection issues uh I think to also
to make it fair for everybody uh we will
not be restarting uh the competition so
it will just continue yeah thank you so
much just wanted to keep everybody on
the same page thank you and good luck no
problem thank you
only this time
internet
okay
fingers crossed okay
ladies get ready
[Music]
foreign
hey
[Music]
nice nice
pretty soon
oh my God
um
[Music]
oh
my God
[Music]
you're doing great
let's go no yeah
[Music]
let's go
oh
come on
[Music]
let's go
sweaters
[Applause]
it's okay don't worry about it
it's okay
everyone it's okay you did your best son
that's all that matters you guys were
fast plus I mean okay we had the two
fastest people though let's be real so
it is great
[Music]
you're amazing
we will I believe yeah
you know what someone in chat said three
candies oh my God incredible candy
amazing
oh my God I shouldn't have made that
the Japanese man
that was good okay okay okay okay okay
don't forget to hydrate guys
[Music]
oh my God
um
[Music]
thank you
I mean I won't be here but
you won't be out there
just thinking about it that's like
making making ramen Ramen
um
pink versus blue
yeah the other other person okay
is very strong
yeah pink is strong yeah
yeah let's go oh
no problem
for anyone who wants to watch can go up
so I think everybody's already I think
we can yeah
um
okay
[Music]
thank you okay
um
I'll do my best
I hope my mouse durability yeah
because hey
[Music]
super focused
no problem no problem okay wow
warming up
moving up
are you ready
yes
stay
calm yes we're ready
everybody
let's go let's go
a little bit
oh
here we go
let's go
okay
I can fly we can fly we can't go down
[Music]
um
I can go
thank you
no I'm not gonna I'm not gonna lie um I
actually thought we were losing because
when I was practicing we were fighting I
was red team
winner go to this I'll explain later I
thought we were losing
[Music]
[Applause]
um I thought we were losing actually
because
um during practice I was red team
so I thought I saw the red go down and
down and I was like oh no we're losing
because that made you go extra you know
yeah you guys are catching up now it's
like two to one but I feel like you guys
have a chance to actually do it we can
do it
for sure yeah yeah how do you feel how
do you feel I'm winning now
can you believe that you're ruined right
now
[Laughter]
please number one number one yeah
um
I stopped I stopped we still won though
okay
yeah
pink Power
finger Queens
[Music]
thank you
thank you we can do it we can win this I
know what's next
[Music]
oh yeah
we are in Kaila a badminton yeah
[Music]
Kiara back
she was
us which is kind of like went somewhere
again hi
[Music]
let's go
you were so good I was watching you
while I was cooking you should have won
honestly
oh yeah you go he also win one the
finger uh competition so I thought it
was great
[Music]
who's that strap
s
she'll protect the back I'll protect the
front yeah okay
[Music]
no pressure
stay calm you'll be fine
otherwise actually eat the clock already
the ball already fell to the ground you
can't actually I know yeah
God
I will see you yeah
[Music]
are crazy at this game who knows you
guys practice a lot so just don't worry
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
so if you if you feel frustrated just
shout like a real sport
ready right ready yeah
who has the first one okay okay ready
ready guys get ready okay
they could shoot any moment now okay
there we go
oh nice nice Kayla is always the best
backup oh
good job good job good defense
no problems
where is it oh
okay
[Music]
yeah
the other side it's on the other side
you're doing great
[Music]
nice
save
that's okay
don't worry don't worry all right don't
worry though don't worry
it's out it's out it's out
[Music]
because it's going towards the wrong
side yeah
you have to hit the
road
for the first hits after the first hit
you can hit wherever you want ah I see
I'll take it
okay
thank you foreign
[Music]
my
mom
that might go out is it out
let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
take it again
my job here is almost done yeah
will there be an interview
thank you oh my God please win let's go
let's go let's win this please
[Music]
at the door
I believe
it
wasn't ready
okay okay
wait
yeah
looking good okay okay okay
[Music]
hi something I would do nice
don't mind don't mind
do you pass in badminton in real life do
you pass to your teammate I don't think
so no no no no no no no no
we only can possibly do like one night
okay
[Music]
okay okay
um
[Applause]
why
oops
I'm enjoying this too much
winning feels good
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
I have the best team I have the best
team let's go cheers
[Music]
yeah okay
oh no
no
it depends on soccer
oh god
oh no
soccer soccer
is
go
go to go shoot
don't score an own goal yeah
United
everyone playing
it's uh six people okay
it's going to be your thing Kyla Kiara
Kelly coyote and do the same time okay
yes
thank you everyone everyone can shoot
okay shoot
got it
okay also you can uh you can also hit
the ball by your body without actually
clicking with the shoes oh okay
oh okay you can wait by your body
without using the shoes
Yeah so basically shoes is for shooting
aha
and you can like
um dribble dribble oh I see I see yeah
dribble right right kind of kick it with
or with foot okay but not shooting yes
got it okay
got it no problem no problem
we can do it
[Music]
very tense
it's tied right now oh man yeah
so everything so I don't have to do I do
I just run into the ball to dribble it
or do I click it
throughout the show you can do both okay
if you if you're if you're alone with
the ball you can actually just run okay
run toward it okay
but if you want to steal ball maybe you
can click yeah yeah we're back yay
nice job
okay so they said that there's ten point
difference and soccer is gonna make the
big difference yeah we are leading but
we still need to win the soccer no yeah
okay
but the soccer is 20 minutes in total
all right
wow
should I maybe try to stay in a certain
area like close to the goal or so any
any uh
uh uh Kiara and Kyla uh are both great
at uh striking right yeah
um
too much forward while the uh the others
can I think everyone tries to stay back
and guard uh but without being goalie
yeah somebody has to stay around the
goal like at least in the area
bye okay yeah before EOP okay okay
second goalkeeper
now can I translate in Japanese oh
please do oh yeah no no no no no like
this is a little information that I can
actually dribble the ball well
oh really yeah
yeah it helps a lot oh boy
um
all right okay
[Music]
okay
let's go
and break after 10 minutes
if it comes
back
yeah
you better not bring the ball to me okay
um
are we automatically
are we automatically running
no no I think you always have to press
it okay girl yes my little finger gets
tired from it after a while but because
I'm pressing it nothing's changing so
it is
then you can jump as well but but it's
like wow
[Music]
they sent it out they sent it out pass
it me oh yeah yeah
to your friends go what oh
[Music]
don't worry
don't worry don't worry
it was close it was close okay it's okay
it's okay
[Music]
um
it disappears it is
foreign
[Music]
Watson's a really good goalkeeper
died
okay go
okay
no you no you don't
know
that was awesome
no
no huh
[Music]
okay okay okay I'm gonna take it to the
left okay
okay go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go
[Music]
Watson
I'll be just staying close to okay
please yeah
[Music]
hi
which direction at the end
let's go
okay
thank you
[Music]
okay
it's not fast enough okay
oh
yeah
[Music]
take it
easy
thank you
come on
I need to stay closer to here
yeah yeah I'm gonna go into the right
side
wait where's she gonna
okay send it to come here
I feel like it always goes further than
you might think
[Music]
okay
okay wait hold on oh
the second attorney yeah
um
I don't even know if I'm running or not
am I running I I don't know yeah yeah
you feel like you're running I feel like
I am but I'm not holding control
nope
I'm sorry
oh my God
[Music]
it is
okay
wait are we already in the second half
yeah
oh there's seven minutes confuse me
nope oh nice
okay
here we go
hey
okay
so they're Betty Betty where's the bowl
look at this let's go
go go go
whoa he came back to me all right
I gotta stay back here in case they in
case they yeah I'm just gonna show them
yeah yeah go back go back this
oh
look where was that
okay
let's go come on come on come on
come on yes
[Applause]
oh my God
yeah I did I didn't know soccer will be
this oh yeah
this is how real soccer works
[Music]
yes
it's okay it's okay no problem
got it
no
oh okay
you
oh no oh no no no no no kick it yeah
maybe just scrap yeah
we can bring it back in the second half
yeah yeah yeah oh my God we have to be
maybe a bit more aggressive
I wonder if maybe I should not defend
that I should strike instead no I think
it's gonna do it no no no you're good
you're good okay yeah you're good okay I
feel like I'm doing a bad job
why do we need more defense though yeah
okay because we can because we can just
kick the ball to the front we don't need
like that much of like you know we don't
need much of the attackers oh okay
defensive yeah so if we got the ball
just kick it okay okay
[Music]
it might be hard to get points if we're
more defensive Yeah because sometimes
when the ball finally goes over to like
the goal side I feel like then often
there's like only coyote Senpai there
and nobody's helping yeah I should be
closer to the goal honestly okay
oh
um
yeah
they're going to be more defensive 100
because they're winning so we we really
need to be aggressive I think okay okay
I am okay
all right
okay
they were interviewing pickles Empire
yeah I think I need to be more in the
central area
[Music]
thank you
coyote okay
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
bad weather by the way I really hope I
own DC
oh don't worry it's over soon just 10
more minutes
we're just gonna tell Kubo to chill out
chill
out
stop stop making rain is too good of a
goalkeeper she is really yeah
I'm gonna kick them
I wanna I wanna make them stumble
yeah and I have a guess
okay
they kind of like ask us if we have any
strategy yeah and then okay just just
leave it to Lady Luck I guess maybe
there's a miracle comeback yeah yeah
um
[Music]
stronger aggressive everything stronger
okay just do better
[Music]
sorry
mm-hmm
just take a nap okay
[Music]
I don't okay
right okay all right you ready ladies
here we go
all right
bring it back
okay okay
I'm Watson day good yeah she's really
good I'm Watson
where is she gonna where is she gonna go
okay
no no no no no no no
dude right over my head I wish I could
jump better
huh
I don't know
I don't know if we can shift from I
don't think the rules are that realistic
it's better to try
oh my God
[Music]
over by the goal
can we just follow her yeah
okay
oh nope
no way
okay
[Music]
I also still have to turn around every
time they're already looking in the
right direction
oh
man come on there is no way I'm sorry
but I'm sorry
it's not your fault
the try good try good job guys
we can surprise them they're gonna let
their guard down yeah
aggressive the aggressive glycember
I'm ready
I might go sideways yeah but nah
nah she wants to go um
trying to be tactical about it
okay okay go go go okay
[Music]
shoot to me what's about amatori don't
we love each other
[Music]
it's fun
oh yeah
okay all right nope
okay got me f'd up over here
yeah Watson's too good
okay
oh God
okay okay okay okay
thank you all right
oh okay okay
[Music]
all right hold on nice
all right
gotta keep going gotta keep going okay
epic come back
this is where we come back
Kelly protect me all right I'm trying
pecora is okay
[Music]
she wants to confuse us
okay
we're here we're here let's go let's go
[Music]
um
we can tie with them we just need to tie
with them yeah
okay good
no no no no no no no no okay all right
it's fine it's fine
I'm here
okay
defense
[Music]
okay protect protection
defense defense
okay
[Applause]
foreign
oh
[Music]
attention
expansion no like 10 minutes oh dude
[Music]
was was a good momentum there was a good
momentum
all sure does fly
it is it's live so I'm gonna get a
ticket for the last all right there you
go
nice
nope nope nope
[Music]
but it is what it is
okay sure
okay
[Music]
my team is the best
we didn't even have penalty penalty
at least it was close it wasn't like
they completely destroyed us right yeah
yeah not not like Pokemon unite or
anything like that
we did decently but
do not get gas lit into thinking that we
didn't do well in that tournament
because we did okay
it was great even though I was watching
it was it was it was really awesome
um
the whole time oh thank you
yeah dang Amit too strong I miss a good
I mean it's a gamer too please we are in
the hub
yoga and Cali also like
um what is it man if I was born
[Music]
I want to get taller
not even wrong
[Music]
I had fun
games are just like all so so much fun I
really enjoy all the games yeah even the
ones I didn't participate in so yeah
badminton easy I think the map is open
until uh
I think somebody says 21. 20 something
something so yes everybody wants to try
it yeah if you want to ask someone to
play with you
Kyle I'm not asking anybody to
I still trying to get a friend to play
the taco floor because I really love
that one my hand is crying
I'll play against you Kyla anytime yeah
you know what we have to uh Kiara we
have to play uh like two two versus one
like okay versus Kyla what wait what
no no no
don't worry I can maybe do it alone
again Skyla oh
yeah I will just die but you know
yeah
it's good games
just a game and that's done
okay okay
oh
[Music]
two
when did I look cool yes I was watching
from above
we should have been cheerleading where
are your pom-poms
you mean in front of your heart
is too strong
of a wall
space
[Music]
that's what they do
okay
give me a five star
Emma did you play soccer in real life
before or what I have I have oh
over there
that explains everything
I Never Had A Prayer
[Music]
are you announcing your wedding with
someone oh
come
on congratulations
good job guys
it was intense and well after all of
those intense game will be announcing
yeah so first of all from the bending on
the capture the floor
with 40 points
and then we also have the sack race with
30 points yet again three candy wins so
that brings us to a total of 70 points
[Music]
what's the next one the next one was tug
of war
in which it was a blue versus pink team
OMG
foreign
[Music]
Watson too strong and we are happy to
announce that the winner of the whole ID
cup is the
subtle
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
too
[Music]
in his heart
[Laughter]
we are going to be awarding the medals
right
okay
the team captain please distribute the
medals to your teammates hi I will
distribute
um
oh yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
let me see hey what if I just put on the
gold medal anyway
do I have access to the gold but maybe
I'm gonna put on the gold I don't know
where it is
[Music]
all right
that's my medal now
take your medals
thank you I'm ready
[Music]
we also got a yoga medal yeah
I think it's better
[Music]
does everybody have their medals
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah there he is
this thing is heavy there's our Shot
Show
it's like the opening we will be asking
for a few words by each team captain
starting from Sri candy teams
[Music]
yeah
that was it that was really fun really
really fun and
um
can we do oh can we do the
um the the yellow together again let's
do it again let's do it again let's do
it again yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
everyone did
um everyone did their best doing the
games
thank you
thank you so much
[Music]
thank you for playing with us as well
we can we have a little bit of words
from the captain of temper TV please
[Music]
to actually make time for this and also
I love birthday theme because they are
all
um hardworking so they practice too yeah
they're like oh my God I just I just
love the team so much I love you too
we put a good thing yeah it was close I
tell you what
yeah thank you so much everybody thank
you so much for inviting us so I thought
this year was really fun thank you
thank you
next year
guys
okay do you want to do the cheer for one
last time
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
yeah
thank you
[Applause]
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
three times
lastly yeah
[Music]
everyone go into the party and please
let's go let's go
if you can be on the top one on the
spruce okay okay
[Music]
um
okay uh
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
good time good fun time
[Music]
[Laughter]
if you guys want to take separate team
pictures you guys can do it now in your
own free time
[Music]
wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait oh yeah we
should be okay okay
with him
back with my team
hello
one of the balloons
she'll teach us how to play Minecraft
teach us how to fly please I wish to fly
this button press this button
oh
creative mode
I can't get the
how do I fly you need one it's gone
updated to creative mode
here there it is
my hands are a little strong
like
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
are you taking
them
die I'm flying all right let's go let's
get in the dragon and the dragon
dragon's mouth and [\h__\h] uh oh yeah there
we go cool
dragon's eyebrows
yeah a dragon's head cool
um
[Music]
uh
you're gonna take the picture yeah okay
okay you you can watch the screen on
yeah I see oh yeah okay
so please make sure that I'm in the
middle so I can get like uh okay oh okay
[Music]
in front
um
we're too far right here I'll stay here
we can go a little bit
in front
yeah yeah or is it good enough like this
name
oh hi okay
okay
this works this one's nice this one is
nice
okay
I got one
got two
um
[Music]
perfect
please
get my good side
let me look good okay okay I think it's
done yeah okay thank you okay I will
send it yay
[Music]
thank you
I want to see what's in the ship this
ship is cool oh yeah
before wow wow so yeah yeah
Indonesia oh
and the other one I don't remember the
other already look
I'm an explorer
[Music]
wow
I wonder when the Japan
sports festival is yeah
foreign
[Music]
well uh that was that was it that was
the what the [\h__\h] do you want oh sorry
excuse me what
oh it's called
hello Google
oh I'm sorry I'm so
look what you made me do
come on
oh gosh get in your hole
get in your hole
I'm your Maury
um oh everyone's kind of like oh shh
what just awkwardly happened there are
you gonna come and get me Kobo you're
gonna come and get me well baby child
hmm oh is there something you want to
say to me Kobo Boca Boca Boca Boca Boca
is there something you want to say to me
Kobo is there something you want to say
to me Cobo
I'm your Maury thanks for hanging out
today tomorrow tomorrow I have a special
guest coming to my home
yeah
uh two special guests actually somebody
else joining along for the ride
um
you'll see that soon
with that being said I'm your Mori you
won't want to miss it it's pretty
it's pretty pretty big deal I've never
had here at my home
and I I don't know how it's gonna go
there are things I'm nervous about but I
think it'll be fun
um
look forward to it
usual time no it'll be at night Japan
time Japan time at I believe uh seven
7 P.M you really you really messed with
the wrong one Kobo oh my God
it's baiting me into breaking things
whatever
whatever off I go into the sunset guess
I'll die
um
see ya everyone
bye
be sure to check out the EP
it's releasing soon I gotta go animate
now for that music video
go get excited for the EP
it's gonna be good
first oh and up
bye everyone
peace
the best team bye
[Music]
foreign
life will never change
[Music]
no one expectations