[Music]
la
n
[Music]
la
e
[Music]
n
la
[Music]
[\h__\h] BM will be loud for a
moment
sorry
uh
okay k k was that was that loud was that
loud was that
[Music]
okay uh
monitor there you go oh oh okay can't
hear it okay that's
fine still sick well yeah a little
bit uh but it's
okay
W on the front page what what front
page uh I I have already recovered
greatly no this is good this is good
this is
[Music]
um way less than like yesterday or the
day before
yesterday uh wait let me move myself a
little
bit I'm a mess mess mess mess mess mess
mess I'm a mess in the stress but we
still the best dress feel let's say
yes uh I should join
snot I I am snot no they don't take new
members I
think um so okay I'm okay I I I used to
have a really strong headache uh but
that's gone and my nose I had to blow it
way more often and uh I had
to spit out some flag way more often
sadly I feel like I want to spit out
flagon but it just doesn't come out it's
like there's I think only a little bit
left and then that that is just like I
don't want to go I want to stay
so I'm at that stage uh and when I when
I when I cough I really only cough
because I that that little bit of fum
that's left is like blocking my Airways
I think
and don't you just sound delightful
wow and it feels like I'm choking um but
I'm okay like um I feel way better I'm
just grateful I feel better cuz like oh
my
[Music]
God
I
[Music]
misunderstood I misunderstood the I did
like a like a spinoff
ofik
or and uh put Coy Senpai a
[\h__\h] I put Coyote's name in there wait I
just realize I feel like I didn't set
the lag properly I think we have a
bigger lag than we should have I don't
know but it's not too bad uh but yeah uh
yeah I misunderstood anyway BL blah BL
blah blah hello uh can you hear the bgm
is it okay is because I can't hear it um
but that's okay
should I make it louder or more
quiet can you whistle a tune huh huh huh
you think me some bb or what be J okay
okay so well as you can tell apparently
I'm not completely healed yet in terms
of fro
so I don't know how much I should strain
it
um I'm okay
though uh we won't do too long uh I was
thinking of reading super chats too
later but maybe I shouldn't
uh so we'll just like recap see I forgot
the word recap I just like just now I
remembered H recap that's the word I'm
looking for BTS and what
what that what else did I
write it's a
recap
um it's a it's a rare uh es PSD Prime
Time stream let's go you know people
always say ES P but they never talk
about like the what is it
CST so
sad do people in the middle of America
feel like they don't
exist cuz everybody always talks about
es PSD but maybe that's just me I mean
in reality everybody only talks about
PSD when it comes to schedules everybody
just puts PSD on there almost everybody
I'm like I don't know why because I have
no absolutely no like connection or like
understanding of what's more popular I
just like put estd on my schedule uh in
the beginning and I just like stuck with
it
uh yeah she explained my my my serving
tweet
anyway we have n yeah she's like
bringing awareness to the
table
what you're the closest non Hawaiian
Time what what
what what ah oh you mean EST is the
closest to me yeah yeah it makes me feel
better I guess when I put EST on my
schedule and uh like it's not as much a
shitty time as
PST
usually makes me feel
better
what what what am I serving you want to
know what I'm serving I'm serving
[\h__\h]
um there you go so I will talk today
about how I served [\h__\h] and you will
listen to
it I can say this with confidence cuz he
English is now my first
[Music]
language goodbye monetization no it
means Charisma and whatever what
uniqueness
[Music]
maybe
um
nervosity uh oh yeah yeah no but it's
people people T so many people Tau me I
served that so what can I do guys
besides agreeing with it they say it so
it must be true it must be
true so today we're going to uh
recapture oh my
God
re recapture the moment di oh my
god wow brain
[Music]
explosion oh we're going to recapture
the
[Music]
moment yeah nervosity is a real word
word
yeah uniqueness nuance and talent ah
there we go Charisma keep serving that
I'll keep on saving thank
you all right uh mind blown so I have
some notes on my
phone um damn it my tea is getting
colder and
colder and I'm growing older and older
but we get Bolder and
[Music]
Boulder okay let me sorry that's so
keyboard let me look at my
now you are now my
property um I'm excited I can stream
again I'm still not home by the way
obviously as you could probably tell
from the time I'm streaming in all the
streams in this
week I think will be B will be um uh
around this time tomorrow and the day
after tomorrow I'm also planning to
stream at this
time and then yeah so I'm in Japan uh
I'm the thing is I'm here quite a bit
longer than the other members like
everybody already left pretty
[Music]
much
everybody gone um I'm I extended my stay
because uh I've got something to do a
little itty bitty
thing and yeah yeah it's kind of sad
everybody only stayed for a really short
amount of time
uh
everybody's here so shortly and I think
I even like arrived
like like maybe a day earlier than most
but most arve probably around the same
time but then everybody left like
already and yeah didn't get to like hang
much with them
because even when all the like
excitement was over and people were like
getting together to like hang at least
for one or two
days uh like to have dinner or whatever
I couldn't be part of that because I got
sick so that's wonderful but um I am not
surprised nobody should be surprised
that I got sick this time I know I get
sick a lot like when I travel
seemingly uh but this time it I I kind
of had it coming if you think about I I
flew to North
America and then it's not even direct
flights it's like connections so that's
more stressful more contact with people
more like stupid uh like weird air and
dryness uh so I fly to North America
which
okay let me get rid of this logo
beautiful logo
so uh you're
up
Japan I have only a mouse today and I'm
left-handed but I'm using the mouse of
right hand so you know okay na of course
there's nothing else this is all there
is on this Earth but so I
fly
I flew over there and as I said with
like I I totally had a collection in the
middle of the ocean um
so and then I stayed like longer than I
wanted to cuz things got [\h__\h] up
uh yeah and and then and then I fly back
normally I was supposed to to stay a few
days at least a few days in Austria
before I then fly to Japan but uh I only
had
hours it was
stressful I'm not tell you what I board
I stopped at
no um so 24 hours at home to like get
[\h__\h] done in those 24 hours I recorded
motion for my MV and all that like
really stressful got some [\h__\h]
done and I couldn't even sleep even
though both of these flights let me Flex
oh what the [\h__\h] is that that's a bee
both of these flights were business
class so you would think oh comfy it was
comfy but I could still not sleep cuz I
I don't know I don't know why I my my my
shoulder was hurting a lot and I was I
guess my mind was stressed out and I
just couldn't sleep and in especially in
the flight to
Japan uh which also was not a direct
flight that had to stop
somewhere and then on the on the on the
on the second flight that was longer
than the other somebody was snoring I
thought I was able to sleep and I slept
like maybe uh pretty nicely for like two
two or 3 hours and then I wake up and
then and then I hear someone snoring the
whole time and like h i I start
hyperfocusing on it and
like could not not listen to the to the
freaking snoring and then I could not
sleep again so all these flights I had
like so many flights in such a short
amount of time over several continents
uh different airspaces different
bacteria and of course this is getting
me sick
of course my immune system got
[Music]
[\h__\h] no the like even when I wear I
have my I brought my own noise
cancelling headphones no noise
cancelling yeah but they're so
Fick
that
when I sleep with
them I would only be able to sleep
completely facing upwards
straight H which is not how I sleep
comfortably um I would like to sleep
sideways and then that that just you you
guys know that just doesn't work with
these kind of
headphones face
R yeah airpods [\h__\h] airpods
so okay
uh that's why I'm probably got sick
that's probably
why so okay let me
see
I Al in
Japan where you doing my tangent even
start
uh uh I I think mostly
my tangents are going to start from the
tour thingy is you know we got to see
the venue
beforehand um and it was so fun we were
uh like so many of us were together but
okay I want to uh tell you I don't know
if you guys know this but um
uh we did not meet Japanese members
there
all the we were only together
withan
and
I
[Music]
love I also have a little
bit h no oh my my tangents are like so
mixed all over the
place
uh God Dam it I don't know where is what
okay I they guys they might not be in a
good order
so uh please excuse me if they're all
over the place what do you mean no from
oh are you saying fumo and Bay are in h
Japan is that the
joke uh okay uh no they were there
uh um so yeah wait let me show you
[Music]
pictures let
me check it so you guys may have seen it
was like kind of like travel an island
themed so I didn't get like a proper
picture of the entrance entrance but of
the side of the
[Music]
entrance it looks like this so good so
good there's a gate over there right and
what are these fake or real PL fake
right maybe not all of
them but asking the real questions are
they real or
fake
huh
now I really I really wonder about that
uh but it says welcome to Whole Life
Island y i
happy looks real looks fake maybe it's a
mix cuz I think the big tree looks real
to me but not all of the big tropical
looking plants down
[Music]
there important question I wonder if
there was
Moss if there was moss and it was now uh
after we were there it was gone probably
because am I must have taken it
no yeah I think it's mixed I
happy I
happy uh so
[Music]
okay so okay so I looked around and we
were like we were supposed to kind of
like stay in a group but
M then everybody just ran off to sign
things everywhere uh so I was like I was
like uh uh what do I do I this is I I
want to why are we not in a group like
everybody's like running up there were
some some smaller groups but
like yeah everybody was everywhere so I
was like I don't know where to
go and then uh I don't know partially I
walked a little bit with go B and goba
manager uh and me and jenma together
partially but uh other times I was just
like me and me and
jenma uh but then we wait let me show
you this before I I uploaded this on uh
Twitter but I mean I took a lot of
pictures but uh and and videos even but
this is the vice Schwartz Vice Schwartz
Bove which is just one of many
booths uh and I I'm I'm an ambassador
there so they have my card and other
stuff really big display over
there yeah the giant cards are cool
M yeah we're like in a circle aligned
there and
yeah yeah excuse
me ah yeah the secret it wasn't secret
was like I was like uh they asked me to
sign this one too and I'm like yeah but
I don't want to ruin the pretty art and
then uh then they like kind of said no
no problem please do please do and I'm
like M okay but like my orange pen and
my green pen probably won't really show
up properly here and the black pen black
pen would have probably been the way to
go but then I just I thought maybe maybe
golden pen
but
[Music]
H then I tried with the golden pen but
the golden pen was too thin and it also
didn't stand out really well cuz yeah
didn't look so good so maybe that's why
I think it's secret I didn't try to hide
it but it just uh was difficult to sign
this
sign wonder if you guys even saw it like
some of you guys apparently saw it yeah
I ended up using gold for this one cuz I
thought that's should be better but yeah
there's like a lot going on in this one
and so big
so it's difficult color blind Bros oh
no yeah sign cards are also usually
written in gold right so I also far like
oh gold like these cards like the the
stamped signatures are also usually in
Gold
so no no no in this picture it's not
signed yet this was
before
it was like finding an Easter
egg yeah I I signed I signed a couple
things I don't have a picture right now
but uh I signed there was like a a big
big you know the main visual there was a
big tapestry of it and uh I I I wasn't
together with Ena in the moment so I
signed it first and I was hoping that
Ena would find it and then sign it in a
way that makes sense uh like as a
response to me and she did sign it like
I signed like a speech bubble above my
head and so I could only breathe through
the mouth right
now uh and I sign a speech bubble above
my head that's like cuz you know we just
had like off collabs it was like uh Mina
when are we going to finish our Mario
playthrough H and then she asked
answered afterwards yeah she wrote
Takaki Takaki Takaki like she's only
like cuz it looks like she's not
listening in that illustration
partially uh a mouth paper not
normally yeah you saw pictures right
like afterwards when I found Ena again I
was like did you sign it did you sign it
did you did you see the thing did you
sign it she's like yeah yeah I signed
Taco Y T
Yak like thank you yeah cuz I was
worried she might not find it because uh
that was like pretty far in so to say
the back like further inside of uh the
Expo and I didn't see too many people
going that far I feel like I me and
maybe goba were the only ones that went
into the second Hall I didn't see the
others going into the second Hall which
is where the the vice rods boo was I
think the second hul was like sponsors
uh booths and all that I know that's
[Music]
there and some stuff you know like that
so I think it was like
sponsor sponsor booths was second haul
but they had some really cool stuff
there
too sorry I'm going to blow my nose
[Music]
again nice nice get that [\h__\h] out of
there that one needs a
ticket no I don't think so I mean I
might be wrong
but Kelly said she found out late that
there was another hole Yeah I just went
really far and and ah I think in the
second
Hall is where I found that stande of me
next to
am and like it was also next to a bench
and so I signed
um I didn't
sign oh the reason why I was running
around was like I was trying to find a
good space to sign my idea that I had my
Epiphany that I had beforehand I I
wanted
[Music]
to I wanted a big empty white space
where I could sign hey touch my hand and
then draw around my hand and have you
guys touch it and I couldn't find it
until the very end so this was the last
thing I did really rushed when people
were always saying oh we got to go we
got to go and like oh wait I I still
could find a good space to do this and
then I ended up uh uh uh doing it
under there was like a like a a little
section with like umbrellas and it was
like Hol live rainy rainy sky or
something like that uh like a the theme
was what do you do uh when it's rainy
and it it was in a ticketed area ticket
[Music]
it like but you don't pay right you just
have to like get like a like a Time
timed ticket to enter I didn't know like
damn I was surprised how popular
everything
was just even the standies when people
told that there's lines to take pictures
of the SES it's like really wow it's
just SES
guys it's not it's not really us guys
you know that right like we're not
behind it or we're not really you know I
mean we might always be 2D and that's
pretty flat in 2D as well but the
standies are not alive guys I'm just
kidding uh I mean that's true but uh
[Music]
why or she shaped closest thing will
get yeah I mean yeah cuz everybody
wanted to take pictures of the
signatures were like what is it really
that interesting I mean I'm honored but
I didn't think people would make
actually make lines but also shows you
how organized or like disciplined
Japanese people are I so pan pan
Japanese people so disciplined to
actually stay in a line if this was in a
in a like American convention I doubt
people would like stand in one line to
take orders and taking
pictures like people would just like
scramble in front of it and like you
know and then if another person comes
they would just like
[Music]
swoosh their way in front of everybody
and like stand in front of them and take
a quick picture and then run or so feel
like it wouldn't be
disorganized which uh yeah it's good
that you it's organized
[Music]
um feeling cold the air cor air
conditioning is so
strong uh yeah so sorry I guess I didn't
sign it in the good space
[Laughter]
huh and then I saw someone like taking a
picture of it actually and like like
hovering their hand over it was that
like a rule cuz I was intending you guys
to actually touch it
[Music]
that was my
hope maybe maybe there were staff that
were saying don't touch or what I wonder
I wonder you guys to actually touch it
touch my hand my hand was on there
[Music]
too hey people are saying they couldn't
go like
was it that busy instructions unclear
too sacred to touch no touch please I
did it for you I even had like around my
hand I I had like an outline of you know
marker around my actual
hand cuz I you know I drew around my
hand I outlined it uh and then it was
like yeah I did it with an orange pen so
I had orange marking around my head
fingers
funny
yeah yeah could be a hygiene
thing I don't know but you know I kept
this idea secret uh until the end
because I didn't want people to like
copy my idea cuz I thought I was a
[\h__\h] genius for it and afterwards I
told some people and they're like oh my
God Kar that's amazing that's so good
that's such a genius thing I'm like yeah
I know that's why have the
secet it's hard being a transend you
know it's
hard sweet idea right I was like I want
to I don't want to just sign things I
want I want to have an original cool
[Music]
idea
yeah I'm a genius
okay um so there were several places for
us to sign and we did that we ran around
doing that and then it was food Ty sorry
I'm I'm just like choking because I have
to talk and breathe but through my
mouth so they prepared uh food for us to
try and I just this is not what I ate
but I took a picture of the burger the
MTO Burger what do you think I wonder if
it was good I mean I'm not really uh a
fan of like two patty
burgers so and generally I I usually go
for chicken burgers but uh
depends uh so I didn't go for this one I
got the smoke
B nugget those are nugget yeah burger
looks better than spaghet spaghet there
was spaghet that was
spaghet that was spaghet I don't think
that was
spaghet or you mean your
spaghet serving burger fries
and sorry sorry sorry
sorry the cheese slices I don't know I
don't know I I don't usually like go for
burgers like this so I can't really
judge it uh yeah but we all sat down on
table
so okay here we go you guys want this
kind of knowledge even the even the
seemingly small knowledge I know you
guys are like you know thriving on that
so I know you guys I'm going to I'm
going to serve you exactly what you
want so
table table
table
table yeah I think there were like we
were like there were even more tables
but we were like around these tables and
there were like
approximately four to five chairs around
yeah probably more like
five and uh like I think this was the ID
table
mostly they were uh maybe on spread on
two tables or so uh and they were so
loud and so excited and so hyped like
the whole time ID was always like even
when we like got together in the
beginning um before going to the venue
uh they were like always likeit and then
the loudest you could just hear them
from far
away when we gathered all everybody and
and you know like all's energy is very
very strong yeah felt like school it did
I wanted to say that it felt like a
school trip like a class and all that
yeah n
[Music]
and like oh my God at at some point I
think uh oh there was wasn't even about
Yago there was
some like staff that I didn't even
really uh know like who exactly they
were but apparently ID was very aware
and when they introduced themselves ID
sang them a whole song like a
cheer like they they they all screamed
in sink and we're
like something like that you
know I'm like what why does this person
deserve a cheer like that what's going
on
yeah I don't
know maybe like uh
I don't know no
idea I wasn't I I don't think it was a
manager it was more like a producer kind
of person or something like
that yeah I don't really
know but as like some of the staff like
uh talk to us Yago was there too I think
but so everybody like spreads on the
tables and you surely want to
know where what did Kiwa sit with home
cuz like this is the interesting [\h__\h]
this is the the [\h__\h] that you
analyze you love to analyze it don't you
so we me and goba even though there were
more seats shared one
table and like I think this was the this
was the
this was a table with like f Nissa and
some other myth I think Ena was there
and so on and he was like here was like
Crow
quason
and some other I think promis girls and
so on but like here was just me and and
Kuba we were like we loner I don't know
about loner but like we just like I feel
like we were
mostly just
like a bit overwhelmed surprising right
that I was overwhelmed with things at
all like cuz also for the signing I feel
like me and gooa we were like mostly
like just wandering around alone is yeah
this does remind me of school so here
together with uh gooa and me we were
eating our food and it was cute goba was
like
excited about all the little merch we Al
you know we got some merchandise too and
she had she had her own drink right a
goba drink um and there's like a little
like paper thickish paper of her uh tail
stuck in the drink and she like took it
out and then she wiped it with like
sanitizing wipes and all that and and
brought it with her like she she's like
collecting everything and I was like
Koopa you do you actually collect like
all the merch and all that like I I try
to keep it as little as possible but
like she even collects like these like
little paper thingies that come with the
food I'm like Dam where do you put all
these things cuz I I if it's like it's
so much it just gets so much so if
anything I try to keep it at uh
like myth group merch and my own solo
merch is mostly one I keep uh or like
try to
receive uh and the rest when they offer
it I turn down because it just gets it
gets so
cluttered and with most of the stuff I
can't even do
anything um but
yeah where were the other myth girls I I
just they were around on these tables it
was just me and gooa
here I just kind of stuck with goba a
lot of the time um
yeah in the bus bus we we sat
differently I I think I I was
sitting uh like sometime I was sitting
next to nista one time I was sitting uh
close to kble and she kept on
like cuz she was like kble was sitting
here oh my God this is so hard to see so
we we were like you know like there were
seats and then there
were single
seats and like this and the path in
between right B the hus yeah so for some
reason I was I was like there was a
seating plan
guys where was everyone sitting there
was a sitting plan and and I was like it
why am I sitting alone why did people
put me to sit alone uh but I think oh
yeah here was quason there's so many KS
and behind me was
Ena uh so so uh kuo was was here and
then she kept on like looking back and
she's like Mommy and like we interacted
like through diagonally over the seats
yeah she was like Mommy
yeah when we were holding hands a little
bit and this and that uh and then yeah
uh I noticed cron quasi and Ena were
constantly
247 24/7 like throughout the whole ride
they were like talking about one topic
and I don't know if they I think crony
would probably be fine with it but I
don't know about Ena if they uh let's
let's say say they talked about like
manga the whole time and I'm like the
whole time I'm just like kind of like
listen like not listening purposefully
but they're right behind me and next to
me so you know I just like hear it and
I'm like what what what's going on why
do they know
every EV every single piece of creation
that they talk about they're like oh
yeah I know that one I saw that one and
yeah oh oh this one yeah yeah totally I
know that one I know that one oh and
they the whole time they talk about
these things I'm like how come they read
all of
them they huh how how do they know every
single thing they read like they just
know and so I turn around I'm
like how how
how what how and then they crony in
detail explains to me uh how they're all
they all have like the same tropes and
you know they just like happen to all
know the same ones and blah blah blah
yeah yeah web
tunes and I was like I I accidentally
misspoke one time and I was like weep
tunes and like wait that's not that's
not even that
unfitting yeah yeah tells me about these
like isekai web tunes and I'm like okay
I have noidea idea about any of this and
then I um I told crony yeah sorry I
can't really relate because I don't read
that kind of stuff I don't read manga
either and I don't really watch anime
and then then Quon connected with me I
felt connected because she was like yeah
actually I also don't watch anime at all
I'm like oh my God okay why and she we
both like kind of agreed that we just
maybe kind of grew grew out of it
and it's just like we we don't feel the
tingle anymore and don't feel so
so I don't know just like the all
the it's just not just not doesn't feel
like I don't
[Laughter]
know I tried though recently I tried I
watch I tried watching dunon
mishy black
I don't
know I can't relate I know I
don't and then one thing I got to
say I I was really surprised because
like the last time I saw her I felt like
she she was dressing more
like you could say tomboyish but I don't
want to necessarily say tomboy just it
just was like not um a dress it was just
like you know pants and all that so I
was like hm n hold that's her style but
then this time I feel like I had a
completely different impression of her
cuz she was really girly and she was
wearing dress and and while her makeup
was so pretty and she was just really
really really cute and like had a
different Aura than usual so I told her
that that I was surprised about it and
she was very amused with it
too
yeah cool
[Music]
croner s this yeah the versatility of
quason she dressed up for the occasion I
don't know I don't know I don't I really
don't know what's like more common with
her I saw like two sides of her now and
I don't know which one is the the more
common
one so I had some nice conversations
with quason here uh and yeah so
interaction was kind of like this m
every once in a while I would like poke
r i be like
hi yeah and I would just sometimes say
like hi when I saw her around
while she was signing stuff and all
that or in the in yeah wherever wherever
I saw her yeah
uh yeah and then yeah n and foka have
were having a lot of fun together I saw
I didn't really want to intrude on on
the Advent T so I stayed away from that
except for the end like when we when we
drove back and I was sitting next to
narissa and I told her narissa my throat
is so [\h__\h] I need I need to stop
talking now okay and she's like okay no
worry about it no worries and then I I I
talked anyway I tented it anyway and
she's like you need to be quiet Kiwa you
need to be quiet be Qui
now and I could stop talking I had so
much to say it's like the curse the
curse
guys did you ever see F fuava and M part
no no except
one time
M
uh there was a occasion where we sat
down somewhere in a
table I sit
here and
like sit like here and like no before
even
excuse me before even
like both of them could sit
down uh Nissa sits down here and I'm
like Nissa is separating them but then
later on it's like she kind of gave up
on it because I don't know they for just
ended up sitting together again it just
happens it's just naturally happens
before I Noti before I could notice they
were sitting differently and narissa was
like here and fuu were here I had them
all across of me all across me she
separated them no I was excited about
that yo like oh you got some guts to
separate
them nice nice
nice that comes from deep within like my
love for
you
[Music]
nice you know it's coming from like
really deep
below um so
[Laughter]
yeah excuse
[Music]
me
nice I'm
okay yeah maybe I have a sinus
infection maybe so okay uh where my
tangents I'm not even getting
anywhere let's
[Music]
see so I invaded ena's and's
conversation I stayed with go a lot I
kept on like complimenting her cuteness
and her uh hug ability I was like
go I don't know why I feel so good to
hug I kept on hugging
her and she was like always so t t
like
[Music]
yeah yeah IIs Iris you know I want to
say thank you to Iris because when my
throat started
feeling weird uh I actually randomly ran
into her
um yeah uh in in a hotel lobby I
randomly ran into her and I'm like Iris
what are you doing here and then I tell
a little bit about uh my current state
of health and then she tells me about a
yogurt that I have right here as well
right
[Laughter]
[Music]
now
she told me there's this this yogurt
that probiotic that she always eats when
she has like a sussy fruit uh and when
she feels like something's coming and it
was too late for me already but I still
felt like okay I'm going to give it a
try yeah probiotic
uh yogurt so I ate it and it really soed
my throat so I want to say thank you
Iris for helping me out with that yeah
R1
[Music]
yeah thanks
I
h i so good to save my stomach
problems yeah she knows she knows she
knows some good
things big tascal iway she's talking
about it a lot
lately nice I got her not so Secret
inside of
knowledge it it's it's it tastes like a
normal yogurt and I'm sure there's like
many yogurts like this so you
know but I'm I'm glad she shared it with
me she's been spamming that lately oh I
see so everybody
knows okay oh her what
really okay moving on moving on or was
there something else here uh about the
Expo like us checking out the
[Music]
Expo let me
think some I think some people some
girls met yagu for the first time and
they got really nervous about it I'm
like like the moment they saw Yago
they're like oh wait is that Yago is
that Yago I'm like oh yo just yo and
they're like oh my God oh my God y y y
and they start fangirling and like
screeching and
like need to take a
picture freaking out and I'm just like
yeah I mean I've seen him a million
times
now yeah they freaked out so much
yes re yeah I finally talked to re that
was uh finally my collection is complete
uh when I when I finally saw her for the
first time I was like who are you we
she's like
yeah like oh my God hug hug hug we hug
and we didn't talk that much in the end
but um it was good to finally get to see
her properly talk to her and all that
now now my collection is complete ultra
rare best girl she was amazing in the
concert wasn't she her singing wow every
year every year you got to look forward
to whis's
Performance cuz yeah uh she's amazing we
were like backstage and we everybody was
like whoa whoa that's our girl that's
our girl let's
go she's nuts lit
[Music]
this performance of Sing Out is
amazing she always delivers
yeah so so so comfy to listen to her and
like she just blows you away
ah so okay let's talk about the dday the
first um so I couldn't sleep
well uh didn't sleep much that was
problem number
one yeah and I was already feeling like
a little bit Oozy doozy I don't know if
that's a
word but I was feeling like sussy
already but I I I was ready I was ready
to rumble the adrenaline was keeping me
on my tippy toes and so me and goba um
went to the uh venue together uh with
our
managers like everybody like we weren't
in like smaller groups I think Bales
like joined a little bit later when we
were already there and dressed up in our
stage
outfits uh but yeah me and goba came in
and when we came into the like uh
backstage room thingy uh there were only
I think two other Japanese members
already there and so a greet uh greet we
greet them and then we immediately were
asked to change in our outfits it was
really early yo really early really
early so so so early like I was like
what are we going to do all these hours
yeah really look there was there was
some some boredom but a lot of time to
think about what we should uh do in our
MC and uh you know to chitchat with
other members and so on and before the
concert started like earlier before that
the Expo was was starting so we were
like watching um on on jma's laptop I
was watching everybody was like watching
somewhere uh like the the the some some
of the footage of the beginning of the
Expo stream but yeah so we go in and we
we get passed over our clothes to change
into me and gooa go into changing room
it was set up like a hospital I was like
this looks like Hospital doesn't it and
and goo's like yeah you're right oh my
God I felt I felt the same thing and so
we change and and and we discuss we
discuss our outfits like oh this looks
kind of funny today doesn't
it and then uh yeah we start like
getting ready and doing like checks
uh technical checks and this and that
and then the technical checks are over
and in the meantime more and more
Japanese members are coming in so I'm
like saying hi to
everybody and and giving everybody a hug
[Music]
yeah
and
con I connected with con again when I
saw her I was like
yeah what is I'm like hi and she's like
immediately she apologizes to
me because uh of
some like plans or that she like
didn't follow up on and like several
occas I'm like oh it's okay it's
okay it's fine it's fine just um and and
she's like next time we can do it next
time and I'm like oh oh you want to like
this time she said it from from
herself out of her
own not necessarily the double date uh
more
like other things I was I was uh trying
to get her to be in my birthday life and
uh originally she said yes and then
scheduling and other things I guess
happened and it didn't happen and then
she apologized to me in person this time
I was like oh it's fine it's fine and
she said next time I I totally want to
you know do it next time I'm like oh
really okay well then I'm going to start
planning you
in
yeah that's unfortunate yeah I was
unfortunate but there's always a next
time usually
so yeah and then and then I was like
happy because like she seemed o she
seemed very open to connecting again so
I was
like sticking to cor a little bit and I
like massaged her right I gave her
massage cuz like she was in the in the
off time where we didn't have anything
to do she was like kind of falling
asleep on the table and so I was like h
what if I start giving her a random
massage so I start massaging her and
she's
like she says like it hurts it's so
strong it hurts I'm like yeah but it's a
good pain right she's like yeah you're
so good and she was really enjoying
enjoying my massage and then I go in
with the elbow for the first time I
people always tell me my massage is good
which I think is because I know where it
feels the best cuz I go to so many
massages but my my hands are small and
my fingers fers are weak so I can't
really do that
much like I only really can do a good
massage around the neck and the top of
the shoulders because that's where I can
get some grip but besides that my hands
are too small to get grip anywhere else
uh but now I tried with my elbow and I
could go in behind her shoulder blades
and all that she was like holy [\h__\h] y
let's go she was moaning quite a bit and
then I found a spot that you know that
goes like you know you just feel like
some something is like moving around
right every time you go over it and I
found the spotlight then and she was
like Oh So Co so so so cool I'm like a
yeah that's it I feel it
too I'm like yo yo I'm making cor happy
with my massage let's
go
yeah and then and then I stopped and was
like if you want
more I'm going to visit you okay and
she's like yeah please and she told me
you know we started watching uh
Wednesday the show uh over at her place
a long time ago last year and I asked
her if she continued watching it and she
said no of course not cuz like we we
promised to watch it together and I'm
like oh okay
oh so I don't know probably not no time
this time um but maybe next time I'm in
Japan again I can visit her again and we
can continue watching Wednesday
y
yeah
yeah season two no just season one for
now but I hope season 2 comes out yeah
just for myself cuz I already watched
season
one so okay okay
okay
uh what
else I just had some small conversations
here and there I I I talked with ayai
quite a bit and I talked with koni quite
a bit yeah everybody was so nice and it
was like ah it was just so nice to be
with everybody and hanging out with
everybody it was a really cool
experience and then there was time
for lunch is something like lunch so oh
oh that trans
transparent uh what's this
oh let's make
new okay
so they this time it wasn't bental they
actually had some kind of
catering did I say Kai again no right so
anyway they say oh lunch or whatever is
served and everybody the Japanese me
Members they immediately like run for it
they they all together in a big group
they run for it and like guda gets up
for a
moment because she sees everybody going
there and thinks like oh I guess it's
time and I I stay seated because I'm
like I think I'm going to wait a little
bit like they're going to take a while
until they all have their food and I
just I don't want to just stay stand in
line out there oh you know I'm just
going to wait I'm just going to chill
you know no need to rush and so Kaa sits
down again seeing how I'm waiting cuz
she wants to go with
me so after everybody comes in with
their food and they're done I'm like
okay good now we go so she follows
me uh and here okay oh
[\h__\h] uh where's the pen this is the
[Music]
pen so here's like a catering table is
thing and
there's a like a salad section then
there's uh some something that was like
avocado with
something and then there were like two I
think that was here two like pork
dishes and then there
was
uh some other stuff some other stuff and
rice and
soup oops
[Music]
see yeah kind of like
that and then yeah here were the plates
and the
cutlery and this and
that I'm her moral
support I think it's so cute how she
just stay with me I have full control
over gooa so I go first
right I go first and gooa is like next
to me okay here so we start and I'm like
no I don't want this and I explained
what everything is to gooa right and
then I said no I don't want this and
then what do she do she doesn't the
first was salad I'm like okay I'll take
the salad and they they give me stuff
from the salad and goba takes the salad
okay we move on it's the avocado stuff
I'm like no I don't want that and I
explain to googa what it is and and she
sees me not taking it and then she also
just doesn't take it and move on and
then there's some pork stuff and I'm
like H I got to eat something so I guess
yeah I'll take it and they put some
stuff into my plate and then I tell go
what it is she takes the same thing and
then we move on to the next it's another
like pork thing and I'm like yeah I
guess a little bit and goba here's what
it is from me and she takes the same
thing okay I'm like I see what's going
on
here
yeah I sense the pattern then there's
some something that I don't like I say
no no thank you and then I tell goba
what it is and she's like okay no no I
don't want
it I move on to the next one and it's
like I think it was some kind of rice I
didn't
really feel like eating it cuz it had
like seafood in it but I was like okay I
got to eat something so I'm like okay
I'll take it and I I tell goba what it
is and she's like okay okay so she takes
the same thing again and then and then
uh I think there was maybe maybe one
more thing where I said no and goba also
it's like okay no no no no need then
yeah I don't need it no fine no I'm fine
and I'm like okay okay here goo here
soup do you want some soup cuz I want
some soup and she's like yeah soup yeah
yeah yeah please
please so we ended up with the same
exact plating there was so many dishes
so many dishes and the ones I didn't
want she didn't want the ones I took she
she
[Music]
took it's so I was
like Kaa even we have the same like kind
of taste and like you know we look at
things and and we decide if they're
appetizing to us or not if we want them
or not and we have the same kind of like
feeling about that Intuition or you just
like you just want to do the same thing
as me I don't know either way I'm
flattered I'm
happy
and then we go eat and I feel like we
both also like kind of didn't have that
much of an appetite to begin with and
and yeah we ate like the same amount
pretty much
and the soup was the soup was really
good though the soup was really good for
my
fruit yeah uh then there was one time
okay so this is without gooa I'm sorry
but this is the the the
the I have a coffee incident and a water
incident I think huh no is it the same
thing no it's different coffee incident
and water incident okay
so why do I even make two of these
doesn't matter so there was uh there was
a
okay there's
two water boilers I guess and there was
one
coffee thing coffee machine which I
think also dispenses hot water if you
really wanted to uh and then there were
like tea bags and coffee and like
everything that you can imagine
there so and also there were like
snackles so I go here and I'm like okay
I got to make some tea my fro Tarts and
so I I put like I take a cup and I put
the tea bag in and
everything
and then I I stand in front of this like
coffee machine I'm like H how's this
work somehow I don't I don't know even
though normally I know how to work these
machines I didn't know how to work it
and I had a tea bag in my tea in my my
cup right and I had honey in there too
and then a staff comes by and like cute
staff she shows me this button and then
I put my cup underneath and and she
pushes the button and she's aware
shut
nice and she's aware that I need water
right hot water H but she pushes the
button for the coffee and the coffee
comes out and we're like ah but that's
coffee we panic and she's like com
outside com out I'm so sorry like okay
should I like pour this out and still
drink it I don't know maybe I just pour
out the coffee and then just you know
put water on top she's like no no no
let's make a new one and we make a new
cup we make a new cup and then she's
like okay this time we're going to get
it
right this time like she she puts it
under the coffee machine again though
and I'm like H what's she doing she was
really P she was really P because she
puts it under the C coffee machine again
and is about to press the button again
I'm
like coffe I'm like this is coffee
though you know that it's like ah ah I
am right sorry and she laughs
embarrassedly because she like we just
had this you know we know what I need I
need water and then we finally get the
water I don't know she was so
pun really cute I'm like don't worry
about it it's funny to
[Music]
me
and then another time I go get another
cup of tea right and I'm like I go to
the water machine and I know how the
water machine works
the so I go to the water boiler or
whatever you call
it and I press the button nothing comes
out there's like a lock button and then
you you press the lock button and then
you press the like go button and I press
the lock button and press the go button
but nothing comes out and I even I used
it before but suddenly it's not working
anymore and so kind
OFA walks out I see her and I'm like oh
hia and she's like oh what's up and she
walks over and then she she decides she
has to help me okay so she like tries it
and it doesn't work and we're like Oh
weird we go to the next water machine
somehow it also doesn't work and it
seems like maybe the electricity just
the cable was connected but somehow the
electricity isn't working we followed
the cable and the cable was plugged in
everything I don't know I don't know
what we were confused why it wasn't
working and
so this is the water boiler right when
opened and there's
like there's water inside so you're not
supposed to do it this way but we open
it
up uh to check if there's water and yeah
there's plenty of water and it's hot too
still so I'm like kind of maybe maybe we
should like I don't know scoop it out so
I take a I take an empty cup and I'm
like okay I'm going to try this but then
I was like worried about my fingers I
was worried I'm going to burn my fingers
when I dip it into it I wasn't sure how
to do it and then kind of does and like
let me do it I'll do it I can do this
and she she really with
skill elegantly without touching the
water with her fingers once she
[Music]
Scoops Scoops Scoops the water pours it
into my cup Scoops the water pours it
into my cups and so on and so on until I
had a full cup and I was like I'm like
kind of the same boy I love you much
tension I'm like you're an angel did you
know did you know I think you must be an
angel and she's like I always has
been and then I tweeted that out and
that was funny kind of Stand by helping
me get my tea so sweet with a Chad yeah
very
helpful and then so from the
beginning uh on like once we like me and
guda got together early in the morning
we were like thinking what could we do
for the MC and they gave us like a rough
pattern to follow and not everybody I
said this in my I think I said this in
my Twitter space not everybody got the
same pattern I think depending on where
your MC was in the
concert uh you they they wanted you to
do something specific that fits that
moment right and we were like in the
middle is so they wrote down do the wave
say hi do introductions through the wave
and then do the capture the moment thing
and that's pretty much it the rest we
can do whatever we want uh but even the
wave I would say was of course optional
we don't have to it's just like an idea
I
guess so I love doing the wave so I was
ready to do the wave but
H right so we were like
like gooa and me were on a table
here
a there were many tables
[Music]
here people were
like down here there were more here most
most Japanese Senpai were like down here
and
then and ban were here is and uh akisa
and mat were in this table and me and
gura and Bales after a while too and
jenma and goba manager was here we were
sitting there right and so anyway I went
around because I wanted to make sure I
looked uh I tried to find all the MC
couples okay everybody was here I
thought so so I go to all the MC couples
I'm
like
I ask everybody what they do what they
do what they do and they all tell me oh
yeah we do this we do this nobody
mentions a wave
nobody and so I'm like okay okay I could
do the wave then we can do the wave I I
tell go okay we can do the wave and then
we plan our whole um a whole MC around
it we still like I had the idea to still
do a like a Japanese lesson I was like
good what do you think I don't know if
this is interesting but this is the only
thing I can think of right now now what
about me teaching you some new Japanese
I think the Japanese people over there
will love it cuz they are so freaking
all over your Japanese and uh people all
know the B phrase that I taught you so
how about we follow that up with
something new that is like similar and
she's like oh that sounds good I like
that I like that so I started thinking
up some things that I could teach her
and like thinking of a whole
conversation that would have a good flow
and that makes
sense uh with maybe you know like some
sui and some
B yeah I I I came up with like you know
ah so first i t taught you Bo now how
how are you feeling now you're nervous
right so our legs are
poo it's another similar word I thought
it would be cute and then we can like
move our legs like that so that would be
cute right and then she's like yeah
that's good that's good and then I'm
like okay we need maybe another one cuz
this is not enough h how about now I say
uh so you're nervous so that makes you
sweaty so how
about but that's actually a little bit
um
spicy possibly so I was hoping for the
audience to be
like
and and then she I told her to be like
oh what does that mean I'm like oh no
nothing sticky and slimy is what that
means and she's like no it's beautiful
I'm like yeah okay then that means s
she that's how you say it's clean but
anyway that was like the whole like the
conversation that I I
scripted uh I thought of beforehand for
us to like you know I I I thought we
needed cuz we were so nervous we needed
something to you know just just go by uh
you know we didn't like have the script
in front of us or anything and I I I
wish we had because I tried to keep all
the points all the Talking Points in my
brain uh and it was it was difficult I
was
nervous such a big
audience
yeah and then
uh we're like behind the scenes behind
the stage right and and we're like uh
through the monitor we can like watch
the others what's going on and all that
and the first MC happens the first
MC and they do the wave I'm like
there's like a there's a screen here and
we all like ended up like Gathering
gathering around it you know and I GAA
stayed here though and and then I see I
see the wave and I look back I'm
like I'm like
Y and she looks to me she's also like y
we just give our ourselves these like
yit
[Music]
eyes for hours we were under the
impression we can do the wave and I'm
like I mean in hindsight we probably
could have but I wanted to like not be
too repetitive you know uh and then on
on the last very last stage free there
were like four four wave MC's or so in
the end so maybe I could have done the
second wave yeah but in that moment I
thought maybe it's not good to repeat it
maybe may now I got to come up with
something else so we we got together I'm
like I go over I'm like emergency
meeting goba what else can we do and
then goba wanted to do some kind of like
call and response so I'm like okay okay
okay leave it to me I'll I'll plan out
the call and response so we were
thinking we're going to do like some
kind of battle where you want to like
split um the audience in half two sides
and they also will change their colors
right uh into orange and blue and like
split it like
this and then we're going to see who's
louder so guda will
say and they
say but I think they ended up saying Sam
was thinking they would say Doo but
while we heard everything the Acoustics
were kind of confusing so I don't think
we heard clearly what people were saying
obviously the Acoustics were weird um so
anyway it was just a loud something loud
screaming and then I say okay KY ke KY
ke that was the plan and then I was like
we need a few more right so uh uh I I
told GAA to think of like what was it
two more three more two I think two more
words to make them scream so my second
one would have been
kfp and my third
one I don't remember would have been
something else and then after doing that
like back and forth back and forth back
and forth
we would have gone like okay how about
horo I together and then capture the
moment and that would would have been it
but
then then it did not go according to
kak at
all at
all so we had an
invisible timer in front of us oh wait I
have pictures for this
this was also like uh the
pose like right before we like uh go
like k k k k k k k you know Sparkle
Sparkle Sparkle Sparkle Sparkle Sparkle
Sparkle in we were like on standby right
standing there and we were going to do
something else I think in the beginning
but in the
very one second before the sparkle
Sparkle Sparkle shows up GAA changes her
pose and and like changes the plan I'm
like we're doing that okay so I swear
like one or two seconds right
before so I went along and it ended up
being like
this yeah cuz originally we were going
to be like very much like unbothered
like we were just going to face that way
and no I guess that way away from the
audience and be like completely
surprised that we're here like confused
where we are and like hi oh hi GAA oh hi
K oh oh how are you oh my God where the
[\h__\h] are we oh oh my God that was a
plan and then suddenly we still do did a
little bit of that but GAA did this cute
pose was a good cute pose very cute so
good idea goba just a little bit last
second yeah it was fun though like was
really funny and uh I had a good time uh
even though it was
stressful and so I was watching the
timer right and it was like they told us
we should do maximum 5 minutes
maximum and so I was keeping an eye on
it and on my on my fingers I had some
notes I had some keywords like k key and
kfp like all the keywords for the back
and forth you know uh and also the neba
neba and the sal sal I wrote that on my
hand too cuz I was worried I would
forget the words uh I had it pretty
ingrained in my brain but I still
thinking like the nervosity is going to
make my mind go completely blank it did
partially make me go pretty blank so
it's good that I wrote it down on my
fingers I haven't done that since
freaking
[Laughter]
school yeah oh there was no sweat there
was no sweat cuz it was mostly cold you
couldn't even
sweat yeah so uh I was looking at at the
time and like the beginning cuz we heard
the audience cheer and obviously it
makes us excited and
like the time was passing by so fast and
we didn't like immediately go into our
introductions so like you know it was
like
wobbly so we already wasted like a whole
minute I think until we went to our in
uctions and uh then like everything took
so much
time and I I really tried to
hurry GAA told me by the way she doesn't
remember anything I I she was like what
what are we going to do what are we
going to do and like okay okay so right
before it starts right I explain her the
whole rundown again like this is this
and this and this and this and then like
5 seconds later she's like I don't
remember I don't know I'll leave it to
you
baa I'm just going to leave it to you
I'm like oh no problem leave it to me I
think I have with all in my brain so
just just follow my lead and she's like
okay okay okay let's
go yeah um I wanted to
be uh reliable so I focused really hard
I wanted good to be able to rely on me
and not have to worry about
anything um so I tried to stay
cool and then I noticed we were like
like uh starting to do a call and
response but it was already 4 minutes
in and I'm
[Music]
like that looks very freaking difficult
I don't think we can do it all I was
thinking that and I was hoping that GAA
maybe was looking at the clock
too but she told me afterwards that she
didn't see it at all she didn't even
like realize there was a timer there
she wasn't aware uh and I I tried to
make her aware though by pointing at it
I thought maybe she had seen it but it
turns out she didn't like realize
anything and that's why she was also
kind of confused when I was breaking the
call and the response of like she said
do and they said do I said K they said K
ke and I noticed the time is at like
4:30 or
something and then uh she says Doo again
and I'm like GAA Doo again okay okay I
thought we were doing different
words this is going to maybe take a
while as she was already straying off
her path I was like this is y this is y
I need to I need to stop this so I was
like H how about we are just we're just
going to be friends now let's be
friendly and just um you know say whole
life together all together no more
fighting and she's like oh really you oh
why not you want to do like something
together no more no more battle I'm like
yeah yeah yeah and I think at that
moment I point at the
clock and people were thinking I was
pointing at the audience no no no I was
like I was trying to do tele telepathy
to
her we got to we got to hurry this up we
only have like 20 seconds left or so I
think were in the end we were even over
5 minutes and we were being told to wrap
it up wrap it up wrap it up like not
told by voice but just told by pointing
at the
clock look look look and pointing at the
script that only said capture the
moment like oh I got to Segway into this
y y so um yeah I break it off I do a
quick uh hold holdu and I I I I see the
staff strongly pointing at cap to the
moment probably being angry why I I'm
now doing H but I'm like trust me trust
me I'm segueing into it I'm wrapping it
up I'm I'm very aware of the time don't
worry about it I'm just trying to like
make this somewhat natural and then from
hor IA we went into capture that moment
and our pose by the way was supposed to
be like a like we were taking pictures
of you guys I don't know if the post was
recognizable but that was the intention
yeah cap to the moment already come
on uh a Big R it UPS I didn't need a big
rra it UPS and I I I I noticed it's okay
like I uh G was following my lead you
know so that's
okay just rely on
me yeah captur a moment became a little
bit of meme didn't
it trust the W trust the
process so this there and that was
really exciting that was it it was
really fast and crazy but I'm still
happy I got to do it with
Kuba yeah yeah yeah really
happy I'm bonding more and more with
Kuba ever ever since like uh last year
uh like around the obviously around the
3D uh debut time already was bonding a
lot with goba and then after like soon
after that I think we found out that we
were going to be together in the H life
summer theme song um as the only iens in
our song and so that made us Bond a lot
cuz we know we knew that we were going
to Japan together for that uh all that
and all that so we were bonding quite a
bit since then looking forward to it and
enjoying our time together and then now
we're like together again for the MC so
yeah I don't know I think we we've grown
to be very comfortable around each other
yeah yeah station archive
yeah
[Music]
sorry
yeah so yeah station archive was also
one of the songs at the the honeyworks
concert uh so basically I was in in two
songs for the honeyworks concert I was
uh wait I have fitting picture Tada
sorry low quality it's a screenshot from
you
guys there were two stages for the
people who don't know h two I mean three
for the people who don't know
uh and this is really cool because it's
new and this way so until now we were
always having our Expo in the event
halls from the Maka makuhari mes okay
and then the makah Mesa has an
adjacent V life Hall venue that we had
been using for our lives until then um
but we were definitely in need of a
bigger venue that one was already big
but we were outgrowing it right so what
they did this year
is they used some halls for the
Expo but they used how many Halls is
this I think three Halls
could I think it's free
holes which is insane it's huge it's way
bigger than last time and this time they
were able to make like free stages and
you you capture each moment sometimes
they're here sometimes they're there
sometimes oh wait you can't
see I was I was ing the stages sometimes
they're on that stage sometimes they're
on that stage you know you got to
capture the right moment on the right
stage and all
that yeah I think it's free
Halls she thought there was a mirror oh
cuz it's so big well I can see how you
might think that that would be an insane
mirror
though uh so uh the
the middle stage was kind of the main
stage but like here I guess in this case
we're over here I think judging
by judging by uh the view I think we
were here on this stage the MC was was
the MC in the middle stage I actually
don't know where we
were I actually don't know it was uh
hard to grasp reality do you guys
know and where was where was my
solo it was hard to really grasp where
the [\h__\h] we
[Laughter]
[Music]
are like yeah the osata yeah that's the
only problem I think there's good sides
and
downsides yeah to this like the good
side is that even like let's say there's
only one stage and you get like a seat
over here and there's no side
stages yeah then you're kind of oh then
you're kind of
um effed maybe but this way you're lucky
because sometimes you know maybe there's
something going on on this stage but
then on other times then on other times
maybe Oshi appears here but you're all
the way over
here yeah it is what it is but but you
know you get a you get uh more chances
of being in the front than if there was
only one stage perhaps you were the
furest from me most of the time ah I'm
so
sorry gotta positioning I was lucky with
the MC but the was abstracted for me
yeah as you can see in the picture
there's like a few big poles holding the
venue
together um I
think uh from what I've seen they kept
some space where there were no seats
around it but even then I guess when you
sit here and you look you look that like
why am I doing this with squares you
look that way I guess it could be
obstructed
yeah it but I think
still uh this is pretty dope because we
can still stay in the same venue for the
Expo to be like next to us and uh have a
bigger venue be able to put way more
people in
um yeah also I mean even if you can't
see like straight over there there's
like screens here screens here oopsie
screens here screens here big screens
yeah and then oh they were like the
seats they were like generally facing
that
way right they were facing what is this
they were all facing that way but uh I I
noticed when for example somebody was
performing here they all would turn over
there and all look there I guess except
could it be
I couldn't see so well but like could it
be when like they're performing here but
all the seats that are the furthest away
I think they were just sitting down and
like watching the screens maybe cuz it
was sasani like a little bit too far
away so they were just like chilling and
watching the screens maybe is what the
impression I
had a vent Guard art that's right right
yeah yeah yeah yeah like and maybe the
middle would still like turn around and
look over there
but the the furthest people would
probably just like watch the the screens
instead I think that's how what was
[Music]
trending no that did not happen oh y'all
also were like looking there oh okay
okay okay then I was wrong I thought I
had that impression at some point maybe
that was just like during the MC or so
there was no sitting down oh my God you
guys have must have been
[Music]
exhausted yeah okay
wow I wonder I wonder how that must have
felt like the first time it happened
okay we start with a big group song and
then then it goes into a first solo like
first everybody looked this way I wonder
when you see like someone appearing here
everybody must have just felt okay I
guess I guess we all look over there and
then how many thousands people thousands
and thousands of people all turn around
at the same time just collectively
decide okay this is the direction we're
going to look at why is this so
fascinating to me it's just so organized
I love
it my legs are dead
a I'm sorry
I think it's it would have been okay to
sit down during the
MC but it's hard to sit down when
everybody else is standing obviously so
I think for the future I'll I'll for MC
I'm going to make it my goal to uh
remember to tell people to sit down
during the during the MC cuz if if the
actual performer tells people to sit
down then everybody will feel
comfortable sitting down because
everybody will be actually sitting down
not just like five people and then they
can't see [\h__\h] cuz everybody around them
is standing yeah I think uh fubuki Senai
told people in her MC I think that was
her to sit down and then people sat down
and I think like from my POV like going
to Idol concerts are like 2 hours long
or so I remember being really relieved
when the idols would tell everybody to
sit down because then actually everybody
would sit down and you just get a little
break from a really
exhausting ERT so
far so next time I'm going to make
people
sit I'll remember that I'll trying to
remember that next time if I get to do
an MC
again yeah yeah it can't be really
tiresome a lot of people also they
didn't just go to the Fest they also
like before going to the Fest they were
at the Expo for a few hours like 2 hours
or however long you can beat her
beforehand which sounds extremely
stressful to me really stressful people
were like trying to pick up their
merchandise and all that and we're
rushing over to the to the
life
venue that were that was some points
that I was talking about in my Twitter
space where I feel
like maybe we should separate it it's
it's really convenient to have it all at
the same venue at the same time but
maybe we should separate it so that this
kind of stressful situation doesn't uh
come up anymore that you can enjoy both
without having to like rush back and
forth just enjoy both
separately uh have a good time that way
don't be scared that you're going to
miss out on
[Music]
something the
Y but you know having it together is
just more hype having both things
together on the same weekend it's just
obviously more hype but yeah when you
separate it I don't know who knows who
knows really not what I can
decide
yeah
H apparently even when the MC's were
telling people to sit down they still
like didn't get people to sit
[Music]
down ah the coolest thing
ever like I got to see this uh in the
rehearsal really
clearly uh
about and then when I I the the only
concert that I got to see like properly
like where I was not involved in it was
the very last one I was able to see
properly uh from beginning to end pretty
much
um
so there I could also see it in the live
stream but okay free screens right big
[\h__\h] and they did this super cool
thing that was the coolest thing ever
they did like a laser and they painted
with the green laser they painted the
logo onto it and then there were like
these white light bars moving over wo
and then they go
like and they do it here and then you go
back and you follow it with your head
and with your eyes you follow the light
bars and then the laser goes
like that was so so pretty cool the
first time I saw it in person I was
like wa this is so crazy and I saw it
without people being in the venue right
uh so I saw it like so clearly it was so
crazy so
futuristic that was so cool
right
I thought everybody would be like so
[\h__\h] hyped about this yeah
exclusive that's why we're all setting
up it's a wayte to sit down well yeah
yeah I mean if you guys have the power
for that go ahead and stand but if in
the future if the MC tells you to sit
down and just sit down just take take
the take the nice offer to sit down and
just sit down you can still see if
everybody sits down then you can see
clearly I would say you just got to you
know be part of the first step of
sitting
[Music]
down that's so hype I think
um going to talk
about
her
she served she served it
all this is her why do I still have this
one up
here oh so many
picturesa so
Kima
Kima uh is my new song that is going to
be out in the first week of April I was
going to release it immediately after
the concert but then
everything uh I don't even have the AL
the album this like jacket artwork yet
and the MV is still in the in the works
and so yeah it's the song has been done
ages
ago yeah but uh some delays so I can't
release it right away I hope you guys
will still be hype like not just you
guys are obviously hype about it but
everybody who's not like a a kfp who
watches it all the time H who who
watches me all the time I hope those
people will still be hype about it but
it seems like I left a really good
impression that people did like the song
[Laughter]
uh I hope people really like the song I
think I think people really like the
song I think the impression was really
good uh even though backup vocals were
missing um
uh uh but uh yeah I I'm glad I'm really
glad I was nervous about it because so
this song just to give you guys uh a
throwback
um to remind you or for people who don't
know
it audition so there was a
Eurovision uh song contest audition and
like we really spontaneously decided to
apply because I didn't I realized really
last minute that it was still going on
and at that time I was together with
Mooney and I was like Mooney would you
be up for this let's let's
go k West Angels let's go and then
within a really short amount of time we
made the song but
uh I mean the demo was already there it
was one of their demos that they had and
I listened to through all the
demos and I was like which one out of
these would be best for Eurovision and
even if we didn't make it for
Eurovision uh the theault was I can
still release it on its own
anyway um but yeah this was the out of
the demos that they had I thought this
is the probably the most hype
uh still not necessarily like if we
could if we had time to make something
from scratch would have probably made
something else and even if there was no
intention about your vision at all to
begin with then my next single would
have probably also been something
different I probably wouldn't have gone
for a theme like this like this is kind
of like I would say like uh girl crush
theme in K-pop you call this I think a
girl crush theme and it's kind of like
black
[Music]
pinkish yeah so your vision
uh rejected
me um and then I had the song already
and we're like okay you know what I'm
going to do this thing I'm going to do
this thing
where I perform an unrevealed song for
the first time at the at the vest cuz
other people have done this before at
like our whole life English concert
right I think and in the fast and all
that and I I I noticed it's always
[\h__\h] hype when people are like oh
what is this song I don't know this song
confusion is it a cover is it a new
original I
mean ideally there should shouldn't be a
confusion about
it uh should know that it's a new
original but I think it's kind of hype
um and I did I did tease you guys a
little bit that yeah there was going to
be something new performed I I would
love to also you know perform my album
songs but having the chance to uh
perform something that's even newer that
you guys didn't hear before was just too
tempting so I really I really wanted to
do that um s
[Music]
so for me I was really nervous it was
kind of risky cuz uh I love I love love
it when the the audience really like
cheers along with the song but when they
don't know the song they can't do it but
this was kind of my specialty to like
have the have like chance and all that
and have people follow
along um so that wasn't possible this
time I tried to get people to
sing cuz I think it's pretty easy that
part is really easy and I sing it so
many times in the song so you can I
think pick it up and I heard I did hear
the audience uh singing along when I
like was like
M and I I'm pretty sure I heard them
saying they were probably like confused
and like H I hope I'm singing this right
I hope I heard it right the Japanese
Bros especially were probably like okay
I'll
try I'll give it a try but they did
[Music]
[Laughter]
wello s with
the yeah I was like come on come on sing
with me and they
[Music]
say
yeah yeah U I'm looking forward to the
VA
uh looking forward to it to watch it
together with you guys hopefully
tomorrow but the VA is still not up
right so maybe tomorrow I'll do the
gaming stream first uh just in case cuz
like don't know they're taking so much
so much time m
but I want to watch it together with you
guys I'm craving that song I'm so happy
to hear that looking forward to the
studio version right the studio version
uh is so good is so good there's again
like we usually you know this is the
same team that's behind do you and
Sparks and a lot of my album songs and
these these songs they uh that I make
with this team they rely very much on
backup vocals they have like so many
backup vocals that I would say you know
it's as important as like any instrument
in the instrumentals like the guitar
or the drums I need I need
[Music]
about okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay so I'm back sorry I brought water
and fro candy I'm not going to stream
much longer
probably um so um I was saying yeah the
backup V is really important like you
guys remember when I played you the
Acappella versions of previous released
Songs From Me which are just so
beautiful and mindblowing I can't wait
to let you listen to the one from Kima
it's
amazing um so to me that's that's really
important and they were they were
missing for the performance
but I was surprised about that uh but uh
hopefully you'll hear the version with
Becca vocals soon cuz some of the
choreography is also um uh kind
of it needs the back of vocals the kick
the little small kick that I did in the
Coro I was hoping you guys wouldn't
point it
out because it's a bit embarrassing cuz
that
kick was a along going along to some
backup
vocal where it actually goes like
haha uh you'll you'll you'll eventually
understand later on I'm glad they zoomed
out yeah apparently
but
uh it's a bit embarrassing cuz I was
like what am I kicking
for you'll understand later on but even
without the bag of vocals it was [\h__\h]
hype right I I'm so glad it was received
so well I was so nervous about
it as I said first of all cuz people
don't know it so they don't know how to
Vibe with it that's a big concern and
and uh yeah I'm just
[Music]
nervous [\h__\h] that water is
cold we need a zoomed version yeah so um
maybe in the future you can see me dance
this again also for the MV um I haven't
haven't seen like any previews yet for
the MV but kodu is working on it uh kanu
told me that my motion capture is not
perfect still um like there's some uh
apparently my my thigh trackers are
maybe a little bit
wobbly so we maybe have to cut some some
chal parts just because it's uh looking
wobbly but we'll see we'll see I hope we
can keep a lot of the cool moves in the
MV yeah I got to figure something out
about
that got to let him work his magic yeah
is it workable this I think so it should
be mostly
workable I hope I hope he sends me some
preview
soon he's he's he's so sweet cuz he's in
Japan right he also went to the Expo and
all that and he's still working on it um
on the
MV uh during all of
this thank
you can he used the concert coros what
do you me what do you mean what can he
can't do anything with that he doesn't
have the data or anything like that he
has my data and he's got to work with
that uh oh yeah yeah I have a I have a
teaser though yeah yeah the te ah the
teaser you guys don't know the teaser
yet I'm probably going to release it
like next Monday or
so um so yeah uh Kima please look
forward to it it's a hype song a badass
song that's uh basically an em
of oh I don't need to if you're a [\h__\h]
to me I don't need you uh I'm strong and
I'm good on my own or whatever I don't
know like look at me look at how
powerful I am I slay um every
day uh kind of like
that uh and uh yeah and then um
so
remember
the
of remember the
of the
reason why I organized that is because
around that
time um I found out that they put me and
Chloe together as a unit I'm like
hm okay time to
bond so I was like
col looking at how things are going to
go do you want to do an off
collab
so yeah yeah yeah we we were the last
unit and also the last song before the
last song which was the big group
song
uh you yeah no not I mean as and there
are solo songs and there's unit songs
we're not like a unit like H toi guys
yeah so we bonding speedrun kind of yeah
as I was like do you want to do an off
collab you know just you know I mean
it's a nice so opportunity I'm in Japan
let's do it so we had the off collab and
then after the off collab I remember we
had a deadline of uh like deciding or
suggesting the song that cuz we we can
suggest songs it doesn't mean that we'll
get to do that song um but we can
suggest it and you know at the time I
was like realizing how good Chloe's
English is and I asked her if she feels
comfortable singing English songs and
she's like yeah totally I would do it
and I'm like okay you know what I
think probably usually 100% 100% almost
of the unit songs the nons solo songs
are usually Japanese songs if we sing an
English song because you're you're
capable of it then I think that will
leave a big
impression it will impress people for
your English skills and it will surprise
people that we're doing an English song
in the first place and she's like oh I
like that idea and I'm like okay at this
moment K just released very recently
like maybe one or two days ago I think
his new song original song Wild
[Music]
Card uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh
and I really loved it I listened to it
I'm like this is so cool I want to
perform this
sometime and then like it it all just
fell in place you know so I was like
with Chloe Chan
and yeah right it's not my sampire
right and I was
like our deadline of suggesting the
songs is coming up you say you're open
to see an English song how about we sing
this one and I let her listen to it and
she's like oh yeah that's really cool it
really good really good once again I
steal a k song yeah and make it my
own and so we suggested this one and
just as a backup we suggested like
another Japanese song
um but we were really hoping for the
English song to go through and it went
through and I'm like let's
[Music]
go
so k k made Kima for me my original song
but wild card was also K so k k double k
k sparkly I was representing K really
hard during this
concert yeah wild card was [\h__\h] dope
it was really fun to do it with Chloe uh
I I I
I think we we nailed it and we had a lot
of fun with it it was dope and
uh I I didn't think too much of it when
I saw that they put us second to last
aka the last before the final group
[Music]
song I didn't think too much of it but
in
hindsight looking how uh other uh how to
say other the other concerts were so to
say closed with big bangers before the
group song by big hitters in hindsight
also cuz you guys were saying it uh I
think in the hashtag in hindsight makes
me think
yeah they must have put us there cuz
they had high hopes and because they
thought it was going to be dope and
going to be exciting and nice big finish
I didn't think
about them putting that much value into
it um until it was over but now in
hindsight I'm like did they you know put
us there because they they really
thought it was going to be insanely good
or really cool and a big smash or
whatever I suppose so cuz like they put
a lot of thought behind like the order
of the songs and all that and The Vibes
of each
song Oh especially I think in the in the
last concert they had like three
emotional songs uh in a row and then a
song that went yeah I think that that
was like really well planned those was
nice yeah they they trusted us to
deliver and we delivered we served I'm
sorry happy because like I feel like
also like in this concert like different
from
honey thanks to me being able to perform
two K songs that are both [\h__\h]
badass Chima and wild card having like
similar Vibes as in like being cool and
badass and a little bit sexy I think the
impression I left this year was a really
good one and and and a mature one that's
why I wrote on my shikishi I wrote on my
that like you know what's the shikishi
that square thing that we signed I wrote
kfp I'm going to show you like a mature
side of me or whatever yeah yeah so I
think I did that this year
I um I'm shaking cuz it's really cold in
this room I'm
freezing but um I'm proud of myself and
I
[Music]
I'm I'm looking forward to watching the
Vlog for real for
real and then in h honey I just showed
my cute side with Kuban uh I I mothered
her uh that was fun dude that was really
cute you know I still I I feel actually
I think I feel a bit more
confident uh dancing cutely cuz I think
it's
easier um it's easier to dance cute than
it is to dance sexy and uh I have more
practice in conveying a cute Vibe
through dance than a sexy one and
so uh yeah dancing
it
withan uh is is like H more chill and
fun and easy for
me yeah but still like I like both I
like to show both sides and if you know
I get the chance to do both then I'm
excited to do both uh but I think I had
a big focus on Che Wawa in this first
concert so I I I think I left a good
impression and I want to follow up on
that with uh my Chimera MV release
ASAP but we got a wait a little bit when
it comes out I hope you guys will hype
it up and spread it all over it's my My
First Single since uh do
[Music]
you right cuz after that was the
album so it's been a while no pineapple
no pineapple was in the album so yeah
since do you since do you my first solo
single since do you
um so please support it when it comes
[Music]
out
at least once the Vault comes up I hope
everybody watches the Vault again and
gets Chima freshen their mind again and
then I put out the teaser I'm hoping the
I'm hoping the vult comes out this week
uh and then the teaser uh refreshes it
in your mind again and then bam the MV
and Spotify and
whatever I'm really excited for this one
like I was ah I think for the release
party I'm going to like talk about it in
detail and I'm probably going to have
Mooney uh in the Stream as well to like
talk about the recording process cuz she
was here with me actually In This Very
Room right next to me recording it
together uh like she was coaching me so
we're going to talk about that in detail
but uh I have to say I have to go quite
out of my comfort zone for this one
and and I was like feeling like I can't
do it I can't do it this kind of voice
now I can't do it but yeah she supported
me really well and coached me really
well through it and um yeah PR praised
me a lot and I felt more and more
confident about it so I have a good
feeling about Kima now and yeah looking
forward to releasing it finally properly
but this was a little not a little I
guess a pretty big first taste of the
song it's even better trust me it's even
better when you hear the studio version
and all that at the the back of
voc you served so hard I aced my exams
let's go
congratulations yeah yeah as I said I
really would have loved to do like
retrospective with the live B obviously
or like sleep talking or pineapple H or
tgw I would have loved to do all of
these
songs but the fact that I got a fresh
song that I didn't reveal to anyone yet
that was newer than the album I kind of
had to you know show it off take the
opportunity to show it
off
so so
[Music]
this
let me
[Laughter]
check me and
kanatan I was like actually like talking
a lot with Kanata if I think about it
now uh throughout the day I was
like flexing to
her uh certain incidents of my friend uh
Sarah
Gutenberg uh you know her well don't you
we're all fans of Sarah
Gutenberg for people who don't know um
that's just me okay uh
but I I told her uh everything uh about
Sarah's gutenberg's recent Adventures of
meeting her favorite Idol and I showed
her a picture of Sarah Gutenberg with
the idol and she was like what the [\h__\h]
girl you winning in life holy [\h__\h] what
she was like really jealous and all that
and like absolutely blown
away
and oh Salah couldn't beg his members
only no not anymore not
anymore and and yeah I told her all
about it and she was like holy [\h__\h] are
you for real she was in
[Laughter]
shambles Flex
tool and basically if you don't
understand canata loves Hello project I
love also hello project K however uh she
told me she's always been like that kind
of fan that stays at home and just
watches all the DVDs and and everything
from home cuz she maybe doesn't feel
comfortable or too nervous or whatever
to go to the concerts in person and all
that but I was very much the kind of
person that would go in
person word repetitive and I would go in
person and yeah uh I was I was very much
uh that kind of utaku who would go to
the concerts and the handshake events
and everything and
so we we however we really uh like hello
project both of us really like hello
project and so we relate on knowing all
the songs and knowing all the members
and this and
that she's going to punch that beef and
get out of frustration
yeah but
so my friend Sarah Gutenberg a famous
model um from let's say Switzerland she
uh got to
meet uh
and one of those Idols from back in the
day in
person uh see her revive her activities
a little bit even though she's been gone
for many many years um and see her
appear on stage again and then take a
picture with her backstage cuz she's
special sah Gutenberg is so famous you
know she's on every VIP list and so she
was on the VIP list there too and she
got to go backstage and say hi to the
idols uh that used to be in Hell project
but are now not there well you know um
yeah and then they took a picture and
then and
[Music]
then
that retired
[Music]
Idol and sarak Gutenberg did not only
take a picture
[Music]
but the
unthinkable thing
happened that I wouldn't even dream
[Music]
about after after the
concert we hung
out
and
just sat together in a
[Music]
bar in
person
like like you know not from fan to
Idol but not even Idol ex Idol
but like on the same level
[Music]
yeah oh and I told that to Canan too and
she was like what the [\h__\h] I'm like I
know it's insane I'm winning she's
winning s Gooden is
winning huge [\h__\h] win you have no
idea even though she's a famous model
and all that she was really nervous
about it
and like
she tried to be cool and all that but
she couldn't stop staring at her and
uh kept on asking questions I she was
certainly not the coolest she could have
been but she left an impression
and
exchanged line contact which is like
Japanese WhatsApp or you know you know
it's like a messenger that everybody
uses in Japan
P
[Music]
[Laughter]
Exchange Bei I'm I yeah holy [\h__\h] to
holy
[Music]
[\h__\h] and
so
yeah um remember last year when I
performed Suki Chan with as my unit song
with uh am Ina and M uh we had a four
people unit and they were like what song
do you want to sing and I said four
people unit one of my favorite Idol
groups which are gone now
smileage uh it was a four people
unit I'm going to if they if the other
girls have no ideas which they didn't
they didn't have any suggestions I was
like I'm going to I'm going to suggest
songs from this group then so I
suggested Suki tan Suki tan Suki tan
Suki Suki suan remember that me and the
girls performed that last year on
stage and one of the members of that
group was this girl that I just told you
about so she wasn't aware of uh that
that happened you know but I told her
about it and I showed her the
DVD uh footage and uh she was like holy
[\h__\h] this is the cutest performance of
su Chan I have ever seen and being told
that from the actual
original person who was part of that
obviously is insane and obviously I said
no obviously you were the cutest version
of that but having that being seen by
her and approved and praised by the
original
girl is
like the craziest thing ever that I
never thought would happen but I'm so
happy it did because when I chose that
song back then and when I was able to
perform it
there I
it was almost like my dream of joining
hello project back when I was younger
that dream that I had that never came
true in that moment when I was
performing a hello project song of my
favorite girl group on a big stage in
front of thousands of people it was for
the amount of that
song it came
true kind
of in some
way like
some kind of fantasy world it came true
and and I I was hoping to one day
because this group doesn't exist anymore
for a long long time but me choosing
that song was also a way of honoring the
memory and showing my love and support
for
them through that so I was always hoping
that they would see it and because I was
already kind of in contact with Canon
another member of that Idol group you
know I've been in contact more or less
like not really we just like follow each
other on Twitter and sometimes talk a
little bit um when I I I sent her back
then I sent her this the like a spawn
code to watch the concert online but I
don't think she ever got to
it so I don't think she ever saw it
um but uh I I'll I'll get her to watch
it too eventually but like two members
will be or are aware of me doing that
and me honoring their memory and me like
once again showing them to thousands and
thousands and hundreds of thousands of
people who would have probably not even
known the song or the group otherwise
surely a few of them knew it a few may
have uh you know overlapping
interests but you
know I think most most of them didn't
know the song most of them didn't know
the group and so in a way you know I I
just as a huge fan uh having the
opportunity to keep that memory
alive and
represent
them up on that big stage to me it felt
like a huge honor and and and once in a
lifetime chance and and yeah as an otak
of that
group I was just so happy to do it and
and now getting someone to see that who
was part of the group and acknowledge it
and be happy about
it it feels like I went full circle and
like I I completed the quest and I fully
accomplished it and and
and I love them I love them and
you I'm going to cry
not
[Music]
good
yeah so anyway that was last year though
but I showed her cuz I you know got to
know her recently and become friends
with her or Sarah Gutenberg got Sarah
Gutenberg got to know her but you know
it's uh confusing
overlapping uh
Consciousness um
ah crazy can you imagine did I convey
these feelings in a way that you can
imagine how insane all of this is how
how going full circle and like an idol
group that I uh have been supporting
since like maybe they're gone for a long
time but like uh maybe 13 years
ago now my first Orosi of that group
becoming I say friend yet but like uh
you know becoming like personal of that
person and then being able to show them
what I've done to honor their memory oh
oh my
God I can die now and then revive cuz
I'm a phoenix but I could die
now sh oh thank you for the raid
sh
oh did that sound like
her thank you oh my God I'm like uh
talking about Expo and Fest right now
and just
shared a fan girl moment oh my
God my life is complete after that uh
once the VOD comes out I want to show
her uh my Chima performance because I'm
hoping she'll fall in love with me even
[Laughter]
more y
[Music]
y she already I'm surprised she's able
to rate me yeah when I'm in Japan
streaming at na prime time but also when
I'm in Austria streaming in Europe prime
time that's
amazing wait I remember when I just
looked at my tangent list and I
remembered one thing you know we were we
were um backstage right watching the
laser thing through the monitor
happening again I saw it in person then
we saw it through the through the screen
right and it was happening and we were
like w this is so cool and because we
were all together there um the moment we
heard the cheers and the laser [\h__\h] it
gave us like like uh Goosebumps and
shivers
um there were some people crying I was
like on The Brak of tears but got to get
your [\h__\h] together for the first big
group song of course but like had tears
in my eyes and coyote coyote was weeping
by the way she was really really really
moved and emotional which was really
sweet so I gave her like a hug and I I
pulled her over to me
actually let me show you cuz that was
kind of sweet I
think
um
so there were a lot of chairs and people
a lot of people were sitting on them
this is the back view of the chair okay
uh I'm sitting
here and
um the the other chairs were all
occupied but coyote was like like next
to me here and she started crying and
I'm like I'm like putting my arm over
her pulling her over to
me and like then she was like like
here you know kneeling on the ground she
L she later got a chair don't worry and
we were like
watching as she was crying and I was
like rubbing her shoulder and all that
like you know I was also like it was
sniffing a little bit but I was just
like you know it was a Tey moment oh
wait ah [\h__\h]
you okay okay okay first she was like
standing there you know and then and
then I IH ah God damn it she was like
standing here yeah and crying and then
we sniffing and I'm like pulling her
over with my long arm and then you know
she sits down next to me
here and um I'm just like rubbing her
shoulder and is that a toilet no it's a
chair and we're looking that way onto a
screen you know and we could hear the
cheers and everything and she was
crying and I'm I'm like while she's sff
snuff crying a little bit I'm like
rubbing
and it's okay he's okay and we're like
cuddling you
know that was sweet isn't that sweet can
you stop talking about my long
arm okay stop talking my long
arm everybody was getting pretty
emotional in in in the beginning cuz
that's when it got real you know I'm
shaking so
cold that's when it got real and
everybody was like feeling it like oh my
God we can hear everything and oh it's
amazing uh I was like
wow
wow it hit so hard it felt so
real
okay
love I was sitting on a chair not a
toilet why is it a toilet it's a
chair heater do go no heater I could
have turned off the AC but I didn't now
it's [\h__\h]
cold ah yeah so I wanted to say like you
know besides
this
happening I was like you know I think
coron Senai was like like somewhere next
to
me and we were watching the laser thing
uh again and I'm like w this is so cool
right so cool and then G is like yeah
it's really cool but like you know when
anybody raises their arm or so and gets
you know um the laser you know going
through the armor so you know it will be
cut off and I'm like no no way she she's
like really confidently bullshitting me
about it she's like no no for real for
real like it actually like it's really
dangerous and like there there nah
there's no way there's no way and she
keeps on insisting on it like no like
totally the laser it's really dangerous
it's really hot and it like burn your
whole arm off cut it off completely and
I'm
like
um n no no you're bullshitting me cor
zire she's like
yeah she tried really hard and I was I
was not believing it but I was like
considering if that could be true but
and I was like ah there's no way because
that would be a huge Hazard like you
know somebody I mean I think it was way
up above everybody's heads so you
couldn't touch it cuz you're not that
tall but even if that would be too crazy
and too dangerous actually true 90 no
way it's not a laser it's just
light
right it's just light right I mean what
do you guys know I should ask the staff
there's no I mean isn't laser just light
too wait don't be so rational there's no
way that they would go for such a like
if it was actually yeah that's just
lying like they can't do something so
dangerous even if it's way above their
heads I was like they couldn't risk
something like that that would actually
cut people's arms
off the coret was is trying her best to
[\h__\h] me and I'm like no no there's
no
way yeah it's not strong enough to hurt
you see okay it's a laser laser laser
light what what makes a laser laser not
light in
that why how is that if you guys agreed
with me that laser is
light how at what point is it now light
anymore with a laser that's what I need
to
know just because it's green and and
[Laughter]
[Music]
thin uh just because it's super
focused concentration of
light so because it's
[Laughter]
thin but H you guys say that this one
couldn't have cut my arm off but is
there any laser that could cut my arm
off yeah right cuz there's
also I mean that is a thing right is
that a thing this one maybe not but
other lasers can cut off my can they can
they
yeah okay okay okay okay okay okay
cutting like yeah yeah there's cutting
laser right
yeah okay huh so was that a real
laser kind of want to know kind of want
to ask staff but it's like such a random
question ah well thank you anyway coron
you can't [\h__\h]
me I'm smarter than that I'm smarter
baby smarter smarter baby
[Music]
smarter yeah I
think uh
[Music]
mostly ah one last thing I want to
mention
[Music]
remember last year at the
Expo uh there
were
Showcases
of things that members made either
previously or after they were told that
they can make something and I showed my
sock puppets
right and I was really hoping
that this year they would have that
again so I kept remember the nails
stream the nail salon
stream after that was over and I got I
took off all my nails but actually even
before that I told the other members
that Iris and Cali I told them keep your
nails keep your nails because if they
have another showcase like that we got
to show off those nails so don't throw
them away I was really strongly telling
them that but it turns out turns out
later on they actually did get rid of
them pretty soon after even and didn't
keep them but I was like whatever I'll
keep mine anyway and so I was like where
can I keep him safe at all times
so how long has it been since that
collab it was no was it
November was it was that in
November I think that's like five months
ago
so for five months I've had my nails
loose in my uh money purse in the coin
section every time I would open it and
try to take coins
out there were also Nails
there I was just keeping them to always
have them just in case do a showcase
again and they didn't end up doing the
Showcase so I still had the nails
recently you know when uh after the uh
First Day concert me mum and GAA uh we
were rushing to do the uh rushing over
to do the the Expo like secret
appearance where just for like 10
minutes we were like talking to the
audience uh just asking them questions
like you know how did you have fun where
did you guys come from far away and this
and that and um behind the scenes in the
waiting room of that
um I was uh I had my I opened my purse
to give someone money maybe I don't know
uh and then M was next to me G was next
to me I was sandwiched between them
and and then I go for my wallet wallet
that's the word word I go over my wallet
and I see the nails and I'm um somehow I
feel the need to share with M why I have
the nails in my in my wallet and she's
really amused by it and she looks at my
nails and I'm like I'm just like
jokingly saying H you want to have one
and she's like yeah and I'm like well I
don't really mean it but and then she's
like she actually for real wants one I'm
like really you want one and I was
actually kind of flat that she would
want to have one I'm like for what
and then she actually insists on having
one and I give her uh the one that was
on my
pinky and I gave it to her and I'm like
you can say on your stream now that you
have one of my nails and she's like
that's exactly the plan behind it that's
why I want to have it I'm like okay
looking forward to you confusing your uh
viewers with that with
having uh
my
nail right I'm so glad someone would
take it off of me because the Expo was
not willing to do that the Expo did not
want to have my nails Expo didn't do
that showcase I wish they did ah
man I guess they don't want to repeat
the same thing all the time but I had
something
ready
[Music]
for
[Laughter]
I wish I did that again it was cool
seeing all the things everyone submitted
for real right it's it was like such a
cute and
personal thing to show off yeah my my I
was so proud of my sock puppets they
were so
freaky maybe we can suggest them to do
it again for next year if there is a
next year
here
yeah guys make sure you if there's like
any suggest was there like a way for
fans to suggest anything for Expo I
think I feel like there was but maybe
not
booths but generally if there's a chance
that you could do it tell them you want
that personal project
to Showcase again okay tell them let
them know
m talked she talked about the
nails she already
did right she did have a she was also
like I think starting her stream an hour
of the M or
so yeah the after survey tell them in
the after survey
survey that there there was the Showcase
in the previous Expo and you were kind
of feeling like it was missing this
year cuz tell them kiata had some really
nice self-made nails that she ripped off
of her fingers that she was keeping
forever and then you guys didn't want to
showcase
it
why 5 minutes for real what no
way no
way she only said she has my nails and
didn't elaborate at all great M great I
think it's great without the context if
you want the context you get it at Wawa
Wawa's stream it's great to just say
yeah so uh oh yeah and I have ki's nails
and oh yeah so the food was really
good
huh back pedal back pedal what do you
mean you have K's s and she just doesn't
elaborate yeah that's
[Music]
great oh yeah so was a good time um
maybe I still have some tangents that I
can think of to share um in in the
members watch along um but for now this
is it and I have to do some stuff and uh
yeah had a really good time sadly you
know pretty much everybody is gone now
and I'm just like
chilling uh in in for a little while
longer but it was so nice to see
everybody and hang out with everybody
and make some
memories uh and not just you know Ian
but like also to together together with
ID and Japanese members um we were all
all bonding and having a good time and
just randomly running into members in
the hotel
lobby uh yeah we were we were we were
having a good time it was like a again
it was like a like a school
trip yeah checking out the Expo together
and all that you still going to hang
with
pomu very soon sooner than you may think
and not only on one day I think I'm I
think I'm meeting her three days in a
row
yeah starting from
Tomorrow ah from
yeah yeah uh F
cute uh yeah F very cute uh very very uh
uh
twinsy
um uh had a good time talking to
them yeah so is
it very cute uh so is it yeah I don't
know what to say everybody was cute
everyone is sweet I was talking with
everybody and uh also k k gave me a uh
spices she told me before she came to
Japan she told me uh on DM she was like
I'm going to bring you um s I'm going to
bring you spices I'm like okay and then
when we meet uh actually she she runs
into the room and she has like candies
right and she was going to give out
candies to us and I'm like she gives it
to me and I'm like you told me you're
going to give me spices not candy and
she she gives me like this like
no like this
huh and then she runs
out and she C she runs back she comes
back with
spices she's so cute she keeps this like
Angry Angry confused look not not really
saying anything but like thinking yeah I
guess I did tell her I would give her
spices not candy she was giving
everybody else candy but uh to me she
brought me some spices I was like maybe
I can do
because it's Indonesian spicers maybe I
can do a cooking stream uh where I use
the spices and she's on on Discord on
the phone telling me how to cook it
maybe maybe we could do something like
that
ah she's so cute she's so small and so
cute yeah okay that's it for
[Music]
now as it for now uh had a good time uh
getting better uh my nose is clearing up
uh my throat is a little bit clearing
up I I will stream tomorrow if the vault
is
up by the evening I don't know if it's
up by the evening when I'm making the
thumbnail then we'll do the VA watch
along members only if not then we'll do
the horo TOA game now I really need to
go to idle meeting so in
we
thank you so much H for supporting me in
this busy time for cheering for me ah I
heard you guys cheer and thank you for
coming to Japan for the ones who did go
out of the way for like I know a lot of
you guys would love to do that not
everybody's able to do it and that's
fine too thank you for supporting me
from home home but also for the ones who
went through this big Journey which was
probably also really expensive thank you
for going through that to support me in
person I think it must have been a
really crazy experience for you guys
especially if you don't know Japanese it
must have been even crazier um but you
did that you did that
guys and I hope it was really really as
special to you as it was to me uh it's
it's it's crazy I didn't think there
would be such a big kfp
representation um
but yeah uh it was way more than I
thought and I'm really happy to have
such a sweet supportive
uh big mass of chickens supporting
[Music]
me
I want to hear it again I want to hear
your voices again someday um so I hope
we can make that happen
again Big Friend shaped yeah pretty
massive big
chalk uh yeah I'm I I want to hear from
your stories I hope you guys the ones
who send super chats I hope you are
telling me in the Super Chat messages
about your experiences cuz I want to
hear them um please feel free to share
them uh also on the kfb hashtag uh I
like to I was so happy to see you guys
meet up do like kfp meetups or like go
eating together even though I was
thinking when you guys when I saw you
guys go to the ton KATU place and I told
you beforehand it's a really small place
so if you go there together like don't
go there all together at once I told you
and then you guys went all together at
once
anyway did you guys like I don't think
you can make reservations but then you
took up all the seats I saw the picture
of you guys taking up all the seats how
did you do that did you just like stand
outside and wait so that all the seats
would be empty and then what how did you
do
that
to how how how the flocks flock
together well you gave them good
business on that day I think think and I
think especially uh cuz that that's like
within Japan that serving size is huge
like the big chunks of meat that's not
normal tonat is serving um but I think
uh considering North American portion
sizes this must have been a good portion
size for you
huh
did you did you tell them did you tell
them why you went
there did you tell the staff did they
ask you like why the [\h__\h] are there so
many foreigners suddenly in our and some
of them are dressed Orange what's going
on with that did you did you tell
them I wonder if they know about the
about the YouTube short that I
[Music]
made h
so much flavor thanks for recommendation
I'm glad you liked it yeah it was really
[Music]
big no just
eight you didn't tell him how am I going
to get my
payment they might have known yeah if
you didn't tell them how could they know
they probably just thinking hm
something's going on but we don't know
[Music]
what
I know I'm glad you had some good food
some good nutritious food to strengthen
yourself for the concert and the
Expo it's so sweet to see
you to see you all out there and about
having fun uh I know we you're already
all said of we do in then there I go
again Tang thing
ah Sarah sensory cards no kiaha sensory
cards
why so much orange weird is it like you
know how on St Patrick's Day everybody
wears green maybe they were like hm is
there a day where everybody wears
orange I need to
pee we're going to end it here in EN
I'll see you tomorrow thank you so much
I love you guys this was an amazing
experience let's watch the B
bye
[Music]
sh