[Music]
so
did a small loopsie but now i've seen
how all good
[Music]
[Applause]
hello
and welcome to
kirby's dream buffet
[Applause]
a newly released game by the highly
acclimated acclaimed
nintendo
yes
small company
um small company big bucks uh but this
was actually cheap
yeah
i was so surprised this game is only 15
dollars
yeah i'm so uh we have gathered here
today because um
the moment i saw this uh release trail
not release trail the first trailer
about the game i was like i wanna play
this there's no release date yet but
then i i hit up these girls according to
their image colors because there's a
green one a yellow one and a blue one
i was wondering how you decided that
makes sense yes makes sense but
i thought you know i'm not pink but i
didn't want to kick myself out of my own
collab so
yeah i was like whatever uh i'm orange
both
close enough this is adjacent to one
yeah yeah
and i did manage to maybe you guys see
it on my screen i didn't manage to get
like a fire red skin already so that's
looking pretty gorgeous
i like their skins in this game yes
yes they're skins and it's kind of like
fauna said fana what did you describe it
as
oh it's kind of like fall guys meets
mario party meets kirby yeah i think yes
yes yes yes
no no no fall guys also has skins you
don't have to put in fortnite there
i don't know i'm getting real fortnite
vibes
[Music]
amma has fish on her head i wanted to
ask amen about her fist delivery tell me
about it
oh yeah i got fish delivered today i got
um six clams they're little tiny fresh
water clams
uh-huh yeah i'm gonna put them they're
gonna live in the sand in my tank and
then i got the two bumblebee gobies a
little tiny striped fish they're very
cute these are cute
bumblebees and water you're gonna kill
them
and then i got um
five black neon tetras and then uh one p
puffer
fish
it's a dwarf puffer fish
is it poisonous
no no it's fresh water and um they're
very very very cute and uh yeah they're
activating right now
can you spell that one
he pumper
is it
p-e-e-a oh
[Music]
oh it's cute it looks like a frog
there's some pictures it looks like
hands
it's cute yeah it's really cute
what are you gonna name the fish peanuts
[Music]
peewee
are you gonna get any bottom feeders oh
well the pea puffer will attack other
fish and stuff so probably not for that
tank because he's just in the tank by
himself
ah
what about shrimp sir oh yeah i have a
ton of shrimp they have like 30 now
because they've multiplied by themselves
what kind is shrimp
[Laughter]
um yeah this is the it's the fish talk
the fish tank episode 2 everybody you
always wanted it to come back here it is
don't get me started i can talk about it
for like an hour
now you can you can talk about it if you
feel like uh
you have enough what what's the word uh
yo i only know it in japanese always
while we're playing
i don't know um enough spare time it's
not spare time but spare
fair
yeah
whatever
space
headspace i don't know but yeah we're
gonna play this game for a while it's
apparently kind of small but yeah we'll
see how long it goes and it looks fine
i'm gonna open up a room
okay so you guys know the the magical
number yeah
wait yeah hiding the screen
i shall grant grand prix uh
um yes yes
you don't have to push that i think
though
oh yeah maybe you do
yes
yeah
good night good good
did we join now
i am i have joined uh you can join too i
already have
chris
okay good good good oh i'm joining
there's no numbers shown here right i
can show now okay
here we go it's time for some fun oh by
the way we didn't have self
introductions left to right crony go
wait what just happened
chronicle your life
crony the cronie die
the moment
um
how'd you get water real quick
the moment asked you for self
interjection wait are we complete even
yeah yeah
i think there's randoms drawn to a crony
introduce yourself go
oh yeah oh good oh god
um i'm oral cronie i'm
oh my god how does this work
explain more about yourself
but what else do i explain like i
i am like i manage time really badly
but i like manage
oh god what's your recent uh hobby
my recent hobby yes oh god i have a
recent hope
you did asmr recently oh yeah he
uploaded like the cover and everything
yeah that was so cool that's not a hobby
is that a house
why not oh my
it can be a hobby
too much for the mental strain
[Music]
it's my first yeah
actually i think
oh i think ome said that too what yeah
me too wow
um
round that i did the fauna
it got really big there you can just
blame it on the lag yeah
wait what is this is this how you win
[Music]
oh wow oh i still didn't do so bad
compared to chronium
introduce yourself girl hi
i'm sarah spana i'm from hollow live
council
and i like
sweets you don't seem stressed out by
this at all
what's your favorite sweets
i like french toast oh i love
foreign
what french pie
pizza pie and french toast each pie take
a french pie and a peach toast too
oh that tastes good
i never had peach pie before oh really
can you make it yourself oh
[Music]
it is pretty hard
oh big why are you so big
please introduce yourself
hello everybody
another one detective
english
is that good enough uh no
no
which fish uh
is your favorite so far in your whole
fish life oh
mommy
i guess uh i like the pea puffer because
it's super cute and interactive they're
like little dogs
oh my god like little dogs oh that's
cute oh
god
ah so whoever gets the last oh you guys
were really close
that's ridiculous
and i'm supposed to win this
why why do you say that just because you
were the pink kirby you're the main
character no i mean i guess maybe that's
the problem because i'm the red kirby
now like maybe i should have been the
pink one
drop those strawberries on me i
i bought strawberries at the supermarket
today i think that should give me a
bonus
i also went swimming today what did you
girls do today in terms of moving your
body hmm
i just woke up
just
fish fish what fish box you put the fish
out of this out of the box yeah that's
that's a smelly something
what
oh fauna defeated you well but now i
have the invincible candy
i will become the largest curvy
oh
oh man what the heck i'm invincible
finally justice has been served
we got donuts
oh
at least first
[Music]
oh
very round extremely
[Music]
via desktop
but that might be the only choice
i just i just get a different character
i think this one's messed up i'll just
uh 30 seconds
okay
the timing we just ended the round
anyway
next minute she's gonna use that as an
excuse for getting fourth place
always the excuses with this girl
i got a burger hat too
oh wait maybe i got some stuff too did
you only get this one
kiara i got orange so maybe you got it
i got the bandana waddly
and
uh
orange
finally i can be my true self hey
nice there's so many colors though i
wonder what other other colors are there
maybe maybe some patterns and like
rainbow and whatever oh
yeah there are a ton of colors aren't
there
so
cute even with a weapon perfect
okay i'm styling
i'm so ready are any feeling the
addiction to unlocking all of the
cosmetics yeah
we fought guys i always missed out on
like the cool items that i wanted yeah
right i never even got i think
when i first debuted it um the oh my god
that's
quite nostalgic um after being awake for
i don't know how many hours 24 hours or
so because of the debut relay that we
did that was really stupid um i had a
stream plans to follow up after the the
group collab and that was fall guys and
at that point i was absolutely sleep
deprived and my goal was to get the
chicken costume back then which is one
of the first costumes that you could get
i did not get it and i sucked at four
guys on that day but
some traumatic stream what do you guys
have any like
big regrets in terms of like streaming
like i shouldn't have streamed on that
day that was terrible what have i done
oh
maybe your debut
my baby oh i know
this council is about to have our
anniversary so it's about time oh did we
get kicked out
get out of the lobby we can make a new
one
my com not my computer my
switch turned off i think oh wait two oh
wait crony was there something you
regret
oh this scream won't be the one
this one's fun um
one stream that i regret
um
was like the model went so wacky that
time and like taking like a clock um it
was stop talking and nobody explodes the
stream with fauna and i was ticking like
a clock there
but it's so stressful it was so
stressful but isn't that you were taking
the clock because game made you feel
stressed out but that's that makes sense
the model the model
like the app
oh that was making you feel that made
you feel weird
like stressed out
you know i tried to get it working and
it's not so sometimes you have to say
[\h__\h] it i don't give a [\h__\h]
true it doesn't matter what about could
who was that with cortana was that you
yeah yeah i always wondered how that
happened that was so funny that's like
halloween stuff
i know
i don't know whenever i say the name to
sometimes it just comes back but i think
i disabled it for now successfully
oh is that a pc thing or a phone thing
oh i'm a bad pc
oh yeah i've been here oh hi
hi oh hi
my capture card seems to have stopped
working okay
why aren't collabs
why not find that just it what
just
the mario kart with
i know what's happening maybe it's me
maybe you can't collab with me
or not well at least uh my internet's
still working and that's good
but the game kept hmm
well test it out a little bit i'm gonna
ask amen meanwhile
what what is a stream that you
have regretful feelings about um
maybe working on ppp minecraft or
something
why you regret that does it it just i
[\h__\h] it up but and it i don't want to
go back and touch it i never want to go
back i used it so often
you know people keep kept on telling me
oh just go to the japan server
everything will be easier and i said no
i'm gonna use what i'mma build here
because i want to use the resources that
we have on this server not cheat and go
to the other one
yeah now you won't let me blow it up
i mean it's kind of iconic right yes
thank you yes
thanks for the memories even though they
weren't so great i guess that weren't
great they were great they were great
they were great uh building the tunnel
that was that was not great
what do you mean
the tunnel was one of my biggest regrets
maybe
but that was also iconic i thought you
were starting to realize all the regrets
iconic screams yeah
yeah
[Laughter]
iconic i guess it's a
yeah i don't know chad do you think that
was iconic
the building the tunnel
itself the act of doing that
it was kind of a troll troll
action
[Music]
gouda was the troll we went on an
adventure
a very straightforward straight
adventure straight straight sometimes
sometimes uh right sometimes left but
mostly straight adventure
good times
an adventure that's for
four to six four to five blocks wide
at least now we can laugh about it
yeah yes it's a long time ago it's
really
for me i'm in the second year
anniversary is coming up soon for
council first anniversary right
you guys feel like you've been around
for longer
oh
hmm fauna is currently
somewhere
hope she can
i'm trying to fix my capture
what could be
can can i troubleshoot it maybe no i
think it's good now
oh really i think
okay yeah the ribbon on your neck
uh yes is it like have you ever heard
that horror story of like the lady who
takes off the ribbon and her head falls
off oh yeah
maybe but no it's not like that i just
have a thing for chokers
seems to have a thing for it too because
he keeps on drawing them without me even
asking for them even in your normal
outfit right yeah yeah and every outfit
so far every outfit
is again this is suspicious though if we
never see your bare neck
well maybe maybe i'm somewhat of a
uh
what's the word the the dude that's put
together
frankenstein
yeah frankenstein frankenstein a little
bit of a kiara stein
are we ready to do another round
yeah do you think yeah
yeah
what what what
you think i can rejoin with the same
code oh yeah yeah i think so
yeah well
wait am i alone oh i was alone in the
lobby so i'm really here
[Music]
[Applause]
i don't know if i can do it in time you
can yeah 40 seconds left okay
password match
our secret password that we will not
share with anyone that is super secret
and super super complicated
go make long plea
i'm kind of you'll be so cute
i'm i think i'm in
am i
oh i'm in
are you here
i see you guys
yeah everyone's here
ah but the game won't ah wait that's
what was the wrong way here we go we're
back
okay yay
time for more
fighting
and looks like different maps than the
one we were on
yeah um i feel like they're all kind of
similar yeah yeah like the the principle
of what's to do is similar but they have
different designs and all that mm-hmm
[Music]
waffle hamburgers whole cakes that's why
you say that yeah it's a german word
it's a tree
[Laughter]
why are you faster than me fauna
i'm rolling rolling rolling hey how fast
you go it's about how many berries you
eat and then how fast you get
okay so let me tell you
uh so uh actually nice nice information
the first time i ever ate a bam cooking
was in japan because they really like
they really love bangkok i guess the
simplicity of it they really like it
there
but uh i think it's a little bit too
simple for my taste i like my cake to
have like some some cream and some
strawberries or whatever
on it no cream um i mean i guess maybe
you could serve it with some cream but
normally it's just a bun
it's kind of boring
but what how come
oh well if you look at the back of the
stage here oh goddammit
[Music]
oh it that in the back it's a green cake
yeah it looks like a tree like the
inside of a tree if you cut up a tree
okay i'm gonna take you all apart now
no more mercy take us apart yes like
like surgery yes
how comforting it's the [\h__\h] european
pink okay
so it's a little rough over here
man it's too short
[Music]
you may be winning the game so far but i
won your mom eating last night
wait
i'll win your your mommy too
i'm not sure my mom is interested in
girls
oh man
but navi mama was so sweet to me you
know
she was so cute
oh wow that
we talked a bit about you and me really
what's in you
did you tell her my secrets
which one which one
which one
told her all your secrets
ah
i also told you all your public stories
not only your secrets are told or
anything or we just talked about your 24
7. that's a joke we didn't we never
talked about you in the first place just
kidding that's not true
[Music]
a single time i'm like i still only have
three strawberries less than you
step up your game
maybe don't don't step it up
[Music]
i don't get this moan
wow that was chocolate oh
have you guys
[Music]
oh
yeah it takes a while
my god i'm too small
oh gosh
why did i keep getting pushed
at least you can see who did it so you
got a tornado
unbelievable i will not rest i will not
let you girls go today until i get first
place oh god
cherries so cherry how did you grow so
large wow
wow
so round so so far
let's go
brown um
what are the character treats
let's play again click
play again
please please ian curtis leave us alone
for one round
so i'm here with
i'm here
wait i'm here with amy
i will be there
i'm here with cronie why did they
separate us
you guys join us for now
now you join us no i joined you last
time
okay we can leave
good luck finding us
oh
we're
yummy no i see you crony i see your
shadow
i see you hi
hi
hey
[Music]
yeah this is like having a table we're
here oh you are here
and i want a tea party how cute we are
confirmed do we all have to press that
oh
i don't think so
it just goes
oh
race to the strawberry mountains
the race is so intense man go go go yeah
this is the part that's kind of like
fall guys
but much faster oh
it looks so good it looks so tasty i
want one yeah
what
you have to go on the sides
[Music]
no
i don't understand
what where do you guys all get tornadoes
and [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
yeah but i never get it
do you use it
yeah
oh with r right yeah
oh
[\h__\h] strawberries
i need my vitamins
i never said i was good
[Laughter]
oh fun i'm sorry hi cronie i just wanted
to be like you
how does she i just wanted to become
round like you
but you already were in the first round
yeah
give the others something to enjoy too
huh
what is this mood
um
i have no idea
get everything i'm rolling
they see us rolling
yeah
she's so hungry
i am
like a hungry hippo yeah
okay i don't see anyone is that a good
sign oh sorry
i don't see anyone nah [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh my goodness guys
ruthless
kirby is ruthless
let me go
oh
oh blueberry i know cronie was eating
blueberries before the stream i gotta go
i still am mr ah
very much in the sweet berry mood
i know
oh no no no no for the middle i'm just
gonna go for this one yes yes yes yes
yes okay two people go in the middle or
no
i don't know i think it's just one
oh yeah i don't really know yeah the
fourth piece
fourth person is just oh i'm too scared
to try to test it oh
i hate this one this one sucks
i like this one they never get [\h__\h] and
i keep getting thrown off
oh goodness
[Music]
give me a box
i'm just gonna throw you guys off of you
guys i should kick this
[Music]
oh the pink
[Laughter]
oh goodness
give me that give me that give me that
[Music]
i have a chance i have a chance
[Laughter]
well i have to see the bonus stars
anything
i don't know somebody looks really big
oh yeah
chunky
what the [\h__\h] one second kfb can you
believe it
they are shook heads
shooky shook head
oh kirby burger
no mini
orange kirby i think oh play again
yes
hopefully they put us in the same lobby
have you ever heard the saying
nintendo online is four dollars a month
and it shows
oh
no also it's bro oh we're all together
no cronies hey
cronie what happened to you not blue
anymore
i wanted to make a darker brown for once
ah
cause i just unlocked it it was cute
oh those donuts look so good sheet cake
[\h__\h] cake marinara
excuse
me
let's go
your little [\h__\h] cake
please i'll listen to my new original
song you little [\h__\h] it's a banger
can you perform it for us
yeah
yes um
a live rendition you little [\h__\h] you
little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] you little
[\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] oh
wait if i could do this we're gonna get
demonetized because that's what happened
to the song the minute i uploaded it
not too many little little shits we have
to balance them you know
keep them balanced and a good good
amount
already so big
this map looks tasty
it does oh christmas cookies
oh yeah bye
oh
how do you not fall off the edge of this
part uh
i thought that one was magical a very
good question
oh
yeah baby
what is this camera angle i don't know
where it goes
oh
gosh oh
let me let me through
look look
[Music]
tonight
there's a lot of tornadoes
yes yes not so bad goku waba go
go kiwamo go oh you can't go through the
odo
oh
[Music]
nice
i want that i think it's new
i want this cake i have no berries
can you stop bullying me
just putting a berry
uh-oh oh more time please i need more
time
oh my gosh
okay
how was that
if you girls take this from me you know
there will never be a second time and
then i will never let you go
through it
don't take it from me
who are these randoms worry about me now
i only have 15 strawberries
it's the only chance i have to win in
life okay
so depressing
you're always winning
in our hearts oh my goodness fauna i
will kill you you just wait
do it
the frets
i'm ready bring it on
yeah i'm
i'm
here go go go go
go go go go go go so first still first
so first
don't shoot there quiver oh no oh
that was a decent safe
oh
no
holy mackerel
crumbled like the crumble of a pie
oh no do you guys know super monkey ball
oh yeah yeah
you know why does they have that a
little bit
no no no oh yeah
oh
why did i just fall off
[Music]
wait this is not over
agreed
chocolate item is [\h__\h]
no no no no no
no i don't want to use chocolate
unless i can hit fauna with it
no
you did
okay i need i need the strawberries
oh
this one box is all i need
[\h__\h]
there's no nobody gives me [\h__\h]
strawberries unbelievable
yes my the strawberries are mine
ow
i love you though
oh
maybe i can still get some extra maybe i
can still get some extra extra extra
number two
it's not enough oh
you need to learn how to wear clothes
that are more flattering on your weight
hamburgers
the bad way out the end is a game
changer um
i think
i think i won
in
in my heart
we just did that one
get mario partied
[Music]
mm-hmm okay well
play again again playing again play
again
the prince i got the carby hat the
carving i'm sorry for me
i'm jelly
jelly i want oh oh you're wearing it
oh that's why you pronounce it
what do we have hamburgers waffle cake
i did order food before the stream and
it's something sweet even though i
should be eating dinner i just ordered
dessert
you're so smart you know it's never
never too early or late for dessert
are there's randoms npcs i'm still
wondering
yeah yeah they're randoms right oh yeah
just like nps knees
okay platforming not bad this reminds me
a little bit of super mario sunshine
those platforming levels that they have
there
the tick tock sand sandy ones
oh
but that's just me
traumatized me what
this the sandy no i'm talking about
super mario sunshine
oh sunshine oh
crony bye-bye
how could you
business it all gets down to business oh
no
go
it's right there
you just gotta go straight sometimes
just go straight down that's all you
need to do
what's your dreams
there we go
there we go chrome
[Music]
this like mint or something
yeah
leaf yeah
fancy
these strawberries are just i don't like
this level the goddess yeah me too
oh no
oh barely i got five strawberries
okay another race here we go
ah matcha run
have you guys heard me
participated in a real like marathon in
real life
no no
maybe in school or something yeah i did
once when i was really young
i was really into running when i was
younger
oh
country cross country team yeah it's
like a long distance running
what the [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] okay okay but no marathon or
what
no
we should go
fun
why did i go this way one day it's over
i wonder that
every day
oh
which way are you going okay i'll go
this way
where's that
i got the middle one oh really oh then
fauna missed out
i tried
[Music]
how do you stay on those
oh orange it's a mistake yeah
it's kind of pudding
oh yummy
oh
oh should i lose my thing
i don't think you lose your item yeah
you do you do
yeah well i haven't gotten a little
strawberry so far
oh oh two wheels green
stay away from kiwawa
i told you
you're dead
it's true why am i not getting it come
on
they're just escaping me
oh my territory crony
i'm swearing
yeah
i was so slow
[Music]
thank you
no
yes
no i don't take no for an answer no no
no no
yes yes
at the last second
[Laughter]
nice amen
and crony did you ever get a win so far
is it you and me who don't get wins
who i
okay one like twice or three
and five stuff you mean the final win or
just one like a single round win rooney
was very large
and at least
wait am i the only one
no
window one
i think i only won once oh no look at my
eyes play again where am i
i'm dead
look at me are you yeah
look look at my eyes
oh
they're like i see there
yeah what
whoa
what happened to you what is that
it's like a skin
cool
cool blind kirby
now i can be a blue zombie cheese oh
cheese fondue like pinata you guys like
cheese fondue
i've never had it
i've had chocolates on youtube
yeah either i'm more of a chocolate
phone you kind of person what about like
a chocolate fountain yes i have i always
had one
i would do it for christmas kind of
growth though oh no they're not gross
no
no they're not gross like they're a
little gross no they're not why
why why is this so rolly
oh my goodness
why can't i go
oh everybody else is still here that's
nice you guys are so slow
hey what are you saying
what
slow did you just call me slow
oh
i paved the way for you love it
what do you mean
one more good items in this round good
items also
bye oh i should have kept that one when
people are around me
science i never get [\h__\h] when i get the
box
just strawberries
i need i need more strawberries but it's
okay just go straight to the middle
straight straight no straight straight
straight keep
[Music]
okay
it's
[Music]
[Laughter]
you okay not play this game without
cucumber
oh
vegetables oh the cheese fondue oh oh
no
what what what's going on what are we
doing
i don't know i i couldn't see who i was
for a little bit
i saw you very clearly on it i got like
one strawberry
i guess if i got
any wow terrible look at that
covered in cheese
what did you say with cheese mine is um
cheddar maybe or mozzarella
or burgata
i like string cheese
oh cheese
cheesy strings
is one you can get that's like a it has
yellow and white cheese and it's like
twisted
oh
no that one
oh goodness oh my god
oh
oh my god how did i do that
what
[Laughter]
very saucy i'm lost in the sauce
wash my house oh
everybody's ganging up
it's incredible
straight straight
[Music]
i'm going to get back in
go
mean sharing is caring
can you actually share them no i don't
think so no because i yara was in the
middle and i tried to get it but it
wouldn't let me oh it feels like you
should be able to
mint chocolate chip cake oh it's so good
not mint chocolate at all
as long as i am
i'm playing a fun game making fun
memories i don't regret any of this
memories of losing sounds like coping
i'm kidding yes
so what
and you have to cope in this life how
can you not
it's all i have
oh no
yeah that was on purpose foreign
oh goodness i keep falling off
ooh burning fire
[Laughter]
you were in the water
oh man i have thrown
[Music]
now it's time for the bonus humming and
goats
tell me what is what is that all about
oh wow
[Music]
cake car mouth okay
cute
pixel yo-yo
wispy wood abilities you use ah ah
so just the r button or what
yeah yeah
okay
next up
well the pre-rolling thing
oh you just like roll around and get
strawberries and that's about it it's
more like a practice yeah
ah
oh crony you look cute with that burger
on your head
you'll get yours too
oh i already have it as an option but i
didn't want to like copy you i didn't
want to steal your thunder
your birthday
banana no let's like do a switcheroo
theme right for kfp yeah it is but uh
you know i i saw how happy cronie is
with it i thought i'll let her be crony
they have a fried chicken hat today yeah
i like that
get out bottle d chicken
white chicken you say
i had korean fried chicken
oh how was that it was yummy but way too
big of a serving and and then you know
they serve you the smallest serving they
have is the four people serving
and it was just me and navi mama
so
we start eating and then pretty early on
nabi mama stops eating and she says like
kiana
um i actually have to make a confession
to you and i'm like what is this gonna
be something serious what's up what's up
and then she says i actually
can't eat fried foods very well
oh
and i'm like girl you're already giving
up on eating wait there's there's still
like a million fried chicken left on
this plate how am i supposed to eat all
this alone
oh
yeah nope yep that that's uh
doesn't like sound she doesn't like
fried foods
oh
now i know where i get it from
[Laughter]
oh
that's cute
do the cups like come up and you have to
be inside of it i think so yeah
i don't know i don't know this one is
i'm winning it's slippery yeah
it is slippery
oh yeah baby i got like three
strawberries
hey i thought i was doing well what's up
with that
man
the races are so stressful i got it from
my mama yeah
my mama
ah how did i miss that yeah how did you
miss
you're
trying to roast me and then i punk you
karma
oh goodness
rng
bro
girl for your life
okay there's no going pretty bad like
how do you find good bad
get up back up faster what you gotta
tickle the joystick
oh really
don't go full yeah don't go full
throttle just go
i thought it was pressing a
sorry
is that you yes
sorry mommy
mommy sorry
mommy mommy sorry sorry
is that a meme
yeah
oh
have you been asleep for the past five
years one year i mean i've never heard
that one the cake is mine
i guess it is i'll go to the left one
yes to the left to the left
all strawberries are on the left
oh catching up
leaving army behind
yeah well i already won once unlike
somebody so now i'm just sabotaging
everyone else unleash my wage
chaotic evil
oh my gosh she really did release
terrain
hell yeah
oh my goodness
calm down
oh oh no no no no
no no spot chance
five strawberries
no no no not off the edge
oh you're jelly
oh
deli is like
invincibility i think yeah
seems like it
oh my goodness
that was crazy
i call that a mukbang
all you can eat strawberries
now don't [\h__\h] this up
i swear to god extra
okay okay i got the hovering ones oh oh
i swear
[Music]
look at that let's go
i've actually been to an all-you-can-eat
strawberry buffet in japan before wait
they have that is it strawberries it was
like strawberry all you can eat
strawberries and all you can eat
strawberry desserts so there was a
limited amount of strawberries but also
unlimited amount of desserts that made
are made with strawberries and i think i
went there
um
with money and senpai i think that was
that buffet
if you if your girls go to tokyo they
have like um
uh all these like uh in japan in japan
in general they have all these hotels
that have like these sweets buffets i
went to so many of them and they often
have like a theme uh the one that i went
to was alice in wonderland for example
yeah or one one that i went to was cats
themed fauna cats
oh
did they have real cats no musical cats
also are you guys
are we separated again oh i didn't join
japan there's a mini pig cafe
oh
all the time i hope they treat them okay
yeah
strawberry cup that's so cute holy [\h__\h]
but i'm sticking oh you can use the
hamburger hamburger hamburger okay if i
have the time i'm still um
receiving my rewards okay okay i'm
coming now i'm coming now
got one minute
one minute we got plenty of time there
we go there we go
okay well i got my win so we can end it
whenever but
let's do another round
let's see if i can
continue this saga
hmm
yummy
sound fish
i like that how come it's always a
strawberry mountain though
unlock more
yeah that's a new map though i think
fast oh my god this one yeah this one
looks new
looks like fall guys i wonder how many
there are
ah
sorry
oh my god are you really sorry you're
like totally wrong
just a little
wasting my time here oh my goodness girl
what'd you just do girl that was so
wrong
oh that's cute that's the new item i've
never had before did you guys have the
sour candy high jump item uh-uh
no
oh i think you should do that like near
the finish line
because you can't get a lot of
strawberries if you use the high jump i
guess so but it also gave me
oh i have a high jump advantage i have i
jumped too why does everyone have enough
no we unlocked it maybe oh no no they're
all gonna catch up
[Applause]
you
the little guys
that fall off
you take what you can get
oh what's this
pistachio oh i don't like pistachios
really
i like the special
taste oh yeah that's good too
oh
[Music]
i'm getting better at this
i'm getting better
yeah belly mountain
ah
i made a mistake wait maybe it's fine
wait you just climb walls uh you can
jump really high
[Music]
oh here we go wheeling
oh
i was just working really hard on that
wall and then she comes there from the
back out of nowhere just
just
destroys every hard work i put into that
it's okay life happens
it's like it makes you think you know is
it really worth trying hard in life
yes yes it's okay it wouldn't happen
kirby would have been fauna but
[Music]
[Laughter]
what are these
i like that it's not just sweet stuff
they're savory yeah yeah and i like the
order sweet stuff first and then savory
that's that's just how i like it
oh i do it sometimes
backwards
ow
how come you knocked me so far
what the [\h__\h]
oh my goodness
later yolk bounciness is just like a
bulba whoa
i'm not doing so well here okay
[Laughter]
all right
uh
we have to go aggressive it seems oh
[\h__\h] oh my goodness bro
oh you did that off the map don't pinch
me i'm really huge i got pinched i went
from first to third how
that was probably oh
yes all the time
over time
i i swear to god
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
it was just too close to call yeah
[Music]
i can be put on the grill now go ahead
carefully sometimes we have to switch it
around you know i i think today we can
um do it that way
switch rolls no
um
can we have it on
can we end it on this happy note of two
wins in a row
[Music]
[Laughter]
i don't know if i want to
be the witness to whatever whatever
you're proposing with your kfp employees
right now
we could we could chat for a little bit
yeah we can do that
can i go i'll go check out my fish
really quick okay hopefully yeah they're
still alive the one in your plastic bag
looks um actually kind of electronic
that really looks electronic
so
water let's talk
can we just talk
yes yes
i already put out so many topics today
it's your turn girls
give me something give me something
but my head is so empty
what did you do with the insides
of my head i think i just filled them
out all into building my minecraft farm
and there's nothing left oh the guardian
all right
yeah
oh you made it i heard about that
what what what is a guardian film what
does that do i mean i know i know
the
you're using like the tower thingy but
what do you get out of it
it's um one of the most efficient xp
farms that you can make and it also
gives you prismarine which you can use
to make
uh those pretty aquatic blocks
huh
sea lantern the lanterns two sea
lanterns and prismarine blocks
[Music]
so i've ever wanted to make something
turquoise blue
oh
no
i'm glad somebody's still playing
minecraft
everybody left minecraft for fun if you
want to have somebody
um to join i feel like people have been
playing a little bit well i don't know
maybe i've just been watching id play
oh my god
it's mostly id
i also kind of i don't know why are you
girls like like playing or
a game called rest perhaps by chance
i have been a little bit i have to go
feed my house after
[Music]
don't talk
i jinxed her
literally said the same thing at the
same time
at least in my timeline it lined up
are you are you eating the blueberries
why are you like gasping for words
i'm just you told me to be quiet you
can't i was like
wait what i never went
beyond that part uh before like what
happens if the jinx person talks even
though they're not oh wait oh do i have
to say her name uh and then she gets
unjinxed
then i guess oh why i've never heard
this before crony has to buy you a soda
or something yeah like oh you owe me a
coke yeah
then okay you owe me
a collabo
oh
okay take this one right now
not this one a one on one collab one on
one i want some one-on-one time with my
my only
oh
my god
my god i'm feeling a little bit caught
up in the middle of something yeah
i actually went to eat a lambion
on the river at the river i instinct
with navi mama
oh
yeah it's fun
funny you can come back come on don't be
shy
i just uh didn't want to get in the way
of anything no no no no no no no no no
no don't worry come back be afraid come
here come here
[Music]
no you're not your cats have also some
weird affinity to like um plastic
um they'll try to eat almost anything
really yeah
that doesn't sound good
okay
stuck over here funny
you told us how about we have some talk
and then you just disappear for five
minutes
sorry
and leave us your eyes on the lights
how are they doing
they're good one escaped into the tank
but it's looking fine
escape oh
is is that good
yeah yeah it looks okay it looks okay
are you gonna eat the clams at some
point no no no no no
could you though could you
i don't yes food you know i don't know
you can like eat anything cool
you trust it
yeah i guess you can eat anything that
you put your mind into it like kirby
like yeah yeah
but you what you
eat we have do you have that saying in
english because we have it in german
yeah you are what you eat oh in germany
rhymes actually oh
do business to east
one more time do beast pass to east to
beat the beast to beast was through east
do this
the best fast food is you are what you
eat the best
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
the way you pronounce the eye is cute
yeah there are some similarities you
want to be
to eat or not to eat to be or not to be
that is the question
[Music]
okay was there something in particular
you wanted to talk about with us
um
i don't know i'm not good at coming up
with topics you're the topic lady yeah i
am because i asked when you were gone i
asked these two and they couldn't come
up with it
hey what's up with that
one
what and then we talked about
coke
and going on a date
yeah
i'm the topic
and the hot topic lady
oh oh oh i didn't want to ask uh
somebody please introduce me to rust i
need to play
rest
yeah yeah yeah we should play oh okay
can you help me
i could teach you yeah thank you
okay
everyone playing rush apparently you
should play around enjoying cronie you
joined too come on join the amateur or
i think he'd like it really oh yeah you
would i think so oh yes you would you
would go crazy over organizing [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh yeah and you could have make your own
buncaroni again
but i have to feed it
yeah you have to feed it wouldn't you
love that
the bigger it gets the more flesh it
requires uh-huh
goodness what the heck
sounds morbid it sounds weird
no it's not actually blush it's just if
you build it out of wood you have to
keep wood inside like a cupboard so that
it it doesn't decay over time
then
you know
flash it begets flesh
um what you can build it out of flesh
can you can you you can
shouldn't say anything else what own
house
yeah you can build it at a bone to think
oh oh there okay
uh uh can i build it out of i'll leave
gold
or gold ashes
oh my god
i don't know
i think fana knows more
[Music]
well really you should ask mumei about
that kind of thing
well she's not here right now is she
[Laughter]
hey guys
okay
i can't i can't do her voice that well
what's up no i can't
this is why i might sound like it has a
fan can you guys hear that no i didn't
do that
all right
oh discord thank you
thank you discord i have a fan on too
hey up top
[Music]
oh i should have brought mine here to be
part of the fan clique
cook
you actually have a lot of fans right
here so don't worry about it oh okay
oh i just noticed all of you guys have
flowers in your hair
oh
oh you don't know you don't have one
whoa
flower fan flowers
yeah oh wow how does this [\h__\h] does have
a fan too yeah
i don't know
ah no
don't worry about it don't worry myself
too much trouble pour some water on your
head for my fish oh let me drink yes
fish water
you know my mom used to have a fish tank
but it was it was
they were supposedly fish in there but
it was such so much like a jungle you
could never see them and sometimes i
would
i would really wonder if there's any
fish there at all anymore whatever
i probably liked it because it felt
natural you know
yeah a lot of places to hide
a lot of green stuff everywhere very
green like a good fish jungle
yeah well
now well well
whoa whoa
are we done well well well i guess i
think we're done does anyone have the
final tallies did anyone keep oh yeah
chad did you guys see who won the the
most
ah on the top right it does tell you
your victories from my for me it's too
oh
i think cronie won the most arfana here
oh it says four one crony free
four
nice thank you
thank you
the biggest kirby
kirby well i mean i think that was worth
the 15 bucks
yeah
i kind of want to play it again
i hope they have a banana hat yeah but
not a hat oh it seems like there's a lot
yeah yeah
they're online yeah yeah yeah i'll check
it out again sometime i need to get more
of those
strawberries and blueberries
cause all of those on my balcony died so
ah
yeah i was growing like a [\h__\h] ton of
raspberries and another weird berry and
then and then uh the heat wave came and
then the wind came and everything killed
my plants and now all i have left is one
small tiny
cherry tomato which
the plant itself is not really producing
anything but as one one tomato
maybe you should bring it inside no
those are balcony plants but like
i was when i was in america you know
apparently it got so hot somebody took
care of my balcony and apparently also
watered them but not enough it seems and
then i came back and it was all dead and
from then from there on it was all
downhill
so
you can grow them again after the heat
goes away
yeah
not this summer anymore and it's not
happening anymore those were like the
raspberries you have one chance for them
like in
at least for that sort for that sort of
over the season um
[Music]
yeah and i had like four
four different like
thingies
but they all died it is okay i am i
[Music]
for a little while i felt like i had a
green thumb but i guess i don't fauna
help
[Music]
approach to caretaking so
nature is like a gotcha game
oh just throw it out and see what
happens then i guess i have to quit the
gotcha game
because i'm not carved out for it
no no
that's a that's a quarter talk you can
do it yeah yeah
but i have a big balcony i want to make
use of it but anyway that's okay well
all it's currently growing is some
weird-ass mushrooms that no one asked
for but they just came with the with the
earth that i put in there the soil
nature
they look so disgusting because they
come out of nowhere okay and the ones
that they're growing apparently you can
eat them in the very very early stage
but it after like one or two days it
already falls apart in the most
disgusting way and it turns black and
it's just disgusting i'm like ew no
wonder i dislike mushrooms
it looks like a horror movie i swear
i want to see i want to see
honestly i probably have a picture i can
send you
[Laughter]
i'll try to find something but yeah
i only like enoki mushrooms oh
those ones creep me out somehow
they look nice
they're creepy
they taste good i think they have a nice
crunch
but sure for me it's just a texture
thing but once you get used to it like i
kind of like it now because it has this
like moist crunch to it
what's the crunch
[Music]
eating coconut mushrooms prepared by
ammo i never thought of it that way
i'm gonna try cooking mushrooms for me
sometimes
okay yeah i made some mushrooms with
like a little bit of butter and garlic
and then a little bit of white wine it
was really tasty wait that sounds
garlic
anything of garlic is good
yeah that's true yeah
okay girls let's end it here
okay
thank you for answering my call to play
this game
um it was fun thank you for inviting me
sorry for roasting you girls
um we're used to
just have to fight back somehow you know
and i'll see you in
rockstar minecraft
[Music]
and in germany south vietnam when you
say fauna
juan well fun wow
[Music]
fun well
bye guys
[Music]
tomorrow i think um you know i have the
week kind of a little bit planned out
but i'm not too sure about how finalized
it is i think i'm just going without a
schedule
um after all but i have planned out
tomorrow cult of the lamp perhaps if you
guys are up for it
uh
probably at 6 00 pm my time
so i'll see you there
my sweet champions i know we can talk a
little bit about the end of my trip
yeah
a fellow coat that's right that's right
bye bye love you guys
have a nice evening
also tunic finale on saturday is the
plan
[Music]
i