n
[Music]
he
K oh wait I'm quiet
h k
[Music]
k
hello
hello it's Halloween time let me get rid
of this so bright so
bright hello how you guys doing welcome
to the
stream and today wait I'm a bit too dark
maybe today we're going to talk about
some things
[Music]
such as my freey life that just has
transpired
yesterday what the hell it already feels
like two days ago cuz it was kind of two
days ago but then not really it depends
on how you see it and what your time
zone is for me it was
yesterday cuz it was at 2:00 a.m. on
Sunday for me
H yeah empress and Halloween office I
don't know if we ever had this
combination before but it kind of
works yeah so and uh the song and the
free the uh music video and stuff like
that I want to talk about stuff like
that and then in the end we'll rate some
super chats um so you know some
chitchatting re re looking at things and
I want to look through the 3D live like
da d d da a little bit through it um and
comment on some
maybe
together and and yeah you guys can also
ask questions if you want to if I happen
to capture the moment
huh when you are writing
them y
yum sure yay so I hope you guys have
been enjoying Mirage so far first of all
if please listen to it it had like a
really strong first day now on the
second day it's like already kind of you
know what the hell algorithm but uh it's
doing well anyway my baby is
growing my baby's growing so
fast I'm so glad you guys like it
because Mirage is really uh I would say
peak in terms of my taste one of my like
within K-pop there's like many
directions you can take and this is one
of the directions I wanted to take for a
while
um yeah so I'm really excited for that
once again well then let's start with
that once again Mirage has been created
by my asteroid team kiaha Angels you
know not K but you know asteroid
consists of several produc producers not
just K and uh the producer for this song
is um I think the same as for sleep
talking uh or wait Moy are you in
chat I think it was the
same as for sleep talking I think so
well it was not the first time
um but yeah it really captured what I
wanted the problem it oh oh Mimi Mimi
amen is also a part of asteroid by the
way she does all kinds of like more
creative things but yeah what was I
going to say um what was I going to say
h yeah actually so for like this song it
was a little bit difficult for me uh
because I think Mirage was the first
time
where well not the first time where they
made like demos just for me cuz um
sometimes you know I choose existing
demos that they already have lying
around um but then some other times they
made them from scratch just for me uh
Chimera was like a a demo that they had
lying around of half finished demo and
then they finished it for me but this
one is like from scratch B the thing was
like um I wasn't like 100% sure yet what
100% sure what exactly we should go for
and then the problem was they couldn't
make like endless amounts of demos with
singing in
it um so what they were able to do is
like send me like two
different uh instrumentals that they
made just for me but I had to like
imagine from the instrumental if this
would be a banger instrumental are I
guess like easy to judge as well I don't
know for me not actually because like
without the singing without any singing
Melody like I'm not I'm not good at
coming up with Melodies myself and so IM
imagining something was really difficult
like is this should I choose this one or
this one this demo or this demo because
yeah no singing is difficult but so just
for feeling of the instrumental I went
for this one hoping that it would be the
right choice and I think it was the
right choice the other choices were
really good too so like man I just just
thought they're so good at creating
exactly what I want almost too
good but yeah Mirage Mirage
Mirage I was just so scared after Kimera
because I think a lot of people liked
Kima a lot because it was such a like
powerful uh Anthem that was like kind of
unusual from oh smoovie you want to
leave okay bye that was a bit unusual
from me like it was more like strong and
powerful and badass [\h__\h] than than
usual right
um and I was a bit worried about
portraying that the right way cuz I
don't see myself as uh such a badass
[\h__\h] really to be honest but but then
Kima it went quite well and I was able
to you know show off quite the attitude
in that um and then people liked it a
lot because it was so badass and then I
thought well
H for the next song I I honestly I I
want to do something more
like how to describe smooth and and
flowy and Airy you you know nothing bad
as I don't want to do something badass
again right away so I hope people will
like it uh and I'm surprised people
really really like this Vibe as well
yeah so I'm really relieved that you
like me no matter what kind of wa I am
showing you yeah kind of
fluffy
so yeah it's still very catchy I think
the catchiest part is the me me me me me
me you me me you just all the me me me
me Mir parts are so cute and
bouncy and catchy I hope you guys are
having earworms do you have
earworms did I was I able to create an
earworm in your
ears yeah yeah yeah
yippee I'm glad to hear that to be
honest um m Mo came up with the song
title of course she writes the lyrics
and she uh usually comes up with the
titles and everything um I didn't even
know what Mirage
meant even after I was told once I still
had troubles from remembering what it
meant I think I know now what it means
it's like an illusion or like a fat
Morana or like something like
confusing right yeah yeah yeah okay see
I know I know I know we good we good
uh but I just in the beginning I just
thought yeah sure that sounds like a
cool word I don't know what it means but
sure why
not I mean sounds nice
right so yeah
um that's the vibe and I don't know how
to go on from this well I
[Music]
guess let's talk about the load go a
little bit because we're looking here at
the album art uh or the art also like
the art I said this in my member stream
I think but uh this jacket art I hope
you guys have already witnessed it by
looking at your streaming services
because that's pretty much the only
place where this art is being used also
I changed my Twitter profile picture of
this now um but yeah I asked someone
because I wanted an art style that's
really pretty and like bright and like
M girl girly too like some some nice
glowy aesthetic you know so usually has
that so I thought perfect and Sone came
in clutch because it was kind of last
minute too me remembering because nobody
reminded me that I needed a jacket as
well I
forgot I was so busy with the 3D music
video and the 3D live and so I was like
soone I'm so sorry this is so late so
last minute book can you
[Music]
please and and the thing was the problem
was also that
like I kind of had to wait until the 3D
model was finished more or
less
because it would have to be the same
outfit so
yeah it had to all be kind of
like balanced you know the the timing
the timing was difficult for
everything
yeah um okay you know what
actually okay let's go for the uh the
logo so the thing is with the logo I I I
usually always um with Spirit
snare uh I I I think I push him
to make things that he can do but he
doesn't immediately go to on his own
like I give him quite a bit of
um instructions I guess like first I
give a theme and he comes up with
something and it looks great too but I'm
like n it's not quite it and then this
time especially I gave so much like yeah
you like it okay I gave so many like
fixes like ah maybe more like this maybe
more like this because first of all we
were again in the huge time
pressure again and second of all um I
don't know I forgot what I was going to
say um but Spirits I hope you don't mind
I was going to like show off this was
like the first draft which I like too
but it just I I I wasn't
quite happy with it yet I just I felt
like it needed to be different uh the
the
like composition of it wasn't quite
there yet and also we did a funny thing
as you have maybe noticed I was like Hey
spirit I need a logo for my 3D live and
actually I also need a logo for the the
song jacket but for the 3D live I don't
know maybe we could do this bamboozle
where recently I see other members
having um a title like a weird name for
their live
concerts so I thought maybe this is a
trend now maybe I need one too because
calling it like simply takas fourth
anniversary Frey life
again boring maybe actually like didn't
we do that before like how are we going
to you know uh but no I think I mean
last time we called it end of the year
live because it wasn't anything anymore
close to anniversary or
birthday but yeah if we did it like that
we would repeat it all the time so I did
like the idea of having like a title for
it and then I needed a logo for my song
too and I thought you know
Mirage wouldn't be so bad as a title for
the 3D Live either don't you
think yeah and
uh I thought it would be a funny
bamboozle once you guys figure out that
that's the song title I don't know how
early you guys realized that but uh was
it that nice bamboozle it's a nice word
right yeah yeah
yeah yeah I basically tricked Spirit
snare into making One logo for me two
logos for the price of one I don't know
is it is it the price of one Spirits
thereare I actually don't know if it is
um but yeah maybe low key in the back of
my mind maybe it was also me trying to
save money could be but who knows really
what's going on in takanasi Kiana's
mind yeah anyway so from that we we did
like a million revisions honestly and
but uh it was so good um cuz Spirits was
really fast with um coming up with fixes
and and uh sending it to me and then I
came up we fixed it and yeah we we we
collaborated on this I would would say
uh and then basically then we made even
more adjustments from the base logo to
fit the darkness of the 3D thumbnail or
the
brightness uh of the song jacket so I
don't know if you've noticed but the
coloring and the Darkness and brightness
is a little bit difficult uh different
um from this it's like a little bit more
bright and
orangey yellows but then this one is
more like purplish that's you know the
vibe I get purple pink and darker more
contrast so that it would stand out more
um when placed in the places where I
needed it because yeah so like I was
making this funna oh yeah right I should
also
mentioned
[Music]
um speaking of saving money it was not
so much for saving money but also
because time
pressure um like again me kind of
realizing
ooh um I'm I'm a little bit lacking the
time for asking for like one of those
illustrations that usually girls go for
like special illustrations that they
commission for their thumbnail for their
3D
Live um but yeah to be honest I spent so
much money already on like
choreographies and instrumentals cuz we
need to commission instrumentals for
every freaking song We perform unless
there's existing ones but usually like
the whole set list is like commissioned
instrumentals and then I pay for I pay
for so many things you know the only
thing I'm seemingly not paying for is
the like uh the usage of the studio but
thinking of all those things I was like
I don't know I'm out of time maybe maybe
because I already had such a good
experience so far with working with
chagy wouldn't it be fun to do a 3D
thumbnail honestly what the hell why not
I think it's cute um
so uh I came up with a oh wait I
actually have I think
the
sket don't
I but
maybe let me try to find
it but here you can see
uh actually originally I had the
brighter logo on here and it looked fine
on top of the Silhouettes but when it
was uh on the bottom left corner where
it had to go in the end cuz otherwise it
was overlapping the girls too
much then it was like not looking so
good anymore and yeah it had to be made
darker wait I think I found it somewhere
here but is this even
[Music]
1 2 3 4 5 6 7
8 I feel like I feel like I forgot
someone in the sketch but let me show
you my
[Music]
idea yeah I don't know I don't even know
who's who except for the ones that typed
there I I wrote I drew this on my phone
with the phone pen really quickly um to
give taking an idea of what I wanted I
mean this is pretty [\h__\h] accurate is
it
[Laughter]
not right 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 1 2 3 4 5 6
7 8
9 I feel like there's someone
missing uh no ena's on the floor
originally she was on the floor and like
chy also modeled her to be on the floor
um yeah no wa I right cuz I don't know
why I forgot about her
there it was like oh
[Music]
oopsie and then yeah we made a few
revisions on that too because I wanted
the spacing and the the composition and
the Heights and everything to be right
um so I feel like I'm pretty good at
directing these things and getting the
result that is best we saw my poor baby
speaking of forgetting things I I would
like to publicly State and defend and
apologize
um you guys saw the introduction videos
the red carpet
[Music]
videos so I'll be honest with you um
it's not really that we forgot her it's
also not that she missed her deadline or
anything it's
um en know was quite a last minute
addition to this live
actually and by the time that we added
her in these introduction videos were
already in
production
and yeah um Pono was handling all the
like getting the voices contacting the
managers and getting the The Voice lines
and everything um and then it was kind
of overlooked and now we actually also
need one from Ena and I legitimately did
not realize this until the very cuz I
thought I had everything ready I thought
I had everything ready and then yeah now
the question is do we want to make one
in hindsight we could we could um so I a
saying happy birthday narissa said it on
purpose apparently I think AI sire
didn't say it on purpose but that's fine
I thought it was
funny m
yeah yeah yeah so you know it's not
perfect but
um I think the introduction videos were
still super cute I had this like
absolute genius
stroke uh
sometime like maybe 3 weeks four weeks I
don't know I don't know how when it was
before the live I was like M
so what kind of opening would I should
there be an opening I like to have an
opening what is that not how you say it
but um yeah I think it's genius isn't
that genius so I asked uh I asked I
asked to make a video or several videos
where
um we are at like
a red carpet like Grammy's Oscars event
whatsoever any kind of red carpet event
maybe some mingling in the background
and a hand reaching in to the screen to
interview the
celebrity and just asking a few
questions you know and I gave the
questions uh you know just typical
questions like uh how you feeling oh you
know blah blah blah message to the
viewers and so on so
yeah I I was so happy that you know I
could do this it was really cute really
really Charming honestly I kind of want
to do it for all of my lives now because
like don't think I can think of a better
introduction video than that it's
perfect it's such a cute little warm up
yeah you got some warm fuzzies a that's
cute
yeah so this cute idea right I know I
know I know very unique I know nobody
did that before nobody did an
introduction like that before so I'm
proud of my original ideas my my my
light bulb moments in my head but yeah
yeah yeah so basically um I made like
the concept and the composition for this
and then you know then I was like with
discussing with Spirits there where the
hell do I put the logo when the
Silhouettes are revealed and then we
ended up putting it on my back but then
it was like it didn't quite stand out so
well yet and you know we made a lot of
adjustments blah blah blah and you know
how it turned out I think it turned out
pretty cute yeah thank you so much chy
for helping me with the 3D poses they
the poses are so cute do you guys want
to see an old version where ena's on the
floor let's see where is Ena on the
floor where is she still on the
floor a there okay but when she's on the
floor Nissa wasn't there yet okay please
forgive
me we fixed that right
after is this the is this it oh my God
so big look at them some of them had
different expressions and
stuff and then oh here she is here she
is Ena off the floor what is your
wisdom
cute but like stuff like this I was like
H yeah this is fun but the the heights
are so you know all over the place I
need to make adjustments so I can fit
this properly onto the
thumbnail yeah floor review you like
that
too yeah yeah so let's see what should
we talk about next H how about let's
talk about
the the design of the Freddie outfit so
I leave it to the artist to uh like show
maybe everything if you want to I have
no problem with that Mimi um I'm just
going to show the one that ended up
being it because this is so funny I
originally was going to draw it
myself and I just was like uninspired
and asked Mooney because she she seems
to really like sending me all kinds of
Inspirations when it comes to the music
videos you know and so I was like money
do you have any
idea like for this song What kind of out
fit would look cute like kind of a
concept maybe anything from existing
K-pop music videos anything that you
know could inspire me for me drawing the
outfit and then turning it into 3D and I
I kid you not I feel like within 3 hours
she was like oh okay hold on wait a
minute she said that immediately and
then oh olly raid thank you olly raid
welcome welcome welcome welcome welcome
welcome hello hello hello hello hello
thank you so much OE has been so
addicted to the card game
huh hello
welcome okay okay okay so um yeah moly
was like okay yeah sure give me a minute
and then I kid you not like 3 hours
later or so
Mimi sent like Moy through Mimi Mimi
through Mooney sent me Mimi is the
artist of asteroid uh music they sent me
like five different
designs sketched
out yeah like I was like what that's not
what I expected what what's going on I
just I was just imagining M to send me
some like screenshots from videos from
other K-pop
videos uh like music videos as
inspiration so that I could draw
something but then they just did the
whole work for me and I was like you
know what this is not not
unappreciated I I appreciate
this you took some work off of me thank
you and then one of the ones that I
picked which didn't seem to be like
their main pick but I was like H I have
a vision
was this
[Music]
one yes you can tell it's the outfit
mainly is yeah like this
uh yeah we added some sparkles to the
turquoise pants parts and I changed the
hair so I said I want a ponytail please
um and the the feathers also like you
know they kind of stayed feathers but
they got a little like a little sparkly
diamond on top of it or
so but yeah reasons why I chose this is
first of all the vision worked well for
me and um also because of physics let me
tell you I think the Fred modeler was
very grateful for
that because uh the other outfits that
were suggested were very they had a lot
of very flowy elements in them and then
we would have had issues probably with
physics and collision and this is all
skin tight so it's easier to model that
and yeah easier and
faster so this turned into the
3D yeah yeah 3D model is written in the
credits in the uh music video check it
out um but yeah this also was a bit
difficult because
um somewhere in this like reference
sheet uh they wrote or or mon told me
separately I'm not sure they told me
that what kind of like fabric effect
they would
see fitting for this what word did they
use I forgot but
um the thing is we tried to make that
work and
I uh i n no no no it ended up being
shiny lever uh for black but but then
for the white one it was supposed to be
like let me see let me
[Music]
see I have I sent like pictures to the
modeler
[Music]
before holographic not Qui but
yeah wait there was this one picture
there it
is I guess maybe that is holographic
shut
up but where did it go
now so something like this but it just
didn't work out it just didn't work out
but that also took a lot of time and
then in the end I was just like whatever
let's just make get white uh without
this
effect and so yeah I was so stressed out
about this the model literally got more
or less
[Music]
finished 6 days before the music video
release
maybe I was so stressed out
oh yeah no that's not plenty of time but
[Music]
yeah the thing is we originally started
with a different 3D modeler and I will
say seon I think you could have done it
too
like but then seon was like I don't
think I can do it and I'm like I think
you can but okay then I got to look for
someone else and that's just like
everything was um scary for me I I
didn't I didn't want this music video to
come out later than it should so I was a
bit
terrified kind of I was so worried too I
kept on checking with kind ofu like do
you think we're fine do you think we're
okay do you think this is going to be
fine but the one thing that was really
good this time is that
so I timed the music video and song
release with the uh fry life for
promotion sake but
also
because I thought if I ask nicely
whatever motion I record in the cover
Studio maybe they can just give me that
motion because I can record the motion
at home with my accents but I would be
alone I would not be really able to
record my back dancers's
motion um
and that would be sad so it would be
perfect if I could have the motion
capture from the data from the studio
and then put it into the music video
because the freedy live needed you know
like all kinds of like editing and so on
so there was some buffer time between
the recording of it and then the release
of
it and so with been like after the
recording we got the motion data and we
sent it to kanu and he was like able to
already look into it and
then while kanu was working on the music
video The Studio was finishing up the 3D
life and then we timed it to be at the
same time yeah
so yeah it's from the same
recording yeah and this way like uh see
let's even put aside the back dancers
that came with this if I would have done
it alone I would have done it with my
accents here uh at home and we did that
with Chimera but the
data was just so messy and kanuru had to
like fix a lot of like jankiness and I
think chy also has experience with
fixing my motion data that I take at
home with my exent suit is for some
reason it's just so janky and
wobbly uh it's just so annoying and
fixing that takes a lot of time
too
um
so I was just hoping to be able to use
the studio data and thankfully we were
able to do that yeah it was it was kind
of funny though there was like this
misunderstanding we had I uh they were
like yeah yeah sure we can give you the
motion capture data okay um but it will
take from the recording day uh till you
receive it it will probably take a month
and I'm
like what
why
why that'll be too
[Music]
late and then I kept on like um trying
to like dig deeper and be like why why
can we not maybe just have the kiata
motion first I don't know what what the
problem is and then eventually
misunderstanding was cleared up the one
month would have been if and they
assumed that they that I was asking them
to do that if they would have had to fix
and like like you know like just edit
and work on the motion capture data in
case there's any jankiness and
wobbliness and glitchiness and whatever
uh but all I wanted was the raw motion
capture data and that they were able to
give me like pretty much right away and
I was like yeah that's that's really all
I needed thank
you but first I was just kind of
panicking because uh that
misunderstanding wasn't wasn't cleared
up for a while and so I discussed with
Kan of how are we going to do this can
we put a placeholder Motion in there and
then replace it like one day before the
music video releases
maybe yeah so that was another thing I
was stressed out about until the
misunderstanding was was cleared up uh
but all is good and it was so helpful I
think I don't know what kind of U has
been thinking but I'm sure he would say
that this was so much easier to work
with compared to my Chimera motion data
that I took at
home yeah so hopefully I can repeat this
in the future but then I wonder what do
I have my suit for well it's for home
usage I'm going to take some YouTube
shorts and stuff with that then it will
still be worth it no
worries yeah it's a good learning
experience
yeah and the good thing is um because
this is not so janky I can upload like
full Dance
videos from Mirage I want to put up like
a dance version a dance cut with only
dancing and and like a practice video
and stuff like that
y yeah yeah yeah for little like 3D
streams here and there like the Fever
Night 3D stream that's when you know it
comes in handy of course definitely so
can you still use a Frey outfit F
Mirage I can for like a special stream
if I want to but I don't know I I I feel
like it it looks good in the music video
but I'm not so sure if I like how it
looks in my like V tubing app um maybe
if I make some if if I have some more
improvements made on it
um yeah I'll think about it because I do
think it would be sad if I don't use it
a single time you know just one little
reveal would be
fun um but
yeah right now I'm not 100% happy with
it uh when the way I look at it in the
3D um like V tubing
app I I don't know but yeah we'll see
we'll
see um so yeah thank you so much like I
don't even I didn't even ask for that
but they sent me these designs and it
really helped me U make the process
faster and it was so much uh better
cleaner looking that whatever I would
have drawn probably uh and I didn't even
have a uh I I think we were doing this
while I was in Japan so I didn't even
have a drawing tablet so I don't know
how I was thinking that I was going to
do that
no maybe I was thinking I was going to
do it once I'm back in Austria I don't
know but uh it was a big help thank you
thank you thank
you ah yeah and thank you for you know
both the modelers who tried their hands
on it um you know especially like you
know after there was so little time left
um we still tried to make it work thank
you thank you thank
you no no no no
I want
to talk about the
live con should I and one more thing uh
maybe a little bit about the music video
um first of
all let me put up the
thumbnail here this is the thumbnail the
thumbnail it's also funny uh I watched
like a draft of the music
video uh kodo always sends me the drafts
when it's pretty much almost finished
but until that time I'm like panicking
like is he is he cooking is he cooking
and then it always turns out he is
cooking uh so I watched the MV for the
first time actually um the a draft of it
a pretty Advanced draft of it uh
together with the PTSD group cuz I
watched it right after the collab cuz
that's when I got it and I was like
girls do you want to watch it with me so
my first reaction was with them
together but then uh you know I still
had some adjustments made uh from then
on but there was this one moment where
Wawa picks up this masks from this mask
from the ground and it just looks so
nice I was just like this is so
aesthetic like oh my God I want this to
be the thumbnail like this strip me
immediately as thumbnail
material um but then I then I was like
well
H with the
logo let me show
you let me show you let me show you let
me show
you where is
it
um I basically had him like remake this
scene for me I think or he just
repositioned me or so but uh yeah
basically first you know if you watch
the music video I'm on the right side
and then the logo I don't want to put it
at the top or the bottom because it just
didn't look so striking it has to be in
the middle but then it was overlapping
with the hand basically when I was just
taking a screenshot from the music video
and then when the E overlaps with the
hand it just doesn't look good you know
what I mean can you can you imagine
[Music]
I'll find it I'll find it I'll find
it ah
here
[Music]
sh here this is literally a screenshot
from from the draft but originally it
was like this and I was
[Music]
like it's so close to
Perfection so
close
no but I didn't want to put the logo up
or down and I didn't want to make it
smaller because then it's too small and
N so then I asked can you please like
give me either me on the opposite side
or me holding the mask with the opposite
hand or I don't know any anything right
better right you
see takas composition
[Music]
genius yeah I mean I feel
like this closeness is almost better but
it's
fine the fingernails yeah what what
happened with the
fingernails they used to be black oh no
I've been
unied
unified what happened oh well
I think though I think I noticed in the
music video even with uh even in the
music video I think the nails became
this light color again but one nail the
fump I think is
black I think maybe accidentally some
Laya was turned off or so oh it was just
a face yeah oh well it's okay small
things small
things so so so so okay and then what
else yeah for the music video like
originally K was still including my
default outfit like the black version of
it I was like no please get rid of it
this has to be fully the new outfit
that's the point of it and and I just
think um my default outfit does not
match the vibe and I'm I'm I don't want
to see it because it's been too repeated
I don't want to see it anymore in my
music videos we already had it in do you
and then we had it in Kima and even for
Kima I was like kind of
like I don't want to repeat it the whole
time yeah cuz then also it reminds you
of do you like and and I just don't want
the connection to always be there like
uh few people will like maybe
subconsciously think oh spiritual uh
successor or whatever but no I wanted
this to have this special Vibe with a
new outfit new 3D outfit makes it
special right yeah and needed to show it
off
but
uh what was I going to
say I forgot oh yeah don't get it
twisted this fretty outfit is not me
getting like a 1 million wish whatsoever
no uh I just got permission to just like
for other like models like the fever
night model or even back in the day the
low poly models this is the same
treatment I can make some kind of like
model but only use it for special um
[Music]
things like a music
video but because it's my um because
it's my
uh what I forgot was I what was I going
to say again yeah because it's my kind
of creation so to say uh and not in the
whole life app cuz it wasn't created by
them I wouldn't be able to use it in
their official studio and so on unless
it's like imported and they normally
are not like going to do that so you
know I can use it at home maybe in my
you know uh home setup uh for a special
stream and in the music video but like
not in like official um situations like
a concert for example yeah but that's
fine I'm just glad that I can have it at
like a different vibe in my music videos
because I really focus on 3D music
videos as you know to show off my
choreographies
and with the lack of amount of 3D
outfits I just like face a wall that
stumps my
creativity
and just like yeah what what I want to
create it's just not possible with this
lack of Freedom so yeah this is what
came out of that as yeah it's basically
[\h__\h] it I'll do it myself exactly
let's just make something on our own out
of my pocket uh let's make a a new Frey
outfit that literally just serve this
one purpose just this one
purpose but I think it's worth it
because that really elevated the look
from the music
video and you know it all came together
it all came together
so okay and then let's talk about the
Freddy life so I wanted to discuss a
little
bit
the set list first of
all I have I think um told you guys
before so times that this life was kind
of cursed uh but I need
to emphasize this it was really cursed
uh speaking of cursed do I have like a
cursor what what did I name this takas
cursor well okay
um let's just use
this I okay so out of the set list
many things have changed
originally I had like a a song in here
that was going to be the highlight of
the show because it was going to be with
an IRL flesh in In the Flesh guest like
maybe you've seen in some other uh
lives um from the Japanese members
especially um people have been like
doing collaborations of like people
green screened into it more or less and
I was planning that and it was
originally in this plan and it was also
going to take up a lot of time of the
recording schedule because setting up
everything would take so much time and
then I would have been able to do less
songs so in the in the end maybe it's
fine this way but um yeah with that plan
uh it kind of threw everything all over
through the like I don't know washing
machine uh when I had to come up with
some solution and that's not the only
thing that changed let me tell you here
magia not the original lineup actually
this magia lineup uh changed like three
times even though it's so perfect Now
isn't
it and uh beat eater also this lineup
changed a lot like like I uh it was not
supposed to be a duet like Ida was there
I think
U maybe originally but uh I originally I
wanted it to be free people and I kept
on having to replace the third person
because I kept on getting kind of like
cancellations and so
on um yeah and then some songs were like
changed also and and because the songs
were changed I had to change the member
or sometimes because the members were
changed I had to change the song and so
on just because it doesn't it just
didn't feel right
anymore um but you
know now the theme
Here you you may have noticed that in
the second half the vibe really changed
especially with this like triple triple
combo here I wanted the first half to be
like because okay generally I would have
liked the whole set list would be like
mostly English songs but it's really
difficult to find English songs that I
can use
on uh on a live uh that is
archived
so uh K comes in clutch I Ed a lot of K
songs but I can't fill the whole set
list with it so I thought okay let's
make it like half half let's focus on
English songs mostly um with h to just
being a nice opening and a nice like
throwback to to um you know how far
we've come from the fir like our first
original song to the most recent one um
and just to Hype it up and I thought
with a remix I can just you know give it
a fresh Vibe
[Music]
too mhm and then yeah these ones are
supposed to be like the English
Representatives because I don't want to
fill everything with Japanese songs I
love Japanese songs but I'm just
thinking like you know mostly English
audience and English members and you
know I I want I want people to
understand what I'm singing about even
if you don't understand Japanese so um
it's just difficult when it's
archived yeah yeah yeah so this
nah and then like for example the iris
combo ah this is really rare I think
this is the first time we sang together
as just us two and the first time maybe
just like for us to be on stage as a
anything besides a full member Holo Ian
performance you know very very very new
and
rare but I had a lot of fun with Iris uh
practicing together performing together
and uh she's so
funny yeah we had a good time together
thank you Iris so much for accepting
yeah yeah yeah generally like uh yeah as
I said like ena's song that was kind of
a I I'm saying it's kind of it was the
last minute
uh injection but
originally
I you won't believe this but originally
ironically I was planning again
something completely different this was
like changed a million times and
originally I wanted to do like all those
little myth song covers collaborations
that I did including I but also the
other ones like Iota and so on um but it
wouldn't have worked out because I
am I wouldn't have been able to do all
of them and then I thought well then
there's no
point and then I threw that away to that
plan and made a new plan um but when I
needed like you know one more song in
there I was like like
Ena cuz you know she was already in
Japan and I thought well you know it's
always fun to do stuff with Ena so I was
like
Ena Ena do you want to join my really
live again um maybe um this time we do e
because everybody [\h__\h] loves
e
yeah which you know was hype you guys
were really happy to see that now we
finally done it so people are happy and
satisfied yippee bloing cons was also
like um the reason I chose this is
because it it it for me to me it fit the
vibe perfectly here um I was like I
think I already had the sticks Alex and
magia set in my mind and I was thinking
about what other song has this like
Godly like Palace kind of vibe you know
you know what I mean like the
instrumentals and
the you know what I mean I was just
thinking what other song kind of fits
into that Vibe and
atmosphere H and then I
remembered blooming
cuns people always wanted me to sing
that and it kind of fits so perfectly in
there and people will be surprised
because I'm singing German yeah but uh
blo C is really difficult uh for me to
like sing in the first place because
originally it is not sung by a German
speaking person but the lyrics are all
German and when you listen to it as a
German speaking
person it it doesn't flow so well when
you try to sing it in like a proper
pronunciation certain words will not fit
the Rhythm
anymore and so I was struggling a lot
with that and I was trying to fix those
things without changing the lyrics
because I wasn't allowed to change the
lyrics uh and I wasn't allowed to change
the Melodies I was like given a little
bit of a leeway to adjust the rhythm of
the words because otherwise it just
wouldn't work and I'm not going to
purposefully sing it with a wrong
pronunciation because then what's the
point of me singing it as a German
speaking person so yeah that took a lot
of
adjustments yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah so I hope you guys
like
that and I want to talk a little bit
about uh my thoughts behind the lyrics
split because I did of course I always
do the lyrics splits for these things
um I don't know if everybody does it but
I just want to take care of that because
I have a vision in my head as you know
and especially with the these two songs
I had quite some fun I didn't go with
the original lyric split from the song
because for example magas um performed
by two people H three people I mean
three people so with fre people
performing it in my life too you know I
could probably just go with the original
lyrics split and make it easy for me but
no no no no no because then it would
have been very
unbalanced uh the original lyrics split
isn't too balanced and it's it's kind of
confusing too
so let me oh let me show you kind of
like an Insight of what I was
doing here this is Japanese but uh this
is basically the part that goes it
[Music]
you know that's that part and then the
the chorus now here um I I I tried to
create a pattern for example so the
first lines are being sung by me and
waya and then waya sings this little
solo then the next part is sung by me
and MAA and then Mauna SES his little
solo and then it's Mauna with waya and
then I need some lines too so I added
here my solos here and then we all sing
together and it sounds really strong
yeah but like I tried to create a lot of
like harmonizing strong moments here
that just feel really good and uh pick
like fitting lines for the
solos depending on you know where I need
the
impact yeah yeah and Symmetry and
balance and like you know a pattern just
always trying to create a nice pattern
and then they were perfectly free long
[\h__\h]
lines where I thought this should be a
solo first of all because it's going to
difficult going to be maybe difficult to
time it well when we're all seeing it at
the same time but also it's going to
really show off the vocal prowess of
these members so I think that really
made a big impact and gave everybody a a
big shine moment right like I was blown
away by Muna and waya singing that that
note holding that note and so strongly
because they have such strong voices
that are so so powerful I love them so
much yeah and they were three of these
three of these are so perfect the first
one was MAA second one was waya and last
one was me yeah chef's kiss right I put
a lot of thought into these things and
then uh sticks Helix was even more
complicated
actually so I have a few like like
excerpts from the lyrics split let's
start with this one this is the chorus I
don't know if you guys noticed but so
there were two japanesee speaking
members right and two well Indonesian
but English speaking let's see them as
English speaking members
um when I looked at the song and thought
about how to split this I realized half
of the song is in English more or less
half of the song is in
English so I thought
I'm just going to split this into the
Japanese members see are singing the
Japanese lines and me and wisu sting the
English lines and it actually like
there's a it creates a good pattern too
because it is kind of organized like
that um and then that gives us a lot of
like harmonizing moments with auki
Senpai and me and wiu Senpai it flows
really nicely and it just kind of works
perfectly
and yeah uh then because I wanted to
hear more of these beautiful beautiful
harmonies let's look at this for example
uh basically like all the like this is
the this is the a medal the uh beginning
of the song It went like
[Music]
I thought it was really nice if somebody
would join in at the K the shimo at the
last line of that basically and so I
always I first I give one Japanese
member the main part and then they join
in and sing together and then basically
that was repeated the other way around
where aaki sampai would sing this part
and then Senpai would join in and they
would sing together and then there was
some English so I come back in and it
just all it just flows so nicely doesn't
it here's another example like uh Wu
singing English as by singing Japanese
Wawa singing English s by singing the
Japanese while was singing English and
then this throughout the whole song
there's only one line at this very end
where we all sing
together why well I don't know it just
kind of worked out this way and also at
the end I felt like we need one more
moment where we sing together and it has
this last like uh like Goosebumps
moment because when all the voices
finally come together in the end it's
going to feel so overwhelming and Peak
and strong
yeah yeah yeah so I really want you to
appreciate uh this kind of like you know
thought process so I hope you maybe if
you want to watch the live again you can
think about that about the lyrics split
that waa has put a lot of thought
[Music]
into actually for get J also I um I
didn't use the original lyric split I
think uh I split it so that Nissa was
singing the English parts and I was
singing the Japanese Parts mostly I
don't know if you noticed that
too um but now I kind of want
to take a look at the fry live while
also maybe pointing out some things
about
choreographies
so let's get into this where did I put
it
um I
here we're not going to watch the whole
thing I'm going to like skip skip skiy
scoop um
I'm
hungry do you hear
this this is me this is wa wa we start
out with a with a default outfit and I
thought in the remix there's a perfect
moment to switch into the main outfit
for the
concert which one it that
SK but yeah we're going to get this song
that that was not like I yeah some of
the coral was adjusted to the remix
which was
[Music]
cool I really love that part so
much but yes um here oh this is
perfect wait do that again my song even
though you know similar vibe to my
original songs so please
enjoy nice time nice time nice time was
so rough man here the stage let's talk
about the stage a little bit um I was
just trying to um match the the songs
Vibe at least the second half songs Vibe
with the stage so it's supposed to look
kind of like a European maybe a goddess
Temple I don't know Palace Temple all
these kind of Vibes combined with like
golden edges and these big big pillars
with the curtains I I asked for all of
that and the um the Mamoa Mamu what's m
Marble Marble Floor and all that so I
think that actually turned out wonderful
yeah yeah very shiny very pretty very
clean very nice Aesthetics I think
nice top bro can we talk
about let's
see here
[Music]
comes you know how rough this move was
for me I'm so old man getting up from
there
[Laughter]
in reality I was like [\h__\h]
me how many times have I repeated that
when I was practicing this Coro I was
dying and my my knees were actually
getting like um like how to say like
they were not getting bloody but they
were definitely like scratched up and
[\h__\h] from like getting on the floor so
many [\h__\h]
[Music]
times every time I went down there I was
dreading what's about to come in my mind
I was like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] it's coming ah look
elegant look sexy in reality I was
like can't my legs are TI and because of
especially this one move was killing my
legs so
much need to know BR music with the
grunts yeah you need it you need it
Bruce yeah uh but like cuz I was
practicing the song so much um to get
like to not look like I was dying but
looked like it was
easy um but because of all that practice
I got such sore muscles from the my what
do you call the the not the fighs the
the the bottom leg
behind the back part of the bottom legs
um what's it called
again I'm so hungry what the
[\h__\h] CES yeah my Cales my cops were
dying yeah I need to build muscles it's
so crazy like this was so
rough but it was fun though once I
finally figured things
out thank God this song was only 2
minutes
[Music]
long oh here also there were a lot of
like going down like this slowly and
then turning slowly and I don't know why
I struggled so much with balancing uh in
this move I fell over so many
times but the chorus was always
fun uh but yeah practicing the song so
many times gave me so many muscle sores
and I had to get so many massages and
[Music]
yeah don't be po
never thought I be nice time yeah okay
and then here uh song with Iris was fun
here it starts with just me bamboozle
it's not just me
surprise this is a pretty old K song but
I really like it I thought this might be
really good for a
doet i
yeah I really like this song and she
sings it so pretty what the
[Music]
hell her voice is so
good yeah and the Coro I think is pretty
fun it's relatively simple but uh it's a
the chorus is kind of bouncy and then
the parts besides the ches are supposed
to be a little bit more sensual
[Music]
and slow and relaxed yeah her voice is
so clear
[Music]
yeah
this originally we were standing much
closer but then uh on the recording day
we realized oh her whole skirt goes in
my face and her hair goes in my face so
we had to be more distanced but
originally we were practicing this with
me being like one full step closer to
[Laughter]
her which I always felt so embarrassed
like cuz I'm looking at her as I'm not I
mean I'm not but like I'm being like I'm
so close my head is so close to her her
butt you know she's just looking into
the void when she's like facing away
from me but I'm facing her so I was
always feeling so embarrassed and
flustered like oh oh
no but the whole sniffer sniffer thing
was obviously a joke don't worry
oh we had to stay so separate because of
all the all the fluffiness of our
outfits oh
man but yeah look at the look at the
[Music]
course when I fall fall baby tell me
cute I want to tell you here motion
capture kind of disappointing because in
real life this was making a perfect
heart shape can you imagine let me let
me tell you um how did we do
it that doesn't really look like a hard
does it does
it I don't know that does what we were
doing is um put like a put two of your
hands up and make a thumbs down and then
twist them a little bit more towards
like a neutral stance not quite thumbs
down more like yeah and then meet the
thumbs in the middle make your thumbs
touch and then the rest of your hand is
a fist right make those uh at least the
the pointy finger make that touch too
and there you go you have a heart that
I've never seen before genius
choreographer sadly our hands don't
perfectly touch here and uh the fists
often don't form perfectly so it doesn't
really look like what we were trying to
do but we were making hearts
[Music]
here here
too I think for Iris it looked a little
bit better than for
me
yeah that
move I like that move but it's difficult
to get
the timing right with me and Iris my
imagination brings me right to
you
IAB me why
why yeah okay let's skip that uh fun MC
I hope you like my MC's I'm actually I
think I'm I I I think my MC's are really
good I always came up with the topics
like last minute but
uh I like to do a little bit more than
just like saying hi and by so I like to
come up with some topics beforehand and
New York was um kind of close to this
recording when we recorded it like a
month ago already a month ago um so it
was just still fresh in our mind and I
thought why not talk about you know New
York and stuff a little
bit Yeah Yeah MC are funny right yeah I
think so too we had fun it was
funny and then oh oh geta geta geta geta
is a song I was like hoping to do for a
long time as a song cover even but I
don't know never found like the time or
you know I would have loved to be
invited to someone's cover too but I
don't know it just never came together
but finally because it's also a k
song and there's a lot of English in it
that's why I included it in the set list
and I just wanted to do a song with
narissa and yeah there's no particular
reason why this song with narissa I I
just had this song in my mind and I
wanted to do something with
myiss so yeah I was singing it in a Dela
soon I was hoping that it clicks with
you guys afterwards you realize oh I now
I know why she had gcha in her head now
I
know um but yeah the the Coro is uh
it was quite intense quite difficult and
a lot of
like hips and
[Music]
[Applause]
stuff yeah that move there's just so
many H her voice I had so many like
vocal powerhouses in my my
life the rap was so difficult though
where is
it oh here it goes I think yeah yeah I
did the whole rap it's so
difficult here we go here we go here we
go
ready here we go here we go here we go
[Music]
[Applause]
that was so
difficult the rap is so long there's no
time to
breathe like tongue twisters
Rap God fire no I'm
not I need to I need to find like a
good iconic voice for
rapping yeah I had to practice that a
lot to find where I could find some room
to
breathe anyway cute NIS W she's so tall
though and they don't have the idol
outfit which is kind of sad I wish they
did um I'm advocating for them to get
the freaking Idol outfit so that we can
match I hope one day they get
them yeah
man they would look so good in them okay
let's talk about this one be eater beat
eater man I love be eer okay now I'm
going to f you back even more uh
remember um waya 3D live where I was
like in the MC and I said ah waya I love
your song ches so
much yeah um that was in in the back of
my mind I already knew my set list so I
was like
hinting
that beat eater I got the idea uh
basically from waya cuz I love her song
cover so much and I I wouldn't even know
the song if it wasn't for his song cover
I just love it so much I listen to it a
lot that was a tease yeah I was trying
to say like I'm going to copy paste what
waya
does the songs she
chooses yeah cuz she has good
taste
mhm yeah it's is just it's that's it's
so [\h__\h] good their cover is so
good but yeah uh turns out Ida also did
a cover of the song before and I didn't
notice until like we were already like
practicing the dance and I was like oh
sorry I I guess I kind of made you do
the same song again but she had no
problem with it and I guess maybe it
makes it easier for her cuz then she's
already very um familiar with it um but
the dance was so
difficult you practiced so much on this
one
[Music]
like using the right leg in a lot of
these moves somehow was very confusing
[Music]
like I look back at this and I just
remember remember the
suffering a this move I got that wrong
so many times
too you don't even
understand I this one ah we talked about
it in the MC
[Music]
but you don't even you don't even
know yeah but I tried to dance
big and energetically hopefully it
worked I was already so tired this one
this one confused me so much too because
after each
like we turn around and face the
opposite way so that turning around got
me so confused about like what what
moves was I supposed to do now the
turning around got me like kicked me out
of the Rhythm that I was in H
and
turn and
turn you guys don't even can't even tell
so much because it was all close-ups but
yeah and then I turn
again not really losing sense of
direction but just
focusing was not possible anymore or
Focus the more I would focus the more I
would
up
yeah I need to give you guys a solo like
wa cam of
this so you can see my dance that I
sweated so much
for you know how so cute it was so fun
dancing with
her
[Applause]
y I like this move throwing up those
hands and one after
another and here the confusing thing
again but this time we don't turn
around I wish it was always like that I
wouldn't have been so confused
[Music]
yeah now I think this was really fun and
came together nicely too you know I was
really unexpected for you guys huh yeah
but I don't know she really likes
dancing and I needed someone who can
keep up with a dance number you know I
was planning for this song to be very
dance intense and Ida was totally up for
it yeah so I hope we can dance together
again sometime
oh you you she she did English so well
in the MC she was Japanese members are
always so worried about it they always
like have no confidence but youa you can
really have some more confidence she
really understood what I was saying and
uh she even was able to reply to a lot
of it so have confidence right Mama
Mia I loved your guys' reaction when I
came up actually the ENA announcement
picture was already a spoiler I was
surprised you guys didn't all go like oh
isn't that hand movement the pose from
the
e music video the hand
movement I thought you guys would
realize but people were so excited when
they saw Ena and me do
[Music]
this Coro was really simple and fun and
dorky
uh but Ena was so sleepy on this
day so we had to redo it so many
times oh
cute cute yeah a lot of references to
the music
video If you think
back on what was there maybe you can
watch it and
see a there we go this is the E move
don't you recognize
[Music]
it so happy
went the wrong way
cute she's so small when she's in the
idle outfit even though even this outfit
has
heels but we wear the same heels
so you see how the height difference
really
is I like this part but this
part I had to
I had to be so careful with like leaning
back and forth
um because also our size was so
different so adjusting
that yeah that was fun and then the MC
on the
[Music]
floor you know it's very comfortable on
the floor speaking of the floor I wanted
to
mention um
usually the studio think there's like a
video of it right or like pictures and
you guys uh could see what it looks like
uh the studio has like carpet flooring
and well you know thin carpet so it's
not too bad but um it's honestly like
turn like some dance moves are difficult
on the
carpet um and then a while
ago uh I found out that we have like
flooring that can be put and fixated on
top of the carpet which is like it
visually looks like wooden floor I don't
know I don't think it's actually wood
but like some kind of
like l lolium or so
um but it's like way smoother like not
coppet it's like a smooth surface um
yeah dance floor installation is
possible but nobody yeah laminate no
nobody tells you that even my director
didn't really know about it uh seemingly
they were just hidden somewhere in the
in the studio and because it's a lot of
work to put them on the floor and then
remove them again I mean it's not a lot
of work but it takes a little bit to put
it down and then fix it with the tape
and everything nobody usually thinks of
using them
but I really I found out about them and
I really wanted to use them for this uh
recording and let me tell you that was
such a such a
blessing yeah my backup dances were also
so happy that there was proper floor
there and not carpet anymore yeah and
then I also for the first time ever I
made a realization this
time so little bit
of immersion breaking I guess but uh the
the shoes the map shoes
uh you know there's like two different
types there's like somewhat normal
shoes um and then there's like kind of
dancer
shoes where the soul is the soul is
mostly different and the dancer shoes
are kind
of they they feel more loose but also
more tight it's kind of weird to explain
but they're just made differently and
this whole time because the dancer shoes
are so hard to get into
too uh I just always was using the other
shoes but um they're so chunky and
big and I was also like they're not
really fitting my foot very well so I
was having trouble dancing with them
this time
and and then the dancers reminded me oh
there's actually actually dancer shoes
don't you know and I'm like what oh
those shoes oh they're so hard to get
into I didn't know those were dancer
shoes but then I finally used them and
also that so the combination of the
Dance Floor being used and the dancer
shoes being
used M it was so much better if I didn't
already had a million blisters on my
toes in my uh behind of the back of my
feet it was already too late kind of but
it made it better at least it didn't
make it
worse yeah so now I know another new
thing for the future I will always
always ask for this floor and I will
always put on those dance issues from
that
one yeah actual game changer so
true so yeah we did the MC on the floor
Pally she's so
small I
can't oh cute yeah and then that's where
the second half starts and that's when
you guys were really Blown Away
apparently from the set
[Music]
list it's just so
magical I love how this came out to
be English
Duo singing English
and harmonizing
beautifully
now Japanese
[Music]
lyrics and AI joining in
yeah it's so
good and here yeah it's me and wiu
singing and Japanese member
[Music]
singing It's so well organized right
M English
[Music]
go
English
yeah
[Music]
oh and then I join
in I think or was it different this time
oh no it was different cuz the pattern
was different
[Music]
nongo we have to watch this whole thing
man it's so
good yeah yeah yeah duet duet sing it
[Music]
girls English English
go yeah they're really great
[Music]
combos see you again
hey hey hey hey hey
[Music]
okay A little bit of Japanese here just
because I didn't get like one of these
big Parts yet up to this
[Music]
point
the bridge
[Music]
oh here
we Japanese
yeah
[Music]
English
Japanese
[Music]
English me pointing all this out only
makes sense if you were listening to my
lyrics split
discussion
before oh yeah that was the one line
that we all sing
together yeah and then whoa what's
happening oh [\h__\h] they're
floating
ah honestly like like dancing on this in
a circle formation was also a challenge
[Music]
but yeah this this this is
so some nice
combos
o louder louder
louder hat it
girls let's go oh the course it's hard
[Music]
thee fore
[Applause]
[Music]
oh that hit so hard way
it she's so good
oh oh
[Music]
this is so good right it needs a rewatch
[Applause]
[Music]
meow
last course let's [\h__\h] go you ready
oh it's going to come in
[Music]
strong foree
[Applause]
[Music]
and mine is not as strong as theirs but
I tried my best keeping that
[Music]
note oh so
epic so
epic and then the big surprise me
singing blooming [\h__\h] what
nobody thought she would do
this who thought of
this crazy set list oh my
God yeah but this is also
epic very simple Coro but the Simplicity
of It kind of confused me
too what so weird to hear German
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah I like this part
though I turn it's so
fun I feel like a
[Music]
ballerina sorry I'm I'm doing it really
clumsily because I have to say kind of
neglected this Coro because it was so
simple I was like whatever this is like
last my last priority I have to learn
the other more difficult coros more
so it was like I wasn't very confident
in it because I just didn't really
practice
[Music]
it but it works out it was all
right sker skipper no skiper
okay o o and now let's dance
tango wow wow turn this really simple
though the Coro this Coro went for a lot
of changes cuz I wasn't quite happy
[Music]
is the flower garden real or [\h__\h]
it I really like this views from behind
where you see the fake audience no it's
real real to
me I basically was just trying to give
this feeling that you're singing with me
in this upcoming
part
[Music]
here sing with me if you know German
legs are so funny to
[Music]
me it got me hot
you are so
[Music]
strong why do you look so
sad I don't
know the lyric are just funny to me it's
so
like kind of machine
translated wow but the song is really
nice and the melody is really nice and
the instrument instrumental is really
nice and everything the vibe is really
nice the the German is just so funny to
me yeah but as long as you guys liked it
I liked end it had I hope I hope I was
able to create some kind of atmosphere
and I hope you like this merchandise
yeah that she is advertising here
wonderfully um one comment on this
glass um so I was this was like um the
last item I came up with because I
didn't know what other kitchen item I
could do cuz I did like teacups before
and stuff but I didn't do a glass yet um
so basically I just like looked at at
that time I think it was maybe still
relatively newly released maybe was it
uh but I saw Ana's class and I was like
I want something like
this so if you look at Ana's class it
looks very similar to my glass now uh or
my glass looks similar to
hers so so much to uh I hate
her no Ana Ana's glass yeah o they're
kind of matching now the shape is the
same and the the fact that there's this
like color
gradation and like I think she also has
like a gold uh thing on top of it yeah
we're matching you
you kind of but yeah then there's Kima
which is yeah you know just Kima is fun
Kima is always a a good time and good
but the real appeal lies in Mir Mirage I
want to talk about Mirage bring me
Mirage I will point out every single
difficulty I had let's
go first of first of
all this like Coral I was basically
handed the Coro three days before the
recording I was I was taught the Coro
free day days before the recording it
was the last song I learned um and uh it
was difficult because so I already
talked about this a little bit before
but uh because of a like tight schedule
for the dancers as well um the previews
of the Coral's Coro that I got were
always like missing like one time the
Coro just consisted of like
two people and I had to imagine the rest
of the people but that was just you know
because it was all last minute and and
but that was just difficult I wasn't
sure like oh okay how is this going to
look with five people in the end and so
on and then even on the day when I
learned it um there there were like
basically the four back dancers there
and me so the choreographers this time
there was two choreographers and they
also took the role of the back dancers
but they they were trying to teach it to
me uh while also dancing the back dancer
Parts when we were practicing so I
wouldn't really like first they would
teach me the move and then we would turn
on the music and attach it to the music
but it's it was just so difficult
because they were dancing the back
dancer moves and then I would forget
what was I supposed to do and I wouldn't
have a reference to it do you know what
I
mean but then they would you know
sometimes change what they were doing
and would do my parts next to me so that
I could reference that but then we were
missing the back dancer that they were
supposed to be and then it just overall
was very complicated to learn the dance
because of that cuz we just needed one
more person basically to cover the like
the back dancers so one of the
choreographers Could Just Dance next to
me to show me how it's done but this way
it was just so complicated
so and I
barely was able to put anything into my
brain on that day I was running on Red
Bull and lack of sleep lack of food and
very stressed
and and so it was it was very very
clutch but it became so
beautiful
yay and it turn around
slowly and then everybody comes closer
this was already difficult because the
dancers uh in the back who were closest
to me they were so close to me I had to
be careful not to hit them but they have
to be close so that we get this
like Vibe of them having their hands on
[Music]
me here you have to like Tom TAMU what's
TAMU in English uh like hold it in hold
it in
and and I always forgot this so many
times I forgot the dancers were coming
over there and making this like barrier
and I'm like wait what move comes next
oh yeah right I was supposed to lean on
them but I like I like this move I like
this
one and as she then she goes down it's
so fun and then she brings it back
up look at doing that
oh she's doing
it this I always forgot that like uh I
don't think you can even tell so well
but the dancer who is like on the Fest
in the front on the left like right next
to me she comes from the back to the
front with her hand kind of like our
hands are supposed to meet and she just
with her hand she's supposed to like uh
twist me you know what I mean but I I
kept on forgetting that that's going to
happen so I was like rarely ever ready
for that to be twisted forcefully let's
look at it again pay attention to
that the left girl the left
girl but I in the end it had not it
didn't have the impact that it was
supposed to have she was really supposed
to like whoosh like slap me to turn
backwards but um
yeah and here the this is the move that
people are saying she's holding my
ass I I I wanted some kind of like
interaction with like you know sitting
on them or being held by them and so on
and that's what that's what we came up
with uh I guess but I kept on telling
the the butt holding lady to let me fall
back even more she was holding me so
safely she was like I'm not going to let
this girl fall under any circumstances
but I was like more more more please I
need I want to make this look very
dramatic don't worry I'm safe I'm
holding this other girl's hand very
tightly let me just fall back as much as
I can so it can look more dramatic but I
think that uh was really pretty
right I could have done even
[Music]
more this part was difficult still
struggling with that walking over
them
tripping this so f ah I
yeah that's
[Music]
difficult and then Tak remember you have
to go to the very right side immediately
after the chus ends okay does she
remember oh she remembers and then I
like this move wow it's like a I don't
know sexy butt
[Music]
move and then we turn around and they
turn after me and then we go like
this and then see I like this in the in
the music video this becomes the press
four moment but it's not like keep on
saying but it was so the choreographers
didn't think of this but it kind of felt
right into the press four timing the 25%
timing the moment when I kind of like go
down like Drop It Drop It Like It's Hot
became the press for moment but it's not
like the choreographers didn't try to
create a press for moment but also in
the in the music video I'm doing this
alone but the point here of the
choreography that I really like is that
I have to like move really fast from one
side to the other side uh while making
these poses that the girls are then like
taking at the same time right behind me
so look at
that see that was a press for moment but
um ah 40% yeah
[Music]
look at it again 1 2 three four and the
last pose is just me on my own but yeah
you didn't realize yeah cuz also in the
music video it's just me on the on the
stairs there doing
that but yeah the last POS the second to
last pose is like me kind of bending
down and that became the press for a
moment just because it's I I mean okay
so originally
kouu in the first draft didn't have an
emphasized press for moment I asked if
any number could be used this time to
create such a thing again because you
guys will try it out and if there's
nothing you guys will be sad and I think
it's like a funny meme uh that will
bring people more interest and will
bring them to the music video to try it
out and it just also becomes a talking
topic so I think it's a marketing
strategy you know so I wanted to
recreate it and I didn't care which
number it would be but perfectly
coincidentally I say I wanted this to
happen but the Coro
coincidentally offered a perfect
solution to it that was not on purpose
but making it happen again in the music
video was yeah more or less on purpose
yeah this part originally the the
formation was very different we last
minute changed it because I kept on
getting getting one timing wrong uh and
so I we had to change it so that the
girls are dancing um in a place where I
can see them so I can adjust my timing
to them so look at
[Music]
this that that you can already see I'm a
little bit
late but this was like the best we could
do on that short short schedule that
that we
had cuz that one was so fast
[Music]
four and they come to the front so I can
see
them this timing still kind of
off but one thing that was interesting
is like um me dancing with back dancers
like this is the first time like I did
some you know of course I did dances
dances with other uh like Hol members
where um it's kind of different like
when I dance a dance back dancers and
I'm the only like artist so to say then
they're dancing around me right and I
mostly stay in one position uh like on
zero on the Zero marker um but because
I'm so used
to like like in a group setting moving
around more on different markers and not
just staying on zero in the middle in
the center I was often like where do I
go where am I supposed to where do I go
oh wait right I just have to return to
the middle oh right it was that easy but
this was one of those moments where I
always forgot where I had to go but it
was all I had to do was just go back to
the
middle and right after this I'm like uh
where do I go next in my my brain I'm
like where do where do I oh [\h__\h] where
do I go where do I go where do I go
where
live just go back yeah there we go the
girls will do everything for me I just
have to stay in the
middle I like this part we're like a
wave maybe you'll see it better in the
dance version but you can also see it in
the music video quite well
[Music]
this is the most difficult part of the
dance and maybe just watching it you
wouldn't think
so but it uh those hands movement hand
finger po positions and so on are very
intricate uh
so what what's with wink we saw oh you
saw a wink oh but yeah look look pay
attention to the hands it's like a on
it's like a piece two pieces next to
each other then they separate each other
then they go up and then they go twirl
and then they go down and then they go
back
up all right it's so
far you can't appreciate it
here I like this
part maybe in the other in the last one
they can see it better but in the music
video you can also see it a little bit
better uh but I think um for the dance
shots and the YouTube shorts you'll see
it even better
maybe yeah Naruto hand
signs see it's so nice when the dancers
are doing most of the work and I just
have to stand
there I like
this I like this you saw me on a Mir I
you up I don't even know what to do
[Music]
you have to look up maybe the screen in
the
back it doesn't even look so complicated
now when it's not like focused on
[Music]
it but it's really cool
you'll see you'll see
eventually should have been my ear
Vision song I heard a lot of people say
that it's funny to me that you guys
think this will do well in your vision
you think so here um I was kind of like
losing balance on those legs I was like
oh God I got to hold it I got to hold it
I gotta I'm not really like only 0.5% of
my ass is currently sitting the rest is
floating I need to I can't fall down I
need to wait until it's
over yeah yeah that was the 3D life a
little bit you know looking back on it
very nice very
[Music]
nice now one more
thing uh I want you guys to appreciate
the Acappella I already let my members
hear it yesterday but I want to
officially let everybody listen listen
to the Acappella version of the song um
because you know my me and my music team
um you know especially like Johnny I
want to shout out to Johnny who mixes my
voice so beautifully and thanks to all
the beautiful oh harmonies that uh are
always involved in the creation of our
songs and the Acappella always becomes
the most beautiful thing
ever
so shall we
where did it go I think I just played it
through Discord did I we're going to
listen to it together and you members
who already heard it will just pretend
that you didn't hear it before yeah it's
nice to hear it again anyway
[Music]
right our tradition of showing of the AC
capellas uh where is it what the hell
here where' it go here oh yeah here okay
I found
[Music]
it Mir reflection going under confused
Obsession I still wonder if I was made
for you if I could only
see oh
please me up
new for you pretending it's
[Music]
old never see what I want what I need oh
do you no no oh do you no
follow through you purs
now you sold me on a i you up shs I
don't even know what to do with this
man be good play your my
Mir told do
anything left I'd be the king a queen of
new I'm begging you to see I'm you you
all of me it seems like everyone wants
it around and on keeping me captive
Escape my way you say I'm way
[Music]
too oh [\h__\h]
oops I forgot I was playing it for
Discord and just changed um Discord
window
to something else I'm so sorry now we
have to listen from the beginning I'm
snacking on crackers by the way while
this is
playing sorry one more time this time I
won't forget that it's on
Discord yeah I wish it would continue
[Music]
playing and
Mir reflection going under confused
Obsession I still wonder if I was made
for you if I could only
see oh
please me up
new for you pretending
it's me don't think so live life in
they got yet I'm asking why you never
see what I want what I need oh do
you do
you
follow
[Music]
you you me on a i you sh I don't even
know what to do with this tell me the it
be good Play Your Part my Mir
with told do
anything but i' be the king and queen of
new I'm you to see I'm you you all me it
seems like everyone wants it around and
on keeping me captive Escape my way you
say I'm way too fragile I'm just your
perfect Idol break me shap me
you never see what I want what I need oh
do
you do
you
follow
[Music]
you you me on a i you up shs I don't
even know what to do with this man tell
me be good play A Part my
Mir my
new disgu on and on and this
[Music]
Mir you make me fall in
love you so me on
I you up shs I don't even know what to
do with this tell me be good A Part my
[Music]
Mir my
I'm so happy you guys like
it such a beautiful
song as always I'm just so proud of my
baby that thanks to asteroid came into
fruition in the first place thank you so
much man for making bangers for me and
With
[Music]
Me Now to celebrate the
occasion perhaps we shall sing it once
live although I am not good at singing
the song Live let me be honest with you
it is difficult it is very difficult
but we shall do it anyway cuz this is a
celebration Cate Good Times come on
hey Okie
doie let's hear
it oh you too quiet
[Music]
o
yeah miror reflection going under
confused Obsession I still wonder if I
was made for you if I could only
see oh please oh make me up a new I
calulated perfectly for you pretending
like it's all just for me think so live
life
in play God and yet I'm asking you never
see what I want what I need oh do you oh
do
you follow through like you pursue but
now you s me on a mirage i k you up into
shreds I don't even know what to do with
this mess help me to crost it good Play
Your Part
[Music]
my told I'd do
anything but I'd be the king and queen
of
[Music]
you I'm you you're all of me it seems
like everyone wants it all around around
running around on and on the cycle
keeping me captive Escape my way you say
I'm way too fragile I'm just perfect I
don't break me shave
me you never see what I want what I need
oh do you oh do
you follow through like you pursue
bus you s me on a mirage I thre you up
into shreds I don't even know what to do
with this mess help me to cross it be
good play A Part my
Mir sing with
me you sting little eyes you disgu on
and on and
[Music]
on fall in
love
you me
oh
no do with this tell me to C it be good
Play Your Part my
Mir see with
me the on and on and on this I'm
not to Heart me right
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
yay that was me rage Mir rage Mirage my
Raj your Raj our Raj my r
it's my rage song this comes up when I'm
raging as a
gamer my my my my my my rage
yeah throwing down the switch
controller kicking the PS5 in its
ass yeah also of course um let me
advertise the song is up on streaming
services now it wasn't immediately when
uh the music video came out but it's now
out so I hope you guys already looked it
up on your Spotify Apple music iTunes
wherever please do please do please do
let's get those uh listening numbers up
so that I get some
royalties to pay back all of the money
that I paid out of my pocket for the
music
video
You're everybody please listen to it
also on on YouTube too though the music
video Let's Not neglect any of it yeah I
would really appreciate it thank you so
much I'm really really happy that you
guys like the song cuz I like it so much
too my baby I really like it it's such a
Bop it's such a
Vibe yeah doing so well so far on
YouTube too I'm proud who do you want
most to sing
this
um go I think cuz she's really good with
soft songs I think she would sing this
well therefore M
too I want the more gentle voices
anybody can sing it though anybody can
I'm I'm I would gladly welcome
anybody good Iris I oh yeah Iris Iris
really might fit the song quite well mhm
yeah but anyone I'd be so happy if
anybody yeah I still need to know what
laas thinks of
it I wonder what what does less think of
the song and the music video like she
has a sub account but uh you guys
probably would have notified me already
if she would have written something
about it on her sub
account I'm going to send it to her
after the stream if I must
yeah laas listen to
Mirage Yamada come
on
yamad what do you think tell us share
your thoughts with us please what are
your most inner thoughts and
desires uh is it is it Mirage of course
it
[Music]
is oh good already heard it cuz she was
there when I like first revealed it to
PTSD yeah crony gura were the first ones
to see the music
video but I think the
first Ian member to hear it did I let
narissa listen to it in Italy maybe but
uh this one I kept I I kind of kept to
myself for a long time like Chima I
think I was like uh sharing here and
there with some members early on but
Mirage I it was like um a surprise
hidden pregnancy I I HD the be baby
belly for as long as I
could Kima was a very obvious pregnancy
because it had three heads so the belly
was just too big Mirage I was able to
hide a bit
better cuz it was just a mirage the
whole pregnancy was just a [\h__\h]
Mirage it was real but the song is real
what is this woman talking
about but doesn't it make sense I think
it makes a lot of sense tell don't tell
this to
ol it just popped out unannounced yeah
exactly I think it's a great
analogy so now we have yapped for over 2
hours about the frey live and the
song did I forget
anything no I think I didn't forget
anything so I will now move on to read
some super chats because I really have
to read super chats I've been so behind
because of my Japan trip and the other
trips that I was on um so let's take
some time to do
that oh yeah we about magia yeah yeah
you can watch the archive later on we
had to rewatch the whole thing because
it was just so
good yeah I gave also some insight about
the lyric split and so on because I I
put a lot of thought into choosing the
right members and giving them the right
parts and everything and combining the
right
[Music]
parts no I don't want to discuss too
much or like say anything about people
who where in it and who got like
replaced by what or whatever things
happened and things changed but me
saying anything like that will um you
know just
uh it just doesn't look good
for The Replacements so to
say and that anyway like that one in
particular happened ages ago so
unfortunately as I said I had to change
a million things with his life that's
why it was so stressful for
me a lot of things didn't didn't really
go well like there were songs that I was
planning on doing and then I couldn't do
it and then I needed to change the song
and I needed to change the members and
just too many
things yeah but there's always a next
time and even the the changes led to
great things like the magia trio wasn't
originally that Trio I mean I think it
would have been great in any kind of um
composition of members but uh yeah this
one was really
great yeah it all came together nicely
in a nice little package that all makes
sense and just yeah you guys were saying
like this doesn't feel like there were a
lot of changes made this just seems like
it was planned like this all along and
it was meant to be like this all
along
right so now where might we continue our
Super Chat reading was I already
told thank you Kaka
[Music]
kit thank you
pudding ah thank you andma recollection
a night's dilemma okay let's go
there Super Chat raing time maybe I
should wait one second let me pick
something let me pick my children up
from the kindergarten Here there they
are
okay what was it Anya
recollection
um oh there it is
okay the Super Chat mins
yeah oh
maybe not
[Music]
that ah H
wonderful
okay let's go this is the last Ian Reco
Super Chat stream Super Chat that I have
left so let's get through it D thanks
for the pinky spoiling the W that spoils
us hope you have had a good rest boss
thank you a good rest oh
good rest good good rest what are you
talking about this was the
the wait no day before this was after my
recording I did not rest I don't think I
did did
I maybe I rested afterwards yeah oh
maybe this isn't meant as past tense
maybe it's meant as future tense because
my body was tense by the
way yeah I need that I need that massage
again that one
massage that's so good thank you Doug
Hood rest what is that I don't know what
is
that but I'm so glad this stressful time
is over like in Japan I had like work
that I had to leave my little apartment
for every day almost every day I had to
leave
it and go to a dance lesson or go to the
Studio or do this and do that or record
uh like the for example the boat program
and the Haunted House program and so
many things so busy I still have some
work to do right now but um it's more
spread out and more chill and my
deadlines are not haunting me anymore
hallelujah hallelujah yay and I can I
can chill with my cats which just you
know it's such a big game
changer by the way I why wa one thing is
not Super Chat reading related but um I
said I won't have a schedule for this
week right I will say though this uh
Wednesday I think yeah this
Wednesday guess
what Hollow BS returns
I uh in the past days weeks have been
trying to organize another Hollow back
stream H Banks is coming
back my chat why is this chat so slow
and the one on OBS is so fast let's
go yeah Hol bags yeah I I really like
doing Hollow bags streams so finally we
have um a good amount of new
members that I I can include potentially
so it is about time for another one I
figured you guys would like to see
another one
again last one so fun I know we had two
so far they both were a lot of fun can
really recommend you guys who haven't
seen it yet watch the um Archive of
it yeah yeah yeah no even from outside
of those new generations there are some
who still haven't participated from
older
Generations so maybe there'll be a
surprise older one in there who knows
who knows who knows just
saying it's not not 100% new
members yeah I'm still waiting for some
back submission but uh they're coming in
they're coming in they're coming in
hot why do you why do you keep on saying
wow NE why are you spamming
that I don't do that project
anymore unless I get some special snack
box from somewhere but haven't been
doing that in a
while you miss and I I mean yeah I
really like that project too but the
snack boxes weren't that
good and yeah at some point they like I
wish I could choose which country I'm
getting cuz
yeah maybe one day I'll do it again but
now is not the time cooking streams um
I'm probably going to do a cooking
stream within the next two months like
or one month I don't know sometime in
November or end of
October but I still have to get some new
equipment to you know make this setup
good I want to like maybe get a
different microphone for cooking stream
and yeah I still have to try it out cuz
I haven't tried it in the new kitchen
yet it's been so
long Chef ch
yeah I want to show off my new stuff but
like it's so
reflexes it's it reflects so
much I don't know how am I going to do
that it is such a beautiful
stove
but I'll have to find like a good
angle a good angle of the camera will
maybe
maybe be able to avoid
Reflections yeah I guess I'll wear a
mask or
something but then if I wear like a full
face mask my face will not be
tracked from the phone I need to have my
mouth and my eyes
visible
[Music]
so I I'll have to try it out and like
figure out what's the best way to to do
it anyway Psy D Studio R Dan for the
pinky T your Celestial boss Knight hence
the extra title oh is that Danto thank
you need not worry about that you will
always have your Eternal companion the
shiny gumy to sue for loneliness you
might be feeling because she gets you
glory to takoni
yay yeah I mean
definitely re especially recently I feel
like that is a very true
statement thank you thank you thank you
so much Studio Rob for the sweet words
check 47 D and duck Hood followed up
with another pinky so honestly I'm going
to give you a choo
Cho yes you have officially combined two
pinkies got and turned them crafted them
into a red one good job you know the
recipe
now can I dedicate a healing Phoenix
kiss to to satify boss D has been
working super hard at fry station with
fewer jkin this week hang in there
that's oh well
that's 1 month ago so I don't know how
necessary my kiss is
anymore but to
satisy I hope everything's better now
did you get sick or something or was it
just busy at work apparently you had a a
a hard time
working do you even remember this
they don't go bad the kisses don't but
the chickens maybe
do are you sick
now he's sick again now I'm sick too oh
great you weren't sick then but now
you're sick so yeah now you get a get
well soon kiss wonderful wonderful
M well then it all worked out it's as if
this was on purpose would we want it any
other way no I want it that
way maybe you got sick now just for this
to make any
sense it was
divine what's the word
divine divine
intervention yeah
calculated delay no divine intervention
sounds
cooler silver
FY you guys are so
late for the Queens yay
Queens in New York
right thank you naan the Beautiful
Queens who cares about the king when we
can have two queens let's go let's
go Cruz than SP thanks for red Super
Chat love cute emojis thank you m MW MW
Mah I don't know why I deserve that but
I appreciate it thank you for your love
Rog r or ratch tun for the red also just
love you oh thank you are you here now
please receive your loving kiss back
[Music]
hope hope you still love me to this day
one month later hope that love hasn't
faded things fade fast these
days or maybe R oh
like racial Rachel
Rachel I like that name but it's
difficult to pronounce okay looks like
you're not here now but I hope the kiss
will reach you one day GD d doing
Moonlight D for the red chat as well
making the mother of all omelets here
kfb can't fret over every egg kiaha
Armstrong 2025 probably for future
context this is about your
Senator what
oh I see cuz uh
Armstrong did
Armstrong was Armstrong a senator at
some
point isn't he an
astronaut I know I know you mean like me
Senator because of my flying
miles but who's is that I I just know a
an
astronaut a metal gear rising why the
[\h__\h] would I understand that reference I
didn't play that
game here you give me future context
that this is about my Senator status but
you don't give me the the context of the
game that I didn't
play that was important think chicken
than
thanks
though GD thanks for the pinky more
massage huz oh yeah thank you thank you
so much I still haven't gone to a single
massage since I came back from Japan
which is kind of crazy considering how
much pain I felt in my
body yeah but I used my my own shoulder
massage thing again it's quite nice you
yeah and my my front throat or like
front neck pain is
also pretty much gone but oh the usual
we're just back to the usual back neck
and shoulder and Spine and everything
pain just just normal the usual menu you
know you know we're
fine H thanks for the
raid time to visit crony I talked to
crony by the way crony got a little
intimidated by how far the molds are so
we're probably not going to go to the
it's not just the farness but also she
said oh that's
pricey uh yeah it gets pretty pricey so
it's fine we talked about some other
destinations though but we're not sure
if like when to do it if we change the
destination um now I wonder should I
still set up M's date with someone else
or I don't know h
someone who's more willing to fly very
far and spend a lot of money on a
disappearing island
[Music]
country well I'll have to think about
that
but I
[Laughter]
volunteer well I don't know I don't want
to really like justice members I don't
want to jump at them with this Prospect
because they're still new with narissa
it was easy because I you know I already
knew she loves me she couldn't say no to
it but you know I was her oi so that was
easy yeah K is always busy it would be
so difficult to
schedule any kind of vacation
H how
how she's
new I don't know if I want to pressure
her to do something like that with
me yeah I'll think about it there's a
lot of great candidates for it but who
who is genuinely willing to do
it
mint
honestly I love to go with her
but how about radin no with radin with
radin we wouldn't go to the moldes with
Ren we going to go to a European city
with museums and stuff to really make
her
happy anyway anyway anyway anyway no I
think generally it's it would would be
better to go with a
Holo uh even though I like the idea of
going with mint maybe with mint I'll go
somewhere else
someday yeah she's a city girl art
girl I got to bring her to like Paris
and
Spain and
Austria and Italy like legitimately if
she comes over I'm going to bring her to
all of those all of the
above
yeah anyway bris tiger dunon Sky
dunon oh oh wait brisk tiger I drew the
ah you didn't you don't mean you draw
you drew it as in you drew the
illustration but you got the the takiki
price in some one of those thingies I
know which one you mean but I don't know
how to call it thank you
though okay next is about Luigi's Manion
too HD Luigi I didn't forget you did I
read those super chats
uh I don't think I
did
okay why not go big and do a full Hollow
year trip yeah because that's going to
happen because cuz that's going to work
out sadly that's not
realistic okay here we go here we
go dark Hood once again the first Super
Chat hey thank you for the pinky dawn of
time the Shadows Audio Drama also 20
second sneak peek of Banger new myth
song from fourth anniversary ah yeah cuz
it was posted on Twitter first and W
tomorrow ah spontaneous Chien explosion
due to happiness
all the blood spilled like scattered
everywhere on the walls I hope you guys
cleaned that up
afterwards the O social activities I
mentioned in memb stream Super Chat are
for same job team building stuff you
didn't miss a new job update from me
more team building stuff today but I
will listen to W and do my best oh I
hope those o social activities are done
with for
now maybe they weren't so bad though H
in
hindsight but yeah I'm glad you enjoyed
the dawn of time Audio Drama like both
of the both of the myth audio dramas did
you guys listen to it did all of you get
it I think it's really really nice I be
honest I didn't finish to the final
version but when I was recording it I
was thinking oh this is really
nice no not yet and did you listen to my
new voice pack back because I think it's
cute you
better saving it for when I'm out of oh
okay that's a good
strategy I haven't had the courage to
listen to the second one oh but it's not
sad you should you
should so I to do okay no time youing
okay well if you still you you just
can't forget about it don't forget about
it what do you want to talk about what
what what's there to talk
about what is
it it's a voice bre in an airplane and I
spill tomato juice on
you I think it's a really fun situation
but but I wouldn't do this obviously
like I I would just I ideally I would
not talk a single word maybe maybe a
friendly like greeting like
hello when a stranger sits down next to
you in the airplane just so that it will
be
less rude or like I think it will auto
automatically the person next to you
will be more willing to stand up for you
when you need to go to the to the to the
ouse in the airplane if you at least
have have some kind of greetings
exchanged it was very flirty yeah maybe
a little
bit maybe maybe maybe there were some
butterflies flying
around ah yeah you like my load of the
Rings reference I was hoping that it was
going to be
recognizable they literally asked
me they were like
uh this show that you mentioned does it
really exist maybe we have to beep it
out and change the name or something I'm
like no no no this is literally like me
avoiding that and changing an
original Show's name so I think we're
fine keeping it in please keep it in I
want people to know I'm talking about
Lord of the
Rings which by the way I watched it I
watched the finale it was so
good it was so good and then I watched
the review of the what's what's their
channel name the nerd of Rings or so
that makes a lot of good like lure
videos and even even that channel like
they have a lot of criticism for it too
for like generally most of the first
season but they were saying the second
season is much better and especially the
whole calab bmore anatar Arc was really
well made he said
so taking that from nerd of the Rings I
think you have to maybe consider the
fact that the second season was really
better and you know tried their
best
mhm
mhm yeah obviously the thing and I I get
it like um I understand that Gandalf was
not supposed to be there in that way
like Gandalf doesn't show up until later
apparently in the real story and this is
not how like he first shows up
originally but you know I understand why
they forced him in there because they
need some kind of recognizable besides
um besides some other characters but
they just really wanted that Gand of
hype I guess and
yeah that that might be very inaccurate
but besides that there are according
even to nerd of the Rings even he says
this season was more accurate and pretty
good
so yeah oh I have to say uh little
spoiler I guess a BAL Rock appeared in
this season quite a bit and especially
in the last episode you see the ball
Rock very clearly and that was insane
that scene was really
good really big
wellmade
CG yeah that maybe they showed the
briefly in season one but this time they
showed it a lot and the holy [\h__\h] that
was a great moment it was really
cool Durance Bane yeah and I also
understand that all these Duran there's
many Duran and this was not the one like
this the the B shouldn't have done this
to this Duren but to a different Duran a
few Generations
off but you know maybe they're just like
you know merging things for the sake of
time skips and all
that who cares I don't
care and name is the same so let's look
over
it a auran once was killed by a b rock
doesn't matter which during it is
right
yeah so yeah no it was really good I
think it was really good uh season
finale as a season finale it was really
like no matter how you see the show the
second season was better that is
objectively the truth and the season
finale was really [\h__\h]
good like if you put stuff aside like
there might still be some inaccuracies
like creative choices from them uh the
season finale was [\h__\h] good
what I literally can't talk about Ring
of Power with you guys it's so
frustrating
[Music]
okay let's read super
chats I'll keep my my positive feelings
about rings of power to myself I I
really just want you to understand this
season is objectively really better than
the first season so give him a
[Music]
break how about you play a game we like
I always play games you like what the
hell what do you don't like about
[Music]
Zelda W wants to send us the usual yeah
I want to and then I'll play rings of
power
there I like it so far thank
you why am I saying thank you I don't
even know but I just feel like I have to
say thank you
people who don't even read the books are
telling is bad is crazy what second
season is super
good so what you liked it but you also
what what was the first sentence I don't
understand the first
sentence please explain why you do you
think it is better than season one well
did you watch season 2 and season 1
fully if you did then I think you would
agree with me
the pacing was better the story arcs
were better the acting was
better like
yeah the visuals were better that stupid
human
lady was gone I didn't like her that
much the the human lady who has that son
who had two to hide from the Orcs or
whatever that the ones that lived in
this tiny Place Tiny Village and the
human lady she's gone they G what was
her name I think bronwin
actually and she was pretty but I think
I said this back in the day she doesn't
look like she to me she doesn't look
like she fits into this
universe her face looks too modern for
me what's my criticism to a lot of these
people face too modern
I was I was quite critical of some
things too you
know
now thanks to nerd of the Rings I had
this one
realization uh cuz I did there's a
million books right so even if I read
the main books I don't know if I would
even notice
but I just
realized what's going to happen
I I had this realization what's going to
happen in season
3 because I realized now why they keep
on featuring the city numor which is
across the sea and barely really so far
has any connection with the rest of the
world and I realized wait those are
humans and saon is going there
huh and so so far numor is already kind
of like more and
more uh in in like a really like bad
downfall
spiral so I see where this is going it's
just going to get much much worse huh
well you don't have to spoil me now
about it I just have a
feeling I think I
understand you always know what happened
to Nan no but I didn't
know what would happen to numo cuz I
didn't really know numor at
all it's moving way too fast well then I
mean is it though like it's getting four
seasons in to Total maybe would move
slower if people would have you know
liked it more and then they would have
gotten more
seasons yeah I don't think they mention
numer in the movies at all right so I
wasn't aware at all of its existence but
now I
understand now I understand a lot more
yeah yeah I know I know Aron is I know
that now uh yeah yeah cuz like uh the
guy the guy who is like so loyal to the
Blind Lady he is yeah one of
the
um yeah he's like in the family tree of
him
right makes a lot of sense
okay oh also at the very end of the
season finale they show where the elves
settle in a place protected by their
Elven
rings and and so apparently those Elven
Rings they keep that place safe cuz they
kind of like hide it from s's view
that's why that place is so so protected
what was its name again in English cuz
yeah rivendel so you see Rivendell
before everything was built you see like
the the empty lands of Rivendell before
they built uh like all the nice
buildings
later they're like oh yes here here we
will stay
safe
Ren
beautiful Elvin
ring what do you mean I didn't know
what I knew Rivendell from the movies I
didn't know like why exactly it was
so
peaceful I didn't know that their
specific
Rings like had that
function yeah so far it still looks like
a random green
place maybe in the next season they will
build it up who
knows yeah region [\h__\h] region is so
over anyway let's let's continue um take
47 d py d Kenny stamps d game 8910 D bab
noin than for the pinky we can be good I
promise I I believe you can especially
you as long as you don't argue too much
with me withing of
power just give up
already thank you 77
D
ro oh K let's say GAA gets possessed by
a spirit of mischief and starts smearing
blueberry ice cream all over soda's face
to get the spirit out of GAA you have to
make her sad how will you save GDA from
the spirit and soda from
GAA so are you saying that she cannot
stop smearing blueberry ice cream all
over soda senpai's face like she
literally cannot stop what if I just eat
all of the ice
cream what if I volunteer to eat it
all then we don't have to make GAA sad
and she can stay mischievous maybe it's
a lie Maybe she doesn't have some kind
of spirit that's possessing her maybe
she's just using that as a front to be
mischievous
H and then we like troll her back we eat
all the blueberry ice cream and then
it's all
good yeah I like this solution I am
outsmarting her yeah it's not true she
doesn't have a spirit possessing her
she's just being herself she's just
being a little bit more cheeky than
usual thanks for the pinky Elsie laugh
and D sir lelot d s no thank you for the
red super chat today I woke up feeling
silly but I had already made my choice
you know sometimes I get these weird
thoughts like wanting to donate to KI
this amount well here's my first time
doing something this big congrats on all
your time in home life and now it's time
for me to slip back into Shadow's realm
do you mean go back to being
a uh a
lurker why thank you doll for peeking
out and giving me this big donation
thank you so
much I appreciate it thank you thank
you I don't even think you're that much
of a
lurker maybe first red super chat but
not I'm I'm I I know you well
enough so come Out of The Shadow realm
say hi say hi where are
you okay either you're stubbornly
lurking today as well or you're just not
here right now but thank you so much for
the support thank
you wake up feeling silly to send a
Super
Chat spend all my money on vtu
girl the
D RS d m arcade d d m d random collusion
thanks for the red super chat super
chats don't work
H I think they
worked it
seems they have worked
unfortunately or fortunately for me
thank you I'll take that money and I'll
run
away golden
pyro Jim Tracy
D7 Jones
D swatter D watermelon wait thanks for
the pinky does that make the Blue Toad
with us Co does that make the Blue Toad
with
us what does this
mean does that make the Blue
Toad with us Co
I don't understand the
question you'll have to rephrase that
somehow if you're in the
chat ah s know where dare you are why
you hiding from me why are you avoiding
my gaze am I like sour Run To
You
H maybe yeah because blue and
Kaki I guess it's the Blue Toad could be
Coble but I don't know weirdly phrased I
don't understand but thank you for the
pinky anyway thank you for watching and
supporting Nathan Kon thank you for the
pinky identity fact is no joke K we need
you to come down to the station please
we have a couple questions for you uh uh
uh uh uh uh uh you have reported it too
late or I'm reading the report too late
therefore this is
not valid
anymore I don't even know what you're
talking about I didn't steal anyone's
identity I would never do that no no no
I don't know you're crazy maybe you were
drunk maybe you were
drunk oh Kam s thanks for WR chat that's
why Kam always good work T thank you
very much wow what did I do oh a it was
after I
wrapped uh she said
thank you I'm glad you liked
that you already read it when I said no
no no no no no I'm refreshing that by
having read it
now
thank
Wonder Tracy D
Fabian d jacob7 d Galahad Marksman
thanks for the pinky pinky pinky pinky
kiala today I turned 30 but I'm not
going to let it get me down do you know
why because the age of 30 is in demand
thanks for always being you I wish you
all the best in your future endeavors
pinky pinky pinky I am glad that you are
so positive about this that you can feel
so excited and
like happy and relieved and nonstressed
about that good for you and you should
there's nothing wrong with being 30 and
uh the age of 30 is in demand so yeah
enjoy your FES they begin now make the
most of them cuz I don't know if you can
cope that hard when you hit the next one
the next big
number thank you pza k d for two oranges
why do I have pain in my I don't
know I'm not in pain at all I'm I'm so
happy I'm
[Music]
fine random thanks for the red super
chat oh what is that no that's your
second one in that stream thank you
you're so clutch I have you considered
speedrunning this
game it may have been a
while but it doesn't mean that I
forgot what this game did to me and so I
know that this is very sarcastic this
super
chat you cannot fool me just because a
lot of time has passed I know exactly
what you're doing I know what you're
doing there you room random collusion
one
month
bye-bye a kiss to
go take monkey Dy Chey D and
s02 thank
you yeah oh my God this game can we just
forget about it I don't want to I don't
want
to oh oh God you know what's next forear
animers kind
get this one has a lot of super
chats all right I think that was
the was I I came back to
Austria uh right at that
point did I I think I
did I think I did let me find the
thumbnail
yeah we're finally there I'm so
scared can't avoid it any
longer you
can't no running
now but can I go to idle
meeting I have to go to idle
meeting I eat this chocolate
okay I'll go idle
meeting be right back
for
oh
[Music]
oopsie sorry if you turn up the audio
that was a controller
dropping that was smoothie by the
way I was able to uh randomly activate
the
smoothie machine the Smoothie lawn mower
the Smoothie
car I saw her I saw her on the floor and
she looked like a little mushroom
because she was
so cutely sitting there on maybe like a
little muffin honestly yeah she looked
like a muffin and she was so cute and I
picked her up and she started
purring so
[Music]
cute I just realized this whole time
I've been playing The Mirage
instrumental and I was not tempted to
sing along that is some progress
compared to
yesterday good job me
[Music]
M smoothie
motor don't eat her up I'm I'm so close
to it I need
to instead I will eat chocolate
[Music]
okay I'm going to
assume if we manage to finish this
one then that'll be all that I'll be
reading today
uh like until the
end let's gumar mus
show I will read this now and no mercy
to these Super Chat shall be given they
shall be eliminated one by
[Music]
one and archived into the archives
forever into the void Into the
[Music]
Depths yeah okay here we
go I can do it I can do it motivation
talk you can do it just do it eliminate
the super
chats you can do like I believe in
myself hook on D motion D for the pinky
four years since I discovered this
Phoenix designed by freaking hook and
enriched my life going for ahead I've
been happier and more outgoing because
the kindness talent and hard work keep
sh since de made me want to improve
despite being around all of these four
years I'm still excited to see you cook
because I know how hard you work for it
and the end result is always a great
time happy to chill here here another
year happy anniversary boss thank
you yeah I'm so happy to hear from my my
old my old uh chickens who've been
around since the very
beginning yeah cuz yeah you've been with
me for thick and thin and good and bad
and dark and good and everything so
thank you so
much appreciate it
[Music]
Good Times bad times we go through it
together dog Hood sends a pinky and a
red to chat sock puppet theater POV
album music video breaking Dimensions
Sports myth one block shiny what sports
shiny Fever Night waa frogy wa return
new game streams new songs you did so
much for us you're so [\h__\h] amazing I
would fry for you without the contract
oh you're such a loving person and a
passionate content creator but please
don't feel pressure to deliver non-stop
content in this next year we love your
content but we love you most let us know
what you need and I promise you'll never
stop loving and supporting you
oh oh soccer I see thank you that's so
sweet of you dark I do think that the
this year like once World Tour
ends I mean then there's well other
things always on the horizon but I I do
think
generally maybe hopefully it'll be a
little bit L
stressful um I like doing musical stuff
and so on but I hope I'll find a better
balance so for that next year I mean it
really wasn't in my hands I couldn't
change these things so wasn't my fault
the way things came together is just how
they came together
we'll see how it goes next year but I'll
try my best to take care of myself so
that I don't get burnt out uh but yeah
thank you DG Hood really really sweet
sentiment thank you so
much Hulu thank you for the right Super
Chat It Seems Like Only Yesterday that
we were all crying to see each other on
our first anniversary but it's already
our fourth anniversary seeing how much
you've all M matured makes me feel like
uh watch graduation from K gradu
what seeing how much you've all matured
makes me feel like watch grad Oh you
mean like it's like as as if I graduated
from kindergarten the way I
matured what was I just a random child
to you like in the first year or so I
was very mature no okay maybe not on
stream I would say that I've always
been relatively mature for how early on
in my life I was already doing my own
thing
mhm but perhaps the way I portrayed
myself on
stream you know with a lot of crying
because of tech issues and so on perhaps
doesn't seem like I was that mature but
um well
I I almost really mature trust
me thank you
Honolulu you thank you
[Music]
for
for jaob 47 D nan oh another Japanese
one thank you for the red chat
d
for
love for
[Music]
TD thanks for the pinky happy happy four
you K crazy how time flies You' have
been hard at work providing us with
great content and I appreciate very much
I'll keep on sharing for you kabia again
happy anniversary H Wings all these like
nostalgic words thank you so much yeah I
do try to continue provide you guys with
great content I I will say like after 4
years of pretty much streaming every day
and working every day and stuff like
make putting out music and you know
things repeat and games repeat and then
there's some new games but other games
are just like you know it just and
projects as well like there's you know
it's difficult to continue be in
Innovative Innovative and creative and
unique um constantly but I still try to
here and there throw some in there for
you guys to not get sick of
me so also bringing back some projects
like Holo bags and so on I hope I hope
that makes you guys feel excited for
upcoming streams always but I also hope
that even the more normal streams the
everyday streams I hope those also bring
you guys Joy
still cuz that's like you
know you know just the normal
schedule you know how it is
[Music]
thank you thank you thank
you Rabbit
Hole uh
cool co
co right that's how I read your name
thank you Kaman for the red super chat
oh but you wrote it in Japanese oh who
whoa whoa whoa let's
[Music]
read fore
it's fate thank you so much for finding
me
[Music]
take it monkey thank you for the re CH
happy Channel birthday AKA anniversary
crazy to think four years have passed
already but thank you for being here
with us to make our lives happier all
these years K I hope the next year is
great and less stressful for you love
you wellet and here's your year number
five yeah
wow it's really it's really so
crazy I didn't think I could make it
this far I really didn't I thought I
would
get fired at some
point honestly that was my that was my
fault the whole time I don't know for
what but I just thought I'd [\h__\h] up
somehow and I'd get
fired so I'd probably not make it past
the first year that
[Music]
far and then oh at the same time I was
also thinking like oh [\h__\h] this is so
mentally
taxing I don't know how much longer I
can do
this but look at me
[Music]
now I can't
stop I can't
just you
know let any of this go to
waste it would
be just no yeah
I can't let it go to waste I've come so
far and I'm proud of what I've created
so far and there's still more things
that I want to create
so
yeah and things are often rough and
depressing and frustrating but I'm here
for the
times that give me the opposite
feeling and I'm here for you guys
yeah we've been for a lot we've you know
spent so much time
together and I'm so grateful for that
time we spent together the time that you
sacrific out of your days for
me so I want to give back as long as I
have you
guys yeah that's how it is that's how it
is thank you tiet monkey
junky
chunk RIT no
worries junky chunk says in his red
Super Chat four years since our debut I
can barely Express how incredible this
moment feels it seems like a both long
time and no time at all and now at last
the real ass at is being implemented
just right as a proud employee of kfb
here's so many more successful VI of the
franchise yay
[Music]
you guys I hope you all are proud of
being kfp you should
be KF
proud proud to be kfp right thank you so
much for the support junky
chunk yeah you still got the H talk
stuff in your profile picture good
merchandise it's rare in 10 years it
will sell for1 million e
[Music]
mm thank you for the support m
do Moonlight thanks for the rainbow
another year pass it feels like uh it
was yesterday when I finished watching
that stream oh I mean CI and was like
cool I can sleep for 1 hour before the
next one but ended up sleeping 2 hours
and waking up when I was already
done but in that moment I knew it that
video I just missed would be my favorite
from the group what the [\h__\h] little did
I know at the time that she would be not
only the first one I call myosi but also
the
last can you see the
future are are we going to die
together that Phoenix would prove to
have the power to make me smile no
matter what and thus I was transformed
into a chicken oh you're sending
memberships thank you and started like
living life like no one knowing that if
everything went wrong there would be a
place to call home and a feather to
bring me back and restore my strength ah
the yeah only one though only
[Music]
one I wouldn't go as far as to say you
SA saved my life but you made it worth
living a what are you for real seeing
you fight your dream for your dreams
motivated me to go after mine again and
so far it's not going bad nice I will
never be thankful enough for what you
have achieved but I hope the feeling
reaches you I you truly you truly embody
the phoenixes of a phoenix you're
amazing # W # Yol # not a
cult well thank you so much
wow that was funny
what you missed my w
stream can't believe
it
unbelievable why do you hate me so much
why do you just hate me so much you just
purposefully missed my debut stream cuz
you hate
me that's okay look at you with your
Golden
Chicken amazing thank you so much for
everything thing for being here for so
[Music]
long
yeah I guess we'll die together Louis
Moonlight guess I'll die guess I'll
die guess I'll die together guess I'll
die
together I remember thinking you'd be my
least favorite before debut before debut
why would would you think that before
debut there really wasn't much to go off
of before debut except the
design and my tweets but that my tweets
weren't so
bad well now you love me and that better
never change cuz otherwise I will make
you love
me pulls out knife threatens
you Orange what's your problem with
orange orange is
beautiful I'm Eternal no I was am
Timeless not I am Eternal what do you
know you need to you don't
remember it's I am Timeless come on
don't get my catchphrases
wrong how dare you we all know it's I am
Timeless yeah nothing's wrong with
orange either why is the chat so delayed
today did I did I said it
wrong but looks a lot
later in my chat window let me enable
hyper
chat okay where are we uh Kazo D TI TDP
T TI TDP D that's difficult unknown D
for the rainbow
happy 4th anniversary kada thank you so
much for everything you do thank you for
making these past four years of my life
so much
[Music]
brighter yeah it's a weird delay
right
T he you have no idea how much happiness
you've given me by just being you you
always make me so incredibly proud to be
you f I hope you know that even after 4
years our love for you still only grows
stronger each and every day discovering
you is still one of the best things that
ever happened to me you truly are the
best Oshi any of us could ever ask for
yeah that's
true I think you already know this but
here's a reminder that I will always be
here supporting you as much as I can for
as long as you allow me to so if you
want I will happily stay here for
another 40 years or even longer 40 [\h__\h]
no I love you w always and forever no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no not 40 not 40 not 40 sorry to like
pop your
[Laughter]
bubble oh for pretty long like I'm
pretty committed to it don't
worry I'll stay for a
while and we can have reunions or
something like
[Music]
that no I know I know unknown like I
know I know you are here to
stay I would never doubt that thank you
so
much yeah let's go as far as we can but
40 is a bit
much Ty and thanks for the red super
chat so hard to believe it's been four
years you've gone so much and despite
the struggles you keep shining so bright
in four years you've changed so many
lives by being you I don't know where
I'd be myself uh if not for you thank
you K we're proud to support you you
guys all underestimate your El but thank
you it is very sweet of you guys to say
stuff like that thank you so much tyun
my legal eagle such a cute name one of
the best jobs at
kfp one of the stress most stressful
jobs maybe we get sued a lot who knows I
don't you're you're fighting it off well
cuz I don't really catch wind of any of
it so you're doing well I hope you'll
continue being our legal
eagle thank you Psy thank you thank you
for two oranges sorry I have so many
super chats so I'm not going to read it
out loud t d Psy D oh another one okay
that's a pinky well you're making me
read so much more you know I'll have a
lot to
read pet see you little
[\h__\h] you little
[\h__\h] that's only a pinky if I do the
math and you know I don't do math
normally I hate
math unless it's
s do you have silver hair in Twin Tails
[Music]
no but I will read this swiftly
goes without saying but the past four
years since discovering you has made a
huge impact in my life I never thought I
would or could have found such a
wonderful community and I honestly owe
that to you from the bottom of my heart
a sincere thank you for everything you
do thank you C for recognizing your CH
talents and potential you are honestly
amazing and you need to hear that know
that and believe that thank you very
much
than thank you you don't seem to be here
right now I guess I guess you're
sleeping as you should if you want to
protect your health thank you for always
going through so much to support kfp
traveling so
much Psy is everywhere maybe next time I
see you you show up with twin tails
you thank you thank you thank you for
the support for a long
time fellow thanks for Pinky happy
fourth anniversary wa time I can't read
time flies so fast there's so much
you've accomplished and so many more
wonderful things to to come you're
always shining brightly and bringing
smiles to the world you keep inspiring
us to fight and to better ourselves do I
do
I subconsciously it
seems I'm doing so much without even
knowing it can I maybe chill because I'm
already doing so much that I am knowing
about and then I don't even realize I'm
doing all these other things that I
don't know
about I'm so busy without knowing it
well thank you so much slapping fellow
M yeah hopefully we'll accomplish a lot
more things so you guys can be even
prouder of you waa and represent kfp
proudly thank you so much for your
support Slavic fellow and Jim Tracy
thanks for the r Super Chad happy fourth
anniversary Ki I can't believe it's been
four years now filled with fun and
memories thank you for all you do for
kfp and her life you're an incredible
person who I'm proud to call my oi love
you boss here's to many more years wa h
a thank you thank you man it's it's nice
going for these super chats like all of
you guys still being here there's like
mostly oldtimers yeah in these super
chats
mostly people who've been around for
several years and it's so nice to see
you guys are still here thank you Jim
Tracy you're the
best thank you thank you thank you I
hope I will always be be Ori Garrick G
what happened with your last name
Garrick why did you remove it h why did
you remove
it
huh did you why did you change it what
happened with G you think I'll forget
about it you think I'll just like not
remember and not
notice what happened with your
name maybe now I'm starting to feel
insane maybe there was never a gara
oh okay okay there was
right right now it's a good size like
it's not so long anymore well that
sounds weird four years ago I didn't
realize that I would find not only an
ooshi but an actual
Idol someone wait I lost where I was
someone who would inspire me and help me
through difficult times you're so
genuine and entertaining you always
light up the stage you make me proud to
wear orange keep me forever why would
you not happily wear
orange why
not why you guys hate orange so much I
hope by now I have successfully
brainwashed you guys into loving orange
hey Mau what the
hell you little
lurker damn damn he's
gold so golden anyway Gary thank you so
much it's so
sweet I feel like
h the way the way the way you describe
Idol is a really nice way to put it
thank you so much I'm glad I can do all
these things for you yeah now I hope I
hope that if I were to open your
wardrobe it would be fully orange and I
would not be disappointed right he's all
orange by now it better
be Wiki Tes thanks for the pinky myth is
power not only did you start Trends but
you've brought people all all over the
world together you personally helped
grow bonds friendships and even lovers
for some yeah
apparently that's what I adore about you
myth and kfp happy four years thank you
yeah you probably said that because I
was uh talking so much about myth myth
myth myth thank you myth is really
strong I'm I'm proud of you know what we
have
created the Legacy I'll forever be proud
of of it thank you so much for
supporting us into and making it into a
legacy thank you thank you thank you
thank you for the
support Mary Pippin thanks for two
pinkies so uh I fired my shelter early
and made the anniversary appropriate
super was recounting your activities
over the past year during your birthday
instead and I'm not sure what to do now
besides wishing you a happy
anniversary no honestly maybe that was
the right way to do it marry P cuz now
otherwise it would like just sound too
similar to others
maybe oh wait compliments you've only
grown cuter over these four years I love
your singing and your dances are always
amazing the fite booty is particularly
bright and raw tuned today one moment
please no you did well it turned out to
be a great Super Chat don't worry about
it you don't have to think too hard it
just flows out of your fingers somehow
it seems even though you don't have
fingers my chat is [\h__\h] slow
thank you Mar
[Music]
PPP chicken fingers thank you for the
support oh
yeah
[Music]
baby maybe maybe another couple of years
together hm with you don't run away you
cannot
Escape thanks for
the happy 4th anniversary I'll keep
support you forever I would hope so
thank you nice to hear from you again
thank you so much for the
support hopefully many more years love
you
rainbow happy anniversary K you always
shot my heart though I can't use English
as well I know that you're charming I'll
cheer for you a long time from Far East
I'm your prisoner of your streaming your
performances and more yeah like the
usual room too in August I went to an
event related home life and I met
someone I have
always wanted to meet I only had a short
time to talk to her but it's the most
precious time in my life
U if there's one thing I regret it all
happened because I met
Kiana next time I want to meet Kiana and
I'll teach you correct pronunciation of
my
name Chu
I thought it was purposefully like that
cuz
you I thought it was supposed to be
ja maybe it's
ja uh life
[Music]
well good English don't worry too much
about it but now I'm really
self-conscious about the pronunciation
of your name
thank you very
[Music]
much no no D thank you
twice
twice thank you thank you D Studio Rob
thanks for the red super chat T to it
you are my oi forever for 4 years you
have been the light in my dark life no
why is it so dark when I'm sad you are
my go-to fix especially sad Sparks my
absolute favorite whole life song of all
time sad Sparks it means so much to me
here's to many many more years of
potential no thank you too I'm glad s
Sparks is so loved by some of you
guys that's so funny to
me the lyrics Don't even fit a sad song
that way
well but thank you Studio Rob you're
always so
sweet you thanks for Pinky you've come a
long way W and the achievement you've
made has never failed to impress
watching you these four years has been
such a blessing to me and I'll continue
to support you for as long as you let me
much love to you K thank you I will let
you support me forever it's more like
the other way around like are you going
to support me forever well now you have
to now you have to I'm expecting great
things from
you thank you so much for your
support pong thank you for two pinkies
Baba H really still thank you for the
great four years he always brings so
much happiness to me your gentle loving
kindness to your fans motivates me to be
a better person I will forever cheer and
support your dreams happy 4th
anniversary also I hope you like what I
prepared for you it took almost one year
to finish it there are lots of fun parts
I hope you can watch the whole thing Oh
you mean the video video was great video
was
fun
yeah I'd love to see it again next year
with maybe even more more starring
[Music]
guests and that was really good thank
you so much I guess you organized it
thank you thank you thank
you I mean the length was a little bit
intimidating but it wasn't so bad when
we watched it on stream I don't think it
felt that long at
all thank you for putting so much effort
into it everybody who participated I
appreciate
it
P lunchbox
than no Mr casic thanks for the pinky
you've done so many amazing things in
your Li in your time as a YouTuber
without you the past 4 years of her life
wouldn't have been nearly as fun You're
simply unreplaceable thanks for always
being yourself I'm so proud of you w ooh
did you ever find those lesbians oh hell
yeah I mean look at Ian
REO thank you Mr casic yay I'm glad I
could make you our past four years here
in this fandom more enjoyable I mean we
wouldn't even know how it would be
without me but let's not even think
about
[Music]
it we are under the assumption that it
would be terrible every day would be
rain every day Would Suck My Life Would
Suck
Without
You as Kelly Clarkson famously once
said I think that was Kelly
claron I think
so we had fun Jeff B thanks for two
pinkies four years it's crazy just how
long you've been going W mhm while I've
only been here for three and a half of
them oh that's almost since the
beginning at this point you really have
made Bright Days brighter or helped pick
me up many times whereever through cute
reactions yaps or openness realness and
mostly
Ving what hello what's wrong with me
hello I'm mostly Ving because of time
zones but I just wanted to take today to
say that you're really inspiring for
everything good or bad you make the best
of it and do what you can for us and
yourself thanks for being for us well
being here for us fell thank you I would
honestly that sentiment U fits very much
to my Frey life too you guys you guys
are just hearing my words you haven't
been through all the clutchness and
scuff of planning that life you don't
even know but I think the sentiment of
good or bad you make the best of it and
do what you can is very accurate I do my
best thank you so much for acknowledging
that and seeing that yeah for watching
over me thank
you for supporting me you're the best
yeah always working hard yeah I mean
except for when I'm not and I'm just
cuddling in my bed and falling asleep in
the middle of the day with my cats
because they're so cute and so fluffy
but it's like my therapy you know cat
therapy I'm I'm totally also working
hard when I'm doing that no but for real
though like I do I do I do put a lot of
work in my job you know it's definitely
more than 40 hours per
week I should count it once I should get
myself like a timer thingy a timer
clock and see calculate how much I work
but it really depends like I think it's
generally always over 40 hours but
there's some weeks that are crazier than
others
[Music]
would be interesting
huh
[Music]
H
yeah maybe one day I'll try that but I
would definitely also count like any
time I'm on on like Twitter or so
because like I'm literally sometimes I'm
scrolling for like 20 minutes to give
you guys all likees
it takes a lot of
time cuz I have to aim my finger has to
what
why why would you do that
OBS oh my
God my OBS disconnected do you hear me
hello you I'm already okay this is so
weird this weird
delay yeah so you heard that I had to
aim with my finger
right cuz yeah you know I have to like
and I accidentally don't aim right I
accidentally open the tweet and then I
have to go back and no but it really
takes more time than you might think
especially when I'm like trying to read
what you guys are saying
properly
so but even if I don't give you guys
likes on some days it doesn't mean I'm
not reading it but I mean recently it's
just been a lot and so maybe maybe I
wasn't giving you guys likes for
everything but I'm still going through
stuff you
[Music]
know but yeah it's definitely work like
that's social media like that's
literally what like social media people
do all day like people who are social
media PR whatever in their jobs
yeah um when I'm on Twitter and like
looking for fan art you know that's fan
interaction yeah looking at what you
guys are writing to me some I I if
anything I use Twitter probably a lot
more than a lot of other members like
cuz I reply to you guys
sometimes there's more more social
interaction there than it needs to be I
don't have to do all of that but I want
to but I will say that like maybe
sometimes after such a long time of 4
years maybe sometimes it just feels a
little bit tiring and repetitive
sometimes so forgive me if sometimes
maybe I'm a little bit more quiet but
it's been 4 years you
know like I'm reading everything but
like liking everything actually does
take more time so like just because I'm
not liking it doesn't mean I haven't
read it but I'm just trying to save time
like I'm lazy I'm too lazy to like
everything but I'm still reading
it don't you think that you can get away
from my
[Music]
gaze you can't
escape
yeah
yeah also there's this problem like when
I do like everything then there's this
expectation then that that will always
happen for every single tweet you write
and then that will really take up a lot
of time if I have if if I'm being
expected to do that constantly for 4
years to like every single tweet that
every single person writes to me hm so
that's why sometimes maybe I'm like a
little bit more
picky yeah
so don't have
expectations my fro gets so dry today
probably cuz I'm yapping so much no
[Music]
surprise okay okay okay let's go next
next next next next next G Kunes thank
you for for the pinky happy fourth
anniversary I can't believe it's already
been 4 years but at the same time so
much has happened that it feels like a
lot
more wish you the greatest fifth year
you can possibly imagine C forever yeah
like now we're in the fifth
year the fifth year is going on as we
speak we got to make the most of it JY
are you ready are you ready put on your
seat bels buckle up let's [\h__\h] go
Chey kunas m
exciting it's past midnight yeah that's
okay like I've been up at the craziest
hours I think I will show up for some of
the later Seven Days Seven dies Seven
Days to Die
streams
cuz there's like some later ones
scheduled
like but only two like late as
in uh evening jst that's the good time
but the in the middle of the night time
is like the main time but we'll see I'll
decide like on the goal like after one
or two sessions do I still feel like you
know streaming this at 3:00 a.m. or 2:
a.m. again the next day we will see we
will see I do kind of want to spend at
least one of the weekend days playing
Zelda to be
honest during the day
so I think I'll at least skip one of the
weekend days to
play
[Music]
Zelda yeah most people are just um going
to play at
the uh PST like Prime Time time which is
you know
understandable I just thought a few more
people would join the other time slot
too but it doesn't look like it so far
and there's no point in me playing alone
because I literally can't play alone I
literally can't because this game I
don't know if you guys know but
uh what was it 1 minute equals 1 hour in
the
game or 10 minutes I'm not sure but
there's like zombie
rushes and you literally can't handle
that alone so there have to be more than
one player at least maybe I did three
plus so yeah yeah there's like a certain
time when uh the zombies show up like a
like a uh and when if nobody's online
the time will not elapse but if even
just one person is online the time will
continue oh yeah 1 hour one day oh yeah
and so every seven no
one every 7 hours I guess
so yeah but yeah I if I also if I'm like
online at different times than what we
have discussed then what they discussed
for when they plan like they planned it
out so that they know kind of when the
zombie rushes would be like after 3
hours of playing or whatever
so yeah I can't really start earlier
either because if I'm starting earlier
and playing alone then the time will
elapse earlier and then the zombie
rushes will happen earlier and you know
it kind of messes things up so I kind of
have to go along with what they're
doing but we'll see we'll see my sleep
schedule is still [\h__\h] up so why not
just play in the middle of the night a
little
bit but I'm probably going to do
a uh a personal like deadline like I'm
not going to play past 5:00 a.m. or so
[\h__\h]
that cuz if even if I'm awake until like
600 7 800 a.m. these days for whatever
reason uh if I stream until that time
that means I'm staying up even longer
because I can't just immediately fall
asleep the moment I end my
stream I usually need like some time to
eat
dinner and then some time to wind down
so that adds like I don't know another
two hours or
so usually sometimes even 3 hours so
mhm it's not a good idea
to end so late
yeah we'll see how it goes I will be
I'll try to be spontaneous that's why
there's no
schedule but don't worry I'm not even
planning to join every day I want to
play Zelda on one day I want to play
Zelda I don't even know if we have time
for bakali this week though I feel like
maybe
not but I want to play ta this
[Music]
week dinner is whenever I say it's
dinner breakfast is whenever what time
it is after I wake up the first meal I
eat lunch is the second meal I eat even
if it is 8:00 p.m. that is still lunch
if it's my second meal I eat and dinner
will still be dinner even if it's at
3:00 a.m. my time as long as it is the
third meal I eat it doesn't matter when
it
is simple as that how do you think
people live who uh work the night chip
in hotels or uh gas stations or whatever
there's people who live like this damn
girl you live like this yeah
yeah and it's still breakfast for them
and it's still dinner for them whenever
it is
dinner yeah well I know I know like some
people might not be happy with those
streaming times but I've been back to
normal streaming already things are
chill
so don't worry it will also go back to
its origin or original time if I don't
participate in any of these projects I'm
going to get complaints too I'm going to
get complaints like oh why is Tak not
participating in any of this no wonder
she doesn't have
friends I can't make everyone happy
exactly I literally cannot make everyone
happy why why do I feel like I'm talking
like I'm drunk
can't make everyone happy but yeah we'll
play the game we'll have some fun late
at
night and then after a few days it'll be
over and then we can go back to our
usual streaming
[Music]
C so
true did you have a Red Bull I did not
cuz I try to avoid drinking energy
drinks as you guys know as much as I can
so here we go let's continue Rama B
thanks for the pinky for your watching
Rama streams your streams really helped
me during hard personal times onto four
more years of w kfp okay I guess the
contract has been signed thank you r b
yipp I appreciate it let's go
together come back to Texas when have I
been to
Texas uh by
B been to Virtual
Texas happy 4th anniversary K where did
the time go I remember when I first
started watching you in
college wait are you not in college
anymore did you have a graduation it's
so [\h__\h] crazy when people move on in
life during these four
years that would be
insane to think about that you're just
as inspiring and entertaining to me
today as you were back then even more
perhaps I would say so too maybe even I
don't know maybe a little bit you
graduated in 2021
wao that's so long ago but now you
probably have two kids and
retired damn wow that's crazy keeping
you your Lov so much thank you now thank
you for even for Life Changes still you
know Lifestyle Changes life changes so
still watching me still making time to
watch me W
priority
right I mean sometimes you can't even
though you want to right like when your
life Chang is like going to the [\h__\h]
military why would you do
that
why long time lurker here it's been
crazy for you thank
[Music]
you indeed
indeed okay thank you for your
support let's go what will you graduate
next
na first college what's next
ehh what will it be what will you next
big life change be that I will be part
of
no I'm not out of the pre why do you
have to put salt into the
wound I didn't even know that I was
still why why would you do
[Music]
that unnecessary comment but I am I
think uh one one3 or so through at least
chocolate Insomniac thanks for the right
of chat 4 years already I still remember
when we were at the first anniversary
stream there has been so many wonderful
moments with you and kfp thank you for
bringing us happiness I'll continue to
support you on stream and at cons and
concerts happy anniversary my
come thank you maybe by the time of the
fifth year anniversary will finally have
finished bucket got tell you watch long
ow
ow ow my sides are
stinging me why is somebody stabbing why
are you guys stabbing oh oh wa now my
chest I I have having a heart
attack
a calm down please do not stab
me ghosts of the
past
oh I think I need to eat
food [\h__\h] this is going to be the end of
me this Super Chat reading is going to
be the end of me
chat maybe it's the side effects of me
not being done past midnight the
Cinderella side
[Music]
effect it's okay I'm going to go a
little bit more but thank you chocolate
on no I think we should be done by the
end of the year
hopefully at least with the seasons the
old Seasons let's do our
best thank you for your
support of the
pinky happy anniversary Tel four years
of Wawa four years of
Love non-stop entertainment laughter and
a hardworking Phoenix thank you for
always being yourself cuz that's the way
we love you the most I'm ready to follow
my OSI for many more years KY loves
you thank
you would you still love me if I was a
worm
hopefully thank
you for the sweet words I saw you so
excited when uh during the Italian
lesson that's when fro fro comes out and
it's like let's f fuing
go I'm
glad maybe
probably we've been over this but yes
what kind of worm a Gummy Worm but if I
was a gumy worm I would be gone by now
cuz froggy wa would have eaten me
someone stop
her war and Nashi as long as you can
tangent I would love you as anything a
oh
tangent that sounds like a worm to
Me Maybe I would be a worm made out of
tangents letters like a graphic design
worm just a long long long long long
tangent can you visualize it maybe then
froggy waa wouldn't eat me though
thank
God a brain worm no no that's different
but I surely do have
those moon dog thanks for the pinky four
years wow wow wow you've achieved so
many incredible things Freed's albums
concerts Etc and have grown into an
incredible talented Phoenix I'm super
proud to call you my Kami ooshi you've
definitely help me become a better and
Kinder person Kinder
person Kinder person
let's say that's you're you've become a
Kinder chocolate kind of person me too
man me too always husband I love Kinder
chocolate I'm losing it chat I'm losing
it even when my life has been getting
busier I'll try to support and cheer you
on has your life been getting busier now
why tell me the reason and I shall get
rid of
[Music]
it thank you for continuing to support
me moon
dog oh really why does it
hurt just a little bit not too bad I can
survive I'm
[Music]
a I'm a phoenix dipley thanks for the r
Super Chat
oh when I scroll down there's not that
many pinks and reds anymore like there's
a lot of yellows and oranges in between
that's good to know not that we'll get
there necessarily
but diply says in the red super chat
happy anniversary W I have only been
here damn it wait anniversary with the
forest a
[\h__\h] why didn't I do that that's the
hashtag [\h__\h]
that was right there in front of my
eyes I've only been here 2 years what I
think this is not the first time I'm
shocked about that but seeing how much
hen has grown shows just how much you've
put in from the beginning mhm my made is
all possible you're so important to
every Ian fan kfp or not I'm so proud of
you you really think so I wouldn't say
everyone but a lot of them I hope they
see it that way thank you very much
[Music]
anniversary man I lost my chance why
didn't you tell me earlier
dipply press for
anniversary oh thank
you thank you D feels like you've been
around for 4 years this probably also
not the first time I said that is it I'm
getting I'm getting dja V R thank you
for the two Pinky
happy four vaav versary nice nice that
sounds good too in all these four years
no one else has ever made me smile and
the
happiest you
mean no one has ever made you smile as
much as I have right cuz otherwise
that's
sad no one made you smile besides
me that's [\h__\h] up in four years that's
[\h__\h] up
don't be sad friend don't be
[Music]
sad make him happy guys let's make him
happy but yeah we understand what you
mean all the laughs all the memories all
the amazing things you've done and
worked so hard on the past four years
has made this chicken ever so happy and
thankful to have been part of your
journey here in Hollow I'm grateful for
that too thank you for all the love Ki I
only wish we can share as much love back
as you have for all of kfp can love
forever thank
you thank you thank you no sad rad happy
rad thank you so much for the sweet
support I do get a lot of love back from
you guys so don't worry about
[Music]
that thank you w
wor hard to say that word
too for you than Trevor J thanks for the
re chat Trevor I saw like a video of
this huge snow owl today on my Twitter I
was like is this AI because do these do
these snow owls get that [\h__\h] big it
was the size of half a human body and it
was pretty wide too but it was very tall
do they really get that huge that's
insane I think maybe rare oh that oh you
saw it too okay it wasn't I knew it like
there's no [\h__\h] way they can get that
big that would be insane like you'd see
those [\h__\h] out in the wild in the in
the in the forest and You' be like okay
my life is over I guess if you're that
big you don't need to eat [\h__\h] mice
and rats anymore you can just eat a
[\h__\h]
human
huh guess it's over guess I'll
die no [\h__\h] snow o that is Owl that
is as big as a [\h__\h]
12-year-old would be honestly I would
love to hug that thing though that looks
very huggable extremely and why do you
guys always see the same things as
me Mama
Mia maybe the Internet isn't as big as
we think it is it's not as vast as we
think it is huh crazy
internet
small yeah well Wings Spang of course
they can be really wide but that thing
you don't even understand that thing was
huge that thing was
terrifying well thank God that wasn't
real I was really doubting it but it
didn't look like AI to me because it was
like really good quality but everything
is [\h__\h] AI these days don't trust it
guys don't trust anything on the
internet like for real you literally
can't trust [\h__\h] on the internet
anymore 4 years ago it wasn't this bad
yet look where we have ended up in after
four years Mama Mia the world is going
to [\h__\h] while we're here having fun
streaming ignoring that the world is
burning good night 7even G7
oh thanks for the memberships by the way
I'm just being extra dramatic right now
but doesn't it somehow feel like we're
in a [\h__\h] bubble you guys watching me
stream every day I'm streaming every day
from home we're all having a good time
we're just ignoring how the world is
[\h__\h] burning out there it's a nice
bubble to be
in I
guess thank you thank you thank you
membersip
[Music]
gift yeah I'm kind of right though
uh
yeah in so many ways oh well who knew
bird watching could make time fly by so
swiftly fly
by four years in the blink of an epie oh
that's a bird too right with' non-stop
squawking I've enjoyed your journey so
far and my binoculars are ready to keep
viewing owl that lies ahead for you from
a save distance what do you mean safe
distance do you feel do you feel in
danger because of
me why I wouldn't know
why happy
anniversary thank you wow you brought
out the big guns again for this one but
I don't know why you feel so frightened
why are you so scared Trev G why are you
so scared of
me don't be scared don't be scared now
don't stay away from me come
closer thank
you that's what happens when you get
closer you get a kiss that's nothing bad
it's good trust
[Music]
me Cru thanks for the red chat happy 4th
anniversary
Patrona it's me is that me that's me I
was sitting in the gym before the stream
thinking about how much energy and
motivation you've given me these last
four years yeah I mean I believe you
you've been hitting the gym so hard stop
hitting it what did it do to you try to
hit on things that are more on your
level in terms of size I mean cuz the
gym is [\h__\h] huge maybe I mean I guess
small human chicken hitting on a Jim is
honestly you're you're not in the
advantage
so I wouldn't recommend
it the Jim knows what it did Jim Jimmy
what did Jimmy
do Li I'm talking about the G ym but
yeah a funny funny way of
misunderstanding that uh all the cons
and concerts all the other fans I met
and just how grateful I am towards you
love you and thank you boss thank you
I'm so glad that you have been living
your best life it seems I hope that will
never
change now stop hitting
Jimmy but keep on hitting the
gym India Taylor D J thank you for the
pinky happy anniversary W once I asked
you Edon about kfp what's your favorite
thing about us what can we do better
what do you want to see more as you saw
into another amazing here is there
anything else you'd ask of your
chickens um
H what can you do better well generally
uh I think it's just a tiny tiny tiny
tiny minority in some you know small
tiny tiny cases but uh don't stress me
out about my stream times and my game
choices and a lack or too much of uh
collaborations or so
but that's really just
like yeah rare
like maybe like here and there there's
like maybe one person or two people or
so um I'm trying my best always to make
everybody happy you know um so yeah and
um besides
that h
no I'm saying yeah some people want more
collabs but some people want less
collabs so there's people complaining
about both things but I think I'm not
doing too much or too little I think
it's fine the way it is
so but whenever I'm in Japan I like to
take the opportunity to do more collabs
as well you know
[Music]
uh but yeah I don't know I mean yeah
maybe a little bit of that talk about
the Twitter likes uh could
be put up there don't just don't worry
um I'm still there I'm still like
checking everything just think about
think
about you know I'm still watching you
I'm still watching what you're doing I'm
watching your every step so I
mean yeah
[Music]
um thank you so much
hectic collapse are fun
[Music]
yeah rings of power yeah oh yeah yeah
why don't you watch rings of power huh
huh maybe that's what I would like to
see more you watching rings of
power exactly that is a good point to
bring up thank you and then my favorite
thing about you guys M I don't know what
I said back then maybe I would say the
same thing uh if I am saying the same
thing then that's lame I guess but you
guys are so
passionate and you guys are so sweet
like
titty you get you get along so well
seemingly it's so nice to see you guys
like interact at
conventions when I'm hiding behind the
tree and peeking
you guys don't notice that I'm standing
right there I see you guys doing funny
things yeah uh what no I'm not there
but it's nice to see it for like Vlogs
and stuff and just like little videos
and pictures on
Twitter you guys telling me you went to
restaurant or to cut a get together or
so it's so
[Music]
cute yeah
yeah so I don't know it's really just
nice to see the community being a
community and thank you for supporting
my music so much right now um as as
always that's
something that I appreciate a lot about
you
guys cuz my music you know it's
important to me I I want to make more
music
and I'm glad you guys are supporting me
in those
Endeavors yeah but let's move on Golden
I ding for the pinky happy anniversary
thanks for working your ass off this
year once again see I have to keep on
adding the ass because I keep on working
it off and then it has to be like
continuously added back again it's it's
really really tie hand I'll send the
rest in a week or two or uh so please
use this time to drink snack and pet
c those are not close by but that's so
sweet of you to think of me golden I
what the
hell you're nice you're so nice so
considerate so that's why
you makes sense huh yeah here I'll take
a
[Music]
sippy Mississippi
n that Mirage ass no I already saw it
gone again
today it's messed
up you call thanks for the red chat with
do some emojis thank you you
co thank you so much and go thanks for
the r Super Chat as well happy
anniversary W thank you for countless of
Hours of Happiness you've brought to my
life life I wish you the best from the
bottom of my heart thank you you've also
been around for so long thank you so
much
yay thanks for always being around and
guys hopefully
forever K you conf the pinky hi W I
wasn't here at the beginning 4 years ago
how dare you but since I've been here
since I've been
here you and the rest of myth has been a
source of inspiration to me sorry thank
you for everything you do and happy four
years to you and the rest of Legend of
the Legendary myth of whole life thank
you we've made it together for 4
years yeah it was a long
journey thank you so much for sticking
through with us through it I can't speak
I don't know if that was correct but you
know what I mean thank you thank you
kiun you are you are very
kind now we have a bunch of non- Pinks
non oh my God
golden wow
damnes thanks the
pinky happy anniversary Kiana ever since
myth
debuted I've had a lot more things to
look forward to every day it's been four
4 years now and I can't wait to see
what's in store for our fifth hopefully
it's a little more spread out
though
yeah oh God I'm
dreading already some
stuff I'm still kind of uncertain about
the next two or three months what's
going to happen I honestly don't
know uh but we we'll
see surely January February will be a
little bit more chill right I think so
now it's chill let's enjoy the moment
right thank you for the support I hope
that I will continue to
be the thing that you wake up to that
you're like w w on the
T C still thanks for the r of CH happy
four years M time really does fly by
when you're having a good time here's
not to four years but to forever oh god
oh no what did I sign up
for I am not signing that contract
forever but let's go through it with the
the spirit of forever and that will
bring us surely very far thank you so
much for the support
Ronin Dan our rest Dan Dominic K Dan
salubrious beats I'm like more than
halfway through I think guys or or am I
maybe maybe not maybe halfway through
celebr spe action for the
pinky wow I see that four years ago who
would have thought I'd someday be
wearing a coat with you on it Oh you
mean you call it a
coat smell like
girl
happy waving around light stick scream
pineapple I've met so many cool
[Music]
people sorry I died a
little I was wondering if you guys would
be worried if I just died right there
for a sneeze were you worried you don't
seem worried
[Music]
you you don't seem worried at
all there's chat delay and I just don't
see any worriedness really much
anything okay I guess you're not worried
cuz I'm a phoenix why would you be
worried nobody's bringing that up
[Music]
longer silence I couldn't stay silenced
longer for
that I met so many cool people and had
uncountable new experiences in kfb love
you thank you for being you thank you
too I believe every word you
said I believe you cuz that's really
something if you weren't in this culture
before you imagine telling yourself from
five years ago like showing yourself
from five years ago a picture of you
enjoying a [\h__\h] V tuer whatever the
[\h__\h] that is and at that time you were
not aware of it
probably like being in a in a like a
[\h__\h] Concert
Hall amongst all these other people
swaying around light sticks in a [\h__\h]
H happy colorful happy
you'd be admitting yourself to a
mental yeah cheering on
like these virtual anime girls on the
screen what would you from 5 years ago
say to this picture of you like what the
heck is going
on that' be so
funny that's such a funny font yeah you
joined the cult what do you mean it's
like you joined the cold you did you
definitely did
[Music]
I knew like nothing about idols and
stuff of her whole life I'd never
believed it right like there's nothing
wrong with it but it's just so funny how
probably most of you guys were not
living this kind of life before like
idols and animal YouTubers like maybe
you liked anime before but still this is
very
different it's so
crazy it's so crazy
I wouldn't really believe where I am now
either 5 years ago if someone would have
told me I would be here now working from
home comfortably for 4
years traveling a lot for my job and
also for fun doing this job as a virtual
YouTuber which means virtual virtual
YouTuber I guess cuz I'm saying it
twice that I I don't think I would be
able to believe that even
[Music]
yeah cuz 5 years ago I mean I was
watching uh like P Senai and so on
before I joined for a while uh but I
think I I really just uh started
watching actively half a year before I
joined so that's four and a half years
ago 5 years ago I don't think I knew
what YouTubers were I mean I knew kizuna
I but I don't think get registered with
me what vtubers were and that she is one
and stuff like
that and that it's a thing I don't think
I knew it was a
thing
[Music]
maybe you were afraid to enjoy it your
family's super religious intolerant but
there's nothing not religious about me I
am I am the
most um how to stay familyfriendly
religious clean person there
is but the way you put it though it's
funny it makes it seem like we're Satan
we to us are
Satan therefore not acceptable by
religious
[Music]
families we're straight from hell and we
are dragging you into it come with us
they call it rabbit hole but they don't
tell you it's [\h__\h] hell
[Music]
guys yeah what iron Mouse is not what do
you what do you say she's a little I
don't know what she's a mouse and she's
like like uh well she's not she's she's
not Satan what are you
saying that's not her character is
lore is it she's a demon well but that's
not quite the
same devil devil yeah she's not
Satan that's not the same she's not
Satan
V iron
Mouse oh shut up why did I get logged
out doesn't even say what she is here
uh but yeah she's not officially like
Satan right
so this doesn't hold up
guys
what what I'm just I'm just I'm just
trying to say it like the way you guys
would probably say
[Music]
it should I just say it in German
Satan
Satan oh she wait she spells it like
that you're not making fun of
[Music]
me oh
Oh I thought you guys were just making
fun of me
again see this is very confusing guys
cuz you do make fun of me sometimes for
how I say
things
aha Mama
Mia
confusing oh
um
[Music]
anyway there so many super
chats Ricky t7 one fre D jaob 47 D for
the pinky four years ago I I was
watching a I was watching subu and suici
clips and getting into Gen 5 I would
have thought you were crazy if you told
me there would be any Ian
bread what the hell sorry I thought a
cat jumped on my chair but that was just
me a really cool bird who off collabs of
s and I'd get them to see in New York
congrats thank you wow you were already
quite into it huh damn so I wasn't your
first okay cuz I'm not special
okay well then thank you for the
support I was very new around Gen 5 yeah
really Gen 5 gen 5 was uh like NY gen
right sometimes it gets confusing to
combine the numbers at these times with
the members
[Music]
oh wo w
w
okay how are you guys doing are you guys
bored by me reading super chats yet I
hope you're not you're okay I hope
you're okay Sai thanks for the r Super
Chat it's been 4 years since I first
watched the debut of a peculiar orange
anime girl hm I wonder who we celebrate
your accomplishments so far and here's
your another year of Wawa huzzah huzzah
huzzah you good okay
you're hungry too me too thank you s h
thank you I shall celebrate your
accomplishments too look at you you've
grown so much too you went from egg
to armor or are you already golden let
me see cuz in hyzer it's armor but you
might have already changed as
well let me see you let me pick you up
and look at you my little
chicken are you here let me look at you
let me get a good look at
you let me look at
you where are
you are you
here I don't
see I don't
see Happ no I was just going to lean
down squat squat for you no happies not
that easily okay I don't see you but who
knows no
squat anyway thank you so much
M man to this day I wonder who that
peculiar orange enemy girl is that you
were talking about mental joury thank
you for the red super chat four years
wow as always I have so much to say but
so little text for now so just well done
so proud of you and what you have
achieved I'm sure you could never even
imagine four years yet here we are going
stronger than ever to four more press
four care be
forever press four press four to receive
another four years of takanashi Kiara
four thank
you you have cracked the SE secret code
there they go there they
go it only works like once at a time you
have to wait up the four years and then
you can press four
again Le thanks for pinking happy for
years SW love thank you for all the
Comfort you've provided me over the
years what have you been lying on me or
what am I your
payow get off just kidding sorry I'm not
funny anymore for everything you do
here's some many more memories in the
future much love to you thank you much
love back to you
I would give you kisses but it wasn't
the red so now I'm like how do I express
this there you
go friendly neighborhood lesbian
Vamp SW the Ste the steel D Lord EV D
Elite fighting chicken
D wa for another wave of other super
jets psychotronic Co thank you for the
pinky oh that's is good yeah
yeah Ling long thanks for the pinky also
happy fourth anniversary well thank you
very much how kind of you appreciate
it
arm arade H thanks I blessed to watch
your stream on
World of Warcraft at
dawn thank you
Ki
[Music]
what
what it's been a while since we last
played World of
Warcraft what do you
mean he tripping but imagine
though hm
[Music]
H I'm
confused but he's got a
point we should play World of Warcraft
thank
youu ter d d lasarus Chris d/t
dangus Rex thanks for the red
wow hey I'm so far C four years ago you
debuted in Holan and have since changed
me oh wow you're beautiful oh have
incredible company Oh you mean myth and
a wonderful
Community well that's you while I'm not
the executive CEO anymore I wish you
well in your future endeavors of CF and
your talent career thank you co what do
you
mean where did did you
quit did you change your job description
where are you going why does it sound
like you're not generally around any
anymore maybe you should
be give me a
chance take a chance on me take a chance
on
me if you love me watch my streams W on
demand doesn't have to be live just
watch archive take a chance on me take a
chance on
me anytime you're welcome
anytime thank you for the support
golden i d Dax Jaden thanks for the
pinky happy four years anniversary T I
may have not been here for all of them
being a rookie kfp rookie nah but I will
be here from now on you're my C oi let's
[\h__\h] go
hey I just did like this move with my
like arm like pulling it in like the
elbow towards the inside yeah you know
what I mean cuz I'm that pumped about
that thank you I mean it though thank
you new people who make me their Koshi I
wouldn't call you new anymore but still
thank you let's [\h__\h] go the kerson
show thanks for the r chat it's already
been 4 years since I've been captured I
mean employed at KP wow you
[Music]
mean you mean birthed by me eh raised by
me eh cared for by me
mhm thank you for everything poal you're
welcome you're
welcome I raised
you all
alone all of you all these
children
yeah I
[Music]
did I made you to who you are today when
I say birth you you I just mean the egg
came from somewhere and I took those
eggs in and I sat on them for hours and
hours making them hot and then they have
been cracked and then they imprinted on
me I basically birthed you you're still
adopted but I bed you cuz if without me
you would not have ever come out of that
egg Mama yeah Mama yep that's me
Mama Mama Mama Mama I did not see you
somebody gave you up for adoption all of
you I adopted you I took you under my
wing but I do not lay eggs how many
times do I have to tell you are you
listening at all when I tell you this in
the
past mama
mama mama yes it is me it is I your
mommy
mama
mama Co is your
sister I guess I don't know she's also
adopted so you're not like related by
blood that's for
sure
mama no you should still call me Tanto
you can only call me Mama during your
egg or or chick face not now most of you
are grown up grown ass chicks grown ass
chickens or hybrid
phoenixes this family tree is weird uh
I've seen weirder family trees like look
at [\h__\h] house of the
Dragon uh there's nothing weirder than
that thank you Kim showood
d d am D or D if not the C than for the
pinky going to make me first post again
as if I could have ever stopped you
thank
you f thank you for the red super
chat that's a circle not
a I guess
oh a lot of you guys are saying that
[Music]
hello thank you for visiting me is it
visitation hours
again I love you I love
you she's I was just sing like I haven't
touched her wet pot in a
while you can go you can go now thanks
[Music]
that hasn't happened in a while it's so
nice of her to come to me right after
she went to the toilet with her wet butt
so nice of her to think of
me I love
her I love her more than anything
[Music]
Nathan cotton sent a red Super Chat
saying hi attention I was going to write
a nice wholesome heartfelt message about
happening onto finding my Koshi 4 years
ago from some fire emblems free houses
clip clip but I got F distracted who
knew black and orange went together
so so are you ever going to elaborate on
that or are you just forever distracted
well understandable have a nice day her
dreams might kill you no no we are way
past it don't worry you guys are so
dramatic you don't even
know what parts of me she has
touched or so what do you know don't be
so dramatic I'm here to read super chats
yeah
[Music]
understand it's too late for me guys not
too late for you but it's too late for
me
anyway I'm going
to die from no honestly what the hell
like what what are you talking about I'm
not going to die
from shut up like come on let me let me
be disgusting with my cats it's not my
fault anyway that she comes to me right
after the toilet it's not my fault and I
have something to do I can't leave my
workplace I'm literally chained to my
chair you have changed me onto it it was
you who put on these shackles or
whatever the word is on
me I am imprisoned by
you you it's you and now now you think
it's
funny when my cat
jumps onto me with her wet
butt while I suffer no I don't suffer
but you're trying to make me suffer but
you can't my bond between me and my cat
is
stronger stronger than
anything
saon you can't you
cannot you will be the end of
yourself the free people will
always stay away from you
s what sorry what where am I what me
what are you talking about give me the
nine I will not give me the nine no no I
will cut off my fingers before I give
you the
nine nothing you can do to make you give
me the
Rings I'll kill
myself gadriel where are you let me give
you the
Rings
gadriel gadriel run I will die with my
city just like the Titanic boat person I
will die with it because that's a cool
thing to
do ma' this is a can't
why don't you guys watch R of power why
why why
why uh sorry um I had a little bit of an
episode there um let me uh let
me wind
[Music]
back I was both gadal and cimro can I
please be credited for both of my roles
please RAV
D Rainer dun for the right Super Chat
happy fourth anniversary T your hard
work and creativity continue to inspire
us all thank you for making our days
brighter here us for many more years of
success and happiness this message was
sent by our long year loyal listener
reer thank you so much for for your
support over the long time and I hope
you will continue to be a big fan of my
show thank you very much uh the next
listener called in and
said that their name is Black penguin
dun thank you and D Hood thank you for
the pink letter that you have sent
us oh you're requesting a song I see yes
we haven't played song for a few hours
now so sure let's play that song Let's
Go please enjoy the song requested by
Doug
[Music]
Hood me spending oh spending all my
money on
her wow that was great thank you so much
for that throwback we love the classics
don't we so much incredible Wawa Coro
Divine voice and point of views you
totally spoil us
Wawa why thank you I couldn't have done
it without you thank you so much for
supporting
takanashi kiawa Radio takanashi K
radio thank you for your
[Music]
support day super chats are never ending
oh my God nobody they're I'm close to it
but I don't want to read them anymore
[Music]
now I quit I
quit I
quit I you can't fire me I
[Music]
quit h
no you can't make me no you can't make
me yeah it's 1:00 a.m. let's let's um I
can't extend my Cinderella time that
much longer right now I need to
eat you fire
me are you sure about that are you sure
about
that remember who threw you who threw
you into the
fire I had an episode then too when I
did that I thought you were a ring and I
was going to throw you into the fire to
save Middle
Earth and it turns out you were just a
chicken and then it was all an accident
but that was kind of fun so then I
thought ah you know what actually this
is kind of delicious I will throw some
more chickens into the fire even if this
is not Middle Earth fun fun it brings a
good
result what do you mean onion rings you
are
chicken not onion
I am on
[Music]
in I think we have onion rings on the
menu so I don't know what you mean we
need onion rings no we
[Music]
don't all right my fellow
Travelers we have traveled so far in our
wounds internally and externally
are making us weaker day by day perhaps
we should take a
rest stay a while and don't listen stop
listening this ends
now as a Tales of protagonist once
said this ends
now I will
take my leaf as I am losing
[Music]
it these are the side effects of super
chats to a weak weak Tak
Shikara although I had
fun I did have a good
time reading your wise words to me thank
you very much I shall now go to
what was it called again the Elven place
I would like to seek
shelter at a peaceful safe
environment please remind me of my
destination Rivendell it is to Rivendell
I shall
March hopefully they will accept
me as they are a little bit
racist towards non
elves but they are good
[Music]
people taking the hits the eyes and God
we're taking the hits the eyes and God
we're
taking we're taking the H
to taking theit to guard taking theit to
guard taking the to I guard guard guard
guard
[Music]
yipp in German we
say Al in
I was thinking of saying something else
but that always confuses you guys so I'm
just going to say
off please buy my merchandise which is
on my right side from your
POV and uh perhaps the link is perhaps
in the description I'm not sure about it
maybe not maybe this um otherwise it's
on my
Twitter thank
you for accompanying
me but all good things come to an
[Music]
end bye-bye
w e
[Music]
no