n
[Music]
w
oh
[Music]
K
caty
hello hello once
again it feels like it's been a
while going to make myself
bigger
hello on
I'm gecko
colored
true you're so right actually I wasn't
on purpose but I don't know I really
like my frog frog
hoodie it's not quite a hoodie actually
not like your guys's hoodie that some of
you have my I guess my budget was
limited I could not add sleeves and a
proper body part to
it m
so one might say your guys's frog hoodie
is better than mine man mine's just a
mantle uhhuh a
p
okay hello hello
hello it seems like I have hacked
mind hacked myself into the YouTube url
system to make it show Mirage but I've
kind of failed
through the uh process of it and now
it's just saying
Mir good attempt though right I I tried
it's uh
resembling what I wanted to
do it lagged out Oh I thought it was
just me no everything lagged out on my
side too here is the schedule of the
week yay yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah kind of a chill schedule just
because uh well today no
yesterday well the past two nights my
mom was
here and today she left in the
afternoon
and why do I have the description logo
oh whatever I guess I don't need it if
it doesn't show up in front of my face
oh I forgot I had the
hand I forgot to have ah but I want to
hold
Jimmy oh well I guess I'll hold Jimmy in
a different
way oh no wait uh that I can still have
the Frog
hoodie but I need
to where is the Jimmy hand did I put it
the
what was I
wearing what was I
wearing why is everything
gone why is everything
gone did you just freeze uh yeah but
that's probably on
purpose
H sorry the program is kind of laggy
where's the hand oh there it is
uh right it's not long enough but I
guess down here is fine
actually oh yeah oh yeah does that look
good Jimmy is still here with us yay I
turned Jimmy into a
card you don't like that fate do you
that's a terrible terrible fate unless
you really like card games and maybe
maybe this is what happens to you if you
play too much of that TC g
game mhm be careful
guys careful a little bit more in the
left I don't know if I
will oh yeah here's
fine would you guys like to be in a card
and be played by people you'll
constantly be played by people that's
not something what you really want to in
real life right M yeah what nah don't be
lying to me you don't want to be a
card if anything you would only want to
be my
card yeah let's not do it but yeah uh
today inscription tomorrow Mirage 1
million commemoratory 3D stream yay I
will be in 3D showing off a really cute
Mirage
model so cute ah you got to come to
check it out because then the the facial
facial expressions are also really
cute
yeah it's so cute we're going to dance a
little bit we're going to sing a little
bit probably and and just show off the
cute model not too long of a stream
again because I mean the 3D always kind
of stops me from going too long anyway
[Music]
in the channel of gy we're back we're so
back I heard you guys have been playing
a little bit still too very nice very
nice so we can play again to again
together
mhm and then Friday well the concert is
on Saturday before
Diablo but uh well uh I wanted to to
stream on Friday but even if I wanted to
I wouldn't have been permitted to unless
I streamed like really early and I was
like
no so it just kind of works out like
that uh did you see Elena's playing
other members are starting
what what you already
played what the [\h__\h]
Rea goes to
Hyer way is she already ah a she ah and
members she's playing members right
now uh she can join us if but it it's
probably a shitty time when we're
playing it it's going to be in middle of
the night for her but we can maybe do
another stream where we um damn what
is she playing it because she's like
into Eden Eternal I can imagine her
having played Eden Eternal when she was
younger when it was popular I can kind
of
Imagine let me what the [\h__\h] I you know
I got the perms for this after like
asking again and again putting in the
perms again and and again several times
of over the course of several months and
I had to to get the staff's personal
attention uh and follow-ups because
otherwise it was useless they had to
like do different had to do things
differently it seems different than
usual did you get me those
perms I'm amazed that uh I'm Not The
Only One using them now
Raina you are playing Eden Eternal
it kind of fits her I I can imagine her
liking those kind of games that makes
sense I can also imagine her playing
like other kind of anime
MPGs this kind of
fits members I didn't know it was also
members okay recently we got like okay
for members for a long time always
because like back in the
day I I would say I had some influence
in this
minimally only a little bit um but uh
I our our perm system has changed
several times over the past years but uh
there was a time where it was like uh an
an Excel
sheet and in the Excel sheet it would
say which games are okay for members and
back then we obviously had of course way
less games than now and so it was a
little bit more over seeable over a
Excel sheet and so I would look there's
this one column for members okay and
just like barely any games were members
okay and I was like hey can we get more
members members like games and they were
like well you have to tell us then when
you apply for the game perms that you
want it for members only and ever since
even if I'm not playing planning to play
it on members only I've been applying
for members uh perms for every single
game that I've been generally applying
for and then and then I swear so many of
the games I applied for we got members
per for and then the list kept on
growing and growing and growing and
growing and then and then the whole
system changed and now we don't have to
write that anymore now it's just like
automatically assumed it seems and they
ask for it automatically so now now we
really have a
lot
yeah yeah I just thought well even if I
don't want to necessarily play on
members it's just good to have a bigger
variety of members only games back in
the day back in the day remember like
one of the few games we could play uh
for members only was like amus which is
great amus and Fall Guys and stuff like
that which was great but like it really
wasn't
much we didn't have so many options and
here we are now here we are now I played
amas and Fall Guys several times on
members
only hey but that's great we could do
members only grinding
streams oh [\h__\h] I didn't even think
about
that oh I think she replied me ah I used
to play e Eternal I knew was you when I
saw
it Oh my God uh this week's stream
probably is way too late for you but we
could schedule another collab for Eden
Eternal at a better time
soon where
you can
[Laughter]
join hey so cool I wonder what she used
to play like what class and so on is she
on the same server I would think so
there's only free servers and then
there's like channels within the server
but the channels you can always switch
and the server it wouldn't make any
sense for her not to go for the English
server I
think
yeah oh she made a gunsing oh that's
what GG started out as no healers but
two yeah maybe we need a heal maybe we
can drag one more girl into the boat who
who which uh em more PG lover out there
in h life English or ID uh said just
like me that there there used to be a
heel slot in mm pgs I wonder if there's
anyone
founder was she also a heel [\h__\h] just
like
me just this time I didn't go for
it wait wait and find another one to
heal us but yeah can always change class
and fans are running after us usually to
heal
[Laughter]
us
yeah I'm not a tank uh but currently in
the gigy and me combo I'm just the only
close range attacker
okay okay yep yep yep yep yep yep stop
stop stop stop um so yeah we're playing
e CH again and then world and then
Diablo uh because last week I have to I
had to uh cancel it delay it to to to
this week and we're going to not play
the DLC yet because I'm I want to finish
the main story first and then we we'll
watch
more keep yapping I missed it no watch
the V VA on
demand I got my clar class to almost
level 50
what oh no I've given you guys an
addiction oh
no what have I done what have I
done claric GL 56 oh my god oh now now
many of you are committing to healer
because
cuz you guys want to heal
me need to watch COI before member's
done why is it particularly necessary
before we watch the second order one mon
[Music]
season maybe we'll just watch them
together then the last
two they're short right you're watching
on your own time uh okay maybe I'll make
a members post and say
hey uh we'll add two k episodes to the
watch along should be okay I've got
time but yeah this week I don't know
who's going in the chat
probably maybe maybe maybe a few uh I
knew some of you guys are traveling but
yeah we're going to have World Tour stop
in Jakarta it feels like it's been a
while um but yeah World Tour World Tour
Al s s s world turn Jakarta let's go I'm
excited I'm excited
we and uh the one thing that I've been
teasing members only that I said you
will find out this week did I say you'll
find out this week I thought I I think I
least said very very soon but it got
delayed a little bit it will be next
week next week
so get hyped for that just give it a
little bit more time to cook
okay I need a little bit more cooking
time not not me particularly but yeah
sorry I'm stalling and yapping cuz I'm
just like
chilling before we get into the game
because that needs all my brain let me
Yap a little more
actually uh I I was busy with my mommy
we were so productive we did so many
things so we woke up on Monday like
around 10 I think we started with
uh I got AAS then we went to buy lots of
groceries we went to buy lots of meat
and lots of onions and stuff to make
[Music]
goulash I show the picture on Twitter
yeah of all the meat that was good meat
good good meat bought a lot of uh
groceries and then
um then we started cooking we prepared
the cooking we started cooking but it
was like a slow cooking thing throughout
the whole day so we had it cooking the
whole day the goulash M there's
different types of goulash we just made
I think a pretty typical
one pretty classic one just the uh beef
uh with like onions and added some added
some bell peppers yeah
it was so tender yeah yummy yum yum yum
and 10 let's see I had like three four
five six seven it was probably like
eight nine servings no wait actually it
might be 10 it might be 11 actually cuz
that those two were two servings per
container many servings in my
freezer now waa doesn't have to cook
every day I mean not I'm not going to
eat that every day but still it's nice
to have something in the freezer welcome
to the membership thank you you uh sorry
I'm yapping some more let me just Yap
what we did on Monday and then we can
play um so then after preparing setting
up the food and it was like cooking
cooking cooking cooking and then we went
to uh oh maybe what did we do first I
don't know but one of the things we did
is we went to the big big store that
sells like things for your
home uh like you can buy paint you can
buy buy wood you can buy toilets you can
buy showers you can buy not
Ika a little bit more
crafty do it
yourself Hardware no I wouldn't even
call it Hardware but they have like
everything in terms of if you want to
improve your home they also have a big
garden section Etc so I went there and
we bought some Nails my mom bought some
painting stuff for herself we bought
some
um what did we buy this and that I
bought a little thing that if you put it
on the wall it
will if there's something there that you
shouldn't risk drilling into finally I
had it it would have been really useful
when uh me and RBF were putting up all
of the wall
shelves Stout finder yeah Metal s it it
sensors a lot of things really nice but
that's so dumb like I looked at we found
them on on our own right this big place
and crazy to find something I but we
found one and I looked at the prices and
it was like holy [\h__\h] like from the like
famous Brands uh the Bosch I think Bosch
brand do you guys have that in like
other countries here it's like the to go
option for a lot of products but um I
see and it was like it was uh the price
was cheaper than usual it was was
discounted but it was still like
85 or
something and I was like what the [\h__\h]
why is this so expensive oh my God and
the others were only more expensive
there were like maybe two more options
and so I go to the staff and we ask like
do you have any
others that are perhaps cheaper and the
guy is like no so we only have these two
yeah this the the only ones we have
only the ones from Bush those are the
only ones we have half an hour later of
us roaming through the whole store we
find some noname nonf famous brand
versions of it that are way cheaper
bro so I ended up getting one for how
much was it they were like I could have
gone a lot
cheaper like there were like three
versions one was able to detect most
things but not like metal behind the
wall I think so I went for the one that
was a little bit better that had metal
detection I think uh and that one was
like I don't know half the price of the
other one you could try out D no but I
could have maybe gotten another cheaper
one on Amazon I don't know but
yeah that why don't they they usually
nice did he just I'm going to give him
the benefit of the doubt and say he
probably just forgot I can't I I can't
really
believe that those uh store staff would
lie to me I really don't think so and it
was literally just like 3 m away on the
other side like the other across aisle
basically yeah he probably didn't know
or he forgot I don't think he
purposefully did that
because they they don't have a reason to
do that it's not like he was specific Al
works for
bshch or gets a commission for selling
bshch I highly doubt
that and B is nice but like I how often
am I going to use that thing and and it
works fine we tested it out and it works
fine
so yeah so we went uh buying all kinds
of stuff there and we bought like a [\h__\h]
ton of shelves like huge shelves but
they were relatively compact when they
were packed okay but I bought a lot of
shelves because For the Longest Time
time uh ever since I moved my cellar has
been absolute chaos everything just
thrown in there with like uh boxes being
half open and stuff and just stacked
partially on top of each other but
mostly just like all over the floor and
I was like I need to sort this [\h__\h] out
yeah basement and
so uh we bought a lot of shelves and I
was like worried about transport board
but we had a nice Uber and we drove it
back and then and then we started the
stacking because those were like
stacking shelves but you I thought okay
stacking shelves that sounds easier than
normal shelves where you need to drill
stuff and so on but now we had some
troubles because there were some like
weird production
flaws um where you try to stack it and
it just doesn't go in and then my mom
hammered so aggressively against the
metal cuz there out of metal and even
then like my mom was losing her
mind but we still kind of managed to
build um
three uh three 1 M long 2 m tall
shelves uh in 1 and a half
hours they're just stacking shells why
did it take us so long you wonder I
don't know it didn't feel too long M it
was okay and then I I I had such
pleasure in putting things into the
shelves and looking at how everything
was so nicely organized and sorted that
made me happy and then while all this
was happening it was still cooking
cooking cooking our food and then we
were we did some other things too um you
know how for like even before I moved
for like the recent two and a half years
I think I did not have a bathroom uh
mirror
because I told you this before but in
the previous place I was just renting
and for some reason it didn't have a
bathroom mirror and I had mirrors
elsewhere but I did not want to
risk uh damaging the tiles of a
rental uh and I yeah I just had like
other mirrors so I was like I'm not
going to do this
I'm not going to risk it and I'm also
not going to add like if I do something
permanent Like Glue it on or
whatever I don't want to add to the
value of the rental that is an absolute
scam with how expensive of a rent they
are asking for I'm not going to add to
your [\h__\h] value by adding a mirror
there should be a mirror usually there's
always a
mirror so I just like lived without a
mirror in that place for like a
year or a little bit I think it might
have been a little bit more than a year
and then I moved again this year and
February and now it's my property not
just rental so I wanted to and the thing
is I had a mirror because first I
planned to even with the rental put up a
mirror but when I when I bought the
mirror I was like not ready yet to put
it up cuz I didn't know how and it was
big and I needed help but the people
that would normally help me were
intimidated it also by destroying the
tile
so I wanted to glue it on and I bought
the glue but then so much time passed
for people to like help me that the glue
uh was um the expiration date it was
passed and my friend RBF was like uh I
don't know about the glue like if it's
expired then I don't trust it I don't
want to risk it like falling off I'm
like okay I don't know you know what
it's fine I'm just not going to add a
mirror anymore to this apartment because
I'm moving anyway cuz then I just knew I
was going to move anyway so I was like
I'm going to just drag it out and then I
came to the new place but
[Music]
then then I didn't have it so I wasn't
in such a hurry because again I had
other mirrors
and the move was so stressful already
and I was like prioritizing other things
like curtains and so on
and the kitchen and you know all kinds
of things
and two years of no M crazy right but I
mean I had other mirrors I would just
like gold and even in the in the
bathroom I just had like a small small
mirror that was like just like sitting
on the on the uh uh washing
machine yeah eyeballing the makeup no I
do my makeup on my makeup table that is
in my uh bedroom so you know I don't
really need the mirror in the bathroom
that much so I wasn't such a like
important thing but yeah then slowly I
was hoping to eventually put up the
mirror cuz I still had the
mirror from a long time ago purchased
like two and a half years
ago and uh again like the usual people
that would help me with things like my
mom she was like nah I'll help you with
a lot of things but I don't want to
damage the tile drilling into the
tile and I was like okay I'll ask RBF
RBF was also like n we we need something
proper we need to check out what kind of
tile that is and what what what exactly
we should use to drill into we need to
like really look into this but then we
never did
um yeah so again lots of time has
passed and yesterday we just said [\h__\h]
it because I eventually want to improve
the bathroom
anyway and renovate it even though it's
like newly built but it bores me the
design bores me and I eventually want to
improve it anyway and yeah also even if
a little bit of a tile because we saw we
saw a
loophole we saw a
loophole
um so
when is she going to play the
game
never
so where's my
mouse here
so these are
tiles so the
loophole was
to just try hope that it's a good
placement if we um make the
holes in between the
tiles but those lines were really small
so we had to like use a really small
drill and uh a little a tiny bit like
one millimeter
like kind of broke and like got off my
my my mom put tape over it duct tape so
that it wouldn't be too bad and then
when we ripped it off it was like it was
like like a tiny piece of the tile uh
chipped off but like really only just a
Time minutes like you can't even notice
and on top of that is the mirror now
anyway but our or I guess our original
fear was that it would like break like
this I guess I don't know if that's
really how it would break but
yeah yeah so finally after 2 and 1/2
years I have a bathroom mirror again
let's
go and that wasn't the only thing we did
so we we did the the we did we got all
the things we went grocery shopping we
went home things shopping the all the
shelves and stuff uh we put up the
mirror we put up the shelves and we uh
did some stuff in the garden that was
that I really wanted to do for a long
time something that I purchased to put
up like also several months ago was just
lying around for a long time and I was
like today's the day I want to do this
mommy help me so she helped me for a
while but that's I also did some stuff
alone and we did so many things so many
things so productive and then the food
was really good
too construction chicken excuse me
construction
Phoenix but I was so tired by the end of
the day and I noticed my my legs were
really
um uh
sore my feet and my my legs are really
sore but it was worth it because it felt
so it felt so satisfying to have some
things uh done that I really wanted to
do for a long
time several fans are telling me they're
going to the jakata concert or to the
Singapore concert from a different
country wow thank
you
what mod thanks for the membership gift
okay okay I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm
so sorry we can play it in description
now okay we can play it
now I just had to tell you about our
successful
day by the way my mom said she's going
to
uh pull an all
nighter why would she do
that my mom is pretty obsessed
with America right
now no she's not still here she's not
still here she's not pulling an all
night of
here she's so obsessed she's probably
more obsessed than me
[Music]
all right all right let's
play she's so obsessed we had some um uh
hot uh hot hot headed hot heated heated
uh discussions but I mean I mean we are
on the same side but anyway
what she's she's
excited sure
oh hello game wait wait
wa there it
is after 38
minutes y I'm sorry I'm I'm at least I'm
in good
spirits uh you guys got to help me again
okay
continue I guess ah we have to start
again from the beginning right but it
says just continue because the game will
know that I already opened up things in
the room and
on and then I have my own cards in the
game I
guess okay okay
okay was it too
loud that is pretty
loud just judging by the OBS
thing
okay I turned it down here we go oh do I
have items already what the
hell top deck GE I may choose no you may
not choose I may not choose a specific
Beast I thought instead you must now
decide on a tribe that you
prefer oh
okay
a I don't I don't even know what these
are I mean I know that these are
probably flying
uh enemies uh
cards B but where would the GE
be ah is that insect looks like a person
to me looks like giggy with the big a
yeah is that
giggy that's just
gigy or herb yeah but it looks a little
bit more you know this could be the the
the the pigtail the twin tail
this part looks a little bit more
childish I don't know what the third eye
is doing there though ELD
G lore accur gy what does her lore say
about her third eye does she have a
third
eye yeah I don't know but he's going to
give me one card for that right I don't
have to build the whole deck around it
um then whatever give me a bird Sparrow
okay randomly chosen Bird card do you
did you wish for something else no I
don't really care
thanks oh I'll take
it but let me choose more freely next
time an ancient woman emerged from
behind an oak tree she carefully laid
out intricate wood carvings then
gestured at them
bruly choose he really likes role play
he so into it wouldn't he be a
great what's it called again DM
DD for
tabletop
yeah it would be so great for
it honestly if someone like Cali had
masks like this she and if we were
playing TTR RPG's IRL she' put on masks
too probably should put on some kind of
costumes as
well to immerse
us into the lore
h ah DM or GM dunge okay so what what is
this what there's a there's but can I if
I if I click on this am I automatically
choosing it again I'm
scared a [\h__\h] yes I am aut choosing it
how do I just like read
it right click damn it you accepted the
wood Carver's offering but what isn't
did I choose a good one at least it is
useless without it second half oh okay
but you in ined that his this would not
be the last encounter with her okay oh
it's been a while I forgot that you had
to click right
click these are icons you choose what it
applies to next time you meet
her right all right what's going on here
he's got wolves why is it so red uh what
is it uh here Sprinter at the end no
that's not what I want to know that's
what the this guy
does I want I want to is there like oh
is that just the general game rule like
everybody will be now
sprinting
probably okay uh how does this work
again squirrel costs no blood so I place
a squirrel and then I sacrifice it
that's how that works right
um what does he he doesn't even have
anything out yet okay
okay could start with could start with
the Sparrow
I don't I don't know if I sometimes I'm
not sure should I place it in front of
them to attack them but then then maybe
I want to do Straight damage I don't
know uh and then oh yeah I I don't have
enough bones yet so I think that would
be my
turn right right
right ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
ding
okay we're warming up we're
um even even if I would have placed the
sparrow in front of the wolf cup but the
wolf cup can't attack the sparrow right
cuz it's
flying or is this only the way other way
around the sparrow can't attack the wolf
cup because it will just go straight for
the other
side oh it is the other way okay that's
what I
[Music]
thought now I can play some more things
because now we have two
bones
stinky I'm going put you there and end
my turn I have no more cards in my hand
now
die wa all right you wolf grw up I
forgot oh [\h__\h] I should have killed it
earlier um
I don't even know what there is in my
deck I guess it's just like a base deck
mostly
now use item not now draw a oh should I
get a normal card and play the
squirrel maybe I should I might get a
cross an item lady
soon bullfrog okay at least I can afford
that with one squirrel
I shall put him here so that he can
attack the wolf once the wolf arrives I
hope I will not regret this and now I
have two bones again so we could dig
again for a bone oh never mind it's
over uh Here We Go Cards cards cards
cards already won already won are you
making me choose like that again is that
a dinosaur or snake or is it
reptiles these ones I can't right click
right I have to already
know lizard rep reptiles top deck KCK n
it's a river Snapper okay
cool okay what's
next what's next what's next thanks for
the membership renewal thank you woohoo
the old wood carver again appeared
before okay so I don't understand this
though
what do you what do you guys mean I need
to choose something fitting I guess the
bird would be fitting because it's like
flying I don't
know I
gu I don't
know well it's
Airborne does it
matter it Buffs all your bird cards ah
if I put the bird head on it will buff
my bird
cards
Ah that's interesting and then I should
have like focus on one thing then okay
oh well bird it
is but can't all birds already fly
anyway
ah uh a card bearing the sigil will
block an opposing creature bearing the
Airborne ah ah ah it will be able to to
block flying enemies but still fly
itself okay well that's nice nice to
have the old woman buried her teeth in
satisfaction your first children was
complete the mighty leap sigil will uh
now be marked upon all your bird
creatures thank you what a nice
lady fight fight fight fight fight
fight oh
yeah now I have my own little statue to
look at me all the time
nice what do you have Birds well my
birds statue does not apply to
yours I wonder what wait actually that's
great we can block his
Sparrow when it comes out
but don't kill it though bro
chill what should I
do
squirrel wait I can still attack
them oh right right right right yeah I
understand I understand
um even if I put a normal card there
I'll be able to block it let's go oh you
actually have have that
too could could
say bullfrog is
bird but it has the sigil on his own
already go bullfrog Go I mean I've heard
frog meat tastes like chicken
right so not too far
off no he's got the porcupine
now I was hoping for a bone
thing no but we're fine still are
we damn
it I was hoping for a bone enemy should
we just sit through this turn what does
the porcupine do again once a card
bearing the sigil is struck the strike
is then dealt a single damage to point
ah ah when we attack you okay okay okay
so not too
bad okay at least that card is
gone a square W it
is uhhuh squirrel and we I guess we
should go with the ah [\h__\h] that takes
two but my bullfrog is almost dead I
don't no should we go with the sto we
should go with the
sto the
bird I guess it doesn't matter
except except this one can attack me
directly so maybe I want to take down
the sparrow
first we still we'll take a bad play
he's just he's just saying things
randomly right he's not actually like if
yeah
I should have done direct
shot will I
die N I won't die
right it's just a hater okay he's
correct no no maybe he's
right
ah please don't die we'll be fine we'll
be
fine
um well I have free Bon if only I were
to get
something
cheap uh if I don't I'll use the the
plier what do you
think yay lucky joh indeed I concede you
concede why is he concede I uh you kind
of
have I mean
ah he has no more
cards ah you have a tiny deck you have a
tiny deck I
see I've got the bigger
deck oh wait but we don't right we don't
take his
concession don't deck shame
[Music]
bro but I I still don't understand why
you're conceding just I mean okay when
you can't play anything anymore but
still you like you're not that far from
winning still at this point but he's
just I guess he sees the
future
go yeah I'm not taking your feather I'm
just going to end you I'm going to end
you with lots of pain I don't care do I
still have two bones
h ah right okay I guess that was my last
card and I don't have any more cards
that uh use bones but
okay just a bit more suffering my friend
just a tiny bit
more
well just a bit more damage
[Music]
why would I would he be nicer to me if I
take his
concession why would you take his
concession to if you're like is there
any point to it besides saving
time no I want the I want the
tooth I want the
teeth speedrun okay W skink the
tenacious skink it moves over when
attacked leaving its tail behind yeah we
like the
skink do we but this WWA is really
good that wa was a good WWA unlike our
first
WWA bifurcated strike a card bearing
yeah this would like attack not what's
in front of it but what's diagonally in
front of it very nice and it uh comes
back into the deck right that's what
that was or back into the hand
even oh yeah in my hand oh
absolutely absolutely
um so this side comes with fights each
uh this one was the items and this one
was one
again I also thought that looked like
Coronet especially if I like only look
at what's next to it then in the corner
of my eye it looks like
Kon so should we sacrifice or should we
get
cards uh items I mean
[Music]
item I think so
too do you have siges to sacrif maybe
not you still have items yeah but only
one
right uh okay a
boulder with five Health a black goat
which you sacrifice you get lots of
blood right away right I think I'll take
the black goat oh that was it I have two
oh this statue counts as an
item
Maga I can't get so I only have space
for two
items in this whole
run no you get free items you have a
hook I did I thought that was part of
the
Ambiance
Ambiance okay oh good start waa only
costs one blood oh my God this wait
that's so [\h__\h] good we start off with
a Wawa
holy [\h__\h] wolf Club let's kill it right
away no mercy holy [\h__\h] this will be a
short
fight oh but ah [\h__\h] I [\h__\h] ah [\h__\h] I
placed it wrong I placed it wrong I
placed her wrong but no I placed her
wrong well something will kill her
eventually and I can replace her [\h__\h]
ah I forgot I placed her
wrong no what does the hook
do can't even I don't know what does the
hook
do could sacrifice her true cuz she'll
come right back into my
hand Hook is really good steals a card
okay what does he do next another wolf a
grown
wolf I could sacrifice laa and squirrel
and get waa and the sparrow
out wait no wait wait I could get the
wolf no wait
yeah oh yeah if I If I sacrifice Wawa I
can bring Wawa and the sparrow
out
yeah oh
yeah but okay this time we place it
smarter but maybe I might want to play
place it here no but the Sparrow okay
now here cuz the Spyro attacks across
the wolf cuup so yeah I was thinking
maybe prepare for the next wolf but no
no no no
no okay there we go wolf cup gone wait
he's dead what oh [\h__\h] I'm so
strong
okay I never expected when it happens so
early my pelts are cleaning off pelts
pelts pelts okay this time I won't do it
wrong I
hope okay we get a free
one I only have two teeth I can only buy
the cheap one why do I only have two
teeth hi chunky
wonky wouldn't buy it not worth
okay well I'll take the free one bye
save the TOs yes okay
sacrifice uh more items or
rest ah the resting what did that do
something some kind of ritual happens
there right okay fire what was it again
how does it work
again and then we got to boss fight oh
yeah it makes him
stronger uh there's room for a creature
around to fire one set the war will
enhance itself that doesn't sound so
threatening well okay this sounds
but we'll be
fine uh yeah I would this gives plus two
health I could give W plus too she'll be
like a
boss upgrade wva really so op then I'll
always have to top G top G top deck
Wawa then I want I would want to trim my
deck to keep my deck small to always
pull the w
W doesn't need HP though you're right
she's already healthy but okay sure
let's make her
overpowered oh did her face facial
expression
change cute waa okay boss
fight looks like cie with the sickles
but a cowboy hat that's exactly cie
smoke the smoke a chill Mist closed in
around you you were not
alone a figure emerged from the
[Music]
fog it was kilano stand in the way oh me
gold be darn but I can literally imagine
Cali role playing this like cie being
behind all of
this stand in the w stand in the whale
oh me girl stand in the wh me gold
be I don't
know
howy okay uh wait so what does the smoke
do what
what is there like a special gimmick I
don't understand right now he has the
pack mule I guess that's the
gimmick the mule is the
gimmick no
WWA wait what what is this
smoke what the card bearing the sigil
dies four bones of water yeah wait you
tell me should I sacrifice a
smoke a free sacrifice bones in the oh
so I should sacrifice the smoke right
away for bones [\h__\h] pelt in my
hand I use it for blocking oh but it's
just one HP
I'd
rather uh sacrifice it but I think I
won't use it right away not right now
cuz I I mean I could I
guess no but like it doesn't I want I
want I want oh a boulder
[Music]
put the I think I'll put the sparrow
here I don't want it to get killed by
the but e h well the MU doesn't
attack I'll put it
here and
[Music]
yeah W
no
what oh well we'll we'll get him we'll
get them
eventually and we've done it without the
m anyway
before right I forgot it won't attack
the mule I'm so dumb
uh I could use my
goat but now that would be a
waste a
mole a
mole struck a car heart burn oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah I remember I
remember uh if only we would get the W
[Music]
but wait I I'll do top deck because if I
got Wawa I know I have nothing really to
sacrifice but I could take the goat and
then play the Wawa and the Wolf and if
you got something bony then that's okay
too well that's not what I wanted but I
can play both of you anyway
I can play both of you
anyway don't play WoW round one oh right
there's going to be more oh [\h__\h] you're
I
yeah wait ah yeah the Black Gold also
has to be the Black Gold also has to
sacrifice can I place the smoke and
sacrifice the smoke but I don't get
blood
I get bones and blood Oh I thought I
don't get blood from it at
all
okay bones okay okay
[Music]
okay wolf kills coyote anytime M Senai
versus coyote not
Senai wait what didn't I get free blood
oh I think I'm
[Music]
misunderstanding doesn't carry
over
oh miss clay sorry I'm learning I
underpaid yeah that's okay we'll get rid
of the
coyote and then the mule will move over
and we'll do some good damage on the
mule and maybe we'll get get wa now but
probably should get a
[Music]
squirrel or but if but you know we could
possibly also get yeah bone card we
don't have so many bones SC yeah
okay maybe I should have kept the scroll
total misplay shut up I'll win
[Music]
anyway mm oh it moved back there no you
should move the other way [\h__\h] mole
in the
way freaking mole in the
way well now my my field is
full I'm quite happy with it
[Music]
anyway I just keep the squirrel for next
turn nah she'd
win yes
no my
wolfy w no W
[Music]
okay go go go go go go
go well that's what you get should have
gotten rid of my Boulder then I'd be
nicer to you dar's gold in them cards oh
you give me gold
not all of
them right [\h__\h] I forgot about this I
don't want this is good and
bad but he has to kill my nuggets
first while you're killing my
[Music]
nuggets
um when an opposing creature is placed
opposite to an empty space the card
thing yeah we'll move over there yeah
yeah but can you make the mule move bro
what but what if I get no okay let's
save a
SC save the
scir I can still win thank
you wa or bone card bone
card one attack and the stank gives it
uh well it will
die against
The Blood Hound should I still place
it I won't I I guess I don't well we'll
see do
something good good stink bug good stink
bug you can place a p too
nah I don't know I feel like that
wouldn't be a too good of a right if we
use the hook when I steal a card I'll
have forever or how was that I want the
[Music]
adder I want the adder just to to to
take his
effect just for the match oh
okay
um whatever I get I can't play it right
away unless I sacrifice a stink
[Music]
bug got to have to wait for him
maybe I'll just take another squirrel
No W
okay the next round I'll play
[Music]
wa okay
okay I'll take the last C too not
hold okay um where should I place one
one not there not in front of the adder
right and even if I did it would just go
back into my hand but
no oh right and also attacks sideways so
it kills the
mule what happens first the mule dies
or the the guy
dies the MU
dies yay meow
wow we got some cool stuff okay wait
wait wait wait wait I have to take a
card right
here
okay what is this do again when a card
bearing the sigil is sacrificed it does
not perish oh cute no
no ah right I could have played the bone
card damn it
I mean at this point it doesn't
[Music]
matter wait what so
cat it does not perish so it stays on
the field oh yeah right that's what it
was okay
well yeah n I'd
win I still want to optimize my turns
though you know
I want to use the bone card but
okay so many bones I need I need I need
I need
more choose carefully what do we
get strange
larva
ew long
L why is it such weird cards a holy
mantis God the perfect incarnation of
I'm sure this is great because all my
attacks and free dire
op should we give that like use that to
give it to another card or should we
build upon the Mantis
God give it to no she already has the
cool effect we should give it to another
card so we have two cards with cool
effect I I
think I think flying threee directions
op wait whatever damage it would do in
One Direction is that times
free for a flying
enemy the man's God is undying it wins
you the game o well who well well well
well well well
well when we get to a place where we can
use the sigil we'll think about it
[\h__\h] give the Mantis health or sacrifice
it to give the ability to other yeah
whatever happens first okay okay ah it
looks like we would be making the Mantis
op cuz that's what comes first I forgot
what that was Ah that's getting rid of a
card
uh the Dank smell of the tepid water
invaded your nostrils you had reached
the wetlands
ypp I'm actually not sure what that is
why you not sure what the [\h__\h] that
is beehive what's what's what's this
about can't even read into
it it's it's en well but like what does
it do has like a skewer with like a
golden plaque or
so should I get
this it's it it it hit based on card on
your
hands
wait once a card bearing the sigil is
struck a bee is created in your hand a
beer is defined
as what card
truck ah there it
is mirror something the power and
some bearing great I can totally read
that I can totally decipher that I guess
the game wants me to figure it out
myself to just take the card and find
out mirror copies opposing card
strength
aha
ooh if I place it in front of a wolf or
something it would have free strength
and its own free health and would be
really cheap to
place I would not trust
it it's not really consistent
then would we go for the
[Music]
bees should we go for the bees we have
more
sacrifices I guess okay even though the
card is really
interesting okay
now I think I would go to the
fireplace Perfection per yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh oh even if the card perish okay
M plus one
strength okay so we will make the Mantis
God stronger power for the Mantis God
don't take Don't Take My Man don't eat
it I know it's crispy if you grill it
very very crispy and healthy but no
hands off of my mantis God it is a God
it is a God
oh I started off with the man is
gone okay he has a tree and bees
wouldn't it be perfect if I put my
mantis right
here actually
op go ahead my
friend you should concede already my
friend
it's so over for
you I'll bring you my own
[Music]
[Laughter]
bees he's got a mantis got too but not
just a normal mantis the Mantis shall
bow in front of my mantis God how dare
it be opposing
me I won already oh do I let me see what
I'll get
oh if I wanton already can I should I
just um can I
okay guess I did I guess I did this is a
good run so far I don't feel like my
deck is that special the only special
thing about it is I guess WWA andat
actually that is pretty good
that is pretty good what is this I don't
remember you encountered a small Outpost
in the woods tended by a mysterious
woman it was the traitor ah the Pelt
trador well I only have one her
appearance was UN selling but you were
mollified by her
offerings do you mind if I examine those
PS of yours yeah only got like one let's
start with your hair pelts here's what I
can offer whatever you give me I take
what for one Pelt I can have any of
these what cat cat cat cat cat are you
saying cat because you want me to put
that sigil
on the Mantis or so
or I wanted to click this
way I swear I just wanted to click out
of the
menual
no what the [\h__\h] did I get
maggots please tell me they're also
okay
no I'm so
good I hope the magot is useful too run
but too easy yeah
magots ain't bad magots are good maybe
we'll meet a cat again these PS are most
excellent my thanks get get rid of that
man get that out of my
face what is that I don't think I've
seen this before this is the sigil thing
should we still go to the sigil even
though we don't have the
cat we should
sigil sacrifice to trim okay
uh the maggot I
suppose what does the maggot even do uh
wa the bottom card is the one that
disappears right uh uh or was the top
card bottom disappears
okay H it doesn't give me the did I
choose the I think I chose the river
order not the
maggot who said I got maggots
uh a card burn the C of submer I mean
that's not bad because then yeah uh then
then the card will like never die we
could give it to the Mantis
God I would
say I mean it might still die somehow
but
okay then they can always hide after
doing a sneaky attack
okay
okay sacrifices to the Mantis
God no G to be seen in this play through
so this is like a little bit more
difficult fight was it not that I have a
choice is that spikes from the porcupine
snarp quill sharp quills
snarp snarp once a card bearing the
sigil is struck the striker is done Del
so all of your cards have that
[\h__\h] but I have both of my best cards on
my
hand that will kill the magic
no
uh what should we put out first
am mantis one shot but wow am mantis
dies
no
no oh they're so
scary a Wawa one you mean like in
huh 4 four four 4 four four * 2 eight
damage uh free free free six damage what
all it takes to kill him is six
damage holy [\h__\h] that was supposed to be
a difficult
fight bad GM bad bad GM what's this over
here this is like getting a normal card
is this like uh what is this five to win
oh
wow that deck is
op mtis got and kill turn one let's
go tribe ah choosing a tribe again
I think I'd rather go to the
normal card place cuz here I don't have
to choose by tribe I know what I'm
getting
yeah cat stupid ant get out of the way
whoa on the Cockroach with the getting
back into my
hand uh
well just look at the cat can I play
the I can't put two things on one card
right like one two sacrifices onto one
card I can probably only do one but we
could put this on waa right cuz she
doesn't have anything on her
yet cockroach and then sack it on
something got
better uh but you can for a different
mechanic o once per
sacrifice oh oh really
you're saying I could put the cat on the
Mantis
too we could put the [\h__\h] sigil on the
Beehive I don't know I'm still not quite
feeling the Beehive that much
yet I'm sure it's great but
ah the number of ants that the owner has
on their side is the value of
attack roach and mantis is a
winner yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah if we
can do that
okay
mushrooms going to get high on
mushrooms ew I hate mushrooms and I
don't like like the idea of getting high
either worst place for me you found
yourself among a Grove of thck and
pungent mushrooms
ew you squinted to see a figure for a
thick cloud of
spores
ew what is that we are the
myologist yes H
yes and we are performing our
experiments far from from we are not
welcome elsewhere we will experiment on
your fluck yes we will need two of the
same creatures I don't know if I have
that what do you mean one for each of
us oh dear you
don't you have no duplicate W what a
waste of a little turn thingy take one
of about are you giving me we will use
it next time if we meet again then that
is he he's duping my
mentis he's steing my mantis
God he's steing my mantis God is he
insane okay well here maybe we should
look at the path ahead of
us uh this this gives me any card one of
free and then I don't know what that is
and then this is I don't know really
what that is either so you guys help
me is that is that I can't see ah is
that the is that the sigil
sacrifice I no is a totem another totem
part or is it are we starting a new
totem with that I think ride is the way
[Music]
okay right for the win oh right side
maybe get better
totem oh it's to replace a part oh okay
great draw two G holy [\h__\h] like when I
feel kind of bad like in this game and
slay the spire and so on uh in all of
these games whenever I have like an OP
deck I I I I feel like I'm just like
cheesing the
game like
don't feel bad he cheats don't feel bad
it gets harder okay he's got the bees
that move to the right okay and I have a
a
tree um okay well I shall begin with my
mantis
God I
guess I think we're winning
he's like
girl don't end my my game so fast like I
I set up the whole table for you it took
me like half an hour to set up the table
and the Ambiance and get the the red
lights working why are you ending it so
fast man he's going to get mad yeah he's
going to kick me out cuz I'm doing
things so fast
oh man I'm sorry he's crying like all
that effort for me to one turn
him ring e the underappreciated ringworm
its value is not readily
apparent
okay is it apparent later it's just like
a sacrifice but a
skink just like me no don't say that
your value is immediately apparent to me
room room is pretty good if you know if
you if I know
what oh the worm Emoji is cute if only
it looked like that then maybe I would
take it this is this run I think ring
ring worm could be good why what does it
do just that it's like a sacrifice thing
or makes me sick
see
secret find out huh makes me sick what
do you
mean the bones of the ancient woman
creaked and groaned as she approached
with gently shaking hands she placed her
offerings before you okay so we can even
change the top part so what it applies
to or the bottom part the effect right
ahuh uh we can make our cards
stinky I don't really know about this
whole statue thing I it's not like I
have many of the same type of
cards stinky birds
or this effect on any of
these how many birds do I have but yeah
for mantis in any case if I put the
mantis head on top then it would my my
mantis insect thing my mantis would have
new effect effect extra
yeah I feel like that might be
good
yeah oh wait do I I have to choose to
put it
[Music]
together
or ah okay I choose
okay
cute the old woman collected her pieces
and shot are you taking my bird
head oh okay boss fight have I had this
one
before it's a bad effect for my this I
mean do you really want to block of M I
don't
know I keep the bird head okay can I
switch it anytime or only when I meet
that
guy not sure you want the Mantis block
yeah but yeah okay it's it's Smoky time
again you beheld an immense man slouched
beside a monkey Pond he appeared to be
tearing hunks of Flesh from a fish
corpse are you fishing no some tunks
were thrown back to the pond where a few
ghoulish Birds snaap them up no and
somewhere sloly pushed into the hulking
man's mouth are you fishing is he
fishing no you I have to think with this
one you bring fresh fish okay help me uh
like every second turn I need to make
sure that my last placement is a [\h__\h]
card
what if I don't Place anything in that
turn at all what if I keep the board the
same I got the ringworms and the
WWA W wa wins I guess the first light
yeah
okay can't just wah can't just W wah my
way out of it
wow my way out of it I like that we
should we should use that
phrase [\h__\h] you're so [\h__\h]
bro as long as he doesn't fish my Wawa
so at the end of this turn he will be
fishing right so I want to play
something that I don't care if he takes
like a
squirel right
or a ring room I don't know believe in w
we win I win any oh because he
placed
oh
oh I'll I'll put a squirrel down
anyway fishing is only first
round I do want to see what the ring
room
does can I or should I not do it
now Overkill him
okay
fine more
tooth thank you that was the shortest
boss fight I ever had that's ridiculous
that is
ridiculous well it'll get more difficult
later right
you will challenge me properly later
will you you will not perish quite
yet damn bro I I I I I I I one hited you
twice in that one boss fight perhaps one
of these will entice you don't give me a
mantis God I I'm already too Godly mle
Man the [\h__\h] I'm guessing he spawns
moles the stalard moleman the Ultimate
Defense the Dows the filthy feral hog it
becomes incensed when its Chimes are
struck and the what the
[\h__\h] is that a
Yeti four blood for 7
s holy
[\h__\h]
um should I take
it meman meman or Y feel like I saw that
one before anyway uh let me read this
when a card bearing this sigil the two
bombs or whatever is played a chime is
created on each empty adjacent space the
chime is defined as zero power one
Health a I see okay just kind of create
a wall I
guess uh card bearing the sigil a yeah
will block an opposing creature bearing
the Airborne sigil but your other
one you move to the to the side where
it's
empty they all kind of bad moment pretty
insane main moment is just a good
wall yeah yeah true he doesn't attack
but he can block like a lot and he's
cheap
okay
nice and he moves to the place where I
need him I guess and I can always
sacrifice him if he's in the way moving
past the P you took a deep breath of
fresh air and continued on let's go
The Wheels on the BS go round and round
round and round round and round we will
need another map do you have
one ooh snowy the relief of the fresh
air quickly gave way to a bone shaking
chill you guessed at the path ahead as
the snow increasingly obscured it you
had climbed to the Snow
Line okay
first we get more cards my my my deck is
getting Fuller we don't like that
because we need top deck cards we need
to get what we want Raven a blood hound
and a
Grizzly maybe we should take one of
these cards for its
effect oh
no Grizzly pretty strong Blood Hound
pretty
strong raven d
do need sacrifice some card soon
yeah Raven nice sacrifice for fly for
making something fly but wouldn't this
be more interesting maybe not
necessarily yeah I don't like these
choices that much air from mantis too
flying
mantis
okay not the best cards but okay now we
can even go down that
way more shrooms later but no what
happens if you have two of the same card
what do they end up doing I don't
understand I don't want them to take my
mantises go towards the shrim find out
as long as they don't take it they merge
[Music]
it did they also merge the health and
stuff oh [\h__\h] I mean I like having
two but yeah it could be one overpowered
card they sigils too I figured as much
yeah
okay what was that other one again the
one before e oh oh no you can't use that
I have barely been using
items the pitiful Plum what the [\h__\h] is
that failure to the user nothing will
happen this bottle of Goo has no use I
don't believe it
I don't believe it take the goo is this
like Story
related it's St
okay he's telling me not to take it so
obviously I must take it now give me a
top deck card that will end this battle
in one turn again oh he turned on the
spikes you think that's going to stop
me hell
no turkey
vulture what is that picture
look at
it
okay am I not winning
again tell me I'm not
winning what the [\h__\h] Waba literally and
is Waba is a speedrun
card if only it had one more attack then
I could like get a bit more Overkill
ah type card
oh but you're not giving me the in
insect card type that would help
to harmonize with the
Statue bird are there any like good
birds that I could get out of this cuz I
I don't
know if there's any more good ones I I
don't
know we could get the G out of this
there's a very good BP you can
get I haven't seen one
yet I'm saying gck add but the effect is
nice we can use that eventually to put
that effect on
something yeah hell yeah and for now
it's a good card anyway oh we're already
at rooms and we see there's a statue
thing again here and I I can't decipher
what that is again I've probably seen it
before but I don't
know okay shrooms combine my
mantises you found yourself among a grub
blah blah blah we've done this a few
minutes
ago wa cute oh but it's still optional
you're not forcing me
huh
oh we're so strong with this other plus
M no we can't we have to combine the
same
card let's go I I think this could get
messy look away oh no I want to watch no
let me see no he's really forcing
me
ooh amazing the art was originally
already like this kind of like
um what's the word again when it's the
same on both sides
symmetrical yeah but if it wasn't
symmetrical would it look really [\h__\h]
up would it no maybe it wouldn't oh wait
would be the same card and you take the
right side and you take the left side I
guess it wouldn't look [\h__\h]
up the m is gone it is uh now one oopsie
ha have fun
thanks fight fight fight fight
higher chance to get mantis now
whoa
who what do you have elk F oh I feel bad
for killing elk fonts by the way should
I use
this or do I just ignore it for
now use the goo use the
goo I'm serious you cannot use that
there's no possible use for it I place
it on that shelf over there for now oh
okay and my advice
avoided what a bad D GM GM GM GM you are
for giving me an item that is supposedly
useless H doesn't seem like
you doesn't quite seem like get up the
table now now I don't think I can do it
mid
battle afterwards
sure this card is so
overpowered bro I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry for ruining your
game there you are my little friend I I
rescued you you better be thankful to
[Music]
me pain is
unbearable even after all these years
what do you
want I have very little to live for
these
days is that all you say uh watching the
angle loose now that soed my pain an old
rival of my dead fisherman he M than me
this time I will have another
chance should I just talk more
the Wardrobe is UN long the fish around
in there surely the master had a plan
the p is so
simple you know what this just
do uh then I already do that oh by way
interesting dagger give me
that give me give me give me give
me until he starts repeating stuff
okay it wish to open those Ro
have you KN wi at
all a card game you've been playing do
you not see the
barall the
no those
W as with the game you must the scales
why does he sound drunk now I don't know
why I'm making him sound
drunk as wi the game five damage is what
it takes to win oh thank you for making
making it very clear for me now uh I
only really understood like 10 minutes
ago how much it
was which is pretty late
no okay he's
repeating okay so I'm not finished here
huh oh I thought it was only the top two
there's more oh
no oh I've seen that one open I just
need to position things right of course
you would need to know what she just me
I think I know by now but I still don't
I know I know just leaves behind the
tail and stuff and the answer I forgot
those but I'm just going to brute for
it oh got it almost got it
[Music]
um oh we got a CED wolf no poor Wolfie
but what are you doing GM why would you
c a
wolf I take but it goes into my
deck man I don't have that much space in
my deck I have to trim my deck
okay
maybe how about this oh two out of
five I don't know
two out of
five I'm not thinking At All by the
way in case you haven't
noticed wa oh I got a head rat head
nah is it is it uh not just for rats but
like any kind of like small
animals a squirrel is a squirrel oh wait
what wait my squirrels my squirrels will
get a buff and I thought I had all the
totems together my than the wood cover
will offer this now ah damn I don't know
will we get the cross one
still is there anything else to check
out give me
that give me those
teeth I can just take them
what okay
hey are they
available wait how does that
work I like how it seems like I can
touch everything is this like does it
matter how I move
that imagine instant uh game over
because
I yeah what it's oh I can't turn them
back on anymore
candle check the
lamp the lamp what which lamp is that
supposed to be you mean that's a lamp
that's not a
lamp take the smoke I can take the smoke
I can't take the
smoke anything
else this a a
[Music]
lamp inhale the smoke can't do that yet
okay okay back to the
game scoozie Sorry I I was speedrunning
your game so I thought I had some extra
time you
know moving on what is
this ah what was this
again a trial of Bones the free drawn
cards must must cost at least five bones
combined to pass ah I a little thing
what whatever is like most likely in my
deck 12 power the free drwn cards must
have at least four attack power if we
get like a mantis or a wa that should be
fine the trial of wisdom the free Dr
cards must not have must have at least
three SES among them to pass oh that
could also be easily
achieved
power sigils
yeah like s just might be might be
really easy come on come on come on
unless you're really unlucky let the
trial of wisdom begin oh [\h__\h] no [\h__\h] no
unlucky as hell I'm going to fire one of
these cards because of that when I
can no what what what do you get again
if you don't
fail ah
[\h__\h] yeah they would have failed both
trials wonder I wonder if the RNG is the
same and you would get the same cards in
the other trial too or if it's like
calculated
differently a you get an enchanted card
okay thank you for the membership gift
let's
go thank
you okay and then we can change our
statue again we can put the squirrel
head on top whatever that does I don't
know should I do
that cuz like items I think we are full
still we still have the fishing rod and
the
plier yeah you got it let's
go totem
totem whu head I am curious indeed oh
but you also offering me a new one right
maybe he can offer me a new body that
works well with the
squirrel wait so basically it just like
gives this to wait if I put this on the
squirrel or the squirrel on this it
gives me even more blood than
usual
oh is this really a squirrel are you
guys
sure this is the one right okay
oh your
Uber
squirrel oh my
God
op holy [\h__\h] wait if I oh if I have if I
start my turn with wa and mantis God in
my hand but only one squirrel this the
one squirrel will be enough to play
both and another
thing
so holy [\h__\h] okay I take it thank you
you made me even stronger no what
doesn't carry over I have [\h__\h] no why
doesn't carry it
[Applause]
over okay okay fine I for Gore I'm
thinking I think I'm thinking slatest SP
I think in slatest fire that this kind
of logic
Works oo what where's my top deck Wawa
or mantis God
Raven egg elk Fawn okay they he's giving
me some time to cook at least should we
try the ringworm now I don't know we can
play the wolf at
least install
wolf
King should
I where should we put it just
here
okay we need the Caged wolf
[Music]
is that
so I made sure to shuffle your deck this
time cuz you were totally cheating oh is
this what GG wait I win already bro I
want to play I want to
play n you
win wait don't I even have like can I
experiment and try this out
but can
I
okay not yet very soon you
can just accept the wins please no I
want to see what it
does what I guess I won't
see okay um mhm I would say not left cuz
I don't think we have any double card
but he would give me imagine he gives us
another freaking
mantis now campfire
okay ring R is not meant for
[Music]
battle elk
mole Raven
egg h
what's this oh
burrowing don't like the effects but the
I guess
elk not good cards we already used up
all our good luck with cards I if you
have squirrel oh okay yeah I can play as
expensive
cards okay
oh this is just the carving again right
I'm not going to switch it anymore so
what is this what is he planning to
do I'm going to go to the fire what are
we going to do at the fire plus two
hearts you're not going to eat my card
yet are you guys you're not that
desperate yet I
hope um do we really need to make these
even
better sacrifice worm
ahuh you know something I don't oh but
they can eat the oh maybe they'll be
happy and they'll all die they they
might all die is that what's
happening and
then ha the help of the ringworm was
enhanced by
the eat eat it guys eat it as one of the
survivors began pulling a knife from the
par no no no no no eat it did you guys
[Music]
uh it
it's too late don't let it
eat can't do it this run did I get
baited what the [\h__\h] CH things they know
but they don't it's too early it was too
early did I did I waste
[Music]
this if I lose this run it's your
fault oh it wasn't even one guy it was
several guys
no but that's
interesting that something would happen
there at some point do they give me a
sign so that I know they'll actually be
eating my
card is no is there no sign
yes one guy there's none yes no it's
random you'll
see it giving me mixed signals
again pass the first time it's oh
no there 20 guys
Le
H it's up to how greedy you want to be
with your
odds
oh thirst
five [\h__\h] I was too op anyway we're just
nerfing myself we're just
nerfing wait why did you turn it off oh
that's my oh yeah right I forgot you you
only give me my one life you little [\h__\h]
a man stood before you a man you
recognized immediately it was the
Trapper I recognize this man do I I
don't remember you remind me please you
reached out to examine his Wares but he
stopped
you what what is is the Pelt guy oh the
Pelt guy wants to fight
now
oh sorry but today you will supply the
P I'm sorry neither my Wawa card nor my
mantis card has first so we will just
kill you instead is that
okay ooh
nice wait so but still like how does
this work strange what the [\h__\h]
he's got like mechanic frogs and a
leaping trap oh
no B gim's
good uh when a card bearing this sigu
perishes the creature so if I kill it
the creature opposing it CES as well a
pelt is created in your hand in my hand
or in his hand in his hand
right got to play safe now now in my
hand oh because he would kill my and my
my card so he would but what if the card
doesn't have a that have fur does it
ignore that
[Music]
logic I can't go that
low okay it ignores logic
amazing everything is fur you believe it
does he's a pro trap but he will make
Pelt out of anything well yeah I guess
he would make if I look at my skin well
you know I've got a little bit of little
teeny tiny body hairs I guess he would
use
that this is the hardest
boss okay wait what what El so basically
just don't put anything in front of the
steel
trap or I don't know I don't I don't
really understand yet what's so
dangerous but we don't have Wawa or
Mattis but that's
okay you kind of have to or use
something very cheap don't kill the
frogs that's the
key
[Music]
why why why don't kill the f
I didn't even want to sing with him I'm
just he's thinking frog change to trap
on oh it makes sense cuz of its mouth ah
it'll become one of the
traps so I want to but I have to I
probably have to
honestly perishes Parish
Parish he's planning to fill the whole
field with that
though bait it the Frog still attack
[Music]
us just be careful of how many you
killed so ideally I'd want to have cards
on the table that that uh go past him uh
this these cards and just attack him
directly
but then also I want to block his
damage don't forget the
hook should I steal one of the
traps no they block all oh
[\h__\h] Second Face
okay you just have to
sacrifice I don't want to okay let's
begin then
um could
play how does this work does this have
do anything special
when going against one of
these or or going against a strange frog
if I if uh my Adder kills a strange frog
will it create a
trap no doesn't do
anything hm
H
yes huh find out
okay I
guess or should I put it here first I
don't know I don't
[Music]
know just try
it Mak
could get some teeth in right if I just
put it
here
but yeah
[Music]
okay if you put it there then it will
die you mean in front of the Frog
[Music]
uh you guys are telling me to
missplay huh
stall with your ring
worm just play I'm scared I don't want
to ruin this run I don't want to ruin
the
Run did I somebody said I should play
this though
now what happens if
I I mean I guess it blocks
at
least gu
[Music]
just I don't understand how that
placement would f
well I mean I don't
know
okay
uh I think I'll go with no squirrel
because even if whatever I get I can
sacrifice the Ring Worm for one blood
can squirrel
first I need a squirrel
[Music]
okay we'll we'll
okay at least we have a strong turtle in
our hand combat the
turtle I wonder know if I should help
help myself with any of the items
[Music]
though is he going to play like many
more of these like what if if I just
steal one of the frogs it will make my
life a bit easier next
[Music]
turn [\h__\h]
Raven Raven
[Music]
ow those teeth gave me weird drains the
effect these teeth have on
[Music]
me I don't know I want to
steal but
okay okay now we have a trap
at least he's not playing anym of these
shitty things anymore
yeah but I I guess I'll play my
[Music]
Raven I mean what else can I
do H the third frog
[Music]
I want to hook too but some people are
saying it's better in the second
phase ah
[Music]
yeah I've
lost I've lost
I only did that cuz somebody said to do
that can I
still
like save myself if I steal
[Music]
please okay that's gone at least I got a
bone from
it and another bone and a pelt well I'm
not de
yet I can't trust CH anymore cuz last
time you guys really helped me so I'm
trusting chat but now I'm scared I don't
want to die though I don't want to
die wolf a wolf
bullfrog where's my mantis my deck is
too
big p to block
comat the
[Music]
pelts big deck
problems brought out an Adder how fun
but now we have a trap
open should I still take a normal card
or should I take a square wall I have no
more items I have a lot of Bones like if
I get
uh a good card like w mantis or a bone
card I'd be
fine you lose evil way no
nois
girl and no more C could save me May no
it's over out4 wait if you can I redo
the whole fight but but like it saves
before the fight is that how it
works we've done that before we slay a
SP I
think save scum save
scum
bye oh no my game crashed oh this is
very nostalgic this feels so famili
faer somehow it feels like I've done
this
before why is this game so
unstable
man I don't get it my PC should be good
I should have a strong PC don't listen
to chat now no I'm I'm useless on my own
too but that's I I I'll try to like at
least not do the same mistakes although
I don't really understand
every mistake I did but we'll
see
okay got Trapper okay let's go Mr
pman with your funky flashy
knives is the is this is this the same
as we had originally I think it's the
same
yeah okay was something wrong in my
first turn already I don't remember did
I do something
wrong yes what did I do wrong was it did
I place the adder in the first turn you
didn't like the placement of it being
here here is is that where I put it I
put the adder here was it or did I put
didn't I put the add here I don't know
other left mid was wrong okay okay
okay okay okay so we put it in front of
a frog instead or in front of a trap
front of a frog
okay uh so this
now okay and
then playing this smoke isn't that also
something I did in the first turn was
that
bad why why would that be bad is that
bad is that
bad I think I played the smoke and then
I sacrificed the smoke with to get the
worm
smoke sack is good smoke ring room okay
it's a good stall
card never play
worm never play
worm
smoke
yeah
okay is a good Locker what
so that I will put in front of the other
[Music]
frog tell me if that's
wrong CU it's too late
now that's fine okay now I will say
squirel I wonder if my deck is shuffled
the same way cuz that means we probably
won't get a mantis or a w it is trff the
same way isn't it because we got the
same first
cards ah then we'll take a while until
we get the good cards well while we're
at it should I should I fish for one of
the frogs before it hurts me too much I
got fish for the Frog
now but maybe not maybe only after
there's something behind it I
don't not a bad IDE okay save fish for
the wol wolf the wolf is there a wolf
coming I
forgot well okay let's take the squirrel
we might have to win this fight without
my best cards cuz they're not coming
anytime
soon all right
[Music]
then
no
what what's so bad
[Music]
misplay
total
what that's F
okay trap is gone I get a pelt bullfrog
is here
bullfrog maybe I should fly now in any
case because it's getting kind of
risky oh um squirrel or normal car
if I get a normal card I could sacrifice
but we know we we know the good cards
aren't
coming do I really get the same cards EX
like maybe just the first cards are the
same maybe the rest of the deck is
different RNG like coded differently
Pelt is a squirrel
okay yeah okay it's the
same okay then I'll put the pelt in
front of the Frog I mean doesn't matter
cuz I'm going to sacrifice the Pelt am I
the Pelt and the ringworm for the Raven
but then I'm not putting the Raven in
front of the Trap but instead going to
put the Raven in front of one of the
enemies can't sack the P oh oh
man oh does this
mean is this sign does it mean can't
sacrifice it
uhhuh oh okay well then I can't get the
Raven right now
anyway then I just need to put it there
to block but we'll use the
pliers
ow but I don't
know I guess so ring worm space will be
empty next
[Music]
turn I was thinking of stealing the Frog
too but thinking of stealing a stealing
a strange frog might be better than
stealing those the
bullfrog that's a horrible
idea my deck requires me to stall m keep
the hook still
okay okay that's fine but I don't know
should I put the P down
now he's going to do I mean just one
damage to me I guess that's not too
bad save it
okay the wolf is
there H okay I Ste
wolf uh but first card
the thing is I know it's not coming
anytime soon but that's meta
gaming
squirrel half for the
Raven oh or for the wait if I steal a
card is it only in my hand I can't play
it right away right it's in my hand I
it's not on the field I
mean ah oh I can only steal what here in
the front ah
[Music]
[\h__\h] how are we here how many teeth is
that is that threee teeth on my
side F
dead P block
GG
no what if I steal this frog instead of
the wolf I don't
know let's put the Pelt
there I can't die don't kill me new Pelt
okay well at least the wolf is coming
but it attacks me too
don't no what if I him for
now oh wait would I still have had one
more no right is it too late to all the
four but how how how can we even do that
[Music]
differently how can we do that
differently I can't wait for
[Music]
the for the wolf to come by
I might not be able to wait for
it can I still redo that or did it
already register in my
failure please please let me
play okay okay well you know I have I I
I will try something okay I I I will try
just uh trust me and I will fail
probably anyway but I'll try something
after all this knowledge that I have
gained I shall do things my away I shall
fish
early okay so uh but wait First Steps
what did I do again so squirrel and get
the adder first was it the
adder oh
wait I'm thinking I'm thinking
[Music]
thinking I wonder if I should put it to
the other if it matters because this one
will be followed up by a card this one
won't be folded up by a card anytime
soon but I shouldn't know this anyway if
I first tried
[Music]
this
um we'll try again if it do if it
doesn't work then I'll change my tactic
I have to get through
this smok into ring worm was okay I
think I remember but we put the ring
worm here
before which I don't see anything wrong
with that yet
[Music]
H uh
okay I could steal it
now but do I want the squirrel probably
yeah yeah yeah yeah no give me give me
hello
here squirrel
you take
frog
um maybe
sacrifice ring worm put Snapper
[Music]
there
no I guess we shouldn't waste the HP it
still has okay that bro is gone he
brings the
bullfrog I'll just uh I have my Pelt and
I have a squirrel and a
snipper ring
room can be
sacrificed can choose maybe normal card
get
raven p
and
now what I'm going to do
now is block the Frog block
frog but block frog with rever Snapper
or keep Riv snap let me think
he will block that's fine that's fine
with me that you would block my bird I'm
not I don't I think that's what I want I
want the bird to go against you anyway
[Music]
bird maybe bird is
okay and now so I wanted this frog
because when the wolf comes the Frog
eats the wolf isn't that
[Music]
good unless ah he places it somewhere
else did he originally place it there I
don't think he did I guess he changes
[Music]
it yeah he adapts okay I wasn't sure if
he would adapt I thought he might always
put it on that spot then my strategy is
falling apart
but still doable I could put a pelt in
front of the last
frog um I think this is fine right this
is fine this is
fine
I keep digging yeah we don't know what's
past the Raven do
we I don't think we know but even if I
take a normal cart now I can't sacrifice
anything
what I could do is take a squirrel put
the river Snapper in front of the Frog
but I don't know the riv Snapper is so
much
HP I feel like I want to use that for
something
[Music]
else P
turn well I'll take
uh I'll take yeah okay bullfrog I think
we we did see that before
maybe well we still fine on the scale
here okay I just don't understand why
why I should not put the Pelt to
block I I want to put it
oh wait I'm winning
guys see my instincts of stealing early
were always
right he does he doesn't even have new
[Music]
cards uh
this this will
[Music]
do H oh yeah okay phase two pH two I
forgot there was a second does he need
get new cards Exquisite Pals but the
cycle must
continue ooh let's trade n n n n what
what what oh what the hell powerful
cards I will accept only the finest oh
oh with my remaining pelts I get to
choose one of these but the rest you
play or
what trade for what you can but no this
the rest will stay and fight for me
ah
oh a
[\h__\h] he has a he has a a returning shark
with 42 a flying
grizzly with 4
six uh a spiky moose bug with
37 H A lot of people like the bear
that's for
sure flying
crazy I can take two things
[Music]
right the wolf o diagonal hits I want
that I think
flying coyote with B I do have a lot of
Bones already I could I could play that
one but it's kind of
[Music]
weak the bat leaves the Tails but I
still don't really not so familiar with
the tail play
yet Tails cre it's like uh squirrels
right I should treat it like squirrels
or what I think
[Music]
well I think I'll take
this oh wait there's two bears I didn't
even see there's a flying one and
there's a there's one that doesn't fly
but blocks flying
ones but if with four attack the flying
one might be better so that we don't
just do four straight
attacks oh
[Music]
b a lot of bat bands
now this is why you wanted me to fish I
get it
now what would I do if I was not so
influenced by chat
[Music]
you would have choosen differently well
you're my
opponent would have you would you have
chosen differently because you like
these cards well anyway the bat I think
I still have all my bones right okay the
bat I can play right
away yeah but then I guess I need a I
still want a squirrel I think
[Music]
ah but that's shitty placement for the
wolf
[\h__\h] is it
okay h
[Music]
well let's see what that
does okay oh [\h__\h] wolf is no bat is gone
but I get ta don't I get tails
[Music]
no no room
oh oh it it doesn't put it I thought it
puts it in my hand um I would put it in
the
adjacent and okay he's underwater how do
you kill underwater mobs again just by
uh take having an underwater sigil but I
don't have any oh wait my mantis does
doesn't it
[Music]
we just got to kill
him [\h__\h] [\h__\h] am I still winning I don't
know I'll put the bullfrog down for
[Music]
now I
guess sorry if that's a bad turn that's
what I
have wolf is gone ouch
at least I blocked the four damage
man y
y I have the wolf P I have so many bones
ah G what what what what G
what no no no no no should have gotten
the
grizzly [\h__\h]
AH mean
one more time this
time this time I know what I I know what
to do my first phase has improved uh
thank you only for the
rain no no no no I do not accept fade no
no no I I might be chasing this but this
is how people do it's okay it's
okay thank you for the braid
yay Ollie how's it
[Music]
going can I remember how I did
things can I
remember I surely remember
just be patient chat we'll get
[Music]
there did I take a
squirrel sh sh did I take a
[Music]
squirrel [\h__\h] I don't remember no I
stole I stole I stole but did I take a
squirrel
though did I take a squirrel what a
squirel no no I stole but
what I hope I squirel my way through
I'll I'll apply for now and um
I don't think we'll get through this
phase without fishing
so you
[Music]
know we kept the river Snapper for the
wolf but in the end the wolf was
placed oh yeah yeah no we kept yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah so we wait
I
think would be nice if I have more pelts
at the end of
this but I don't think I can change how
many pelts we have at the
end um I have a square out of a r
Snapper am I doing this the same
way
[Music]
yeah is this how I did
it now wolf goes there again okay
okay
[Music]
uh I think I then ended up putting the
pelt in front of the
Frog what if I put
this
[Music]
no yeah
this I could put this
does that change
things kill for
[Music]
True we'll
try I didn't really want to change the
first phase but I'll try I wonder if I
out of no it's okay to run out of cards
because then I will get to my favorite
cards
no how do I get for of
wolf yeah that's my problem
now
GG just put
us should I just put the scre don't need
to I got
leao oh I yeah the
frog the frog is still there helping
us we didn't get that Pelt but we wait
no I got less pelts now bro I got less
pelts now what
happened
[Music]
no I get a free
one is that did I did I Al only have one
Pelt at the end of the prev oh I
did oh that's where I thought I had two
pelts on my own okay still same pelts
let's
[Music]
try [\h__\h]
the wolf is nice but um I wish I could
place him in the middle by keeping these
two he leaves them in the middle and
then that's kind of
shitty but we'll
see yeah but the problem is now I can't
last time I played two cards because I
had the bones for it but now we need all
of the this the grizzly wow wow I only
have one place all right wait no wait I
I still have a squel up
here oh I forgot about that prepped
scribble I meal
prepped
um oh wait Grizzly flies bad flies ah
this one also flies so the grizzly can
be put in either of them
they just fight each other right or does
it just like do they both attack the the
card
holder yeah we want the wolf in the
middle so that it can attack diagonally
here we
go wa okay now there we are there we go
there still kind of
nerve-wracking um
but wolf will do some damage on him
directly free damage on him directly uh
will not well I think we will kill the
grizzly right I win
okay should I just put the squirrel
down if I win anyway but he can block It
Go squirrel go squirrel we win we win
yeah I just just believe an alt f4 like
five times I'm sorry I'm sorry that was
difficult when I don't get my own card
my best
cards and also getting misled but okay I
should be able to play it on my own so
I'll take that L
oopsie a mantis SC and a
c
n I think I'll take another mantis
God I'm sorry g e i I don't even
remember why it was so great
anymore I don't even remember because it
doesn't take anything to play
it it's only good if you put the the the
back into hand card on the
GE okay okay top that g it is in the
title I owe it to the G
you could see a light in the distance
the end is near
really really a
moment o
oh oh
finale uh wait a second is this a Sigil
combination thingy that's up
ahead I could put the adder on the Geck
right that's what I think I would or oh
no wait wait what's different no no no
no the the the Cockroach on the I need
items
true I need items too otherwise I don't
know if I'll make it but they have a too
big of a
deck ah
[\h__\h] unkillable
gck you'll be fine our
items uh
uh all right let's
go I better be fine with items the
bottom one is the
one getting the effect I
for
uh no B bottom one dies
okay cockroach right unkillable
okay it's so
back our gek is so
back your eyes have fixed themselves on
the small cabin it doesn't even have a
boss fight symbol it's warm light a
beacon in the O oppressive darkness of
the night surely surely this cabin
marked the end of your travels I don't
know
when you put it like that it probably
doesn't we got the G back I got the G
back oh
whoa where am I what's
happening am I
outside it's like I'm walking
backwards oh I I have to go
the
[\h__\h] what the
[Music]
hell can I go back can can I
leave uh steps away from the strange
cabin you were pres I was going to read
pressured presented with an opportunity
I don't offer my Boons to just any
travel are you going to give me another
card I don't need more C
give me something else no cards
[Music]
n items
items look at the table
first oh is it trials oh the trial of
the ring if you have a ring a
ring have a
ring the uh the free drawn cards must
include a card of a waterbor I have a
ring I do
oh the Ring Worm don't tell me that
counts I thought we were talking a
proper ring from somewhere in the room
for the puzzles the trial of the wing
the free drawn cards must include a card
with an okay I have a very special ring
surely not the ring you're thinking of
but uh I am hoping you will accept it
Marry Me Oh is he going to let me
through because he'll be so flattered
that I'm like he's just asking to get
married he's like just really desperate
for for settling down and he will be so
happy and we will live happily ever
after because it will be an automatic
proposal and he'll say
yes oh you see several things as a ring
you see this as a ring because of is it
because of the tail or because of the
circle and the add because it can shape
itself like a
ring so romantic
is it this circle well I'm not giving
you my G I'm not giving you my Adder I'm
giving you my ring room
success okay well I didn't know you were
so loose on these rules I will grant you
one of my most powerful
bonss cards that dramatically alter the
game and you don't even need to draw
them oh my God the Boon of the magpie's
eye when you draw from your deck you may
choose any car
best what's with me what's with me why
do I always get the best thing should we
look at the others though the Boon of
goat's blood you will start a battle
with a black goat in
the the Boon of the bone Lord you will
start a battle with eight
bone oh these others wouldn't have been
so
good oh no oh
no we'll repeat that once more
more why you keep on strengthening me is
what comes now really
bad the trial of the Swift free drawing
cards must include a card please give me
like a something like the ring trial
again the free Drone cards must include
a rare
card the trial of skins the free drunk
cards must include a pelt I don't think
I have any more pelts
so this this is the most likely Maybe
yeah okay please let the trial of the
Rarity begin okay win I
win are you rare too who how do I know
which card is rare if it has like a this
[Music]
squiggly well I hope that this luck of
me pulling the Mantis God here doesn't
mean I'm not well I can just pull it if
I want to
the border the color uh this like used
color and the
squiggle both okay okay well then
success he just ignores the mole oh what
more
Boons huh are you just H the Boon of
ambidex you may draw twice at the
beginning of your turn every
turn holy [\h__\h]
I passed second TR so yes more
oh oh my
[Music]
God I just
wish but I Dro twice but the second time
in the first turn I cannot choose again
right you will start a battle of a grand
nah [\h__\h] that and the Goat okay well
obviously I'm taking that holy [\h__\h] I I
can't no
way no way but would it really be smart
to choose both the Mantis and the Waba
in the first turn
because what if there's more phases
where they might be gone but one of them
returns my hand right but not
yeah yes it's
disgusting ah
[Music]
ah top deck Geck well worst case we can
out f
for also we have two mantises the other
one isn't buffed though you manag to get
both of my Boons I rarely say this but
I'm impressed and I I got your best
Boons too buddy you have been a worthy
adversary but unfortunately I must soon
put you to
death um American Healthcare be like
sorry I'm
sorry at least you find that funny okay
good you took your time with oh whoa are
you revealing yourself to me is this
face reveal holy [\h__\h] vtu face reveal be
like
and I'm itching for another game are you
ready to play yeah you're playing as
yourself oh I start by looking down
okay it's not worth to Safe scum this
fight what
why the masks are his vs yeah he's a
vtuber a varder a card tuber I hope you
are adequately prepared oh I'm very
prepared that's actually Canadian
Healthcare what
really perhaps one more to be say I
thought so I thought you would give
yourself free lives free free free
phases yeah stick it on there where you
going to put it in the nose in the mouth
are you just holding
it
whoa whoa are you ah are you going to
switch Mask wait you told me I can
choose I get to choose now I guess okay
so I get a starting hand and I get to
choose the only thing that would be good
is to have one more
squirrel cuz
the but I can sacrifice The
Beehive out of next
turn oh
next uh this music is so loud
music is loud isn't it let me turn it
down okay he's got a m man and what the
hell is that what amalgam I guess just
some rare card it's like a crazy oh my
God it's like a chimera is that a wing
and an insect and like a goat
foot it's
everything how do I
start wait he's a I have a Mulan we both
have m
I
[Music]
shall Hive and
frog
yeah and frog I can't do both
to be in your
hand should I put the Beehive at the
very right but it will only survive two
[Music]
hits M man what what do you mean
smoke ah ah okay
[Music]
I need something strong to put on the
mle man and we need to keep the middle
empty for the mantises that will soon
follow
um I'm not sure I feel like I could put
any of these cards against the
amalgam mman will move ah right wait and
space would be struck card bearing oh
okay but I would put the mle man just to
block the Amal gam cuz if I if I do end
up putting the Mantis or so here it can
attack the Amal amalgam while the
amalgam is attacking the meman what do
you think about my
strategy roog to move his mole okay but
but can I think I put my mole
here block his mole
and
then we have the
squirrel No I don't want to I don't want
to put any but know I can I can I can um
bait him to come over
[Music]
here I also would think about passing
because then I have more things I could
sacrifice next
turn yeah I don't need to like he's not
going to hit
me I'll
pass he's got a m is
God yeah right wait I if I choose cards
I'm not getting get squirrel so of
course I need my squirrel now
bro okay um I choose
my man's God or the WWA or the
G grab
G oh I could I could get a squirrel
but but now I don't know if I put the
waa here to attack the
amalgam I will attack the mantis got to
just not what it's in what is in front
of it but the Mantis will take care of
it later if I get to choose
again do I get to choose every turn I
don't get to choose every turn right I
just get to um pick twice like I get to
draw twice every
turn Okay
um and gek is just good
to huh get one blood
right yeah I I
have a hard time
remembering we go
here wait holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] geek
you're reminding me why you're so great
I could
now put something here to block the
Mantis God
attack I could put down the bullfrog
or the
Beehive think
might he will pickaxe them
H he'll you mean he's going to make them
into
gold uh
right
away only if the phase is over right
only if the phase is
over okay then I don't want to waste too
many of my beautiful
[Music]
cards G block
it hurts it hurts it hurts it hurts me
it hurts
me it's so painful I can Bobble back
never F I'm good I'm
good I'm
okay I'm actually
[Music]
fine oh I got the choice again wait wait
I actually I thought I just get to draw
twice I thought I in the first turn I
get to draw and know what I'm drawing
twice but and then I thought from now
then then on I would only get to draw
but twice but not knowing what I'm be
drawing but I actually
oh
oh I don't need any more cards but
maybe the
adder maybe the
adder cage what what does it actually
do does it have to be hit six times to
then be uncaged and then it will work
like a normal
wolf Maybe
have him die okay and until that point
he's just like a
free wall that doesn't attack back but
okay interesting he has the meman in
front of the Mantis God so for now he
can't even play the Mantis God cuz I'm
not going to attack anything so his mlan
won't
move so I can't do anything right
now you just you'll just have to are you
fishing you're fishing
now [\h__\h] okay
his Amo gam got rid
of [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I I'll put the get glass
yeah or
yeah but then that means if he fishes
the g at the end either way I will have
to take the amalgam damage of at least
one of the
amalgams which is free can I afford that
I I can't I want to look at my teeth oh
look at my teeth he won't let me look at
my
teeth going to take a squirrel yeah cuz
he's stealing it he's not putting it
back in my hand we don't want anyway I
haven't choosen chosen
yet um I wait I still have the ring worm
I thought he would remove it from my
deck
uh honestly anything's fine maybe Raven
or
Adder Raven just because I don't know
maybe not
good I want to block
his Pak s oh
[\h__\h] oopsy
yeah cuz he makes them weaker
right who this what ah yeah he makes
them less
strong right how we going to do
this if I put the Mantis God in front of
this Amal gum and then a wait I play a
mantis God by playing a Geck put the med
SC here and then I put a squirrel here
is what I would
do oh
[Music]
okay I just
gone so next turn I'll just get uh two
squirrels or so if I need
them M mm
holy
[\h__\h] I'm winning I'm winning I'm
winning wa
W yeah must free the wolf I know I
know well he's not getting rid of my
gold nuggets and
uh his squirrel is blocking his Amal
gum wait am I not Cho choosing one more
uh yeah I'll just pass but I'll take
another squirrel thank
you bam bam bam wham bam thank you
ma'am stump you capably endured the
onslaught of rare creatures but the true
challenge was forthcoming shadowy
figures appeared before you and their
eyes glimmered a recognition of kinship
but colored by guilt they were betraying
you Reginal looks familiar Casey does
Cas Casey doesn't look familiar to me
though I remember that one fondly
KY n these are not cards that I
necessarily met met right it's just
random players from
before Casey has diagonal attack and the
spikes that's that's a bit messy
and Reginal let makes me
perish well first Casey oh if Casey goes
down there she won't even take care of
the gold nugget
bro who will then who
[Music]
will we win
already oh I guess
so is he like he's not he doesn't have a
mask on right
[Music]
now how many squirts do I have squir
squirel
squirel I just get more cards into my
hand okay
this
is too
easy this damned moon it's dramatic yeah
but it provides no value to my
board I
wonder
uh
eh now that is value
huh
oh interesting one big
boss in all four
Fields one damage and 40 Health blocks
flying and is a [\h__\h] planet tidal
loock at the beginning of its owner's
turn a card bearing the sigil will pull
small creatures like squirrels into its
orbit uh you mean if they're in my hand
even
uh one Taps
to just add
it but it has to be on the field right
it it it it doesn't like if it's in my
hand he won't take everything in my hand
right that would be
unfair I don't want no I don't like that
that's too easy easy but wait he will
also take my [\h__\h] mantis God won't
he just squirrels on the field does he
see my God as a small
creature what about the
wolf won't mantis hide oh it's swimming
oh okay okay okay
okay and that's too are you telling me
that Adder oh will I don't know I don't
[\h__\h] know what about if we sent the
ringworm I don't want to do this one
turn I the [\h__\h] ring
worm
um can I give him a ringworm he just
does one damage per turn
[Music]
right I'm going to give you r
I don't want to insta whenn
[Music]
uh take the Ring
Worm how about we debuff he doesn't take
the Ring
Worm what what do you think I put it
there for it's my offering to
you I wanted to debuff myself by not
giving you such a giving myself such an
easy way
out
man H sorry I don't I don't have enough
[Music]
cards does he is this a small creature I
want to satis satis sacrifice our first
card
it's only squ only really only
[Music]
squirrels Dam I don't want
to well now I can't get rid of that card
unless I sacrifice it
[Music]
I'm not going to do it I'm not going to
place my
Adder ah
[Music]
[\h__\h] why would I place a squirrel and
why would I fill him up with squirrels
why would I even want to do
that to
block sure feed the
moon wait is this still the same
yeah wait I should have put him on the
side why did I do that I don't
know it's just so you don't stall with B
squirrels buff
squirrels lots of squirel if you had no
attackers and lots of squirrels you'd
live a few turns at least ah it's like a
way out for me if I had no good
cards I should have put Wawa here I'm
aware
but yeah
[Music]
can you please free my wolf before you
die [\h__\h] it's too late it's too
late is that the last squirrel oh you do
run out of squirrels eventually
oh oh I see oh God so many
cards I want to see him eat his
[Music]
squirrel
no
no iose all that's left is to finish me
off a man should I have overkilled
him dot do dot go on no I don't want to
end this either
bro oh wow I did the finishing blow
wait what oh it's just
[Music]
oh bro bro bro I have my whole deck in
my
hand but what about the wol
bro
damn
no that was antil
[Music]
climatic oh my did I just that's I think
I just beat him what is that poop
whoa wait what is that supposed to be
like a reaction from a
player well then good news oh okay oh
[Music]
oh who is
that is that the
developer he can't he's not good at uh
how do I get out of
here how do I get
out of that and watch the next
one now there you go hey there card
Gamers I'm the lucky Carter and this is
another pack opening video is this the
real face reveal patch monsters packs
and diing is this how he becomes that
guy and here I'll add some crazyx with
he didn't though okay ladies I am about
to open my first pack the cards are real
just for the video
right
we okay and our first rare is a birch
uhhuh not exactly a is that magic card
magic
gathering imagine just playing a
different card game here next pack
feeling even better about this one M
you're going to get a g is it feeling
extra silky today silky are you is that
a hint they're so smooth not sure what
they're doing down there great
commentary oh are you are you saying
somebody smoothed them with
something that's not how you do a card
reveal you need to show each one after
another to the
camera our rare p is it's not how you
reveal cards bam dog
not exactly rting so this the cards I'm
getting for the next
run here we
come oh
it's wait what phone is that Nokia what
phone's uh ringtone
again is that [\h__\h]
noia
noia who called him Gamers I'm the lucky
Carter and this is a vintage P opening
What happened to the of the other one
rare old packs I sag at AAR sale I've
got four packs of
inscription you would not believe the
deal do they really sell these cards IRL
you will even remember this game I'm
barely old enough to have seen these
going around in my childhood uh for
whatever reason they only did one set of
these cards and then stopped no what the
[\h__\h] uh there's not a huge market for
them anymore but at the rate I got them
for there's not really much so there's
supposed to be like old C cards people
used foil mantis God goes for a couple
hundred bucks
really was mine
foiled oh really cool art on these
definitely show them to the
camera and our rare for this pack is a
blue Mage blue Mage oh from Lord of the
Rings cool looking card but not going to
be where is's he going to what is he
doing why is he not in the movies what
we got going on in the second
they didn't have budget to make actual
cards has
open hope no one stuck the rare out of
it bro you got
scammed so bad come on honestly no maybe
somebody put a weird card in it the card
that turns you into a card wait
Reginald there's a set is this re
coordinates no don't go there no don't
go there no don't go there
Reginal no no go
there no Regal no don't go there I
think I'd have to check but I think
that's pretty nearby no [\h__\h] no don't go
there Reginald or he is the guy I don't
know no
Reginald no this is Patrick what
what was he also on a card cuz I'm
thinking like oh maybe he becomes one of
those card
guys oh
[\h__\h] AR right you guys he's going there
why would you go there there's a serial
killer there life are you lost trusty
headlamp are you digging and
shovel always come prepared kid I like
this this is so cool this is immersive I
like it as if it has Real History real
lore
yeah
okay getting close I think getting
close no so
sorry can't see so well this brittle a
skeleton has
coordinates is this like um is this
Nokia is a Nokia showing him what noas
can show you coordinates of where you
are right now really that's Hightech BOS
Beed skeleton skeleton
card getting close I think wait you're
going to find a skeleton bro don't you
realize skeleton card with a with
no he's freeing the guy I don't know a
massive
waste no bro
no uhhuh [\h__\h] why is that one like
that that's why you always bring an
extra battery oh his battery is just
died okay no
worries you got to come prepared
get digging
bro is that the spot that looks like a
good spot this is this
reminds this video reminds me of my
challenge video from uh last year's
anniversary where I was pretend where I
was dangered in danger engrave danger in
the
jungle he's probably just in someone's
back yard just like
me the harsh
Wilderness scary
scary this is it why is it so dark over
there the great Austrian
Wilderness we di the coordinates are
real can we go to those coordinates can
people go there where is it is it in
America how this not how you dig you
should learn you should watch my videos
on how to survive in the
wilderness where he why you taking like
that I give a 75% chance it's a
rock she testing the waters I
guess people went there cool did they
leave something
here a card oh skeleton this is a
skeleton is that that's a
box oh my God you guys I can't believe
it it's a rare card there's actually
something here
a
grave are you Grave Digger right now oh
so small
box floppy disc it's
sctive a does I have to game
in that's why the game looks so
old it's supposed to look like it's from
long time
ago I'm
uh I'm a little confused what the
sigma and take the box of you too or
close the hole
bro wait
so
um that must have been the first
ever like PC card game except for I
guess the typical poker game on Windows
P or so sure they had that before
Windows
XP H but like the first proper card game
to play on a computer
maybe Solitaire yeah isn't solitary the
game where you find the bomb you try to
avoid the bomb afle Gore okay now he's
checking out the
game he's spying a floppy disc drive
I certainly don't have one he has a a
candle there and a mask and the square
roll wow great
video all those things
[Music]
are
hints that's M
oops okay time to figure out what's on
this
thing
uhoh
D will something happen or maybe he's
just
chilling who even has 400 minutes of
batteries that's crazy oh
retro are you excited bro tell us your
feelings
bro it says continue not oh because
somebody played this
before is it my play file am I dead
[Music]
I want to know more of this story give
me more videos what's his uh I want to
review what's his game
[Music]
review that's what I did what that's
me oh that's me I'm the
guy
oh was just supposed to represent me or
so oh
hi what is
it wait I can't do it ah I do not
celebrate often and I seldom give
gifts I'm John
inscription oh
really but you Challenger you are
worthy please do not be polite dig in
but is this just
crap it's so sparkly though
is there something wrong yeah rotten
meat from the previous people that
doesn't look like rotten meat floppy
disc Graphics be like your
price very
well come with me oh you're going to
give me something
better card floppy
disc stand right there oh I'm scared
he's going to murder
me you're so scary why are you so SC are
you going to take a picture of oh I take
a picture of
you
cheese please do not be foolish there is
no film in there I will need that are
you taking one of me after
all you Challenger are a champion and I
wish to commemorate your victory
cute okay
um W what
to enter cheese sh do not
despair why would I despair I wasn't
even worried now you worry me sir you
are a
winner I don't believe
it I don't think we can get this wa
better than in the first one can
we congrats on passing the tutorial how
is this game not over
yet are we the
guy the last Challenger maned to defeat
me a rare a rare event go and ask how
they did
it wait what POV is this you will find
them hanging from the
door you mean the card
ah wait are these cards I had in my deck
that I can choose
again what there is not giving me
mantis the St the squir we said that
before is it more Square than before is
his neck bigger than before or does it
have free
legs is does it just get more more s
sorry does it just get more and more
weird shaped is there a payoff to always
choosing the
sto suit
yourself it makes sense
later M Cube sto proba why is
he no I I don't want to make up all my
own kinds of theories wild theories
again again but he's getting squarer and
square you know what I won't say it I
won't say it I won't I won't say it
should I say it should I does he become
nah n that would probably be a person
the blue liquid in the bottle will
probably be a person right because like
I don't know that became kind of square
but not really I don't
know that's just a fear that's a a w
Fury
okay I want to take the sto just because
it's funny but taking the
wolf is kind
of
[Music]
tempting oh I get them all
oh oh okay wait is this is this a shitty
RNG could I have gotten cards from my
previous deck and one of them could have
been like my
mantis or do you always get the cage
wolf there no
okay what's at this again I don't
remember oh you're wondering about the
painting I'm see Stu come out of
it oh can I take it the C I just right
a light just
right maybe not for
now pu in this room maybe
oh maybe I have to do that three times
oh no never mind I get smoke I do relish
snuffing out your ex's candles before a
boss perhaps you will now enjoy it as
much as I
do is that my in my deck
now oh we oh look at
[Music]
that do you say something
new I witnessed the final defeat of FL
over there quite a
spectacle though I had no hope that it
would bring me
freedom for that to happen I think you
would need something special up your
sleeves
H oh look at that oh is that all my
winds are going to be on the door or
what wa to I thought you were going to
put wa to in my
deck I feel
deceived I don't know if there's
anything else I
can do right now
here maybe
not oops okay well then let's play I
guess again
okay the clock I you know I can't read
clocks what could this mean I can't yet
okay
oh I
see I I understand something now
Reginal ooh bloody the tyrannical great
white the master of the
deep um well Reggie has the parish
thing but great white Tru is so strong I
do always have a lot of Bones though and
having no single bone card kind of a
waste of the
bones okay good we
agree
um do I still get do I still I don't
have my statue anymore do I so he would
give me one piece of a statue
here I do have starting items
though I keep on calling it statue
but I still have to SC a yeah because I
got it in the room so it keeps okay give
me a nice body
please after an overlong moment of
silence she moved over off over the
carving uh flying or flying block well
maybe we'll get a better body later I
want the the blood body again
please I'll take fly block for
now wait but then all squirrels well
that's Well for now it's useless then
we'll get something out of it
maybe well maybe not completely useless
but
still I want to get the blood again
ideally me again yeah what's happening
with you are you taking what's it what
is it
steroids
um just stay natural bro all
net you can do it trust your
genetics okay he has porcupine Sparrow
and the
stum I want to bring out
the the wolf but maybe now it's not the
time he flies over me anyway and he
needs to be attack
[Music]
wait ah no yeah uh going to put it
there s there here we
go going to block the
sparrow okay
I think I'll just put the sto
there free the
wolf well can't now I don't think I
really
can I want my op cards back stall to
free the
wolf but like
no I I can't anymore well the sparrow
will attack me instead of the Wolf
okay sacrifice is still okay
okay but then am I going to defend
myself from the
sparrow oh a squirrel I guess but I'll
have to take one
hit or I take the squirrel
here well one hit I can
take wait did he attack it yeah okay
really
really I guess the wolf will just be so
worth
it this may take a
bit top tier G oh hi
Reggie but what if I put Reg down he's
going to like n we're going to we're
going to be fine he's not going to end
the the the fight too early we'll be
fine yeah
um and the Wolf is
free I got an achievement ah I knew it
was a normal wolf I knew
it behind it but now the thing um
outside of the table will be free too I
suppose maybe maybe that could be uh
like a wolf statue or something for my
statues who knows really who
[Music]
knows Overkill
please no not quite yet okay I only have
square Wheels left
[Music]
okay here we go you
free what did I do with this present it
to
you ah should I will they eat the
wolf over here wait I can't like here no
no
[Music]
oh I can put it down
too oh maybe it is like a thing with
the ah
here murder
murder you finally pried my special
Dagger from the paws of that squirrel
though you may wish that you hadn't is
it an
item for the battles upon us is it here
now I can't see oh yeah it is
there okay uh for now uh ooh that's new
I
think um it's the gold digger maybe as a
actual
NPC uh this was the Pelt guy
this is the sacrifice this was the
statue kind of want to go here because I
want to get a
different body for my
statue knifing
dime yeah I want I want a good
one but wait are you giving me a free
Pelt
again after being defeated by that
Challenger while I'm thinking of
clearing me inventory trying something
else oh just counting PS are cheaper
now I do have a couple
of teeth uh later on you're going to buy
the Pelt so what was it I can actually
buy the golden
Pelt oh he even sells you more than that
I could also should I get another one or
should I keep the rest of my
money okay go one one more pelt
keep
okay
okay I
take yeah there'll be more cards in my
deck true we don't want to spam my
deck please please please please blood
blood everybody press your thumbs down
into your fist and pray for me to get
some good
RNG I need your help no you failed me
Chad what the
[Music]
heck
bro I don't need any of
these but I'll take this I guess maybe
we'll get a epic combo for our future
mantis cuz now I want the Mantis at all
cost
too I believe we will get
it uh I'll still combine the squirrel
though oh maybe I
shouldn't whatever I actually don't
really
care I really don't
care yeah battle
onwards squel
and two pelts in my hand great he's got
what the hell is that that's new prong
horn it oh it fights diagonally and
moves around
to a yeah just after your
[Music]
turn damn
oh wait I should have put it I'm sorry I
should have put it diagonally use
knife um what does it do can't I wait I
have to choose
[Music]
first
screel ow ow ow what the hell oh
hey my eyeball
bro that's like a better plier but yeah
why why now why
now no why not do it in the boss
fight bro I'm going to Al a four for
that you'll see I'll
see story for R
okay I I I can't see so
well skipping my
turn uh least okay um give me something
good reie I
don't I don't feel so
good he's he's a he's a
fauna player I think
just need one
damage let me just block with is that
dumb maybe that's dumb maybe should have
blocked with a pelt
[\h__\h] should have blocked with a
pelt wait uh two bones
[Music]
yes I think you've got me this
time
oh this time I kind of want to take
it take
it huh interesting why are you saying
that I would have taken a tube
of
H cuz was I doing so badly
was I soft luged it did feel kind of
bad this isn't much fun if you're half
blind are you giving me an eye perhaps
you'd like to replace
it so many oh do they have different
effects can I check them before I take
them the top left one looks funky the
others look pretty normal except for
that one and also they have different
colors
yeah this one looks
[Music]
crazy kak kak clock find Salvation in
kak
clock a
better yeah I think so we go the choice
is
final oh
no hey what would have happened if I
took the froggy eye the froggy eye or
whatever that was m i see now you want
me to move that but how do I move
it you want me to place those there a
there there we
go does it matter which
one it might
matter uh I see that there's like some
extra thingies there but you know I
don't know how to read a clock
[\h__\h] maybe it has to fit in like this is
this this fits does it though yeah yeah
yeah yeah this this one
fits oh okay
okay take the film roll before he sees
it
now what are you doing over there turn
you turn to face me ah the the the film
roll ah this one what are you up to over
there ah nothing can I close the doors
again no no we're fine we're fine film
roll do I use that
somewhere I don't think there's anything
now in
the um okay I think I'll go to the cards
I
forgot what um is this also cards but
like rare cards or
what now you have to win you have all
you need now really to win for real for
real as the pel trader we should go in
to the pel
trador ooh show me some Exquisite belts
yeah I got some hair pelts
then what about my golden Pelt are we
doing it separately are you doing one by
one um oh Cat turkey
vulture cat cat cat cat cat cat
cat yes is that a a golden Pelt
magnificent yeah cuz you got him on
discount child
13 m is God m is God what the [\h__\h] is
child 14 though
what is that like some
experiment long elk I know it's quite
funny I kind of am tempted
but I love my mantis
God he's a better card cat oh why
better I have to take the Mantis God I
at least already know how to use
that and I wonder I don't think we have
any good effect but wait we can feed the
Mantis God but wait also are they
dangerous now group of serving survivors
there's room for a creature enhances its
power so I would put the mtis god in
there
obviously I'm
scared let's do it don't don't eat it
the fire warmed the very man's got
enhanced its power run run run run
okay
okay first time save
okay don't forget to switch
totem ah you're right I did take the I
did didn't take that how's it been I'm
trapped wait wait wait in the body of a
sto wait he's a robot now paper of a
card what what I see that and I have of
course set up a way to reset once more
Oh you mean the film go on our player
friend here they already hold the
key so you found what what's happening
with everybody I've seen this play out
of enough times to know that a plan is
in motion make
Hast huh why are they all changing is it
just a joke or is there proper reasoning
behind
it you guys look
funny
okay what does he have uh ahuh
interesting uh diagonal and moving and
the mole moves to
wherever wait stuned w only one cost
that's pretty
nice I don't know I'll put it there I
have still brain empty so far
ow I know I know maybe not so smart but
you know I'm just not a smart
person this spot you sure well at least
you didn't say it's a
misplay stinky
bug ha stinky bug should have gone here
honestly
then it would have zero attack oh
well ow don't die yet stinky bug I need
you
still
okay I'm a
genius
really double mantis o I'm a genius that
would be great
again um
I might block of a scrw I don't know
I'll keep it I'll keep
it let's go no need to
block what do we get man is gone oh wait
oops order wrong man is gone let's go
let's go let's go you're not as strong
yet as you as I want you to be but just
like your predecessors you will become
super strong Overkill believe me I will
make you strong I will raise you just
like the previous ones powerful and
merciless turkey vulture eight bones
Flies free attack free
health bat four bones so many bone
cards flies to one and Elk
fwn maybe the bat I don't know I don't
know maybe
took sometimes I have especially cuz I
don't have any other bone cards I might
end up having so many
bones fall might be good for God
why it can the mantis grow into a more
powerful form
[Music]
but uh wait was the amount of sigils I
can put on a thing limited because I
don't know if that's the one I would
want to have on
there all cards
can only one
combination well then I don't
necessarily want that but I'll take the
f for now maybe we can put it on
something else I don't want it on my
mantis
necessarily oh we're right in front wait
we have the cat don't we have a
cat I can combine with a cat no wait
combining with cat is not really good is
it I don't want to sacrifice to mantis
[Music]
maybe
mantis mantis on the
wolf I could
yeah I don't know
yeah maybe I'll put but Reginal is
pretty good I might put
the if only we had like a less good card
with that
but yeah okay I think I'll do that or we
strengthen the
Mantis [\h__\h]
maybe maybe we'll St from the Mantis and
wait
for
to I do still want the
blood I'm fine with not going there
because I I might want a
better
sigil if I don't get the freaking
blood uh statue body now I'll be so mad
cuz that's it's a thir time I'm not
getting what I want please please please
please please pleas please pleasee
please please
or that's so bad I've wasted like four
three places to go to Ala for can that
roll the RNG for this does it
change flying mant is
God I mean that's fun but
I get
actually I can try okay cuz that means
direct damage onto him unless he blocks
it I guess that's all
right but the
blood think about the
[Music]
blood blood donations do you guys should
donate more blood this is your sign to
do that what the hell Creator smoke oh
what it has attack power now and maybe
more Health that smoke it is great
indeed but still same amount of Bones I
think all right we're in the boss fight
you passed the mass bow is this the same
as
before seems a bow was designed for a
dog but what Earthly Hound would require
a meal of that size
I'm so sick of this
boss wa little immersion break but not
really it's actually more
immersion where's that Hound of mine oh
you're are you the the one that turns my
things into gold my plan nears its
moment of truth but you must defeat him
first I'll try my
best ah the pack mule okay you're the
pack mule guy but wait don't you also
turn my stuff into
gold look at these
wolves this guy looks
like
snake yes he does okay interesting we
got a bone
card we can use him as a proper
card
okay wait so maybe this time we can kill
the mule early um
[Music]
CH ah [\h__\h] I
forgot uh cat next time
maybe come
on come on
how's the cat work
again does this make sense no it doesn't
make sense
what I
forgot no I need two cards for
that I'll just take the
smoke just skip
okay forgot about second ah all right
because
no he makes everything on my field into
gold no no no no no no
um well
[Music]
then [\h__\h]
yeah come on kill the mule kill the mule
kill the mule kill the mule kill the
mule
yippee CS wh what Alpha I wait is that a
good bird my meal will curse
you okay is this
whoa leader creatures adjacent to a card
bearing the Sig gain one power that's a
good bird is
it cost for bones oh [\h__\h] I got
bones but wait no I don't want to play
it now squirrel
C hi regie
um but I need to kill this [\h__\h]
coyote either way I got good cards in my
hand um
Pronghorn
n that's not that's not a bird I thought
oh oh look like an owl to
me
sorry I need
to put something there that I don't
mind
um but wait doesn't how can I ignore and
just uh two no maybe not how many does
he have three
just
blocket ah okay good good good good I
was hoping that that would do it there's
gold in them
cards it's gold digger time and the
boulder is gone but you gave me so many
bones thank you and I got a different
cat from your mule so I don't mind so
much about losing the one
mule okay oh but yeah can you coyote
please take care of my nuggets
first thanks thanks perfect placement
too
[Music]
because two
two I was gonna ideally I want to play
this one in the middle next to
Alpha but I won't be able to do that cuz
not enough blood but I can play Alpha
with Reggie next to him
maybe oh [\h__\h] I didn't draw one yet
yeah that's
fine oops but now he's still not getting
rid of my gold
nuggets take a
squ oh well
Overkill kind of wanted my board to look
a little bit different but okay need a
light thank you moving on perhaps one of
these will entice
[Laughter]
you
oh funny guy child 14 and oh amam canine
K9 hooved reptilian feathered insect to
the
amalamal if only one of
them was a
Geck child 1 better care
[Music]
what if we put the effect of the Mantis
onto the amalgum N we want the we want
it to stay
cheap amalgum uses any oh cool
[Music]
true where hits like a
truck also true but how do you get four
blood in one go
bro they're all
good yeah we don't have
n
n I'll just take this at least that
makes my all my weird
totems not completely useless moving on
getting hungry here
good that I have goulash in my fridge
many many
goulash okay we're in the swamp aren't
we the the wetlands is that the same
thing cart and then sigil
maybe how's my dick
looking yeah still hoping for a good
card that gives me a good
sigil how low can the chances be of me
getting something good oh here we
go what's that what the [\h__\h] is that I
don't recall making that one wait it's
another one of those weird Eno
cards Bell
B does that make him skip wait the Bell
is to end to
turn red rep represented by this blah
blah blah
great oh the number of times the Bell
has rang is his
attack oh so pretty good for long
fights but I might pass again cuz
um yeah I think I want this on the
Mantis isn't that what we had
before yeah
the bottom one disappears
right yes yes right
yeah the the bottom one
disappears
okay
uh let's
go I am finally religious guys I believe
in the Mantis
God I will go to church from now on
every every day honestly every [\h__\h]
day we meet again
ye okay cat squirel okay nice nice nice
[Music]
be where to put you I could have also
also just gone for the cats I don't know
why I don't do that I I I don't know cat
behind stump okay next
turn I'm so hungry why am I so hungry I
had a little snack before the stream but
I guess it's been 4 hours maybe it's
okay to get hungry
again yeah not enough bones let's
go a little bit of pre- damage thanks
for the pink super
chat ah the new Mario
lady so far I wasn't really planning on
it I'm not too sure about those kind of
Nintendo
games I don't know didn't it also not
get the best reviews I don't know but
it's still pretty cute and good I don't
know I need to look into the game play a
little bit
more squ
squirrel squirrel cat cat
cat ah one more bone one more
bone he's got a mantis but not a mantis
[Music]
good ow ow wait maybe that wasn't so
smart oh I'm almost
dead it's okay I'll get out of
this I could have not gotten regad I
didn't have uh free bones I only had two
now I have free
[Music]
bones now just uh put him here s
o mantis will still kind of hurt me
though a little
bit oh oh no never mind I killed
it another wolf but you're you're so
done for soon you will
die you should get used to death it will
be your permanent State
soon m
a little bit
more a little bit
more ooh but I can't play it I don't
have enough blood how do I produce more
blood need to be on my
[Music]
period uh I guess I all I need to
sacrifice more than I sorry I've been so
used to only having to sacrifice one
thing I forgot that I can sacrifice
several things in one one go that's how
it works
but I don't know if I want to do
[Music]
that
ah attack attack freely as you wish my
beautiful
Monster my improved
[Music]
Chimera what was this again sorry I some
sometimes I don't I really don't
remember because they don't look really
like
anything uh the trial oh
trial uh getting rid of a card fancy
battle and another trial versus cards
sacrifice uh didn't I still want a
sacrifice no never mind battle and Pelt
Guy the one that sells pelts
right
okay open up
wa I for I forgot that I can still have
you w wa is back first wa best
wa y'all we have my de again pretty much
and she can still be sigiled ah do I
have something good to sigil her with
it's right in front of
us um
um Evolution I wouldn't mind doing that
I didn't want it on the
Mantis or we do the
parish
[\h__\h] uh the should we do the fwn change
it switch it up a little
bit and she would be four free
[Music]
Cat Why
cat no
no so you can sacrifice her without
needing the to pay blood to get her back
isn't that just an endless cycle wait
what so you can sacrifice her why would
I why I don't isn't it plus one plus
two
NY Oh you mean not necessarily for her
but just for
others I guess because then the
cat then waa will have two functions wa
will have the function of just being
Wawa and being the cat I
guess saves room on the board
true or transfer Evolution to the cat F
on cat F on cat
sure I mean why
not several nice
options maybe we'll find something even
better for the
Wawa wait other the way around
what what do you mean this is not what
you wanted I thought you want we want to
make the cat
stronger so
that Fawn on cat otherwise it would be
cat on Fawn it still kind of
works I'm so
hungry let me eat one one of my
chocolate
sticks just one fire in the water
why so hungry I can't think anymore I
need the
Snickers it's not a Snickers
though oh the ring worm is here
again good memories
that's
begin and end it
immediately do I have teeth to buy
pelts
mhm I
do oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'll keep the
rest I
[Music]
think maybe one
more maybe the wolf P oh wait
what ah okay I I thought he exchanged it
okay good I got both Wolf Pelt and the
fancy Pelt
[Music]
I don't have two of the same cards but
he could give me imagine imagine if he
would give me the Mantis god with but a
he gives it to me without the
sigils can he give me a a
pelt another golden
Pelt get double mantis gone
again this path can bring me back to the
right track but we already have full
items so I'll I'll go to the
mushrooms and hope he will give
me yeah you you'll give me a a duplicate
mhm I know you do don't change your
rules on me now I'm golden Bel I
knew I was just asking in Fury if it's
possible to offer me pelts I did not
want you to necessarily do it but if we
got another golden help we have a choice
of another rare exchange
later
but I don't
know
yeah I don't know if I want the
[Music]
double
fuse wait if I fuse amam will it be 66
but will it also cost four or will it
still cost
two two c for 66 she but kind of want to
do this is like gcha golden p is like
gacha I'll do
gacha um I'll make that choice on my own
I want to do gacha gacha brain Rod is
leading me to Greatness I'm
sure oh bro you're so
[Music]
done although your tree is going to
block it so I should put it here in the
middle see Waba understands at least
some things in this
game
MH I top de waa so often was this again
I forgot again is it the challenges the
trials
those the trials okay yippi I like the
trials now they're
fun uh two of the drunk Cuts must be kin
to pass what's kin this what ah they
must be of the of the same type like uh
I guess I think I
understand they must like they must be
like you know the same type to each
other T of power draw four attack power
combined to pass H I think maybe power
again please we failed last time except
for like the the end of the last like
the the boss boss thingy but before that
we failed oh oh we're f are we fine oh
we're fine we're
fine I passed let's
go
what free blood wolf card card reading
bearing the is free
what wait I could always put a squirrel
down then get the wolf and then
sacrifice the wolf that
way if we put like a the the thing that
puts the wolf cup back into my head hand
on it I but it can't because it's uh it
already has a special Sig anyway uh four
bones and the spikes ah but I think I
think I'll go for the
wolf I think I take the wolf
yeah if I sacrifice it like if I use it
as a as a powerful squirrel and even if
I don't want to I can
still I can still like Let It
fight mhm
mhm yes yes yes oh items
[\h__\h] I have space for one
uh bones I haven't used these in a while
is this like getting rid of one of his
cards oo I think I'll take that
scissor
um I have no I'll definitely take the
scissors
yeah let's go I haven't had that in a
while I like this I like the scissors
very useful here we go boss fight are
you fishing what what's this boss
fight what you first mistook for a
mishapen boulder misshapen Boulder
appeared to be a hulking man you attempt
to sneak past him but your footmate cont
with a metal bugget I we're
fishing I am the angler you are the
fish angler do you say in in German we
do say Ang angler
angler I think to
fisherman do you actually say angular to
fisherman in
English okay
doesn't wait we say fisher Anga Fisher
wait maybe we don't say
Ang wait okay I'm getting confused I
don't know anymore what we say in German
I only know we say a v z in maybe that's
all I need to know that's all you know
usually
anyway okay
uh interesting starting hand no Wawa but
interesting
what do you have king
fisher you're not going to fish this
turn
so I think I'll wait just play a normal
card for
now Pelt is good for the fishermen to
take yeah get it back right I will get
it back into my deck so it's not forever
gone right wait he f anti
Dives
damn can't even kill him with this sted
wolf might put it here to keep the
middle empty for the diagonal
attackers cuz I can't block that guy
anyway
bring out the Cub um
no I don't want
to
yet because then it will grow up and
then I'll feel like it's a waste of uh
like sacrificing him I guess I could
still sacrifice him in the first well
well I don't know
no king fish is he fishing this round no
right he didn't say anything is he
fishing he looks like he wants to
fish did he say he'll fish he must be
fishing he fishes every second
turn damn it I need to get a
squirrel or ah could have hoped for bone
card
I can put down the squirrel then the
wolf then the
Pelt or
even
yeah
squirrel wolf in a different POS ah well
it'll be
here it'll be
here
P oh all right it doesn't need a
sacrifice
oops uh ah if I put it here he'll he'll
like bring back
his king
fisher so let's push him pull him back
hey wait he didn't fish fish there we go
thought you would do it earlier okay
well now we have a
wolf uhhuh
[Music]
well uh he might be done anyway is he
done I think he's
done yeah never
mind [\h__\h] pelts on my
hand right I get you bro Go Fish so
you're fishing this turn
right I'll get the maybe a bom
card [\h__\h] [\h__\h] B
yeah the the voice is a little bit
creepy I could cut one of the
buckets but do we really want to use
that don't cut the buckets cut the buck
write one and you
win not yet
play
smoke
[Music]
yeah oh now he's fishing oh [\h__\h] I
didn't realize those were great white
sharks ah
[Music]
wait we have a squirrel here I might
drink
it
w w what took you so
long wa
go
here is he fishing what's the I don't
know if it's fishing
anymore huh he's not fishing right is he
fishing he won't fish in any case even
if he fished I I would get to kill him
first if he cast a shadow fishing oh
okay only in first face sorry for Gore
reignite which card will we get this
time thank you 49 mons oh my
God yeah oh
been that's what I said that's what I
said that's what she
said that's what she said bro a
moment yeah sheets of I yeah blah blah
blah
blah Pelt
traitor do these are the trials and this
was wait which ones which is this a
trial ride for pel ah okay nice I
thought so I wasn't
sure I P I wish it would just like show
me if I hover over it what it is like
the name of what it
is um for the rabbit pelt which is the
cheapest one right we get we
take oh [\h__\h]
oh oh there's good choices maybe the
road
um
yeah for the wolf P what that was
already great I'm already satisfied but
okay oh I didn't know the wolf pelt
gives you these shiny things
to right uh this mantis is the one that
stays on what was it
says
yeah it's uh it stays on the field I can
always this is like the cat mantis that
we considered creating I think Grizzly
with
Tails could have a man's
deck I do have like the the the insect
head Turtle evolution is
good possibly but I have a mantis
addiction
I have a mantis addiction and I am brain
empty wait I have two golden pelts right
I have two golden pelts
gotcha is this only the choice for the
first Pelt and then I get a new Choice
am the [\h__\h] is that question mark
amorphus when a cart bearing the sigil
is drawn this sigil is replaced with
another sigil at random what a c bearing
this sigil is drawn this ah well when I
when I draw the card I will have a
random sigil I won't know
what
AA wait does it actually have a meaning
I only know the Japanese amiba
[Music]
site CLA for insects wa what what will
it become after will it become a
mantis that would be too
crazy bug
dick
am
am goes up like four times
whoa but stream tck yeah I don't know I
like to go with familiar things I'm
sorry I'm I'm a coward oh I I don't get
a new selection okay then we can take
that one too okay I thought I would get
a new
selection all right all
right items [\h__\h] only used one fro wasen
a possum all right I think I see I saw
that before uh maybe
plier uh
for really rough
situations bones yeah I know
[Music]
but plus you guys don't even want the
players he even needs teeth
anyway emergency
zck to the user a frozen aosom is
created a new hand a frozen aosom is
defined as zero power five Health Frozen
away wait why uh just to use as a
wall is that why I would take it
I don't know they're all not the best
I'll take
this can't
decide okay three am man is God whoa top
deck
[Laughter]
crazy monkey
no no no no you will die you will die by
my
hands maybe we'll
[Music]
see get him get him get him get him get
him get him get him yeah together
teamwork yippee
okay we can buy more pelts how many
teeth do I have do I see that oh yeah
one two three four five or six kind of
difficult to
read no more
pelts would be good yeah we can go there
either
way
ow I don't like PS true oh yeah I'm sick
of pelts too in my in my
hand whoa I never saw that before what
the
hell the Bountiful Warren it spawns a
rabbit pickle when it is played pickle a
rabbit when a card bearing the S played
a bet rabbit is created all it's just
another little like sacrifice I
guess an elk and a pronghorn H maybe
I'll take the Pronghorn could always use
the sigils as well to
sacrifice I guess what do you
think next to strain um
oh oh kind of little oh
yeah it's getting better though I mean
the the pinch nerve is getting
better it's not as apparent anymore
prong hor for sacrifice yeah Warren
Warren nah
n wa need to do more things that Wawa
think even if wrong wa W do what wa
do um now but wait what what do we what
what are my cards can I take a look um
cuz we have we could sacrifice the
Cockroach right for the G right isn't
that what we wanted to do I did want to
do
that so we're we're choosing the upper
one now so I can choose the GE right
this is the right order
right bottom
disappears okay I don't want to mistake
it well last time it wasn't a mistake it
was a misinterpretation I suppose or
miscommunication but here we go we're
repeating
history
uh left can go also right afterwards if
you wanted to but right can only go
up h
M this is the the type cards this is any
cards I think yeah let's do the heart
fight for
fun Left Right
mushroom I don't know as long as we go
to the mushroom I guess we're
fine oh top
deck
[Music]
bro I want to get to a campfire to
strengthen my mantis God but what if
they eat it I still don't know really
when that happens I've been so lucky so
far stink bu what are you do again you
look so weird like I don't recognize you
anymore can't tell where who you are
where you
are
Tails tails
don't even have to think about the
gimmick
byebye ah but uh campire and the shoms
are in different
directions I don't
know huh come in
sky is this another ex
player merge the Mantis Gods okay holy
[\h__\h] moose Buck kind of crazy I already
have a prong
horn he
lost sounds
polish why are you laughing at him
leave him alone he's already
dead one bone is good yeah I don't have
much else use for my bones I guess but
he does not have any attack power I
don't understand so his only use is
being struck and then
dealing the sharp quills and then dying
but in any case definitely moving to
that point where he would be struck
a free sacrifice okay we'll see him as
that but I don't really like him very
much I don't like these cards uh we are
combining which makes the Mantis
stronger in the end anyway so I guess
that's what I
want do you have victims they're not
victims yes yes necessary sacrifices L
the Beauty and the beauty of
it no oh let me watch I like this
ritual I have a Deja Vu
guys I've done this before but it's my
winning strategy so why not do it again
right so could go left
again where do we want to go in the end
maybe look for funny totems
[Music]
again I don't want any more you only
give me stupid
cards I'll go left because in any case I
can still
decide and it won't be too difficult
anyway but wait that effect on the
totem ahuh you give it oh okay never
mind then we good
oh wait can I
also she stays on the field right no I
don't know whatever kill him do
it don't even think about
it 10 memberships what so many
memberships you guys are so nice
ah well I know somebody said left to get
rid of a card to trim my deck but I'm
still getting a card here too am I not
so it evens out maybe I don't
know yeah maybe that's the best
though getting a card totem has more
potential than one less
card I do I do still want the Bloods man
I I know I would just repeat my strats
but I do still want the blood please
give me at least a good card Grizzly egg
Snapper maybe we can take one that we
already
have uh do we
have Snapper we don't have
Snapper we don't have Grizzly either
damn it otherwise I would like combine
it eventually
but yeah
M grizly so it can eat the
perer what what
perer huh oh oh that's
brutal that's BR
what oh wait I thought it was brutal
because I thought you know G uh they're
like the same like family but no wait
Grizzly is a bear perer is a wolf never
mind we're fine not so brutal after
all okay come on you can't can he even
like is it possible for him to offer me
the same bodies that I already have
because if not then we have higher
chances
now
please no dupes okay please stop giving
me heads give me bodies ah interesting
actually though that's at least
something
else tails in my
hand do I want tails in my
hand so uh wait every when a card
bearing decision would be struck a tail
is created in this place and the card
bearing decision moves to the
right uhhuh it always moves how will I
use
this they don't go into my hand they go
on the board
okay um should I should I still combine
it with my mantis insect
card uh
things mantis what good for mantis go
never getting
hit saves mantis for a
turn okay let's try it
out I missed so much of the stream yeah
we've come pretty far we're going to end
this game now I will not lose no matter
how many times I have to Al F4 fight
fight fight fight okay this guy was the
Pelt guy is this a pelt guy
[\h__\h] what does the Pelt guy do again he
puts pelt in my hands or what was it you
took you're in the familiar sides and
sense of the Trapper pelts but something
was different the once friendly man now
beheld you with a Ste
gaze a Rob no not the fr no that was why
I had to out enforce so often today but
maybe we have better cards maybe we have
better RNG from the getg go we must what
you I'll be skinning you today did he
say that originally
[Music]
too no my no my no mantis
bro can I still get this
done ah he also gets the tail
what uh oh I was going to say maybe
squirrel card but I don't have squirrel
card uh bones also nothing necessary
right
now kill smoke with trap kill smoke with
trap wait we can get the wolf out at
least trap K smoke with
trap smoke of trap a
I right he's every
time not all I mean I don't want to make
the same mistakes again to listen too
much to
chat even though I do think you guys are
still like you know giving me useful
advice but uh I'm scared now I'm
traumatized
now why there because chat
settle but then I I did see chat also
saying left but then I also saw chat
saying
right uh anyway I
shall
place the
wolf
here I must trust you that doesn't sound
like too bad of uh opinion
could also cut one of his stupid frog
cards but maybe not right cuz this
doesn't this have a is this ah this is
the one where he has all the rare cards
at no no no let's wait with the cutting
until after he's showing me all his rare
cards right
[Music]
and I am
traumatized ooh bones and a
pelt all right but I also want to have
pelts mhm Maybe maybe we should have
gone to the Pelt shop one more
time
um
[\h__\h] feel like that's already bad
because maybe I hope for a cart that
takes
bones and then use my
bones or or I block of squirrel
n ah or I try to get the card with the
free blood
uh hook a frog yeah right we have a hook
and a scissor maybe I should hook one of
the frogs again or we keep it let's see
if we can do it by keeping uh those
items until the second phase
okay I appreciate that oh and you do
have the tail and you make what's in
front of you
weaker you go
here that was good that's a good
draw he counts as an insect even though
he looks like a person now more pelts
for
me oh my God I thought I died oh my God
I thought I died oh my God I thought I
died uh
[\h__\h] sh [\h__\h] wait what do I do
[\h__\h] I mean that was a good draw but I'm
still in
trouble well he's going to kill that
frog why did he not create the would be
struck oh because he's not getting
struck because he's weakening him with
his stinkiness bro you're useless right
now that's evening itself
out Heart Of Cards
H I think I need to
hook or or I use one of the pelts but I
kind of want to have more pelts but I
mean either I keep my items or I keep my
pelts in the end we don't need both of
that
stuff I think I'll uh okay uh I'll hook
a
frog and take a
squirrel
I'll I'll hook the real
frog and a not real
frog and I'll
put
SC in front no maybe a pill maybe the
Pelt I'll put the pelt in front of
you is this
bad cuz I want to sacrifice the
squirrel
okay then I could get another squirrel
and put bring out amum but
wait no he doesn't turn the things I
have up here in the P right I get I'll
get another
Square wall
wait wait I don't have space to put both
of them down
ah should I sacrifice
my wait do I get no I can't sacrifice
the Frog can't sacrifice the Pelt can
only sacrifice stink
bug H well
okay uh
pass the
[Music]
turn okay I can probably afford that cuz
yep these take care of each
other get another Pelt wolf comes down
get a trap
okay let's see what we get here red
okay let's
Place Amal
gum front the
frog or maybe not but
okay maybe the other way around would
have been better
but either way should be
okay
and I get the P yippe many
pelts neck is oh [\h__\h] wait
[Music]
[\h__\h] no it's okay I I still have about a
good card so
and El can oh okay little
mistake I I'll hope maybe I'll hope for
another bone card do I have another bone
card Wawa is a bone card right no waa
was a one heart
card but
oh
huh if only if wait I can't cut his card
because it's not up here yet [\h__\h] mantis
is good
[Music]
but it's okay I'm not that
sad um
probably need
a
[Music]
squirrel to play my
mantis how are we on the teeth oh we're
fine on the teeth wait
so um just to remind
myself not perish okay but I I can't do
it like three times in a row I suppose
so okay good good good
good okay now we have free pelts and we
have the scissors so we can actually get
rid of a whole
row show me what you got give me some
good
stuff oh
oh we're so much better in this
situation than last
time I think I want the
shark
and what's this again this is moving to
the maybe one Grizzly one
shark maybe even the
Moose yeah trade offer what yeah
take this nap it will be annoying to
deal
with
okay uh
here um
[Music]
this see the front row okay maybe not
the full front row because
I wanted that shark but I can cut the
remaining one in the front row
maybe this diagonal one The Raven isn't
even so bad I
guess I don't know if the Raven is worth
cutting should I cut
it a
raven no I can kill him this turn
have to blood H shark
three
four ah one two three and he stays
that's five five
damage right
[Music]
1 2 3 4
5 six oh cuz my man's does it
twice huh
okay was good was good was good was good
and I didn't completely rely on you
yeah okay I didn't even have to out for
my way out of it oo
oh don't do this to me why why
why more more M this
Gods what do you call a religion that
has several
Gods I don't know I'm brain empty I I
can only choose the things I already
know poly
polym Pol po Pol
polym I believe in polym
now oh we're already at the
end kind
of went through it really smoothly now
what do we
want I didn't even end up using the
scissors did I can you he just cuts the
boss surely you can't do
that
um should we
yeah definitely sacrificing what
combination do we have something for the
Mantis uh top survives top
becomes new man is
God sacrifice the small man is got h
I mean we could put the Mantis effect
on I'm a
gum
maybe
sheesh he's got glowy eyes
now
crazy ah yippe I'm scared but the last
boss fight was a little bit too easy
let's see how it goes this
time do I have an adder in my deck is it
going to be the same bus fight check the
room no did I do something wrong
hopefully not oh do we get all the funny
trials again I'm excited y
woo woohoo I want to do it yeah I'm not
going to run away this time I'm excited
waku waku waku waku n
uh trial of Rarity oo High chances we
did that before pretty sure we have high
chances uh we want one card with
Sprinter
or pelts I don't have any more pelts I
think so
Rarity I think notice hint on bottom of
table 11 no
no I I I feel bad for using chat too
much I would not have noticed this
otherwise do I have to turn the clock
behind me can I even still go
back I don't know maybe later I don't
know let the trial of Rarity begin
please please please please yes I
win that is a very rare card
indeed may choose one
choose twice or choose what I
want I think choose macpie maybe we can
still get this one again
okay
uh ah do I have a ring this time surely
have a ring right I mean don't you
always have a ring with how how loose he
was on the Rings
do I have a ring I don't have a ring
worm I don't have a
ring check your cards can
I I can't I think I
can ah in that case maybe
flying
yeah press W oh it no no no no no can't
look right now can't scroll can't click
I think we have more flyers I have the
ring but doesn't he also have to
no he pulls only the ring cards if I
have a ring card he doesn't do random I
do have
[Music]
shark I don't have a ring in this run
let's go flying please please please
please please please pleaseeee please
please please please
please I fail does that mean I don't get
to choose another one of those
cool um cheat
cards
[\h__\h] damn it [\h__\h] failure did you just
call me a failure wait can I get go away
no how do I check the no okay I'll be
fine that was still pretty
op yeah last time it was too op we want
to be a little bit less
op ah you
again sit mm
gladly um but wait can I also choose to
not sit look like I'll have to beat him
again
mhm oh how I relish this
moment me
[Music]
too two flames will not suffice this
time I will hold one and play with one
hand moon it's the moon
again cat Okay cat is a good
star uh we put some effects on the cat
that weren't the the best but could put
squirrel and then cat
right let's beat up the Moon
draw no oh wait oh yeah right no we
don't
draw
yeah
scre mole I'm like remember I yeah right
what does he have he doesn't have a mask
on
yet uh he's going to bring an Amal
gum but also this thing is going to move
wherever I attack first so I can't
really prepare for the Amal gum can I
H all right the amam won't move down
until the um okay wait let's put
squirrel
cat and then
bullfrog on the right so the meman will
move
there and we'll slowly take care of the
moment the bull but then I'm like I
won't go down
okay okay he's going to be
digging for gold he's going to make my
field into gold right that was it right
he's going to make at the end of the
turn my field into gold into gold no my
cat don't turn my cat into gold
yeah I don't want to play anything I'll
take a squirrel for
[Music]
now no not my
cat I he's going to bring down the
Mantis okay we'll prep we'll prep
um should I play this no we not play the
smoke
Oh I thought he would only move like
once he actually moves back and forth no
matter how many times I hit okay holy
[\h__\h] what did he always have so many
Amal gums I guess
so all right I choose I forgot that I
choose uh we shall choose our stronger
mantis and destroy everything in front
of us I think
[Music]
squirrel mantis he's not is he still
going to wait does he have he doesn't do
that thing again right he doesn't have a
mask on
so good to go could also still
cut one of his things
off but maybe I'll wait for that when
the amalgam comes down I don't know
isn't this
like no we'll see what happens he goes
there he goes there a he's gone
okay he's going to
fish ah my tail worked it happened so
fast why you gave me a lot of damage
though got a little little
tail uh that's un
killable comes back into my
hand
[Music]
oopsie that looks weird right maybe CU
it's a tail from a from a combined
mantis yeah it does damage I don't
really I thought it was a weak
card it's a free two out of two free
yeah
uh I'm still scared though
I'm not sure what to
do play
squir okay we'll put one leg leg in
front of one Amal gum wait I should just
I could still just this is the last
fight why don't I just cut
one should I not just cut
one I want to cut one
[Music]
free you would have one of you cut meman
before H well well there's different
ways to do to go about it I
[Music]
suppose
H
[Music]
oops for
how many bones I he'll die if I if I
just put it down anywhere but let's put
it down here is that okay so that we can
do double the
damage 1 2 3 4
5 there you
go phase two the moon soaked Forest bed
gave r to shadowy figures gasping for
night air after their long and torturous
Slumber ah yes I remember that one I
don't only remember
original okay
uh so he doesn't do the mask thing
anymore does
he he doesn't do with the mask thing
anymore I think summon the leg
yeah I'm still deciding
re I'll do this
what w is it
you could replace um him with Wawa right
away I mean the only reason to not do
that would be to give her a better
placement
[Music]
aren't we already winning this round
yeah wow was on the board baby moon time
this ought to work
again oh yeah okay I was like why do you
take a picture of me now I thought that
was later he took a picture of the
Moon still works just
[Music]
fine can we actually cut I thought no I
I said that before the battle as a joke
I can you that would be ridiculous now
that would be too op it shouldn't work
on the boss
card try it there will be a funny like
no oh you need a bigger scissor for that
my
friend yeah there are no cards of mine
that you can cut
yet how hold up wait until I have
something to cut oh I'm sure you have
something to
cut uh never mind here we go
okay at least the gold nugget is
gone
um oh [\h__\h] he's he's so dead oh he's so
dead oh he's so dead
oh oh oh he's going down he's going
down what you going to do
what it's fine I can still I can still
summon them right away oh that's a
different
tail that I got this sun huh ah it's
because it comes from a different uh
card I
[Music]
suppose oh
sorry sorry
you can pass now I don't want
to oh maybe M got would have been
[Music]
better when we kill we kill for
real oh let me least the overkill I want
more teeth
well go on finish it oh yeah we still
got to do it ah same reaction as last
time look at all these
tee
y okay now let's get the ending the real
ending let's take a picture of the
picture
taker you had won the respect of the
strange cabin's inhabitant your body
quaked as the adrenaline of the Bott
bad will subside leaving you with a
gwing hunger you had not eaten for days
that's true at least for hours I'm
hungry is it not
so oh surely this food will please
you I took Extra Care in preparing
it really does this not meet your
standards no I'm going to eat goulash
today my goulash is better I can share
with you I have I have many
[Music]
servings stand there Deja Vu
everything's a Deja
Vu it's just immersive for me
to use the same kind of
deck put it in who gave you that quick
click click click smile
cheese wait was that too late did I have
to to
click
I I clicked really late was that did
that matter when I
clicked could I have failed I got him
could I have failed I clicked so
late he's there it's
beautiful it's like a is this like a new
game plus is there more things to look
at there's is are these the bodies oh no
oh no all the bodies
it's so shiny blinding me
huh am I him now
oh is this just a starting screen huh oh
oh go it's the starting screen
H what about
this
oh oh now instead of continuing we do
the actual new
game that really wasn't there before but
begin data
wise oh purging deck
data oh oh oh oh renal start a new
game in the beginning the world did not
know cards there's a hand shape that
looks like the globe that was in the
room that is until the day the scribes
arrived oo oh he's so Square he looks
like the St each had their own method of
inscription to create cards it's like an
RPG
intro grimora used her cool to inscribe
the EP TS of the
Dead Oh Lei used his wildlife camera to
capture beasts Ley isn't that
the po3 used the particle scanner to
copy the CPUs of
robots and magnific magnificus used his
brush to paint his wizard
[Music]
pupils with the cards created the
scribes had solid solidified their
power until one one day a challenger
arrived to replace one of the
scribes huh
replace
why it's like a Zelda
story n choose a starting deck to mark
your
ambition
Oh Oh you mean I oh no because I always
had to start with like this lame dick
can I look at them
properly is I is this automatically
choosing them I want
to I don't want
[Music]
to okay but like should we just do this
next
time a strong advice against don't you
guys hate the magic deck why it's too
difficult
no okay then we can stop here cool cool
oh alter deck ah for a new game is
that oh we look at that another time I
guess
interesting you can now make custom
decks it's so different then it's such a
different game
then oh wait did it as longest tutorial
I don't really see it as a tutorial
though maybe the first like run so to
say but this what we just played now
that didn't feel like a tutoial that's
just story I wouldn't say it's tutorial
it's just the
story and this is like like just the the
gaming grinding mode you know what I
mean it's like when you finish the story
part of a game and now you can just
enjoy all the mechanics of it or
so it was the first part is there more
story but is there more story about the
guy that we um kept on seeing and
hearing
today yeah oh
sick he's making some Grand discoveries
with this lost floppy dis
oh I just saw on Holzer there's another
person playing inscription later in a
couple of
hours how fun how far see the
inscription addiction
continues I wonder maybe she can also
get to where I am
today she hasn't started it yeah I
thought she played once
already
oh ah she hasn't won yet but I think she
has the
[Music]
eye
oh sorry you
lied oh no
worries did not trust us about the
ringworm me or her
I think with the game being a bit spooky
and octob being just passed a lot of
people are playing it up soon yeah I
chose it because I thought it would be
maybe a little bit creepy but it wasn't
really the best kind of game to use as a
Halloween game I guess that was just me
cheating my way out of it once
again but um I I don't know I'm happy
with my
choices ooh I got DMs many
DMS okay something to check out
later I got to check
out a video
[Music]
later let's move to a room where I can
read super chats
[Music]
yay 5 hours 20 I didn't think I would
play the game so long today but I still
got time cuz I started early today
yippee um maybe let's go
here
sure
uh Girls Talk
night
oh a little bit of
[Music]
Center there we
go hello welcome to my room it's super
chat reading time Super Chat reading
time Super Chat reading Super Chat
reading Super Chat rating Super Chat
reading Super Chat reading Super Chat
reading
uh audio stock let me choose
something AIO
stock how about this one
yes okay I hope you liked watching today
I feel like uh you maybe it was a bit
disappointing cuz I tried to rely on
chat too much I'm sorry I I'm just so
scared of
losing but I tried to after being
betrayed so many times I try to focus a
little bit more on you know just trying
things out a little bit but not too
much I do the same thing okay thank you
not at all no worries it was fun you're
having fun we are thank
you I think relying on T led to most of
the losing right but I I do want to say
even with without that I would have lost
anyway I think either way I had to lose
to find the the light at the end of the
tunnel a little reminder for all members
in casee you haven't seen the wallpaper
for the me uh for the members for this
month is up on the community board check
it
out
and super chats yeah where where do we
continue I didn't know you could out
afford to avoid
losing yeah that's also something I
probably wouldn't even have considered
trying if it wasn't for chat but I I
should have considered it because I did
do that insulate the
Spire actually let me try to remind
[Music]
um uh
uh C
model I can't continue with the shorts
because we still don't have the Cali
model
unfortunately sorry so we probably have
to do again something else first
finished Mirage did I stop Midway
through oh where is
GD is GG
here St on please send model yes please
otherwise at some point if it takes too
long I I had a feeling it would take
longer and then we should just do
different outfit but I wanted to give
them the benefit of the doubt H bags
okay thank
you is CD taking a day
[Music]
off where am
I
here oh that's why you said gig is going
to stream soon Oh I thought you were
just randomly bringing it up I was about
about to scold you I love gigy but we
should
still like I was thinking of reminding
people anyway let's follow the rules
like I generally don't really mind and I
just often often I even react to it when
other people bring up other people
randomly when viewers bring up people
randomly in my chat but yeah not really
supposed to do that and it gets a little
bit uh like sometimes sometimes
appreciate it sometimes it's n like H
but generally I feel like I'll could
just ignore no need
to make a big deal out of
it but a general
reminder but generally it's not a big
deal is GD bonked no are you suffering
oh ah you sent a Super Chat to tell me
are you
bonked uh send some hearts
in the chat GD in the in the bottom
right
thing
[Music]
oh oh G is bonked I think
so otherwise you can see her
messages oh wait now I see it what what
where were you you were just like you
just wanted to send the Super Chat to
make it like unmissable for
me okay okay maybe I just missed your
uh normal chat message by human era or
Phoenix era
oopsie all right let's read some super
chats ja 47 D oh wa
thumnail Hol
bags where's H
bags oh right hold b i Ed I reused the
thumbnail
[Music]
some thumb nails are just so good I
don't think I can improve it anymore
check 47 D Studio Rob thank you D for
the pinky T you got this in the bag T A
pun a good
one good bgm right I know thank you
Studio Rob
I love I love my Holo Bag series I'll do
it again sometime please look forward to
it py D Cru than orbital Vagabond
Vagabond v v Vagabond Vagabond
tun fat
kner what a name thank you for the Super
Chat tun zipley thanks for two pinkies
and an orange one hey W kind of off
topic but I just watched your last V and
saw you having a d Vu about me being
here for only two years did some diing
found out that my first private chat
message was in your first whole back
stream the hell how topical I kept
looking for a good while after that and
started chatting more frequently after
your Fe simulator
streams simulator stream you reply to
one of my messages got me hooked line in
Sinker oh yeah I know I can get people
hooked when the streamer you're watching
replies to you then you're like oh my
god wow I've got
noticed now I feel feelings I've never
experienced
before yeah the interaction hooks us
just like the guy who's fishing for
cards I'm fishing for you
guys streamer noticed me let's [\h__\h]
go for me it was you threatening to
disappear me in a river
I did that why did I I threatened you
why didn't I go through with it huh I
wonder a cute Ang look fishing for
chickens see chicken see chicken chicken
chicken why wouldn't I be fishing for
you
guys
H sea
chicken chickens of the sea
it's real oh by the way I gave my mom uh
some
souvenirs SL
presents and finally I gave her those
sardines that I got in New York I don't
even I think I told you guys that I went
into the Sardine
store right the New York sardine store
that has all kinds of funky sardines um
but I don't know if I told you that I
actually bought one I bought the one of
the birth year of my mom um and she
didn't know she was surprised by it when
I gave it to her but she was delighted
by it because she actually likes
sardines yeah and I gave her lionello
that I got in Italy lemon cello and
proo uh she really likes lemon
jello and prco of course too and I gave
her
um I have a picture of this but I don't
have my phone right now damn it um
I gave her so I was in Venice right and
Venice is known for a certain glass that
is made in
Morano which is a place a little island
I guess in Venice next to Venice or so I
uh I don't know if it's a city or just a
village um but yeah they have like a
special glass technique thing and it's
really famous and so if you if you're in
Venice and 80% of the souvenirs will be
Morano glass it's like really colorful
and pretty and they make everything they
make bowls they make glasses they make I
don't know anything magnets and so what
I got
was a chicken rooster big rooster
shaped
uh
bottle closer
thing cork thing it's not a cork it's
made out of metal but it's like you put
it into a a usually like an alcohol
bottle I think to close it again you
know what I mean and on top of it sits a
big rooster out of Morano gloss yeah
yeah a plug a
stopper yeah so if you put the stopper
into the uh the wine bottle or so it
looks like a huge rooster out of M glass
is sitting on top of the
bottle yeah that's what I gave her cuz
she likes
chicken she likes chicken very
much
yeah she liked that
gift yeah
she likes you guys yeah of course she
[Music]
does yeah she was happy I think I gave
her some other stuff too but those were
the most important
ones okay where was I oh yeah ziply
sorry I tented it ah no wait we're not
even done you sent one more not sure why
I went through the trouble of digging
through the logs I guess I was
questioning my memory now I should be
flattered that you think I'm an OG or
not that two years with me feels like
four what no no no no not no it's not in
a negative sense it's just I don't know
feels like you've been around since a
long time and and two years is a long
time too but no there's nothing negative
about that's not like no it's not like
that don't take it like
that I wouldn't want a kfp without you
you
know thank you so much for your
support nice that you're not Angry
Anymore
also El La D CeCe D bro D rection
D and Nath coton than for the pinky I
find the sheet blanket discussion
interesting sheet blanket
discussion ah that one for example I
normally sleep with only a thin sheet
over my body and can't stand sleeping
with a blanket unless I'm actually sick
and trying to get better hey yeah you
must be used to it like you must think
of the fact that they even sell
weighted weighted weighted heavy
blankets to give you even more of a
feeling of being hugged by it so I think
people generally just like this feeling
of being cozily hugged by this fluffy
fabric that is a
blanket I don't necessarily need or this
desire heavy blankets just a normal
blanket is fine for
me but yeah in summer sometimes like I'm
also so desperate
for a less hot experience during the
night that sounds weird a less hot
experience I I desire a less hot
experience during that interesting um
but uh I really like just the Sheep
is like less hot but then the that kind
of gives me a harder time to sleep
because it just doesn't feel like what
I'm used to like a
proper hug you know the the sheet is
just too light
and so I sleep worse with a sheet but at
the same time in summer I also sleep
worse with a proper blanket cuz it's too
hot and I I do have two two different
blankets I have winter blanket and I
have a summer blanket but even the
summer blanket that's supposedly a
summer blanket is
hot but the summer was okay the few
weeks of the summer that I spent in
Austria were okay actually pretty very
bearable but the ones I spent in Japan I
had air conditioning so that was fine
but you know I had other problems the
[\h__\h] pillows
or the one
pillow yeah that was
rough to find something in between a she
may be really I've tried that too I've
tried like different blankets that I
have that are just like th cuddle
blankets they they're kind of thinner
than my um W summer blanket but I don't
know well this month this year was fine
anyway maybe next year I'll have
troubles again we'll see
I'm in Croatia I usually just use a
blanket cover by the way Tassimo I was
like I was I was
perplexed when I was
watching uh the VOD of a certain Creator
playing life is strange I
think and I saw I heard him say your
name
bro but I know you speak German so did
you like start
watching did you start watching nendo
after I mentioned him so
often or did I just imagine him say your
name pretty sure I'm pretty sure he said
your
name we all start watch no why would you
do that you don't even understand
him I checked him out yeah
ah I was like wait what the [\h__\h] why is
my chicken here
but with you it at least makes sense CU
you speak the
language
funny my chickens follow
me I can't I have to I have to always
expect chickens around
me no problem with it though but I I was
really uh Bamboozled by it
we're free roaming aren't we I guess one
could say
[Music]
so free roaming
but if you choose to stay in the
coupe I shall be very
delighted but it depends as long as you
still treat me as your one and only you
can still roam around
[Music]
anyway just got to prove that you're
good to go you're safe to let go
otherwise I'll put you on a leash when I
let you free
roam I roam around
you
cute wow jealous maybe a little bit
maybe maybe sometimes a little bit but
whatever
yeah anyway thanks Nathan for this uh
blanket tangent mp53 g d non Square
pixels dang Sky dang mp53 G dang setac
dang SP
spite dang potato x d v d chatino lawyer
D Black penguin D V D chatino lawyer D
Steph sings
dun uh eight King maybe dun Brown
oh no we don't do that in
holo no no no no Kenzie dun Lo of pine
Channel dun thank you thank you
oh thank you so much for the sweet words
I'm glad we could help you star Creator
D not a high tier D Kenzie
Dun A I watch anime only like Members
Only Watch Longs these days otherwise
not really
Sky no J swag d tantum d bot the
g d for the pinky oh is it time to say
Kami this is I guess this was when I was
reading the super chats and I reacted uh
very dramatically to everybody who
called me Koshi
I love the notes of no context I only do
that because I know some of you guys
follow along when I read hyzer super
chats anyway
and uh the ones that I'm saying no to or
so or I'm replying to without reading
the Super Chat probably know what I'm
talking about anyway because they sent
the Super
Chat yeah saves me some
time so yeah uh best idle for four years
and forever let's go PS actually failed
to make rainbow due to App Store
delay oh no app store why why do you
betray w
w bad bad bad under you thank you so
much W
come y y
yay game
8910 edtion com right d Jim Tracy D and
unknown d
[Music]
okay next is seven days to
die oh the Seven Days to Die
Arc how does Jacob 47 manage to send the
Super Chat in the beginning every time
do you have a bot or something
how do you do it how do you do
it I miss it a couple times
really always kicking off my Super Chat
readings Jacob
47 he who fa Jackson FB D
Evan black friction d
Brandon
R and ni meet you son or son I don't
know where Ed son D for the red super
chat K Mirage is amazing thank you for
all your hard work I love you thank you
for enjoying Mirage keep on streaming
Mir we're over a million now
but it's still growing steadily I'm glad
very proud of my
Mirage thank you so much for listening
M there's still videos to come so it's
not over yet and tomorrow we have a
special
stream in
Fry to show off the Mirage
model
yay test people d g g
d time black
and thank you very much for the Super
Chat
everybody
next is another seven days the surprise
surprise I guess it's only 7even days to
die from here on
out maybe this was a spoiler all along
that I would sing for
blood on my Halloween stream hey no it
wasn't actually wasn't
[Music]
Gabriel Martin thank
you ghost of mint h
d
RAR
D soldier of Joy action forgot how to
read that for a moment I was about to
read
soldier soldier soldier boy na la re re
rise k
re D thank
you thank you I'm glad you enjoyed my
music let's
go Crank That old boy
you so
deer Sky d n diesel thanks for the red
chat hi Waba I got a World ticket for
Indonesia and Singapore all n diesel
will be
traveling can't wait to see more vaa
performance and get to know more KP IRL
by the way today it's my birthday can I
get a birthday song from my oi Rak and
can I sign up to be your
assistant I wish maybe if you lived here
uh wait you didn't go to the one in
America right so this these are your
first ones but getting getting to go to
two is already quite the privilege good
job I hope you will enjoy
it and share your thoughts with
everybody make sure to be as orange as
you possibly can
thank you so much I'm excited to hear
your your you know experience
report happy birthday to
you happy birthday in your shoe happy
birthday in your pants to happy birthday
Nene let's go
congratulations mwah mwah mwah
yeah aren't you traveling
already I think I saw something about
you traveling today or
so safe travels to
you hope it goes
well uh Pugo dun s or sin8 thanks for
the picky might as well rename the
stream to ELA genan experience after
nights event Ela Jean
experience why who's Ela
Jean what you
[Music]
mean does someone know the meaning don't
look that up
context don't look that up scary is
it now I want to look it up
that
thing
huh too
spicy tasteless joke okay then I will
not
look thank you v action D Super Snake
Mario thanks for the pinky hi K today's
my birthday o another birthday and I'm
glad I got a chance to spend some time
here today with you and my fellow K
thank you for always being my ray of
sunshine seeing you always brightens my
day I'll always love and support you my
Kami oi thank you so much yay I'm still
your Kami oi I'm happy to hear that
happy
birthday happy birthday to you happy
birthday in your shoe happy birthday in
your pants too happy birthday to Mario
[Music]
congratulations I hope you had a lovely
birthday even though it was already a
while
ago hope you don't
mind yeah I would appreciate your
ongoing
support you guys are used to that song
yeah it's not weird anymore at all never
has been
reard D thank
you oh all no problems it was worth it
that jacob7
and thank you for super
chatting you hear it in your sleep oh no
not the best song to hear in your sleep
[Music]
should be hearing Mirage in your
sleep that would be
better here we go next
one Ari D ja for7 V faction D spank
andham D for the r j I've got my popcorn
and my cat is ready I'm ready for we wa
let's
go thank you I'm glad you were able to
watch and have a good weekend
hopefully thank you so
much
taga Brandon d d sphe d fur d sphe
d soldier of Joy d i see like some
unusual super Chatters here is this the
time
zone cuz I don't think it's necessarily
the collab partners because other people
had their povs open and
stuff interesting thank you guys tanuk
dang joar hero thanks for the pinky it
is now my 30th birthday in my time zone
it's been a rough lead let up lead up to
due to personal matters as well as
hurricanes hitting all the places my
family lives oh my God everyone is safe
okay but I'm glad to spend part of it
with watching my favorite
Phoenix yay thank you for spending your
special day with me dun and I hope that
from now on nature will go more easy on
you because what the
heck a you guys got it rough with
hurricanes and
stuff take care of yourself and happy
belated birthday happy birthday to you
happy birthday in your shoe happy
birthday birthday in your pants too
happy birthday joa
hero congratulations the 30th is a
special special Milestone to achieve
you've done it can you imagine living on
this crazy Earth
that like it's so difficult to live
in so many challenges and so many weird
things like for 30 years can you imagine
holy [\h__\h] if you think about it damn
you've this is like a game that you've
played like and suffered
through for so many
years leveled up for so
much you've come so
far still
kicking yeah 30d is a badge of honor for
real
I'm awful at this game NE I need to be
back seated
too
Oho I mean I feel
like being back seated for my first
couple years would have been useful but
nowadays I'm I'm okay at least I I
found uh a good job that will take away
some of my worries
yum problem is most people that get back
seeders in life do the opposite of what
back seaters
say not necessarily I wouldn't
necessarily say
so like you could even say your back
seaters are your friends or so who give
you advice and I feel like a lot of
people listen to their friends maybe
they won't listen to their family but to
their friends more
so Billy bom
D elpp
cabalo thank you so much for the
support El Dapper cabalo again thank you
H and small cookie bear see another like
unusual
one thank you for the red super chat
dear Ki I'm sorry for suggesting to
fauna about abusing your Phoenix
rebirths to harvest you for infinite
food in seven days I completely forgot
that the girls can also use feathers for
arrows too
ah you mean my
feathers wait a second wait a
second
H but that's a waste of my Phoenix
feathers for [\h__\h] arrows maybe it
makes the arrows a bit more overpowered
gives them some special buff or
something but don't
not without my
permission thank you TD oh work
time thank you for hanging out good
luck okay next one oh wait think we get
a
kiss even though that was concerning
Super
Chat cute made one
cute here you
go these are also short so we can kind
of Zoom forward and catch up a little
bit ja 47 n hul nag for two pinkies I
lost my armor and I can't find it
anywhere I'm now naked please don't look
at me I'm too much I'm too shy I can't
do my job properly and safely without
armor so I can I wait didn't I read this
already sounds so all 100%
familiar I just reacted in Pre
chat didn't I already also give you a
new
job you didn't change it
though might lose my armor but some
things will never change such as your
streams bringing me joy and inner peace
and for that my Lord belongs to you and
you alone for past four years for many
years to come much love my Kami y thank
you thank you so
[Music]
much H okay well what but I did suggest
you new job I think in the
chat h
but why can't you keep the current One
Winged haard and that's isn't that fine
that seems
fine are you still not happy with it do
you still want to change
it you can see your chat oh I guess
so I don't know how I don't want
to you don't see my didn't I I didn't
say anything really
maybe I just gave it a heart reaction
cuz I definitely somehow reacted to it
fighting with an armor can be no I told
you gold is the armor it still make a b
b clink clink clink sound when I knock
on your
body that's still armor it's just really
fancy
armor and you're still winged
so it's not too soft
no it's it's fine it's
fine otherwise okay how about uh okay
okay okay for now you shall be uh if you
really
so desire a new position don't don't you
dare you have to take this position now
that I'm giving you and you may not
complain you shall be Christmas tree
decoration if you really think you're
useless for battle okay let's use your
shiny goldness and your roundness is to
just hang you up on the tree on my tree
on the kfp
tree mhm merch
idea what will he do for the rest of you
I don't know you'll hang on corness
Empire's tree I guess
H what do you think
hokan now I almost feel mean now but I
think it's a cute idea but it's just
very seasonal we can change it again
after the
season maybe yeah maybe he's hanging uh
hanging himself up right now on my tree
my tree doesn't exist yet
but changing the
name oh
you changed it
yay okay you don't seem so
[Music]
disappointed saluting and everything all
right then satisfied
customer I'm so good at customer service
just so
good thank you so much for your
support well let's hope that you'll be
happier with with RGB in the future cuz
I'm telling you RGB chicken does not
make a clink cl cl cl sound when I knock
on you so you're going to be even
squishier but no but at the same time no
because I did say you guys have immunity
or something like that right because
you're going to be
[Music]
like
yeah all
right that's definitely something to
look forward to ziply D Cruz D spank
thanks for the red of Chat Cat codling
time is the best small cat and big cat
lovees sleeping late even if it means
their breakfast is delay
oh man I'm jealous I've seen some stuff
on my
timeline um today and yesterday
about
like dogs and cats being confused
especially dogs though because like they
don't freaking care about uh daylight
savings
time and you sleeping in and giving them
food one hour
later for
me the like I know some cat owners who
always feed their cats at the exact same
time pretty much but my time is so
unstable I feel like this is more common
with dog owners though feeding their
pets at the same time every time but my
cats are used to me just feeding
them like whenever I woke up and
whenever I go to sleep which can be
different times varying between a a like
a time frame of like 5 hours or so
sometimes I go to sleep at midnight
sometimes I go to sleep at 5:00 a.m. and
yeah but they always have Kibbles so
your cat is struggling with the time
change really my request my cat request
the same time
what is it because you guys raised your
cat like that though because you you
raised your cat by feeding it you
decided to do that at some point right
always feeding it at the same time I
never did that so
what Valencia got flooded really hard I
was wondering what you were talking
about cuz I like
Valencia
[\h__\h] that
bad holy
[\h__\h] no no Valencia
damn that's not the Valencia that I
know I didn't know about it at all what
the
hell what it's been going on for
days I haven't heard about that at
all my algorithm is clogged up as
[\h__\h]
sad where was I oh yeah oh yeah yeah I
find this interesting a lot of you guys
seem to have a a rhythm with your cats
or dogs or
whatever I
don't skill is you guys should have
raised your cats and dogs
differently my dog would ask to go out
at night and every every day every
weekday because that was when my
grandparents would leave him leftover
around a
cute every time I walked in the kitchen
there was no they yeah same same same
same you know chunky wony okay I here
comes tangent that you absolutely do not
care about and can't really relate
because you're not there to experience
it but it's so [\h__\h] cute believe me
so chunky wonky normally only eats cbles
right but um
she always likes I feel bad for her like
when I I give I give smoothie like wet
food every morning every evening and I
just feel bad that chunkies chunky wony
always eats the same
stuff so at some point I started this
year maybe to sometimes give her not
always not every day but sometimes I
would surprise her while smoothie is
eating her wet food cuz chunky wonky
she's like going around a little bit
curiously when whenever I give her wet
food smoothie when I give smoothie wet
food chunky monkey is like just looking
around
curiously so I started giving her those
like licky thingies the licky tube
thingies um like half half of uh one
usually I don't feed her the whole thing
um and not every day and surprise her M
and she's so happy with
it and she just gets so happy and so
excited and now now she expects it like
every time to and but she gives up and
and she doesn't like wake me up for it
she gives up very fast when she no
thises oh it's not happening today but
but but now she's
like she gets so excited too and it's so
cute I can't resist giving her like more
often
now yeah it's basically Go-Gurt
oh there's like yogurt in in those like
thingies too for kids right
never had it but it's a a really nice
treat for
them who has been condition cattle or
owner
both no but she's so cute and she
deserves it you know I really wonder why
she completely refuses wet food it's
kind of weird because like like she
doesn't even maybe it's like the
dominance that smoovie asserts over the
wet food but she shows like no interest
where I I feel like she would like it if
she tasted
it but she just doesn't it's not like
she doesn't like wet things because she
likes the the licky
thing and I do think
um when I served them like tuna out of a
can they ate it before too which is kind
of similar to wet
food I think she gobbles up tuna so
doesn't like the flavor but I've tried
so many different ones over the years I
feel like maybe like in the beginning
she may have tried it and then she
decided she doesn't like it and now she
thinks it all tastes the same or so even
if it smells differently cuz they got
really big really good sense of smell so
she would notice it smells differently
but maybe she still thinks well I tried
it once I don't like it we'll never try
it
again some cats just don't recognize wet
food as food don't think nor knows why
you
cat oh any anyone those why
oh yeah it's weird but so because she
doesn't eat any of it I've been giving
her lots of tritos and she's so happy
and she's so floppy and so what I do is
whenever I give any of them treos I pick
them up and I force them because
normally they're not um lap cats but I
force them to be a lap cat and I I put
them on my lap and like put my arm
around them and then I give them tro
right in front of my face that's the one
time they will tolerate it only for the
the length of being treated the
treos yeah happy I'm hoping that one day
that will result in them being naturally
trained into liking the lap
again cuz I know like people treat their
cats and dogs to with treats to tolerate
and like things and so on but so far it
hasn't worked at all I've done it for a
while now man I always put them on my
lap when I give them a
treat never anywhere
else they're too smart they
know
that they that I'm like brainwashing
them them they know
it damn
it one day one day they'll return to
being lap
[Music]
cats simple thank you
Valentine H for the pinky you're are no
long T aim thank you
a never
was py D mysterious stranger dun daku
dun and PSY D again thank you so
much two times W oh is this where
I this is where
I cloned myself in the end
huh oh
no oh wait this is where I had a
different stream in between
huh I had whole life Treasure Mountain
[Music]
okay but I'm getting really hungry and
tummy acting up so let me just read this
one and
then H wait did
I yeah right
yeah I read this one and then we'll call
it a
day my tummy is
[Music]
grumbling okay Cruz D Jacob 47 d I hear
you missed it you missed being the
first take
monkey T thank
you Tim Tracy Anthony web thanks for the
red chat K thank you for always being
our amazing T always Sicilian caring
happy belated four years and here's to
hoping for many more to come ooh a
little bit of a belated anniversary
message thank you so
[Music]
much I try my my best thank you for
seeing the best in me
Anthony hopefully hopefully you'll stay
around if you'll make me stay around
then you got to stay around
too thank you welcome back
snowy oh you going to go again I'm also
ending soon
Anthony did you get a kiss though
Anthony there you go ashar face with
pinky 3.5 years since finding you and
the rest of myth for years since
becoming a member and I had so much fun
in all that time thanks of being who you
are here's to the Future
a thank you thank you for supporting me
hope you've been
enjoying to be part of kfp and being a
member time does fly yeah on to more
years yeah to the
Future go go go
together thank you so much the sign
[Music]
painter for the
uh reer CH I
[Music]
earn
uhuh what what do you earn well I earn
99.99 bucks thanks to your red Super
Chat thank
[Music]
you py D and delar D thank
you y okay hold up a little
bit a little
bit Yeah okay after the cuts I don't
earn that much anymore that is
true progress was made yeah we're
getting at least even if in number
there's uh so many to read at least uh
we're getting closer to the date of
today only two weeks behind now yay
maybe I can read some tomorrow too we'll
see I I don't know we'll
see we'll see how I feel how the vibe
is but we're not reading the ones from
the Halloween stream you know for the
Polaroids so don't count that
one it was one month before Improvement
see got to look at it like
that
yeah okay I don't know why I had to stop
it like
that
continue
let's let's Let it go
smoothly I will have you guys know I'm
jealous at a certain non vtuber content
creator
who is on Twitch has all the twitch
Fame random tangent and so see see what
they did this is like one of those Clans
okay and they I don't know what the hell
was happening but they were doing a
stream where they were like celebrating
subscribers or whatever and they were
bouncing and listening to music and the
moment they hit that special Milestone
they were listening to a song from new
jeans and so that was clipped many times
and the way they reacted you know a lot
of new jeans fans reacted to that and
and and they like everybody reacted to
it just it the the pure coincidence that
they played a Eugene song made this
happen but uh it became kind of like
viral and a meme and then Eugene saw it
and they recreated the moment in a in a
YouTube short SL Tik Tok SL whatever and
then those guys they reacted to it again
and we're like oh my God oh my
God and now now I saw a clip of that one
particular
guy uh who was like most affected by
this going
viral
um getting to meet new jeans flying to
Korea and I need newans and it should
have been me what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
bro how why apparently he had context
Who had contexts who had contexts who
reach new genes and because I don't know
it went so viral or something so I need
to become viral with something Eugene's
related
to I love them more than he
does I love new jeans more than he
does newans
[Music]
that's all I wanted to
report if H life can cover English songs
now I hope you can cover cable songs in
the future as
well um I if I cover it the same way
like that I still have to pay for rights
and it might be expensive
I don't know I would I feel like I would
have a chance if I were allowed to do um
dance
covers that could somehow reach them but
I'm not allowed to do it so maybe what I
could do is I make
unarchived new jeans k/ dance
stream sing your songs and dance them
people can clip that and send it around
the world around the world around the
world around I can't upload it but I can
quote retweet everything on Twitter and
hope that on YouTube it also goes around
around the world I need I just need my
my clippers to support me on this
endeavor pudding El Lain C IO where are
you guys help me are you in or are you
out smk you too
are you guys in or are you
out I was planning on doing a new jeans
K sometime soon anyway because at this
point there's already quite a bit of new
jeene songs on the K application that we
use and as you may know we need to use
um tracks that we have permission to use
so we usually use that application
nowadays
well it doesn't even have to be Clippers
who clip it of course it can be anyone
but Clippers already have a little bit
more of a reach maybe maybe but
everybody should clip I guess I know
what I'm clipping
tonight the the
plan Clippers
sample okay it's a plan it's a plan
let's do it let's make it happen
okay I don't know what exactly you're
clipping but yeah do it in the fever
night fry no maybe in the Mirage
Frey Fever Night fry a little bit too
lud and Mirage fry looks a a little bit
more official because the face is the
same as my um default official
one fever Knight has shocked many people
people and I need to go easy on that
model okay I leave you guys see you
tomorrow in Germany s bye-bye thank you
for watching yeah yeah yeah had fun
description very good game very
addicting top Tech GE Wawa card best and
montis God the only God I believe in
besides the other montis God
bye-bye ah merch merch sales ending soon
so merch
reminder Link in the description
[Music]
m
down