[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign foreign
foreign
[Music]
thank you
hello hello
welcome
hi it's a people it's people okay
[Music]
English Advent and I'm a sparkling Gem
and
I'm on coffee and I'm on not very much
sleep but that's okay that's okay
because we're playing beeping Baldur's
Gate however
um
okay so the time that we have together
uh where everyone else is is asleep
right now I'm gonna introduce my
character to you guys okay meet uh
people
is going to okay
[Music]
okay first of all what do you mean what
is that I'm a gnome I'm a gnome I'm a
gnome I'm short
[Laughter]
isn't that aren't they cute I'm cute I'm
a cute gnome
I'm a gnome what you mean was she's so
cute so cute dang it and okay look okay
I'm a forest gnome I'm a gnome because
that way I can get talked to animals and
I can get heated but that'll come later
okay I'm a no so I can speak with
animals because I had to talk to animals
even though you know I am not being a
Jewish okay
now you may be wondering people you're
starting as a cleric no I'm not gonna
end up as a cleric
we was going hardcore people's
multi-classing
so I am going to be multi-classing so I
am not going to end up as a cleric but
we are starting as a cleric
um and then we are multi-classing into
sorcerer
I'm going I'm going Pew peel mainly
because I can fly I want to fly a lot
because you know that's my thing so I'm
Gonna Fly and in more ways than one
and and I can shoot magic you know I'm a
magical girl so why not
um okay so 10 tips I have whiteboard
guidance lights okay normal pretty
normal uh
sub class I'm doing Tempest domain
because I'm gonna end up as a pew pew
sorcerer so we're doing we're going
Tempest domain cleric
um to to start with
Tempest domain Clark stuff
lightning Shadow wizard
game
so we're going tap this domain and then
we're going to swap into storm sorcer I
planned it out I have a plan trust the
trust the process okay just trust the
process
which means adorable I'm getting to eat
it I can talk to animals you're just
jealous okay
she's adorable
um and then and then we're getting we
got Tempest domain clear comes with
Thunder Wave and fog cloud and then
um
my deity is all is is obviously
Gerald glitter gold
uh the king of gnomes
yeah king of gnomes obviously
um and then
or otherwise known as I don't know how
to say his name so whatever I think
that's that's his name
um and then background I'm a guild
artisan yeah
I sell stuff I guess I make money I make
money and
um here are my stats trust the process
you might be thinking your wisdom's a
little low no it's not I need Charisma
trust the process
trust the process this is my stats Trust
I'm not very smart and I'm not very
strong but that's okay because I have
risk
that's okay because I have a raise so
it's fine all we need is rizz that's all
we need yeah
yeah and then we're gonna take we're
gonna take we'll create water and bless
and healing word and it'll be great so
that's my character
this is people
this is Bieber
this is Bieber The Gnome I see should I
should I be be boo or Be Goo be should I
it should it be good for the memes or
should it bee boo what do you think
ah
beagle
bagel oh so I just named myself Bagel
that'd be funny
I kind of want to name myself Bagel I'm
naming it I'm giving myself Bagel now
okay yeah okay
[Music]
oh oh they're unmuted they're unmuted
help
yeah
I have to ask you things Yes actually
this is good maybe you know because when
we were creating characters yesterday
people said it might be good you know to
like balance out everything so that we
are have ever like you know uh recover
everything yeah you know what I mean
yeah and then they told me people they
told me uh just now that I shouldn't go
with magebreaker because true strike
sucks oh well they kept saying that's to
me too but then other people said that
true strike is fixed now and then they
fixed it so fixed it
yeah what was wrong about true strike uh
I don't know I don't know too much about
I think you know I think it's hard too
because it's just like everyone always
has their own play style and things that
they like and dislike
um
okay then let me just ask you people one
thing did we say somebody is gonna have
investigation as their thing or
um let's see if you guys look at your
abilities and look at your proficiencies
what do you have because we should cover
our bases okay yes
let's do that all right uh I'll go first
okay go first so I'm playing a barbarian
um as like my class I'm a huge huge half
orc
um Outlander and my abilities I have
really high strength 17 strengths uh
dexterity is pretty good 13.
Constitution is 14. uh stem and physical
endurance of course because I'm big and
girthy uh intelligence nine because I'm
just not very smart uh wisdom wisdom is
pretty good
it wouldn't let me put it into other
things so this is how it has to be uh
Charisma is uh is 10
um like it's it's how is [\h__\h] Shrek
smarter than my house
don't call her that her name is not true
it's Murray okay get it straight first
of all
um but yeah I guess I can kind of tank
because I have high Constitution as well
um and then I have plus two bonus to
strength one plus one bonus to
Constitution uh my skills in particular
I've got plus five to Athletics which is
really good
um you know most oh that's good I have a
negative one on Athletics Good Luck
running away
um and then animal handling three oh
plus three
um and then Insight plus one medicine
plus one perception plus with survival
plus three good Survivor I'm pretty
intimidating so I've got plus two there
um yeah that's what I'm good at where do
you have all these weird stats if you go
to abilities and skill proficiencies and
you can hit change and you can see what
you have I'm saving oh yeah okay
okay you can handle a lot of weapons too
so Cali what's your strongest points
then in ability in skills skills uh
let's see so the highest my highest role
is Athletics
um uh well I don't know my Athletics is
plus five
um okay let's see and then survival plus
three animal handling plus three
okay I'm strong
okay excuse you
what was that I got plus four in those
but
all righty what's your strength uh
uh 12
okay well you can't beat me in strength
so in an arm wrestling match you're
gonna suffer anyway continue onward your
turn your turn
well I don't really know if I should
change any of this um you you don't have
to so just read it off okay well right
now
[Music]
um
uh stealth is plus five
oh that's good yeah or another strong
one is animal handling inside both a
plus four perceptionist plus four
survival is plus four
um I don't know what do you want to know
people should I tell you my weak points
too then we can cover those or so
um
yeah sure
I'm weak in history
and religion oh yeah we wanted someone
to cover religion and history huh oh I
have plus one in history I have negative
one oh no I have negative one in history
I have plus one in religion
okay okay okay well we don't have to
cover everything I guess but
um okay and then yeah basically my
question was if it's if it makes sense
to go in uh you know bounty hunter that
gains me Proficiency in investigation do
we have anybody else who has Proficiency
in the investigation because if yes then
I won't do it I have a negative one in
Rusty okay
so go ahead go for it go for it okay it
will only bring me to plus one but okay
then then I'll just say with what I have
now uh yeah
I think um we'll be fine what does
narista focus on uh well I'll read my
downsides first with all the other
skills I don't have so my Athletics is
minus one aerobatics plus two sleight of
hand plus four stealth plus two Arcana
plus one history plus one investigation
plus one nature and religion plus one
animal handling zero inside zero
medicine zero perception survival zero
deception plus five and then invitation
and performance and persuasion all plus
five but then strength is eight wow
dexterity is plus 15. Constitution is
plus 13. intelligence is plus 12 so I'm
smarter than all of you wow
I can take that wait does does anybody
have deception on a decent amount
because me and the wrists are on zero
um I have plus three I feel like maybe
well maybe you could instead choose to
roll persuasion or intimidation instead
of a certain I don't know can we choose
that zero
multiple it'll give you multiple like
dialogue choices and you can choose what
you want to roll on yeah yeah okay I
have plus five in my deception too oh oh
you're the charismatic one oh wait you
have plus five interception well then
there was something else that I heard
was Zero yeah okay okay cool oh
do we have persuade persuasion covered
yes I have plus five persuasion okay
good good
me and people will do the perspective
yeah we'll do the talking I think both
of us uh scale on Charisma so we will be
the razors hi you guys do the talking we
do the killing yeah am I the only selfie
one well I'll kill two but yeah it might
be yeah it's good to do both oh yeah
you're also healer right Bijou no cleric
oh you're not clerical I am swapping to
sorcerer I'm only going to be clearing
for about two levels and then I'm
swapping to Source where uh for extreme
magical violence
um I didn't have heels and Marissa
should have heels as well yeah as Bard
so we should be okay I just need to have
some potions with you well then I really
didn't need to be a Healer okay good
good
um yeah uh did everybody show everything
off on stream then yeah
the what my my thing right
yeah you haven't introduced your
character yet oh yeah yeah Google yeah
okay hi
they forgot about me it's okay
I need you you're important not cleric
yeah I'm
not cleric
um strength is nine bad strength our
next is 13 Constitution 13 intelligence
eight I'm not very smart or strong but I
have Charisma and that's all that
matters
um and also wisdom is 15. here's my 17
and then my proficiency
I got persuasion plus five performance
plus three intimidation I'm very
intimidating plus three deception plus
three survival plus two perception plus
two minus and plus four inside plus four
and we're handling plus two religion
plus one and then nature investigation
history Arcana all negative one but I
got still flight of hand acrobatics and
yeah
there you go
I can't
oh
oh they're telling me to add one
Constitution but I can't
yeah
I did but the plus is grayed out even
when I have one ability Point extra I do
I wait like this okay
wait what but it still has no no where
was that where did uh where did I go
[Music]
okay it'll be
fine we're gonna take a picture and put
it in the group chat yeah
go check real quick it's okay thank you
for the reminder it's okay no need to
panic we have no worries we got your
back
well I'm good but they really want me to
have more Constitution
and I can't I've got the constitution
for the group
um
oh wait no the picture I think was of
something else
[Music]
now I don't know what to do okay
well I think we just have the
recommended because we didn't really set
them right
hmm
okay so you could probably it was okay
okay okay I wouldn't sweat it YouTube
recommended yeah
okay okay we can start then maybe cool
awesome right so we're all gonna eat as
our as our characters
but yeah I think we're all just us
except for you oh yeah
easier
how is everyone's Guardian oh yeah did
we make a sexy a sexy love interest or I
already showed it off but mine is my mom
mine is just so grown up
[Music]
come on it's just a random a random that
I could have made yeah mine is literally
just the older version of hello bearded
lady
hello bearded lady let's go all right
are we ready to get started yes let's
Venture for
fourth
okay here we go
it's gonna happen look oh
oh
yeah
like Caribbean yeah the Kraken oh uh
David Jones
[Music]
wow he's got alien feet
Paco is Taco Time
stay single ask later in the game
on a big ship yeah
that's so cool yes I thought you may
have missed the first cut scene yeah we
are on that ship watch it later
we don't like it there though we were
there against our will okay you look
very evil that doesn't seem right
I did not choose this life
that rendering is great on that that man
no right really high quality graphics
man
um
they're getting captured I thought they
were getting disintegrated
suffering let's go
technically they're not dying they're
getting teleported
the goal the calvary is here I'm gonna
ride a dragon like that in this game
what the [\h__\h]
yeah
did you hear did you did you hit generic
the real home scream
they're the targaryens obviously oh my
God they're not blonde though it's fine
let's go I guess oh the other the other
ones weren't blonde right
yeah yeah
[Music]
all right well cable management
let's blow this Popsicle stand boys
yeah and the Frosty chat is the audio
and the visual is fine is it lagging or
anything
specifically or to save all everybody
is that Kelly who wants that board no
that's not my character okay
she's a character she's always angry all
the time
yeah she's kind of cool though kind of
Base your character still seems much
more stand out here than that one even
Italian oh yeah when I check yeah she's
a star moriope is a star
[Music]
I am
your husband don't save people Dragon
people hate tentacle people oh I'm
waking up yeah
it was slimy
we will not be joining forces I'm sorry
you're going straight to the camp but it
was nice to see you anyway beautiful
rendered and also whoa excuse me
I like that you like what no it's not
enough but it's a snail
boulders
immediately
wow she looks so good in this cutscene
so did everybody miss the part where
they put a worm yes yes when did that
happen just just know there's a worm in
your head because that's very important
okay we got worms yeah you got worms
yeah
private dialogue off
pretty
I have the ugly
yeah I look great
I look awesome
looking real good here let me oh we're
all together all right let's freaking go
um
playing with like a much like not a
wider screen hello if you guys don't
mind I'm very going I'm going to very
quickly turn my settings to best or
extremely good instead of ultra just a
moment please yeah see Cali face
let me really quickly change the video
to not be ultra how how do we do that
Could you um if you go to settings you
gotta press the start button
for me
okay wow well we have the same chair
cool
nice sisters yeah it'll work again later
or the genitals what no none of them
yeah I get to throw you later on why
aren't the genitals the genitals what do
you mean the genitals because I
thought from the beginning of the game
but apparently it's not really turned
off so I need to turn them off go to
settings it's probably in settings be
careful okay okay okay uh maybe instead
of unchecking it yeah we're all scared
what about cinematic genitals
[Music]
is it an accessibility
yeah in game play and then scroll down a
little bit actually you should even see
it
cinematic nudity off share private
moments off yeah none of you guys are
getting my private moments yeah
none of mine are checked so I think
we're good you're going for the demon
lady I wanted to go for the demon blade
too bad she's so cool
we can fight for her you can have the
bear the bear I don't
you were so excited about the bear what
are you talking about okay look the
Bear's cool all right don't get me wrong
look
should we turn off karmic dice oh my God
what's happening
karmic dice avoids failure streaks while
keeping the results mostly random no
that feels like a good thing to have on
right
say it again
[Music]
off off
okay
wow are we ready wait wait star's trying
to turn down some things no problem I'm
turning everything down to like medium
and low I mean or medium medium
you know what medium is good
medium's good actually
it's better than whatever I was playing
on the other computer I don't know how
to do anything by the way well but never
saw
oh same I don't know what the hell is
going on okay bee boo and Cali you will
have to like uh tell us everything sorry
I know a little bit that's about it I
know a little bit too
just a little
um
okay wow it's so pretty though the game
is pretty yeah yeah it's very very
detailed
oh we're moving I love how you move like
you do in League of Legends I thought
that it was gonna be like I gave myself
a controller oh yes you're the league
player
where's the karmic dice by the way
uh
I don't know hey Chad where's karmic
dice
I'm here also on the first one gameplay
so we're turning it off right yeah they
say turn it off okay
is a league player yeah I like League
are you ever gonna play those kind of
games on stream uh it's kind of hard
because they're more fun I want to get
more people to play with but some people
just don't like want to try it at all I
feel like you would be filling a niche
because no other Ian I think is playing
those that genre on stream I'm not good
though make it bigger
I might try it I want to do Dota 2 too
because I haven't but I I'm more
familiar with League than I am DOTA
because it's been a really long time
look at uh whoa It's shaking why is it
so wide
why whoa whoa whoa I think I need to
change the solution to not be white and
then we can start and we can start
aspect ratio gotta change the aspect
ratio
this is called sphincter I don't like
that
why not well we're in a thing
you heard me you can heal you can heal
there's a healing right here
why are you flexing in our faces people
all right
perfect guys off
okay anyways
[Music]
I don't want to
I know it's gross but you have to oh
okay come up here come up here
well I need to get used to those
controls okay get on the platform yeah
that's kind of weird oh yeah you got it
okay so let me try and throw you uh
Bagel
okay somewhere is that you someone go
talk to that person right now
we'll drop Charisma people oh okay hey
get it done and then I'll loot them
afterwards who is he
oh no he looks dead no he's still alive
barely
find out
yum yums
you've come to save us from this place
Quivers and expectations
before they return those are the yummies
turn the music up uh
this is important what I say say
whatever you know what would what would
your character say
um
uh yeah hmm maybe the first so high-res
it's a high-res brain
is your Talking Tom I like your face you
look so you look so like disgusted oh
yeah oh you're all looking good yeah but
you see the same cutscene with yourself
oh okay we can we can also give you
suggestions yeah we can suggest things
as well
let's ask more
[Music]
news
okay
oh okay I see guys I'll fix it in a
moment
s let's
Rock them soccer no before we destroy it
we have to you know cover all options
what's the plan yeah
free free to break it sounds pretty nice
it sounds it sounds pretty nice
it does sound very nice it's nice to us
it's a nice little brain
well my strongest one would be the
dexterity one I see I say go for
investigation
definitely prized the brain from the
skull bro
I will I will do that let's just take my
look good
skill checks some dialogue options
require skill check a dice roll that
must meet or exceed a target number your
character skills add a bonus as well
okay okay
your first rule good luck
oh it has to be minimum 10 right
yep then we grab it if it matches it
it's fine too
crippled the strange creature keyboard
subservient should prove the threat
looking at
uh yeah
the brain yeah
something bad uh-oh oh no do I does the
brain take over me oh you just wow you
just stuck your thumb in I think you
just killed him dude
I'll see I think you just killed him
sorry it was so wobbly legs
it ran away oh it's running away oh
destroyed I destroyed
well I don't destroy today hey we lose I
I knew we should have killed that thing
yeah
I'm sorry no it will follow and haunt us
forever
we'll be back oh we left we left
tomorrow
okay I'm here wait um do you have
do you have it do you have improvised
melee weapon use it
on you improvise yeah
improvised melee weapon yeah
and then click I have that you don't
even know how to use it
improvised melee weapons too heavy to
pick up
okay handle it yes I can't hold on a sec
[Music]
it provides melee weapon yeah
[Laughter]
Target is blocked get over oh oh
[Music]
yeah it sucks well anyway you'll get
enraged thrill later and that's the big
eat
I'm hyped for that that's the one yeah
we're gonna oh we're gonna use that
okay
yeah you're sick
they provide some so the second Ambiance
for you guys it's fine why thank you I
like your playing tiny horned winged one
wait you don't know the best tiny horns
hey guys
okay I changed my whole uh layout in OBS
I'm ready now okay
oh
sorry bye thank you
good luck fighting whatever's over there
ah just kidding
oh man it's gonna be a long journey
let's go okay let's go time battles
forward
ready to Bonk them in the head with my
the hammer oh
oh my gosh
beautiful orange I like it oh no oh no
no you cannot join our party
excuse me I am much more beautiful oh
she's so insulting
yeah
Abomination doesn't sound too wrong
uh we share a brain we share a brain
cell
s
cannot join my party
sorry what is this they all want to join
us yeah okay so we're just that cool
they want to join the squad party's full
yeah squad's full sorry
together real sorry guys
she know well you gotta go to the camp
um are you making these decisions now
who are you what do you suggest who are
you your only chance of surviving are
you who is you uh
what made you think I was a fraud
Paris
unless we are cleansed
bodies basically if we let the things
stay in our head we turn into one of
those tentacles
oh yeah
so we don't want to do that I mean that
could have its up science too yeah yeah
wow can we escape sure God this must be
our priority together
okay
the snatch the munchies
we will address the matter of a cure for
this Perfection once we reach the
material plane okay okay bye
um go to the camp and wait
teach us combat
oh so angry
oh look at that Bloody smile exactly I
kind of get it all right guys we're
starting to fight let's go
around you during combat so you have
time for them
is there a [\h__\h]
uh wait there's water
yes
all right well anyway you're never a
dull moment candle okay they were pretty
strong right off the bat
I can't move he's the dirt
nice yeah yummy
and ax I don't need that I could sell it
though collect everything sell for big
money
okay
I took it all right we attacked okay we
have to wait for
does everyone have to end their
individuals yeah you have to end your
time I think so yeah ah okay
Goblin engage
okay our tank should shall be in front
of us
I guess I'm also playing wow
why would they do that to you
but they're leaving all this nice loot
around here what is she left it for you
because we know
my head so I can get all the loot first
it's got so much good stuff hey hey
no no restoration
dude I want to go up there we go let's
climb up
I did
that'd be faster than that but you'd
better share the money from it the
revenue yeah
put the profit no why
oh there's a girl in here
oh yeah they do not react okay
what about this one
I pushed the buttons
I'm sorry I probably it's okay what am I
doing oh what happened what happened why
are we all missing we're killing a guy
I guess
it'll take us some getting used to team
but that's okay
um I have to end my turn uh nice hits it
was still alive here oh you okay not
enough movement I guess I'll just move
forward I might have any range ranged
attacks all right
it looks like a pro
do something to me nice nice Miss idiot
here we go no I want to do something oh
oh
[Music]
I'm Barbarian oh hell
yes no I will not help help no she needs
no she needs us there's no brain the
brain you told us not to kill let's get
him die
okay all right cool I mean that works
wow wow I'm so powerful
you're pretty strong
already
is there any lube left
I can't see what's over here how about
you what are you holding why do you guys
not want to see this oh
thank you
I saw you snatched that before my eyes
open piece of dirt what's this too
can I push this I'm gonna go free Shadow
I'm gonna push this button
what
oh
all right I'm gonna free what what's
happening
everybody needs a ranged weapons
[Music]
did you get her out we were free here
I'm freeing her now free the captive
place your hand on the console just let
her out let her freeze you feel a
shittiest squirming in your head
you took my keys
mine was was this dark mine excited what
are we doing
oh
wow
he's rejected me
no it's over did he die
yeah no she's super dead console hum
steadily tear it opens I'm not giving up
this is all my fault
what are these ass rolls
oh what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] are you kidding me I'll throw you a
shadow heart I'll free you hey no I want
a free Shadow heart I won the
Panic Alliance of the device making
some like a
big reaction shocked this device is
different from them already limited
helicopter already in use
uh can I do it critical failure I
haven't even had a critical failure in
my game that I'm playing right now
okay so I need to if it fades I can't
for you the sensation washes I'm still
trying to open her thing connection
it won't work
only one open uh-huh yeah only only one
at a time
do you need the key
how did I get glasses
[Music]
with Shadow heart it was nice while it
lasted okay
[Music]
oh poor oh what's happening to her oh
it's just
so dead
I mean she's still alive you can use
that key that you got to oh you already
emptied it you know how to play this
game I guess we should just move along
ladies no I don't know what
is the romance option well it's not like
we'll never see her again if we don't
frame her okay you got this you got this
you got it
[Music]
[Laughter]
there's four of us am I right ladies
critical success
across your mind we look so good
together
iconic Duo
it looks pretty good looking I'm so glad
I could free you wow thank goodness I
freed you from wow wow I think I freed
you myself
all by myself
you feel that just now dangerous
companies what you need in a fight looks
like there's plenty of fighting there's
more let me come with you she is very
pretty
good yeah
no heart beautiful no you're on your own
if you're if you're one thing if you're
wiping full complimental
lady I want I want a shadow heart I
think okay you can have shadows okay I'm
taking Shadow heart yeah yeah
you look good yeah well
thank you don't want to call dibs don't
worry so there's a very nice vampire
dude no no we will not allow him on the
team he will never be anywhere
I know why not he's so funny you can't
tell me what to do something
all right you know what Marissa live
your dreams too
oh leave your dreams wait isn't this the
way back it's gonna have the Bears yeah
yeah we came that way let's go to the
right
so we have a big party now yes you
vampire out of our camp but he's yucky
nearing the hell once inside do as I say
okay oh yeah
you got it now we step on the fire get
in the butthole
time I don't want to I'm ready
we're ready oh yeah yeah we're ready oh
you know it the school squad's here
whoa the whole Squad oh
no
I mean yes wait
[Music]
get in here get in here Wawa
Jay Must Escape after we escape uh we
got it we're on the tentacle dude's side
for now yeah
that's my brother no no who am I right
now on Lily kill everything that we see
yeah
probably do some other stuff oh yeah I
forgot to rage
dad
so angry
oh that was moving okay
who's alive here
I mean okay we're pretty strong Jesus
yeah we're strong we can try and shoot
let's go
good luck with that
so dumb I mean it hit
it oh
foreign
[Music]
what if I want to fight the devil
okay never mind all right never mind
maybe you mean the commander yeah the
commander person sounds like quitter
speak actually oh Mori open kill
everything
[Music]
by the way we were on a time oh I see so
that's how everything works I should
probably use it
that's what I'm about to hit I'm about
to strike my rage ended
flute
now okay
is that correct
still shooting at him
yeah
you're going for the transponder bro
there's three enemies right here I know
I'm I'm trying to get up there
dude
yeah okay
yeah let the tentacle monster men fight
we gotta get those guys but I'm just
very slow I need some assistance I'm
trying
okay
no I'm just very slow
I didn't need your help I can't reach
everyone's dead now
everyone's dead
who's Dash do I have Dash yeah you do
have Dash It's on your it's on your
other side how did I miss it okay
people you're too strong well no one was
helping me so I was like fine I'll do it
myself
yeah I just killed everyone here it was
all me oh he's dead
okay I can take it I can take it oh I'm
gonna go for the thing I'm going for the
thing
oh go for the thing the hell is alien
transponder
made it in time
[Music]
you're single players in fact I'm
playing on normal mode
however I have not really played much of
the strawberries
good at Magic but I'm not playing Magic
this time can you guys see the cutscene
yeah okay good
yeah big old dragon
I look painful
wow
people be careful
[Music]
sounds about right
get ready this is the rest of the
campaign
it's okay I know how to dash now
good I I don't know how to do anything I
wish I had a con say I wish my
controller worked because this is so
confusing that like I have to use my
mouse to move and then to turn the
screen stuff I have or Like to Move It I
have to use the things
to wrote I'm like what
let's click it I'll try it
I mean I prefer controller personally oh
the Goblins I know those guys
are they your friends
no no they're not okay definitely not
foreign
goblins are never good guys in any
medium
can I say the things
I saw it in chat before you even said it
Darkness will fade oh
like oh God your way
oh
okay
who's safe hey big up
who did say it was I don't know
oh Magic that was clutch then you are so
beautiful
thanks I know
real gorgeous Bella the ball
oh what's up sis
we look good what what me
[Music]
check for injuries am I okay other than
the infection you're more or less intact
yeah Miracle given everything you've
been through but it'll all be for
nothing if you don't find help soon
the death sentence and the clock is too
I love the narrator's voice yeah it's
very soothing very ASMR
what to do bagel
okay okay I know
I know please teach me where the dash is
um it's on the left side of your bar
it's like a foot with wings
such a dummy
I just don't think I have eyeballs all
right
uh is very important and jump is also
very important you will need to jump
right so oh yeah definitely nowhere to
jump on all right leave it to me
hey
oh my God hey
oh what's that
it's the it's the cube from that one can
I link it that one's scary franchise
can I take this take a ticket
Hellraiser tesseract
give me some and Pinhead
oh [\h__\h] dang it I think she woke up that
one's very friendship good morning I
don't know the name of it oh people what
were you doing
oh uh checking to see if you're okay of
course yes she's in love right away
and speaking of
how are we alive I saved you obviously
uh
we made it doesn't matter seems like
we're the lucky ones judging by all the
corpses strain about
I remember the ship
I remember falling
than nothing
damn
I love the deadbeat inside jokes
where where are we
I don't recognize this place
but anything's an improvement on women
she look good first things first I'm a
steal her clothes shelter no I want to
see we must have escaped
no bad oh no stealing clothes let's go
together we need each other
no it's like you can steal their clothes
as long as you don't steal their
underwear it's a company
yeah
I've seen overburdened with Hangers On
already oh
excuse you still at the camp that's all
you're good for is you stay at the camp
there you go bye
yes
all right ladies let's let's Bust A Move
yeah all right let's go girls
oh I'll click on your character portrait
level take a second to level up still
breathing I spite everything level up
a lot
unlock them what a danger sense nice and
I'm getting tankier
oh I have to choose the Spells now okay
and we're gonna have to read these to
give me a moment I got destructive wrath
okay I'm good
I'm choosing spells man takes a lot of
reading oh look at these bodies while
they're busy leveling up um
[Music]
is good
oh yeah you're a barbarian you just hit
level up and you're good yeah and then
I'm good to go
you guys have to tell me
are you a man do you have a man voice
I do but I'm a lady use you sorry
it was you sister
oh you're so cute and small yeah I'm
perfectly eatable yeah oh we'll be doing
lots of Thrones
then he throws away us both
Waypoint discovered let's go uh
what did you just find oh this is a four
point you can this point on the map yeah
I think this is our first one though so
we can't go anywhere
where's everybody uh where the [\h__\h]
we're over here where'd you go
seeing you no you never split the party
there you go that doesn't seem like we
know oh I I'm exploring so oh yeah
I found some little brain guys did you
guys take all the fish too are you okay
just insult them insult them okay please
they're so close to me it's not worth
checking anything oh
[Music]
that's fine
oh okay help me
there's nothing I can do whoa whoa nice
nice
oh that was good
are you okay turn I guess yeah yeah I'm
good
she's fine she's okay
mockery
yeah we just kind of we just gotta kill
this guy though
uh they said biboo apparently you hit me
yeah you you hit me
so there is uh friendly a fire yes it is
correct correct
[Music]
I got you I know
you can run so quick why all right I got
you I'm gonna throw you a potion here
I'll heal you yeah here yeah you're the
clearest you have so many attacks
um
I hope that helps to equip a bow
do not throw uh we're fine we're fine
someone smacked this thing right in
front of me
excuse me did you miss oh no you didn't
okay good
okay yeah I didn't hear a smack or
anything oh it was weird
oh god oh
no I don't know what's going on too late
I want to go up here
a nice elf man I do I do I do want to
meet a nice I'm over here will he join
my team and help me yeah he'll do a lot
of things if you want him to
that sounds more than one thing okay you
really want him too
okay walk up the hill
go talk to him
I don't see anyone just keep walking
yeah keep going
how big will this be oh I see a man yeah
I gotta kill bro s
you girls are so fast
I'm sleeping for a kind soul what are we
doing right now
oh you're listening okay that was so
based of Marissa right there
he does that uh
good luck
hahaha Nebraska
[Music]
he's playing hard to get nerissa he's
playing hard to get
bounds whilst I was trapped in that pot
oh [\h__\h] off man and those tentacles tell
them how it is
chaotic I like it though why does he
think we belong to them
we're obviously good people
you're mine to share a brain cell you're
looking out of unfamiliar eyes
that's how he shows affection
the Mind flayers weren't we connected at
that sounds
it's those tentacled monsters whatever
they did whatever they put in us no he's
annoying created a connection
let's go
whatever just happened the typical DND
slash world of Darkness vampire is
he even a vampire yeah
yeah but a little bit less obnoxious
still yeah true
um
oh well Dorian option
[Music]
are we all are we all Builders I think
it's better assistant
what various ways are we yeah I think we
are all of us yeah I think we we all got
we all got like yoinked from from the
city I think okay is that so
we clearly move in different circles wow
this guy in the face yeah beat him up
ladies
he's like Bernie
in 1985
can I kick him out I don't want to talk
to him anymore why did you guys make me
do this
no I don't like [\h__\h] men I like evil
men not [\h__\h] men ah what's the
difference
the big difference big difference
yeah kick them out
no thanks uh
it won't let me think do what you want
I'm leaving I'm a dog
that's [\h__\h] hilarious is it gonna
make you send them to the camp
I don't know I don't want a base for
trying
it won't let me pick any of them
no it makes a sound but nothing is
happening
it's like a double
like a triple he's never gonna leave you
alone I'm clicking so much guys help
maybe
vote time
what if we stop listening yeah guys get
me out of here
stop listening
it's on the top right
excellent oh
all right bye Marissa oh my cute friend
oh did you find this Kiara oh I I
summoned it I have I can summon like
five six different animals I just
realized then oh this is sick this is
from numbers don't work numbers aren't
working you guys can we can we knock her
out of combat yeah can you like kill me
I got you
I'm sorry guys
[Laughter]
is that even possible
I got a different option I got different
options oh
okay
uh wait no no I'm stuck again kill me oh
oh back put it back down put it back
down so we want her to survive no kill
me
I don't wanna
all right sorry I didn't mean to okay
help you okay did you get it did you get
an option now
no
I'm staying in safe distance
oh my God she's already down
at this point I'm just having a good
time I'm having a good time okay Kelly
you need to save and reload apparently
can you read your mind let me see I
don't know what data it's gonna show
hang on let me you got it yeah yeah I
got your back let me save the game
really quick
can I help you
okay
third game
save successful
[Music]
did you get into a loading stream or
screen yes okay why is my game not done
a bit late to save
now I'm safe after everyone
sure it'll be fine we're new at this
okay
we still have a game I'm dead because
you killed me
you'll be fine sorry we can
we can save you oh you're back down okay
let me help you up
okay yeah
talking to this freaking guy yeah yeah
well someone else talked to him yeah I
don't want to hello
oh my God
oh okay well I can't
I can't move can I kill him
I I can move my screen but I can't I
can't move
oh uh oh oh God they're broken
The Matrix oh do you have an earlier
save do you have I have a quick save I
think yeah here let me maybe go back to
that earlier scene before we met this
freaking guy yeah and it all fell apart
and everything all right let me see auto
save all right um there's us on the
beach okay we probably lost some loot
but that's okay again better than better
than whatever's going on right now yeah
whatever whatever this is thank goodness
for autosave it's like pasta
oh yeah save save Lots because you know
something like this might happen
we encountered it early now that we're
cautious yeah okay thanks before
conversation back here oh I think we
have to level again too yeah that's yeah
oh no I'm good I don't need to
I can't level oh oh Shadow heart hi
oh we talked to her again
what are you doing you do your thing
uh true okay
remember the ship going to the camp
we might have escaped but we still have
yeah I don't have the leveling thing
guys
neither do I I think I already love it's
already after we leveled it yeah I'm not
sure because mine's only at 13 and I
thought I was at like 20 something
just popped
okay get those levels
[Music]
yeah let's save if we decide to talk to
that guy again beforehand uh since he
broke the game
yeah oh yeah oh you know there are
always other greener pastures like uh
baby houses you know I bet you'd like
houses next time who
house and is a great Pine soul I think
you'll really like that character
um
no why wouldn't you trust me I mean I
feel like he's just a very Charming
character that you'd like that's all
that there is to it it's really surely
no tricks no trickery no anything just
give me different clothes
Syrian because the stereo has nice
clothes too it does have nice clothes
but I don't I don't want it I want to
steal them
okay now we're all here
can I walk around this
I'm probably gonna have to move around
it
okay how do I need to equip something
long range pretty sure I have a short
your frog you're so cute
can I
Yoshi
why does it hurt me still
you stepped in like the little corner of
it Ash
is an action
hey can I not how do I can I not attack
when I dashed oh no because you can't
yeah you use natural right now I can do
this
I can at least leave a Hunter's Mark
nice good it'll do more damage if you if
you shoot him just throw axes oh I can
throw axes oh you're so right Chad I
didn't know that because I don't play oh
boy
you're good you're good on the way can I
control the Frog
you should be able to yeah if not the
Frog's turn yet
oh okay you wanna realize it was
starting baseball
oh yeah
oh you're boned
Froggy's friends
wow loot
yummy brain frog only one HP
oh there's another one up there
Maury smash
angle
my turn I love the Frog's portrait ah
okay wait now it's frog okay now it's
froggy time
some things can frogging attack no not
enough movement okay froggy just follow
oh cute he can be butter you know Cannon
Potter or bait
oh yeah I guess so I can't do anything
special ah wait wait A Touch of creature
but it's okay
after good oh
you need help okay
am I gonna be okay
he's not bad yeah that's fine eat the
Frog good
shoot the other one girls he has a
hunter's Hunter's Mark on the Hunter's
Mark nice yeah
oh oh how what oh concentration broken
uh sucks what does that
what is that I had to concentrate to
keep the Hunter's Mark active
he's good you're good good luck that's
only for me
nice yay can I do anything else and rage
nah there's no reason to end my rage
yeah keep raging keep raging I think
it's over though after this turn
oh yeah
yeah nice one I need healing
um do you have some uh oh there we go do
you have a potion maybe oh that was on
that was on the wrong person it's fine
[Music]
thank you
thanks
[Laughter]
smash
and only smash
all right time for you to go kill that
guy we can also apparently
we want to steal his clothes we want we
need to save right before we talk to him
then
I'm not talking to him again this is up
to someone else I don't want to deal
with that
you were so cool when you like when you
like got him to the ground and like beat
him up that was safe
okay
make sure you say it's my worst
nightmare okay
[Music]
oh yucky ooh yucky
so you got it this is useless
[Laughter]
yeah good luck
push yourself to yourself can I have
Adam both at the same time Arctic
inspiration
is that okay
I want to be cool
wow yeah success huh apparently yeah I
would have picking locks yeah he's a
stealthy one yeah
all right I haven't done anything to you
yet he's kind of a jerk you know
yeah you're looking at unfamiliar eyes
prowling dark busy streets no ribs but
it fades British
get out of here Dollar Store
that
the knife away and I'll tell you any
everything yes I'm not an idiot
something they did
they took you to
cute eyesore during
it just happened everybody tons of
things I was ready to decorate the
ground I would like to after this
cutscene rest for a moment you bet but I
can heal my HP apology oh yeah um how
you can press short rest I was the
strongest
apparently everybody too
[Music]
go to the camp dummy all right we can
rest we can do a short rest we don't
need to do a lot yeah there you go
oh much better yeah I feel rested let's
go ahead and do a save here
oh yeah good let's go
good call yeah
off and off and heat hello
oh let's kill it yeah kill it
beat him up you guys talk to him yo
little [\h__\h] it's you Jesus
the base I don't know what
what it's good you're right for that
yeah that was kind of Awesome
all right I think we need to go this way
oh it's like it's just suddenly die
oh Goblin scimitar
Ian
oh The Bijou Kayla during the cutscene
yeah I found him right in the head that
seems too good for it
what is that
that looks uh crazy Marissa do you
really want to stand so close to it
yeah particularly yeah
malfunctioning
Arissa was stuck because of a party boat
I don't know what that means though
oh uh I don't know because every other
time when people were voting it didn't
get stuck like that if people didn't
vote so I think I think the Voting is
just like a suggestion isn't it yeah
yeah exactly I don't think it was the
party though and give it my hand there
was uh man
Prisma
look let's go
wow
twenties already I'm just too good well
critical fail hairs on this whatever
you're doing is
a quick little pull should do the trick
I don't have any I don't have any
strength so
my weak little Bard arms
it doesn't really look like you're
pulling that hard there is some oh wait
who's he oh oh this is what you like
it's a wizard I don't know I want to
know who he is though
hello hello
apologies
he's Mr Magic Man yeah
a bit shocked I'll be nice to him he
doesn't seem like a mean guy you've had
a pleasure to make your acquaintance
I like his fluffy hair in a manner of
speech
you were on the noise load as well
the wizard of water d
ude I assume you two were on the
receiving end of a rather unwelcome
assertion in the Oculus
worms in our brains
no sugar coating it is
a wizard apparently
excruciating
gestation's really it's really cool
cleric by any chance do you a doctor
soon to be something else
hmm we do have one I suppose few enough
can
not exactly a common Affliction we're
most certainly going to need it I'm a
really dumb cleric though I don't think
you would trust me to like get each
other worms out of your head
I trust you oh
okay oh
so you're traveling with plenty of
company already
perhaps I can join you later instead
you will never leave yes go to my Camp
stay there forever forever if you play
solo are all these dudes like joining
you yeah yeah if you play solo they they
join up and then you can like hang out
with them and do their like story class
but we have our own we have our own
Squad we have our own which is so much
better
I wonder how we get their approval
though if they're never on our team like
out in the field with us oh this way
you got to get their approval if you
want to raise them up but if they're
always in the camp you can't get their
approval why are you walking like that I
don't know I don't know what are you
doing
she's like I think it's normal yeah
that's back to normal okay
hello
there's so much to look at
oh there's people here hello
yeah it sounds fun I just saved the game
I don't know what that thing is uh I
wouldn't uh
hey what's up it looks like one of my
old cats I am not impressed like a
raccoon I summoned a raccoon ship oh
really it looks like a raccoon but it's
supposedly a cat
okay attack
[Music]
oh I love I have a meow action and what
else just meowing attract the attention
of nearby creatures to draw them closer
to you don't knockers
oh
cat cannot move too much
distraction no one will hurt this cat
I heard the cat
wow
well it did attract attention so um
no
hi are you kidding me
bye
hello
all right hold on I got you
yeah
wow
your nostrils
what's with your nostrils
oh she did
yeah I killed two people though I killed
two people so it was worth it I'm in
danger too never says in danger too we
only have Cali at full HP
what's happening right now
um uh someone stirred up oh
oh what's wrong with that person
oh nice nice all right let me hold on a
sec
thank you you're welcome now let me see
if I can anything else I can do I'm like
asleep
[\h__\h] how dare you do that tonight
so rude I use a potion
no I mean at least if I'm knocked out I
heal right if they make me sleep that's
how it works in Games
bad news
I'm gonna try to wake you up okay
next time I kill him
I'm not the team baggage am I doing this
right to chat
oh I threw a potion at her dang it um
can I help you wake up
oh wait um
how much 80 I'm dying still
don't range yeah not what I wanted to do
yay oh you guys yeah
even though it would make me auto do
that
nice damage something
I am holding a ranged weapon now
uh oh wait the movies are still alive
okay okay
go down beat her up oh wow
why did you do that when we're like
right in front of her I'm literally
right here well he's arranged we don't
change
it doesn't matter if it doesn't matter
wow
thank you
[Music]
stop taking the gold right before my
eyes hey
what's happening
[Music]
Point Blank oh oh are you okay you want
to ground
oh what oh hello
guys
oh dear okay hello oh this is like a
dungeon oh Jesus okay
um oh that is a lot of people okay
that's a lot of dudes yeah that's more
than one okay we got this who are they
do listening oh my god oh good yeah
oh oh
it's fine Raiders okay I'm gonna try to
blast all of them here we go a blaster
okay anyway I start blasting how many
can I get oh okay
Yates look at this
I blew up the cookies I got I got nobody
was that even you did good I tried my
best it's your best I did not have good
rolls so it matters
push this person
okay I'm not on fire somebody set the
oil on fire do it oh it was a fireball
you can shoot it
oh
I don't have fire ah but there's oil on
the floor now I don't know if this
really works I also do not have five
How's It Go five power light the fire
yeah
[Music]
oh yeah
right here good try for the tank
of course they just point blank ignore
the tank
wow
I don't know what that means but I think
you call them stinky
oh he is stinky he's smelly dude
what are they doing wait what's that oh
they added more people enforcements
hold on a sec
if I go here and then
uh
I didn't do this get him
ah let me get off this oil
just in case
dang it critical Miss wait don't leave
me
alone
gotta fight them on your own
reach I'm still in Rachel I'll apply
haunt this Mark on him I'm going to
perish
I'll find him next turn
hopefully they will yeah
please let me take the damage
go for our tank what do we have our tank
for don't attack the the weak ones
these not the glass cannons
help
oh oh man y'all oh dear
good luck
I have no spells
ow
it's like they know I'm about to die
wait let me use this on him can I not
you dash
oh it's gonna be fun looting this place
afterwards
ah there we go we definitely will
um
oh
yeah what
I did zero damage
I did zero damage to this person we are
winning so well don't worry Bijou we'll
take him down
I bonked him on the head and he took
zero damage
um whoa you're choosing how to react
uh you can react yeah you can react
sometimes you can like hit back with a
counter spell go go
[Music]
die
oh I didn't know I could do that okay
cool
I wanted to throw a hand ax
okay well that's one person
it's a fish
was your father a fish wow
goodbye
it's up to you guys no no no we'll
revive you somehow I'd love to revive
you but I do need to do something about
this yeah no no no you do something I
I'm on my way
and I have a Revival thingy oh yeah
[Music]
um
uh I'm gonna try to revive her then
if I can the only thing to remember is
when she comes back it'll be at one HP
so we gotta make sure
[Laughter]
path is interrupted oh I'm in the way
yeah
I'll be small though shouldn't you be
able to aim over her head
come on now why is it only 42 of me
being able to throw it properly that's
because throwing is difficult you know
growing's hard can I oh wait is there
anything else I can do like they say
just touch her yeah just touch her okay
it'll give her one HD though so you
gotta heal pretty quick after that or
someone will just knock her out real
fast all right
oh oh retreat
your little [\h__\h]
again
he knows what he's doing he's using real
friends wow I mean smart man I should
play like that um
right have any do you have any potions
[Music]
look on the right side of your bar
okay ah if you throw the potion right at
her it would hurt her because it's an
attack roll so you have to throw it
right to the ground next to her is that
what happened to Cali before yeah
like the potions made of glass so you're
throwing a glass bottle yeah so let's
throw it on the ground when we want to
do that thanks for the help chat on the
ground
I can't do anything
um oh except uh perform okay
[Music]
do you know Ragnar the red no you're
Ragnar the red you gotta learn Ragnar
the red
it's my favorite color of the bar dance
this is this is all this is this is what
you're getting does it do anything oh
good oh good wow okay it's fine
um
[Music]
I'm helping
oh Mommy nice nice nice
cool
thank you no what was that I want to
change back to my other weapon was it
[\h__\h] okay
foreign
I think that didn't do that much
[Music]
wow
that will deformity putting them on
blast yeah I don't know how I feel if
someone called me that uh
are we
okay okay
let me add them yeah
nice one yeah
thank you okay
[Applause]
okay let's go
[Laughter]
um I suggest we all take a long rest
good
Long Way well I sit like such a lady oh
okay no no I don't I just wanted to sit
down
apart
[Laughter]
Shadow hot
reliable
[Music]
we look like oh my Adventures
wow there are lit fuses in our heads
sooner or later they're going to blue
ones everyone's backside is
gross yeah
we need to find a Healer I want a closer
light
why do you want to take off her clothes
so badly maybe we'll get lucky no I
don't I want it wear her clothes because
they're nice
I doubt that they will fit her
uh just FYI says somebody in chat I
don't know if it's a one guy situation
you can't steal their clothes with four
up
players without killing them ah dang it
I think a note really
up seems simple enough
oh
I mean so loud I need a Starion right
uh I guess we could just murder him how
do I take his clothes
by killing him with anything watch your
damn mouth
how's the text like full-on murder in
the camp just okay let me save the game
okay I'm gonna slap his cheeks around a
little bit yeah
roll initiative
yeah saying it literally
yeah crimes certain actions are frowned
upon by others like I give a [\h__\h] let's
go
yeah kill him oh
my God
[Music]
what is he doing
so messed up the right outfits no
Witnesses
take his underwear oh yeah well the
panty raid I think this always happen
with the Looting
yeah it was sick
why I want his clothes and I got like
fancy clothes I'm pretty sure we could
just undress them I don't think we have
to kill them no we gotta kill him you
want their clothes
sadly with four with four player
anyway I'm happy
well
would you like to go to bed yeah sure
yeah I'll sleep you can't you can't
resurrect them back yeah somebody
canceled what what
me not me
what is this oh yeah yeah
somebody cancels again not your boy
another players it's currently choosing
camp supplies for long rest yeah okay so
someone I think what I think Kelly has
to choose that's the choose it okay okay
what are more players denying the
request
go to bed yeah okay yes
[Music]
just refuse to stay close
yeah well I don't think anyone's
interested
Force the tadpole out of your mind I'm
not very intelligent so I'll use wisdom
I'm smarter than all of you all right
I'll use wisdom I'm Wiser than you
though I think that yeah you focus on
that spot of pain from when it slips
okay I'll try it too so I used 80
instead of 40 whoopsies I succeed you
know it's our first meal in the game
maybe maybe we want 80. what is there to
fear it is the one stuck inside you yeah
it is a minor victory
but enough to soothe you to sleep no
it's a brick wise is a mountain exactly
I mean it's in character right
then character
using too much food
Mario pay no understand food I can't
wake up because you guys are a custody
but when I get to sleep if I failed this
what what would have done what what did
that even do the fact that I succeeded
hmm what would it have done if I failed
I don't know no idea
[Music]
come on mentions uh somebody says you
you said you wanted to multi-class yes
apparently we can't on this difficulty
what
yeah it's disabled on the difficulty
because it's fairly Advanced oh my God
what should we do
um it's okay I'll just when when can we
change when the re-roll happens I can
re-roll
changing difficulty and menu option I
can change it oh yeah change it so
normal yeah change normal we'll be fine
yeah we'll we'll live yeah we'll live I
don't know about that you guys
we've already been on the bridge of
dying a lot of times well we'll be fine
maybe if it's too difficult yeah but
then the multi-class things
it's fine change multi-class then go
back
yeah
so
really really
mean girls situation that's a mean girl
situation I'm looking at right here
oh my God beautiful enough for you no no
okay
it's kind to me Liara
Mori okay love Liana oh
you take like two spaces
there we go oh look at that hey nice but
there's always going to be one girl
excluded why is our our posters so [\h__\h]
why do we sit like that how do I steal
people's clothes without killing them
are we gonna go back to the fight yeah
I'm already here
yeah
all right click on the bed click on the
bedroom
the bed roll the bed the bed thing
I'll leave Camp okay
all right
no look okay
how does it open
are you trying to end the day why are we
going to bed now I didn't
for ladle no I don't need this stuff
open this
oh
I already took all the treasures I took
it for me
where are you okay I'm good now
over this way
hey
why would I need
you guys are still inside yeah yeah
I'm on the other side
stealing all the money from here
it's weird why does the books have HP
that might be working though oh my job
what's this it's just the story what
does that do is there ever something I
did something
did something happen
I don't recognize the language on the
plaque oh
loaded sometimes girls have magic oh
there's a there's a door I opened over
here
I'm on the way
um
no which door
this way this one yeah this one mm-hmm
where is
yeah why are you giggling
[Laughter]
so I'm just exploring some more she's a
little thing let's go
like where are you going okay
it's
it's like nothing of value in there did
you already steal everything in here
people no I
oh oh where you going
oh shoot oh
no
uh turn the game has passed around and
then time is working down into another
okay
what's gonna happen
fine what's happening
I think we're fine
what what's happening for you girls I
mean I ended my turn uh I think yeah I
think you have to end your turn
oh but there's a button apparently
what button
go back to entrance okay okay let's go
so far
oh okay that's about what I thought
[Music]
yeah at least it wasn't hit this time
did you get them maybe now I don't know
maybe now it's it's not as dangerous
anymore because it's shot once you think
it's gonna shoot again oh
but
it'll be fine no it's not safe it's not
over okay okay I love bug sleep
yeah yeah yeah what if there's treasure
oh
okay oh stand in there with your hands
on your hips okay fired
I'm not until you turn out of the print
baseball okay
whoa whoa okay
oh
they're like
fighting are you guys fighting something
uh oh we're fine no it's fine it's fine
it's fine it's fine oh uh people yeah
never stop you're dying I'm dying yes
yeah you're almost dead over there
oh [\h__\h]
a little bit yeah there's a button
there's a button I mean do you want to
walk into that I mean I already got the
blue is the thing in the middle
you did is there more loot than done I
don't know it says I can shoot the
button oh you took the loot I I earned
it I earned it I went and grabbed it and
survived I earned this
I turned it off
okay we'll go find them
oh oh is it good now
yeah I turned it off here oh
I found something with 71 Health there's
a trap oh he's dead though
but his tentacles are still kind of
moving oh no I don't know what it was
blocked
oh
you know um
you're finding I want to see what you
[\h__\h]
is this better than what I have I'll
reopen only find dirt
Holy Dirt
should I use this is a mystery to you
we're too dumb to understand what's on
the path
and not very smart
equip the shields
are you guys still down in that uh yeah
we didn't finish exploring it Lauren
okay still exploring the Crypt now now
it seems is finished
yeah it looks like we oh there's
something over here
um
there's dead people with loose oh cool I
love that
my aesthetic
that statue religion failed
oh they have so much money
I pressed the secret button oh
nice mine mine Oreo Memorial bed things
maybe it's a trap again
[Music]
I'm very happy to see their Maury oh
hello
okay where is it I hear okay there's a
person next to me oh yeah one right next
to me too
away
oh somebody oh
get him dead beats whose side are you on
boy
all right
oh he almost died I wonder how tanky
these guys are I need to see their help
nice shot
oh we can take them looking now that
[\h__\h] attacking Bijou now
they're surround
oh
it wasn't a crypt it looks so strong
though sheesh I have the same thing all
right fine I'll go help my friends
before I do I was having a good time I'm
really angry
on a little solo Journey
yeah I was a looting looting things on
the beach the beach side
rattle them boys oh he's dead oh
another one
it's been frosted
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay
yeah bye
I love that spell
um
okay okay
yes okay one HP left
hmm
use the other one
oh wait
back off deadbeat you don't want this
you don't want any
I'm too lucky
they never hit they always me
let it all out it's good to let it out
uh let the aggressions out
the feet back off
deadbeats have a bad aim yeah
a lot of things do I already use my
bonus actually I'll live through this
shortly oh yeah yeah it should be fun
oh I forgot about him
he has a different Target
it's cool with six
six
[Music]
how many enemies
only three oh
they're all pretty beaten up
yeah yeah we got this
boom
oh he died he did die
[Music]
destroy you
is there there's one left gun
there's still one dude yeah on the rides
behind people who come behind me oh SPM
I see him okay
oh
money seems they worship somebody I have
money Scala
all right
yeah
what's in there what's inside big
treasure beyond my wildest imagination
oh
this doesn't this scares me I know this
guy
oh
he's got pretty eyelashes oh my God we
found your remote
[Laughter]
Supreme deadbeat
feel that snow
it's got a little beaten up
now I have a question for the what is
the worth of a single mode this is a
test from sensei okay um
let me see the multiple choice questions
crawling out of a tomb peaceful and dead
interesting why aren't you attacking me
attack that's the reason
no attack nothing
my question
on the quiz I'm trying to remember the
real answer this ogre is having a harsh
time answering the question matters is
mine money depends on the Mortal oh my
God
I am sure thou believest was I right
sensei
there are different ways I can phrase it
[Laughter]
we will see each other again no join our
team
[Music]
oh he will he will
see each other again
[Music]
mine I got magic mystical magic missiles
oh actually
Ally do you want this Amulet of lost
voices unless you speak with the Dead
oh yeah you can speak with your homies
okay here I'll give it to you yeah
cool
you hold on what is this oh Soul coin
the coins can power infernal engines
um so you want magic Missile
I'm not gonna use it oh sure I can hold
on to it no wait I don't want to stop I
don't want to use it
still the controls they still Escape me
okay sorry I remember how to do this hi
Lisa hi
there's a ring on my finger
you
know why are you holding a Starion
someone what did you just do
ladder way out
same underwear
all right it's a little weird but
alrighty Alan come to us wait who has a
serious underwear yeah is wearing it
yeah what
no yes you are what do you mean I'm
wearing it for wearing it I checked your
inventory
oh
what
what I didn't
consciously equipped anyone's underwear
well
you're wearing it
there's a ladder
I find you guys don't worry Ollie left
there was some stairs all because all
half underwear is the same okay
I didn't know that that's a lot less fun
oh
no vampires
but I don't know if anybody did that
all right I'm out I'm on the way
where shall we go next team the question
can you do a short rest we were here
before yeah
oh so I gotta I gotta do the short rest
huh
as the host
s
don't worry
we came I'm here now
where are we going
you guys need the way okay I'm going
this way
I'll follow people okay Advent together
strong together
you never split the part
um
where are we going
um actually no not this way not this way
we've been this way we didn't go up this
way yet
um
left or right
wait actually actually wait hold on
there's someone over here
all right anyone can short rest but it's
good to talk about it gotcha oh oh it's
the it's the girl it's the the girl you
had yeah oh wait no no that's not no
it's a different situation
oh
no she's like a prisoner uh-oh mine
hi
what are we doing Liara uh
ah it's up to you do what you think is
right good luck
get rid of them well
um
shoot the Trap down oh
wait but am I saying this to her I think
you're saying it to to the the
tifflings yeah
uh
but I don't really have much persuasion
and deception at all yeah
I could I could try to talk to them
because I have both of those
I'll
I guess I'll try do your best faculty
over ten come on
let's go we need to check out that blast
German by the way for for deeplings oh
really
that cool they just make it sound fancy
you didn't hear it shook outcome good so
we came for a look
I'm in dire need of healing I don't know
not really
[Music]
the rooms I ever had yeah oh okay
fine okay
totally doable totally doable yeah yeah
[Music]
worms out
look for Nettie whatever your wound
ready
you say whatever really there are goblin
traps even the worms cool they're pretty
nice I killed these dudes
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
well then you're gonna stay up there
too bad
you'll hear goblins
you could just kill her I don't even
shoot it
but if we accidentally shoot it
the first ones don't
we throw something at it what does that
mean what a panda
wait hold on
bro
yeah hope for us is there
[Music]
release me and Sheila share it okay
you're free you got it maybe next time
next time talk to her
[Laughter]
right uh
we'll go our separate ways I I thank you
what's that uh what is the correct it
sounds like a French uh a training
grounds it does
yes they're chill Camp when infected
with a cake tadpole we must report to
Augusto for purification
[Music]
all right well journey together
dismiss your weakness
[Laughter]
you're the weakest Warrior
get out of here
go back to the camp you you're the
weakest historical
we're all very strong ladies yeah
although her armor looks like plastic so
yeah it does
you play made
oh yeah yeah the thing they just told us
about before they left
the area the campsite they came from and
you're shouting up ahead yeah we'll get
we will get there for sure okay
oh something's happening you quickly
save hold on
oh quick little things
oh yeah okay this is I think this is the
right direction
more like good janky
goblets
the yucky one
I got nine Hells now you open the gate
yeah when the when the bad guy is there
sooner
[Music]
yeah right
that's a that's a life they lost for no
reason
can we help him
yeah we can let's do it
let's go well I love will will Wilson oh
[\h__\h]
yeah Mr Hero man oh
um there's literally one right in front
of me okay great go far back yeah I
can't I can't do anything
we are pretty far back I I might need
some help
well you've been waiting for us
am I dashing I want to dash yeah we are
pretty far away Dash might be in order
why does it even start when we're so far
away should I get on the hill or stairs
go on the hill I need L okay
oh wait no oh that's I thought that was
one of us
okay uh
um
you're gonna finish the battle before I
get there
well good luck babe
it's really far cool
[Music]
you guys look like they can handle
themselves yeah
Kelly is this why we never split a party
yeah this would be the reason
oh ow
[Music]
oh
oh we're doing a little dance
[Music]
[\h__\h]
I get better accuracy the further I'm
away with both oh
interesting
yeah I thought I thought that was
another one of us that's why I got so
close okay
[Music]
day
the old days
wow
wow Miss toys
I pushed this person and I'll help forty
percent I will I will risk it push do it
Athletics films pushless speed day
a couple year movement speed all right
talk good good
[Music]
I'm sorry
okay cool
no I don't know how I did that but
so you can push and then also attack
still I guess so maybe I'll try the same
thing
chat if he's like down here and I'm up
there
can I shoot him yeah cause like
realistically I don't think I could
[Music]
he wouldn't be what do you mean do you
see what I'm pointing at
it
so like you know what I'm pointing at I
mean right below like right it doesn't
matter
do you win with him and it says and it
says that like he doesn't say your past
is obstructed and it just gives a
regular like percentage
[Music]
well done
hmm
and now we shoot yes oh nice it's nice
we get him
intern
hold out and right click
almost in the battle I'm almost there
was helpful
I don't know
you girls know how to Ping um
I think yeah like that
what I meant here oh nicely I can see is
it right like or left click right click
okay oh okay
yes yes
go help them
good luck go ahead
they're really far away
yeah I'll use this I think you can scale
down the mountain
or the hill that we're on
there there she is see there I am get in
there because what if he has arrived
um
throwing
uh let's see
you're seeing shot
oh
good crit
I know I can throw the knives but I know
it works from
oh
yeah he hated that he's mad
[Music]
come on
go it will be strong because throwing
would be nice what was that
[Music]
uh
because they're still far away
I did not see them
yeah right
so
[Music]
they're they're front lining I'm in the
back
is dead
yeah
he'll be revived surely
okay I'm gonna go stab this thing oh I
can't do this anymore more accuracy
[Music]
okay
you stabbed him okay I'll stab this one
then
one damage
that was not that that was a poke
but good good foreign
um
[Music]
oh good try I'm gonna put the mark on
it
oh um
[Music]
okay oh oh that's AOE damage yeah it
would appears
well now I know that I have AOE damage
on that one
you guys left
outnumbered I think they'll definitely
win
yeah
we need to fight more things so we can
level one more time yeah um I want more
stuff yeah we're weak oh
I got two oh
oh yeah
thank you
okay all I can do is stab so I'm just
gonna keep stabbing
foreign
[Music]
yeah
I didn't do anything to him
uh I didn't I didn't either the battle
isn't what what happened that was but it
doesn't like you Looting the dress
was a guy I think you may have
accidentally looted one of the dead
people do we okay can we run away
is he temporarily hostile or Perma
hospital
I'm sorry we put him to sleep or let me
see I think I think we both did it Bijou
I'm not sure oh I don't know I just
thought the goblin was a bad guy
you guys can travel non-lethal attacks
and we need to fight him I think oh so
how do you turn around
yeah there's like a switch so like you
know where you have all your spells and
stuff like go to the first wheel and
it's like at the top wait okay can we
just disengage
okay I'm not sure
goodbye
okay very well sorry
one person toggles it for this oh
he's after me
[Music]
I might resent you but they won't be
actually awesome
he got Charmed okay good okay
come on be nice pretty let's go nice one
we
can we just okay Enter
I'm leaving I just nowhere else
[Music]
don't worry you hit him he'll never be
your friend we just gotta run from him
don't enter stay safe one person says
don't enter
charm just means he won't attack you
you're gonna run away and then flee to
Camp uh-huh oh okay I'm running away if
you enter more people so you have to run
away and get far enough so it disengages
from combat so just well we love will I
want him on our team yeah it was great
he's awesome
I wouldn't even lose it wasn't even me
he's not up for reasoning okay just just
run oh
I remember I remember that yeah I should
have remembered that was gonna happen
it won't work on him he can't be an
enemy please
this goes poorly no no no no we'll just
have to run away far far enough
it looks like a heart I like it run away
can I disengage now
can I flee from college
am I far enough
how do you how do you tell if you're far
enough I don't think there is a far
enough
get out of the battle
again
yeah
27 meters okay well I'm far enough now
okay
whoa leave me alone
I I spam the red button the red button
didn't work
see
right I should be okay flea combat yes
Lee combat flea combat it's not working
is it working for you
yeah I flew I fled to Camp how come how
long for me I'm like
are you not far enough I got pretty far
away I'm using oh you're using death
yeah I'm like super far I also have flat
the combat
yeah his eyes are open just keep keep
running keep running you can flee from
combat and go to Camp if you are far
enough from your enemies and it's it it
says it's fun enough
a little further how many camps are
there
this one's pretty
can I buy arrows here
yeah it won't it won't let me press the
button okay well I'll keep running I
guess
maybe a game
[Music]
ice arrows
oh
it's okay I'm still in combat too so
wait oh he's coming after you
people are you pressing the
disengagement
the bottom white red one I'm pressing
the bottom white red one but it's
probably I think it's bugged because I
keep one thing I didn't say how many
meters you're away from him because for
me it said I need 27 meters
I was out of his range because it didn't
say the 27 meters anymore but now he got
closer so I don't know
but he's chasing me
well they say that he likes you when he
chases you
it doesn't say 27 meters anymore because
I'm far enough but it won't let me
disengage still
um I am going to perish go on without me
remember me
how do I volunteer without killing him
is that even I think he's gonna kill me
hide I'm gonna hide okay
I need to find a way forward
we can reload if you want and we that
battle was easy so
yeah you can just do it again
you want to relax be unarmed or using oh
I can maybe I can Bonk him I fail yeah
hold on I'll try to I'll okay I'll try
to Bonk him hold on one second yeah as
long as this damages
yeah
what does it say you're creating ease
knock someone unconscious okay I need to
be unarmed so I need to take off
weapons okay come here I'm gonna Bonk
you
I messed up oh no Marissa
I'm chilling you look so beautiful
they're investing in the sunlight but
also partially being covered by the
beautiful leaves above you thank you the
sunlight you know I'm just work Wonders
on you you guys Romancing each other
[Laughter]
I'm sure glad you guys are having fun
[Music]
oh another chance
why
why did nobody nobody carry away the
dead body of a Starion no it would leave
it there it's hilarious
to another camp
[Music]
to bring them back to life well maybe my
skeleton friend can help for a prize
um yeah
hey buddy can you help me bring my
friend back to life
by cross pass
um
yeah can you help me change my class uh
resurrect someone yeah resurrect
Ed I died
in its pose wow no it's the gold oh
okay I'm gonna bring you back oh thank
you sorry will
surely he'll forgive you yeah yeah you
killed me I'm a new person now excuse me
really thanks for noticing if you're up
turned fast now is any better oh thank
you hello
at the battlefield or where are you
girls no I'm in I'm in Camp now okay
okay I'm talking to a lady I might want
to rest I have one HP oh yeah
we have one short rest left but maybe we
should just sleep we should just do a
long rest probably let's just do a long
one oh that [\h__\h]
whoa
yeah
oh oh this oh he's still here
yeah huh
we just we just keep bringing his dead
body with us to kill yeah
I guess so that we can one day bury him
which is very respectful exactly that's
what it's all about the respect and are
we ending the day
yeah yeah because because uh okay okay
someone in Camp still wishes to speak to
you go to bed anyway
Marissa if you want to speak to me just
speak to me
I mean I don't know who would want to
talk to me
why can't we
[Music]
if you're too sad you can DM me
every day I spend in your DMs yeah
all right good morning everybody good
morning good morning dead person good
morning
you guys ready to go back into this
place yeah let's go back into I really
hope he isn't still mad at me well we'll
find out won't we okay
fingers crossed where shall we enter to
grow
there's a lot of blood around here nice
yeah that's that's where I died
[Music]
it's bagel's blood right there whatever
reason the don't be done being angry
yeah is he done
is it safe now
come on
yeah level
who do I get to choose a subclass now I
wonder
[Music]
additional rage charge nice
okay I get to choose a subclass gonna go
berserk okay okay I will need to take a
moment to maybe look at the Spells do
what you gotta do okay so don't run away
everybody no more cleric I'm done being
here now yeah I think the one I wanted
to do was a college of lore oh
should I go for this one now that's a
good one because you girls or guys
wanted me to take this one
um
yes okay
so is it even with animal enemies like
the work just now that I could speak
with
or just like random dogs and so ones yes
also with the words oh okay I'm gonna
hit the shop really quick don't mind me
I can now speak with animals let's go oh
animals should be helpful should I take
Shield or magic missiles magic myths
were useful
I gave you a one magic Missile scroll so
you can test it out well not now
obviously or I'm taking orb never mind
I'm getting an orb or yeah
Thunder damage lightning damage okay
ignore okay
do not bear
do not the subclass was already the one
I wanted to be I think
um
[Music]
yeah
that was what I already chose
I think beforehand yeah I remember that
[Music]
cast speak of animals friends are strong
as a spot okay until long rest
so until we rest I can speak for any
animal are there any animals here I
haven't seen anything
are you animal
and I can use Chad I can use frenzy
without using rage first correct
Pals
hmm let's do this
oh wait why do I have to press this
again
and can I speak with my own animal they
usually frenzy replaces rage
I see
the better rage okay
okay
because it's my best friend
sorry guys I walked into something oh oh
what like something what happened I
don't I don't know
we in here oh I see you're in the hollow
I was gonna talk to the shopkeeper
anyway so a bear
[Music]
oh did you just walk into the crowd
yes can I talk to that video now can I
talk to your crap
I'm not wait you also have to speak
without yeah I'm a gnome so no one's can
speak without him
can we stop shouting hello
I'm talking with a cow be gone I am
hungry
huh oh the cow didn't want to talk to
him let's freaking go
I am going to bring in never sound
Ed new good armor
sick you know what all right Larissa I
stole your Raven
you're Raven's Mine
He's Savage Raven likes me
yeah yeah
you know I I understand it because I
like you too it is what it is
cute you can talk to these uh you can
talk to these cows I'm feeling good
right now
he's my eat my ravened ones I'm not
shiny bit s oh my god oh yeah you're
right I don't need armor cause I'm a
barbarian
oh God uh Callie can you do me a favor
what's up uh when you have time can you
save and reload the game I'm stuck in
combat music probably because of the
real thing oh
you got it
bugs a moment
really quick
um
hello oh
what I just rolled a success
um
[Music]
is a cow being mean to you oh oh sorry
had to quick load the game it's okay I
should have said something I am very
sorry I should have said I'm quick
loading the game
pardon me
like pardon dude I'm sewing gross but
like I have I don't know what's
happening
I'm like I've watched and there are
people there are people like praying and
they were really mean they did not want
to let me in oh yeah that's right no no
one's fighting me I'm just talking to
people
all good the music's best thank you
no problem
ah wait this one's good
come on give me a good roll I'm gonna
eat you cow you better tell me yeah hey
sixteen
not with this death embrace it ah
that's my job
oh hello it's me hello
I thought you were housing
around confidence
apparently animals in this game
I believe it
this this this
um this pig wants a mate
[Laughter]
oh it's a bird it's noisa hello what's
gonna say it looks like Shadow yeah
that's the one I summoned I can summon
two apparently
good one New Birth familiar and another
one in the middle
there are different choices I can have a
board I can kick the bird spider
excuse me let's not kick the birds
following me this thing
fine I won't kick the bird are we down
in the groove
honey I love these random animals
honey
how'd you guys get down in there I just
walked in
they were like cool
yeah
all right right he's done something
right
oh
can I still kick it
don't don't hurt the birds it's hard
fish
I think that the Druids won't like that
yeah it might get a little offense so
I'm gonna anoint this key from the bird
no that's a new pickpockets bikini the
bird
no I'm just borrowing stuff thanks bird
okay
what's happening
and you did it
me I didn't realize I thought I would
talk to it but I took it
they don't seem to have noticed
no they they did I'm in a club
they didn't notice it was you the thing
they all just lost house
oh gosh
you have started a conflict
yeah oops
um
let's reload I'm so sorry but I will not
take the idol again
this is wait hold on there's a little a
slight spoiler though which is why I'm
confused in the campaign there's a child
that steals it
yeah well today it was me
huh
it was supposed to happen
I mean I think it'll happen regardless
maybe maybe not it's just a difference
of who does it I think the child tried
to steal it and she failed
foreign
[Music]
I feel like I'm stuck in a Time Loop man
this is the first time I'm talking to
this cow
[Music]
is
this
she's right over by me and bee boo by
the pig
uh-huh
I used words
YOLO
bolo stop it help help
hmm
Dragon they go display can I have your
key
a little bit of leg you like
of course
so much for the perfect
jump I love getting to the bottom of
Ebola we believe in you
oh
I found I found another barn
nice
connect
I'm talking to his Queen one
[Music]
what do you think
oh no
it must take the things
did you stole from the bird
wow well if we didn't reload I would
have uh
[Applause]
[Laughter]
squirrel because I had critical success
in using it
well that's chaotic
so what are we even have any loot
um oh my God I only we only have two
five
five battle
[Laughter]
you can't steal things
you can't steal this year I lost the
roll okay
I won the roll last time but then you
reloaded
not aggroing the Grove you gotta tell
you gotta tell me hey Maury I'm about to
do a really risky action save the game
so shall we reload another time okay
[Laughter]
maybe you can do it in the next life one
more quick load okay
with him again then we lose the bear
because we just gotta play for
okay if I if I lose I won't steal the
key okay listen it was the bird's key
why did humans get mad at me for
stealing the birds key I don't
understand nature they love nature
they're Druids no yeah don't steal
anything don't steal [\h__\h] we want to be
friends with these guys we can steal
from the Goblins okay well no it seems
like it seems like they're being kind of
corrupted they're being kind of like
racist to the tieflings and stuff you
know like they're they're bad like yeah
so I think
I can tell you where Nettie is listen to
me she's in a room through the carved
door deeper in the Grove yep so that's
what she says
and eye dot touching the bird because
I'm scared okay I'm gonna talk to the
bird
again
oh my God I'm Gonna Save the game oh
thank God no it's okay I won't I won't
you want it if I fail
I'll I'll be good and for the sake of
plot I'll be good
yeah
I know how you really want to play
this look good okay I'm gonna add
guidance in the middle
I'm gonna go find that Bard lady again
she was cute okay
not just looking into a mirror
[Music]
I mean a cute part lady I only know of
one
she's another tiefling she's another
tiefling Bard so I'm kind of curious I
wonder if she can join our team
okay save it so I don't have to kill
this bird yeah okay we're good now we're
good and
yeah I'm chilling by the stone door
what's going on here where we can find
the Healer inside so much lag here oh
wow
oh
yep right over here
once we go inside the healers inside
okay I'm waiting
see
I'm ready to enter
save the game
I saved the game yes
all right into the stone door
shall we follow
yeah sure that'd be cool
I got the cutscene there's a small child
here oh no
oh
this is sad I'm sorry
Wrath
a thief oh wait I was like a dragon the
devil
and I will cast out every stranger as a
child
I do not
uh what is the girl's actual crime one
of your guards outside said here I am
first
judgment must be passed
no care about this
holy Idol in thanks
wrath lock her up
she remains here all right I do have a
moral compass interest
Tila is restless ah she's so mean
come cooker with the back the idol
surely do it
all right
[Music]
let's go Mario pay mad all right I got
these added so let's go please work
let's go let's go
yeah
I
can't see her roll
to me
Let Her Go nice persuasion
my Grace has its limits oh that was
really cool Mario
I think you guys will really like
Allison
um
purple chest here I'm not gonna open it
of course because that would be thievery
[Music]
friends
I'm a friend
guys we lost I lost I went to rub your
belly well what's up nerissa where are
you guys oh we went into that where you
said Nettie was yeah anything just now
I don't I don't know where that was okay
I'll leave and then you can see where my
icon is and then just go there yeah yeah
yeah yeah
okay
all right I'm outside so follow where my
icon is
okay
okay wait yeah I see it okay I can get
there you can go back in thank you all
right you're welcome I save game
I save game every two seconds yeah
probably for the better in case I
accidentally steal the idol again
oh did you find the Healer yes nice oh
I'll start a conversation she's healing
a verb good woman
oh
um
excuse me and more important than some
bird now whoa who rude I can do it
[Music]
there
why the feathers like so weird
what was it you need it
um
I'm looking for Netty you need help now
I need help
do you know anything about mind players
why are you asking
I've got plenty of them
um I have a tadpole in my hand
I wish it was a frog tadpole
that'd be kind of gross too though oh
yeah what other kinds are there it's not
like a frog hopped into my house I mean
sarcasm
help me
I'll do what I can come four of us can
you help all of us please
let's go
oh
all of this stuff that she has I can't
pick up sad
she'll get mad at me
you should have expected to be a thief
I'm really sure huh
take a closer look what's that oh
look at them can I stand on his body
bro drow's letter
brew and find whatever bro he runs to
and report back to me remember you are
only a scout do not engage not kill
anyone simply observe and return I shall
decide what we do next m
what who are you talking to I was
reading a letter on this person's body
ah
I'm hoping for a less grave cured so you
killed him away
[Music]
this tale ends but one way
with the Outlander rot cleansed
forever shouting ignoring you given the
other cold shoulder eh
okay he's gonna stick it's pointy
oh she does have a stick
so what are you gonna do with that
instead of him hit me with the pointy
ends these things
still
oh the bird does look like Shadow let's
see what I can do
oh God Jesus what are the cats doing
what I gotta keep going they knock down
I don't want to be so rude
[Music]
I'll take anything
no
any symptoms strange events
oh I have a bug
you see that right
I wonder if what I click is actually
though not what it seems to be
um I'll just say victims okay okay
not that the others know they're victims
of course how'd you pick up the parasite
housing was desperate to find where all
this was happening
okay uh
she is asking a lot but I mean okay but
she's a Healer
should I go for the first one I think
that yeah I'd go for the first one okay
they're okay they're safe they just
knock something over
was sure
perform here
that's a good Soul yeah you deserve a
chance to save yourself thank you oh
watch you put the stick away this is
okay she's not gonna swear to me you'll
swallow I'm sorry can you say that word
again
how did she pronounce it was it wyvern
or wyvern
I would say why foreign
all right let's go
I swear to me you'll swallow it if you
feel any symptoms
I thought you could kill me what about
that branch of yours The Thorn
quoted in a fatal toxin
[Laughter]
I was gonna kill you she's very honest
though saying that I'm sorry for
misleading I think she likes us now at
least she's nice versus like the mean
lady outside yeah definitely yeah
yes
I swear I hope it doesn't come to that
but I mean thank you we can use it on
people right yeah yeah
treating folk and never once saw a mind
flare infection then suddenly there's
dozens of you see Irish a lot of us
Master Houston and I were tracking pick
up a hint
I'm trying to figure out what the hell
is going on
apparently we can kill Gaga you should
all be changing
the jerk lady what is that what does
that set the whole Grove against us I
think we could I think we should kill
her
I mean I agree that she's mean
what do you mean it should be changing
uh
maybe it might be more than seven days
mmm
hard to say
to say maybe we're special
infection of course we are have been
converging on an old Temple of salute we
have plot armor we're the main
characters
we're heading that way he saw a chance
to get us okay let's go find him
okay he didn't make it back
um
but the place is rotten with goblins
it's okay we can kill the Cowboys yeah
we got plenty of us yeah
technically speaking I mean kill someone
carrying their parasite oh you can find
house and get him one of us one of us we
can discover what he learned and perhaps
he can save your life okay how's that
sound okay no they'll find him let's get
him
it would mean everything to the groom to
me I'm gonna try to tell you more
players know what happened out there
oh all I can say for sure as they all
went to the old Temple of saloon Master
halson didn't make it back sounds like
there's a lot of treasure okay
remember your oath hi hi okay let's go
let's go
um
well four I accidentally steal something
hold on I'm sorry guys just a moment my
cats are batting something around out
there and I don't want you to keep
batting around it I think they might try
to swallow so just is it
is this so should I uh you keep this
because it's single use
a new outfit
yeah help me it's like I could use it
drink it
I can call it a weapon of it yeah
amazing armor too oh
yeah
apparently there's a secret room if we
check behind a book yes
I took it away from them
we're good I don't know how they found a
little thing to play with a new toy
let's get out of here
room behind one of the bookcases
but all the bookcases are red meaning
like yeah meaning if we touch them we'll
we'll get into combat save the game oh
wait I got perception what was the
perception for
open locks maybe we need to be friends
with them first
three stone top
[Music]
yeah there's there's apparently a chest
so it'll lead us to her room
oh
all right maybe my snake
oh apparently this this door can open
but it's red
oh does it say locked or is it yeah and
it's also red
ah
yeah maybe maybe if we go save we can
loot this Mouse oh yeah I'm gonna touch
this room
not this room
everything you find
negative five bagel
I didn't
even do it are you sure yeah I just
randomly bling
I just readily making people angry
that's a big woof
I'm sorry it's cute no one no one fought
me though so it's fine rats I want to
talk to the rats
yeah the rats surely have lots to say
can I kick this one too did you find it
oh you found the servants quarters now
what about you
boring I wanted to kill the rat okay
kill the Russian I can't I can't they
won't let me
do anything a little cool
I mean I think you probably can you
probably could kill the rat if you well
I know
I don't think oh okay
oh you found it
but I don't know how to get into it it's
locked oh
oh I heard it look I probably need a key
maybe you could pickpocket the key oh
wait how did you guys get up on this
chest
walk around ah yeah you go from up here
I thought I picked up a thief kit
I mean if no one's here I have a thief's
tool
quite a handful
something else not sleight of hand the
same my sleight of hand uh only got six
oh I can roll
yeah I'll try it
nice
all right Luke Goblin it's up to you I
just want to see what's in it I just
want to see what's his name
so
yeah yeah
and they can't just sense that it's on
you right so you're fine yeah okay let's
go let's go though what did you take
what was inside let's see there was a
ruby there was a
there was a book oh was there a note
there was a letter in to read it okay
I'll read it
um okay
the Mars Chris crossing the page don't
look scribe so much as slash uh kaga
swamp docs tree meet me alone allodon
okay
I don't know where the swamp is oh no
Don wasn't that one of the rats oh we
got a quest though we got a quest for it
you do Journal updates
well done all of that is one of the rats
really
okay
try to talk to me
rat Whisperer
do we follow all of them I don't know I
only heard the last word all of them
that's all I registered in my brain
that watches yeah I remembered one thing
anything
what well done is not actually a rat
maybe we can make him say something
cool
[Music]
I'm beginning to feel like
hold on
let me talk to you again
now speak to the rat
now okay really doesn't want to talk
okay I guess we gotta go to the swamp or
something
yeah I think yeah well let's go okay
they want me to talk to the tafling
leader and they she's like get them out
ah yeah that's right get him out so we
could just like escort the tifflings out
of here but read the book
you heard what happened to the squirrel
okay
balance is a myth where any clowns trust
nature struggles Unity is a fiction men
of mere flesh seek only to tame beast
and raise Flora we are the Thunder and
we are the rain we shatter Mankind and
grow new life in its place okay
I'm looking at your outfit people I just
realized can you give me your cleric
outfit
oh can you wear heavy armor
I don't know
I don't think you or can you wear medium
armor
isn't there and just I just want I just
want to change out of what I'm wearing
now here I'll give you I'll get oh
I'll give you
asterion's clothes here you go uh okay
I don't know where they go in my items
perhaps yeah just checking your bags
who did I give it to
eh I I gave her two white yeah you have
it a padded armor padded armor okay okay
I was in the wrong I was in the wrong
[Music]
uh can I uh live for uh two minutes or
one minute
go for it we can uh you can eat some
chips too Cali yeah you're in um
underwear
yeah so the reason for that is because
um as like a bird as a barbarian yeah I
read that it's better that you don't
have uh armor oh okay yeah are you sure
about that
I may have been LED astray here
um they're basically correct they don't
count as armor okay
your normal clothes don't count as arm
okay well I mean this is bad I mean
it's not bad
wow you have you'll have like a six pack
yeah you know she she works out it's
almost an eight pack you know we'll get
it there though okay
does that look better are you happy in
new clothes they look good on you I
think yeah yeah I feel much more
comfortable not in the ugly default
clothes
I could I could play a little ditty
they're not what I meant to do
you have that tire on it's not it's just
the equipment armor you don't need
gotcha
I can work with that hey nice tune
thank you I like it
what the [\h__\h]
did you what was that what was there
what even was there yeah
he's a pie you could throw the pot
well I just wanted to show her oh my God
[Applause]
oh my God
put your butt away look at that G Street
mine are way more decent than yours okay
isn't the top so cute like oh my God
yeah it is but put some pants on please
how do I take my clothes off okay
you look like you're about to go to
Coachella
[Laughter]
ready to go
you're so my sister really likes
Coachella
that's kind of nice yeah oh wow let her
you will look visual but not at me
[Laughter]
I don't think I can't unequip my my uh
instrument because
wait wait wait keep it on keep it on
morning
[Laughter]
what is the stream turning into okay
yes okay
thank you and Cali too in those Club yes
okay okay I don't think they're
unfashionable yeah the cheeks are
protected yeah
very strong buy another vase to throw at
you guys
okay how do we make progress where what
are we in yeah where do we go oh yeah we
got distracted
no not very very distracted no no no no
okay
um now here's what we can do
would you guys like to go to find the
goblin Camp yeah let's go mom yes
all right I really want to steal the
idol again you know
something
okay wait let's save let's save let's
save and test our power level
right okay
get get close so we can all be kind of
together what what are you white no why
wait wait wait wait wait wait I want to
talk to Polo okay wait okay are you tell
us when you're done okay
I won't grab it I won't grab it until
you guys say you're ready
but I just want to see if we can take
take the idol you know all righty wait
can you hide that's a friendly looking
I'm trying there's a lot of people
around I think that the sight of them
too widespread
um
I succeeded in history let's go
unbelievable
um
yeah no they're they're questioning
they're like why are you sneaking around
they're watching
this is a legend
he's a legend
oh
well I have an idea okay
are we ready to do this ready wait yeah
we need to wait for kiwama to be ready
uh
he's a lore important NPC legendary
figure in DND
okay uh
there was no dragon how do I how do I
play my songs for some reason I only
have the option to do bartic inspiration
and I don't want that I want to do my
actual song playing is there no like
regular I I think I broke it somehow
because I don't remember how to get to
my regular performance
common
I mean like this is the bottom part okay
yes I found it I found it you were so
smart thank you
you passed the performance check blank
is hard the NPCs will come watch you
play your instrument and then bibo can
pickpocket them from behind oh yeah yeah
but I think they're busy these people
will leave yeah just for the future oh
someone's here
maybe don't pick talk at him maybe maybe
I know
everyone can see
okay here let me see if we can distract
these people
amazing probably not but
we'll just see I'll Stand between these
ones okay I think they're crazy
I think so too but just yeah just we're
just seeing they're doing like their
blessing you know
I can't yeah but I'm a bard
I think they're ignoring
[Music]
um
don't ignore me
oh the boy likes it oh the bar lights
so adorable look at him look at him
dancing he's taking his little butt
so adorable I'm done okay Steve are we
actually trying this okay why not okay
okay come here and I'm gonna do
something okay okay what are you gonna
do
okay
yes yes
oh wait go get it there's a fall Cloud
go get it
huh
pick it up
nice okay wait oh no they noticed right
away
[Music]
I mean they were blessing it like two
seconds
so I just
welp I'm
oh watch this guy get beat up again yeah
watch his skull get bashed in it was
pretty pretty sick
you know that hurt
oh yeah that's gotta be painful wow
but like oh he's feeling it wasn't it
was his fault
they're just blaming the tieflings for a
lot of things apparently I don't
understand
[Music]
it's not very nice
let's not it
but
are we battling or are we running
battling of course
don't they shoot the bear
yeah tough it
hey he's gonna try to kill us
yeah I don't know man I don't think
there's a way to win yeah
we could always just reload again too if
you guys really don't know I guess yeah
and since our since our plan to steal
the idol didn't work with the with the
smoke cloud
yeah
yeah I don't think you can steal the
Idol without getting everybody upset
sadly
um
attack our creatures eyes and blinded
oh
we're there oh you can see this is
yeah
well we can't
we can't kill the bear
what's happening good job shadow
your weapon Kylie's still naked
[Music]
and webbed you all right
I like
photos
nice
yeah
I fly somewhere safer
no probably not
dang
oh that's I'll throw them apparently
they kill all the two flings when you do
this so even if you beat it all the time
silenced
[Music]
I have a good idea if you guys want to
kill a bunch of stuff we can go to the
goblin temples
I was trying to win a battle we are
going to lose against the Bears can I
drop my ax
[Music]
I I remember where the goblin Camp is by
the way
make our way over there yeah I remember
nice I follow I have only ever gotten as
far as the goblin Camp has that I do not
know what happened okay
so let's we gotta exit the town first
I'm following you yeah just follow
follow Mario Pez lead that's it oh let's
look at Cali's butt while she's walking
up the stairs let's go let's go oh yeah
there's a shopkeeper by the way if you
guys want to buy items like healing
potions Etc wait which one which one
uh up here uh past these cows there's uh
a merchant does he have ice arrows
selling stuff here
but maybe I think I saw ice arrows
really I'm pretty sure that I saw some
in the inventory but you might want to
yeah grab grab some stuff really quick
well met is there anything you need what
are you selling
just some bits and bulbs
as well
can I sell all these muffins uh guys I'm
sorry
I'm stuck oh wait no I got out I got out
it's fine it's fine oh
I thought one at a time yeah one at a
time that's too realistic I know it'll
even go this way I'm just gonna open up
this part of my map oh I can actually we
can fast travel there and go there oh
yeah when you guys are done shopping
yeah I'm just selling stuff
okay
oh money
how do I get him to give me money oh
give me money
give me all your money
oh um
I think
okay whatever you can do that guide your
path please
definitely has a frost Arrow I think
can I oh that's a good idea well met and
thank you is there anything you need
yeah that's fast if you do
about this
doesn't will normally appear around here
you guys
um doesn't he like show up and he's like
hey and he's like teaching the yeah
he's not here
he's good
he's not very bad
surely we'll run into him again we
didn't kill
himself we don't have will can we not
find Carlock
wait I don't know who that is but I'm
down to find whoever no no no you don't
need vote for Carla a lot okay I don't
think this is about your preciousness
the hot demon yeah
[Music]
um do I need any I wonder if he's
wearing I wonder if he's where like he
killed me
um
Vengeance first
should we go look I'm gonna go check
around where I died
I really hope he doesn't agree on me if
he's there though
we just need to have a chat with them
yeah
oh if you go to Carlock first he will
find you apparently oh okay so we could
we could go find her
yeah what's bartering I kind of
we need to look up oh he is there oh I'm
scared oh I was scared
maybe just go talk to him did we say the
game maybe yeah
first hello
hello are you okay
hold on I wait I have no money oh I
can't even click on him
yeah I can't interact either I have no
single money
how is that possible
I got gold but didn't I did I I feel
like I picked up money before
you remember opening like a chest and
having yeah several I mean that's all it
was gold
oh well I'll sell things
gotta loot more
yeah
I dug that up that was my pleasure thank
you
I'm never helping you again
[Music]
yeah I'll give you I'll give you some of
the loot you wanna
um
money is shared in the party yeah
it's on zero okay does people use up all
the groups money oh I didn't I didn't
buy anything it's weird because yeah I
didn't buy anything
well it was definitely on zero and now I
I made some money but
I was gonna try attacking inventory I
don't want him to aggro we shared
apparently
we can but we don't she has to send it
to you this is party gold is 329. ah
nice so I guess technically we can use
each other's money yeah I mean if you
guys have some gold I'll give you some
gold for stuff
okay territory right now I could just
take y'all stuff right now don't do that
I won't but I could is the thing
next time I see oil I know you can't
make it go boom
cans I will I will punch you so far over
the mountain if you steal something else
baby
doesn't do anything huh
okay
um
okay and anything else that's worth
buying here
should be common drops luckily
okay
okay yeah I have the amulet
you're gonna talk to the Dead Guy
I'll talk to him later
please I want to look and see if I can
buy anything
ah yes uh green Greenville rainbow
sorry I'm blind uh uh
I'm blind I'm so blind
[Music]
um
this Wing okay okay that's that's okay
cool insufficient cold
uh oh that's expensive I'm never
reaching that money uh
yeah
yeah maybe another time
oh
please donate gold calm down
I wonder if she'll notice
maybe you never time what did you do
what are you in here I did something
good go check yeah yeah what'd you do
look at the inventory
and I don't know what's different
look at Cali's inventory I see gold I
don't know how to even look at other
people's inventories press tab I love
this it's just mine okay
do you not do you not see my message
it's very message can you scrap of paper
oh it's not reflected
um
man too bad I spelled something for you
in your inventory but I guess it doesn't
that's fine oh I see it says hi yeah
yeah it says hi futures
you just care about your stupid
apprenticeship why are you fighting I'm
gonna take your word for it
Kiara Kiara saw it
yeah yeah that's very strange I mean
she just placed the items in an order
that makes it look like a letter I see
um
no I'm using a controller oh it's
different with a controller oh yeah I'm
I'm ready let's
Goblin camp we got some goblins to kill
let's gobble those goblins up gobble
gobble
have you guys ever seen a turkey in
person no but you don't want to why not
they're [\h__\h] huge they're terrifying
that thing called body ubu
I'm sure all of you have seen a turkey
for facts
they make me feel so powerful when I eat
one you know I have some big ones that
used to live near the old my old place
their flag five yum I remember seeing
some cross the road once and I was like
holy [\h__\h] strange
oh my God
before we go to the goblin place I want
to
make a little detour I remember sorry
okay all right there's it's combat
though
okay we're ready
ah I already saved okay let's go we
gotta go this way oh we gotta see the
dog too hold on yeah the dog the dog's
over here
where are we here before no really but I
see dead bodies yeah we were just
acknowledging them we're like
a puppy
[Music]
wait wait don't don't lose the body
accidentally okay
[Music]
I'm not an enemy it would just you just
hear the sound
so one candy
oh I can make it I can make it yeah
and believe in people power
is death in your scent yeah
my friend is injured I think your friend
is [\h__\h] dead
to him
he's with this God now I'm sorry it's
not over yet he'll wake up he will we
have a Revival scroll home revive a fly
I have a skeleton yeah come with us come
with us no
[Music]
um here
follow my sense if it comes to that
leaves the side office okay now now he
may show up
okay another detour we are going over
here there's combat it's the combat
detour all right let's do it
I'm ready to fight
always ready to fight
me too me too I want more fights I spent
too much time in that City yeah yeah
yeah it's okay soon and then we got this
yeah okay definitely take all those
goggles here we go
I need you to kill the mom and not kill
the child okay why do you remember this
yeah yeah yeah kill them kill them
not the kid okay you can get Hella cash
okay yeah don't kill the baby I don't
want to kill a mother well she wants to
eat them oh okay yeah that's that's okay
she's really mean
yeah maybe you guys should wait for me
yeah just a minute yeah
so we're not like spread out super far I
love the little animals
yeah okay let's go okay
you can talk to her actually because you
can talk to animals
uh okay
have a little chat how do I talk without
uh killing Oh no just walk up to her
yeah oh okay okay oh it's never said
though oh all the voices are you talking
to her oh I didn't mean to
oh do you have animal handling no
well time to get eaten
it'll be fine we were planning on that
anyway no please no lunch time yum yum
yum yum yum yum
yummy
so pretty
[Music]
as well
we have to kill him
I know
oh nice striking while the iron is hot I
guess
you just don't look at her go it's kind
of Awesome
oh oh
um
can't go so far so go as far as you can
fly to Target position
um
I wonder if I could throw your bird
you probably could you have enough
strength for it
[Music]
don't worry
um
the baby is coming to defend his mommy
um there's a bonus Ash and then I can
also do a rage attack
oh
[Music]
I feel like you're scarier with
underwear on
all right
she's cute
little bleed
okay
oh
God it's really angry what did you do oh
The Voice came out of it
who killed the baby
still alive the baby's still alive I
don't know but the baby's still okay
okay
um
crab crab no crap attack crab cannot
attack crap oh maiming pinch I'm like
one step too far away
um
I believe crap Maybe
maybe act as a faith
damn it that would have been so epic if
the crab would have gotten the kill
and now I'm
yeah
yeah someone maybe talk to animals
preferably what you're wearing the baby
where is it it's over yeah let's save
let's save real quick before one of us
accidentally kills it
but don't um don't accidentally use
by the way okay hungry oh a single
strike will end don't do it
let it live
okay I'm gonna come back and kill us
someday it's gonna eat the mommy is it
speechless yes
[Music]
we will find
and again later yeah they'll come back
to kill us because we killed his mom no
no we we we'll take him as a pet yeah so
there's a shrine back here isn't there
yeah yeah look we can't do anything with
it because it's sealed by Magic
I want to go look
I remember correctly
I see a chest yeah it's sealed by Magics
if you try and open it
oh
don't touch yourself big man oh yeah now
also Bieber we might wanna you know
[Music]
yes please oh yeah sure no problem
so it when you try to open the chest is
that when you got damaged yeah
it doesn't happen to everybody who
touches their chest volume yeah I think
so
I want to touch it I know that might be
worth it they're dedicated to Saloon
imploring all to accept the moon Mains
blessing and share in her Bounty Justin
I like her no religion failed oh no wait
I think I have religion
there's a prayer behind the statue
how do you jump again in front of the
chat it's one of the actions on the
um the second one in the first row okay
all right here I took I picked it up I'm
gonna send the prayer to one of you guys
to use it because I could not do it so
who has good religion I have plus one I
think just unlocked
it works just smells prayer
eh did you get stuff
oh oh
what
necklace Bloodstone Idol pendant
okay now we can go kill some goblins
let's go oh free work all right Goblin
goblin killing times
that one suck yeah
you don't have to pass the check if you
just know what to do wow
pretty nice it's true
an old prayer I'm dummy
well I mean I'm not smart I'd be dumb
why not stupid it's okay
do we have who's the smartest one in the
in the party again me ah in terms of uh
same steps
oh I see
um okay
bedroom Goblin okay I think I think
Memorial upstairs Goblin you're up here
yeah they got across oh wait yeah that's
right across the bridge and then we go
that way yeah I will wait
yeah I'm trying to catch up
um any charismatic people want to leave
oh yeah I'm charismatic hello we're both
we're both charismatic
yeah you guys can you know take the
charge wait there's no one here
why did they get mad
I don't know oh they didn't even give
you a chance to they no one
oh they're up there
[Music]
I am here now this is I did not have to
fight this so I'm not sure how this will
work we'll figure it out get in here and
help us goblins yeah goblins goblins
okay well we want to fight those little
Goblin men oh let's go
oh not where are the memories they're
they're on them they're up on the roof
yeah
or the house right next to us yum what
what
um
Alex really don't see them
okay you see where I am
go to the left
and in the middle of that roof ah and
then there's also one at the end if you
go down just downward
with the arrow okay well we won't come
back here we are
I guess yeah
I don't know okay
I guess I can't do anything
ah let's go bird let's go
near the front door
how's the flying work cool oh hi
can I not
what what does that mean not enough
resources oh it means you already use an
action or something yeah or your bonus
yeah movement Etc
oh there's another guy
oh
I got some from oh can I get some 65
percent
yes I can yes
let's go this might have been a mistake
because now I'm up here yeah
otherwise you can handle those guys
we'll handle these other ones
yeah it's a little
thank you
[Music]
oh you missed
Miss
oh I missed that would have been so
awesome
[Music]
yeah
good songs
I'll be fine I know what to do with them
there's one on the other side
um and there's one inside the house
oh that was good let's go
you really couldn't take me talking to
him like that yeah I love your insults
insult me please I could never you're
perfect it's Waypoint discovered
um heal myself at some point don't die
[Music]
we can get them let me get a bit closer
um
foreign
[Music]
no why not
go here
oh you burp getting closer
how many archers okay
if this this person has a ball right so
that means they won't attack me if I
move behind them right I'm not strong
okay nice
looking at the building below
here we go don't miss
do it yeah
beautiful beautiful so good and I feel
myself
I think two goblins left
now that we got the Waypoint we can
return to Camp as well yeah for us there
okay
wow your words are very strong my words
are hurtful
it's my job demon avoids not soup or
song
oh no I said if you go too far into the
village you'll aggro more people
oh okay I'll stop moving in I thought I
needed to get by the Waypoint to unlock
it
[Music]
yes
okay there's one in the house and then
one by Marissa oh there's one in there
there's one by me yeah there's one right
in front of you
um I mean oh
oh yeah inside the home
almost forgot about that
what are you doing first
that's all right I can survive this
you got it
oh there we go
are you okay I'm okay I have one HP how
do I yeah how do I get this person
and I like shoot it from the
can I shoot that guys he only had free
HP that's why I didn't do it I'll do it
on the next Target
Cali only one HP what the [\h__\h] yeah
that's okay I'm good don't worry about
it not okay I'm good
I'm waiting in the house because I've
been taking damage I guess it's the
address
oh well I think we can just shoot him
from the window yeah
oh
I don't know where the other oh there's
one in there
um take the killing shot on Cali what
excuse me so you can get exp from her
um
we're literally about to go rest at the
camp
I'll just chill here
you guys might need for help
oh I'm not close enough guys
mom
um
take the shot get him
oh
[Music]
nice all right
and I wanted to check out these bodies
whoa fire everyone here
got the fire arrow
okay yeah
oh
go shadow
good try oh
[Music]
this is nice okay we go to the camp Camp
yeah all right we've got this uh already
all right so let's let's go back to I'll
take us back to the camp go to Camp yes
mm-hmm
oh I think you guys gotta return on your
own oh how
uh so it's in the scroll wheel same one
where you like go to your inventory and
stuff
okay press that and then it's the
bonfire icon click that
the LSS what the LSS
I'm Gonna Save really quick
victory
chilling with one HP at the camp all
good you understand again
living my best life okay end the day
okay
well let's all take a little nap go to
bed
someone on the camp was just a speedy
they always keep wanting to talk to us
why are there too well no well what are
there too okay
why is he why is there two of them
like Taylor Swift
what
let him cook I don't know what's going
on but I'm into it
what's he gonna do with himself
Megan already
oh Shadow heart wants to talk to me
really
oh no we gotta talk to Shadow heart
are you hurt him I'll protect you always
Shadow heart
oh Gail what are you doing here this has
nothing to do with you brother I let him
live I don't know oopsies I failed oh
yeah thank you very much
you made her mad
how deep is this inventory you can talk
to her separately can't you hello
did I aggro her forever
no she's she's fine we should get to
know each other a little more must we
yeah no harm in a little mini don't you
think
um
zero res easy is often less interesting
besides with plenty of reason to rely on
each other already
let's go maybe I'd like to get to know
you better what if I do sweet of you but
don't worry watch this
what happens
wait oh wow whatever she's wearing is
very sexy okay
I'll leave her beef and I won't press it
doesn't even work she approved of me
okay hold on oh nice you're getting it
I'm doing it I'm doing it
um
okay there's no story
none that you're entitled to hear
anything I'll talk to her again later
when we have more time to bond I don't
think she wants to talk to me she
doesn't want to be interrogated right
now so I'll leave her alone gotta give
her space yeah I gotta give her space
all right ready for sleepy mine
yes
sleep
Supply pack we're gonna need to steal
more of these from the Goblins yeah
saving her risk for the real prize you
caught me
oh
it's a good doggy
[Music]
okay
so cute that's so sad
hope you're keeping well right oh he can
talk to me
um sorry but what happened to your
master master
I stayed with him until
oh
but I'm glad to have met you
baby
pets you can pet the dog 10 out of 10
games you can pet the dog
I mean you're small enough you could use
the the dogs
everyone approves when you pet dog pet
him again
more pets
hey stop that
I wonder
maybe not can I keep petting him
we get tired oh thank you I can only
leave now
well he liked it yeah
okay
shall we save now that we're all full
health yeah good idea good game
um
Goblin
whoa whoa whoa there all right another
another crab
how about this
oh that's so cool that's a big one I
didn't expect it to be so big I did I
wasn't expecting a spider
that's a big nobody it's just another
crab look they look so similar
same amount of
legs and hand right yep
you know you've got a good point
an armored spider
aren't shrimps the Cockroaches of the
sea or is that crabs
it's definitely not crabs the excuse me
yeah no I didn't I didn't mean it I
didn't mean it I didn't mean it I'm
sorry crab
[Music]
um
[Applause]
Marissa at it again
you know yeah play music for me do all
my duty doing what I meant to do I can
bust a move too oh yeah
everybody
likes me
amazing
what
wow these shoes
why
I thought Advent was like really
friendly with each other it's always
going on
there's a lot of blood now
guess we gotta sleep one more time
because y'all are injured uh no we can
just weekend just we can just short rest
time to load the save
here
[Music]
try me again
the way we shoot you with my lightning
do it
you you hit me first I literally did one
damage
after we just healed
down down down by the river
[Laughter]
all right what do we want to do you guys
okay fine fine
but like actual enemies wait did we end
the date we did okay yeah how do we
leave the camp
um so I'll leave uh well you go first uh
it's the scroll wheel where I don't know
how it is for PC um
click the bonfire again ah
okay
um all right we're in the blighted
village which okay this is close to
where we're supposed to go you may
follow me and well I know where the camp
is from here oh wait uh
I pressed the I pressed the uh the the
bed right no no no no no
bonfire so go to the scroll wheel
um where like you have like level up
inventory Etc bonfire again wait I can't
click anything right now it's waiting
for it to play no yeah cancel can
somebody cancel this oh you just have to
wait till the time
oh okay yeah
um Dad bonfire okay different bonfire
yeah yeah
the only thing on this scroll wheel I'm
using a controller sorry
leave Camp okay I'm so hungry
okay where are we going don't mess with
these guys I recommend not really
messing with the blighted village right
now
you gotta cross this bridge over here
it might be
locked that across this bridge I believe
okay well let's cross it okay Crossing
is there a reason you're letting me go
first
waiting for Wawa there's a
there's a there's like ogres in in here
yeah yeah
I don't think we can take them
they're really strong and there's three
of them but don't worry they have no two
no okay yeah maybe maybe just do it yeah
let's just keep going keep going
you sure we can't kill them
for now maybe later okay come back later
yeah when we're really strong we can
beat them up
[Music]
hi honey
now if you have high enough ribs you can
persuade them that you're cool okay okay
hello I have oh good you saved it okay
hello
hi
this was boxing casually people go alone
first
yeah there's like poop on the ground
yeah
what did you just call me
close Okay we don't need to hire those
big ogres yeah in response
I feel like that was a mistake do I have
studying
um
I have perception
oh I have deception okay let me ask
guidance yeah let's give it a go yeah
okay I made it I made it
nice yeah yeah nice nice okay
yeah well
I guess women with All Souls stays down
hey what's that supposed to mean
that's kind of rude
no you're one of us
[Music]
do it
how did we get here
absolutely not do it do it you follow
him now or you follow him dead the sake
of the team
go on here
[Music]
all right
um let me see is there one close by I'll
just Dash into battle
let me do the rhythmic next time what so
you were gonna put poop on your face yes
why would you need to when you could
just kill them
we need to make good relations so we
don't have to fight so much why not it's
fun yeah
oh oh
[Music]
um
fly as far as you can
and speed down speed.com
okay
there is a large dark monster up there
that is very frightening
yeah I'm nervous what it is my dark
monster what's that there's like an icon
for it I don't know what it is it's like
a pitch black spooky thing it took some
damage already claws
oh
oh there's one monster behind us indeed
you're spooking me it's a different one
well sharp-eyed nerd what a name
probably five
the icon didn't load at all no it's
definitely there I see it it's very dark
hmm
ah pitch black portraits goodbye
goodbye
classic
come over here
I love that dagger
thank you for taking that sandwich for
us
why are you so mad
fan damage good good good
oh yeah oh
that really sucks
no no we're not we are not thriving
let's add some better accuracy
oh can I talk to the work
even in the middle of a battle
oh oh no
we have to kill the person going for the
alarm
[Music]
knock them dead
what's the matter so the one that is
behind us
oh bird is gone too
okay Shadow is dead there is a no bird
for you anymore
uh not the not my ability
what would you like to have next
you can bring you almost any animal food
not kitty cat because I just don't want
to see how that ends ever again
[Music]
oh
yeah
ah are you gonna kill him oh yeah okay
okay please
I was about to say Jesus
get him
I'm gonna get him
that's my girl oh
nice nice
I can't reach it's the one over there
okay wow
be careful gotta be careful of the
daggers it's fine
uh the water is electrocuted
my dad uses non-lethal I don't know it's
not why is it not toggled why does it
say non-lethal damage I don't understand
you can't I can't take it off yeah we're
screwed I have that too
I think no I guess if it's grayed out I
don't have it on it changes
straight out for you
there we go I don't know what difference
please
[Music]
hmm
medium
[Music]
yay and then I think I can actually I
can bring you back
nice
well because I got an extra turn I'll
try and be like kind of bait I guess
this guy hopefully targets me instead of
you
got anything nice on you no
oh
and taking a shot
yeah nice okay we just got that one left
yeah right always going
oh I got you okay you try to run don't
let him leave arms
oh
looking back this whole time I can't
believe I didn't see that was toggling
electrocuted
nice oh team
is that it I think that's it
yeah she seems like this
poop on her face we could have just
killed them let's kill everyone yeah do
you need need a short rest I'm worried
about Nurse maybe short rest yeah yeah
it's that short rest real quick and I'll
save the game
[Music]
yeah my loot oh
he's popping off and he just bring my
babies back I've never I didn't go up
there what are these guys
what's happening um
I know the goblin the temple is over
there
is over there but then there's these
guys
[Music]
distracted you're probably gonna want to
fight yeah
they're small
simple time
I'll quickly change some graphics
settings oh yeah what happened oh sorry
oh uh brain worms
[Music]
yeah
the Temple of the Loon
you've always said whatever it is it's
irresistible
I thought himself
I can barely hear her
louder three figures
an armored male elf ah power and command
me younger man with
a piece
with even pale yeah
[Music]
huh
sick
oh
[Music]
you
know oh it's the tesseract
let's go take me to the underworld
make needles in my face let's go
[Laughter]
[Music]
I raised volume I know DND die
voice those visions uh put the artifact
away
get away
put it in the old pocket okay uh this is
another situation where I really think
you guys should go I'll stay with me in
case it turns into a battle and I need
to tank but I think in terms of Charisma
is
[Music]
it but it's not supposed to be
entertainment oh he's performing for
them
chicken chasing
the owl bear
let's go let's go guys outshine that big
silly
see they all came over when it was me
I'm gonna crank a brand new move it's so
cute backup dancer
thank you
boss did a move uh only the greatest
game since egg sprouted legs okay shall
we move on yeah yes I mean you've really
captivated them I don't know man I know
I'm distracting them wait I found the
album
oh yeah I'll bear cubs
wait I want I want the owl Bears
used to be goblins a taste
how do I get it
roasted dwarf legs
[Music]
where are we going I'm exploring before
we go into the temple
wait can you can you talk to the
people
give him a chat um
it's chicken chasing
it's so cute
oh chicken chasing sounds fun Count Me
In
respects mates are they gonna burn him
is this like a steak business we can't
be about oh I hope not stop whitening uh
we gotta get rid of Volo first so I
found a waypoint yeah
okay we gotta get rid of Volo then okay
do you mean kill
no
I think
quit fraculous dialogue is moving pretty
quick
not a whole doll let's go
feel funny
[Music]
oh come on I'm just telling you how it
is
a tick
friend of yours
I'm busy here you lying uh-oh
he's so British
yeah he's a shitty Barn continue our
palette
why is he here
[Music]
I am Patrol
I don't think he's doing very good
he makes the words like I do
all right
sorry guys I tapped out he's crazy
your child H oh there we go
gauge them up
nice chicken chasing time I'm not brave
enough to take on our new tomatoes in
the chat
no distraction time Well Chad I don't
know if it's normal but it's taking up
38 49 of my CPU and
7500 of my Ram I don't know and you got
coin to back yet oh
now
okay I'll produce a fat
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
weren't always this bad but now it's fun
wait where's
he's running oh
what's he doing
oh wait how did that Albert Cub even
come here
was it already here before
yeah yeah
[Music]
oh I can't use both okay I'll use
guidance
okay yeah
yeah
get the Goblins get them
to be very angry oh and we're not
involved in that battle right yeah
I think I think there's a straight arrow
that hit you might want to get out of
the way
oh
[Music]
um
can we reload
I don't I can't save
everything here you you know we boo
but there's gonna be a better way to
save him
oh nothing
you can later apparently but yeah then
we have to bring him back to life
yeah I can't revive this this little guy
I don't know how long ago we we had to
save yeah I don't either
weren't we supposed to get something
super cool for leaving the mama laugh
we're leaving the baby lion
hell of money I guess right
um
well shall we go
yeah are you sure we're in Savory silly
hold on a second I'll give it I'll check
it out
all righty let's see uh
last save load game
um
I have to do the Volo thing again
through it
the same scum I mean yak
some people are saying you could group
them with a performance and then use all
the AOE attacks on them
oh nice that's huge yeah that's a good
idea that's actually really awesome
so should we should we kill a ton of
goblins or yeah because they're not
fighting us and I really don't want them
to fight us you know you really don't
need to I don't think we should enter
the temple yeah
I'm sure he'll find a way out himself
Albert is worth keeping around chat says
by the way okay
um I guess we can kind of skip this part
because we've already seen them
put it away all right cool nice
let's Jump Right In now bear I'm gonna
Boo this guy off okay someone if you can
stealth it you can slip poison into
their boost
tube wait do we have the wyvern poison
remember
[Music]
wait where's their beard where's their
beer tub
I love it
game save
let's see okay yes I'm right here
the crab looks so cute so what do you do
uh just toys Poison you gotta put put it
into the boost up how do you put it in
I I'm not sure but there's a ton of
goblins around so um maybe what if you
did a performance
do a performance
look at you
oh my God
okay
mine hey wait another one's coming over
so
[Music]
no okay wait there's a guy right behind
you guys yeah
I didn't do anything he's got a sharp
eye
yeah it's a good thing
yeah yeah it's a good thing
yeah it's an extra delicious it makes it
makes it tastier
I should afford yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay he's happy with it now uh
okay are you distracting people
I'm crying if you're not they're not
paying attention
let me let me try a different song
power cool through it'll give sounds
okay
why is he watching you like that
why don't you walk away from it for a
minute and see if they don't maybe you
know walk away and then you can try yeah
nice idea
still watching me
hey is he he's like the potion guy
looking at it
oh you ran away
nice
[Music]
it's hard to be The Bard
okay yeah yeah yeah okay people walk all
the way over here sneak sneak up don't
even sneak come over here
[Music]
they're taking some booze
how do I
um there's no one around here anymore
yeah there is there's a guy the guy oh
yeah he's over there yeah oh now he's
gone but now my crab made it up but not
the wolf okay what if I oh wait this
guy's leaving this guy's leaving this
guy's ah
hiding success okay did you get it no
there's too much you're really thirsty
cool
I think you can
does this mean that they're not saying
anything that's in here okay it's poison
it's poison now yeah okay okay
huh what's happening let's all drink
boys I'll die
ah no thanks oh thanks what's happening
um
oh are you guys seeing what happened how
come I didn't get a cutscene
um
okay well may I met each and every one
of you before the sunset that's crazy
tell me tell me what happens okay
oh boy
it's rank up I'm like uh
through the bartending drink
oh cool I'm stuck let's see how this
goes oh why do I have to enter the cut
scene yeah it's okay
make them drink it I trust you
yeah
surely it was a success yeah no way go
do your trick
I want to see it too
oh my God no I see him I see him
oh
or something
oh boy
[Applause]
[Music]
I should have your arms ripped off
please please work because I need to
roll a 20.
good luck
let's [\h__\h] coach
it's not really that I got a second time
it's fine I'll take critical success
all right
yeah nothing yeah I still think we
should kill him so many of them are
still alive yeah
oh wait is there okay now there's only
there's no matter I should save the game
yeah same hungry I'm safe because that
was gangster
okay save him
he runs away only time will tell yes
[Music]
the game
okay yeah
yeah I'm real quick oh my God okay get
out of this leggy area
it's a lot smoother inside the temple
okay
hello
get away
he knows the big idea
what's your business guys a strange
a great question
to figure out a story
their story straight
um
I've got an audience with the one in
charge you have good deception I think
yeah a master deception
right well
you ain't the first foreign type I
suppose us Rose gonna have to be a bit
more specific though mate
absolute's got a few favorites around me
oh
what is that you were here to see
Priestess god boss Rags Me or the drown
oh we're here to see we're definitely
the drought the dwell yeah
audience is right she's a celebrity one
and no mistake but she knows her
business
she's in telling the war Chiefs what's
wrong oh X-Ray's gonna be a beacon oh
yeah
restart the game okay oh you know
actually I was thinking maybe we maybe
we stopped yeah today okay yeah yeah
okay we've been gone
four and a half hours I've been
screaming for five and a half yeah so
the journey began yeah yeah the journey
began and it's only going to get crazier
well yeah well the goblin Temple next
time we're gonna try to do this we're
going to try this weekend Ryan yeah yeah
at least once a week you really should
drink this we want to beat the camp it
we really want to yeah
yeah
more Baldur's games for inviting us yes
yeah yeah no problem it'll be fun
um I'm hyped to see where our journey
takes us from here on out yeah
that was fun um oh I'm also kind of
playing on my own as well at the same
time with a different character so so
maybe next time you'll see some improved
gameplay I don't know we'll look forward
to it I think you did pretty good today
though yeah I've learned in the
Barbarian ways you know and yeah
he's after my own heart oh you never put
those clubs back on no way confident
lady you know it through sweater stuff
um so yeah everybody take care hope you
guys have a lovely day wherever you are
please thank you guys
you guys are uh doing well and have a
lovely day yeah yeah are you all ending
the stream uh I'm gonna talk for just a
little bit and then end so yeah yeah I'm
gonna I'm Gonna Leave the call here
[Music]
thanks for tuning in yeah bye bye and
peace bye
okay
hello
hello I'm going to sleep
[Laughter]
a whole lot can I
I'm going to sleep
I need I need to eat I am eating but I
hope you guys have fun uh yeah so fun I
love apology skate
um we're again we're getting close to
like the part where I left at because
this is only as far as I got the goblin
Camp from Early Access and um yeah so
all of the rest the rest of this is
going to be new new for me next next
stream next stream will be all new to me
so I'm very excited uh to try the new
stuff and yeah yeah folders folders gate
okay I'm I'm EP
uh what are we doing tomorrow oh yeah oh
I'm going to join narissa later today
um probably after I eat for a while
um we're doing we're doing Terraria so
you'll see me in Terraria later today
um but tomorrow
burden ring yeah
Eldon wing onion ring yeah onion ring
tomorrow and then Thursday on my core
yeah well I I really
obviously I gotta go get some rest you
can wear the supers everyone ah thank
you thank you thank you for the
supervisors take care
I'm sleepy I'm gonna pass out
oh yeah
I haven't I slept I knocked for like
less than an hour before stream so I
would I'm not
okay but yeah thanks for coming so early
thank you thank you thank you for coming
so early I hope you friends had a good
time finally me streaming in your time
zone and then everyone else who is in
the morning or late at night with me
[Music]
thank you for coming to watch even
though it's like super different from my
normal normal skin time okay I'm going
to sleep
I honestly I love you I'll see you uh
later today okay later goodbye good
night
good night morning good morning good
night morning good night okay
[Music]
laughs