[Music]
hmm
do
[Music]
uh
me
[Music]
goddammit cakey
[Laughter]
goddammit
hey hey hey everyone merry christmas
once again
for the five millionth time
hello no i'm not muted anymore i'm like
[Music]
i might only be reading super chats in
this stream but i hope we can have some
talks
in between some tangents some nice
sexy paintings
and um i wanna i wanna talk about some
things i guess
probably ah
great
ah how's everyone doing did everyone
here
everyone who's here now i guess you all
who came to my
karaoke stream you better
would be weird if you didn't why why
wouldn't you
although i guess i i realized something
it might have ha might have been a bad
time for me to do the karaoke stream
because it was like what 11 p.m est a
little bit early for pst
so i was thinking okay
maybe like maybe many of those people
are with their
family right now
maybe they yeah can't spend it with me
right now and maybe that's why
there is not so many people
i realized it at that time i was like
oops i didn't oopsie
oh well well you missed something
special it's gone now it's gone forever
anyone oh my god thank you guys so much
for the
support oh my god there's so much
already
it's gonna be a long super chat reading
stream huh um
i if you have not noticed uh maybe you
guys got some notification but
um i i'm sure there will be clips
yeah but watching it live with my stupid
uh talking and mistakes in between is
much
better than watching it as a clip
uh anyway what was i gonna say oh yeah
did you guys gonna
get the notification i care your accent
is addicting i don't have an accent
how rude uh did you guys get a
notification i made a reservation for
the i made a premier premiere video
premiere
notification and i
did a reservation for the halloween
collab
did you guys see those two
okay okay no notifications wonderful
youtube good job youtube
you are amazing youtube wow
wow wow wow wow anyway yeah i did i
didn't make reservations for those
so yeah just check it out later the
the video premiere is at 10 pm japanese
center time which is in exactly seven
hours from now and uh
the holoyan collab is at
midnight japanese center time which is
in
nine hours from now now the question is
are you guys going to be there or not
you better be there the reservations
stir up okay good
i don't know where i fought normally
maybe the notification
yeah the notification i guess only comes
out when when you start to stream i
guess
oh yeah anyway um
so that's that uh i have to maybe in the
beginning i'll
i wanna mention
[Music]
that i'm thinking of
uh cancelling the fire on livestream for
tomorrow
because up until now i didn't really
have time to prepare whole talk
and whole talk is the day after tomorrow
and if i do fire emblem i probably
barely have time uh
your banner says second fast watch along
what for this stream
what you bad what do you mean
banner oh that all oh thank you
true we're not doing that
super chat
and stuff yeah
that's what we're doing yeah hotel i
have to go
through a million of questions
and i have a bad feeling this time
because i don't think there's gonna be
many good ones in there i i did like a
i sneak peeked a little bit and i have
to be honest they're not looking that
good
but i'll try my best so get some good
ones
[Laughter]
and we'll do our best thank you guys for
the super chat
uh yeah it's like oh shion senpai is
very cute
that that's the question
anyway we're gonna start reading the
super chats from sims 4.
well i mean maybe
maybe maybe that's okay maybe maybe
tomorrow and the day after tomorrow
maybe that whole talk will not be as
deep as usual
i guess that's okay too we can just have
a
fun talk i guess i'll try my best
to i'll get some good questions there
it's really it's really hard to go
through
a thousand questions i think wait please
please don't write any more questions
at this point because this will be it
will be hard to go through them but
let me see how many are there now let me
see
uh
okay 570 questions
on on in english on youtube
on youtube plus the ones on twitter i
don't know how many those are
yeah i have to go for those alone it's
going to be fun going to be fun
[Music]
literally did this to yourself yeah
go through them on stream big brain hole
i'm probably faster alone discord
let's chat about what happened kayla
wait what happened what happened wait
discord what happened wait what
what happened hey what happened what
happened
what what happened
[Music]
guys thank you for the super chat
discord why are you even here on
christmas you you're spending your
christmas with me i'm honored
[Music]
hey wait what happened though what did i
do oh
this one oh
well i don't i
[Music]
i i don't know man it's just a game
i didn't do did it everyone was acting
as if that stream
was so scandalous but it wasn't
it wasn't it was
we just did a wool and that's it
[Laughter]
there's nothing scandalous about that
street i don't know what you guys are
talking about
honestly anyway
for real though you guys are making such
a big deal out of it
okay let's let's start reaching
[Music]
it was only a woohoo it was only a
woohoo
thingy
[Music]
destiny is calling me open
up my eager eye
ugh
[Music]
this is awkward i hear the people
outside my house
this is awkward can you please move on
move on move on go into your house
stop standing outside i don't want you
guys to hear my donkey shoes
anyway i like the name change i like the
name change
[Music]
is
it sounds like the original name would
sound so close
to it merry christmas
thank you thank you for the pinky
cyrux yeah you're truly a woman of
culture
yeah everyone liked that something it's
great isn't it
i i have um created a masterpiece from
now
i'm quite proud of it everyone liked it
i was pretty happy
looking for the top thank you
[Music]
sian
and honestly thank you for it
thank you for coming what do you mean
you literally kill yago and
see this is something i've been
wondering about while i was streaming or
right after nago's account
got like i don't know not bad
but what was that
does anyone know the reason because i
saw one comment and i don't know if that
was a joke
but one comment said he retweeted my
my stream and then and
then his twitter got age restricted or
terminated or privatized
temporarily suspended and i was like
really did he really so
i went to his twitter when he was back
and there was no retweet
so i was like maybe maybe he retweeted
and he then he untweeted it
but i don't think he would retweet that
stream like he usually only retweets
like special things
why why did that happen it's a joke okay
okay i was
i was wondering if that if that was
legit or if that was just a random joke
[Music]
in
don't tell her don't tell me what
what don't tell me what wait what are
you hiding from me
huh i'd like to pick your sisters
oh yeah she sent me another pick
afterwards she she is
apparently on the whole i've read it
looking through things and seeing what
uh you guys think of me
uh could you guys like
praise me a bit more on reddit than and
portray me as a as a pure idol please
because my sister
my actual sister is checking the reddits
[Music]
i don't know if she's watching my stream
still
i know she's not looking at the reddit
these days
it sounds like casper is in my room what
the hell man
[Music]
on derek dear santa i've been so so this
year i stay out of trouble by watching
where we're a very sweet and
tangent prone youtuber who brings out
the best in people oh
since i've been good can i please get
two presents i want a pair of kiara's
shoes
and a pony
denied what one more time
the night
[Music]
thank you for that super chat i was
waiting to use that and that was perfect
thank you thank you
i was waiting to use that
[Laughter]
let's see if i can use my approve at
some point
[Music]
i got these um i got
the other day of my stream i was like i
want a deny
and an approved stamp and then um
a clipper session me asking me
uh made them and showed them in a clip
of like when
when i was doing that a clip of me
saying i want those stamps and they
added those stamps
and then in the description it said dm
me if you want the stamps
and then i dm'd them and now i have
these thingies
i'm waiting for something that i can
approve of though
thanks for those animations i think
i can use them very much in many
situations looking forward to
using them every day i love them
anyway
[Music]
uh
no words with it but thank you thank you
thank you
thank you so much for the
i appreciate it very much i know i don't
know if you're here but
uh next time please write a message with
it
so that i can properly react to you
please also thanks for the membership
uh f-o-d-i i also have a red super chat
but with no
no no text that goes over it as well
i appreciate it still thank you for your
generosity
thank you and merry christmas merry
christmas
thank you thank you for the support
so sweet all of you are so so so
generous
oh yellow you are here i saw you in the
[Music]
chat
are you guys just talking the chat a
little bit
is
[Music]
merry christmas eve from the states
how can it be it was not christmas eve
at that time in the states definitely
not but okay
i can't travel for the holidays this
year so i just wanted to thank you for
all of the holiday streams you are doing
and giving me something to look forward
to
i hope everyone has a safe and healthy
holiday season
yay thank you that's a very sweet
message
thank you i think yeah it's christmas
eve now
something oh yeah i got rid of it there
it is again
we're reading the sims 4 super chats
right now guys
anyway banjo kazooie thank you i hope
you're having a nice christmas eve i
hope you enjoyed the cutout okay if you
were watching it hopefully
i was able to make your uh holidays a
little bit better since you
cannot travel unfortunately but
i am here for you
thank you for your support jack payne
thank you
[Music]
great you don't you didn't even write
the name
anyway four does x says i just want to
thank you for touhou for the total
stream afterwards i bought and
bought it and the hallways and dlc for
my friend for christmas
and well when you're having a blast
before what oh
i'm happy to hear that that game is
quite a lot of fun it must be even more
fun when you played with a friend indeed
because i i was playing it alone against
uh
uh computers um
good choice good purchase quality
purchase thank you so much
thank you for the support enjoy the game
and enjoy your holidays merry christmas
every now the calls thank you castrol
thank
[Music]
merry christmas dancer sadly my wife and
xander
both caught that certain virus
and i'm alone for christmas so i've
never been more glad i fell
wait you don't have it but your wife and
you and your baby have it
your baby has it
so you're away from is your baby okay
[Music]
sander are you in the
are you in the chat the baby
oh the baby's crying that's not the red
baby now that's wrong baby
oh my god isn't that pretty dangerous
for a baby
little kids are in the high risk when
they cut really little kids maybe but
babies
all right is the baby gonna be okay
that won't let me know that the baby is
okay xander is okay no need to worry how
do you know
how do you know
baby
[Music]
baby that's on discord okay
well that sucks well that sucks what a
horrible christmas oh my god
oh i hope you get i hope you're your
baby and your wife get better soon what
the hell
oh my god sucks the [\h__\h] sucks
horrible horrible
[Music]
that's not that's not fair what the hell
i'm really mad now
please please please take care and uh
get well soon please thank you
thank you so much
we're working hard in the salt mines to
season the fries
and the chicken though with your demands
for a console the kfb geology
department may need additional funds to
build the hardware
excuse me but the geology department is
not in charge
of that what the hell i'm not gonna give
you any more extra funding
i mean that has nothing to do with it
but thank you for waking so hard keep
getting those
uh that that's all in the salt mines
we got zero funding anyway exactly
exactly
oh wait wait wait wait oh no i missed my
opportunity
let me read it again
[Music]
no with your demands for a console the
kfp geology department may need
additional funds to build the hardware
good night
[Music]
there we go mark's nostalgia professor
nope
overseas fan thank you soon kitchen
thank you for the pinky
thank you merry christmas boss
so hype for this stream fake chicken
fries save live see i read correctly now
i read it correctly
aren't you proud thank you thank you so
much
merry christmas to you too are you 18
thank you
surprise thank you looking for the top
ten kitchen great file
fail thank you view 18
tyler rvg
guys totally random tangent
but
you guys remember when i tweeted i think
i probably tweeted it in japanese maybe
or partially japanese but do you guys
remember when i tweeted
and i wanna play that this japanese game
momotetsu which is like a monopoly
i guess something like that i wanted to
play it with someone so please senpai's
invite me
you remember that remember remember that
when i was asking on twitter for
someone to invite me to play it with
them because it's a japanese only game
[Music]
i have been invited
it's some interesting memories um i will
not tell you when
or who but you will see it soon
ah yesterday it happened and i was like
oh my god this is really happening oh my
god oh my god
and then i quickly i quickly told my
manager i was like she asked me
she asked me to participate look at
those members oh my god
so exciting so yep it's not it's not
going to be on my channel
it's going to be on someone else's
channel but it's very very exciting oh
my god
very exciting wow
[Music]
the game though because i haven't played
it before and i think it's a bit
difficult to understand
i don't even own the game yet
i'm gonna hopefully have some time to
practice it because it
the collab is happening soon soon tm
[Music]
there there's this one well there's one
certain member in the collab that makes
me a bit nervous
but yeah i'll leave the imagination to
you guys
[Music]
you will know about it soon i think
convinced me to buy a ticket for second
fest and it was great experience
i had to watch both as a vod but it was
great seeing all the amazing talented
whole life hope to see the young girls
up there soon
yes hopefully thank you for watching and
thank you for
enjoying the concert i was not part of
it but still
i'm happy
[Music]
that's just an announcement i want to be
there for real
ed fan m8 thank you soon andre
thank you tickets
[Music]
just saying you really made my first
whole life as extra entertaining oh i'm
so happy to hear that thank you sean
i'm glad i could make it uh extra
entertaining for you
thank you for not muting me i guess
[Music]
uh the dino dlc i wonder if i had that
downloaded
maybe not but yeah now now that i gave
myself the cooking job
and i feel like it would be quite
fitting to get the dino dlc and make it
make an actual cafe restaurant yeah i
agree with that
we have to do it good idea i was
thinking of that too
i would never mute you oh thank you
me i guess there you go
oh
approved
[Laughter]
ah
it's hard to it's hard to find
the timing for that
steven thank you 18 steve
stefan
you should be able to change the goal
and stuff oh
oh i think i mean you can still change
it afterwards but
it doesn't matter that much to me
[Music]
you look like hayley williams from
paramore
ah i think that's this person meant my
my chiara in the game and i think i
i'm very flattered by hearing that we
need the papers please
stream now approved
i i like that idea because i wanted to
stream that at some point
[Music]
so i i approve not now but soon
sometimes sometimes
oh thank you so much
he is wishing you a merry christmas and
a happy start of 2021 dental
thank you for the heartwarming and
amusing streams and for helping us
expand our language skills oh
you're welcome thank you pinkerton
thank you my christmas was normal
my new years probably will be
a bit more a bit more i don't know
maybe a bit more fun uh the thing is
though
in my country where i'm originally from
and i think in many other countries um
new year's eve is celebrated by
yeah letting fireworks go admit that
right
uh and you know in japan people love
fireworks and they have like lots of
summer festivals where they do fireworks
and all that
but in this country where they love
fireworks so much
they don't do it for new year's eve
chris uh midnight they don't do it they
don't do it at all
they like to keep it quiet on on new
year's eve
so for me it's like
um
kind of too quiet
there's no fireworks in japan even
though they love
fireworks so much and in every other
country that i know of you do it
you do fireworks at chris at new year's
eve
midnight yeah huh
very interesting but they have a
different um
tradition uh on the first of january or
any other
close enough day somewhere in january
everyone you know how
in japan there's uh shrines from the
shinto religion or
uh temples and whatever um they
um there's something called hatsumode
it's the first time they go to a shrine
or a temple
so on the 1st of january the 2nd of
january and so on
the big shrines shrines in tokyo are so
crowded you can barely move like
if you get off of the train at the train
station
on the 1st and 2nd and 3rd of january
you will
barely be able to move and it takes you
from the train station
to the shrine it takes you maybe like
one hour to get there even though
normally it would be
maybe 10 minutes to walk there but
because of the
crowds and it's barely moving it takes
like an
hour
but maybe yeah maybe this time because
um of
obvious reasons maybe maybe they don't
all go
on first of january 2nd of january but
anyway
it doesn't have to be like in the first
and second it's more like
any any time of the year when it's your
first visit to a shrine or a temple
that is your hatsumode
so that's that's a new year's tradition
for
uh japanese
[Music]
foreign
but we have mikko senpai let's just go
to mikko senpai
let's just go to mikko senpai's house
and do our hatsumoda
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
uh i just told the japanese bros a
secret knowledge about me
i actually uh worked
part-time as a shrine maiden for a
shinto shrine before
so i had like you know a miko classic
not costume it was not a costume it was
actually my word my work clothing was my
uniform
at least kiana that's right
[Music]
don't you need to be pure for that
how dare you say that to me
also that was a long time ago i was i
was
i was pretty safe so victim okay i was
pretty say so
[Music]
who's on
foreign
anyway that was fun that was a really
amazing experience
[Music]
it was an amazing experience i would do
it again but
i'm uh after you know phoenix lives a
million years and now i'm a bit too old
to do that
so normally they take like teenagers
for shrine maidens
they usually like do that part-time
after they
are done with like come home from school
they go to
the shrine and then do like part-time
work there
usually it's like so usually like that
yeah
oh sorry i can't speak i don't know
what's wrong
so yeah anyway uh how did we get to that
ah because of happystarter2021 okay
fingertint thank you for leading me to
this wonderful
long as hell tangent
thank you michael thank you
[Music]
b
merry christmas attention just have to
say your sim looks like someone who got
forced out of bed after
spending the whole night watching
netflix shut up
shut up my hair is fluffy
great job on capturing yourself
perfectly attention oh shut up
i mean
although i do want to commission someone
to i wonder i wonder how much they
charge
like i want to commission someone to
make my hairstyle where's the graduation
i don't know who to ask anyway am i
singing
wow thank you so much i'm glad you have
seemed to enjoy the sims
stream let's do it again sometimes and
merry christmas to you too
happy holidays thank you for your
support as always
[Music]
is from australia yeah merry christmas
is back to my home country
[Music]
18 thank you
merry christmas thanks for a bunch for
attention for the smiles you bring to us
i think real kelly sings better than
sims kelly
best wishes to vote for you and everyone
watching thank you
yeah yeah real kelly does sing better
than sam scully
for now we will see we will we will
train sam scalia
to become the best singer in the world
merry christmas
[Music]
oh but i wonder if you can can you be a
rapper in sims
i want her to be a rapper and not a
singer
[Music]
tim scally voices
uh her voice
why are you guys saying it's accurate
anyway
[Music]
thank you
all right finish night shift gonna
listen until i fall asleep looking
forward to the archive also this
super chat is to excuse the fact that i
can't attend to karaoke due to the night
shift
[Music]
writing in japanese please burn these
because i was burning money in the sims
4.
oh my god i didn't even notice that one
during the stream i think
did i
[Music]
wow i'm
impressed i'm impressed
[Music]
thank you thank you for the support
thank you for being so generous but i
will not burn it
don't worry i will not burn this one i
know you told me to burn it but i will
not burn this money
i mean i'm burning in another way by
using it for
food and for my rent and for new games
and stuff and
uh streaming equipment so thank you
merry christmas
claymore 27 thank you high fructose corn
syrup
thank you for the red super chat with no
text though thank you
[Music]
merry christmas to you and thank you for
your support
hope you're having a lovely time and
happy holidays
thank you ambod thank you so much
ass casper is loud
merry christmas
[Music]
release number
i want to wish you a merry christmas i
wanna wish
you a merry christmas i wanna wish you a
merry christmas from the bottom
of my heart
[Music]
that song when i was in in junior
high school in music class
we would sing that song around christmas
time
in music class we would sing and i i
loved it so much i enjoyed singing
feliciary that so much
every time the music teacher would be
like oh what should we sing today
i was like i want to sing felix now we
got because i like the part right
because
even though that's not like you're not
supposed to sing that but i always sing
it i always go like
[Music]
that i always do that
i had so much fun with that
same really really
oh good night oh yo
if you have to sleep good night that's a
sleeping sleeping so early
getting a bit more confidence it's gonna
be long
hello hello hello hello you hear me
i moved the microphone you guys still
hear me
[Music]
again
no no you guys spend so much money
uh for getting my attention or
thanking me maybe but if you don't write
a message there
and i'm like
[Music]
that's so much money like at least oh my
no no no no no no
no no no no
no no no no no
[Music]
no no no no no no for real
no
i never know what to say when you guys
sent me those super chats i'm like
duncan and i'm trying really hard to
make up stuff to talk about and be like
oh thank you for your generosity
i hope you have a happy happy holidays
i'm like really trying hard you know
i'm really trying hard you're making it
really hard for me if you write nothing
and i can react
too no and but no
no no no
no no no no no
[Music]
no no what am i supposed to say to all
those
i oh sorry no no
oh oh no
no no
write something like i've always loved
you so much
thank you for being the lights in my
life
thank you for bringing me hope
you're the reason why i wake up every
day
oh my god you guys oh my god no
stop it
[Music]
see even that lorem ipsum dollar seat
amidst it
even that is better than nothing
[Music]
okay are we done now are you guys done
now
oh no no no no
[Music]
thanks yes see that okay that's just one
sentence but okay
you guys get so many um emojis you get
so many
improvements no no
it's not that easy to be approved wow
that's no
you get so many so many letters
to write wealth and that's what you do
with that
oh okay stop it now i don't want
i don't wanna no stop no
oh you all just wanted to night stamp
now
we can do this instead of a slap
this is the because we can't slap
anymore because of the noise gate not
picking up my slaps
we can do that the night now
[Music]
no no
why you guys you guys know you guys
gonna you guys gotta use your money more
wisely
for real though
you one day later you'll look back and
you'll be like [\h__\h] why did i send that
super chat i didn't even use it well
no no no no no what have i done see
that's what i'm talking about oh i guess
uh
yellow is just uh regretting that
yellow start of it and not regretting
sending those super chats but
still
[Music]
stop it okay i gotta continue reading
guys so stop stop stop
[Music]
i i am a wise decision but you you have
to you know
write something something long and
meaningful
i'm happy we're saying oh my what
what is going on
[Music]
i i will now ignore you until
it is your turn everyone i will not
react to
no
i will i will now continue reading my
super chats eventually i will reach you
guys
you you
[Music]
and then i'll bunk the [\h__\h] out of you
okay
you lord where was i
wait where was i somewhere here while
next
time you
history was made today i joined the
exact moment
[Laughter]
merry christmas
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's what you've been waiting for
that's what it's all about oh i agree i
agree very much with you
[Music]
um
thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
something oh
oh see i see let's see the manager sent
me something
nodded to the hotel
another to the frodo
i will get back to you soon manage your
son
soon soon lords turn it back in on
shorty duncan
so this is what would have happened if
kelly actually got the penthouse
stop it don't make me feel like that
could have actually happened
[Music]
thank you for the rest of the chat
thank you
thank you thank you thank you i
appreciate it thank you
very much
[Music]
oh that's it for those
next up is
[Music]
also thanks to everyone who also thanks
for the membership
thanks to everyone who came to the
stream even though they didn't really
understand what was going on
[Music]
thank you guys i was mostly
pretty much only speaking japanese and
answering my
marshmallows thanks to the ann
translators during the stream they were
helpful really really
were they able to catch up and and go
fast i wasn't
wasn't uh
i i yeah yeah pudding was translating i
saw that i saw that
thank you thank you
um thank you guys i appreciate it very
much
[Music]
this might be my last super chat for
some time so here's a big one
thank you for everything you've done
you've not only brought happiness to me
in my trying times but also
countless others as well merry christmas
and happy new year
didn't thank you buy your chicken
[Music]
thank you i appreciate it very much oh
no
no worries about not being able to send
anything for a while don't worry at all
well that was a lie but did you send one
again
thank you though i'm happy that i i was
able to bring some happiness to you it's
very hard to imagine but um i i want to
believe
that it is true oh thank you
sketchnon what the hell
what no
another one oh my god
no no
[Music]
m
sure
[Music]
what you can't send a message full of
nothing but meows
that's weird
um
[Music]
m
these people
[Music]
m
merry christmas to you too and happy
holidays
i hope you had a lovely evening
or a lovely morning whatever time zone i
i guess uh you're useful on christmas
eve right now i'm living in the future
for me christmas is way over
but flaming to pete i hope you had a
lovely christmas thank you for your
generosity and your support i hope to
have you
uh with me next christmas as well
[Music]
account name
translation
[Music]
what is this one
m
red one red red super chat she says
merry christmas kiara and happy new year
happy new year almost but merry
christmas to you too
time's gone so fast and 2020 is almost
over thank you for providing us
so much fun this year i hope 2021 is a
great year for you because when you cry
i cry when you smile i smile
please continue to be our son our
happiness ah stop being so cute
oh come on
[Music]
well i hope that you know in 2020 i
partially tried to
speed round 2020 because funny funny was
so shitty i just wanted it to be over
soon
and now i'm like [\h__\h] it's it really
went by so fast
and i don't know if i'm sad or happy
about it but
i hope that 2021 i can enjoy more slowly
and treasure each day
more more carefully
because i don't normally i don't want
time to go that fast
[Music]
thank you thank you tickets monkey
let's go 2021 i'll see you there
if you're not here right now i'll see
you in 2021 maybe
thank you
[Music]
translator
thank you for the pinky
foreign
i think sally did not watch
the sim stream she probably only saw
uh screenshots maybe but she definitely
didn't see the
the stream so i think we're safe
we we are safe and i don't think she has
the time to watch my archives
either and every time she comes to my
stream she's only there for one minute
so
she doesn't have time for my streams
anyway so she probably doesn't know what
happened
it's all good
[Music]
merry christmas from australia merry
christmas back to my home corn train
with the kangaroos here how's my
kangaroo doing can someone check up on
my kangaroo
is it doing well
master danke san patrick sanderson
and wait i cannot write this name
they have babies now oh that's that's
happy that that's
good to know
[Music]
congratulations thanks for being part of
the membership
[Music]
you are bright as a sun personality and
amazing positivity
is what stopped me from self-harm which
i was doing for the past five years wow
i wish you the best in life and that all
of your dreams would come true
oh i'm i'm glad i could um have such a
positive effect on you
[Music]
keep it going good job really i'm proud
of you for stopping
let's uh enjoy life together
and you get an improved dump
[Music]
[Laughter]
so
you guys know what's left
this the current stream super jazz yeah
yeah that was quick huh i haven't been
going on so many tangents
[Music]
hmm
which is good because i still gotta
prepare something for the um
halloween collab um we actually
uh you know how the title says
presents and stories
uh i have to we're we're doing something
like secret santa
um so
yeah since i was uh subtitling my story
time video
i didn't have time for that yet but it's
okay i am we're doing it like in a
in a special way in a very creative
way so
i will i will prepare that afterwards
after this stream did you leave your
presence till last minute no
the thing is this idea even came up last
minute
and um num we got our secret santas like
yesterday the information
who it is so
and we're not doing like a physical
presence
we're doing like um but you will see you
will see
you will see just come to the stream
what have you done with that
i'm not yet sleeping
oh that's okay in if you if you're still
not sleeping
in like five hours i have a
german story time video coming out
at 10 p.m japanese standard time and
that should help you fall asleep
so stay awake until then so that you can
fall asleep with that
but then you would probably miss the
collab which is not good we don't want
to do that
[Music]
just don't ever sleep how about that
just stay awake forever
and then you will miss nothing
yeah but yeah for the people who missed
it in the beginning i'm probably gonna
cancel fire emblem for tomorrow probably
which means probably um hundred percent
uh because i need more time to prepare
holotalk
i don't know why i thought
that um this week should be fine
but i have been working
the whole time behind the scenes for the
past few days
preparing everything so like
preparing the karaoke stream preparing
what was i preparing i was preparing a
bunch of things man
i was recording uh the storytelling and
then subtitling the storytelling video
and all kinds of stuff so that i didn't
even get to do whole talk stuff yet
i have to do it tomorrow so
i have no fire emblem tomorrow
unfortunately nothing at all tomorrow
taking tomorrow off unfortunately
yeah but
sunday i have two streams i have holo
talk and i have
that one secret stream which doesn't
really need to be secret anymore but i'm
still keeping it secret because i don't
i don't know what's the right moment to
announce it
but the secret stream is not on my
channel
i will let you know who it is with
probably tomorrow
maybe please announce it now no
no um nine
[Music]
nine
oh uh oh yeah tomorrow i'm taking off
yeah but
i might just tell you on twitter what it
is
uh yeah
right let's read those uh super chats
[Music]
jackson d love santa seven ducks
with a huge red super chat
oh my god end with a long message so i
approve i approve
of this message i am takadashika and i
approve of this message which says
merry christmas i'm limited in character
so i'll be brief
thanks to pudding translating we heard
about whole life saving you
it may be true to an extent but please
remember all life is just a compass that
helps people find you and that we stay
for you i have no doubt that we
if we'd found you any other way in any
other situation we'd still be here
derek
[Laughter]
thank you oh man
yeah that's something i talked about
before i was like
if i was like an independent youtuber
you and me all of you and me would have
probably
never met because there's a ton of
english-speaking independent features
now and the chances that he would have
found me out of those is very low and
and i'd probably
um i'd probably
not have enough motivation to do it
independently
i think it is only possible for me to do
it this often
and so consistently and put so much work
into it because i'm in her life because
it's um it just motivates me more
so probably i would have independent is
probably not even
possible for me yeah
so i'm glad i'm in home alive and i'm
glad that i was able to meet all of you
including you deloaf thank you
merry christmas to you too merry
christmas and thank you for the lovely
kind message
and thank you for your generosity thank
you for always supporting
me so so much it means so much to me
um thank you from from the bottom
bottom bottom bottom left of my heart
but also from the bottom right of my
heart and the top right of my heart and
the left
uh in the top left of my heart
from the from all of my heart
thank you thank you the love i hope you
had a good christmas though because
since you're watching my streams i guess
you're spending it alone or so
which is a bit sad but i hope you
enjoyed it spending it with me
[Music]
packaging
that work all week so no family time ah
that sucks
that sucks but
we're the same for me it's the same
i'm i'm in i'm in a whatsapp group with
my family
in australia and uh i see all those you
know
pictures of them making delicious food
and
decorating the tree and all that and i'm
like
oh sad
but it's okay it's okay there's many
more christmas
christmases to come so many more
opportunities
right i'm not saying this for myself i'm
saying this for you guys as well
this is so many more years to come i
mean how old are you guys
huh 10 10 years old oh my god you
probably have 19 more years to live
but you're 20 well then you have like
about 80
80 more years to live probably depending
depending on
how healthy you guys are living
but nineteen nine
zero ninety
three months well that's very young
i hatched a month ago that's not what
i'm talking about but okay i like that
role play i like it
if you want to get the switch oh i think
like because of the christmas market uh
amazon is going crazy so he only has the
games now the switch is coming in a few
days i think
but it's on its way
[Music]
let's just put it behind behind us leave
it behind and move on
um thank you thank you for the red super
chad
the year is not over yet but i can't
express how much you in the community
has helped me recover my confidence you
changed my life more ways than you think
and i never stopped being thankful for
it
i can't be forever i approve of this red
super chat
message thank
[Music]
thank you so much also for the adorable
art always oh by the way guys the
chickens on top of the comment section
are also made by takuma um
i love those cute chickens i love them
thank you for your support takuma thank
you
i hope i hope we can keep up that
confidence
um keep on drawing we love your eyes we
all do
[Music]
wow thank you for your support yeah and
then indeed viva lucky like a kfp
forever i agree
[Music]
thank you for being such a fun and kind
house friend this year
my casper stop being so cute
i'll miss you when you're gone from the
house but for now enjoyable time that's
left oh my god
stop you making me actually being
sentimental
even though you're not even the actual
mouse
why you're making me feel so sentimental
it's as if as if you're actually
casper stop
[Music]
so cute casper
casper
that's a cutie pie merry christmas to
you two casper
[Music]
doing cars along the hello pro songs was
so much fun i'm glad
you got to sing a very song too so
emotional
i'm i'm happy someone knew the songs and
also the calls and not only me
when you move back to australia we won't
hear about casper anymore but you will
hear about my kitty cats they will be
like
wow and they will be so fluffy
you will love it i promise you it will
be i'll i will be so happy
can you imagine when i'm finally
surrounded by my cats and i will reach
pure bliss happiness
oh my god
they will go like
now now wow
[Music]
yep that's how it will be i see the
future
[Music]
that's how i always am with my cats
crazy cat let it go
that's how she goes is that what you
meant
[Music]
oh
i love when cats purr like they're like
some dove or something that's funny
[Music]
merry christmas kiara i was able to
catch you up your karaoke
and it was amazing yay thank you the
silent night singing with night on my
window was particularly
emotional let's say it was your
christmas present for kfb boys because
it was that good oh
thank you i'm glad you liked it
i was um trying to be a bit serious and
emotional by singing that
it's sure when the ingredients the best
yes when you're like
i'm like hello baby i love you too
nice to see you anyone said finger thank
you for the pinky
thank you
[Music]
yawn so much right now
casper's family passport are you here
no no i don't think that was classroom
so it's so weird there's so many noises
so many noises reindeer and rooftop it a
bit late but it does sound like that
maybe it is a reindeer
isn't it afternoon it's uh yeah it's a
half past 4 p.m
rat rate it's a mouse not
a rat
santa got presents for casper
you are loot so not when you what
and i i deny that statement
but i got all these presents from you
guys i got only super chats i have
already been rewarded
and i have pinot noir bgm for christmas
no no because that's not like christmas
we're gonna we're gonna keep the
christmas museum so
i'm sorry but good night
sorry but you got a denied stamp oh
that's that's pretty nice
[Music]
plural file thank you thank you
postcard tickets for me thank you
and merry christmas to you too
i wanted to say thanks for all this
thanks to me
you are listening for a whole life the
past few years have been hard for me
but your streams have motivated me to
start doing better
thank you ken i merry christmas thank
you
no i'm i i i i i
i just i just i i don't know what to say
i just
i just wanted to i'm just happy to be
here thank you
i'm glad i'm glad that my streams help
you thank you
merry christmas melta duncan
thank you cara for making the holidays
less lonely you really brought joy to me
and many others yay
i'm glad you came into our lives thank
you thank you i'm glad you guys came
into my life
thank you miltery naked
you always give us something to look
forward to so that nearly every day is
like christmas you're incredible and we
love you thank you even though sometimes
i have to
cancel my streams because i made too
many plans
thank you turkish thank you merry
christmas
merry christmas so sorry i messed up
sending in my card but you
hope you still read it oh don't worry i
i will go through them
probably tomorrow probably on my own
time because tomorrow
now that i cancel the stream i'll have
more time thank you for the membership
thank you thank you
thank you for the red super chat with
alex
thank you and you only sent um a smiley
but okay that's better than nothing i
guess
thank you thank you for your support
always you're very
very generous very kind
very supportive i appreciate it thank
you for being part of kfp
wow merry christmas to you hopefully you
gave yourself some presents as well
[Music]
thank you
thank you oh it's christmas already the
past few months went by so fast thanks
to whole life especially
you time flies when you have fun that's
why i want to give you my first forever
super chat merry christmas canada thank
you
thank you for the support and merry
christmas cody witton thank you
flame extinguisher and thank you for the
red super chat
merry christmas tingel here's my
christmas bonus oh
wait a minute in all seriousness the
past few months with you and kfp have
been the most fun i've had in years this
is my first akka spa
thanks for making my day day of the day
keep staring hayasuki
now this is what i call a good message
for red super chat i
approve oops no no no i approve
i approve thank you flamex
[Music]
thank you that's a very sweet message
and also thanks for
for the first red super chat um thank
you for your support
i hope it's not actually your christmas
bonus i hope you have a lot of love
a lot of love savings so that you can
actually really afford this thank you so
much for your support
merry christmas to you too
thank you thank you
monkey
[Music]
again and everyone cats thank you soon
thank you merry christmas to you too
40k high balls thank you for the music
and other fun streams thank you too
thank you for watching
i really appreciate the positive energy
you share with us like many i'm spending
the holidays alone this year thank you
to thank you
thanks to you and kfb for keeping me
company thank you to you guys all for
keeping me company
so thank you so much after sharing all
of you
and feign monochromic tankishan oh
monochronic sending a red
chat which apparently continues later on
with more tech stupiders
let's read uh this one is german though
thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
hello streams
thanks for the pinky ryan b
duncan also thank you for the pinky as
well wow wow
wow good luck learning german frs thank
you
and tai chi thank you soon i think that
is a red one
merry christmas thai wow merry christmas
merry christmas ho ho ho ho ho
i hope you had a lovely evening although
i don't know is it even evening for you
oh wait
wait you didn't read mine yeah i didn't
read it on purpose because i'm not sure
why
why that message has to be
sent to me
[Music]
and i don't have an obligation to read
every super chat
i appreciate your support but some
some messages are like i don't know
[Music]
um
thank you for the support i appreciate
it i appreciate it very very much
merry christmas to you too
um
i'm happy to hear that
thank you i was a bit nervous about
singing in german
that's my kitten thank you and thank you
for the pinky as well vanquishing
happy christmas kiara the year is almost
over but you've made these last few
months so good
you being here is the greatest christmas
gift i could have asked for
i'll stick with you all for the new year
so let's do this thing love your dork
thank you
what do you mean dork i am i am a genius
phoenix okay
genie is phoenix
thank you thank you
little kitty cat meow meow meow meow
as soon as i say so excuse me
[Music]
um
please don't please don't be rude
to that person
[Music]
just because i didn't want to read that
super job please don't be
rude please
thank you for the pinky that bye kitten
monochronic also thank you for the pinky
i already read the message so that's
that thank you
only message i've gotten this christmas
is from uber he's letting me know my
food will be here
[Music]
thank you for helping out with the
lonely boy hours tenta and cafe
manny
well at least ubereats is there for you
isn't that wonderful i hope you gave
that late sky a big tip
[Music]
swamp thank you
lastly outer dankester i don't have much
to give but i just wanted to say that
this year has been quite a lot to bear
but your bright and energetic
personality has made it infinitely
better
i can't thank you enough merry christmas
kiara please please please please
no need to feel bad about not being able
to super chat much or not being a super
chat
and being able to super chat at all
especially on christmas you should you
should you should spend that money on
yourself
but thank you i appreciate the support
leslie thank
[Music]
thank you
you're a pretty groovy gal keep cracking
out those baggage tunes i'll be
listening to these on
the jukebox i'll catch you on the flip
side to that
hope you have a cannoli christmas my
bird is this for real
[Music]
did he ask you to send that
thank you i guess
i was really drunk okay i guess that's
an excuse now
thank you that's a nice message though
didn't expect
that from all people thank you
[Music]
oh wait that was not a red white super
chat i i retrieved my kisses
[Music]
i have retrieved them give them back
thank you too merry christmas
well thanks to thank you thank you for
the pinky also merry christmas to you
i hope you made your day a little
brighter oh yes you did you always do
i'm so thankful for you and the kfp crew
if it weren't for you
this year would have been lost you've
been such a bright spot and no amount of
words will be enough love you kiara
thank you i love you too
thank you by the way i think i need to
make some more tea
even though i think we're close
somewhat close to the end let me make
some tea
[Music]
yep i need that
ah it's got enough water i want them
oh yeah
you know when you're close yeah i mean
i have to refresh but at the point where
i
open the superchats
and and the point where i am at now
if it wouldn't have changed since then
then i would be near the end
you guys went a little bit crazy one of
the red super chats
caramel melty yay oh we are not close
you've got 10 years ago oh come on
you also get that honey
[Music]
yellow no i did
hello no i did not read but um
hey wait didn't didn't know i did say
your name once but the
night
[Music]
i heard it for a moment
can you hear me yeah you do okay yeah
for a moment uh something went weird
[Music]
seconds to last caramel tea i need to
buy more camel milky
[Music]
shut up it's camomila
wait it wasn't my what it
wasn't my yankee candle supposed to raft
today from amazon
oh maybe it did while i was streaming
oh but i think i chose time before
maybe they left it in front of my door
and i didn't check it yet
[Music]
kelly milk i know
i don't think i read yours yet
maybe it's still coming but i know it's
probably hard to
hear your name uh when i'm reading so
many names
[Music]
what's going on
thank you for the membership i can't
speak anymore standing in the microphone
[Music]
i don't hear any study okay it's fun
okay
okay uh
[Music]
ah oh there we go what the hell
something's weird this microphone costs
a lot of money why are you just cutting
out without me even touching you
without me even moving you why are you
cutting out like that
okay right now i should be back though
what the hell uh
uh what the hell stupid microphone
why you do this to me there's no reason
for you to cut out i'm not even moving
you
pop my super chat cherry oh
i'm glad to do that you
are welcome all right so let's continue
um
until my my my my tea is a little bit
more cool
i'm not going to buy an asmr microphone
nah
i don't want to do asmr and i'm i mean
i can do loki asmr with my current
microphone
i can be like hello i love you
you're stupid stop it stupid chicken
insult me yes chicken abuse
[Music]
[Applause]
i love you guys you guys are so funny oh
my god oh
my god
[Music]
so logical paradox thank you for the red
super chat mwah
saying merry kitty
here's a christmas present as a thank
you for all the hours of a great
entertainment you have been giving us
which i wish i could also share all the
reasons i enjoy watching it but i'm
afraid i can't fit that many characters
into this message thank you
see i i approve of this message because
this person tried their best to fill up
the message
and i mean the last sentence was not
necessary because that last sentence you
could have actually used to tell me
what do you like about me but instead
you told me
that you cannot fit enough where's in
heels
but good enough close enough close
enough
using your super to talk you should you
should
because then we have more one-on-one
time
i'm absolutely sloshed right now what
does that mean
and i want to thank you so much for your
bread and bubbly demeanor
your positive editor's attitude and
happiness nevertheless make me smile
rock on super chicken thank you another
chicken doll
i am not a chicken a drunk oh
i was thinking it must mean something
like that well well well
thank you logical paradox
thank you also for the red super chat
really
thank you for your christmas present yay
honestly it's crazy like
how how generous you all are but
really from the bottom left of my heart
to you as well
thank you
[Music]
well i hope you give yourself something
too though as a
as a little reward for getting through
this stupid here
[Music]
buy yourself something nice please
and keep on supporting please
not saying keep on super chatting but
keep on supporting just always come to
my streams please thank you shane
frs kfb overused mob
and i just want to let you know that the
positivity and just your whole
personality is so sweet
like a long lost friend i've been
waiting to meet again oh i'm so happy
you exist
much love from this very great chicken
nuggets
thank you that's sweet
oh oh that's adorable
yo says merry christmas it's my first
red super chat i've been watching since
day one and you've become my favorite i
love the energy and positivity you bring
do you bring to streams i've been
feeling sad ever since the year started
and i feel like i can
enter you much happier now thanks to you
ah
oh joy thank you
thank you wow that's so sweet
thank you for the kind words they mean a
lot to me really
thank you
[Music]
i hope i hope next year will be better
for you
i'm sure it will be so merry christmas
and happy holidays kazuha now thank you
for the support and thank you for your
first red super chat thank you
i appreciate it brandon wilson thank you
thank you for the pinky and the karaoke
earlier was beautiful thank you
thank you thank you we give a free love
and thank you and also for the pinky
thank you so much
merry christmas kiana many people can't
celebrate in the ways we normally would
which is why it's awesome that we get to
spend the day with you yes many people
around the world chose to celebrate
christmas on christmas crazy right yeah
i mean that's just crazy don't know i
was thinking for some reason that
if i do the karaoke on christmas eve
for american time that everyone would
come
but i was wrong
i was so wrong i was so wrong
i guess many of you still have a life to
live
thank you shindo
[Music]
thank you so much for bringing so much
light and joy into my life these past
months
i've had a bad couple of months but you
and the kfp have managed to put a smile
on my face through it all
i can't find the words just thank you i
love you i love you too
[Music]
was it a red one i don't even know i
don't know i still this this currency
always confuses me
sorry
i watched the color looking next to my
family while fangirling good job
good job that's what i like to see
power lorry thank you thank you for your
support it wasn't read
okay good good good good i'm trying to
remember these
currencies but some of them just look
crazy to me
thank you
i'm happy that uh not only me but also
the kfc community has helped you
to you know feel a little bit happier i
have heard that kfb is indeed very sweet
to each other and very
very supportive very loving uh to each
other and that just warms my heart to
hear that i have such a sweet community
who don't pick stupid fights and [\h__\h]
but to actually like
care for each other that's really sweet
i think that that's um if the community
would be [\h__\h]
then i think some people would not
want to be in my stream so much i think
that the community plays a big part
uh so thank you all for being decent
human beings
for the red super chat
thank you ready for christmas
merry christmas thank you to you too
thank you for making you see a lot
better you are one of the reason i got
into this rabbit hole alongside julian
thank you for being so open to us like
we are all your friends i love this
community and you ah
thank you i love this community too and
i love you too
thank you
i don't know what to say i feel like i
keep on repeating myself sorry guys
i appreciate your support very very much
i hope you had a lovely christmas and
happy holidays
is it snowing is it snowing at anyone's
place
is it snow is it snowing from somewhere
no no no no no
yes oh where the hell
do you live in the antarctica
[Music]
indoors
that's cool a vancouver huh
[Music]
minnesota got snow nice
try russia snow everywhere
i can imagine
oh no there is some places with snow
apparently but those places seem like
there's always snow
nice i remember like 10 years ago
roughly when it was christmas
there was a lot of snow
oh maybe maybe like more than 10 years
ago
ah that was nice we made so we made um
snowmen
or out of snow and we made snow angels
in the
on the ground and stuff and now it's
like for christmas usually no snow can
we move christmas to like
uh january 24th please
please kiara confirmed more than 10
years old
dun dun
scandalous oh my god what
[Music]
i talked myself oh my god [\h__\h] yeah
don't you mean january 25th no i mean
january 24th because for me christmas is
the 24th
anyway back to topic thank you
come on fodr also for the red super chat
like a
double almost triple red superchat thank
you etho
what what what what what merry christmas
angel i wish i could have write a
meaningful message but i have no
confidence when it comes to these things
i want to be
able to eventually go oh don't feel
don't do that
i'm sorry for pressuring you guys
pressuring you guys
i think some of you do it on purpose uh
not writing any message
and i think some of you could do better
if they wanted to
but don't worry about it please please
please please it's okay
and i i appreciate the thoughts that is
behind the super chat
um i just i just hope that you guys
don't regret it you know
i don't want you guys to be like oh she
read my name
and then continued five seconds later
it's like i don't i don't want you guys
to regret sending those huge super chats
with no
we have no text because i i i i don't
have much to say
and then it's over so quickly you know
what i mean
[Music]
i want you guys to be like oh that was
worth it and i
i got the the reaction that i wanted
um
no regrets just yet
i think they pay for the reaction yeah
but if there's no text like
what am i supposed to react to
[Music]
what did i miss my research denied
button on views
no i can still continue using them
i will continue forever
[Music]
your reaction no texting is pretty great
you know but i don't like it
i don't like doing dance
hmm anyway everybody thank you
merry christmas to you too ho ho ho ho
ho
fodr have you been uh have you been a
good
a good good child
have you done some good things this year
i think you have
oh what do you wish for christmas fodr
or tell me tell me tell me in the chat
tell me don't don't tell me for a super
chat i dare you
i dare you tell me in a normal chat
message
that costs no money please no for real
i'm not even i'm not even oh i'm scared
now
i just want to use my deny and my
improved messages come on f.o.d all
right
give me something give me something
[Music]
i'll see you where are you oh my god
make the way clear forever they are
there oh he's thinking okay he's
thinking he's thinking what what do you
wish
what do you wish for christmas
let me be your santa come on come on
say say something i'm giving up on you
now's the time come on
what is your wish boy
don't be shy just tell me just tell me
hello come on i know you can do it
don't you have any wishes i guess if you
had wishes you would use the money on
yourself
if i had to say yes yes yes well it's
really hard to find
your your chats and all those messages
if i had to say
[Music]
she said no to my poor
oh come on come on come on
[Music]
[Applause]
no i i i lowkey saw that coming but i
was like there's no way he's gonna send
another one he sent so many already
[Laughter]
no
ah don't you want i don't know something
from gucci or yourself
i would have i would have approved that
i don't know
i need my tea too i mean i need the
camomile tea to calm me the [\h__\h] down
oh so hot it's so hard
[Music]
slurp
merry christmas i hope our christmas
cards bring you some joy we put our
hearts into them it's so cute you guys
did that that's so adorable
this year has been rough for all of us
and you've made it so it isn't
ending on a bad note thank you for
taking one more shot at your dream love
your channel
you that's i'm happy to hear that and
really then the whole thing of the cards
is super cute i just don't have the time
right now to look at them closely
but i i i will take the time tomorrow
and look for them one by one hmm
i was thinking of uh showing them maybe
a little bit but i don't really have
time on my streams this week to show
them and next stream
next week christmas is way over
so i guess i'll just do it privately and
that's okay because i feel like some
like one of the cards had baby sander on
it i was like i can't show that on
stream probably because i
i i i i don't want to show someone's
real face on my stream
i mean every other every other one
doesn't have
a face of center but i mean maybe some
people don't want it
to be be on stream so and i wouldn't
know unless you told me for each and
every card if you wanted to be on stream
why not so anyway
i'm just going to look at it properly
[Music]
yeah i mean i know xander's face is
public now
but showing it on my stream is something
else so
that's a different style
[Music]
thank you my mom told me i've been
looking a lot happier these days it's
it's all thanks to yukiya
the kfp crew and the other girls oh
that's cute oh
your mom told you you look happier well
that must it must be true and what the
hell
that's so cute if your mom notices that
you look happier that's cute
[Music]
i'm happy to hear that monochronic
duncan one one of u thank you thank you
for the pink team
merry christmas kiana thanks for being
the best thing to come out of 2020 oh
this year has been pretty rough but
thanks to you it's been a lot easier to
deal with so thank you it's really from
the bottom of my heart
the best thing to come out 2020 you guys
a whole life is the best thing to come
out of my life
so thank you for being there i love you
thank you
sad question
don't worry i didn't even notice
xi'an thank you sorry i'm not sure how
to say your name it's probably
xi'an roy thank you
[Music]
make a body pillow she has one oh
what do you mean with that you mean my
boobs are my body pillow what do you
mean
how life has improved my life way more
than i thought it would that's great
[Music]
thank you for all the fun loves you've
given us the last few months cheers to
your continued success
and all the good times to cover in 2021
thank you
carlos and also thank you for the red
super chat tyler son
yeah merry christmas to you merry
christmas kiara thank you for another
awesome karaoke stream coming home from
work and watching your streams on
archive
was a blessing in these past days thank
you for all your hard work
thank you too for like staying by my
side and supporting me all along thank
you
and happy holidays mary kurisumashi
[Music]
i appreciate the support i will do my
best continuously
for you guys thank you
[Music]
thank you alberto i am now very curious
about your cards
i am very curious
wonder if it's actually a positive card
or if you're roasting me or something
rosie dances thank you for the pinkie
like many i got into her life at a low
point in my life and it has done so much
good for me but none of them have pulled
me in quite
like you tension i hope you know the
happiness you bring to other self we
love you happy holidays
thank you i'm happy to hear that
[Music]
i will do my best to keep you in the
rabbit hole
i will never let you out of there you
better stay forever
[Music]
okay and now it's the time for me to
turn off the super chats no
more no more stupid rat super chess i'm
turning them off and now i'm breathing
the rest
kitty master you
[Music]
[Laughter]
they're gone they will be back soon
though
i'll be back in the next stream i i have
to get this done
and you guys i don't know you guys go
crazy sometimes
you just go crazy let's see where have
we left off
i have refreshed
when do we get our boing boing mouse pad
the thing is i i don't
i don't think there's there's a need for
a kiara uh boy and boy mouse bag because
i am resting my hand right now on the
pickled ass and by boing boing mouse
pads
and it just makes me happy i don't want
to produce anything
that replaces that i mean i could still
use that one and you guys
use the one for me but i mean maybe one
day
i would like to have a cali mousepad
though
that would be comfy although i mean i i
personally have to have to say that the
piccolo sent my mouse pad
i just slapped her boops
[Music]
i just slapped her boobs so good um it's
not so big
like the the the boob area
is not so big and i it but it's not flat
either
and i think it's a good height i feel
like if it gets too big
then like how how are you gonna use that
mousepad
i think the the piccolo senpai size is
quite
good for resting your hand on it
[Music]
i doubt callie will want a mousepad that
it's not a question whether she wants it
or not it's a question whether we
want it i i think
one day we get her to make a mousepad
wait we we just have to believe don't
give up
[Music]
otherwise i will really release it as my
own merch
i'll put callie's face on there and call
his boobs and i'll say uh this is this
is kiara merch
i don't know maybe you need glasses or
something this is totally chiara
merchandise
[Music]
it has to happen
see you shh wait i haven't found you
oh god oh god there's so many
yeah bye yoga
ah i found it i found it
let's continue that's a lot of red super
chat soul
revolver lancelot thank you long overdue
first super chat thank you merry
christmas kiana merry christmas to you
too
sorry i can't read every message fully
maybe but i will continue reading the
the red ones and the pink ones mad
reverse duncan
merry christmas thank you for the pinky
i didn't get to spend christmas with my
family this year so i'm happy to get to
watch the halloween streams to make up
for it keep killing it thank you
i am glad to provide some entertainment
for you
k-813
[Music]
i did it again i did it again kian
you've been saying my username wrong for
a while now it's not k813 it's k
8 i3 emphasize on the i
i'm sorry i know when i read your name
it makes me want to read
the i as a one k8 i
three okay okay okay it's a small i by
the way so i don't know how
if it was a big eye i understand me
getting it wrong but
[Music]
i'm sorry i did it wrong again but i
noticed your message and i will try to
be more careful now
he's been baptized by you now yeah maybe
he should change his
his name you can just say katie oh
that's supposed to be katie
oh i guess so oh i
ate oh okay katie
let's see if i will remember that
probably not
katie duncan chevrolet thank you thank
you for the ping for the red super chat
trapper gee
happy holidays oh my god here
here he comes again with the with the
puns
you probably don't want it but here's a
two toucan of my appreciation
i think thanks for helping me take my
mind off of being
all by my i'll buy my owl by myself
today
i might be a bit emotional
but i can't stop rave
about you our beautiful songbird i will
dub
you forever oh my god
you know what you know what i approve of
this message i approve of it
i like it i like your creativity
this is how you use a red super chat
this is how you do it
thank you thank you soon
thank you soon
are you saying fourth or do you want to
write first
confused thank you for being an
inspirational birth
despite everything going on in the world
you bring the silver lining keep
reaching for your dreams the only one
who stands in the way is yourself
[Music]
a very sweet message thank you um
it is true um
it's a very very inspiring thing to say
but yeah the only thing that stands in
everyone's way is yourself
[Music]
so happy holidays and merry christmas to
you kawaiicos thank you for your support
but this claiming discord i see you
there is discord again here
discord
[Music]
this my discord really is in the chat
you can only tag people if they're in
the chat right
they're still working
what what is so interesting about the
super chat reading stream i am honored
thank you
let me eat a little bite of my of my of
my breakfast by the way
it's um it's half past 5 p.m but i'm
still eating my breakfast
i'm getting hungry
[Music]
superchat is quite interesting when
you're reading so you're superchat
reading and that's true
wow thank you once again for your
support and your kind words thank you i
appreciate it
crispy thank you gumbo nightstand kawaii
are you meant first okay there we go
corrected yourself
thank you in a very sexy pink super chat
[Music]
very funny very funny
thank you soon thank you susan small
brain also thank you for the pink super
chat
merry christmas merry christmas to you
too marcus alfredo
sotelo
[Music]
thank you thank you so much great merry
christmas to you
it's probably not an exaggeration to say
that you've changed the
lives of many people this year and mine
included
my heart my heart you guys are making it
go doki doki doki i feel so happy to
have you guys
thank you patrick
[Music]
you know thank you for that
merry christmas merry christmas to you
too this year was such a letdown but you
came along
saved but you came along saved at the
end
[Music]
thank you so much for your effort to
bring smile and joy into your life i
don't talk much but i'm always cheering
for you in from the corner
of kfb by the way sims 4 was legendary
thank you i'm glad you're supporting me
thank you
and uh i don't know what you mean the
sims 4 stream was totally normal
there was nothing special about that
[Music]
well i'm glad you enjoyed it i hope i
hope i can
provide more entertainment to you in the
future as well and that you
will continue supporting me merry
christmas to you and happy holidays
thank you jingle
kitsune 12th pancake food
i hope you get credit for all the all of
the copies of sims you sold yesterday
you think anyone bought i think everyone
already has the game
yeah you think i sold some ho ho
business brav
working her way up there once again
love your channels your channel the kids
love it too
your kitties are your cats like my
my content oh that makes me happy
sims doesn't cost much anyway
i i mean if you just got the base
game okay but if you're like if you want
to get like old expansion packs it gets
extremely expensive in my opinion
but yeah it wasn't sale it's maybe it
still is on sale so if you're thinking
about getting it go get it now
it adds up it adds up if you want to get
everything
uh but even when i get all the expansion
packs it adds up to
a big amount of
pineapple and pizza yes
yes of course yes
anyway spanking heim maybe
maybe your cats and my cats should be
introduced at some point just kidding
not in that way maybe they just want
friends you know we we
we need to i i i genuinely i genuinely
don't
think about like when you have cats in
in your house
and you don't let them out because
they're house cats in my case that's
that that's the case um
i'm just uh i feel just a little bit
like sorry for
them not being able to travel and see
the world you know and not seeing any
other cats and so on
so
at least what i want to do is get a
garden sometime at some point
so that i can at least let the cats
outside and
experience actual grass on on
under their paws cats don't even think
about what the world is
yeah i know but that's the problem
they don't even know that there's like
this huge world outside with other cats
maybe they think they're the only cat
and i just feel like that's kind of sad
that's sad i want him to see more
[Music]
you know cats shouldn't go outside well
yeah uh
generally but like if you have a garden
garden would be awesome
but also i've seen them uh
i follow a certain instagram cats
i mean a bunch of instagram cats
and they uh their owner keeps them as
house cats
but puts them on a leash or in a in the
in the in like a you know
where you put in the baby the thing that
you push
like a um
a baby car or something like that
[Music]
they put them in there a stroller yeah
yeah
stroller so for her cats she uses
sometimes a stroller depending on the
cats
some of them don't like the leash some
of them uh prefer to be in australia
anyway
so those cats are actually really
enjoying it they
and i think um as long as the cat enjoys
it
that's i think a cute idea to every once
in a while
you know go outside and and show the cat
the neighborhood
if it's a good neighborhood um
i mean it depends like i've seen another
um i've seen a different
um instagram of a cat where the owner
got like a baby cat and like right away
brings the cat tries to train the cat to
get used to being on a leash and go
outside and all that
and in that case it was just like it
felt kind of weird because that cat
didn't seem to enjoy that much
and then i had to unfollow because i
didn't want to support that
i don't know that the cat seemed a bit
uh
stressed out and i i felt like that was
just for instagram content
but the other cats seem like they
enjoyed it very much
how was your poinsettia it's still live
thanks for asking it's still alive it
still is alive
for for one or two days it seemed like
um
i probably didn't give it enough water
but now now it's still live it's very
much the color that
that it was in the beginning my
plant is still alive but that is a plant
that actually
is hard to destroy anyway
yeah so it's not not a big
accomplishment that it's still alive
green palm sandstone no no not really is
that a new record
yeah but like as i said it's hard to not
it's hard to destroy that plant
[Music]
for the people who don't understand it i
have one of those plants that you
um that people like to put uh that
people like to buy for christmas
you know that the christmas uh plant
that comes in
red and and i have it in pink actually
it comes in red and what was another
color
my mom has literally killed the cacti
what
red green white pink oh oh
see i have it in pink uh yeah poinsettia
not a mistletoe no no no and anyway
um that plant is uh by the way uh
dangerous for cats and dogs and some
other animals so
please be careful uh this is something
that
some people don't know especially
people who don't have a pet anyway
i assumed i seem to have to
oh okay
i had to check something yeah yeah the
red flower that appears every christmas
exactly
yeah yeah yeah don't get it if you have
a pet
toxic i don't i don't know if it's uh
only toxic if they eat it or if it's
toxic just by being in the room i'm not
sure
um i forgot about that but just don't
get it if you have pets
oh anyway mkk 2004
lambeau field sanction discovered thank
you for the pinky
[Music]
between the big c and losing my grandmom
back in april it's been a really rough
year
oh man your streams have been a bright
shining spot thank you for giving us all
funny
fun silly heartwarming place to enjoy
and for being you merry christmas camera
thank you merry christmas to you too
that must be tough i
i i wish you my condolences and
uh i hope that it gets better for you
next year let's move on let's look into
the future positively
let's go silent
[Music]
thanks for telling me because i wouldn't
have recognized it uh
as a red super chat because it's a
currency i don't have the colors where
where for the people who don't know
the place where i read reads the red
super where i read all the super chats
it doesn't show the colors uh the list
that i have to go for it doesn't show
the colors which kind of sucks
but oh well my first recipe
to my most favorite youtuber thank you
i'm happy to hear that i'm happy to be
someone's favorite
just wanted to thank you for all the
entertainment you give us but make sure
you also do a lot of stuff for yourself
in the last few months you have left in
japan oh yeah yeah
we love you no matter how many streams a
week you do thank you
oh that's that's very very reassuring
thank you
that's very kind of you thank you i like
your message i
i approve of this message
uh i actually i have a i have a trip
with cali planned in
february and january in the first few
days
um i'm going somewhere for two nights
uh three days two nights without
counting with uh
with a old uh childhood friend actually
i'm just going going on a little trip
and i will not be
i will not be uh streaming no
i will not give you an exact date of
when me and kelly are going
don't even know do i
and i will not tell you where we're
going with cali until it happened
and my trip that comes up in january
beginning of january i will
i will i was thinking of maybe doing a
stream after i come back
where i show you some photos and where
we look
uh i i tell you what i was doing i was
thinking of doing that after i come back
if you wanna if you wanna hear about my
little
my little adventure
you want to see that
yeah yeah
okay i'll try i try to prepare it then
so yeah i'll i'll i'll try to travel a
bit more but
judy could corcera i really appreciate
your thoughts but i
i kind of i don't have much time left
anyway
and i i feel like i have just accepted
the fact that i can come back
anytime anyway especially now that
i am not as financially [\h__\h] as i was
before so next year
once everything's chill i can come back
and visit all the places
as a tourist whenever i want
i guess so i really wanted to go to
okinawa this year but i didn't i wasn't
able to go to okinawa so
uh i'll just do it next year when i fly
over here
my cats are strangely very clean and
cuddly to me
and that's lovely i'm a bit jealous
continuing simpsons
flagship thank you soon christmas
lights
that was dangerous merry christmas carol
made a new year bringing with success
thank you thank you for the red super
chat jslog
oh i hope the new year
brings you a lot of success too
and merry christmas and a happy new year
to you
thank you for supporting me thank you i
appreciate it
i hope you had a lovely christmas and
thanks for being part of kfp thank you
galaxia xd
[Music]
cafe navy admiral danishan
this chick chicken gives me the funny
ever since
my day has been sunny bottom left she's
a whack too hot
need some ice packs so here have some
pocket money
thank you sir looking at my job thank
you for the ransomware chat
thank you how did you have a good
christmas
hey so you're 24 was normal but how's
your 25th with your new kfp family going
so far
[Music]
what do you mean if you treat each
message as a virtual hug i think you
will feel a little more connected with
your fans despite the distance oh that's
cute you know
i wish i wish we could i wish we could
all give each other some big
big comfy hugs i wish we could
are you having fun basically oh yeah
um i mean it's just like any other day
it doesn't feel like christmas i don't
know
it doesn't i don't have a tree
i mean i could have gotten one but i
don't have a dream
and um i don't have decoration
i could have gotten decoration but i
don't have decorations
i don't have my cats i don't have my
family i don't i didn't even eat any
good food i only got some food from the
convenience store i don't know it just
doesn't feel like christmas but it's
okay
it's not it's not a nudge thank you
guys it's just uh
a bit of it a bit weird because i wanna
i wanna hype you guys up for christmas i
wanna
i want you guys to enjoy christmas with
me but i'm not in the christmas mood at
all
i don't know i i was so focused on like
streaming so much for you guys that
for me personally christmas was just
like work 24 hours
oh wow but it was worth it so
it was worth it i don't even know what i
would have done if i wasn't streaming i
would probably just be watching netflix
[Laughter]
so it's probably better that i did what
i did here
uh well i i will
i will however you know uh
make it make up for it by going on my
little trip
in a few days so thank you looking for
the top
you for your support what's more
important to me is that you guys had a
good time
spending it with me
[Music]
thank you thank you guys
thank you for the red super dad merry
christmas june
thank you guys i hope you had a merry
christmas
and i hope santa visited you with some
lovely presents
happy holidays
[Music]
m
i want a sweet message you guys who
don't understand german
your loss this message was hella cute
and i
approve of it
[Music]
thank you for the double double double
red super chat
merry christmas to you too thank you
thank you for spending your holidays
with us thank you for spending it with
me
it helps those of us who are also unable
to see our families i tell you
to rest uh all the time but jitsuwa i'm
even worse when it comes to
vacations i took time off today to watch
your streams oh
thank you i hope it was worth it
it's always those people who tell people
to do something
it's always those people who that don't
do it themselves they tell people to do
some to do something but they don't do
it themselves well i hope you can
uh rest a little bit more sometime
unfortunately i cannot force you like i
did with kelly
because i don't know you whisper in
person unfortunately i cannot force you
and go
with you on a vacation i know it's bad
and i can't stop well that's
the bad um
i deny i i do not approve of this
message
just kidding i i hope you can maybe
change your ways a little bit
just as long as you're as long as you're
um
healthy and happy then it's all right i
guess but as
as soon as you feel like you don't feel
healthy and you feel stressed out please
please do yourself a favor it's
totally okay to rest and it's okay to
take a break
it's okay really to just
stop for a moment
it's okay to watch five hours of netflix
per day it's okay
[Laughter]
it is okay telling myself that it's okay
to watch five hours netflix every day
that's totally fine
[Music]
continuing
good luck on your fgo wells good luck
[Music]
what do you think of casey william kfc
releasing a crystal is that actually
like for real now i i'm still confused
about that is that for real
like is it an actual console where you
can play games on i don't get it
i don't understand it's real
but are they gonna take it seriously
like an actual console or is it just a
joke where like one game will come out
and that's it i wonder
[Music]
but it is a pc not a console it's a pc
it's a pc where you can warm up your
chicken
is it a good pc it's a pc
then the name is misleading
that's confusing me because you know i
thought it was a console so i was
thinking of okay kfc
turning into kf console console okay
they did something there with the name
so i was thinking about
what do we do with kfp and then i was
thinking oh how about kf
because that's a p and paso you know
japanese for computer pasok
so i was like okay they make a console
and i make a pc but now you tell me they
are making a pc
so what the hell what am i supposed to
do very misleading name there they i
thought it was a console
it's a pre-built pc that also serves
chicken as a chicken one that's
it that's that's insane and i love it
that's insane and i love it maybe can
they
send me that over is it a good pc did
they reveal the specs
did they reveal the specs for it what's
[Music]
inside is it good
what so what is the graphics card i mean
i don't know [\h__\h] about graphics card
the only thing i know is that this uh
what's it
for we prefer like something like a 4080
really
[Music]
if that's the case then i i would like
to leave my current pc in japan sell it
to my manager because um
i am scared it will break if i send it
over to my actual country
and then once i'm in my actual country i
would like kfc to sponsor me and send me
that computer
i will gladly use it and advertise it
the whole time i will put my chicken in
there
and warm it up there as long as i can
leave the current pc
here and that the new pc can keep up
with the same specs
that would be an amazing plan they can
send me a new pc
[Laughter]
please kfb selling out the kfc
disappointing
wait we can work together come on come
on guys that's me it'll be nice
let's be let's be friendly
[Music]
hmm but did they did they write when
they're releasing it
is that public knowledge
[Music]
not yet um
i would need it in march
i mean actually i don't have i do have a
pc in
back in my home i do have a pc
oh those specs are those the real specs
i don't know that looks good to me but
what the what do i know
[Music]
don't be alarmed but thank you for the
pinky by the way
i enjoy falling asleep to your streams
because i love listening to your cute
voice plus the energy your students have
are always great to wake up
me and wake me up in the early morning
so they make you fall asleep but
eventually they also wake you up that's
nice
thanks for being such a kind energetic
person well thank you straw hd thank you
[Music]
oh my god i am on fire thank you hi kira
i just wanted to thank you for making my
doll work that's a whole lot more fun
oh i'm happy to hear that thank you look
at krishna
someone said the pinky pinky but yeah
see this person has no name and that is
a
very confusing
um because this person says
dear santa all i want for christmas is
for kiara to say my name
well i would like to say your name but
you have no name so
i deny
[Music]
thank you for the support though thank
you for the pinky
i got some vacation we'll be fine thank
you
maureen
before but thank you for cheering for
the holidays
you're welcome thank you for watching me
even in the holidays
losing marble stun cushion kurtz rhythm
pickle duncan
hey girl a very special person to me
ashton is a big fan of you really made
our life so much more fun
with you and ian and i was wondering if
you can tell her merry christmas ashton
there you go i did thank you
for watching my streams
[Music]
flip tcs thank you
sending another pinky writing dear kiara
and that's it that's very confusing
what's going on
thank you
i want to read your name the struggle
guys burritos thank you
i love your accent and attitude
by accident what what's your problem
with an australian accent huh
even though i'm a native english speaker
i still picked up a bit of an accent
from my parents when i was a kid
i still sometimes say paxy instead of
pepsi that's cute
that's cute what that's cute merry
christmas merry christmas to you too
tacos burritos
thank you for the sweet message max
roland thank you
[Music]
i hope your cat feels better soon thank
you tom
donkey shin pak bear dankest strange guy
again
vampiri
[Music]
wait i can't read that that's let's just
translate
[Music]
sending a pinky thank you thank you
thank you
approve the night emoji uh probably not
because i already have
my my stamps
nothing better than that
phantom joker thank you for the
red super chat
hey kiana thanks for being an amazing
chicken
i'm i'm confused this is like
did you want to send a super chat to
someone else
and making our days better with your
streams i look forward to seeing more of
his streams in the new year also i am
the true kia i swear
oh yeah your name is kiara kfc
we have an imposter among us
[Music]
no i deny the super chat and i deny your
statements
and i'm also not a chicken so everything
about this super chat is wrong
but thank you for your uh generous
donation thank you anyway
duncan thank you
thank you for the support martin halas
thank you
thank you for a thing possibly a red
super chat i'm not sure
merry christmas sadly i am sitting in a
stat in standby for hospital calls for a
12-hour shift
we have another doctor here guys buddha
you have a new friend here's a doctor i
have a doctor here
nice kfp doctor team is
being assembled assembled but america
says to all of you and stay safe thank
you
and thank you for your service thank you
for working on christmas
hmm thank you for your hard work
thank you
[Music]
i'm home visiting my family and my cat
is practically glued to me
i think you're in for a pleasant
surprise when you get home to your
your fluff balls she does keep laying on
the keyboard and i'm trying to watch you
what do i do
you let her lay there it's her keyboard
what the hell it's her house
it's her keyboard it's her lap it's her
bed it's her toilet it's her bathroom
it's her food it's her steak it's her
tuna
it all belongs to her truth
give it to her she's who deserves that
she's a cat every cat deserves
only the bestest leo stella lion
kitchen men's dancing thank you for the
pinkie
thank you red one confused sorry thank
you for the rest of the chat
also thanks for the membership uh
merry christmas to my favorite phoenix
thank you merry christmas to you
too please accept this gift from me it's
the least i could do for my inspiration
and hero listening to your beautiful
heavenly
singing voice is the best way to start
christmas oh come on
hey why are you making me blush
keep being the blazing flame that guides
us oh thank you
[Music]
that's such a sweet message thank you
for your kind words
[Music]
i'm glad you enjoyed the karaoke
i hope to do more soon thank you
i love you i
i a problem of this message
very much thank you
happy holidays to you mens chimipah
dankeshu and sankashan siren thank you
for the red super chat
there's our moment finished night shift
and i'm now listening until i sleep
looking forward to the archive again
boys
thank you for your hard work um
thank you cyrux for working for united
night shifts uh
i i actually my
um my original job before her life
i worked somewhere where there are night
shifts i usually did
the evening shift though not the night
shift but i
did not envy the night shift people so
[Music]
although actually sometimes i did
because i i heard that they have been
playing switch games all night
and not really working much and when i
hear that i'm like
boy boy they get paid extra for being in
the night shift and then what they do is
play switch games what the hell
and another one of them played some kind
of shooter game while they were on shift
and that person was actually um
a night shift supervisor or something
like that
supervisor plays some kind of fps game
during the stream and watches twitch
streams and all that
i mean okay i guess i can't judge that
because you guys watch my streams at
work partially
some of you
so i guess
can't i can't judge that let me move my
microphone please don't break microphone
[Music]
i feel called out i'm sorry
i'm sorry it's okay you can do whatever
you want i mean if you have the time or
if you
if you have the time to play games and
watch streams okay and go for it
both words i say gotta be honest i
i watched not a lot of netflix in my
evening shifts because like where i was
working before her
life there were some times where
where the shifts were very boring uh
sometimes where they were very very very
busy but
other times they were very boring and i
had like nothing to do so i would watch
netflix for for a really long time
and do some other stuff
[Music]
netflix dixon has a long history yup
hello kiara i know you aren't going to
read this one from manny but you are the
best merry christmas thank you
thank you i'm happy to hear that
my boss never notices but then again i
work at home
i'm stuck with facebook gaming oh man is
there anything good there
what is what is that anyway i don't even
know i never seen
i've never seen that
i announced this book to have stage free
netflix addiction
[Music]
no no
not true what netflix shows those kia
watch i tried to recently i've been
mostly only watching sitcoms and funny
stuff because i
i just need something to you know shut
up my brain and then not think too much
about it because deep
deep deep stuff just i need to use my
brain for that
[Music]
but i do i do want to start watching uh
what's it the gambit the ladies get
what's it called in english
what's it what's it called an uncle a
queen's gambit ah
i want i want to watch that but right
now i i just always
whenever i have time for netflix i just
i just need something
you know lighthearted but i'm running
out of those shows because i'm
at the moment just re-watching
everything i've already seen
um and now i'm watching something that
apparently
disappears from netflix at the end of
the month so
i'm like [\h__\h] i i i gotta watch all the
seasons before it's gone
because i don't want to watch it
illegally so
i mean it's not my first time watching
that but now that i started i want to
binge watch it until the end right
um anyway i gotta get this going man
thank you cyrux
daisy thank you and take my first super
chat you thank you with your fruit your
first supercharger it's a red one thank
you
i've been watching for a while but
between christmas and second fest i
haven't had the funds to pay my salary
until now i hope this is enough to cover
it since october but if not just say so
no no no it's enough it's not enough
waste enough don't worry about it
you shouldn't make me decide that decide
yourself how much
salary you're gonna pay well thank you
for the support daisy
and thank you for watching all my
streams hopefully
thank you i appreciate it very much
thank you soon
happy christmas merry christmas happy
holidays
next up something there
uh evan mcgowan thank you so much karen
thank you soon yellow
thank you for the no text red super chat
thank you for the support yellow i have
finally read your name
yellow you still there did you fall
asleep
thank you hope you're having a lovely
christmas
spending all your money on me
thank you
thank you for your support you have been
a good child
i'm barely awake oh should i
should i slap you away dude
unfortunately i cannot slap anymore and
my microphone does not pick it up
anymore
or maybe this will wake you up done
done
good morning sunshine yellow
thank you for your lovely support
verge raphael thank you
[Music]
i look at my super chat list and
it's pretty much all of it is blank and
red super chats
how huh
thank you for the support thank you wow
thank you
for your generosity always and always
watching my streams
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat thing
approved
i will approve that because at least it
says something everything after that
says absolutely nothing
thank you looking for the top wow
merry merry christmas to you ho ho ho
aurelion small thank you thank you for
is that a red one i don't know
i don't know that currency are real and
small
but everyone sent red one so i suppose
maybe that one is the one too so you get
a kiss
wow thank you for your support spicy
chicken taco
also red super chat actually don't let
me
there you go that's for you and thank
you though mwah
thank you for the support spicy chicken
taco i hope you had a lovely christmas
thank you so much leo thank you and
hamburger thank you
and also thank you for the red super
chat with no text i do not approve of
that not at all
thank you though mwah good night
though true max thank you for
uh that that that's not a red one that's
not a red one but thank you thank you
i love omega thank you
mbot thank you for the red super chat uh
however there is no text that goes with
that mate
denied your job
thank you for the support and vote and
merry christmas
however this one also with no text to
bully me with money thank you
but deny dan kashin
i'm going for this quick now okay
because cause like
i don't even know what to say i don't
even know what to say
it's your fault oh nice necklace
ah sirec thank you for the rest of the
chat once again
but the night you have to write
something with your super chats thank
you don
merry christmas forever
with money again no
thank you for the red super chat though
oh thank you everybody
[Music]
you're always there so thank you for
your support
livestream sketchnone thank you thank
you for the red super chat
nothing to say well i deny that
i do not approve of this message
but thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you for the support
thank you for absolutely you sent quite
a lot of them so
i hope you're not gonna um ask for
refunds after this
thank you thank you and merry christmas
happy holidays
fodr red super chat with no words i deny
but thank you for the support i cannot
be mad at you guys
but uh still i do not approve of it
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you for your generosity
mr no thank you soul thank you thank you
for the red super chat
from canada but i don't know
thank you doll thank you for the support
pew pew soul i hope you had a lovely
christmas i hope santa claus came to you
thank you thank you thank you for your
generosity thank you for supporting the
kfb
[Music]
strange guy i think that was it wasn't
that a red super chant
see i don't know i think it was
ah now i'm not sure
that russian money how much how much is
uh 200 goddammit google
i need to see if i have to deny you
russian
rupaul too
oh it's not i think
it's also not really blank
[Music]
now you need it unsure
unsure about my decision i will think of
it
come back to you later anyway syrian sky
thank you thank you
spider dankeshen and boston
uh
however you have not not
written any message so that's a denied
thank you though for your generosity
thank you for supporting kfp we will
grow stronger and bigger with your help
thank you soon very much
[Music]
spicy chicken taco again with a red
super chat but it just says what you
said so i guess i approve of that
i approve that because you were
basically saying that what i say is
is good thank you
lindrick thank you for the red super
chat thanks for paying us with your
streams buzz
[Music]
yeah i guess that's what i'm doing i
guess that's totally what i'm doing that
makes sense
oh no no no approve
i am paying you so whoever complains
they they're not getting any salary shut
up
you're gonna be salary the salary is my
streams
thank you thank you lynn drink wow
thanks for the membership oliver wright
also
thank you for the rad super chat
[Music]
what is this what is this a romantic
message here
i've loved you so much why is it past
tense
thank you for being the light in my life
you're the reason i wake up every day
why is it past tense though why does it
say i loved you
what oliver what happened
[Music]
soon
thank you for your support thank you
i hope you had a lovely christmas you
told us to say that ah
oh i guess i did ah yes that was the
message tonight
oh here i thought you were being a
little bit cute here
[Music]
this stream is shadow band on my hand
are you for real
guys is this is this stream in your
subscription box
[Music]
yes okay
so oliver right thank you thank you for
the support
i hope you really do love me though i
hope you do
banjo-kazooie with a blank rat super
chat
hmm what do i do with you
up until now you have served me so well
with wholesome messages and now suddenly
you
you come here with a blank message but
what am i supposed to do with you
i deny it i deny
it
[Music]
you have betrayed me well nexus you have
betrayed me
thank you thank you as always
you are the reason i wake up every day
is this what you wear after
[Music]
i i i guess i guess so i guess that's
close enough i approve
however you you're the one who tried to
say that that i'm the imposter and
you're the real kiana
now that is something that we have to
talk about in in the usual room and i
will meet you there after the stream and
we'll see
where we go from there you know
well we will see kiara kfc
you you think uh you're the real kiana i
will show you who the real kiara is
there can only be
one kiara
there can only be one
[Music]
yara
what the hell
[Music]
you cannot just write good message that
that does not make it a good message i
deny it
thank you for the red super chat though
my rose wow
please next time you write an actual
message with text
please oh please do me a favor
because i don't know what to say to all
these messages
i just don't know if thank you
thank you for the rest of the channel
with no text
so i deny it but merry christmas
my microphone broke what i mean you hear
me don't you
[Music]
oh god is this ever going to end oh my
god i just want to lay in bed and watch
[Music]
netflix
okay let's go see i don't know if thank
you for the rest of the day once again i
already said it but thank you
laurie i think that is also red super
chat are you crazy
you wrote nothing you wrote nothing
what a waste thank you shindo thank you
for your support
wow merry christmas if i rest on
sapphire kidson thank you for the red
super chat it's literally like every
super challenge that rents in the chat i
can't
i deny because there's nothing written
here not even a meow
not even a meow
[Music]
magazine
there you go i approve of it i will
stamp you
thank you for the red super chat
crackerbot thank you i hope you
enjoyed the christmas themed streams and
all that
there's still a bit more to come so
i hope you will be there as well thank
you for your support oh
merry christmas
[Music]
i think that is a rat super chat and it
only says yes
you little punk i deny it i think
i will take your puppets away from you
if you keep on doing that
i will take them away
[Music]
australia is on fire but um
you mean it's like actually on fire or
is it just hot
but the key i don't mess with you is
cool yet
hot very crispy mess thank you for the
red super chat your your super chat is
very confusing
probably both oh damn
those does this does so straight i mean
i probably should know because i'm
obviously from australia but
this is actually like something is
always on fire here
australia always fires somewhere
wait you say that as if it's a joke or
something as if it's like
nothing to care about
[Music]
but is it like so fun what i know
australia is like huge
like huge areas of nothingness
if those areas are burning it's not that
not that bad is it
but i hope the animals are okay
it doesn't get very dry or is it very
humid
[Music]
it's very dry
that's probably not so nice for the
animals
although i personally have to say i
prefer dry heat over humid heat because
the humid heat in japan
and summer just makes me feel like i
can't breathe and like it kills me makes
me feel sick
it's really bad
[Music]
probably generally not as hot as like
australia
probably but it has it has much more
humidity
in japan the humanity is what kills me
like when i first came to japan
years and years and years and years ago
uh
i i came when it was summer my first
time in japan was summer and i did not i
did not expect
i did not think that japan would be such
a tropical country
i had no idea so i arrived there and it
was so goddamn hot but i i
i could still somehow handle it somehow
but a few days later
i went to a cat cafe for the first time
in my life
and i threw up in the cat cafe because
the heat just got to me completely
i threw up in the cat cafe
when i made it to the toilet i made it
to the toilet
all good all good
but yeah the heat in somewhere in japan
i can just not go outside i'm glad i i
i'm glad summer is over i prefer um
the winter which is ironic because i'm a
phoenix
it's ironic but
don't don't don't talk about it don't
don't
talk about it
so yeah anyway i hope you save meister
please be safe
just stay inside and turn on the air
conditioning i hope you have air
conditioning see the good thing about
japan is though that pretty much every
every apartment every house even the
small cheap apartments they
all come with an air conditioning it's
just normal that it's included
now maybe for some of you guys it's also
normal but where i come from this is not
normal
we don't have air conditioning in our
homes unless it's like a
like a like a penthouse or like a
a castle no no castles also don't have
air conditioning but like new new
apartments that are really really really
expensive maybe come with
air conditioning maybe but generally
nothing gets filled with air
conditioning
sounds like we're on the tangent
you still literally juice a little bit
don't get used to it
[Music]
i have an air conditioner in my house so
that's nice
texas would die without i see oh is it
so that in america
most apartments have air conditioning
we got ceiling fans in australia are you
kidding me
are you are you kidding me
if it's that hot in australia as i
imagine it like
it if it when australia is actually on
fire i
you you're actually telling me a country
that is on fire
does not build the apartments of air
conditioning
but with ceiling fats
[Music]
only high end have a conditioning
not oh we mostly have ceiling fans
ceiling fans don't do anything today
ah is this dry heat easier to take in
humidity
[Music]
does it help though i feel like it
wouldn't help much
you take what you can get
oh man i i i
in in australia
you know my my kind of australia the
summer is
tough without air conditioning
it actually is tough i tried to
use fans and stuff to get through it but
it actually stuff i wish they would
build more air conditioning
it does get very hot every now and then
but it's not humid so that's
thankfully something it does not get
humid
um
[Music]
is that a red one could be
in case it's a red one it has no message
so i say
[Music]
thank you for the sweet message happy
holidays to you too
thank you very kind carlos g was the red
super chat that says nothing
oh my god it doesn't
end
[Applause]
i'm like actually suffering
because i try to give you guys like more
than just one word i don't want to just
skip them
i don't want to just skip them ugh
[Music]
just hit the stab and move on really
i don't know i just feel bad for like
i'm not saying
it's it's yeah it is their fault because
they don't write text
they don't write anything so it's their
fault
all right call of duty i i want to say
before i
get into this i love you all
and i appreciate it very very much
and i i am overwhelmed
by the support really
but i'm serious i wasn't trying to like
get you guys to send more super chats i
actually wanted you guys to write actual
messages
because now we have the problem there's
so many and i don't know what to do with
them
so please just
[Music]
thank you thank you okay just know that
i'm very very grateful for what you guys
are doing
but i am i'm also overwhelmed and i've
been exhausted um
suffering from success
call of duty
[Music]
red super chat thank you doll thank you
soon i love you
i love refrigerator sunkishing thank you
thank you for the red super chad thank
you very much i love
you too merry christmas to you sydney
thank you for the red super chat however
it just has a stupid face on it so i'll
deny it
thank you thank you for your support
merry christmas
is calming down it's calming down at
this point we went we were able to go
through most of it
who came up with such badges for
sponsors
you mean the membership badges me
i don't see any problem with them what
are you trying to say
[Music]
what what's your problem with the
membership membership badges
are you
[Laughter]
you got a problem little boy
why do we have to be fried says
a member i mean you got yourself into
that you didn't have to you didn't have
to
it's your choice it's your personal
choice okay i don't take complaints
it's a beautiful life waiting ahead of
you to accept it
send him to the usual room send him to
the usual room send them to the user
room
use your room usual room use your room
use your room
chickens chanting in the distance use
our room yourself
to the room thanks for the membership
there you go we have another
another sacrifice sorry i mean uh
employee welcome welcome welcome
spicy chicken taco i think i already
read that one but i deny it
thank you thank you for your support
spicy chicken taco
michael balo thank you why ot thank you
for the
pinky with an actual text i cannot
believe it oh my god
there's a there's a actually someone who
used uh
like the whole limit oh my god
merry christmas you know tony has become
one of my favorite songs to listen to
throughout the years and
thank you your adorable voice has
energized me during my roughest weeks
on the job if you're making another song
next year which would you prefer opening
or ending
um not really aiming for
anything like that uh but next song
i want something that is a bit more on
the
cute side maybe like a bit a little bit
probably not probably not gonna be like
a super cute pop song but
i want the theme to be about love this
time
so let's see where we can make we'll
probably start working
on it in january
would you do any touhou covers in the
future well actually you know
i i've been thinking like um i wish i
could
work with some touhou project circles
like martin senpai did
and really some toefl project uh music
i mean the guy who made my hinotori song
gojo
he is the owner of one of those toho
project circles
sink arts so it is not uh
impossible and i know a few people i
know a bunch of people
so maybe in the future that's something
possible but
the problem is since i leave japan i
will have to
record it in my home and i don't know if
if that's something
like i don't know i don't know if that's
something producers would want to do
like having to sing or not with them and
not recording with their microphone but
recording me
i mean my microphone is decent now but i
don't know
um should be probably higher quality
than that even
[Music]
anyway i have front teeth someone asked
if i found you look
you see that
[Music]
i only see a beak
you did that on purpose it's a pinky
[Music]
has stopped responding yes i have you
want to stamp too
there you go thank you grandpa duncan
thank you for support merry christmas
happy holidays please be
healthy and happy in everything
much love to you sketched on also have a
red super chat and never register for
nothing to say
these are not supposed to be just for
fun
[Music]
thank you for your support
merry christmas great fire chicken you
are great
i'm not a chicken but close enough
thank you what is the point wow i
appreciate you thank you thank you thank
you i don't know what to say anymore i
keep on repeating myself
suffer chats
[Music]
um thank you for the red super chat
another blank one yes um
bye why thank you like i shouldn't thank
you
i love you thank you very much say extra
red lion thank you
soon effects come out
uh
[Music]
oh my god sketched on another it's not
like you six stories something
fifth fifth red super shadow is still
good
thank you thank you for the red super
chat thank you soon
lord black went also thank you for the
red super chat
but no nothing no message with it what
the hell
[Music]
thank you thank you
happy holidays merry christmas to you
lord blackwind
[Music]
says
uh russian name
[Music]
oh
oh oh one second
how do i even pronounce that
how do i pronounce that
the translation for the name is another
name that i can't still say
[Music]
i see what you did there russian man
thank you and the message says good luck
with that
you know what that's funny you got a
proof sample
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you as well
i'm glad we can make you happy
i think the recipe
[Music]
thank you for your support thank you
thank you soon merry christmas for you
and happy holidays
hopefully you get into the new year
smoothly
thank you soon
[Music]
it's too long i can't read it
thank you for the pinky atlas thank you
for all the hard work you put in
for our enjoyment i hope the rest of
your year and 2021 after that
is as enjoyable for you as you've made
the past few months for all of us merry
christmas thank you thank you sorry guys
i'm so exhausted
thank you oh my god how long has this
it's almost
gonna be like oh
[Music]
i'm
getting closer and closer here okay i'm
i'm pretty close now i'm pretty close
let's do it let's do it
let's do it
[Music]
i'm hungry though thank you atlas thank
you
an optimus prime thank you for the red
super chat actually with
a proper message i can't believe it what
i'm what i'm seeing with my eyes oh my
god it's a proper message
merry christmas as a fitting end of 2020
i broke my back
what i needed to go to the hospital and
your streams
really entertained me while lying there
and also distracted me from negative
thoughts and pains and i think that
helped my miraculous quick recover oh my
god
[Music]
are you okay but i guess you already
recovered
miraculous quick recovery that's because
of the phoenix
no that's because of you because you you
were such a brave brave brave person
good job on
on healing so quickly maybe you're doing
some therapy still to get you back
back on track but please please be safe
i don't know how you did that
let's pull some backflips or something
don't do it anymore okay
don't do it anymore optimus prime merry
christmas
and congratulations on your recovery
you know that could have gone really
wrong so i'm happy you're you're staring
you're healthy so
don't do it again whatever you did don't
do it again or maybe maybe it wasn't
your fault but
it could be could be a possibility
please be safe okay
[Music]
back on track
funny
oh man optimus prime ah merry christmas
dude recipes
thank you thank you for the rest of your
chance sorry peter likes i'm so
[Music]
i will not read that navy boy duncan
thank you for the rest of the chat
actually a proper message so i will i
will gladly read that
my first read super chat you've been my
favorite streamers ever since you
debuted it your love and
beautiful personality has given me so
much joy
merry christmas and happy new year i
can't even begin to tell you how much i
love you
i hope you and casper is staying warm
that's such a lovely message
[Music]
approve everyone
use this person as an example
for your own super chat because that's a
lovely message
even even worrying about casper how
sweet
thank you wow baby boy thank you
merry christmas to you too and happy new
year to you too
and i'm i'm happy to hear that i've been
your favorite since the beginning that
makes me
very very very happy
because the beginning was kind of rough
and uh
i i didn't have the best start uh
but i'm glad there that's people like
you have been sticking around
um thank you of all my heart
huh
[Music]
i mean i mean i know that there's people
who
don't really like it usually it's uh
haters but um
uh i don't know there's
there's more than enough people who
enjoy that kind of content and the thing
is like
in many cases it's not even me uh
initiating it but it's the
viewers initiating it and asking for it
and hoping for it
so um i don't know as long as people
enjoy it
and me and me and kelly are just you
know
we are also enjoying it kelly wouldn't
do it she wouldn't
enjoy it and i just want to have fun
and i will i will not um
adjust myself to uh
someone just because they don't like it
but so that's why i don't understand why
it was necessary to tell me that but uh
yeah well i don't know it's okay it's no
problem but um
once again though i don't have the
obligation to read anything but
[Music]
also there's like um
more than enough other content for me
where i also don't mention cali
i mean that's right but the chat often
also just always brings her up
like when i sing all i want for
christmas is you the whole chat is like
oh she's saying this for kelly she's
singing this for kelly you know
it's it's not only me
it's not only me bringing that kind of
stuff up
but i don't even have to mention her in
the chat chat's dimensions and i
personally i don't care
i i think it's funny i don't mind you
guys bringing her up the whole time but
then there's other people like
complaining that i bring her up to mine
too much
but like partially that's because the
chat brings her up the whole time
which i don't care about but other
people are like
oh he talks about carrying me well
excuse me for having a friend that i
really
appreciate and i really love and that i
think about
excuse me
i just want to have fun
well you send another super chat so
that's i guess why i had to talk about
it but
um i think it's uh i hope it's
i don't i don't i just don't know what's
what
you would want uh from
sending such a super chat what what do
you expect
what do you expect me to say like oh
thank you for telling me you don't like
my streams thank you thank you
i don't know i don't know
[Music]
but
i don't know let's just move on i'm not
i'm not mad at you or anything so please
please don't worry but it it it's just
it's just
hard to hard to say anything about that
also it doesn't really help the mood
does it
but thank you for your support i i guess
[Music]
super chat
you
[Music]
um
all right i'm trying to um
thank you i appreciate it very much
[Music]
kitchen
that's all the super chats guys thank
you so much i have to prepare some
things
for for later so
um
[Music]
thank you guys sorry sorry for rushing
the end
i'll see you soon
in german we say i'll feed us in
are merry christmas to all of you
merry christmas
[Music]
you