[Music]
foreign
so
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
key
[Music]
hello stream was stuttering
lag
what really
really
nice hat i'm a sim
i'm the same it's fun for some people's
regional okay thank god
oh that makes me so anxious
[Music]
of course i created the language duh
hello everybody
um
welcome to
a new
series
i don't know if it's gonna be serious uh
it would be nice if it was if it was
gonna be
uh but a new
a new theme a new adventure
in sims
i think it was called high school years
the new um pack came out
a few days ago
and
i wanted to play that
wait let me pick some i need some kind
of
bgm maybe
how about this
no
something
sims-ish
something sims-ish but i mean we're in
there i feel like maybe later we want to
hear some music you know
um
nice hat thank you it's not a hat though
don't get beat yeah no when you're like
in in cass and create a sim then yeah
you get bgm but like
just doing random [\h__\h] often you don't
have any btm what were these tracks that
i downloaded the other day
[Music]
i guess it needs to be even more chill
than that
uh no it shouldn't be obs it's only
original so it's not my fault i hope
uh so welcome welcome let me go on audio
stock really quick
[Music]
i will i will show off um because i did
it off screen but i will show it off now
i will show off like uh all the outfits
i created for everybody
and we can still make some changes but
i'm overall like super satisfied
actually
um
the the reason i did it off screen
was um
because i i was thinking you know it
might take me a long time and i kind of
want to do it like without being
stressed about the time
it ended up taking me i think at least
two hours if not more
uh so yeah i think it's good that i did
it off-screen
okay let me find some bgm
what's this
is it like if i look up like sims like i
love like bgm that gives you sims vibes
like generally the whole soundtrack
soundtrack of zim sims is so good and
it's also not repetitive so i love that
i love that
i agree
okay
oh no
you would think audio stock has
everything but when i look up shimazu
it has nothing that is so sad
like honestly sims 4 or like sims in
general sims bgm i could listen to that
all day
like uh it's a good bgm for like chit
chatting too
what did i just play oh
ah
[Music]
how about what about this
oh
that might be chill enough
but maybe too calming
but i want it
wait i downloaded this one before
what i don't remember
when did i ever use that
[Music]
okay
so we got that one
and also i really need to name my tracks
again because they're all just audio
stock track one five three three seven
and so on again
and i never know what it is
[Music]
oh
that kind of has a little bit of a sim
slide actually
that instrument
i don't know what it is but
oh i'm taking that one it's mine
yeah you feel it you you get it right
i don't know what it is but
oh my god
that could easily play in casts when you
when you're in cast for five hours you
know some weird
when i was in cassie yesterday for like
two hours they played some soundtracks
that i've never heard before
that actually
don't quite give me your sims vibe and
that was surprising
yeah
but okay so here we are
okay we'll start with this one though
okay so
let me give you a tour
from the sims that i've created this
time i have
uh yited myth and counsel
uh we are going with turducken this time
for this specific series of high school
and
yeah turducken
turducken is the three members the three
original members of horotoli
yeah can i grow up yeah i created her
from scratch again and one more thing
that i want to note is that i did not
use any
uh custom content so
i'm i might have been a little a little
bit more limited but i actually found
some good stuff i would say yeah
just by creating it
with you know in-game outfits that are
just in-game which is also by the way
maybe if you guys want to play sims with
these sims i put them on the gallery you
should be able to use them exactly the
way they are because i didn't use any
custom content
yeah so let me go for a little bit so
first of all you know the hair i found
this hairstyle that
okay here we have mixed uh bgm okay
uh this hairstyle
is i thought the most fitting one the
thing is like you know there's a
gradation but depending on like
uh which color you choose the greatest
graduation changes i liked um i like
this one too
but yeah i thought maybe this one is
still the closest
yeah i wish i could mix like some of
them
the way i want them oh i like this one
too but then i mean this is probably
still the closest i would say and then i
found one more that i gave her in other
outfits i don't always have the same
hairstyle
yeah um i'm not quite happy with my face
i might still work on that sometime but
oh well i'm happy with them
with the casual outfit because it looks
like my casual outfit and i got pretty
close i would say the choker uh was in
that color in in my casual outfit too
yeah
um yeah i had i had some good choices
for like
tops i went with this one in the end
because the boobies look quite nice oh
by the way so
they're they're all supposedly teenagers
okay
they're teenagers
um
but you know i don't know why i can't
edit this right now but
the sad thing is that teenagers don't
really look any different from
adults
in sims 4.
um but what i did is that you know
originally i wanted her to have like
badonka bodoka hips
uh but then i sized them down
uh to make her look a little bit more
teenagey
yeah you see here she's not as not as
badonkadonk
as i am
to give her a little bit more youthful
look yeah
okay
so that same goes for the other ones
although i kept reina quite mature i was
thinking you know she might have been
the type to mature early as a teenager
it was sure
uh okay let me
show you the outfits so this is one
yeah there's one casual and formal
i tried i found this dress and i thought
it kind of gives you the vibes of my
of my empress outfit and you know my
hair is more fluffy in that one so i
chose this fluffy hair
yeah this is um
this dress i felt like got pretty close
oh game of thrones vibes i guess yeah
but i can i could see some
like not similarities but at least
similar vibes yeah
yeah and i changed the makeup here i
gave myself this like feather makeup but
okay i was just playing around with this
one yeah
and we have sporty which i think is
hella cute booty shorts stick shoes six
sneakers
yeah yeah
and so that's some athletic and we have
oh yeah um
now
with myself i have you know input of
what i would wear to sleep and
you know i just wear panties but i can't
let her go topless
so we just did this yeah and yeah see
this braid hairstyle i basically have
that for my jendel
so that's nice
and here you see the the earrings which
are not really earrings but in this game
this is what i can do this is all i can
do
uh but yeah that hairstyle actually
you know i thought you know for sleeping
putting up the hair to have like when
you wake up have this fluffy hair makes
sense um
and then here you go this is the other
hairstyle i was talking about
uh this is now party party outfit
yeah now i i kind of let my personal
taste
influence
my own outfits
in some places like i would totally wear
this
yeah i think i have a dress like this
and yeah this is the other hairstyle
um the thing is you know there's other
colors here too
and i wanted to do this one but i i
guess that there's probably a way around
it but when i change it to this
then it changes this one too
there's probably a way around it but
that's why i went for this one for now
well
yeah
so
that's a different hairstyle cute right
and i love these flat
black scenes i i used to own a pair like
that but they broke they fell apart i
need a new flat pair of like elegant
looking shoes like that i need to buy a
new pair
um and here we have my swimsuit i was
the last character i created so at this
point i was like [\h__\h] it i'm not even
trying to make it look like anybody
anymore although the swimsuit you know
it's like my
more or less official swimsuit
yeah and with the hair i found this fun
hairstyle and you know i i have like
different colors in my hair so i thought
why the hell not it's like when kiwawa
add this to my lore when kiwama's hair
gets wet
it's like you know one of those
color-changing mugs
or so
it changes colors like this and gets all
crazy how about that how about that
mood ring hair oh
no dead okay
and then here we have just the hot
weather where yeah again at this point
you know this could already be hot
weather wear easily so but i didn't want
to repeat it so i just went with
whatever
um but here you have the glasses that i
have in my casual outfit
and again the braid hairstyle because in
the hot weather you want to have your
hair up
it's less hot
yeah so there are some things that i
kept similar and some things that are
just personal taste
um
a fashion review yeah here's my my
cold weather where i again
personal taste
not
not necessarily how kiwa would dress
maybe
[Laughter]
but maybe maybe it is i don't know i
like i like it i like this look
um i tried i tried to give all three of
them
a different look and it wasn't difficult
because i just feel like we all would
wear such
different things
so kiwa is like kind of the
i don't know how to describe this the
puppy
poppy hip hey
cause i'm so hip poppy hip cute style
but still you know comfy
and then and then who do you want to see
next super duper rainy
cause reyna is here let's look at elena
let's not waste her time oh [\h__\h] that's
her oh oh yeah she's in her um pajamas
right now okay so here we start
reina is like the more elegant um but
also
i mix some some other non-elegant
elements maybe i don't know
yeah
so kind of like elegant and mature
i think she turned out so pretty i gave
her several hairstyles too
and those earrings were perfect
now i think she's so pretty i love that
outfit it worked so well for the top i
was really not sure though because there
were several ones that kind of would
have worked well
you know i ended up going for this one
the pants noise everything perfect look
at her
right looks accurate that's her casual
outfit and i made another one
uh it's the same but just with the short
hair because actually she has short hair
with this casual outfit
but i didn't quite like the choices for
in a short hair
like but this does kind of get close
enough because she does have her
her um ear out on one side
and i gave her glasses and i gave her
some nice earrings
but it's mostly the same as the other
it's just two variations yeah
yeah
so reyna can basically cut her hair off
and grow it back in an instant oh i
asked her what um inspiration she wants
and she told me after i created the
simpson let me change it now she said
she even wants um i let her pick it out
let her pick it out from a whole list
she said she even wants best-selling
offer creativity or angling ace
fishing aspiration wait where is the is
it this one fishing
actually i used to be funny i guess but
i think for going to school the offer
thing could work quite well because we
gotta be like on the pc and stuff anyway
yeah fanfiction fanfiction writer and i
see where she's going wishing she was
fishing
she can sell fish as a hobby
uh where was this this one here i think
um best-selling offer the other one is
musical genius master actress painter
expert yeah we're going for this one oh
yeah for chihuahua by the way let me go
back for a second
i gave myself the cooking aspiration
master chef sim wants to master the
culinary arts
and
yeah uh
yeah i also gave myself foodie
these sims become happy and have fun
when eating good food become
uncomfortable and eating bad food and
can launch cooking shows for ideas i
just wanted to make the the free sims
just very very different
um
to be honest my life aspiration is not
becoming a master chef but you know
kiara it's takanasi kiwawa so let's have
her become a master chef
let's stay in character oh and cheerful
these sims tend to be happier than other
sims
go back to elena
so we have now best-selling offer
uh
and then i gave her also animal
enthusiast
that one i gave her on my own
these sims are obsessed with animals and
will seek their company often they will
have an easier time caring for animals
and getting closer to them and goofball
now when they grow up they get another
um one more um thingy
and i will give her a romantic den the
reason i didn't give her a romantic now
is because she's a teenager
we don't know she's still a teenager
i don't know how she acted as a teenager
but i would say you know
oh
she maybe wasn't
you know maybe maybe she was hiding it
back then
i don't know
but for now for now she's still still
you know very satisfying only thinking
about
um animals
and goofballs these sims tend to be
playful yeah yeah okay so looking at the
rest of the outfits uh we have formal
which she looks like elsa now i know i'm
sorry i wasn't sure what to do with
formal so i just wanted her to look um
gorgeous
like she is gorgeous
yeah the hair as well yeah i think i
think you know this kind of looked good
i tried to keep her colors at least like
blueish colors and i don't know
also i maybe pay attention to the nails
i i i gave her nails i gave all of us
except super nails like nice nails here
she actually has
some very similar nails that she
actually has with this outfit she has
like these green turquoise greenish
green bluish
uh nails
and i gave her like also they're longer
you can now give them longer nails
yeah
i gave her some fitting nails i would
like to pay attention to that
yeah
and then uh here's sporty
i don't know at least it has all like
you know her colors i thought i thought
it was okay
i feel like she would
i feel like lana would wear this for
sporty yeah kind of cool
very cool yeah nice color coordination i
would say
and then we have uh her sleeping attire
i thought you know she would like it to
be more comfy
and um not completely naked and and also
i gave her a hair updo like a like a
like
actually not an updo i guess a
ponytail thingy that i thought would
kind of make sense lengthwise
and all that
i think it looks nice
wait [\h__\h] she has black hair i just
noticed oh you're right they added leg
hair
what the [\h__\h] i just i didn't see that
because it's like gray
that's a new feature
i thought how did i get rid of that i
know that you can shave in the game
though
so i guess we'll just shave
what the [\h__\h] i didn't notice that until
now do you guys see that it's probably
hard to see for you guys
yeah they added leg hair and facial hair
and back hair oh god i hope she doesn't
have it back here
[Music]
no
i don't see back hair i only see leg
hair
[Laughter]
i mean i mean it's natural i guess but
we have to shave that now party attire i
went with a dark
dark um blue
and also i gave her dark blue makeup i
think she looks hot
very good
also nails again
pretty nails
mustache chicken
yeah i think everybody can get all kinds
of um
uh
yeah
um like lady ladies can grow beards now
i think
which
i i can't do that but sims can do that
now
yeah yeah very very um
strong makeup like the others don't have
this strong makeup it's only raining
because she's a bit more mature you know
for her age
then we have swimwear just a blue
swimsuit
and then did i miss any secondary
outfits no okay oh i like this one
it's a short version see
a short version of her normal casual
outfit
and a bit more like
hipster cool
right i also gave her like a different
shortcut
same shoes and all that and then the
pants it looks so similar but it's just
shorter
[Music]
i like it too eat a chocolate
with some golden
accessories some sick glasses
oh yeah
can inspire a lot of fan art oh i
wouldn't mind i wouldn't mind
and then for a warm this is just i don't
know i didn't really find anything for
them but like i could see you
i could see dana in this i think yeah
whatever
okay next up is uh
don't don't look at subaru in
in pajamas embarrassing here's that
outfit
[\h__\h] what
they didn't they she did not have that
arm hair when i was first creating her
that just happened because i already
loaded her into the world i think
ew can i how do you how do you get rid
of this
ah back hair leg hair oh dear lord okay
no
no i can tell you subaru does not have
that much
no enable hair oh you know what yeah
let's get rid of it completely why does
it not disappear
oh there you go now it's gone
okay
thank god can we do the same with reyna
um
okay
normal leg hair
i mean it's i like the feature but you
know my idols have to be perfect
you know no no body hair for them
that's not hair that's better
i'm getting rid of it here too
shocking
ah here
so
realistic kiwa did not grow any hair
in that short amount of time because
kimono actually uh
yeah
quinoa got rid of all her body hair
well almost all of it
okay ew just look at that
thanks sims for adding that you know i
want to play around with that maybe on a
on a dude yeah
uh i think that adds a lot to a dude sim
um cause they were always like so
perfectly you know baby skinned
now you can give dudes all these
different kinds of yeah look at those
look at dolls look at those
yeah ooh
wow
fuzzy like a caterpillar
yeah okay so yeah yeah yeah i turned off
the the hair growth now now we're good
okay so
but it was a bit difficult because
um you know first i tried to recreate
the the very first default outfit
um but for t-shirts
like for these kind of t-shirts
there was not so much good variation
like i wanted a white t-shirt with you
know orange white light lime green
elements and all that but this was the
kind of the closest i could get also
there is no such thing as two different
socks
yeah and the hat also unfortunately
that's the best choice the one color
orange hat
backwards forward hats there's much more
options but backward hats barely any
options
lala but i think the shoes are quite
well
yeah and then i gave her however a
second outfit now i don't think it
turned out well either
but this is now trying to be a bit more
like her most recent casual outfit
[Music]
if you compare it it does get quite
close
but in terms of you know when i look at
this skirt and all that and the shirts
the texturing the shading
kind of froze me off
even though it does get pretty close
um
it is super close i know but
somehow it looks like [\h__\h] to me
yeah well well now the hair also hair
was really difficult
having like you know she has
uh long twin towels long straight twin
tails and long straight uh normal hair
in that outfit so i went for the long
straight normal hair but it doesn't get
any longer or straighter than this this
is the best choice
i need more hairstyles but this is a
problem because i didn't use custom
contents
which i also kind of tried to
lean on to
this look
then that outfit
also kind of similar there's not a
single beret in the game i was shocked
this hat
is not really a beret but
the closest i could find wait now it's
um
where is it
i don't know where it is there but
there's no bara
we're gonna go
there's no beret though i'm so mad like
i love berets why is it
i don't know
but you know she has that beret in that
outfit and i really wanted to give her
the ray and i don't like the other hats
with the
with the um you know the what do you
call it brim brimmed
yeah
because that's not a beret a beret has
no brim dude
oh well so then we have um i like the
sports outfit yo
i like it
i like
what i combined there you know the
bright yellow with blue
and
you know
sporty um modern cool
style mm-hmm
i think it suits her well yeah
yeah
then we have a sleepy style i thought
um
maybe
just a shirt
on top
and then we have party i don't know why
i three times three times i tried to get
close to that one outfit that she has
with the high waisted
skirt uh the high-waisted long skirt and
the blouse underneath
yeah i should probably give her
something else but i don't know
i don't know
i'm not so happy with this one
this one is cute it is cute but it
doesn't necessarily look like what it
was supposed to look like
um but then oh here we have swimwear i
thought somebody would wear some shorts
with the swimsuit also she's ripped hell
yeah
and she would still wear a cap because
she loves caps
[Music]
a little preview the whole live summer
yeah
and then we have oh i love this one hot
summer outfit
absolutely love it the the sandals with
the little bow it's hard to see but
i thought that's very subaruish like she
combines sporty with cute you know
sporty with cute and comfy
yeah i gave her some fun necklace
as well
that's the catty necklace there and some
minecraft stuff
gamer
also i barely or yeah not really i
barely gave her makeup because i thought
super doing no makeup is good
and here we have a worm
uh cold weather which i like really a
lot too um
it's uh
you know
skinny jeans
and a comfy
big
cropped
parker
i really like it with the beanie
i i i love this outfit on her
couldn't admit just ski yeah cold
weather is still exposed yeah it doesn't
get that cold where we're gonna live and
at least that's what i decided
yeah
i love this because it also has kind of
like
sporty vibes a little bit i think it
fits her and for her inspirations we
have
extreme sports enthusiasts
this sim wants to explore mountain
commode wilderness and participate in
extreme snow sports now it might not be
100 accurate you know there might have
been others that may have been more
accurate for subaru but i just thought
it would be fun and fitting for her
anyway
um like we can actually send her to the
mountain to do some stuff to climb the
mountain um yeah she's gonna be very
active that's why i also gave her active
these seams tend to be energized can
pump up other sims and maybe become
upset if they don't exercise for a
period of time because you know she
dances so much she's really an active
person so
and then
cheerful and also i gave them by the way
i gave them some like likes and stuff
like for her i did comedy dancing
fitness media production aka youtubing
and video gaming and then
for example for lana i did
i did uh dj mixing because she did dj
before yeah singing and writing
and for me i gave myself
baking cooking dancing painting
singing that's it
so i'm gonna be basically the
chef
of the group
elena is gonna be the
money maker because she's gonna write
fanfictions and hopefully bring us some
money
and somebody's just gonna have fun
add fishing oh yeah i think i can do
that yeah yeah
because we didn't use it as an
aspiration now so we can just add it
here
fishing
[Music]
i was wondering like i wanted to do this
because of keyboards but programming you
know it's not really
about that i guess
and it was not really anything that
would work well i guess maybe handing
him so i'm not sure
um
don't think you can bring money with fan
fiction um sure she can
she can't she's that's literally what
she's doing now people give her super
chats in her streams when she does
fanfiction stuff so
that's one way of making money
yeah she literally can
[Laughter]
nana can't do anything she wants to do
so yeah that was our
my
turd duncan sims that i created
yesterday
yeah
gosh i love her hot weather outfit
it kind of looks like a k-pop star
uh
[Music]
my god but yeah
i need to buy some
buy i need to get some
custom content for subaru eventually
yeah
so these are up on the library i think
on the
online library if you want to get them
okay
now
we
can go to high school
in this pack
so
that's what we'll be doing eventually
[Music]
okay
oh so oh yeah i got us a little house
surprise surprise surprise i got his
little house
let me show you
i will
show you around my desk afternoon there
we go
oh [\h__\h] yeah ignore that this is my
house i ran i chose one from the library
and then i renovated it
changed uh some furniture and changed
the
out like the wallpapers and floors
so i did
give it my own
you know
taste and now i'm out of money so i hope
my sims make uh some money
oh yeah double bgm right now
also i'm lagging i'm lagging
i'm landing
stop lagging iwa
so let me show you around
that's the usual room we have a little
bird's house outside also it's a very
small house so hopefully we can upgrade
it sometime but here we have a little
shitty kitchen
yeah shitty kitchen
there's barely any space we have here a
little little pc area
pc is nice this cute girly pc some bird
pictures here
i don't know what that is like
yeah then we have here a little eating
area who knows if sim's gonna use that
normally not
i changed the flooring and all that to
in the walls
oh
but these were from before i don't like
them
get rid of them one of these red arrows
it's a starter home
but it was a i think it's a pretty good
one already
to like begin with
uh here we have the bathroom
change the amenities here a little bit
too
here we have chiara and reyna room
together with a nice
uh people
uh rug yeah
and that's back to the classics hell
yeah we have a really cool
wallpaper in here and somebody because
somebody is our senpai she gets uh her
own
bedroom small one small but at least
it's her own space you know
and you know how she won already so many
athletics prices there as you can see
yeah
so that's the
tiny
house that we're living in
okay
so let's hope all goes well because i
heard that there's some problems with um
the game since the update came
[Laughter]
yeah apparently there's some issues
there oh well so i literally i just
placed them here and then i tested if
the beds work and that's it that's all i
did
so they don't really know each other yet
i'm actually surprised teenagers can
live with each other alone without an
adult
that's pretty surprising
yeah oh
i'm so lacking
huh
i didn't i'm so lying is it because the
game resources
nah
i'm playing windowed but pretty big size
oh well that's fine no it's fine again
uh the first objective i don't know
tomorrow will be the first day of school
and then we'll see how it all goes
because we can follow them
to high school that's the thing
special thing right right it's some
class in 24 hours
and we need to do our homework so oh my
god it's been a long time since i played
damn
okay we can uh have super to start with
homework and then we have we'll get
reina and
what's y'all we'll get arena and oopsie
yeah
yes it
rain and uh me to get to know each other
a little bit first
huh what are you doing
chilling on the bed that doesn't look so
natural the way she's sitting are you
good
wait wait wait wait how about
uh
compliment appearance
by the way why does space not work
anymore as pausing why is it secret what
the [\h__\h] i think it i'm pretty sure it
used to be space bar
i tried to
see if there's like control change
anywhere but i couldn't find it
what
see
[Music]
has gotten her first taste of puberty
things will only continue to change from
here dana can try to manage puberty
changes with shaving to avoid out of
control body what we got rid of that
and skin care routine to help mitigate
the inevitable acne oh right now she
still looks fine
wait what
why am i floating hmm
it doesn't even answer to my flooding
why did i become flirtier
from attempting romans while in clean
surroundings canada is feeling as fresh
and clean as the room she's in
she's flirty because the room is clean
roman sounds a lot better and everyone
can enjoy a dust-free ambience
what it's because i renovated
[Music]
okay i didn't think that i would be the
one
[Applause]
i see okay how about
well gonna vent a little bit of our
puberty problems yeah yeah yeah
sharon is the niece
what what's your problem maybe maybe
can help you out
oh
[Music]
that's wonderful
that was easy uh
wow
heartfelt
confess daydream of a question you [\h__\h]
disgusted the chicken came first that's
a good question to ask you allah
oh
can we do a sexy pose while sitting what
[Music]
how about changing into your normal
outfit
i was so dark oh so dork she called me a
dork
ah that's much better
now we're both flirting
oh my god
discuss interest let's not go so fast we
literally just started
you
[Music]
mingle with us
how about
uh
i don't know tell a funny story come
join us about group
numbers they got quite a comedy skill
good job
[Music]
great i wonder if that's possible so
uh-huh
[Music]
and any interaction is fine to be honest
i just want them to get to know each
other oh oh somebody also got the comedy
skills course
[Music]
they always bring fruit uh hello did you
bring fruit cake to welcome us here who
are you morty mcguff he's a famous
person in sims let me talk to him
well no maybe not because then he will
come in and call me all the time and
annoy me
kiana is a foodie who seems like
obsessed with eating disgusting and
cooking high quality oh yeah i should
learn cooking to begin with because i
don't even have that skill uh
[\h__\h] we don't have uh
we do have a bookshelf
can i read them
because i gotta cook for this family you
know
but i don't see a
i don't see a cooking book
oh [\h__\h] maybe i just have to
try it without learning first okay hmm
surf brunch eggs on accent toss okay
come on we can do that
and then
uh so where are you going
oh somebody's playing games okay well
subaru you know wants to become
uh a beach over i would say
there's one more thing that they added
with uh the high school is a
occupation
dana is practicing a debate wow she's
such a good student
let me see i want to see how
this would work oh can we do it already
here
find a job is that also like part-time
jobs though
[Music]
uh you can use your phone here change
this here too oh
there's like new things you can also
like
like sell second-hand clothes and stuff
and buy second-hand clothes
[Music]
okay let's find a job maybe
oh she was gonna do push-ups
wow so proud of you savannah so active
your abs are amazing
okay so what do we have we have babies
oh fast food employee oh my god i should
do that i should do that one
is that actually after school yeah okay
5 p.m that's probably after school see
influencer
video game streamer i think that's the
one
[Music]
if i think that's the one playing video
games for fun is that the is that the
v-tubing thing
[Music]
i wonder what was this influencer
got a
webcam
blah blah blah
[Music]
i think maybe this is the one
sounds close enough
casual streamer
9 p.m to 11 p.m
20 per hour
not bad
we can try that at least some money
and she can do it for ah there we go yes
yes yes
[Music]
look look look
you can choose your sim tube avatar now
if you're on twitter you probably saw
this because i um we talked about it on
twitter
but turns out uh what was it creating
creative director or so like some some
director
from the game
uh like the top director of this pack of
this pack
she's
she said in the live stream where they
introduced this pack that her or she is
me
and then surprise surprise look at this
avatar that you can choose
orange hair chicken hat
that is
obviously a reference to me that looks
like gouda
some others i feel like also i see
similarities like that looks like
manners to me
and i mean you know they're obviously
not gonna be one-on-one completely
uh
completely obvious references
no i i know okay yeah but i think it
looks more like niana's than okay
i think
yeah then
i mean this could if you if you really
stretch it that could be kelly
[Laughter]
yeah yeah
that
that also
has similarities to
certain someone ah yeah yeah so i see
some similarities so but now we're doing
swadu so
i guess we'll just go hmm
none of these looks like subaru
so let's just go with the normal one oh
yeah so you are now
just a normal youtuber i guess
work assignment talk to a friend about
side hustle
what oh ah the side job you mean
should somebody ozara get us jump start
and accept the assignment of course
of course wait let's uh oh
let's talk
oh [\h__\h] i need to get used to this new
camera i changed to sims free camera
because it has this
this camera and i i think that's very
useful
let's ask
let's talk to dana
baru
uh
spread the word on side hustles okay do
that
so there's now a casual stream at
streamer corporate if her street she
starts monday is that today no tomorrow
okay at 9 pm okay
how's the cooking going kiwawa
[Music]
wow that looks delicious mmm oh yeah
oh yeah two dolls eggs around scramble
those eggs
[Music]
oh she's finished why is super
tense puberty also
oh no
somebody has gotten her first taste of
puberty okay it's the same text here is
some food at least
you're welcome
so we don't have to hunger
but i'm not really hungry yet so hmm i
will also
get a job i want that fast food uh job
actually
uh business
find a
job i want to get that one
we're gonna be pretty busy with school
maybe but i think it's good to also get
a job
just you know
we need to make money i'm not cheating
in this play forever
you know after i cheated so much in myth
for money i'm like it's boring
it's too easy and yeah we have to pay
the bills
earn a little spending money serving
food to people you know and wiping up
after them for a while table cleaner
oh man i hope we get more than the paper
table cleaner soon
cleaner at hamburger man okay the place
is called hamburger man not even though
do i have to and get some skills
get one skill to level two ah that's
that's for uh high school
and then for the the food job we don't
really need anything at the moment noise
okay
anyway
oh man it's always tough to control more
than one sim super do those browsing
books no no no no you need to like do
something for you know streaming how
about
how about social networking check social
media timeline
oh okay i was using the pc no we only
have one pc eventually we want free pcs
hopefully because this is a family that
is eventually all going to be streamers
maybe
i've posted on the pen pal phones you
don't need a pen pal you have to duck in
what else would you want wait dana wait
let me show off my outfit serena
anyway look look look at my hot outfit
we both look freaking hot way back
oh she's so supportive
oh he's sitting down okay
she's complaining about something let's
have a deep conversation with yana
about our future
well i totally agree
oh listen jackie
oh with venus so cute
[Music]
it looks so cute
panda lindsay nerska oh
and fobby narble i'm gonna frog
how is it on twitter what's going on
how about you please sims foreign
oh just remember we have to do our
homework
dana also has to do homework um
[Music]
what is that sign here
is it because we're talking
sentiments
oh yeah this is new too i think and none
more sentiment
is crushing hard on kiwawa what the [\h__\h]
new
[Music]
oh no she wants to prank the toilet no
please don't
we live together as free
we only have one toilet
please don't
thank you
you need to do your homework sorry i'm
like you know i'm not surprised anyway
you little [\h__\h]
i'm gonna make you go on to that verse
[Music]
when they do that
maybe there's an unprankable toilet or
something oh one more new thing that
they have that they brought back from
sims 2
or sims 3 as well
is these um wishes of what they want to
do apparently they're really repetitive
though
i'm not sure i heard they're really
repetitive
uh
well okay um if you do them you get some
extra points for like you know
aspirations and [\h__\h]
yeah
honey
you know what there's also prom maybe we
could have reina ask out kiwama for prom
sometimes since she has a crush a
natural crush i didn't even do anything
it wasn't me
chat with dana chat replaying a
compliment appearance now this is all
autonomous you know i'm not doing
anything here
it's just them
yes
okay and then oh somebody's getting
hungry so we can
grab a serving
also somebody wants to go for a jog and
listen to pop music
we currently don't have any workout
thingies for subaru
we need to get that at some point
ah
talking about cheese shell she's also on
the phone
it's just you know teenagers normals
normal teenagers
in their everyday life you guys need to
focus on your homework
do you want to ever eat
gold
[Music]
turds
i want to live with turn duck duncan
i want to live with them together
somewhere ah
it's jessica
hello
you're my favorite
see
what
what and someone's favorite youtuber you
know i was so excited to hear that like
set by someone
publicly like that in the stream
like i'm usually
not
i'm not complaining or anything but i'm
usually not
people's favorite because i'm not so
mainstream you
ah that's know but i was just so
flattered tonight when i heard that
thank you oh so happy
thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you so much
i'm glad you made it to the stream
yeah
you're my favorite i know i'm your
guys's favorite but you know
is a cheerful soon cheerful sims tend to
be happy more often yeah yeah yeah kiwa
also needs to go to the toilet but let's
eat first and have
later go to the toilet that she pranked
herself need to finish this homework
come on come on
use
after that after that go go go go go
oh no
this is gonna be a love triangle
somebody has a crush on it
and it has a crush on kewala
who is
gonna crush on
oh no
i did not expect or anticipate a love
triangle between turtle king
[Music]
oh no
and now she's going on the toilet did
she prank oh no
you know
you have to fix that
you fixed you you did your homework nice
but yeah yeah you can't go on there
because
prepare go
okay
you ever gonna eat first fix it
somebody was uncomfortable because of
that [\h__\h]
that's not i didn't mean it that
literally but you know
oh man
repairing the toilet in that outfit is
there a problem
okay look at somebody looking at her
crush
smell hi
[Music]
oh she's like oh i i wish i wish i could
tell later what i feel for her
literally like she's
look at her lip
what are you feeling
[Music]
ask what happened
wait
this is
is this gonna be sad like
having swells see how late it
confesses her crush to qiwaba and it
will break someone's heart oh no
oh no
that would be
really really bad
oh you wanna eat you wanna eat the toast
close to subaru
we really all have to go in here
eat
your freaking food
where did you put your food
handy not dandy
[Laughter]
slinging hammers and nails left and
right is not in this cup of t-shirt
laying advantage to self-abuse and admit
that she dislikes handiness yes because
i think that's very fitting
i mean handiness as in making keyboards
she likes but
toilets repairing toilets
and uh
um
did you really eat that wouldn't it
she's still eating okay
um so is that fixed now
okay okay okay
get out of the way just go somewhere
i didn't you didn't eat yet grab a
serving now can we all just leave the
toilet room so that kiwa can
go to the toilet
while she's eating i guess no give me a
second
thank god that was close
that was a close one
okay
okay okay now everyone ate so let's put
that into the fridge
[Music]
a dainty sneeze what's that you so much
okay well it's gonna polish to
perfection okay because
chihuahua
is gonna take care of this place she's
gonna take care of these peeps here
as if it were her daughters
oh oh yeah
oh no wait i thought it was on kiwa now
it's super new subaru is polishing sorry
sorry
okay
well it's uh 8 p.m
what can we do let's i want to
get a skill up for school how about we
uh
practice dancing oh
hey yo
good idea i think i gave kiwella the
likes dancing treat
toilets
what are you doing
view something outside
what are you looking at
by the way you should add birdseed here
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
she needs to she oh
she needs to pee so badly oh oh
yo
let's go get those abs what happened to
the dancing though
did you already stop
more dancing go go
go go
subaru once fit this equipment i think
we can afford something
i think
i think we can buy subaru something to
work out with
[Music]
uh wait which where would that be again
oh yeah oh basketball
what should we get somebody to work out
liv
something that fits outside maybe like i
don't know if i want to put a running
machine outside but a basketball court
would be dope
super shop basketball super shot wall
hoop
hell yeah that would work i think
basketball i'm gonna oh yeah we can put
it here nice why not
[Music]
let me test that
oh
dream big is an option
practice dribbling okay practice show me
show me what you got but in the rain
it's okay
it do be like that oh
you're going on too
you're also gonna practice dribbling
whoa hey yo
oh oh rain is going to join too
what
uh
wait
while i swooning over crush
wait when did you get a crush
you don't have a crush
do you
what i wasn't updated about a crush who
who are you crushing on wait
i mean that's not you don't have a crush
on her
got it
i really want her to have a crush on
maybe both
so that
kiwama would be like oh [\h__\h] i don't
know what to do i love them both so much
what should i do
can we do that
he needs to crush him yeah that would be
the perfect love triangle
yeah
maybe we need to you know interact more
with subaru to make that happen
ask about romantic interests
[Laughter]
give props
you know we can also talk normally you
know
ask
dancing we both like dancing you know
[Music]
what he's doing what are you doing it
looks so cute though
stop taking those selfies kiwawa and
talk to somebody
our dramatic love triangle happen
what what she just canceled everything i
guess because stupid was busy
she can't do it right now then i wanted
i want you guys to talk to with each
other though a tell joke about penguins
okay kayla
uh
give props
here we need to talk when you're talking
oh social bunny i don't care about that
right now no i have my hands full
ben's protagonist
she does look like a dance protagonist
sula hello
[Music]
maybe she doesn't know yet
she's feeling loved but she's not sure
about it you know
reyna enjoyed the conversation because
she's worried about her crush falling in
love with someone else
and someone who has left a chance
oh she's mopping oh cleaning
oh
thank you subaru
oh everybody is flirty now oh [\h__\h] wait
what
dreamy eyes super just got her crush on
her mind yeah but superman is crushing
on dana right yeah
uh
everybody's flirty
[Music]
how did you know that that's your bed i
didn't even assign them yet but let me
assign um
uh
this is gonna be oh wait it's
ready assigned oh i didn't even do that
magical i think it's sleepy time
i think it's time to sleep so that we
get up early cause school starts
when
uh
8 a.m okay
okay let's sleep guys
good night
nice
we got to know each other
fine on the first day we also fell in
love with each other
i really did not expect that what the
[\h__\h] these teenagers are so horny
so horny
get your [\h__\h] together
focus on school focus on your grades man
love at first sight yeah first day first
day
we will have some teenage pregnancies
man
a good morning everybody uh let me see
how is it looking how's it looking uh oh
yeah you're hungry that's okay because
we got food in the fridge you're already
taking something aren't you oh
stretch oh
chat with kiwawa you want to chat love
you all another tool no stretching let's
um
get leftovers
react to first purity
oh no
oh no is it the return of acne in my
life
she just reacted no i have a pimple
ah
this gives me ptsd
[Music]
i have two people oh for oh no i have a
lot of pimples [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
no
okay can i clean my face or something i
mean it doesn't [\h__\h] help though
conceal acne apply facial cleanser okay
let's let's apply a facial cleanser
and um and then we can conceal them but
we also have to take a shower
we gotta go to school in two hours oh
what that's not cleanser
that's not a cleanser that's powder
okay uh
wait um
shower doesn't work let me use the
shower
i know okay
uh take a brisk shower
you're cooking something oh please don't
burn the kitchen gulper
it looks good what's your make
mac and cheese blackened
cheese oh
thank you subaru i'm supposed to be the
cookie oh
don't take that away from me
okay
she's she's eating it okay
newbie yummy it does look yummy yeah
now i kind of want some meat too
hmm
okay well i guess i gave up on showering
so how about
no wait how about elena take a shower
first
go go go go no
why are you guys oh i think i can't use
it
did i place it weirdly
[Music]
i think i have moved objects on when i
did oh
okay yeah
i thought this works
[Music]
ah
originally this was actually
no
let me
see if i can do that
[Music]
okay
no i can't use this one
ah okay whatever it fits so perfectly
but oh well i'll use um like a normal
shower
here
like a one one tile shower
oh i could even use two of those no no i
can't wait what's the problem i guess we
have to do
like this
wait what
what are you in winter
that works
[Music]
okay but this one probably breaks so
often
oh oh i like the invisible shell of
those
hygiene free hygiene fuller
reliability free reliability
okay what the [\h__\h]
are we using this one wait what
okay here it works
okay we have this shitty shower now
i'm sorry you girls gotta live with this
for now
it's the math in the white hill
is it
no
something's up with the walls
[Music]
something's blocking oh there's nothing
here except the lamp but the lamp is on
the left side
oh well
it's okay
we use
okay
yeah we use this one for now
the door
there's no there's
it's okay
who needs to shower
you you need to shower
subaru
i know oh oh oh dana's showering now
super duper
not again i thought you were gonna
shower in it you're dissupporting me
okay
i thought we could have a moment where
somebody would walk in accidentally on
daniel showering but i guess not
okay
can we get everybody ready for school
like yo
uh
i don't know how it's gonna work it's
the first time but oh look she changed
into the other outfit
oh
we see two sides of superhero now
my god can we get a quick shower like a
screen shower go go go go go go
i think the only one who didn't shower
is elena but she's okay she's not stinky
she'll be fine look at the bath look
it's a burp hot spot
oh oh oh select which students to follow
okay so now it's time it is time oh yeah
okay
it goes on school time
turn talking goes to school
ah
who's gonna get the best grades
who's gonna be the popular kid who's
gonna get bullied
okay welcome to school
so let me oh they're already playing
michael what's that again
football right
football
full spy but not quite
so this is the school we have like a
cafeteria oh what's that burgers and
fries and
some salad salads and sandwiches some
i don't know what all that stuff is
i'm hungry
we have the
toilets
we have i think there's a principal's
office
a waiting lounge we have a classroom
here
and we have another classroom over there
and what's that library or just a chill
place for students to
uh
learn
and more toilets and then we have a
second floor
oh art class i don't know
i can use the
oh can you even use the piano here oh
and the microphone oh
i don't think they actually have music
classes here it's just like you can use
it if you want to learn something i
guess
in your free time
okay
and then
wow it's so dark
but
you have this huge
field out here
yeah
i think you can run around there well
yeah okay okay okay
so
what we have to do morning free time
ends in two hours it's morning before
class the students are gathering a lift
to their own devices grab what you need
from your locker and feel oh your locker
lockers oh yeah we can claim our locker
don't forget to make it to class before
the bell rings learn about new school
from principal okay
okay can we can we like all together
uh i forgot how you form a group in this
game oh are we a grub though
oh yeah go here together i just said go
here together i guess we are a girl
so let's uh go here together
and talk to the principal let's try time
passes vine sims very fast like two
hours and sims time
isn't re real time like
uh two minutes
literally
yeah we have our group okay okay can we
like talk together um
yeah
i guess we have to introduce ourselves
first
okay
friendly introduction
friendly instruction
okay we are here we have arrived hello
oh we are the new kids we're turducken
when we
uh come here there's trouble so
yeah be prepared turducken brings
nothing but trouble to the school we
will
destroy school why are you playing
computer games what the [\h__\h]
drop out of high school no that's too
fast learn about new school is she going
to tell us alma do we have to do it
three times
[Music]
did we learn
no we didn't learn
there we go
ah okay she said it only too dina
let me learn then
learn about your school
and
[Music]
wow this principle takes a job real
serious hello free new students famous
students mind you right in front of you
pay attention to us please
we have one minute left wait okay wait
wait uh reyna is done reina learned
about it so let's get elena a locker
lock
locker claim locker ownership
oh subway is ready too
subaru wants to go to the toilet no no
no wait get yourself a locker
did you do it
there we go get yourself a locker can i
and
i guess i'll get a locker here maybe
okay
oh no my locker is so far away i want to
walk right next to you
okay she did but we can add some ooh
sporty decorations
dana will can we have romantic
decorations
where we have gamer document anime anime
decorations oh kawaii decorations
how would reina decorate her locker
maybe anime
um
what do you think golf
kawaii yeah uh she's been golf recently
really
i'll give i'll do some anime decorations
yay
oh that's lena's locker
cut
okay okay
also
decorate locker
[Music]
i wanna i wanna see what the preppy ones
look like
let me see i think i can still change
them
uh-huh
wow
outside i you know like in in my school
times we never like really decorated our
lockers like this if anything on the
inside a little bit but not really
though nobody really did that
and i was in various schools you guys
actually do that
oh sporty decorations
ah nice to battle what else can you do
with the locker
buy a football
grab an apple oh you can have like a
little snack there nice i guess there's
unlimited apples there
usually the inside here too yeah i guess
they probably just did it outside so
it's like easily visible in the game
i like it it's cute
and a pain to clean
i always had so much [\h__\h] in my locker
god
go
maybe maybe maybe somebody should buy a
football
get that football
oh
fifty dollars fifty dollars our football
is really that expensive though
okay morning free time ends in 40
minutes that's 30 seconds so let's go to
the classroom which one will be our
classroom though
that's actually a good question
which one will be our classroom
maybe we just sit here together i hope
it's the right classroom
i think the other one doesn't give me an
ah
don't be late
you know it takes sims a long time to
get to where they need to go
different class
i even said go here together wait do we
actually have a different class
oh no
wait kiana is going to the other class
now
oh
yoshi baka you're not going to make it
in time
turducken
don't be late don't be like quinoa
because they're really strict about it
by the way i saw they're really straight
thank you where the [\h__\h] are you
you're [\h__\h] slow seven
six
five
[Laughter]
she's in the room she's in the room
did that count did that count
does it count
did you make it yes you made it they all
made it oh yeah
oh yeah turducken in school i'm on
second row hell yeah i don't like
sitting in the first row
i have i have the
no if i was one more seat behind that
would be the anime protagonist no
i'm like the the the side character that
sits in front of the anime protagonist
um
front row nobody sits in the front row
in animes
how do i take uh hi get rid of the
the ui again do you guys know i forgot i
want to take a screenshot i wasn't again
let's escape it wasn't escape was it
i forgot about the pgm
yeah near the window near the window and
as back as far back as possible
it wasn't an f key i mean i guess uh
what oh
no
it doesn't work
tap tap
tap aha
okay
they don't look so good right now
nemo
hey girl barb ahoy grush
oh yes totally listening i mean elena's
just fantasizing right now she's totally
just friends deciding about kiana
they're already over
what
oh
we're trying to learn [\h__\h] here is that
does it always happen on the first day
uh-huh why are we we're so chill about
it though because it's obviously just a
fake one right it's just a fake one
quiet the logic scale okay where are you
girls going
why are we always going separate ways
[Music]
girls girls don't get burnt
also was totally not me what
they're going to the other class
what are they doing
[Music]
dude are they going to the next class
fire drill ends in one hour though
[Music]
if i could okay now you're huh
now you're kind of late if this was a
real fire you know i have to go back in
and then rescue you oh my god oh i'm
talking to you
i'm talking to a fire dude he's like
girl kiwawa i know you're phoenix but
you have to stop starting the fires
today
[Music]
please stop streaming spanx speaks
sparks streaming i can't
talk
i am so sorry
oh not really not really though
i'm sorry
no i'm not all right
and i am gone this week
can i go to the toilet even though we
have to be outside
[Music]
everyone's chilling here now
because she has a crush on you come on
oh oh no we're done we're going back
i want to talk a little bit though
wrong where were you guys going okay i'm
going to the toilet now
i'm ignoring the fire drill and we're
all safe anyway i'm the one who started
to fire anywhere so
i'm safe watson watson watson watson
galbadore
that's a watson oh the granny
[Music]
we barely even had like any classes
right now
okay let's already go
go here together
best time best time in school lunchtime
yeah food food food food food food food
food time
did you got a toilet okay where is the
lunch lady
i need my food maybe i need to become
the lunch lady
hello i cannot wait forever for my food
come faster
i ever ever
what am i doing practice debate no no
it's full time now order food fried
chicken slider
for the food
uh what would subado order hotadoku hell
yeah sausage fight you know
[Music]
chicken slider because she loves kiwa
she wants the chicken
or the phoenix obviously
no we need to sit on the same table
the food looks good
it actually looks good
[Music]
okay
what do you have
yummy they look good
oh they made new proper food for this
pack and it actually looks good
danny will you sit next to quinoa please
this seems to be oh wait somebody's
coming over
and this is this is the popular table
now
yeah oh
no more eating by myself no all by
look we're together
look at my eating face oh my god
not not very flattering
it's not there
let me take a nice screenshot
um
can you have a better face
that's okay that's okay
oh [\h__\h]
i don't know
oh you already finished your food no
[Music]
okay
taking screenshots
[Music]
hell yeah
turducken in school
[Music]
[Applause]
motivated okay are we going uh in one
hour we're going back to class i guess
okay
oh some some dude we don't know is
joining us but you know these birds are
very social
so i don't wait someone who i thought
there was someone who was gone
oh okay okay private time scuzzy
is being a good student and browsing
books wait i need to be oh wait be
friendly with a faculty member do they
mean like the lunch lady
okay let me do that let's have a
successful day at school
friendly pay yourself some time
oh friendly let's be friendly for the
need being for landoni
oh now suddenly everybody's been maybe
where
ah we never had like i guess no wait we
did have lunch ladies
we did have lunch ladies i guess but
like no no cafeteria
only like some some
stuff like sandwiches some snacks like
chocolate
[Music]
but i was just thinking if we're nice to
the lunch lady if it's a cafeteria she
might you know give you more food
we never had a cup of material like this
and do you guys have cafeterias like
this in your school
[Music]
wait that didn't count as being friendly
oh well it's back i don't know what you
did it's time to go back to
class are you guys gonna go
yes attend science class
uh
so whether would you also like to attend
science class get ready okay okay oh
they're actually doing it on their own
pretty much there we
go okay this is my seat here not here
now
much larger tables more crowded
[Music]
quite common in usa it seems so hey
hey i kind of want to experience that i
also kind of always wanted to experience
japanese school i wanted to do like a
year overseas in japan but
it never worked out
never got accepted for
a year overseas
that's so sad wait wait i want to take
more pictures
[Music]
okay okay
here i am i'm ready to take pictures
i wish they would sit closer together
for example in one row would be perfect
okay
[Music]
look at her studying
so proud of yuki kiwala i erased that
girl because it's me
oh interesting
is in the first row the second time in a
row
she's so motivated
you don't have assigned seats no um i
think i got that too like in school
there was like one home class that we
would always be in but then for some
classes we would go into a different
classroom and then the the seats there
were free free to choose
but i think here you can't choose like a
permanent seat which is fine
it's fine
[Music]
oh yeah okay it only gets checked after
you done with one completely
[Music]
free seats are the best no i like having
my own seat because like i would usually
put like a lot of [\h__\h] under the table
and also scribble on my table
and i don't know i just want my own seat
i was always usually usually in actual
school my seat uh was like um
independence for some
[Music]
years i was in the very very very very
very back row and we had like five rows
or so
very bad bro with like five of my best
friends
yeah
and then at some point before that a few
years before that i was in the middle of
row on the
very right at the wall which i love
because it was great for naps
yeah you don't stand out so much when
you're like on the very edge of the of
the room
five friends that's crazy
hey
the back is fun yeah yeah the bag is fun
usually like i in the first few years i
noticed that only the cool kids who
don't care about school or in the back
but then later uh when when we got a new
classroom and we got new seats me and my
friends we ran to the last road to make
sure that we definitely get the last row
for ourselves
yeah because we always wanted to go
there and it was always occupied by
others but
yeah yeah yeah we managed to get it and
then
and then yeah we made our corner back
there it was nice and oh i also actually
know i did have i did have one year my
last year of school
uh
of art my last year of art school i was
in the first row
uh second table like left on the wall
was my very unpopular friend
and next to her was very unpopular me
okay it wasn't that unpopular but at
least not an art school
um
yeah yeah oh and then later in hotel
school
i was
the layout was kind of weird in that
school weren't many many students either
but i was like in the second row middle
seat or so
yeah
oh i'm getting hungry
so basically i tried out everywhere
actually in my in my school time i was
in the middle i was in the corner i was
in the back i was in the front i was in
the everywhere
hmm
i could have quite some variety you know
i didn't remember all this
because it's so engraved in my memories
i was not a school bullying what the
[\h__\h]
i was the one being bullied if anything
joking wait wait what's uh i want to see
feeling happy and pretty tasty
oh
the food here apparently is pretty tasty
feeling fulfilled kenna checks one more
task off the list of things she wants to
do
and she's now gonna play just apparently
i think we're done with school for today
end of day report
the teachers have collected homework oh
and dismissed their students some sins
are still hanging around but
everyone is free to head home after
noting how students performed in their
homework and in class here's how
everyone did
okay everybody did the same we all
impressed our teachers and learned a lot
yay
a plus students
students
i'm so proud
i'm so broad wait now there's showers
here oh dana can take a shower at school
nice
but
um
3 p.m i think at 5 00 pm kiwawa has your
job right
uh
yeah 5 p.m
start ah but ah not today working three
days ah
and then uh dana has currently no job
and then six hours for subaru until she
has to work yeah you might want to take
a shower too
we'll take that shower hell yeah take a
same shower room is there
[Music]
ah no it's separate okay
[Laughter]
go go somebody will take the shower next
to her
[Music]
yeah
oh no so far apart so close yet still so
far
but somebody you're taking a shower at
the same time as elena how does that
make you feel
or rather rather rat oh there's so much
workout equipment
oh
[Music]
let's get some cardio going oh yeah
nina play chess with me
[Music]
come on
play chess with me
[Music]
it's
just ah i wish this was reality
[Music]
i mean we can make this a reality of
course playing chess
[Music]
but i mean like you know going to school
together living together
[Music]
got busted is that what you just said
hell yeah
oh you're looking so good
it already stopped me
he looks so good in that
outfit she's going to play regular
football practice
you're going to the chess table why
don't you give up on that oh
[Music]
why did you not actually let me try that
like how do you
have to choose my
oh
play regular football practice with well
the other two are playing chess so let's
i don't know go with this girl mae
prescott
let's see maybe may can play
some football with me with subaru
please
oh she actually has a school uniform
oh
what where'd you get those skills sort
of
[Music]
trying to take some screenshots for
thumbnails
[Music]
shoot shoot shoot
from it
[Music]
is that hard to do i don't know how to
do that
[Music]
i'm generally really really bad with
balls in general
[Music]
okay you do your thing how's this going
oh oh they stopped
[Music]
right now
aina laina is gonna watch a funny video
that superhero is going to show her over
huh
chat with lena oh
[Music]
look at those birds
wobbling waddle waddle waddle
cute birds
cute birds together being birds together
so typical i'm bird watching
hanging out with my besties hell yeah
we went back down here again
fine with me okay are you guys gonna
play chess now
no spar
okay
well i think it's time soon though oh
no
are you a sentiment about that
wait what's your sentiment what's your
sentiment
how can you open sim card file
bonding moment oh so whether it may feel
a warm moment of shared experience and
skill that's good for them
[Music]
still has no sentiments
people walk you all up
discuss fine cuisine with sweaters
[Music]
want the funny love triangle to happen
leave a tape
yeah somebody needs to stream
wait when you know
[Music]
yes
bless
[Music]
i don't want to force it i want it to be
natural i'm not gonna force any robot
what
[Music]
we have achieved the love triangle
kilala has a crush on suvaru
[Music]
subaru has a crush on dana and elena has
a crush on kiana
[Music]
i'm so sorry i made your life so
complicated it's not not what i wanted
it's turning around
oh nathan's gonna work out hard to
impress her crush
oh yes
uh what would you like to do uh let's
ah we can work from home yum or we can
go to work okay let's go just go to work
then and then the rest will go home
[Music]
well you gotta go make things so
complicated yeah see the way you're
oh you have more time because okay now
let's just all go home once and then you
go to work
go go
going home first day of school was a
success i would say
um
we were really good students today
maybe in the future one of us will stand
out more with shitty grades or so but
we'll see how we can keep up with like
homework and all that kind of stuff
we're just not too good
so good
oh super hungry let's
i already have to go to work oh no but i
think she can eat at work maybe and
she'll survive she's not that hungry yet
but okay quebec get some food
reina there no needs to sleep soon but
okay she's already going but wait
raining no no sleeping time yet that's
right
pratt is writing
let's go to sleep at the same time as
kiwawa
yeah
after you're done eating
take a steamy shower
i'm sure you'll manage to juggle school
work and tina's rom-com antics without
any trouble at all
[Music]
raina needs to know about this love
triangle
i mean the real retainer you know what
the retainer nana is actually gonna eat
the leftovers from chihuahua
let's go go go
oh
oh barnacles did super duty confidential
update that a highly secretive
development team gave her
what is what are going to do this was a
clear bridge of the nda that she said no
no no no
somebody wouldn't do that sweetie is a
professional okay
super has been in the whole eye for a
long time
she does not breach nba
she's the most professional senpai i
know
[Music]
but then if if she did something like
that i think she would come clean and be
very honest about it and professional
about it yeah so i say come clean
[Music]
and i think it will pay off oh
mine is sixteen dollars it
seems braces super prices braces herself
for the company's reply thank you for
coming clean we appreciate you honestly
unfortunately due to the leak of
information to the public we will have
to charge you for breaking contract
but it is a small thing and we would
like to continue working with you just
be a little more careful
okay
okay well that's a weird start to her
job
okay i guess
okay you finished eating let's sleep
[Music]
yeah sleepy time until the super duper
comes back someone comes back so late
[Music]
working hard oh forty dollars she did
some great work yeah besides breaking
nda
[Laughter]
okay wait wait wait you didn't get food
at work oh man i guess it was a short
you know
a short day short shift
okay let's let's have some food and then
somebody can also finally sleep fast
fast fast fast gotta eat fast at least
no one's distracting you
okay and then we have another day of
school once we wake up
right
uh
here class in eight hours okay
this is so aggressive
we didn't do homework now but we can do
it in the first hour of work of school i
think
okay while i woke up okay
uncomfortable because you're stinky okay
understandable yeah you take that shower
and then we can do your homework
homework by the way is not necessary
uh i think it just helps you
improve your grade
in the sims like you won't get fired
from school or so
thankfully
how's your acne doing by the way
she looks fine
i think the the cleansing worked really
well if only it was that easy in real
life man
like i i didn't have it that easy
my pimples didn't disappear that easily
that magically
[Music]
four sims hours
yeah it was taking quite long i don't
know if it's for some salads though
and then we should eat some breakfast
maybe we can serve some breakfast now
there are still some leftovers oh no
clean out spoiled food
[Music]
ladder
hunger okay dana is about to wake up you
know what she's gonna get hopefully some
edible leftovers
gotta fix your diet
no it's not always just a diet
it's also you know hormones
you should know that
it can be the hormones you can't like do
[\h__\h] about it sometimes
and it sucks [\h__\h] sucks
okay how about there's still leftovers
what but i wanna
no no no wait
let's make some more so that subado can
get something to how about oh
we can do brownies and stuff cool
and bake but now let's uh
cook oh i'm gonna wait
serve
serve breakfast eggs and toast oh it's
the same thing okay
lumber
so you can do homework too
[Music]
even though you still have some food in
your inventory okay
no idea about hormones and but it's the
same for guys you get acne too
don't tell me you don't get hormonal
acne
[Music]
don't start the fire today start it like
tomorrow so
not today
school starts in an hour
that was a close call
so wake up
wake awake
quick
get ready
try to eat fast
oh god we have no time
uh we have 30 seconds left
oh the toilet is broken again [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
someone who has time now didn't even
have time to do her homework because of
her side job okay well we can't stay so
long in school tomorrow and [\h__\h] around
we need to you know
we need to organize our lives properly
it would be nice if because lena has no
job it would be nice if she could do
everybody's homework
teamwork
[Music]
why is everybody so uncomfortable
nearby crash
uncomfortable but nearby crush oh my god
oh my god what to say what to do just
smile
for molena sweeto has a different reason
oh
upset crush
devastation
something is bothering somebody's crush
okay elena how can she be happy in the
face of that oh
you know what's bothering your crush
that she's close to her other crush
that's not you
and kiana is just chilling and vibing no
wait kyla has the same thing but it
doesn't make her too sad
oh she's she's bothered because
subado is bothered because someone is
bothered because reyna is bothered
and nate is bothered because of kiana
he's teenagers
oh no so much but you know they don't
really show it much they seem fine it's
not drama no drama unless so well subaru
okay let's follow them again
[Music]
perpetual stress love triangle
oh man i can't help them
what do i do what do we do about prom
can we like go as free or do we have to
go in like couples we can go solo i
think
morning free time where ends in okay
wait elena wants to work out on the
treadmill before did you do your
homework though
completely
50 done
i know you should finish that that's
more important wait she didn't bring her
homework though
how are we gonna finish it if you didn't
bring it
oh god damn it okay well then i guess
she left it at home
okay
then let's work out on the treadmill
what do you what do you want to do
study for exams
okay
how do we do that
high school
study for exam
and you want to do work out an exercise
machine we can do that too
before school starts who does that
eh
who who does that before at six no okay
eight a.m in the morning before
before the class starts
which student does that
okay elena and kiara are gonna get
buffed now because they want to keep up
with subaru
[Music]
oh
pokemon news tomorrow what
did they announce there's pokemon news
tomorrow
[Music]
uh
about crx gifts i have to ask
you know i'm not there in person so hmm
[Music]
what about toilet gross prank
goddammit
pokemon presentation tomorrow morning
oh
oh tomorrow morning
[Music]
what could it be
i guess just more details about
the upcoming pokemon game right
nice i'm curious i actually never ended
up watching the last one
i never did watch the last oh look at
those little arms holy [\h__\h] those little
lives
[Music]
that's me yeah yeah yeah yeah that's
pretty much me
that's realistic
surprised that i even wanted to do that
to begin with
impressed
okay
is this check
no
only chatting with winter duncan
oh sure okay we could even have
breakfast here if we wanted to
oh oh okay okay
it's time
wait ah i guess uh whatever we did one
of those tasks
let's go
[Music]
let's go let's go everybody
let's be good students and be on time
[\h__\h] wait 15 seconds we're not gonna
make it
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
yeah this is the problem i've seen that
i've seen that when i watch them james
james turner oh god [\h__\h] five wait what
she's pretty cool yeah shut up i have
other problems now i'm not gonna make it
in time but why don't they run when
there's no time left
no
wait i'm going through that
wait
does it count as i'm attending
[Music]
i think it does oh my god i'm late but
i'm here and i didn't get scolded for it
whatever you use social studies
social studies social studies what's
social studies
[Music]
self-adore id and culture skills oh
like history oh
archaeology skill oh
you learned so much in school
do we also learn this if we don't follow
the students
history
nice okay
so
very serious today health class a
communal grown stretched what
across the classroom as reality said in
that today was a day health class to go
over
most students wait health class that
reminds me my least favorite day
i don't know why well my least favorite
day in a year of school
was the day of health checkups
you guys had those too
well you had to go to a doctor in in the
in the school and they like you know
checked everything
i hated dan yeah i always felt so super
super super nervous about that
no you didn't have that
we had health checkups for every student
i think once per year
[Music]
yeah i don't know i was embarrassed
um
i health checkups oh i guess well the us
doesn't
doesn't um even though you have to pay
for school you don't even get health
checkups huh what is sad sad
[Laughter]
oh man
they're just like get sick whatever
don't care
okay hey but did you have like at least
a doctor in school
that like when you feel like feverish or
whatever during class you can go to
because we had that i loved like when i
was nervous about some class
i would act sick and i would go to the
to the to that room and i would take a
nap because they had a bed
they had a bed and there was no one in
the room and i would just spend like two
hours there
[Laughter]
you did have a nurse
i had nurses but no doctors
oh
[Music]
and did that because i got no sleep me
too though sometimes yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah sometimes when i was playing and
playing in my mom begins for a little
bit too long into the
night had to go to school then i would
sometimes yeah i would say i have a
tummy ache can i take a break in the
room
and then i would just
this is an after two hours sorry i still
feel so sick continues to sleep for
another two hours
[Laughter]
[Music]
don't go back into class until the
second half of the day
afternoon classes
i have arrived i am fully uh fully um
awake now
[Music]
delinquent yes such a delinquent
no i really wasn't though i mean i would
say i was average thank you i tried i
tried to be a good student
yeah yeah
anyway so uh most students would have
stayed home had they known nobody wanted
to be here to learn about their bodies
how embarrassing there aren't many ways
to get out of this now which means keanu
needs to find a way or decide to stick
it out no we're gonna stick it out we
will learn about our bodies
wait what kind of take some deep breath
and remain seated despite the
cringeworthy diagrams the information
seems like it could be useful
someday
oh
[Music]
let's get lunch let's be the first ones
for the food
let's take
the hot dog again for souvenir
i need some peanuts do you guys want me
to play that sausage game that's
somebody played before sometime
have a junior lunch let's have
food
meatball
tamale bites
yeah
let's let's play it sometime then yeah
why are they
[Music]
this dude is in the chess club
there's dudes in the chess club i guess
okay
play sausage legend with shiva wait is
that you can call out
[Music]
oh wait that's the chess club and then
that's the computer club because she
also wears this one
is that also something like a
programming club or so
yeah that's also she also wears the same
thing and maybe that's like programming
club or something
we could join something like that too
like an after school activities thing
but we're also two two of us are already
busy with a job so
i mean you can do both if you check the
schedules
it doesn't overlap it actually works you
could do both but that sounds too
stressful with free sims
yeah
okay uh wait did you eat
how much time we have two hours how
about you take a shower though
and then you
you also ate you could also take a
shower while we're here
kira is a bit tired
we have two hours how about we just like
in the good old days can we take a nap
somewhere here
[Music]
i think there's a
i saw a couch oh yeah here
we go
oh yeah
[Music]
okay wow it's time to take a nap during
school
hey you can't go
oh no
can we suck up to the to the principal
[Laughter]
[Music]
i don't see that but
we can suck up to the lunch lady
[Music]
brighten day
heart felt compliment there we go
yeah
silva's taking a shower dana lina
what happened to the shower you stinky
girl
a value of time
it begins nothing beats the feeling of
crushing that final boss level whenever
reina is gaming she is as one with the
universe is it safe to say she likes
video gaming
[Music]
i think yes
but you also like showering don't you
don't you
so but i don't need some fun
difficult football practice i guess
that's fun yeah you can do that
um but we don't have much time left with
one hour you're not gonna be able to
play much
oh but there you go there comes the bun
okay
now you have to go
we all want to go to class
can we make it are you done sleeping
i don't know if that helped much
oh well
yeah cause kiana woke up so early
today that's true
oh wait wait that's a good constellation
for a screenshot
that's what it's dreaming about what do
you call that
when the when the string is attached to
the
what do you call that
[Music]
you call that game
paddleball
oh thumb
oh how fun
what's up okay
thanks everybody
for uh posing
for the picture
what are we learning language arts class
that sounds so fancy
that sounds really fun
what's language arts are we just
learning a language which language
what was it paddle ball stream with hand
cam
kenneth
i was never able to do yo-yo properly
neville are we done for the day
we're done it's only two classes per day
oh we all did ah we all did great but
sweden didn't do so well probably
because um
i
i mean she did good but she didn't do
her homework i guess
yeah
so doesn't it oh prime is coming the
dance takes place on saturday evening we
have tuesday now at copperdale high
school auditorium dinner will be served
at the venue and the students are
excited about the big night here are
some ways to prepare create a promposal
sign
oh
ask someone to prom ask someone to
promise friends prepare your formal
outfit i never had like prom before
we only have like american style prom i
think oh maybe we do i'm not sure
not like exactly the same i would say
okay then i say we all just go home
yeah
i didn't go for prom either
i had prom oh
who did you go
social awkwardness you can actually can
give your sim a social socially awkward
trait
now which is interesting i didn't want
to give it to any of our sims this time
because uh i wanted to give them some
other traits
alrighty
welcome
[Music]
welcome back home okay so
how about you just take a nap so you
don't have to sleep too early um now
and the rest looks very fine
hunger okay
let's
get leftovers
and subaru it's what it wants to play
but how about we repair
this toilet i'm so sorry i'm making you
do this
[Music]
sorry
what can we do if leno doesn't have to
no reina has no job right let's do
homework
wait where's the homework
okay is that her homework do homework
okay
[Music]
i wish you could access it from anywhere
and that would be good
prom was canceled oh no
uh
somebody did leave that mess no i think
it was raining because lena pranked it
it's not stupid it was fault
you fixed it good job
all right let's let's clean it let's
clean it
so that you're not uncomfortable about
it anymore
okay and then
when we're done with that
then you can talk to your crush reina
reveal crush
oh no we're not ready for that ask the
problem ask for oh
what are we gonna do about bro
let's ask for some tips first
it's about a being like this i've never
imagined that before spurgle wong
danger here so she woke up and i think
she wants to join the conversation
[Music]
ask to just be friends
claim to be prom
royalty hmm
i will claim that i'm from royalty
[Music]
i will do that
boy
[Music]
i am from royalty
i don't know what that means but yeah
girlfriend noise
can we have a freeway relationship
flirt with souvenirs
how about your flight with somebody
right in front of canada's eyes
[Music]
yes try to get over crush
oh wait i chose myself
[Music]
someone you crush his kiwawa
no oh no yeah
but her wish is to flirt with sober
[Music]
promise to skip prom together oh that
you can do that too huh yeah but how
about wait wait wait you can do like a
prime pose or sign right let's make one
great prompt pose a sign
everyone will make a promposal sign how
about that
because is still doing her homework okay
we're distracting her
oh oh wait you're already done no
homework is complete okay so dana can
also do her proposal
sign
i've never seen something like that
before i guess it's like to make an
impressive
proposal
well you got to prom with me
oh they're making different ones nice
annie can you do yours
i like how mine's more colorful
super is more like black and white
straight
oh
don't don't don't inhale it don't inhale
it [\h__\h]
i'm gonna get sick and throw up all over
the promposa sign you don't want that
everyone's making the proposal signs
[Music]
oh i think so what it was done
it's done
oh pinched finger oh no
[Music]
what does it look like oh look at it
poor quality pour
[Music]
there's something special about the
self-made proposal sign this grand
gesture is sure to have them say yes
right maybe you should have spent more
time in the art room but all this effort
is sure to make an impression they'll
never forget can i improve it i can
scrap it
uh well
it's a gesture that counts right
let's do let's do homework
oh man
[Music]
okay how they got this gonna turn out i
guess
kiana's kiana's turned out
excellent
i didn't even have an art skill i think
but i did give myself the the likes um
the interest the hobby of of art i think
of painting
[Music]
okay okay okay okay so
okay we still have some days before prom
so
we don't need to make any decisions now
yet
anyway you can actually sit down now
take a seat feel free
and talk to your crush
oh no but your crush has to go to work
we can work from home i think
from home baby
oh oh oh oh when you work from home as a
casual streamer
you get like a home assignment update
online bio with business headshot okay
we can do that once raina gets off the
pc writing her fanfictions again
first can we do
the homework
yeah thank you
oh man being a student doing your
[\h__\h] homework every day hate it
ah
deroy ah
i hated homework i hated it so much
don't forget to ask vayner to prom no we
still have time i'm not ready yet i'm
not ready to make the decision yet
[Music]
what to say kenneth's trying so hard not
to panic but her crotch is right there
she's so tense about it
oh yeah your crush is indeed right there
that's kind of cute yo
oh they know lina is already going to
sleep oh no
okay so what do you stop stop that for a
second you need to do your job i guess
um
is it here
[Music]
no wait where is it
huh
how do you do the
job thing
ah
oh upload business headshot by taking a
photo with the camera on the phone and
then click on the photo object in the
inventory oh
come on
do i
look at the bright side i guess wait we
chose here and then camera
take
is can it be a selfie or
wait
thinking um take a photo
i guess a selfie should suffice
that's a great selfie what
where am i
[Music]
um
ah there i am wow
oh
[Music]
there we go i never took a selfie before
instance this is how it works okay
does this look like a business headshot
how do you change the isn't this
expression she doesn't change it
[Music]
i think it's bugging out
that's pretty good
okay let's take that
nice
[Music]
um
ah
i think it's because the room is so tiny
cute look at her
so dynamic quiet
oh my god
[Laughter]
[Music]
i like that expression
but maybe not good for business business
profile how about this oval face
[Music]
anime poses and what
oh wow
cute wait that's cute that's a cute one
i mean the eyelashes are kind of bugging
out but cute
pretty cute you know putting your hands
so close to your face makes your face
look smaller
[Music]
how about relaxed
how cute oh
you may have those already what about
these
oh yeah we had these already
[Music]
okay fold this remaining one more okay
excited how about that one
[Music]
okay that's a bit crazy so i don't know
it's also kind of holy [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
ah those eyes
it's not so flattering it's not very oh
that one is i guess flattering i guess
okay
okay do those work
oh it should be an inventory oh yeah
apple faces headshots yes
yes
oh
somebody what's wrong don't slam the
door like that
so aggressive
upload it maybe nice okay i think a
clever i think our job is silent for
today is done
okay
that's all we need you to do that's easy
wait staying doing it from home
is so much easier what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay i know you really want to sleep but
let's shoot let's do the homework a
little bit longer
and keep up also doing homework you
should stop talking because you're never
going to get it done
there we go there we go there we go
speed
okay
i think elena is going to be the one
to wake up early tomorrow
take a speed shower
and then we sleep pillow
we do need some fun
well primo fights new i think they will
find a new wait oh that's awesome i want
to do that i swear to lisa pedo if we do
a pillow fight now she might
accidentally pee her cellar below
rafa in a dangerous party well rain is
sleeping
oh
wait
[Music]
but this is a happy moment for kiara you
know having a pillow fight yeah we're
just with her crush savannah go get her
go get her
let her accidentally tackle you or
something
[Music]
oh man i i don't remember when i ever
had a pillow fight before
some intense
intense bad action
bad action
that is the most bad action you will get
from these teenagers
now please go go to the toilet yes
please
do what you gotta do and now
we barely have
let fun do [\h__\h]
wow okay never doing a pillow fight ever
again
okay i wish you could like sleep
aggressively to like sleep
more effectively
wouldn't that be nice
wait i i was done with homework but it
looks like i'm not done
no it does say complete okay how about
you 75
and complete okay
when kiwano wakes up we're gonna do a
little bit more homework
yeah sleep aggressively
like how you can wait faster and it
totally works
totally
wigs trust me
trust me bro
ask a crush out
it's time reina is ready to ask out her
crush
i always saw you already
are you sure you're ready to be turned
down
[Music]
oh
well her dream was to go to the toilet
nice eat food
okay
now you should um
get leftovers
[Music]
okay how we doing
time to wake up soon
okay first get leftovers
and then use
don't even talk to each other
[Music]
how about we do something for high
school instead of being on the pc all
the time studying for exam go aina
[Music]
you don't want to get kicked out of
school
your parents will be so mad
[Music]
your mommy
so disappointing
that's past past oh she's gonna pay
yourself
wait wait wait wait where is my homework
it says i'm 75 done where
is
if this is not mine oh no it is now
that did work
i thought that didn't work
okay
subaru is awake so about a quick
quick grab a bite
and we can have some fun in school
hopefully
with some ball practice
or so
i'm so close go quick
no just do your stupid homework
do it
[Music]
oh my god oh thank god that was like one
second
okay
okay okay if you're so tense
we can um
what what makes you less tense play game
blink block
get that tenseness out of your system
now and what is wrong with her
angry about crush
how dare dana's crush aka kiwawa just
wave at someone else aka subadu waving
is something special only for an anus
oh
she's so angry she's so like into it
she's so into it
oh
spicy drama
nina it was just waving but oh man
[Music]
okay
going to school
with this drama queens
[Music]
will any of these girls find happiness
will we
okay you know what um uh
we will
[Music]
we will do
somebody's dying to talk to her crush
okay
um
try to calm her down
and
give pep talk
and then we want to have some fun so
we're gonna
uh uh
play with our ball
croissant your water
so mad glass okay nice parsley maze
around right somewhere
so what are you doing you're gonna read
a book
that is
not very in character not very realistic
oh
but you want some fun let's see what can
we do in school for fun
[Music]
oh i think it's fun to practice
prank a whiteboard
hell yeah i'm gonna be a jokester but
wait are you already pranking the
whiteboard
class one teacher how do we prank it
when the teacher is already there
let's see
maybe we can make her leave
oh yeah okay the teacher is in the room
but um
she will surely not notice
acquired the mischief skill
oh she's watching me
oh
oh diva witch for possible i'm getting
scared
sentiment gained how can i trust you
when you act as suspicious no
so you fancy yourself and prankster mr
stuck i'm not saying well i can give you
all the time you like to strive
we're not supposed to work today
i can't go to detention to work in nine
hours
i can't have detention today
wait did that update to uh to 5 p.m now
wait let me see
3 p.m okay
but 5 p.m is when my job starts
no
no i want
i'm gonna call my mommy what if i don't
go to detention huh
[\h__\h]
caught maybe kevin should be a little
more careful next time when she's
feeling sneaky
um
okay delinquent people
can i scribble on my on my table i just
want to have some fun
school is not fun
okay i'll study for exams
also like really really really not
having fun
can we
where's where's laina let's make elena
happy
[Music]
apologize what did you do
what's the most fun
[Music]
thing you can do together
support lay his body
support plane body hair what
okay i don't see any fun options though
can i do something fun on my own
practice singing maybe singing should be
fine right or cloud gazing i know cloud
gazing is really good for like improving
relationships but i don't know about fun
it's fun let me test it tina
you're ah there's a pc oh yeah right
everybody's using the pc
okay that is fun
a little bit
meanwhile okay while i'm alone in the
classroom absolutely embarrassed trying
to make it bright again oh
not really having a good time though
[Music]
it's okay
the teacher will not hate you forever
probably hopefully
hopefully
there will be exam prep session after
school today all students are free to
join us in a class too no thank you
okay we have to go
no thank you because chihuahua has to
stay longer anyway
for the tension
looks sick
okay we're in this constellation again
noise
[Music]
she's japanese
i like her fashion sense and her
hairstyle
oh we're acquiring
photography and painting and acting oh
yes there's so much to learn here okay
wait [\h__\h] what i'm still studying for
the exam girl you need to ah well we
already have detention so [\h__\h] it
oh okay passing notes somebody was about
to start dozing off when another student
passes her note and points at another
student uh-huh somebody didn't even know
passing notes was still a thing with
social media and phones
oh you're right wait is that not a thing
anymore
[Music]
back in my days we still pass notes
is that not a thing anymore
is it though
[Music]
it's not a thing
boomer
excuse me usually
only when the phone is out of axes yeah
like
maybe it's like less i think it might be
easier to pass
nah
yeah
[Music]
i mean getting out your phone like that
you're gonna have like quite the
technique for that
i barely
i i think um
[Music]
in in my junior high school years i
never used my phone because i also
i didn't i mean back then
we didn't really
none of us really used our phones that
much
there was not much to do with your phone
back then
i feel like a boomer
oh man and then in high school i guess
yeah films became more
a little bit more apparent
a little bit more
important
someone didn't even know
does someone continue the note chain or
maybe add some changes to the notes um i
think subaru even though she wants to be
a good student she also wants to you
know be like not wants to but it's
automatically like popular she knows
what to do so
and she's like you know the kid that
everybody likes and gets along well with
so she would definitely pass the note
along
or add some changes even yeah
and let's add some changes
oh
somebody added a few scribbles she
thought would cause a laugh but
she's just got a minus
no one was happy about it also what it
got for her additions was a little extra
irritation from her classmates hey
no way
god damn it
yeah we really desperate fun we really
need some fun for these girls for all of
them oh man
maybe we should all cloud games together
after lunch
okay
okay it's lunch time
uh
we're not even hungry i'm not hungry
okay i wanna talk we're all not really
hungry let's um
that's all cloud case
go here together
let's see let's see let's see
you know
i feel like dana would stay
um in school until kiwa is done with her
detention
i feel like she would do that somebody
too probably you know turd duncan
we value
each other
now i want to
[Music]
joke about ducks
with a great option no i want
[Music]
like can we all cloud gates wait don't
go away
can i join oh [\h__\h] someone's really
stinky oh it's so bad
oh dear
it's okay i don't mind that
okay now let me join
how do i join
no
wait when you stop
let's
let's cloud case
[Music]
oh no cloud case
okay i'll just cloud games alone
you're cloud case too
oh wait no
ah sweater also has spoiled food in her
inventory
ah
[Music]
they all have spoiled food in their
inventory ew
ew they brought spoiled lunch to
to school you know
okay elena is finally having fun cloud
gazing doesn't work so well maybe maybe
we should try singing too
oh look at the bright side
is that fun
look at the bright side did you did you
look at it what's there what's on the
bright side
mr mrs bright side
me
[Music]
but i really am not having any fun i
need some [\h__\h] fun
that's not fun either nothing's fun
nothing's fun in school why can't i not
practice singing i'm too tense to do it
ah
[\h__\h]
sit on ground
okay i guess was at least a little bit
fun
a tiny
bit
[\h__\h]
[Music]
lunch ends in 10 seconds
go go go go let's go time
you're right the pc [\h__\h]
are they they used it a little bit i
think
i'll cut them in
programming skill
pa announcements the pa loudly trips on
for some announcements kiara doesn't
really care to hear about the weather
forecast or updates the school's social
calendar with no lessons going on now
seems like a good time to listen to
teams no kiwama
we already got into travel just listen
to the announcements
that's under response methodically drops
we found the create drone on and on
repetitive and unimportant to anyone
listening one student even knows that
it's better than listening to music and
get caught by the teacher
although i i used to do that sometimes
too
what do we have today so by just seeing
a little inattentive
you need to make sure to
make sure her class skills are out
before next week oof dana seemed a
little inattentive too
what about cuava oh ah i guess my school
day didn't end yet
serve detention
all right i'm serving
i'm i'm serving
okay well then uh the others will just
wait and get some food right now
order food
fried chicken oh i'm getting more and
more hungry
in real life
before super chat rating we're gonna
snack
you know what i had for dinner last
night
because i was kind of too late to
realize i need some food
i had i had mini yakisoba mini um
instant yak silva that genma brought to
me from japan
a while ago
thank god i had that
because i actually couldn't make
anything else
yeah
it was nothing special but
[Music]
maybe that's fun watching that is fun
baby is that what happens in attendance
i never had to go to detention before
never
wow
holy [\h__\h] um
um okay
i don't look so bad as a student anymore
do i
work for kiana starts in about an hour
oh my god kiwa does not get a break
kiwam is also hungry can i eat during
detention
may may i
just not witness the fight you know what
while everybody's witnessing a fight how
about i go to eat
will i get in trouble
i don't really have time anyway
fast eat
eat fast
yes yes
okay i think we're good
[Music]
oh can i get the tension in the tension
don't don't i have to go to work now
i got done eating just now
i will never fight oh [\h__\h] is that the
same people
ah
[Music]
okay i'm dismissed it seems fine
i i'm fine during the tension apparently
you can just go to the cafeteria
uh no time to practice i have to go to
work
oh no
well good luck kiwawa
i guess we'll stay here or should we go
home i think we'll go home
yeah let's make some money but actually
we're not we don't have much money but
it's not like we're spending that much
money either we're fine
seemingly fine
yes after work um even those icons of
the fast would make me hungry
[Laughter]
[Music]
what did you guys eat today huh
huh
tell me
watch birds
tell me about
the food
nothing yet
pizza
oh that's what i'm gonna eat today i
think
is that fun you should do something fun
there you go
nothing yet nothing at all did you guys
all just wake up or what
[Music]
egg yep and spinach okay
i don't like the spinach but that sounds
like a good breakfast
tuna melt what's what's that
tuna with cheese melted cheese or what
swordfish and dumplings
sweet chili lit
waffles
big mac avocado pizza
no salad with milk juice yummy i should
try them
mozzarella and meatballs
oh guys i know i asked you but you're
making me suffer that's
i can't listen to
that oh
oh man
subaru can now discuss game strategy
with other sims
wait right now it's just so better to
entertain it
somebody who has a crush on mourinho
you know i would imagine
somebody would take this chance
[Music]
this chance
so i don't take this chance
and present her from posing
oh no i'm self sabotaging
well what can i do
i have to make everyone happy
quick before kibaba comes home
oh i don't even know when she comes home
okay okay it's happening guys
[Music]
yes
[Laughter]
hey don't you love kiana
[\h__\h] you don't you love kiana what
happened
sentiments about subaru impress my
proposal golly that proposal from
survivor is one data isn't likely to
forget
[Music]
good job oh
successful proposal they said yes
oh my god somebody just spent some
quality time with a crush
i am happy for you guys
and all this happens while i'm at work
that's so [\h__\h] painful
oh man
um
yeah
this is just gonna be painful once
quinoa gets
i'm the third whale i'm always the third
wheel
in real life
kiana's on a roll this joint is so clean
she can see her face cleaning back from
the table tops but then she notices some
kind of pinkish glove jiggling from the
seat of a chair
she could just wipe it and throw it out
her rag but then again her job title
does say table
what seat where
and just clean it up i guess
sure i guess i'll go to prom with you
really
rainy really looked way more exciting
than
it seems in that sentence
yeah it's disgusting the mystery glop is
chunkier than it first looked and reeks
of repossessed onion
kiana drops her rag in the trash and her
and scrubs her hands raw but the stink
sticks for what seems like hours
oh wow
oh it's tough out there you know
oh reyna still wants to ask kiwawa out
here
i guess we can do that
oh man
also working still now today okay okay
okay okay go to work then
go go
see ya later
oh what are you doing clean then
all right
bye bye
bye bye bye bye
wait are you going to wait no you're
playing hoops how are you going to work
[Applause]
30 minutes okay okay i guess you still
have fun
yo get fit wait what no did she just
just have it
what just happened
dream big is that what that is
[Music]
you can hear applause whoa
holy [\h__\h]
she's falling
hell yeah she is nana or anyone to sleep
what the [\h__\h]
um
[Music]
i think you should go to work
sixty-four dollars king huawei is home
and now super duper is gone
kiwawa is home
survivor is gone
[Music]
what happens can can dana still do a
promposal to um to kiana even though
chat with crush okay see we will do that
look at you
it's even orange
it's actually orange
she's doing that pose like the mean pose
like where hey where is everybody
what the [\h__\h] just happened while i'm
gone
can we do it
[Music]
prom
we can still do it
does that cancel out the other proposal
we shall test it out
okay go go nina
let's have some drama baby
[Music]
oh my god i'm so happy let's go
i love you i love you too
what does that mean
[Music]
oh i'd be delighted to attend prom with
you says kiwawa too later
what what hap what happens with subaru
is there like any info about
prom here now that like oh this person
is going with this person are they going
together now or what
it's
spring angle what the [\h__\h] on
[Music]
super tense so let's give her some
computer time
oh play sims forever go go
dana
dana first you say yes to subaru and now
this
oh
mama mia
i'm
predictable okay time to do homework go
go go go go go
[Music]
let's do homework
i don't think uh
somebody's gonna come home late kiwawa
needs to get some fun up wow this is
actually kind of stressful now
id harem system
canadian knows what she wants
yeah yeah yeah
i i wonder what's gonna happen now like
how does this work
are they actually going together
tip up the gods a rude fan is just
spamming and annoying other sims in
super juice chats
it is about time to deal with this band
once and for
the defenders give the largest donation
that's what it has been has seen since
she started streaming
what did super to do
the money could surely help but is it
worth it
but there is no such thing as declining
it to be honest super chats they just
come
in and yeah well you accept it
that's your biggest super chat so for 30
dollars
there is no room against taking a live
donation from a fan right someone who
thanks the viewer for the donation but
gives one final warning about the rude
behavior the fan quickly apologizes and
promises to never do so again
someone who tells the chat that she
believes in second chances but asks
everyone to be respectful and caring to
anyone in the community
i'm so funny
because this is like our
you know this is where we are
oh thank god my phone is looking a
little bit better
no time for homework today though okay i
was grades
[Music]
my time keys are not working anymore
it's one two three it doesn't work
anymore
why
bugged
okay time to sleep
somebody goes back home
so
what happens if somebody talks first
kiss
oh my god it's about to go straight to
bed or what no let's do a pick-up line
wait no somebody was
i'm getting confused somebody was in
love with dana right and they didn't
look wow
it's kind of confusing
dana completed her homework nice
uh
is prom safe
i'm invited
okay
prom seems to be safe
what if kiwa asks subaru out for the
prom now
can we actually all three
go with each other
all right my arrow keys also don't work
anymore
is there like a fix for this okay i can
do this with the mouse but i can't move
with wasd anymore
did i lock my keyboard
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
kiss nick
okay wait so but you're not that tired
yet wait do your homework
[Music]
homework here we go
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah okay tomorrow quinoa is gonna ask uh
who is kiwamo gonna ask
supernova
somebody right yeah
to prom
oh
the love triangle
it's so confusing
okay
then sleep you're done nice
homework complete it's it's already so
late oh my god
yeah i could never have a side job
while going to school i don't know how
people do it
like i definitely would not have had the
time
like people nobody back in my time
during school
nobody had a side job
i don't think it's a normal thing in
austria
[Music]
what about u.s because i know japanese
students do baito adubaito
quite a bunch of them
if they don't do after school activities
what about like america
common in the us really part-time jobs
while going to school like high school
[Music]
i know not a single person in austria
that did that
wow that's quite a difference
[Music]
did you do it because your parents
didn't give you pocket money or
[Music]
or like what why because you had to
afford your own apartment or the school
you wanted to help out with school fees
or
what's the reason
you want to cook mac and cheese don't we
have leftovers anymore
we don't have leftovers
all of the above
we just want to cash extra money always
nice oh you didn't necess some of you
didn't necessarily need it but you just
wanted some extra money yeah
wow respect
did i do my homework yeah i did okay
okay lerna's looking fine hey we already
have to go
oh two persons are still sleeping
oh man
okay here we go
[\h__\h] hell i think after prom
we're ending the episode for today
one week takes a long time ah i think if
i understand correctly uh one year
or like one you know teenager time of
high school
is two weeks two in-game weeks i think
and then you have two prompts basically
i think
okay how can we fix this
rain is fine
subaru needs to go to the
toilet and shower can we do both of that
before
yeah
come on be fast
and then you
and you can also shower
ask
reina can actually do something that
she's being asked to do study for exams
that sounds good
study for exam
okay
shitty weather today what the fun
[Music]
thank god there's showers here
cannot manage this high school life
it's tough
one hour and 20 minutes
until uh
okay let's eat something
let's have a hamburger slider
[Music]
it barely moves it doesn't move at all
i'm not getting clean
go go go go
[Music]
just use a different shower
okay go go go
why am i wearing my work outfit
i'm in school
am i going to be the lunch lady now i'm
the lunch lady now oh [\h__\h]
oh quick quick quick
i can't
i'm going to eat in class can i eat in
class
that would be amazing eat hamburger
slime i got them i think they're in my
inventory no where are they
love day tomorrow valentine's day
oh my god
so stressful where is everybody
attend business class where are you
oh my god
you're gonna miss the whole class
why are you sitting here
what
what are you doing no you just
i did attempt class
i attend class
[Music]
wait that's the wrong class
can i attend class
i can't how do i attend class
uh in the last ten minutes
uh totally suffice but i need to
she needs to be
no i'm
is there any consequences
there we go we did it
okay kewala
eat her sliders oh those are my
slightest thank god
apparently in the classroom now
it's a [\h__\h] mess here
okay what is the weather doing
so whether you need to eat food you're
gonna order food
wait for food okay
you're like fighting for food
stay standing alive for god's sake
how about a veggie slider
what am i doing okay okay i ate my food
okay everything's good again
how about did i ever do my homework
i didn't maybe if i do it now
we have some time
wait the phrase did you hear that it
said attention students and then some
similar started they actually spoke
english for a second though what the
[\h__\h]
i'm impressed
i think that's the first time i ever
heard english in the game
[Music]
what
proper english
[Music]
you're also playing something okay good
good good good jessica needs to do the
hustle go go go go
[Music]
go
the homework oh i can't i won't i wonder
is there no option to like
show them the homework
attempt to seduce oh no not now
not now
oh
oh two birds in a computer room what
happens next
oh never mind
we're not alone anymore nothing can
happen
nothing can happen
oh we're about to finish we can finish
in time maybe more or less
nice
yeah yeah now go to
class your boss okay you also go to
class how about that
super duper went
just in time and you you're missing it
again you missed already one full cl oh
my god this one's also just 20 minutes
left
[Music]
this might reflect in you know being
attentive or so at the end of the day
i before you some say simulish is hard
but there are some languages that just
have confusing rules don't even get
started on how conjugating a
verb works this might be a good time to
make a cheat sheet for any of uh
you know how i did teachings
back in my day in school
i was
pretty much the only girl
um in in class that wore um
skirts
and
also a lot of the time i would wear um
over knee socks
so i had i had two
two strategies that always worked
because since i was the only one
there was like no
like like the teachers wouldn't know
that this is a thing
so
sometimes i would put a cheat sheet
underneath the top of my over knee socks
because there's no [\h__\h] way that
anybody's gonna check that and then i
could basically just you know look down
on my thighs which would kind of look
like i'm looking just on the sheet in
front of me
and then i i turn around in the over
knee sock the top of it
and there's my cheat sheet and then the
other thing i would do sometimes
is um
when i wear a skirt
i i you know
i pulled up the skirt a little bit and
underneath um i think i would sometimes
wear some
little bits a little bit see-through uh
black tights or just cheer tights
and just have it you know taped to my
leg
under the skirt
yeah i know i'm a [\h__\h] genius
delinquent
no
everybody cheats sometimes how did you
get away with this i don't think i ever
got caught yeah i never got caught
before but sometimes i would just go
with the easy
write it on your hand and even with that
i would never get caught
i would just be very careful that um i
would not show my open palm of hand to
my
to my teacher smooth criminal
i never cheated
no way
i was getting away yay
never got caught cheating damn nice uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
one thing i also remember is like
um there's some dance teachers out there
um you know they give you the test
but they never look at the chalkboard
and we noticed that and i uh it wasn't
me but some other student wrote some
help for i think it was a math test
actually
on the chalkboard like some formula
formula yeah
and
i think i remember the teacher noticing
like halfway through but at that point
it already helped us so then he was like
laughing and
he wasn't mad the teacher wasn't even
mad he just you know wiped it off but at
that point it was already too late we
had what we needed
yeah it's ballsy but you don't know like
you can't even be mad at the student
because you don't know who it was
because it happened before the class and
honestly that is such an obvious like
big cheat sheet right in front of their
eyes if only they turned around so
i mean i i think we only have to blame
the teacher for that
yeah
so we will uh
simskivalvado
is an idol
and will
study hard and memorize the rules
come on you can do it
[Music]
korean if you love you come sanita
small classroom performance laws oh for
[\h__\h] sake
at least i can be proud of myself oh
we're all impressed with teachers and
learned a lot everybody did good even
though they was barely there
what the [\h__\h] okay
um we need some social we need some fun
and bladder okay
uh
with kiana we wanted to ask subado out
right okay let's not do that right now
let's um wait let's do that at home or
so mistletoe kiss
it's not christmas season what the [\h__\h]
shall we ask about elena's love life
how's your love live
and so someone is doing so well oh super
should do uh
[Music]
wow we're doing so well yeah that's a
football practice with
me
mei
the side character the npc that never
gets a line to speak
okay
what's happening
are you talking
oh way beau so far
away
okay um
wait wrong
oh gracia bombosa
exchange numbers you haven't exchanged
numbers yet
zomas
declare love publicly
wait but in gamelina yeah she has a
crush on kewala okay now what i think
i'll do that
huh
what happens if reyna confesses her love
publicly
in this classroom while subaru is gone
let's make the love triangle even more
complicated
she's singing her love song
oh my god
[Music]
thank you what
what do you think about that
oh anyway that's still the
from the the sentiment from before it
didn't change
feeling smitten just seeing a sim can
set the heart of flutter oh my god can i
just spend some quality time with your
crush but she doesn't mean she doesn't
mean reina with that she means uh
somebody with that no
what's the reaction here
no reaction
besides just you know
but athena is like oh oh oh dana you
were just like
control that's it reyna has had enough
of that nagging feeling telling her to
do this or that either she gets her way
or nothing at all
is she mad at me the one who's
controlling her god
wait wait from unfulfilled dreams or
what
wait where was that i saw that somewhere
what's your problem
here
rain it feels unfulfilled and
dissatisfied with how life is going then
occasionally you become upset with her
life ah that's just it's just a face
that's just a teenage thing it's just a
face
she's fine against me she's fine
she's very flirty
practice writing can we
i guess we gotta go to the pc for that
okay
let's practice some writing here
uh right
practice writing
get down on those fan fictions let's go
[\h__\h]
from a close sentiment towards someone
feeling bad saying that someone super to
cherish his suffering makes her sad ah
oh
that's so sweet
she has so much empathy there's a senior
lunch wait that's noise let me let me
try that all right so but let's eat food
we'll get happier after we eat food i
promise you
yeah
[Music]
and uh kiwawa needs some fun too so
kiwama will also go here
and then
it's just these two again
we can't leave these two in the room
alone
you wanna ask somebody to prom now i am
gonna do it
[Music]
take part in pizza fitness with the
football competition or chill out and
grab a smoothie from the merch stand
what
wait is that wait sorry i didn't read
properly
sports day is starting wherever it's
done
show festival info oh near kappa daily
high school
build up skillful football froze and
beat a winner
somebody needs to take part in that and
if only kihua and elena could be their
cheerleaders
oh there it is oh
on a rainy day
i can see where to go there
oh
it looks kind of dead
are you guys actually doing that or
how do you do that
[Music]
maybe maybe
somebody should join the
football team
is there anything happening here
are you vandalizing this thing
dude
[Music]
love
why are you not running
oh lyna can now self-publish books let's
go
oh that's why quebec was wearing her
work uniform all the time
it's because she needed to go to work
afterwards
oh ken
can
can somebody would do like a solo
routine that would be fun
[Music]
oh okay it looked pretty good at first
wow impressive well for first try
[Music]
wait
i thought i turned the hair growth off
she has a [\h__\h] ton of leg hair do you
see that
need [\h__\h] we need to shave the
leg hair
[Music]
we gotta go to the shower for that how
are we doing how do we do that
look at how
freshen up
no wait
shave oh in the shower shave leg hair
okay
afterwards after we're done with the
routine
[Music]
we didn't enjoy much here but you know
kiwa is coming home soon
so we want to be at home when kiwamo
comes home
nice nice a good uh
good day at school
are you
going home anytime
he wants to click the clackity of the
keyboard
[Music]
by the way i'm i'm receiving the
keyboard soon i just i got a
i got a notice
a tracking note is that uh elena
sent me the keyboard and it's coming
soon in a couple of days maybe
sooner or later
yeah
oh
then i can finally switch out this old
disgusting dirty keyboard that i'm using
[Laughter]
uh
[Music]
right now i'm using also a japanese
keyboard
okay i think uh
wait
reina nina's hungry this still seems
fine let's eat that
welcome mackiewalla
ozza
big autumn
let's eat something
[Music]
and then and then we think about wait
someone else up [\h__\h] oh somebody went to
work ah
let's let's stay up late and when elena
is sleeping
we invite survivor
to prom
[Music]
apparently it does not matter how many
people you invite for prom
noise
[Music]
the ultimate love triangle
coming soon
nina is in a really good mood actually
let's do homework
it's it's first day okay friday is the
last day of school before
you promo also do homework
okay
ah homeworking together
suggestion you're doing homework
focus
[Music]
yeah
i love my blob i look like a sim
oh
[Music]
do i have the option of shaving no so
i'm i'm not growing any hair
dana has the option of shaving oh so she
currently has leg hair you just can't
see it because she's hiding it under the
pants
we can do that afterwards although her
hygiene is pretty well it's like when we
actually need to take a shower i wonder
if that does something for hygiene
[Music]
she's angry about the crush again and
then she's also happy about it she's
like all confused she has so many
feelings
swooning over crash
[Music]
get your homework done
went straight to bed
[Music]
don't go straight go wake up wake up use
the stay awake a little bit longer come
on
you need to eat food anyway
oh there's no more leftovers
um
what's canning
oh
cool you can make like
apple jam tomato sauce and stuff like
that yeah that's new i think
let's cook for everybody
oh no um
cook together
wait you can cook together
that's so cute wait
that's so cute does it make the cooking
faster that's new i don't remember that
[Music]
let's make some mac and cheese together
okay okay okay waba help huh
hiwa do help him is a chef here
dana completed her homework nice too
okay
oh
are you helping
how are you helping
oh there you go
oh they're so cute they're all in the
kitchen
helping oh
oh super slime yeah
what part of the mac and cheese are you
making are you wait what
how are you
it's already done what are you doing
no don't sleep no
no finish your homework
okay you can sleep later that's okay we
wanted you to sleep early that's what we
were waiting for
i'm just
[Music]
just clean it up
and when we're ready when we're done
with homework we're gonna do the first
proposal
[Music]
what it was it was kiwa proposing to uh
somebody right yeah
you cannot sleep now sober it's an
important time now
[Music]
it's happening
she's really tired but come on you gotta
nail this
[Music]
you have to nail it
we're doing it outside so it ain't it
doesn't hear
[Laughter]
the gnarliest
[Applause]
[Music]
not ending yet though but uh
happy what she's
[Music]
kiwawa chooses
wait what
[Music]
devastation something is bothering
kiana's crush how can she be but she got
accepted why why why is she sad why she
said
her crush her crush is stupid what's
bothering sure i guess i'll go to prom
with you when what's
looming inside it had anxious feeling
looms over super that as she discovered
something new about herself the fear
that wasn't here before growing inside
ready to overcome doing to paralyze this
at any moment
oh my god so dramatic passionless job ah
that's
very passionate about me too being
no but that's what bothers her
what's the point anymore i get to work
mine will say good job get paycheck
sleep repeat what is somebody even doing
here
from fear of dead and job
[Music]
is we doing a dead-end job
oh
monsieur
you should be happy
there's a fruffle
when kiwawa is so sad and she's
looking at the bird picture that's
hanging on the wall instead of going to
sleep to sleep now it's okay
[Music]
don't give up
no it's not a dead end job i think i'm
not sure what is a dead end job
something that just there's no way of
going up no way of
like getting
promoted or so
[Music]
or
you can't get promoted but you know what
the end is and
it's just love day happy valentine's day
oh dear valentine's day
not getting anywhere in life no way to
progress to korea
but there is like i'm sure there is
oh
oh oh school starts in an hour okay um
can we take a really speedy shower wait
is
is kiwa was
crying herself to sleep right now
i think i i can't move anymore but
i think i saw and heard her crying
chihuahua she's crying for subado
because somebody was suffering
she's she's oh my god what an empathetic
queen
oh my god
[Music]
whoa these kids you know they're
teenagers
they have so many hormones
okay we hungry we didn't get to eat
breakfast
so
everybody go eat
rainbow brownies for breakfast
um
you're not that hungry i think you could
wait you could probably use a shower
you need to pee and food okay
[Music]
okay let's go
hunger tomorrow by the way is uk snack
box speaking of hunger right tomorrow's
uk snack box review
why are you going so far to eat
oh we want to both eat with the
oh wait may is the principal the one
that we keep on playing uh football with
with subaru is the principal
oh yeah british box
we're gonna eat some british snacks
tomorrow they better be good they better
be good
they better be good mate
oh super juice
oh
hit them hit that sausage it looks like
a sausage don't you think
sausage water
[Music]
wait subato has acne ah onyo
oh let's uh apply
face cleanser
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] it's time
oh [\h__\h] i'm gonna pee myself in class
ah
yeah it goes on you're looking better
you're confident now
yeah acne is gone magically cute
[Laughter]
can you go faster
[Music]
why am i moving okay i guess i didn't
like that seat
i got pushed away but now i'm in wait
i'm in the protagonist's seat what are
you doing oh [\h__\h] no no
don't you dare pee yourself in class
you go now
[Music]
are they downstairs are they only
downstairs i'm not gonna make it
no they're not that they're here okay
there's one here
okay thank god
thank god
so whether what the [\h__\h] are you doing
why
take example
but what about class take exam
well they're both taking
[\h__\h] kiwawa you need to take exam two
probably how do i
oh
take exam it's exam day
[Music]
oh
oh i can do it one lunch okay
huh
except rta
what about you guys you're taking the
exam here
no practicing did you take the exam
oh
let me check is it an option
is it an option on the classroom
no okay so subato did it
reina
did it too okay
so we can eat food with lena
um so while you can also eat food nicer
did everybody do their homework by the
way
ah
subaru did not but whatever it's exam
day so [\h__\h] it at this point if we have
some time after food maybe
ah
okiwawa did her homework
you did
[Music]
i didn't get to give it to the teacher
am i [\h__\h]
okay wow i couldn't do the oh [\h__\h] why
am i
why am i so [\h__\h] in this school
my dear
[Music]
it's also funny that after taking the
exam the next thing it asks you to study
for the exam it's a little bit too late
for that well okay it seems that every
friday is exam day ah
sad dana said purpose of life what
agency does serena really
even have
what she wants to do always feels out of
reach replaced only with an overarching
arching directive
of what she has to do
oh man
dana is like really quite a dramatic
teenager isn't she
[Music]
you did your homework what did we do
with you
you're like
wait we can study for exam
[Music]
there you go all right but hey
performance excellent
performance excellent performance we're
all doing good
i would say
[Music]
not so bad
wait wait i didn't ask somebody for pram
no i did i did i did that right yeah my
internal quest is completed i was just
about to say
i think we could
[Music]
okay
lunch ends in one hour is everybody
filled up yeah yeah yeah
honestly can wawa need some fun but oh
well
yeah
i did okay
i'm excited for this love triangle
everybody's gonna look so cute
and they're prom dresses
oh sweaters somebody's sucking up to the
what
we're trying to kill the principal
okay time for
next class yeah
but we might want to finish the
we still have like nine eight
seven yeah whatever go go
afternoon class let's go attend another
exam oh [\h__\h] right oh every class is an
exam now um can we like do this one at
least okay
[Music]
would you like to subaru um
not
zone out and maybe take the exam
she's giving herself a pep talk
no no no no no no no no no no
we want to graduate properly okay
please what did we what did we do all
the homeworks for what did we do all
that studying for
come on come on
seventeen
these kids are so stupid
[Music]
oh my god she was on her phone
are you done
are you done oh you can get done pretty
early i guess okay maybe the others
still have a chance um in that case if
we're really done
then
i would like some fun
uh in the computer room
[Music]
yeah have some fun
incredible sports
oh
okay
i don't know how that went
okay what's this what is this what's he
sees a pinch of satin left they say too
many cooks will spoil it bro okay
exams are finally over
oh
swagger had a rough exam day she might
want to study harder but the other two
did a great job and ace the exams
subaru really
i thought she was doing fine
oh man
okay
well i mean i think we still have one
week of school right
yeah so i think we're probably fine also
we're completely ignoring valentine's
day because we don't have time for that
prom is coming prom is coming tomorrow
okay can we do something about prom
we don't need anything anymore i guess
well we're fun
um all alright just singing
[Music]
do i have to work today
while i have to work again
it's all ours um
does not get a [\h__\h] break we don't
even need money right now we should quit
but we're not a quitter
mama didn't raise no quit uh
hmm let's get let's get our social up
yeah
social social social social social
social
social who do we talk to where is subhan
where's shaban
bye
kiss hands yeah
oh
yeah okay
let's do it
[Music]
what else can we do
oh
has two crushes
so widow has two crushes now
maybe we can get everyone to crash on
everyone
oh
open to improv
yeah some of the sentiments about
playing a crush
and impressed about the promposal
super sentiments about kiwawa
oh cooking together oh crush
but this is
this is
we're
[Music]
ah maybe we can get everybody to have
required love
hmm
i mean it's not really what i planned
but these sims are just too hormonal you
know
what can i do
[Music]
she just passed by and was oh reina is
losing control again but it doesn't
necessarily have anything to do with
this situation here
yeah she's fine she's fine she's fun
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah
okay kewala is going to work now we can
have some time to
[Music]
wants to perform a cheerleading routine
oh i'm gonna watch that
oh hell yeah
where's chico reena
where is that isn't it on the other side
of the school why are you going that way
what no wait uh it is here oopsie
okay
can you like run here
[Music]
ain't a
cheerleader let's cheer elena on
can we cheer the cheerleader oh they're
doing it together
[Music]
if that's not a special memory together
then i don't know man
yeah
nice turn
please
[Music]
yeah yeah they're so insane too sassooka
idols yeah
they're done
hell yeah i am
impressed ladies i am impressed now
let's do some flirting because
if if we can't have only some of them be
happy and in love we need everybody to
be happy and love you know equality
we need we need this to be fair and
equal
equal amounts of love for everybody we
don't want nobody to be sad
fooba
yeah
exchange number
oh damn super dude that's leg hair oh
dear
uh uh
it's fine it doesn't move i i don't i
don't mind it
embrace
yeah
oh
come on
did you just kiss your phone
oh yeah because you saved the number
[Music]
no no i can't do that we're not going
that far we're only platonic lovers
if anything
[Music]
oh yeah congratulations no wait shout to
my dad to my dad
you want to do another routine though oh
they're doing another routine
so motivated
give me a h give me an o give me an l oh
give me a t-o-r-i to skip some parts
[Music]
somebody's thinking oh yeah dana's
stinky
shower time
[Music]
i can't go i can't go
okay let's go home then
going home go home
now let's take a shower at home
we're actually doing pretty well now for
love day i guess oh
was calling she was checking up on the
girls
i i couldn't i couldn't pick it up sorry
sorry kawawa
why were you already home or what call
again
please
hold again i'm sorry
ah no sorry ghosted absolutely ghosted
okay left over time
stinky bird reyna takes a stinky shower
maybe even shapes how about that shave
that leg hair and let's see
how that happens
because i haven't seen that before
[Music]
she's smelling herself and enjoying it
oh
they put foam on and then oh they
actually have an animation for it
ah
oh and it does get the hydrogen up but
maybe not fully
i know it does it's just maybe it's a
longer shower
takes a little bit longer maybe oh
her legs are squeaky clean again
[Music]
voice
noise
oh so bad you're sleeping
so fast okay
it works out in an hour somebody just
wants to sleep uh
maybe it's time to quit oh just call in
sick yeah [\h__\h] it
someone is kind of depressed about work
anyway there in this cheerleading group
of chief to score of zero
go to the competition judges no no [\h__\h]
we're home already [\h__\h] you
hey we got 64 for sleeping yeah
that's how you win in life
yeah
that's it
[Music]
have you been around the whole time it's
been pretty [\h__\h] spicy
oh who is that oh thank you
candy bar for me
you already have two girlfriends is that
not enough
[Music]
she's that's that
is serbian excuse me go back inside
don't talk to these strangers
um
just what can we do aina
write write a fanfiction let out those
romantic feelings in the form of a
fanfiction
yeah
but
kiwawa needs to have some fun but the pc
is occupied
how else can we have fun
maybe practice dancing
[Music]
no okay she just goes to sleep okay
brenda was placed
even though we had zero points
i i guess there was no one else doing a
performance
[Laughter]
yeah congratulations later first in
cheerleading
nice yeah sometimes this is this is
pretty typical for sims
because no one else does anything so you
just automatically win
yeah what are you writing right now
uh
and
while reyna was showering somebody took
a peek
and was
feeling very romantically pleased by
what she was looking at meanwhile
while reyna was taking the shower being
peeked at by subaru she was actually
thinking about kiwawa
fantasizing and you know what why kiowa
was
no way while elena was sleeping thinking
about kimawa kimwa was
in bed dreaming about subaru
yeah love triangle
love triangle hold on love tori
love tony and guru tori
[Music]
is the title of this fanfiction
[Laughter]
don't don't write it like that subaru is
sick
definitely
today
[Laughter]
that's another name for our trinity
today
tony trio
uh turducken and
tori anguru
we have so many names
let's go
so many names man okay uh
we can sleep now also i think we have no
homework right and we do but i guess
over the weekend because classes and
free days
it's prom day tomorrow
it's prom day
prom day
everybody's sleeping to look pretty
tomorrow
yeah yeah yeah loved it was awful shut
up
i decided what it was like it was great
[Music]
okay thank god the toilet is so close
go why you gotta walk around there
well do this and then we um play sims
forever
get that phone up
how's your acne doing by the way ki wawa
you fine
yeah she seems fine
guys i'm so hungry
need to get prom over with soon
missed out on dreams it can get
frustrating when a simple task keeps
getting you mean these ones
[Music]
i've been too busy i can't take care of
all these things i know you can turn
them off though i think
yeah it's okay you know teenagers just
they do be frustrated it's natural
i'm just gonna roll with it
my moody teenagers it's just a phase
anyway
and then we take a speedy shower when is
prom how do we get to prom what are they
going to tell us also high school c
students let's see
i'm sure about that
everyone's flirty turd duncan
everyone's playful and flirty oh dear
these birds
oh so
sorry you wanted to eat something i'm
sorry
okay
[Music]
it hasn't been pranked in a while thank
god
dana finally has her pranking needs in
control but she does not have her
fantasies in control
suddenly she's mad did you see that
[Music]
drifting love
there it is
there it is guys
you have it
[Music]
caught the love of her life flirting
with another are they joking around or
losing interest
[Music]
rather
yeah
wait your love of your life is
who
chihuahua
do you have feelings for both now i mean
you're actually
[Music]
see
you're crashing on kiwawa but you have a
better relationship with subaru
[Music]
where did she flirt though right now i
don't see anybody it's you're if you're
imagining it
laura
you're imagining it
it's all in your head
[Music]
chatting with kiara and somebody
oh man how about you know let the anger
out by by cleaning the dishes
um
it's gonna be all right
hi joba just have to oh [\h__\h] you just
what um yep uh why
ah embarrassing
like nope well you could have cleaned
the dishes here it did sink
okay well
well it just gets worse and worse and
worse
um now nina
you're going to wait right until subaru
gets out yeah okay okay
[Music]
anyway
what do we do with you yeah let's go
with a little yeah yeah yeah
bring the spark photo and then let's
play some hoops
let's practice dribbling
[Music]
oops when is prom it's still early in
the morning so i guess
i have a lot of time
[Music]
why
repair that [\h__\h] i know you don't like
handiness but sometimes you gotta do
what you gotta do yeah
make lana flirt with kira so she gets
happy again okay
please mercilessly
ask for advice
now let's just let's just part
oh oh she can't she's too sad oh
denounce the merits of uh handiness okay
let's ask for advice
nervous
let's stop playing games let's focus on
elena cause she has serious problems
okay
it's just so hard being a teenager you
know
it's so rough stop taking selfies
[Music]
because
she's on uh
look at that one's just sad in general
let's be sad together i guess let's cry
it out together okay
oh my god these teenagers
[Music]
ah now she's sad because she's so cute
what's that but she's sad because you're
sad
[Laughter]
oh my god
girls
[Music]
for 450 dollars she just
are you in a midlife crisis girl
[Music]
why why would you do that
i did not she did that autonomously i
did not give her the permission for that
she just suddenly wants to climb him
climb the mountain
i thought somebody was gonna you know
what we can give the maybe it's a gift
to subaru
maybe
maybe she wants to get us to this good
side can we actually gift it i wonder
if the culture no
can i give it as a gift
is that a thing oh yeah gift gift
currently gift oh
because you know someone who has the
goal of climbing a mountain in her life
and elena would be in this way
supporting it we're totally gonna act
like as if this was always the plan
[Music]
subaru
was always gonna receive a gift from
elena
towards achieving her goal
definitely
don't be so sad you're doing a good
thing
i will forgive you for
wasting 450 bucks
if you give it to somebody oh
yay
happy right you're [\h__\h] happy let's
go
[Music]
how do you feel about that
quite happy huh
generous surprise
somebody was so happy to get a gift
recently from someone in this feeling
pretty special now you are spencer
elena made somebody feel special
okay let's complain about problems
that's me so when i was the only one in
this family who's not sad
but what if that makes some money
listen to that
[Music]
boy
ah let's ask for advice
[Music]
very positive person surely she'll be
able to give us a good advice to get
through this
these rough times as a teenager
oh
god rule yum
i think she's gonna feel better soon
[Music]
embrace
don't be sad she's sniffing again
deep conversation here
it's okay lena
what am i doing i'm just sad alone wait
i'm sad dude can someone cheer me up too
hello
oh my god super do your leg hair holy
[\h__\h]
i'm coming
can we can you help me be happy too
[Music]
can we cloud games together
oh yeah
oh hell yeah i'm not happy and i'm not
sad anymore but elena's sad clean it
what does it take to make you happy
maybe you can let out the frustration
online
[Music]
internet
read arbitraries blog about feelings
there you go
yeah
tell them tell them elena tell them how
tough it is
on blogspot
fulfill the dream oh okay
[Music]
finish reading
no
stop crying
finish reading
a book
discuss fears or after fulfilling once
discuss that okay discuss it with
chihuahua maybe
uh
where is that
[Music]
discuss discuss
disgust
[Music]
i don't see it her wishes are not the
best right now
i'm gonna get rid of these
can i get rid of oh i can't i can only
pin them
um i guess let's read a book
[Music]
ah last resort
read
love in time of sandwiches
sounds very romantic okay go go go go
oh she's not sad for much longer though
i think kiana just became good friends
with subaru
territory
what are you guys doing
watch funny video ah ah you're trying
trying to cheer her up but she needs to
read this book now okay she needs to
fulfill her dreams of reading a freaking
book
[Music]
actually it should take a shower though
stinky bib
[Music]
take a steamy shower
yeah they can be friends and still you
know it's important to build
a good friendship as a base
otherwise you know a relationship is
just not gonna work well this is the
best kind of relationship they say
is
you don't
is if there is like a good friendship
as a as a base layer fish pepperoni
[Music]
wait why don't you give up okay whatever
i need to read this book
stop annoying her
[Music]
of course that applies to love triangle
too
they will go through a freaking van they
will be able to you know go go for any
kind of struggles
chat with non-household sim
it is time to mingle no it is not time
to mingle
it's time to go to prom if anything
where is the info about the prom
fear of that
you know what
we will quit the job from subaru soon
but first we will shave those legs
shave leg hair
losing control
okay
what can i do for you
you want to ask danny to be girlfriend
chat with the non-household sim or
discuss fears after fulfilling once
those are kind of tough though
[Music]
crew
i'm sorry wawa
[Music]
take an angry poop
[Laughter]
[Music]
this world sucks hashtag life is unfair
hashtag it's not the face
crazy
it's true relatable it's okay it's okay
we all feel the same
oh
oh [\h__\h]
we pooped destroyed the toilet
oh you know what we're gonna replace it
i don't give a [\h__\h]
yes tom stomp on the bottle
destroy the bottle
destroy destroyed oh i'm happy again oh
no need to stomp yay
i'm inspired now
what can we do with this inspiration
[Music]
maybe
practice
did you finish the book she finished it
i think because she has a different wish
now oh no she's
she's reading
a different one the lord of the swings
he that sounds familiar be mischievous
miss jesus how can you be mischievous
besides cracking the toilets
i guess like a like a
hand um
shocking prank there you go
trick of hand was or
personal memories that still sounds like
the least
what
[Music]
mischief not so much
aina doesn't feel right about all these
tricks and games should you turn a new
leaf and accept that she dislikes
mischief but you just
[Music]
so it was just a phase
okay no more pranksters hallelujah
we're free from it listen to roman's
music listen to sing songs like okay i
think we don't have anything to listen
to though so we need some speakers
let me get some speakers
[Music]
oh can we have like some more um normal
ones
oh okay
like a like small oh this one's cute
it's like a small small one probably
even portable
okay
let's use that you know you're good
romance music oh yeah cause i i gave
lena uh as an interest in music i gave
her dolmen's romance music and sing
songwriter music for some reason don't
ask me why
[Music]
listen to
oh
i have to work on prom date wait didn't
say saturday or sunday for promo
[Music]
me
everyone is so inspired and confident
oh now they're traveling every day she
dribbling
wow um she's actually better with a ball
than i am
and that says a lot looking at that
ah even that slowly i would not be able
to dribble like that
it's kind of embarrassing but i
yeah i suck at that
i admitted
flirting
oh
whoo
complimentary appearance yeah oh no
she's going to work no
[Music]
with my noodle arms that's more like
skill
i would say
don't necessarily need to be buff right
to play
ball
[Music]
what i am doing
that reminds me of friends um
of joey what are you doing is that what
he said
oh second day
oh oh my
gosh
didn't you say what you're doing what
did he say
hey how you doing oh yeah
how are you doing
thank you for the rose berry we should
dance
we have a new crush all right so now she
has uh required love too cause like
because
crushing on nina
wait so is is elena crashing on two
people
[Music]
crash that's incredible that you can
have two crushes at the same time
yeah
oh
lovebirds
a connection of curious heights this is
shaping up to be a beautiful room
[Music]
okay
cute
love birds
very companion yeah
it's okay
breathe in breathe out i have the same
fear it's gonna be daijoubu okay if you
say so all is good
[Music]
ah
black virgin
that
i asked about that before i think but it
doesn't like always work um
like apparently
certain hairstyles
don't work with other outfits because
that's not the way they were like
intended to or so i don't know
yeah i know i mean that
[Music]
why it's not
possible with others like in some cases
i guess i maybe get it but
it would be nice to have them for
everything yeah
[Music]
you don't like being mischievous
i'm pranking
[Music]
felt inside joke oh yeah
and i'm practicing my new look
[Music]
oh
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
[Music]
no
i'm gonna cry i worked so hard to get to
this point
[Music]
oh
is it really because i'm at work or
would i really only be able to choose
one
uh
can i come after
i tried so hard again
[Music]
i was fearing this but i would think you
know
they would let me go before or i would
get an option to go to prom while at
work or so
no
[Music]
less alert never work
i gotta accept how it is guys this is
how it is ah we're not here but
but
but am i
am i at prom with them
or as a third wheel
oh [\h__\h] this looks pretty in here
all right we're just gonna make the most
out of it we're gonna enjoy it as if
we're all here together because we are
probably it's fine probably okay
can we like form a group
because i the way it looks like right
now when you're not in a group how do
you form a group again
[Music]
i don't see it i never did that before
i click on myself
[Music]
it's actions oh
actions aha thank you congress hi here
we go okay nice so can we like all drink
together oh we can't do it together okay
let's grab some fruit pouch
i never had fruit punch but i mean i
guess maybe i had like children's punch
before i guess i did have prep but not
like in this kind of situation you know
wait your dress is cool
dude who's singing
i just
oh nice
how can i like become prom queen how do
i become prom queen
kimono is an empress she needs to be
prom queen did i already get the drink
vote for primarily dance talk to someone
okay get the fruit punch
[Music]
oh you're already snacking
what they have oh they have a whole
roasted chicken and some yummy looking
stuff oh
[Music]
oh you can vote here okay
okay okay
we will vote for kiwa
will we
yeah we will yeah yeah yeah
thank you will vote can i vote for
myself
[Laughter]
i can't okay
i'll vote for elena then because she
looks like elsa right now
[Music]
hey well uh you can't do it right now
okay okay can we
can we take all the cups no we're gonna
leave with one
i thought we could do it we're all free
okay i'll take some pictures
lena lena voted for me that's very sweet
of you thank you can you go to the
toilet
[Music]
can i look inside
unfortunately there's not much to see
here except for this abdomination
this is how
we would look combined i guess
[Music]
that's what they were actually doing oh
come on
wait you can't woohoo in the photo booth
because i feel like you should be able
to do a woohoo in the photo booth
there's crazy at places that we that
sims woohooed in before
okay did i vote already i didn't there
you go
now
it's time
for elena to take
a romantic photo with subaru
we'll have all combinations maybe
we'll try
that skill required noise show of outfit
oh oh useful yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
uh
why does it say useful for me i already
used it
do i show off my outfit to just a random
person
[Music]
and a little bit someone that i already
talked to maybe
for you you're cute
dance with you
okay
[Music]
they're back they're back they're back
okay show off my outfit
is it here
oh
look at my beautiful gorgeous outfit
please
[Music]
i don't see it anywhere
ask to see out but that's not quite it
[Music]
ask about last night
actually is that access to
romans
[Music]
no
maybe it's a
pick myself option
[Music]
change outfit now
nope i don't know where it is
missed it twice
wait there it is show what happened uh
the first in the first place
wait we didn't take old pictures yet
wait wait who got the picture the last
one hey guys
[Music]
i thought you guys were like you know
i thought you guys had recruited
feelings for each other
why why are you pushing her away anyway
look at i think i got the most votes but
i think i kind of rigged it but oh well
you're gonna do what you gotta do
now
[Music]
can we dance
where are you going where you going
[Music]
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
why am i not the prom queen
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
wait wait prom where are you getting it
[Music]
i guess the strangers voted for her
it's only summer
okay well later looks looks fitting for
being a queen
too look at her
don't have a mental breakdown on stage
when you just became prom queen
okay okay well then you know you've got
that happy moment we're having another
happy titty moment okay we're having a
special time with each other
did i take uh photos with somebody
before yeah okay then i gotta do it
but but but but but let's um
let's like dance can we dance together
uh how can you dance together
not
here not here
not here
go get it
and fuse about dancing
it's not here is it romance
[Music]
i'm saying
i'm here how do you dance with somebody
dancing i try to
it just says go here
[Music]
um i mean i don't know oh it was i
forgot haven't played sims in a while
sweetheart dance
see that dance
show me tell me
she's enjoying herself up here alone
[Music]
oh sweet that is sweet what are you
doing chat with you okay okay okay you
know now is the time for lady
and chihuahua
to take romantic photo
go
and kiwa did get oh
dance of someone that seems like it's
done
yeah i'm gonna grab a drink hell yeah
let's get drunk
teenagers get drunk on the fruit punch
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
let's get those achievements wait why
are you still voting what are you voting
for can i vote again no i can't why
didn't he do that
[Music]
yeah i got the queen for myself all for
myself
oh there it is oh we got the same pose
[Music]
how about the friendly photo
no price complete
when it comes to the after party
after party
i guess we'll go
[Music]
hey
are we going to disco
the dance floor is not letting us go
oh what oh that's yeah i didn't show you
guys this place at all like there's this
new world you know where the school is
and has this whole thing here it's kind
of cute
yeah oh we can do some stuff here
together
can we go here a romantic ride with no i
want to do one spring
okay
well lena the queen
you
what can we do with you what is this
order drink
order
[Music]
iced coffee does that give her some
energy
also by the way they just go in and you
can't see
what they do during the romantic ride
unfortunately
oh it does help
just friends
[Music]
sudo has decided that she wants to talk
to kiara about her relationship
about their relationship
and what better way to communicate a
serious relationship than through a
cheesy plum bite pure attraction
is that twinkle in kenda's eye a hint of
attraction or irritation from the atmos
atmospheric fog being pumped into the
room does she try to try out the smolder
and attempt to win kiara over or does
she try to try and de-escalate the
romance and encourage a stronger
friendship
keep flirting or ask to be friends
i don't know somebody what do you want
what do you want spicy keep learning
somebody has learned canada's romantic
orientation
wait
nothing says i want to be more than
friends than being stuck on a ride with
someone while you're serenaded by the
smooth sounds of frank the flying womp
womp the two flirt for the entire ride
keeping within respectful boundaries but
also not backing down
not too exciting happened nothing too
exciting happened but something has
sparked within keana's heart that could
be a perfect opportunity for subaru to
pursue a relationship will there one day
maybe you'll find out in cuddle carts
the sequel
gained romans between writers started
crushing on ryder ah okay okay
yeah wait uh so subaru crashes on lane
on kiwawa now as she hasn't before
wait
[Music]
yeah cause she has she had a crush on ah
she had a crush on dana before
okay so they're crashing now
and then
kiara is
crashing
ah only on superhero but not only okay
okay i mean i'm [\h__\h] tired but maybe
no don't go home
no
can you take a romantic ride with uh
venus
come on you can fall asleep on her
shoulder or something that's cute too
oh don't go home no
[Music]
apple pie it's not over come on i should
sip one of those coffees too
okay okay we're going
wait go go go go
she gave up again
please please please let's not have this
a sad ending that only only ordained it
has unrequited feelings
[Music]
how about you eat something order food
what do we have oh puffies and hot
okay oh we could have done the horror
house ah they probably would have given
us a different prompt maybe
thank you for the pinkie thank you
courtney jail don't you mean horny jail
cuckoo
wanted to make the perfect romantic
atmosphere and found the couple cards
would be the best way what she wasn't
expecting was just how cheesy the ride
would be which isn't exactly the vibe
she was going for she looks at elena and
tries to gauge her reaction she can't
tell if she's in a corny into that corny
atmosphere or not oh i think she is does
cannon poke fun at the rat and add some
flirty banter to try
uh to try and make the moment a little
bit more romantic or does she embrace
that she's an attempt to show dana a
slice of playfulness
let's uh lean into the atmosphere
kiana has learned elena's romantic
orientation oh
it's cheesy short but it's adorable and
keanu can see that dana's enjoying the
ride
that's enough to encourage kiana to go
all in the rest of the ride keanu puts
on the performance of a lifetime in
perfect sync with the rides over the top
exits oh dana wipes tears from my eyes
from laughter and loves that kiana's
playing along with the classic ride this
playful side of kiana couldn't be more
attractive to lady
it's a fan picture
the sound of giggles from the cuddle
card put the rest
of the ride's lovey-dovey displays to
shame gained romance between riders
oh but didn't gain a crush
but this sounds wonderful though
[Music]
okay but i think
writing tongue of love
okay okay and then we need to sleep
and go home and
sleep enjoying that hot dog okay it's
time
can you make it to the toilet
oh no she fell asleep um
yeah that's uh
yummy uh let's um let's how do you like
immediately return home wasn't there
like a button to immediately return home
yeah
i want to stop her from peeing herself
here if possible party too hard
[Music]
i go maybe this way
press m
ah thank you
thank you genius
oh oh oh okay let me go here this is the
world by the way i didn't show you guys
i want to check out the place with the
cafe and all that at some point maybe
next time
okay i'm stale yes i'm still falls i'm
just trying to do
uh an msu video you know
[Music]
hi
hey in today's stream i'm just doing
these three but previously i made all of
myth and then i made all of council and
iris
yeah
and yeah now it's turducken time
can't keep well make it to the toilet
let's go please please please please
please please please please come on
oh oh oh oh oh oh yes i know you can do
it kibaba i believe in you
you know this is not so normal sims
often just you know
riding
right in front of the toilet even
sometimes
they still pee themselves
okay leftovers and then sleep super
noodle is not hungry so somebody just
goes straight to sleep nice
yeah
seem very interested in sims when uh
oh [\h__\h]
okay whenever you sleep
or just eat i don't know [\h__\h] you're too
sleepy to eat
asleep
um yeah when i saw luna on twitter she
was you know
excited about sims
i'm glad i'm glad that there's more sims
fans there
oh yeah the toilet was pranked ah
at the worst times man
okay
dana you have to repair that
you made
chihuahua feel miserable in that moment
okay
and we can meet friends online
yeah you mean on the pc like you mean an
option to meet friends online is that
gone
[Music]
really
i'm not social bunny dog because that's
a new feature now that they just added
of high school
uh i wonder if you can meet friends for
that
on twitter
why muna did you have troubles finding
friends and sims in other ways
there's so many ways it's so easy you
just go out into the street or like you
you talk to the first person that comes
to your house
shayna
is why is she walking like this
i've never seen a sim walk like this
before
okay that may have been a bug
it was
here
it's summer
[Music]
what oh the music what
what woke you up
[Music]
i rolled you up
wait if you take a shower you should
shave your legs
because that's the thing now
do that too yeah
co-op
same spring
there's a mist oh there it is
hey really i barely played sims 3
i think
oh no no no
when it when sims 3 was the most
newest one i think i barely played it
was there really a co-op feature
i don't remember that i guess i just
didn't have any friends to play
like sim spray co-op with
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh well before you use it yeah clean it
was it actually like good though
are they
yeah
i'll i'll look it up
i don't i can't imagine i feel like i
would have heard about that maybe i
heard about it and forgot it
because that's
like an online sense that
that's legendary
i thought he had five friends well in
school maybe for a while
not when the same spring was
anyway
um
we successfully lived one week
with turducken
we did our exams they were okay
uh we did prom we did have to party and
we have everyone in love with each other
which was not even the original
intention
so
i'm gonna end it here and i'm gonna grab
a snack and some uh go to an island
meeting and then we'll read super chat
though so i hope you guys enjoyed this
turd duncan episode
this is how it would have been
if turducken was all we're all teenagers
at the same time in the same place
yes
this is how it would have been 100
accurate as always
i'm glad that kiwa made it to prom in
the end even though for a moment i
thought she wasn't gonna make it hmm
nice can't wait for the anime adoption
yeah yeah yeah no this is the anime
adaption it's animated
yeah
spicy episode
you know i just feel uncomfortable um
making them actually do something we'll
see about them but
there's teenagers okay
gotta be careful you know
but
yeah
we'll see how it continues at some
points
[Laughter]
[Music]
on
yeah yeah but i can't i have to make a
good example for my viewers you know we
have some
children watching maybe
laughter
i have to
you know
you know be a good example yeah
i can't let my
sims do two spicy things spicy hmm
educational
[Music]
family friendly yeah yeah yeah yeah
we'll see we'll see um thank you
everybody for watching so far i'll see
you in a few minutes
uh in my office and then we'll talk
about that union that i heard about
yeah
i'm very disappointed
and very angry we'll talk about that
you thought i would let that slide huh
no no no no your little shits
i'll have you all lined up outside
outside of my office all right in five
minutes
if you're not there
you know where you're going
[Music]
you
me
[Music]
away
[Applause]
me
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
now
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
yummy
so
i ate
johnny
it was quite yummy
and i hope that's a
warning
for all of you
uh-huh
johnny
is no more
now
it was my brother
i don't care i mean in theory you guys
are all
adopted by me so you all are adopted
relatives anyway
it doesn't matter
johnny is
dead
johnny is no more
okay yeah had a yummy toast of chicken
on top i guess
like quickie
that's how quick it can be guys
be careful y'all always say oh i want to
be eaten by chihuahua but when it
actually happens it's terrifying
terrifying i tell you
for sure
exit game
yeah yeah yeah that was high school i
mean we didn't do much in the aspect of
youtubing i guess but we can do that
also next time like you know there's a
few things to explore
in high school years so
another time not immediately but another
time
we can check out the the whole v tubing
thing a little bit more i don't know if
there's even like that much more to it
besides you know choosing the avatar and
then sitting in front of your pc and
maybe getting some prompts every now and
then
um yeah i love triangle i was so busy
with that
it kept me freaking busy
okay
[Music]
first
ah don't you sleep i will sleep yeah
it's still well it's just 9 p.m now so
it's all right
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay i'm scrolling i'm scrolling
scrolling scrolling nobody man you don't
hear this oh
what about now
now you should hear it
still got some angela yeah now that i
had like a quick
a quick snack i'm i think i can go along
although i kind of want chocolate to
chocolate chocolate
yeah nostalgic bgm
we're going with that now
hope it's okay
go grab some okay
didn't need your permission anyway
my cats
my cats want my attention also my legs
feel weirdly like
jelly
it's weird like not like you know noodle
arms ha ha
they feel like uh jelly
maybe it's because i didn't have a
proper dinner last night
oh [\h__\h] there's only two left in this
package i have like
you know those those
bars and messi no those um i guess
they're like those
java cakes jelly cakes huh
with the jam inside and the chocolate
and the biscuit
noodle arms and jelly legs yummy
you could snack on me i look like a
snack
jaffa not jabba i guess okay
yummy i only have two left
adobe snack
hmm
you know there's several
versions of them like there's a version
with raspberry jam but the classic of
orange
or
i think it's orange jam it's just the
best one
classic
oh
okay i found
the beginning
okay
you don't like the orange one oh
yeah there's dark chocolate too
as i grow older i'm starting to like
dark chocolate hmm
now i understand my mommy always asking
for dark chocolate it's like your taste
buds they just change
yeah yeah but i still mostly just eat
milk chocolate yeah
and and white chocolate yum yum yum
okay
let's do this
let's
do this let's do this
okay let's ignore the mentions on on on
discord for now
spinach ew now not even going to try
i'm not even going to try it
your taste you change tastes every five
years if you don't like something else
right in the future
i don't know
maybe in 10 years
[Laughter]
[Music]
have i ever told you how cute your life
is it's been quite the run everyone and
i hope we can continue having fun
my laugh really is it cute
i have many different ways of laughing
though
it's cute thanks guys
can i love being part of kfp and
watching your stream you're an amazing
entertainer that have inspired me to
pursue my dreams of being a pro fighter
oh
however i must say goodbye tomorrow the
deep fryer waits and i will accept my
fate as a bucket
don't say goodbye
it's not a goodbye you continue watching
my streams right
even as a bucket you can still watch my
streams um don't scare me
profile to do what what first we have a
pro racer
pro car racer now we have a pro fighter
i know
you guys dream big huh
okay have fun and put don't don't get
your nose broken too often
that kind of job man so
kind of dangerous you [\h__\h] up your body
don't you
yeah a tank driver yeah
well good luck and thank you for the
support i hope it goes well
beaks are sturdy um really
we're going to test it out
[Music]
robert carney thanks for the pinky best
girl kiara
i'm the best girl
am i also the best verve oh yeah hell
yeah right
i would say so
best everything
best cutie pie
best
[Music]
thank you
yeah there was a house somewhere that i
didn't do right
mr is done
thank you for the red super chat thank
you
[Music]
thank you other animal songs
just like animals yeah that was a
oh
thank you for the pinkie thank you for
huh all these songs are different when
you sing them really
thank you it was not a solo shakira song
but you know two birds with one stone
by singing shakira ex rihanna
yes
yeah yeah they're both really really
great artists
yeah thank you thank you for listening
um i hope i can sing more shakira songs
for you but actually
you know i used to when i was younger i
was listening to a lot of rihanna and uh
black appease and so on but shakira
only really knew two songs or so so
yeah
i would have to learn them
yeah the music video was spicy right
yeah
t-y valgus or thai team bogus thank you
for the thinking as well i love you
singing your karaokes are so much fun oh
thank you very much
um i'm glad i could do another
um
i know i got karaoke for the first time
in a while thanks for coming in joining
and having fun together thank you
[Music]
chat
there are a few things that can end a
week like a kiara okay no matter what
the week has been or what might be
coming you make a smile a beautiful song
bird that just makes the worries and
stress of life mouths away keep singing
you amazing feelings you're not tired
thank you
i know like i don't know
for the first half of the karaoke i was
like
i don't know
my my voice was just not coming out
properly i felt like
it was a bit hard to sing
hope you still enjoyed it the second
half was okay is i guess
i love every channel okay thank you
sweet escape was good
so much fun
i hope you guys are singing along at
home
type on youtube
yeah thank you so much for the sweet
words thank you you're so kind
[Music]
ellen thank you
i just wanted to say thanks for all the
streams you gift us
and no matter what you do it's obvious
from your charisma how much you care
about your chickens you radiate a unique
fiery energy
that warms my heart every time i see you
oh thank you
yeah
so warm and hot and fiery that every
time i walk into a building the fire
alarm goes off
i'm sorry
yeah
too too hot
too hot
thank you so much thank you
taco
sauce sauce
that alone
but i will trust you for now and you
will welcome to stay in kfp
continue supporting kiwa
also i see that the superchat is in
euros
so you're from europe makes sense are
you okay if we taco taxi because you can
watch like kibaba
and then you watch inna and then you go
to sleep probably
[Laughter]
brandon thank you thank you
thanks for another beautiful kia logan
my big cuddle demanded to be held for
the entire show
really we love you edm dancing thank you
oh was your cat following the screen
with its eyes
i can imagine like the way i was moving
around the screen
the cat may have paid attention to that
because like smoothie also
i feel like she may have reacted to that
if she would have seen them
hmm
oh man i'm so jealous
my cats they don't want to be held
you need to appreciate that every moment
of that spanking ham
not every cat likes to do that you have
a good cat
good god
yeah
treat your cutter well
give love to kato
give everything you have to kanto
thank you
i watch all kiara broadcasts 4 am korean
time i watch it even when i fall asleep
ah thank you
thank you oh fighting
[Music]
for faith all mortal possessions to
cuddle
yes
i agree
that's what i'm doing always
[Music]
why can i do it wait wait can i go like
this
[Music]
rooney are you here are you in the chat
you need
then i do this
thank you wait oh no it didn't show it
was supposed to be my heart oh well
it didn't actually work
okay already
[Music]
it doesn't work like that i don't know
never mind oh well imagine hearts
uh jules verne
valkyrie
[Music]
ah
please don't hurt me oh yeah when i was
thinking [\h__\h] but i have my money
that song oh man
when that song first came out it freaked
me out i think the whole like what what
is this what is this huh
how intimidating oh no
but apparently it had a good effect on
my viewers too
pay off kfc
[Music]
please spare me no
no one gets spared simply the fact that
you super chatted means you actually
gave yourself away
out of your own will so i don't see why
you're complaining
[Music]
on
okay just don't hurt me
i could never
could never do such a thing no
i didn't just eat somebody one of you
guys no
probably not
this works too well i guess i'll take it
now thank you dragon spire
where'd you steal duncan you are dancing
[Music]
these are still all from [\h__\h] but i
have my money
belt
speeds
i need to sing the song every time i
sing karaoke
man
that's quite the miraculous effect yo
the satisfied question foreign
[Music]
i don't think it's been said enough but
your singing skills are really great i
know we always say this is the best kind
of ever but you do really do improve
every time you do karaoke and that's
amazing
oh love you
thank you
[Music]
mystical sampling non-cushions
flaming pants functional vibration
kitchen they give a creepy thunder
but you really are a talented singer and
these karaokes are always great thank
you i'm glad you enjoyed them
[Music]
my
i sang it for you basically because i
saw you know i saw that request i was
like huh
shawnee
can't be helped yeah
he really wants that hey yeah
[Music]
hey
makes what makes but what makes a living
[Music]
one of the best songs in existence
i can never get that part right though i
stumble over my shakers shake it shake
shake shake shake it
shake it shake shake it shake it shake
shake
[\h__\h]
normally i would just go you know
randomly go like shake shake shake shake
it [\h__\h] i don't know but i realized when
i was singing it in karaoke
that the lyrics are not quite the same
just shake it shake shake it shake it
shake shake it i think
[Music]
thanks for the pinky
listen to our attention on one and only
ocean i don't know who that lucas is but
i can surely tell you that with chickens
would never plant a new uni and we're
too scared i mean we love you way too
much and you raise us to the good loyal
chickens
i said look i said yolk
all right i think i trust you fro fro
yo trustworthy chicken
yeah
you can be trusted you're on my side i
know that
thanks thanks guys
look angie thank you so much
[Music]
do birds fly when they go to school
no
because we want to blend in and be
normal
like the others you know
unless it's a bird school
it's called birds like a school of fish
huh
you don't say that about birds huh
no flying no no
although maybe it would have helped in
some situations
um
yeah yeah
marshall come on thank you soon
[Music]
nice hat it's not the hat
but it's pretty isn't it shiny whoa
whoa
i'm a sam i always wanted this thing
above me it's so cool that i can do it
now perfect for the sim stream i
couldn't place it any higher though
because then it wouldn't place to like
it wouldn't stick to my head
but it's like kind of
low
but it works
lovely shade of green right
it's so pretty it's just so full of life
make it smaller no this is the size it's
supposed to be
thank you
soon
when was this where were we going i
guess just maybe this was after i showed
off my
my
sims
i think i did a great job this time i
feel like if i would have done it on
stream i definitely wouldn't have done
such a good job
so i hope it was okay for you guys that
i did that
i hope it was okay
you didn't really you know i showed you
anything so you didn't really miss out
on anything um
if i just have to make one sip you know
that's okay but the more i have to make
the more accommodates and we're trying
to make them look like somebody so
yeah i don't know you know i had a day
off so
suddenly i felt like creating the sims
on my day off yesterday
yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
thanks for the pinky today i woke up and
something
in my back cracked and looked at the
calendar and noticed that i'm getting
older yesterday is my birthday who can't
believe this is my second birthday here
thank you my auntie that i can spend it
with you and carefree for a moment i was
worried about you yo
well congratulations
[Music]
i already kind of gave you a birthday
gift by playing kyle the other day
[Music]
congratulations
again mcfee duncan
for the rest of the chat
and so the story begins a long time ago
in a burp house far far away
yeah i think it's good it was a good
choice to go with turducken
yeah i thought you know i kind of want
to do odenza too but i thought two two
characters is maybe a little bit too
boring
three minimum
for this kind of
playthrough i would say
don't think it was a good choice yeah
a perfect long triangle yeah
yeah i think so too
yeah
golden number number three
yeah thank you glad you guys liked it
thank you james big
wow
oh how can wait there's another pinky ah
every year it's getting better and
better here thank you for creating such
amazing community that i can be part of
and being lovely phoenix love you thank
you so much thank you again for sharing
ko on memphis i appreciate it a lot
i'm glad i could make someone happy with
that game because everybody else didn't
seem to know it but
you knew it i'm glad
i didn't know it either before
[Music]
but good to know it's from poland ah
interesting
that poland also makes some
decent games like i i thought it was
nice oh it was fun
oh
so now you get a kiss because it was two
pinkies haha birthday case for the
birthday boy
yeah
patsy duncan squiggly mustache
oh no
entry log four looks like jim survived
maybe that will help me get forgiveness
from mamma inna
can't go back yet it's no longer about
survival i found out kfb has a secret
must find a secret for tentacles
secret
what secret could he mean
we may have many secrets
must protect maybe it's the spices
the spices in our recipes
i will say nothing without my lawyer
no everybody you have to protect
the secret i don't know if it's a secret
you guys don't know either but in any
case we have to protect it
no i want a burger
well okay i'll eat some pizza afterwards
y'all
[Music]
jessica here yes you're my favorite
youtuber so happy you're enjoying the
pack oh
thank you for the research i don't know
if you're still watching
or if you were watching you know the
whole thing until now
well thank you so much for coming by
oh as i said i was so happy to hear that
and
you don't have to you don't have to
admit anything
publicly
but
we both know
that avatar that's me that's me
i was actually not even the first one to
notice nothing was my viewers who told
me about the stream and the
the avatar and i was like no [\h__\h] way
you guys are just teasing me again just
pranking me again was in pre-chat people
were like oh look at this hey yo
[Music]
official sim stream is referencing you
there's a reference of you in the game
and i'm like no [\h__\h] way shut up
[\h__\h]
yeah cause it sounds insane
this sounds crazy like i've been playing
sims my whole [\h__\h] life
and now
apparently i'm i'm relevant enough
to be referenced to secretly in the game
yeah
that's amazing
wow yeah it's crazy
[Music]
leads to things like this sometimes
huh yeah
[Music]
um
next step is official kiwa
um dlc
i can't really see them doing something
like that but as i said before i feel
like i said this somewhere
i know maybe i just wrote it to genma
like um
uh
what sims would do
is like maybe at the most
make an npc
um
with a name like takanasi kiyada
and you know make her look a little bit
like me
that's something they might do yeah
yeah yeah yeah
because also so far what they did with
like other sims related custom
content creators not custom
content creators in general on youtube
it's like they they got um
some fans who make videos like building
videos and stuff
to
make actual official
lots that come with
an expansion pack
like a recent expansion pack
had
you know every expansion pack comes with
a new world
and one of those worlds
single lot was made by one famous
sims youtuber
oh
thank you for getting my merchandise in
any place cafe thank you
yeah so they they are quite um the
how to say
sims 4 or sims in general
the creators
are
like i i don't know any other game
that listens so much
to their audience they try to make every
wish of their audience come true
yeah
there's so many things that came out in
the game
like packs and stuff content items and
so that were
asked for by the community and voted for
by the community there's literal whole
expansion packs like the like the extra
gameplay packs or whatever
that were voted
uh
for
by the community like they decided they
had a choice like what do you want and
then they vote for it and that's what
they make
yeah
sims has become
like so much
like a community created
game at this point
yeah
crazy
they don't have to
listen to so many
you know
requests and
opinions but they do they do
i mean there's still definitely room for
improvement
like for example the very recent the
high school pack when it came out it
came with a lot of
yeah by bugs that need to be fixed
immediately because those are actually
very disruptive of the gameplay
like apparently
like aging automatically out of nowhere
i don't know i didn't experience that
bug but i don't know what exactly
happens but
yeah there's a lot of problems and uh
thankfully we didn't really run into
those big bugs today yeah
yeah
it's all right but yeah i think they're
trying
their best they want the best
for the community
and yeah
yeah that's cool that's nice to see
oh
oh i think i saw
like a clip i didn't click on it but
it's all clipped like that
that scrub
yeah i'm sure she doesn't want you guys
to be sad yeah
it would break my heart too if i had to
leave kfp behind like that holy [\h__\h]
that's that's the most
heartbreaking
and sad thing
to consider to think about like
you know that's definitely one big thing
that keeps me
from
[Music]
you know
you guys are
big big big big reason i'm still here
i couldn't break your heart like that
yeah
i don't want my
i don't want all these people
who call me their ocean
to be sad and lose their roshi i don't
want to take that away
i would feel
really bad you know
feel like i have a
an obligation
to be here for you guys now which is
okay like i'm not feeling forced okay
i'm still enjoying it so it's okay
you know it's not like oh you want to go
but i have to stay
no no no
but it just felt again so real when i
saw you know
in the chat the satellites
being so sad broke my [\h__\h] heart
yeah
very heartbreaking
[Music]
yeah
anyway
thank you jessica mwah
i'll play sims again sometime and if you
if you want to you know
involve kiwawa in something let me know
i'm fully open you're probably not
watching anymore but i'm fully open
wait you're still watching you just
joined the membership
yo yo yo i'm serious yo yo yo i wanna
you know i i understand you know you
know you probably wouldn't like sims
probably wouldn't sponsor
my streamer so i don't know but um just
you know you know like you know keep put
put like a kiwama npc in there
yeah
like as a famous person that you can
meet
hit me up
welcome
to the membership
it would be so cool
a tour of the studio
wait where is the studio i'm guessing
somewhere in america but
where is it
oh i hope if it's in
if it's in la then i just missed it oh
man
where would that studio be
san francisco
oh
no
that's a good reason for me to visit san
francisco again
cool i'll remember that
yeah probably not within this thing
would not have been this year i probably
wouldn't
go back to america so soon
but next year
maybe i'll do like a little tour
through the big cities
a couple of big cities
in america
yeah do a tour
need to go to
new york
new york a gamble in las vegas
should i go gambling in las vegas just a
little bit just a little bit just a
little bit just you know she's a tiny
[\h__\h] i go with a budget of um
[Music]
200 bucks
what cities i see only l.a to be honest
so far and even like from l.a i didn't
see that much because the trip was
relatively short
and mostly work um
blackjack yeah blackjack i could do
blackjack hell yeah
i'll do blackjack
and save scum
oh
yeah
no safe's coming huh
damn it really we can try i uh let me
let me
let me try to pull up the menu push this
escape button push this escape button it
doesn't work
[\h__\h]
what if i just look at them with doggo
eyes
[Music]
push
yeah no i can't play poker i don't know
how to play poker like of
any any of those games because i don't
know the the value of the cards and all
that and the rules i don't know anything
about it
yeah
the only game like that that i can play
is blackjack
i need to teach myself sometimes
learning clubhouse but they don't uh
they don't
they explain like the main rules of
poker and so on
but they don't explain the values of the
cards they assume you already know it i
think
poke a teaching stream is there any
whole life member at that length is
known for liking poker
very much and
being good at it
those polka like poker
[Laughter]
furuka just because your name is poroka
are you just saying that because her
name is produka i'm just assuming
it seemed like the yen girls know poker
oh
yeah maybe i should really have one of
them teach me at some point
[Music]
kylie's card game is texas hold'em
uh-huh
chloe
okay well well
i'll think about there's no no um sudden
urge but before i go to las vegas i want
to learn how to play poker
nah nah i don't know what about roulette
for that i wouldn't wanna i would wanna
try roulette to
roulette
yeah
because you don't really need to do much
you know you don't need to know much for
roulette right you just you just uh
choose a number like a little
little square thingy
and then you hope that
it lands
on your thing
all on red
i'm gonna pick a color and a number and
then just hope but the chances are so
low then
because there's so many numbers and so
many
fields
aren't the chances like incredibly low
why is roulette so popular
there's math involved
really really
it can be combinations
only ah you can also only pick colors
but then i guess the
the payback is small
i suppose
the point
yeah
better than the slot machines it's not
my shoes it's just boring like so
boring
like that's really just to
help your addiction
but like roulette and poker and so on at
least they have like some kind of
gameplay and and
i don't know it feels more like a game
slot machine doesn't feel like a game
yeah it's just gotcha
it's just
it's just staring at numbers and signs
in front of your
face
like when i see people in front of slot
machines look looks like they
they're just not there like
looks like they're zombies
yeah lifeless zombies
the other people look like they're
enjoying it
the roulette people
the polka people
they look like they're having a blast
unless they lose but then you know
they're still not lifeless
okay let's let's read let's read
pinky high tension didn't win the crx
lottery but going to the expo anyway you
know if gifts are being accepted i have
a certain white strats card that i have
two of okay so actually jenna was
listening when i first read your super
chat
she wrote to me already in a dm a gifts
are not accepted but letters and cards
are so
since you just want to give me a card
you could put it into an envelope with a
letter
and that would actually work
um in that case it actually works
yeah also pokemon uses one time again
it you guys said morning time didn't you
morning time for me or morning time for
your what
morning time for japan
open
when when
preview my time
oh
i could even stream it but it's not a
it's not a nintendo thingy it's only a
pokemon thingy so
ah nah not worth it because i actually
want to do something tomorrow um around
that time before my stream
i actually need to get something done
yeah i'm probably not around anyway i
mean i could i could make time but it's
not really worth it i think
mm-hmm
if it's a nintendo direct i would do it
yeah
yeah no need
yeah okay
we agree we agree we agree to agree
but i will watch it anyway and i'll tell
you
about my opinion in the snack box stream
then uk stock box
yeah
i wonder if there's any uk snacks that
are also available in
austrian supermarkets
that i could buy to enhance my snack box
a little bit more last minute
but you guys wouldn't really know unless
you're austrian
is there something
chocolate cakes
cadburys camper cat the berries
kitkats are british
really that's actually amazing
category chocolate let me see have i
seen that before
no
and that might even be in the box i
didn't take a look yet
uh toblerone that's not british isn't
that switzerland
[Music]
england
mars bars eh
really
is that from england england is a
snacks in supermarket
i mean here
yes swiss
snow white gets a british did i get
bamboozled
let's start by
christian superman
after it's oh i don't like after eight
last time i ate them is a long time ago
maybe i should try again
i mean yeah i just don't really like
them
oh
maybe brexit made it harder to get
snacks from england
and now in
supermarkets nestle is british
really
much
[Music]
wait i found some kind of website but it
says
nestle swiss stop lying to me guys then
these people trying to claim everything
is england to save
them their asses
from being
exposed
they're originally from the uk
huh
apparently not though
nestle
is in switzerland
but apparently originates in america
kinder is british [\h__\h] i know that's
italian even though it sounds german
because it's definitely german
but i don't know why they chose a german
word why did they chose a german word
[Music]
deutsch
um
[Music]
right it's not just a german
name in here
it's not an answer it's not an answer i
want an answer i need answers
i need answers
i guess maybe they just wanted
to get the germans who like their
chocolate
hmm
like he wanted because kinder is german
for children
and the answer i find here is the the
dude wanted the italian dude wanted
children to like his chocolate
but why didn't he name it the italian
word for children
when he was italian
and the whole brand is italian
clothes with children
uh
startup this is in germany
oh well
kinder is catchier
maybe maybe
sounds better
maybe he has he had some like i don't
know german ties maybe he had
and i mean thai it's not fuzz
maybe he had like a dream and a wife or
something german girlfriend
some kind of connection
i
[Music]
oh
yes and i know thanks for the pinky
that's another dream real kfc work i'm
really glad i hope working here for you
generally korean coffee loves you
hey did you dream about me
it's not a dream it's real
oh
lady
said
i'm so happy that
that korea likes me i'm really really
really honored and flattered
that you guys like me thank you
thank you
very happy thank you
yeah
so i'll come to korea soon and i'll see
you guys somehow
thank you thank you
thank
thank you thank you for the pinky
and tears about something i already
answered this thanks for the pinky
thanks for the pinky
i might check again though if some some
some hairstyles are like movable to
certain
bottles
yeah it would be cool but
i think you know there's some
surprisingly it's not that easy
apparently
mp one side three garlic's function
rodney a brew baker thank you
maybe something like a prawn party in vr
with your friends oh
yeah we could do a prom with whole live
english like a prom world
get everyone prom dresses
oh yeah sometime maybe
it's cute
drink punch
take photos in the photo booth we could
program a photo booth
and then yeah vote for prom queen
and try to dance with each other
oh yeah
thank
thank you
yeah girl's complicated very complicated
krishnan supra muni thank you for the
pinky first time sending you super chat
just want to say thank you thank you
was necessary but i appreciate it thank
you so much
well i had something to do mandy and
sign um priorities
important priorities
i needed to make it happen
soon
more vacations for you for me i'll miss
this okay
as a public supporter of the carefree
union i must make our intentions clear
we aren't requesting more pay we are not
requesting workplace safety we willingly
want to be cooked our desire is more
vacations for you
if that is true
[Music]
then i might you know have nothing
against it but we'll see i don't know i
feel like there's still some people who
are trying to use me
[Music]
fox70 thank you soon
chuckyfund thank you we're gonna make a
hot or like a cold chocolate after the
stream
because i have some milk left over
that's gonna go bad soon maybe
once one chocolate milk
rice or free time the four arc angel
cereal
this was one of the best tips for
streams really i wasn't sure i felt like
you know because i was trying hard to
handle the sims
that i felt like i was so occupied with
it
[Music]
thank you
scrub thank you soon
[Music]
it was fun really you're not just saying
that
really
thank you
scrubs
no scrubs
sorry to scrub
sorry
so much fun thank you
great stream thank you
you think too much
also known as a buster
love him thank you yeah the love
triangle spice it up spicy
oh man
and you know we can
we can have you know this triangle
romans but i don't think like you know
triangle marriage is possible
that's not possible so we can never go
that far it will break someone's heart
although i think if anyone would um
leave that
on their own
accord it would be subaru
subaru would
surely
leave
pawanashi to themselves
supportively
and cheer for them
if we're talking
real people
i don't know about sims value
seems someone is a little bit different
a little bit
with mods anything is possible
oh
i guess so
probably
polygamy polygamy
bud
see
the thing is like um
generally
mods are not allowed for games
that we stream
but then for sims you know they call
like cc and all that they also call that
mods but that is kind of like allowed
like no travel with that because like
the sims 4 community like the creators
they support it
they support it but i don't know how far
it goes like
how far
that would be supported and and okay
within my
permission to stream the game
when is a mod
like not acceptable anymore i don't know
acceptable
but i don't i don't necessarily need it
right now so i'm cool with it
yeah minecraft i guess is an exception
to
maybe no but the thing is with minecraft
we also have to ask every mod creator
yeah and shader creator
so
it's not that easy
yeah i'll just uh
deal or chill with what sims has to
offer for me now and i really really
really want to play sims 1 sometime soon
the games are waiting i have them i got
all the sims 1 games yo
[Music]
it will be insane but
i need to play sims 1. you do i need to
feel that nostalgia um
can you marry girls and sims one oh
i think
yes maybe
but you know since one was so
underdeveloped in terms of you know
things you can do in the game that you
know
children would not even grow up into
adults so
don't don't expect too much from sims
one
in terms of what you can do but the
thing is though sims one had so many
great expansion facts like the magic
expansion pack was
incredible
at least back in the day i felt like it
was insane if i would play it now i
don't know how i would feel about it now
maybe maybe now it's not so much
incredible anymore but it was incredible
it had really cool expansion packs
ah according to google they can't get
married ah
and well that's um you know
old sims
orange for sims one two people will be
hot enough to help that is true yeah
true true that could we could do that
because yeah i was i was already like
scared of
handling too many people in sims 1
anyway yeah two is already
even two is tough
in sims 1 you have no idea man if you
didn't play it before you have no idea
it's really tough out there
black rich and duncan
thank you for the rest of the chat hi
attention this birthday message is late
because you've been crazy busy me
i guess so
even though you sent me to the usual
room a lot i want to say you'll forever
be my aussie and i l word you
you mean you love me
[Music]
why you why won't you say it
happy birthday kia i'm looking forward
to what you'll do next also hello genma
i albert you too telstar thank you
thank you very much for the red super
chat
and i think genma is not listening
anymore but thank
you mwah
please continue
supporting cuba
in my endeavors
[Music]
thank you as you may know i enjoy
drawing however since i fell into this
rabbit hole whole life ideas have
plagued my mind how can i ask my osha to
stop living rent-free in my head without
she sending me to the usual room
why would you even want me not living in
your head
no i will not move out i live there
small place my home
yeah
you can't kick me out what the [\h__\h]
for the pink super chat
they're getting it they're getting it
they're picking it up correctly
i hope
i hope patrick will cast a guilt was an
understandable concept for korean
viewers
needs subtitles we need to put subtitles
on the on that video
yeah
hashtag vocabulk
[Music]
let me see um
watch
only
kiara every day
hashtag walk means
[Music]
that's what it means
brew up two flashbacks
that's all right it's funny i like room
of truth
okay
okay everybody i'm done reading
i will go now and
make food
and then sleep and then
tomorrow i will eat delicious question
mark
european uh
english
british snacks
yeah i have to go
i have to go
that was by accident
[Music]
i'll see you my
my
british friends i'll see you tomorrow
tomorrow
yeah tomorrow
thank you for streaming thank you for
watching oh six hours down
damn
[Music]
did i say i wanted to remember something
the thing what thing what thing the
thing i want to do tomorrow oh i won't
forget about that it's my skit it's my
schedule it's in my schedule
as a uk resident i apologize hey but i
really liked your potato chips over
there i really liked those enough
[\h__\h] the proper corn
those were amazing
i might like your snacks
i think your snacks are probably better
than your actual like you know
restaurant food and all that
hmm
i think that applies
correctly
a new remix of fifa night really
send it to me
what you remind me about what thing
what i didn't ask for a reminder and the
memphis wallpaper okay i can do that but
you didn't mean that right
arrived late
thank you for coming though have fun
with the ball
you guys are just trolling me now
you don't even know what the thing is
you don't know i don't know we don't
know we all don't know but i will put up
the members wallpaper yes
thank you and in german we say our
freedom
thank you
thank you for watching
good night
[Music]
later
thank you thank you
thank you
yeah
thank you light oh thank you
oh saturday you missed saturday
oh you're going to miss saturday
all right one of the first streams
you'll miss in a long time that's okay
have fun
[Music]
why why why you're so late
ah
i hate the korean
oh
[Music]
korean pronunciation so cute what the
[Laughter]
[Music]
kawaii
you