[Music]
k
k ah sorry for the weight H where's my
[Music]
chat there you are
hi party time yeah I I figured what
should I wear and I realized oh I hav't
wear this for a while and we also
weren't in this room for a while oh
let's turn this Echo
off 47 months thank you hello welcome
[Music]
everybody yeah fancy
w a little bit perhaps a little bit
fancy for the
occasion oh guys I'm so sorry sorry oh I
oh this stream stressed me
out I was trying to prepare
things uh and learn new songs and uh
it's yeah difficult difficult I did
learn some new songs but we'll also have
to sing some songs we sang before and
perhaps even some of my own songs but
that is not something that is something
regrettable right m
but yeah I I've been doing a lot of uh
un unarchived caras yeah yeah
um actually let me put on some chitchat
[Music]
bgm how
about that that was
loud
is
this just for the inet don't worry you
won't go crazy uh I
think yeah
maybe um so besides this okay I don't
even know where to start like I don't
even know um after this I'll be
redirecting to T sleep talking
Tak the last music video for point of
view so for that I want you all to stay
until the very
end um I don't know if like if I'll have
enough songs to like fit it all or if
we'll have to stall we'll figure it out
um I have no idea this might be awkward
I'll go here and I'll put the song list
like everything on the right side you
can go here yeah let's go yeah yeah
finally um I wanted to put up the
reservation higher
earlier uh but things happen and
actually I wanted to put this out last
week honestly I wanted to put it out
before the month ended in November as
you know but that also didn't work out
so it is what it is and it is what it
is
yeah uh I I am excited to then be
finally done with uh you know putting
out all the mvs I hope you like it
because I uh for this one there's a I
mean
I guess you could say it's a bit more
intricate than the others the like love
rush and reg perspective and
tgw cuz originally I wanted to do a 3D
music video for sleeptalking and that
was the plan but then my accent suit
arrived too late
and overall just like in terms of cost
uh it just wasn't a smart decision so in
the end this is what happened
something in between of the more lower
budget MV and the higher budget Envy
something in between um I think I think
it does it
justce well enough so sleep talk is my
favorite really thank you might also be
my
favorite yeah you can already see some
art on the thumbnail
and I think the thumbnail since it is a
screenshot from the video really uh
speaks for
itself so it's going to be sensual s
[Music]
sensual
my sleep doong is a banger it is yes
maybe I'll sing it today too and also
there will be an announcement right um I
almost forget about it but there's an
announcement that we'll also do at the
end uh exciting I I I I like it when I
can do announcements um
so what I wonder what it will be uh in
between can I write down a little bit of
a
uh okay I want to have a little Tex tent
list so uh anime Frontier
Ina one tangent is Anime Frontier one
tangent is Ina Life One
tangent I don't know that's all I can
think of right
now tangent
list or in between maybe we can think of
[Music]
more uh uh uh please not middle left
yes yes Tang here's my little just for
me don't look at my memo just for
me feels like that's plenty maybe
ah true I can talk a little bit about
the Advent
calendar okay okay but later later
later so okay yeah 1 hour and a half we
have to fill 1 hour and a half okay that
that should be fine
is what song should we start with let's
start with one of my songs okay I will
sing other whole life members songs I
will s sing uh not whole life songs and
I will sing my own songs so three
categories
[Music]
okay so a a mix a mix a good mix a good
balance
okay okay okay okay uh okay
[Music]
stop sorry I'm I'm stressed out let me
get out the
[Music]
lyrics I can't breathe this is going to
be
great not being able to breathe is
great everyone says that love is just
like a
dream feel like I'm meling from the heat
love it feels so s
oh yeah ooh just like that you know just
how it
goes don't ever stop or you already know
you're just a sweet my baby got me
wanting more so tasty yeah I don't got
no worries I feel good good good to warm
on me I want to go and party don't let
this love and now I won't pretend my
best recipe for love is you plus meat
I want to try it now P I'm going one 2 1
2 three it taste so so so sweet when you
go and kiss me I'm taking the perfect
picture you stop to me like a
stick one 2 one 2 three it taste so so
so sweet go that way
yeah yeah yeah oh
keep going you know
me
PPP hey I'm with you beating the heat so
sweet it's hypnotizing got you daning to
my you going be myo yeah now you see me
see meab I need just give me give me no
more hesitation don't think twice cuz
you're mine the time on me I want to go
and party don't let this love and now I
won't play at my best recipe for love
you me I want to try it now P now one 2
one two three it tastes so so so sweet
when you go and kiss me I'm taking the
perfect
picture you stuck to me like a
[Music]
sticker let's so
pineapples are so good I like them on
pizza and and then a burger
too uh
yeah pineapple hey pineapple pineapple P
come on boy let's go pineapple pineapple
come on baby do it over over hold my
hand
now take it to
the 1 2 1 2 3 it tastes so so so sweet
when you go and kiss me I'm taking the
perfect
picture you stop to me like a
[Music]
sticker pineapple one 2 one 2 three it
tastes so so so sweet go that way yeah
SP it like a
pineapple keep going you know
me
pineapple
hey
the the whip
Lush
bam the song is so
busy goodbye chickens goodbye dancing
pineapple chickens thank you for your
support in this song
[Music]
T ah so sweet so so sweet oh when you go
and kiss
me I'm taking the perfect picture you
stuck to me like a
sticker oh those those lyrics they were
all the real lyrics by the way even the
ones about pineapple and pizza and
pineapple and
[Music]
burger real lyrics I'm telling you so
trust
me uh how how are you guys
[Music]
doing I already have next week planned
out oh that's a tangent too next week is
uh exciting too just letting you know
next oh next week is very exciting for
several reasons
so I hope you guys have a lot of
[Music]
time I will make the schedule after the
stream and upload it uh Monday not
taking the day off Monday I will be
streaming too so they're all tangent yes
everything's a tangent sleepy but okay
good morning good morning 1080
snowboarding 1080
[Music]
snowboarding today is
snowboarding let's go
snowboarding
[Music]
yeah oh hell
yeah it's finally happening the game
that we've all waited
for more than games like GTA 6 or even
portal
free I talked with crony about um portal
free and uh entropy Center and all
that
yeah no no portal free ever I said don't
give up yet don't say it don't
don't
yeah I hope she enjoyed it I couldn't
watch it her did anybody watch her play
entropy Center cuz I played it last year
um and I was wondering if anybody ever
is going to play enty center besides me
and then she finally picked it up you
did I was really curious like if she
would like it did she like
it to the ones who did watch it she
enjoyed it did she have troubles she
lost her
mind nice
I I did lose my mind a few times too I
think right didn't am play it am did she
man I don't think she did she played it
a lot she lost her mind at the last
puzzle I don't even remember it anymore
but I probably also lost my mind about
it confusing ending yeah I was probably
also confused I don't remember anything
[\h__\h] I did lose my mind you remember she
overthinking a lot oh yeah I also
overthought oh man
me and crony we're the same person
[Music]
Quon we we're the same I'm a mention I'm
a
mention but so she finished it right man
good job Quon wait now I have 4 DMS what
the
[Music]
hell
oh
[Music]
oh there's
a remember last during my baking
oh it looks
better
oh it
oh it is better oh okay remember doing
my cooking
stream the [\h__\h] um when baking stream
when I showed you uh um the like a
little video of like just like my first
test what's that sound what sound
[Music]
my first test uh of testing the exent
suit the yeah and I mean it was okay but
we definitely want more Improvement
right and chagy the one who helped me to
put the data onto my body because I
don't know how to do that uh has since
not been letting go and been trying to
find the cause like maybe to see if the
the stiffness is really from the mo cap
or if that's something that could be
improved in the like the conversion or
whatever and what I what I just was sent
now actually does look better do you
want to see
it dance dance dance Wahoo Wahoo so uh
please pay attention especially to like
the the B the hip and the waist and all
that um like even this looks better okay
there's some
weird okay then look at that there's
actually some bounce bounce oh yeah oh
yeah Twerk It Girl Twerk It Twerk It
Twerk it
girl there's a weird boob physics and so
on that's okay here's some there's some
weird physics going on yeah yeah yeah
but besides that the important part was
uh this that looks better than last time
oh oh oh it I'm actually I I feel like
I'm the twerk the
twerk
sheesh wait I don't even think it worked
that well
IRL look at
[Music]
that twerking stream sleep TW
wait sleep twerking in my dreams I'm
sleep twerking all these nights it's
you no hiding it sleep twerking sleep
twerking sleep twerking sleep twerking
sleep
twerking I love I love saying that I
love misspelling my song as sleep
twerking that looked good okay got a
little bit of My Hope
back
nice what did she say shake it like a
pineapple wasn't that something else
spin it like a pineapple I
think 2D girl got excited about her 3D
model twerking of course of course
please make 3D version oh chy did you
hear that I don't know if you heard that
we need a 3D version apparently anyway I
forgot to write pineapple okay next okay
let's let's keep on like twist like uh
uh taking turns next I'm going to sing a
song that I sang before that you guys
liked a lot
okay
[Music]
good
that yes yes you guys like this one so
much from Golden
[Music]
bumper tell me if the audio balance or
or everything is good
okay oh
[Music]
hey he
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
[Applause]
foree
[Music]
me me St me to
Li
[Music]
for
[Applause]
[Music]
spee
to the
[Music]
side
M hey hey
[Music]
hey
oops
hey hey
hey ooh
[Music]
hey
spe
[Music]
for
somebody said did you Skip Leg
Day so funny aren't you so funny well
with this song like this is part of
their their original chos I always have
to do this like going to the side going
to start I wish I could dance more
thanks for the memberships and the Super
Chat so far thank you guys
this one's so
fun also somebody said top heavy I'm not
sure what that means but I'm guessing
it's also a
joke yes mandatory Tori
oh T
duy please sing something in German not
today I cannot sing German songs in
archiv streams not really unless I don't
know not really it's not an easy task
unless I sing German versions to
Japanese anime songs that could be okay
I've done it
before look it up look it up Bender done
that German
K German do
you be Maya be Maya we get us my I don't
I don't even remember that be
Maya German
original I Won't Say Never
but not interested at the
moment German to
op which one I don't know no it's
probably fine but like which one have I
not I sang a couple of like those old
school everybody knows
animes uh in German
[Music]
before German bad
apple bad
apple I sang it before right generally
not in German I just mean generally did
I sing it
before or maybe I didn't because now
that I look it up I'm I wouldn't be sure
which instrumental to even
use cuz like there's the original one
but I don't know if I would be allowed
to use
it I don't know maybe next time remind
me if I ever ask what I want to sing
next
time yeah okay uh I think actually
TimeWise I don't need to stall so much
anymore so let's go to the next
song so
next in in this category would be I
suppose going to another whole life
member
song I've prepared a few let's sing
uh one from
way there my song list I want to sing
sip some te
no sip some
tea okay let's
[Music]
go everything was easy I did it did all
alone so effortlessly I spread my wings
and let my magic unfold got all problems
so without any set that there is nothing
unol there's no way I can begin life
that I need to win I need to feel how
all these things crumble into little
pieces I know I got to sore a little
higher alls could be the things
[Music]
I
we'll never give up as long as we got
the strength in the St we could rise
above the pain we're stronger and down
walking step by step trusting my own
place giving me what I deserve to have
just believe me then let go they'll
never bring me down just believe me Let
it go it will never bring us down just
believe me won't let their royalty
stealing my royalty when the universe
works against me I will just let it go
if it's spicy let it go let it go if
it's spicy let it go let it go if it's
spicy something let it go let it
go I've been living Carefree there's no
B words in the world that could affect
me I spread my wings and let my magic
unold now that it show but I'm bigger
than my feelings so that will be enough
there's no way I can begin dream I need
to win need to feel how all these things
crumble into little pieces I know I got
to be better than ever hope
[Music]
be love and we'll never give up as long
as we got the strength in our Stu we
could rise above the pain we walking
step by step justing my own face giving
me what I deserve to have we let it go
they'll never bring me down just believe
me Let it go it will never bring us down
just believe me won't let D Coy stealing
my royalty
when against me I will just let it
[Music]
go let it
go
go sip some let me sip some tea
too I messed up several times that's
okay I love this song though like it's
like some of the lyrics are kind of
funny but uh I mean it's a banger
nonetheless if it's up something Let It
Like It Go
like pyy thank you thank
you oh what a banger
yeah I want to sing more Way songs but
this one spoke to
me if it's spicy just zip something Let
It Go the Indonesian part though thank
God it's only like a little bit most of
the song is English tasar thank you waya
for having mercy on
me
gura okay okay we can already go to the
next one I feel like yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah wait when is this
it no oh no wait we still have like 1
hour right oh
okay how
many probably
fine let's let's
uh let's
[Music]
sing let's sing another non hul life
memory song m
ah let's sing this
one I don't know if I sang this one
before did
I what
the did
I from
Kumi might sound familiar to you
[Music]
later
yeah
[Music]
honey
FL
[Music]
yeah
h
[Music]
he hey
he we got to
M whats are being prod cover some big
what take a
[Music]
okay
he
[Music]
honey yeah uh honey flash you guys
recognized
it I think it's quite well known but I
guess it's really old but the the singer
is also like incredibly famous Kaki
really famous lady in Japan
mhm cutie honey it's a OVA well I don't
even I don't even really know it because
of the anime just you know myself
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
okay what's next in the in the singing
roulette it was a direct to video title
what I've heard the song once before
once maybe it was from me too maybe I
did sing it before attack on the I mas
cover oh I love Tak wait did she cover
it it really I don't even remember that
my I have to look that up that sounds
interesting overa means direct to video
what I don't understand that yeah I I
feel like for me overa is just like when
an anime series doesn't release like you
know several episodes but like one one
like almost a movie not quite a movie
it's like like a long
episode not quite a movie right like
something like a movie but not
quite original video
animation oh but it's what I'm saying
right yeah yeah yeah yeah oh man what
now I have this really weird rare
feeling right now that I want to watch
anime I never have this
feeling maybe I should end the stream
immediately and make use of this feeling
and go watch
anime no I can't I can't too bad ah oh
too bad I have to do the stream and then
redirect
you
NY okay you know what we're going to
sing
next and
enjoy
dance
[Music]
uhuh
announcement announcement the flock has
arrived fling your heart in a cage we
for a good time but
we birds of a f f
ho the spotlights on us Mak Some Mo on
the floor give us a sweet solid beat bet
you wanted andc you ready Al call crial
committing Foul Play R impecable we're
only getting started track the power
to swing it to the left and right show
you what we got here
[Music]
flying
power do the
[Music]
Dan
yeah announcement announcement and this
full Breaking the noise so this part is
not
ofy stand up stretch your St migrate
onto the floor give us your best
clocking moves we want to see you sorey
toic not acceptable we know you want to
stay this like there is
come on it's
CRA till we Tak FL show you
[Music]
we
down do the
[Music]
down
yes yes
yes
no oh on that
note I think I'll talk about the Adent
calendar but let me add this to the
list I
S cutie honey and then hor
[Music]
dance right I didn't anything in between
I
hope
dance p p p thank
you thank you thank
you tangent
tent so ad did you see last night last
night was uh or like yeah yeah last
night was me and uh some BBS narissa and
M yeah I thought uh I want some unit so
I thought H who could do it with me
narissa is always up for something how
about we do something with like
H and you know originally I was talking
to M I was like you know I was thinking
about H what could we do and then my
original idea
was I I told her too like M how about
like we tell
narissa that um we like we're telling
her like any normal kind of idea just
tell her let's tell her let's for
example say we're do an adlip and then
um we're going to like you know gther
and then before we start start recording
we're actually already recording we're
going to start a fight you and me m
we're going to prank narissa and and
we're just going to fight just have a
fight about anything really and then
we'll see how narissa reacts you know
the the new intern BB she will probably
try to like resolve the issue and help
out but you know I just want to scare
her and and trouble
her and I was really going to do it but
then I got the idea for an adlib just
like doing an actual adli like Christmas
Story with us just coming up with
something cursed
and yeah and then I thought well I don't
really know what we could fight about
anyway so I ended up just going for the
normal adli I'm so sorry but I do want
to uh do like some kind of like prank
pre-recorded uh videos that I upload
done separately not as a stream to like
just randomly call some other whole life
members and then prank them in some way
I do want to do that I I'll eventually
do
that yeah I wanted to do I wanted to
Haze the intern
yeah it's okay though now we I told
narissa though I told
her I told her like narissa you know
that's actually what we wanted to do
don't worry I mean I I'll just prank her
in in different ways in the
future so yeah we did an ad lip in case
you didn't notice did you guys notice
when you were watching the video how
long did it take you to understand that
we're doing an
adlib and not just reading out some
existing story did you
understand
20 seconds 5 Seconds instantly oh really
okay a few lines in instantly
okay but I heard from your feedback guys
a lot of you guys didn't really
understand what the hell is going
on like you didn't understand the
[Music]
story yeah but yeah we were thinking
about what to say that's that's why we
didn't like you know even immediately
burst out our lines because there were
no lines there's no script it was
unscripted it was our first try too I
said if we can't like come up with
anything interesting we can do a second
take but I I kind of liked the first
take so just went with the first
take was there a theme I said uh we
should make it about BPS that's all I
said
beforehand so it's it's pretty long it's
like 10 minutes long so guys if you
didn't open the Advent calendar door
you're missing out go on
Holan Dash not minus but
minus uh hellan minus calendar or Advent
what was that what's that
URL you guys know what
again hen
minus Advent okay Holan minus Advent
which would only be promise and
myth the way I say it but admin is very
much involved
um and the new store H is h m narissa
and me and narissa the H to
intern doing some adlip yeah please
continue watching every
day
[Music]
has been really fun thank you I
appreciated I have
like I think yeah I had this issue that
I I still had like uh ouch 2 days or so
um not filled
up and I was like [\h__\h] what do I do
because I don't want to fill it up with
someone who already has like a video uh
free like any time like three four days
after or before because you know that
would be too close I want to balance it
out and you know and I also didn't want
to ask narissa again cuz she
already has been helping me a lot but
yeah uh
yeah finding someone who's available and
not too close to the dates that I'm
trying to fill is
difficult but so far it's been working
well and yeah I'm proud how it's going
oh the only problem is like I don't know
what happens to the sock puppets because
I told management sent me my sock
puppets back from Japan and they're like
in a storage
apparently oh if they send it like now
on Monday or
[Music]
so that should hopefully make it in time
so that I can make a little
video I hope
so damn it yeah I wasn't sure if I had
them at my home or in Japan but there's
still in
Japan okay guys let's go to the next
song I wanted to segue into something
a there's two segue
options let's go to this one I want to
sing the Advent Rebellion song but it's
so difficult to sing it alone so I'm
going to sing it with them okay just
this one
because uh there's some overlapping
stuff and all that it's kind of
yby so let's sing it
[Music]
together
yo b
[Music]
e a v e time to get this party started
fire fire light fire brigh highest
chasing all that WEP out
wildever
with come pull me out iest you to count
this Overkill saddle wearing me down
step out of the system break out give it
everything this is our time we yours to
discover hello brand new
world would you welcome the
light and free us from the
night fire fire like the fire brigh
highest you
desire to the of
[Music]
life until the end of
time fire fire
fire chasing all one step to the left
two steps to the right then back to
where we started and then
again step out of the circle break out
we got everything this is our time we
are
still Sky take us
home to where we
belong and free us from the
night take us to Paradise fire fire
light the fire brighter higher to desire
night Beating Heart Dan into the flame
life so let's all land all safy Dan
until the end of
[Music]
time I know that I can still be the
future of the story I know that I can be
free the one and the only they tell me
that I'm crazy I'll never let them stop
[Music]
[Applause]
me Till the End of
[Music]
Time Flame of
Dan the end
time
[Music]
all
oh narissa I love her lines in this
[Music]
song you guys better not start a
rebellion over
here you're not planning on it right
M I have my eyes on you
[Music]
yeah she's she sings the Japanese
lines then no Rebellion or Union both n
g I cannot tolerate such actions from
you
guys frog week frog
week it's not frog week right now is
it let's get rid of these chickens these
pineapple chickens
when they are planning a rebellion they
don't deserve to dance in pineapple
suits
nuh you Rebel
chickens okay I think let's
sing let's
sing that was that was a whole life song
so I guess I'll sing one of the not H
life
songs
this this song
actually fits the vibe I
[Music]
think can't
time the [\h__\h] where's the minus
there
rail
[Applause]
gun
[Music]
w
for
[Music]
in my
heart so that suddenly I'll reach the
next stage to realize it
[Applause]
[Music]
all
for I believe myself PR
[Music]
motion hey hey hi hey hi hey
he
[Music]
my
heart
[Music]
hi
hi hi
hi no I have a headache I've had a
headache to be honest for the past three
days or two days but I've been taking
pain killer now today I didn't take one
and now the headache is coming
back
it's okay it's okay we are we are G they
I need to watch rail gun again yo maybe
me too I don't know I wonder how I will
feel about it if I would watch it now
I'm a bit scared of that
feeling take your meds have you drunk
enough water I was thinking it comes
from that so I've been trying my best to
like uh drink more and more yesterday
and today
but I drank a lot today and I still have
this
headache I don't
know H it's in the front of my skull
like in my
forehead oh yeah like for headaches it's
like
pretty uh like knowing where it is
really gives away like what the cause is
doesn't it heada ache uh in a
[Music]
forehead
H stress okay well that makes
[Laughter]
sense well I'm always stressed so guess
I'm [\h__\h] guess I'll
die H likely
cancer I am I am a
cancer anyway let's sing another song
because I noticed we only have less than
40 minutes left oh so maybe I have to
hurry I don't know do I it's really hard
to tell it's really hard to tell let's
[Music]
sing
uh
sh
oh okay there it
is Ana's new
song Anya's new song I want you guys to
appreciate Anya's
music so let's
[Music]
go oh never break down Everlasting
kn never break down Everlasting
[Music]
night
fore
[Music]
[Applause]
I'll never break down Everlasting
[Music]
night
[Applause]
[Music]
foree
youe
[Applause]
I'll never break down Everlasting
[Music]
night
ana ana I wanted to uh sing the other
one too unreal Veil I was practicing it
but I didn't have enough time to like
really get it down well enough Ana that
was from Ana from Whole Life
Indonesia yes yes yes M it's her new
original song she I think um the mvy is
about to come out sometime in the next
few days right I don't know she
announced it like recently and I was
like what the [\h__\h] this so
good I never break an everlasting life
oh yeah whole life
[Laughter]
[Music]
Japan
next few days oh in January yeah so I
thought I had to wait for the MV I was
like what the hell I really like this
preview I want to I want to hear more
and then turns out she uh like the audio
is already on YouTube so didn't have to
wait I like all the the BL
[Music]
sounds and also then there's this like
this one time where like she stopped
singing for a moment and it goes
like
the the uh yes mouth
flute I like that part the whistle mouth
flute and then there's that that ADM
breakdown
bam so it's a fun song I really like her
her song so
far yeah yeah yeah that was the ever
knife H how
about how much time 30 minutes H okay
okay one two three
oh let's sing one of mine we haven't
sung one of mine in a
while okay and with that afterwards I
will segueway into the anime Frontier
tangent because I sangr the great
Wanderer there and it's like recently my
go-to song to sing at conventions
alongside retrospective because I know
you guys go crazy with with those two
songs and really love them so yeah I I
push sleep talking and pineapple for
music videos and for conventions I'll do
you a favor and push the great Wanderer
and
retrospective please
enjoy the great Wonder
uh
okay
oh sorry that was really
loud
[Music]
louder passing by famar roads I couldn't
find the reason
why who I am you couldn't know St in the
ruins my
disillusion in between a d
reality my own
desire keeps
me ooh moving faster than the light can
I'm in the
absess alone looking
back then I lose my way I can see that
day when I can reach you again then
camera like oh I can hear your voice
leading me through the vo fade
away to the
Grave it's turn I'm walking by the
lights that flash before my eyes alone
the silence defitely still I'm reaching
out to you con sacrifice the life I tell
myself so I'll survive one day
eventually the light it will lead me
back till you see
me I am the
[Music]
wonderer I am the
wonderer faith is gone the well is
dry no more
believing just
deceiving ooh feel the day light on the
edge but I can't feel the heat fall back
I'm too
deep I lose my way I can see the day
when I can reach you can canot let
go I can hear your voice leading me
through the voice fade
away to the
Grave ially I'm walking by The Flash
before my eyes alone the silence stening
till I'm reaching out to you conne saice
the life I tell so I'll survive one day
eventually the light lead me back to you
see
[Music]
me I am the
Wonder I am
[Music]
Wonder
W Wonder k w
wonder I am the W Wonder w w wah the
great wa the
great thank you it's such a good song
my God it's so
good ah it feels good to sing too I
really like singing the verses and
everything everything
really chorus is a bit difficult with
the up ups and
[Music]
down thank you thank you oh oh yeah
so
let's talk a little bit about anime
Frontier and let me put up a picture on
the screen too why not why not
imagination oh I guess yeah so I was I
was
uh I was I was
[Music]
here this is this is Fort Worth in
Texas
yeah t this a picture I uploaded on
Twitter we had a t panel that was really
fun where should I put this let's put it
here for now that's really fun it
it it it felt like well panel I didn't
have a panel or like not not quite a
panel but something like a panel
recently right in was it New York was
that New
York
or you know the one with the VR boo uh
with with KU and you the others and it
was a big room yeah it was a huge room
wow Who whoo it's hard to capture it in
the picture
honestly anime so it was New York yeah
and but like I didn't do a meet and
greet there and here at this convention
yesterday I had a meet and greet again
the first time in a while and oh let me
tell you it felt so good talking to you
guys for the first time in a while and
cuz it was in an area that I've never
like shown myself in before um I had the
pleasure to
greet some of you guys for the first
time and like you know there were some
some some newcomers some lurkers but
also some veterans that I see in the
chat every day so that was like Wow
mindblowing to me and really really
really like special to me like whenever
they said their name I was like oh
you're that person oh my God W let's go
I'm so happy to see you like in person
oh my god let's go yeah I was wow
finally after so many years putting a
face to someone's chat name
finally it feels so different so
personal so I I enjoyed every minute of
the meet and greet
M yeah what's funny is that there was
one person who I feel like
normally people find out about us on
like YouTube mostly like pretty much
YouTube and one person told me they
found me through Tik Tok like people
clipping me more less into a meme or so
me and others on Tik Tok yeah but there
was this one person who had had a way of
like finding out about me that I've
never heard before and this person was a
really new fan like a one month fan and
I thought that was really special so I
wanted to hear like why and they
said
that they were going to go to this
convention and then they saw in the
announced guests us you know me and cie
so they looked up my content and got
hooked immediately I'm like
what so the convention
announcement is how you got into this
and now decided to go to the meet and
grade even I'm like
what yeah that shocked me but I I for
one welcome my new uh chicken
employee need more yeah that's really
unique normally it doesn't really like
happen in my opinion like a lot of
people like look look at this huge room
filled with people I think pretty much
all of these knew
us through not not through the
convention but like from before yeah we
bring people to the convention which I'm
quite proud of you know that we can
bring
people yeah so I was happy about that
but yeah you guys I wanted to cry
because it felt like it's so crazy you
know it's kind of like let's say you
have like a like a pen pal across the
continent I never had this before but
you know there's people who have that
right they write letters to some person
on another continent and imagine doing
that for years he's in a chat yeah I saw
see like they're totally like in the
rabbit hole nice um but like imagine
having a pen pal for ages and then after
like 5 years or so you decide to meet up
and you meet for the first time and it's
just mind-blowing it's it's wow this is
how I feel when I see you guys in the
medum
grade
yeah H so many special special people
and and you told me your stories and I I
was just so happy man
man and everybody was dressed so well
too in merchandise or some others in
Cosplay I saw like a pomu cosplayer
too and then I I took a screenshot and I
sent it to pom but I told I told them
that I was going to send it to Pomo so
they were
aware and Pomo was like oh I know
[Music]
them yeah so I my my be a greet was
before the panel so and and then I had
like only uh like 15
minutes until the panel and my mind was
like wo I was so emotional I
wasn't and I told cuz like she was going
to have her meet and greets after the
panel so I was like man Callie these
meet and greets are you got to be
emotionally ready for them this good
stuff this the good
stuff so and then I was like um setting
up because I was the one uh you know who
was like organizing the room and the OBS
and everything uh for the panel so uh I
I think I was also in the waiting room
earlier like in the waiting Zoom call
waiting room thingy a little bit early
on Cali so I was like setting up
everything I was putting like a
background on and like the logos on the
screen and all that and then I was
thinking hm this background is kind of
lame maybe what what if I get a picture
of Texas in the background and then I
put one in the background it was kind of
funny and the staff that were like there
setting things up laughed as well so I
thought hm what if I get a few more let
me get some variety cuz I don't want to
claim like only this is what for Worf is
so I I went on my ice do because I have
a subscription for ice do stock photos
and I I gathered like like 10 pictures
of the city that we were going to be in
and surprisingly they had quite a few
some recognizable some apparently not so
recognizable and I put them all up as
like the
background uh and then I like I was I
had this idea that like we were only
going to do a Q&A and uh the singing
portion but I I realized we could do a
little tour that would be fun that would
be cute mute that would be something I
haven't done before at the panel so uh
with these pictures I asked the host
beforehand if maybe uh they can help us
out to like figure out where these
places are and you know it will be like
I can't be there in person but cuz I'm
there virtually but this way I can like
get a little bit of a tour and a
connection with the the place that I'm
in right so I I thought it was a genius
idea now and it it actually I think I
think it landed quite well I think the
people there liked it actually in the me
and green I heard like half of them were
like Yeah from Texas but like uh one of
them who even was from Texas took it
took them like 9 hours to get there but
then others they flew in from like
California and so on so I was surprised
that it wasn't only like local people
you
know so I guess like in this convention
hall also not all of them are from Texas
but so for the not Texas people I guess
it was also a tour and for the people
who were from there I I think like if
you if you have like someone you really
idolize come to your town to like a
convention like this I would be like
really excited if they take their time
to like you know like study the place a
little bit and like tell their stories
like what they experienced and all that
so you know I thought I thought that
would like create some kind of
connection and yeah it it it really
worked really well well we had this
little tour and then we did a Q&A we had
you guys ask some questions um and uh
and then we sang our songs and that was
really dope and I got staff to record
the audience a little bit for me for my
private use because I wanted to really
hear how you guys cheer for the great
Wanderer and ret
retrospective but the good thing is oh
my God I'm tting so much even before uh
the panel started cuz I was setting up
for so long um early on uh I watched you
guys come in and fill all the seats
and uh and then they were playing uh our
songs right and they were playing
retrospective and the great wandall and
some Kelly songs and so on and so in
that I I I could listen to you guys I
could listen at that time so that was
really good I heard you loud and
clear I can't read I really want to
burst that one out don't
we I heard and saw you cheering and I
mean it's it was kind of hard to tell
for me personally the people who were
there have to tell me um there do you
see on this photo the left screen right
in front of that the were apparently I
was told the meet and greet people were
seated in right in front of the screen
in the first couple rows because they
weren't able to queue up because the
meet and greet was right before the
panel so they gave them the seats there
which is so sweet so sweet but those
people happened to be the most
passionate and Loud fans in the whole
room there were like hundreds I don't
even know maybe even thousand I I could
imagine there being a thousand people in
this room um and I would hope that
everybody was enjoying and cheering but
those in front of the left screen they
were so loud they stood out so much and
it was so fun to to watch them and re
like see them react to everything even
when we were on screen or even when we
were not on screen screen so that was a
great time yeah the left side was the
absolute hype Squad and I'm so uh happy
you guys didn't like get shy or
anything uh I was hoping and trying to
get the rest of the crowd to
cheer like as much or like a little bit
more like you guys but it's hard to get
that crap out goinging and the contrast
was so strong but I think everybody had
fun right I hope
so I hope
so yeah right
[Music]
side I kept on like cuz we had several
cameras on the audience on our view and
I kept on switching between both of them
and it was
like it was kind of like 9 and day just
because the left side was so
crazy when you guys like especially at
at the end me and Cali announced our
upcoming original song which is coming
out next week um and the like we already
teased it so I think you guys already
saw it coming but when we announced it
for real you guys lost your
shits these people lost their shits
especially the ones in in front of the
left screen cuz those were the the most
passionate ones they lost their [\h__\h] and
uh it was so funny and then immediately
after the announcement we we dipped and
we I was still watching very closely
though so it was like announcement and
then bye-bye thank you and then we are
off the screen and then I see like
people are like clapping and then and
then the the left side all the people in
the left side they jump up and they like
you know they bounce and like bounce at
each other hug and bounce and then then
another one joins and another one joins
and they're like jumping and bouncing in
a circle while like holding each other's
on each other on the shoulders you know
what I mean that was so cute to
watch everybody was like so happy and
then oh like I I will not say names but
one suddenly like like really loudly
screamed something that I didn't really
acoustically understand but somebody was
like yeah [\h__\h] yes or something like
that I don't know what it was but yeah I
watched your reactions
afterwards and then I watched everybody
slowly walk out slowly slowly because I
was feeling so
emotional and they were playing the song
that I actually kind of liked and I put
in my have to sing in my kok
list and I was just like I had this I
really felt like I was there I had legit
this feeling that you get at the end of
a great convention that you don't want
to
leave and this was just great I felt
like we all felt
that especially the me and greet people
we all felt like I think that's what
came across to me and I it it it made me
feel that way too like oh man yeah I was
so immersed and emotional okay oh my God
H that was great it was great really I
wish uh I could share this experience
with everybody with the people who
weren't at the panel at the convention
at all you know but just know that this
was [\h__\h] dope let's do more
conventions next year okay
oh let's
sing
H what the
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] wrong
[Music]
side why did I T so
much put your hands up put your put your
hands up put your hands up put your put
your hands
[Music]
up
papao put your hands up put your put
your hands up put your hands up put your
put your
[Music]
hands
know
[Music]
for love you
forever
[Music]
put your hands up put your put your
hands up put your hands up your hands
[Music]
up
your hands put your hands up put your
hands up put your put your hands
[Music]
up wait wait we have to we have to ah I
think I'm going to move the premiere cuz
there were songs I really wanted to
sing just for like five or 10
minutes I just going to move it for five
or 10 minutes is that okay put your
hands put your put your
hand I [\h__\h] love that song so much I
learned it properly for
today uh
wait how do I change the
time can I change the
time I can change the time right wait it
doesn't what if I I can't change the
countdown okay let's change the
countdown to the maximum wait no it
doesn't it doesn't let me change
though huh huh
so okay um next song I guess yeah bye
and the announcement the
announcement [\h__\h]
okay uh let's
[Music]
go
fore
[Music]
Doe
foree
[Music]
[Applause]
foree
spee
[Music]
foree
for
[Music]
wait one more put your hands up put your
put your hands up wait
Bong song I made
the because these are too I really want
to do these because I made backup vocals
for these 2 minutes warning it's okay
there's five minutes uh for the for the
uh countdown so probably D next song is
only 3 minutes and 24 seconds so it's
dju let's go last one TIY chy bang bang
they I will say it don't worry ch ch
bang
[Music]
b
i
[Music]
fore
t
[Music]
dancing oh
yeah let's go
[Music]
Shin
baby
woo
i
i i b
[Music]
i
I I ch ch b i Chi CH I ch ch bu I ch ch
ch bu Chi CH bu a chi CH a chi CH bu a
ch
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
ta next week
Sunday uh yeah 17th the
17th uh uh uh 10 p.m.
jst this H my T fre celebration end of
the year where we are celebrating my
birthday half a year late let's
go okay okay I'll send you guys to the
premiere of the sleep talking and
hype hype hype hype hype thank you for
watching the uh the stream and hope you
enjoyed it K okay was it okay I hope so
I want to sing even more but that's okay
now um I hope to see you all here I
worked so hard for this H you don't even
understand so much sweat and so many
tears have been left have left my body
for
this
so okay talk to you again schul later uh
MV now uh let's go oh my God
[\h__\h] I'll redirect you
guys