[Music]
e e
he
[Music]
wow where's the music I got this
[Laughter]
[Music]
H I'll be your music once you find
eliminate what you I found it I found I
found I found it like after I
said well good morning afternoon evening
[Music]
everyone it
is what what
yeah no you go on do
your I forgot where I left off anyways
it's it's not Taco I mean it is kind of
Taco Time but I'm gathered here today
that sounds too formal
um anyways okay real answer them cut cut
cut okay today we are starting the
stream to share our enthusiasm about the
world tour to every to to to everyone me
you and you and uh since the first stage
is
already next
week can you believe
it wait Did you know about this I didn't
know about this B what it was it's next
week excuse me I fly so fast who has
tickets uh wait next week is an anime
NYC right exactly which which happens to
me at first
stop if you didn't
know I now know should we do a volume
check first oh yes all right I'm looking
it okay no bgm there is
bgm oh wait
maybe uh hold on I can fix this
[Music]
okay how's how's it
now apparently not okay um I can fix
this
it's fig out bgm still no
what wait I don't understand I hear bgm
bgm let's
go that's
weird I had it all set up and it was
[Music]
working it's just really it's really
small
yeah I mean I can raise it up oh
mhm I just didn't want to drown out you
guys right okay that looks really low
yeah it is really low looks really low
but I if I if if if I raise it I can't
hear you
guys can you raise us they're saying
we're quiet you're quiet it looks quiet
and OBS
indeed doesn't go into your whoa hold
on whoa I think my audio is broken okay
hold on it's
okay t t t t oh that's definitely broken
okay um
huh broken
broken yeah something with the sound
driver is very messed up oh
no P we might not have to uh we might
not have bgm I think that should be fine
right I mean I could bgm I mean I could
add okay hold on I can totally do this
don't worry guys I got this are you
adding a boost volume boost
filter on OBS I mean yeah yeah yeah see
every time I set everything up and it's
working
perfectly and then it's not as soon as I
hit go
live the audio was low from before
really okay hold on guys close your ears
for close your ears plug your ears for
one
second oh my God I feel bad for
that
that I'm sorry that was red that was
very red that was very red I'm sorry
okay and blood that is coming out of
their
ears I need a blood coming out of ears
emote um and then I think doesn't Amma
have that emote maybe Amma has an emote
like that okay can you guys keep talking
I do testing testing hello did you know
wow it's it's
uh ready for out the world's happening
starting next week wow
yeah okay T
[Music]
thing looks good I think now good H you
guys hear the bgm too well you guys you
twoo don't hear it but the
chatou I literally have her at maximum
on Discord I can boost on my side
too I think the volume they're saying
it's fine
okay I think it's good enough
cool all good everything good all right
we're good we're good ready to start
okay now we're starting
cut want to do the introductions okay
let's do the
intro it's okay it's not my usual setup
so everything is going to be scof um
joking
okay and and
definitely don't have everything written
down today we're starting the stream to
share our enthusiasm about the world
tour to you all since the first stage is
already next week can you believe
it oh my
God time flies so fast who has a ticket
have you freed your schedule everybody
I'm so sorry we already I think we
already kind of went through that
yeah okay
anyways I hope you all remember that
Hall life stage World Tour 24 sore is a
3d concert tour y yeah not cardboard not
cardboard not live today Project going
on several
dates will be everywhere
except
Europe well it's also like I I think
it's very Monumental cuz it's first time
in whole live production history isn't
it yeah our very first world tour yeah
and um I love how it's called
Soul can you say s again B so
s she saw it just all will have seen it
I I hope that you know with the world
toour we can sort even higher than
before
wow I'm sure we will yeah so this time
it's not only you know just one gen
branch no it's everybody some people
from the Japanese side some people from
the ID side and the script says ID and
ID but it is ID and Ian yeah what's SC
we definitely don't have what script
what script what script are you talking
about I just found that one funny so I
just wanted to mention it so it is Japan
ID any
[Music]
so and me yeah there's free m free free
of them they have no names but uh that's
seven of us and we are so ready to rock
you w
something I would say so ba I know you
didn't know about this world tour thing
but do you happen to know how many
cities we're going to visit I have no
idea about this world to none whatsoever
but I know exactly the cities are going
to be um so we are visiting New York
City Jakarta
quum Atlanta
W it says a wait wait wait wait wait uh
I'm missing one which one am I missing
uh Singapore sing Singapore that's
right we definitely don't have a scam we
don't have a script we don't have a
script yeah so uh each concert will be
held within you know one of the biggest
Anime conventions or like uh culture
Japan culture whatever conventions in
each region so before or after a concert
you can also you know hang out at the
convention with the
other other people and have I think
that's so cool that we got to you know
partner with different Anime conventions
across the world yeah hijacking them it
means like all like all the H life fans
and just you know new fans too maybe you
can just bring random people to H life
but yeah that's exciting and it's also
like you can make it into like a whole
trip you know it's like you go to the
convention and then there's a concert
and we're touring no no no you are
touring oh
yeah anyways we will explain more about
the conventions later in the Stream but
before that I want to know how much you
all know about each City we're going to
visit oh okay I failed
[Laughter]
geography I I I don't think I've been to
any of these places like in person
before so I don't think I know
anything but but you know maybe maybe
you just have some knowledge you know
just randomly by passing from from the I
don't know knowledge yeah general
knowledge and stuff maybe maybe may
maybe not but that's fine we can learn
we can learn everything now yeah so I
think nobody I've been to Jakarta I've
been to Jakarta yeah yeah yeah I've been
there oh my God thank you guys for
reminding me that was a fun trip
yeah besides that so we're going to
start with our first stop on the tour
which happens to be New York City
W in New York City we will be performing
on a Friday August
23d so we're kind of also in a way
kicking off the Ian concert
it's going to be such an exciting uh
weekend my goodness you ready for three
days of sh no no no no I'm going to be
melting on the floor after 3 days in a
row performance yeah melting also
because it's apparently really hot in
New York too yeah ladies 86% humidity
let's let's
go all right so so so do you guys have
any you know like knowledge or
impression about New York City you know
anything you've seen from like shows
Pizza o Pizza New York pizza hot dogs
hot dogs I remember so I've been to New
York once in person when I was in school
and I remember I remember I bought one
of those hot dogs like in one of the
small stands and there were somehow it
was like one of the best hot dogs I've
ever had I'm just like what what they
say I did not expect this but it's
really
good well know H you've been you've been
in New York more than just that
time you've been on the on the Time
Square oh yeah the many multiple times
uh or copies of myself being on the Time
Square know that is
true oh I I still think about it I'm
just like did that really H did the fans
really do that but it did
happen is it real is the time scare
real are we real I need to see it with
my well maybe maybe we'll get to see it
during the tour oh yeah oh yeah okay I I
I guess I got to share uh so uh anime
NYC um I've been reminded that last year
I was there with GAA and in in the booth
uh we did like a Kad but I think GAA
didn't
sing I think her voice was broken our so
I sang for her and then the year before
we had uh no both years I guess we had
like a you know the VR Booth right oh
yeah V stuff and then yeah so the year
before I uh did something with fauna and
I think fauna like showed her cute VR
outfit for the first time there it was
really cute very cute oh yeah goba hit
her head yeah the F her gooa had her
phone fall on her head and that's why
she didn't participate in the
C that's a
very anime and YC is also I think the
very quote unquote like all 3D activity
that's where it started for me too I did
um the 3D karoke parties two years in a
row and it was very fun U we also did
no we didn't do that never mind it was
also I think Jad cast but it became a
bayus cast I been a lot of conventions
okay guys sorry I need to transition to
my next St I toally forgot I was
like wow wow sorry I slid your chairs
where you weren't looking but uh I
totally was flipping through the slide
and I was like yeah this chat's seeing
this and I'm just like you know they're
not seeing it Ena cuz you forgot to
change this oh
now you're seeing it okay now you're
seeing it see it all right very
clearly to 25 but we're there on the 2
yeah the world tour uh uh live is on the
23rd and then we have the Ian live on
the 24th and the
25th in our own venue yeah very cool
okay you gotosa yeah that's exactly why
I was trying to get to this point show
show us I have to show you some pictures
and enime y see from years before we
have what do we have
wow nice nice nice nice there's so last
year I think so I think so it's got to
be
yeah this isn't the photos from the
future so this is so big I know and
there's so many fans
watching so exciting and then there's
also the booth we
had yes yes yes yeah very exciting and
this
was so cool was this um who was this
say yeah maybe hard to see but I can't
see SC oh by the way you know bgm gone
because
you same but you know what no no no it
was on purpose it was on purpose because
I wanted to show you oh yeah this video
of anime NYC let's go
oh the
cospl
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
so
oh they had arcade games
there and rythm games
[Music]
wow oh there's something for everyone
here
yeah so cool I love an
convention old
books wow the cospl are amazing
[Music]
wow Javits is it Javits is that how you
say it
ja javitz Convention Center I
think that's where we'll
be so now that you guys have seen some
exciting video video video and pictures
of anime and YY are you guys ready for
the
the worldwide quiz anime NC Edition
oh I'm ready to get zero
points no I believe we can do it okay
how about we also get chat to help us
you know they may have more ideas about
the locations we're visiting yeah Chad
can help us yeah I'll I'll question I
allot that but but from what I know chat
also likes to be confused so that is
true that is all right so the first
question wait youa you are you
participating I'm I'm the quiz Giver
this time I know the
answers okay and this this one is pretty
easy cuz there's like one building that
I know the name of in New York City we
turns or do we do we in what do we do
maybe we can switch turns after like
each location or something we'll see
we'll see no I meant questions do we no
you I'm asking the questions for New
York and you guys just but as
in no you both answer at the same time
yeah oh okay it's a team effort I would
normally not know the answer to this but
chat is already spamming Empire State
build famous New York City building has
oh I only know one
building which one is you want to say
chat your so also trying like kind of
make them confused too so throw out some
wrong answers
too no maybe we shouldn't look at the
Chad I mean I mean it's up to you you
can look at the chat or not look at the
chat I don't even if I tell Chad not to
spoil it they're going to say it anyways
Statue of Liberty
oh and Kiara wait that's not a building
well I shall say then Empire I was
joking Freedom lady okay and the answer
is the Empire State building building
[Music]
wow nice one very nice this is the warm
up question Freedom lady yes important
uh that was the warm up okay we have
another question okay which New York
City in borrow was once a separate City
before becoming a part of New York City
in 19 what's the B not 19
1898 it's kind of like a
um subsection of a city kind of almost
part of yeah part of
oh like how I guess how there's like in
Tokyo there's like Shinjuku for
example like oh okay like suburb yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah which newk suburb
was a separate City before becoming part
of
oh do you know I don't know don't know I
wouldn't know even chat is very throwing
out all kinds of different things I'm
looking at chat cuz I know the answer
you can look at chat I'm looking all
right using the my means of my my my
Sherlock Holmes deduction skills yes I'm
guessing this quiz has is supposed to be
linked to the hollow live world tour
wait some is it I don't know I don't
think I mean the only the cities oh well
the only other
city name that I know is Brooklyn
because that's where the Ian second life
is being held I don't know any other
name it's in Brooklyn yeah King said it
is in Brooklyn isn't it oh oh okay final
answer are you sure I I no I I'm not
answering I say I say uh rhod Island
spell spelled with r o a DS please
and the answer
is
Brooklyn let's go let's go I saw that in
the chat I
sawad is I'm going to go for Road Island
yeah okay I believe okay okay okay
question three anime NYC is the largest
Anime conventions on the USA's East
Coast true or false I don't know East
Coast so I would
it's true it's probably true they want
the fle it says on the East Coast what
is the East Coast and West Coast I'm
Australian I don't
understand really really even I know I
mean she's Australian so she's upside
down so our East might be her West you
know yeah what do you mean you don't
know East Coast you don't know where
East is or where where I then like what
considers the East Coast what is West
Coast is it um okay so if you look at
the map East is on the right and West is
on the left wait so is it all the cities
on the
East Coast yeah so like it's basically
saying anime NYC is the biggest anic
conventions if you look at the map of
the USA on the right side of the USA
kind of like oh okay so is
oh
oh does say true or false true
and the answer
is
true
F good yeah yeah good question good
question okay nice nice nice wow you
guys are getting it down very well I'm
I'm
surprised okay thank you this one though
trying my best this one
though what year did anime NYC first
debut
um maybe when was there when was any my
NYC debut stream H was there de wait
well how how long has Anime conventions
been a thing in
America I think longer than anim man y
see is a
thing because I I don't know the
date but honestly I'm bad with dates too
oh yeah it's
it's I don't know it but I know it so I
don't know it what
what my answer is pass pass I know I
don't know all right it's a late Comer
anyone SE is a late
bloomer okay that gives me a clue okay
cuz I'm judging off cuz I know like kind
of when I'm thinking back when like
smash was a thing which is the anime
convention in Australia and I think
that's been around for a while mhm so if
anime and my SE are late I want to say
15 later later later 2016
later 2017 no way final
answer what Final Answer seriously
2017 it is indeed 2017 you're
joking
wow
what oh my God it is
2017 wow wow that's like that's really
basically yesterday pretty much oh my
goodness it's a it's a pretty young
convention but despite that it's you
know the biggest one in the east
coast how did they do it Dam fast these
days that really makes you think how
much like anime and like Japanese
culture like fans have been growing like
over the
years big big big so this is I think
going to be the last question of the New
York
City it
is
oh in what
ear and the N while she's mascot what in
what year I think there's a little bit
of a copy paste error here in what year
was I think I think they just forg
that's completely yeah gone just uh
anime anime ny's mascot is named
Alice what is the name of her chinula
side I'm guessing that's a little cute
uh chinchilla in the back cute very cute
chatino
chatino legally distinct
chatino about UMO Final Answer how about
Chiller the chin Chilla chill like
Chilla the the chill the chiller chills
the chiller conqueror of the
[Music]
world sure let's go with that the answer
is not
MO rocket rocket rocket rocket rocket
Alice and Rocket Alice and
Rocket why is it rocket maybe that's
just uh something you guys need to look
uh likes to bully the chinchilla so she
froze him around like a rocket I mean
she does kind of look very like you
know very energetic playful you never
know do not throw your
chinchillas Justice for Rocket Justice
for Rocket Justice for
Rocket got to go fast we have a special
message also from
mc mc is excited that we will be the
first stop for Hall life stage World
Tour 24 sword that's such a long title
sorry we look forward to welcoming fans
from all over to experience the
spectacular level of entertainment and
talent that Hall life is known for the
addition of Hall life English justices
panel and the talk show with Hall life
Gamers further enriches our event making
this year's NC an unforgettable
experience for all
attendees wow wow thank you thank you
yes so even asides from our world tour
we also have justices panel and also a
hall of Gamers so a lot of a lot of you
guys to look forward to yeah
exciting we we have a boo to
not just the P we have a
boo come check it out
please thank you for having us at nman
wiy once again thank
you Yi and so let's you know let's do
our bu everyone's really looking forward
to it so and all of the tickets have
been sold out thank you
guys how do you guys feel about I I'm
interest
yes I think all I can say is that I'm
putting a lot of effort into practicing
and doing know rehearsing and stuff so I
want to make a very memorable show for
you guys it is opening stage yeah we got
to set the set the standards you know
yeah oh but that's the first stage yeah
yeah want to do the you know the tally
of the points I don't remember I don't
remember I think I
lost so I
mean wait it's okay I expected this
outcome you know what we'll we'll start
counting properly from now this it was
warm up New York City was warm up but I
legit wanted to say some okay okay well
just just say it then well I did my
research on what New Yorkers say oh
oh okay there just an explanation guys
loser is supposed to say an
apology in in a way that reflects the
region
so I want to I'm not going to go out
here and say hey I'm walking here cuz
that's too basic I'm just G okay I hope
there's New Yorkers here who will get it
CU otherwise it won't be funny but okay
I'm just going to say
it me me walking through the streets of
New York oh oh they're filming Law and
Order over there oh they're filming Law
and Order over there too oh they're
friending Law and Order there too it
seems to be a common thing it's funny to
New Yorkers okay see Lal LOL they're F
They're laughing about
it don't cringe at me Bae They're
laughing about it it's
true does you just want to show everyone
your
impression you you did amazing wow wow
amazing amazing
lovely see they're they're laughing at
Le laughing thank
you yay thank you all right back to the
script what script W you're going to
just naturally introduce us about our
next stop
right wait are we oh sorry can I
interject real quick
yes are we really not using bgm for the
rest of the stream oh
um I hold on is it broken still okay
it's still broken um
okay we'll use this one PGM I got it I
got it can you copy paste um oh yeah go
back No it should it should be it should
be working now no I think you added in
after no no but there's bgm now I'm
playing it through uh media player can
you guys hear
it we're good chat chat's hearing it
okay
okay I'm totally a professional streamer
that knows everything how to do stuff
that was our first stage and ladies it's
been 36
minutes oh dear let's go fast okay back
to back to normal Wa Would you naturally
introduce our next
destination sure uh after NYC uh our
next venue will be in jakala where I've
been to uh it will be held on November
9th Saturday at Indonesia ComicCon
yes we're so back goodness Indonesia
also I have been told that the pre-sale
tickets have already been sold out wow
really last week oh my goodness thank
you so for the support thank you um and
then I think uh normal General sale
tickets and stuff will be starting soon
either in August or early September so
have your eyes peeled for more
information Elie doy
yeah all right you you before I've never
been
before I've never I have I
have how was it it was hot um as it
seems to be a theme for all the places
we go to it's hot it's hot that's hot oh
yeah yeah I I went there it was just a
short time but it was really nice how
was the food I yeah I got treated uh to
food by
way a yeah I had some some like local
food uh it was really good it was really
yummy I want to go again of course I've
really hoping to go man I've it's been
on my bucket list same I heard they have
really good like spicy food so I'm just
like I really want to go yeah my
goodness I'm sure our Indie Indonesian
uh friends and like you know especially
the ones who are part of concert can
help us when the time is here yeah oh
yeah and maybe they'll treat us to some
durian oh Duan durian challenge let's go
and the durian I mind
actually oh you had it yeah it's oh my
mama R is a big fan of Duan so we it was
a always in our
refrigerator open and just a whiff of
durian it's always in there then yeah
you get used to
it all right well I can't wait for
November 9th please wait for us look
forward y y yay yeah moving on to our
third stop after Jak we will stop in
Singapore Singapore let's go um I think
we've we've been to Singapore we Hol
live has done many things in Singapore
over the years and this time we'll be
performing in anime festival Asia
Singapore AFA Singapore let's go yeah
yeah previously there was uh what and
also the ID girls doing a concert in the
same event so it's it's our turn
now well do you guys know
Singapore uh I've never been I've never
been yeah but AA I I always wanted to go
there like I've heard so much good stuff
about
it like it's one of the most famous
conventions that I know of and yeah true
true true I really want to go I'm
looking forward to the food yeah I think
we have um some photos and videos from
AFA to show us more about like Singapore
and stuff so I'll go with the uh photos
first ooh oh yeah this is at the
convention that happened uh last year I
remember I think CH had a panel there as
well soow
yeah yeah
there oh I remember
now I remember oh my goodness I'm so
sorry I remember like when we were going
through through it earlier I was like
wait really what did we do I don't
remember I remember B do you I'm sorry
for you forget I just have a small pap
brain I'm
sorry yes and this is also the show they
did the IDE
girl po over there oh so nice yeah
[Music]
remember cute yeah that looked really
exciting just from the photos when I saw
them back then and I also think we have
a special video video oh that was sent
over to us let's see all
right oh my
God introduce yourself hi us my name is
SE uh I'm currently the festival
director of anime festival Asia
otherwise known as
AFAA not me calling it AFA sorry no it's
AFA AFA AFA AFAA AFA is all about anime
comics and games our main mission is to
bring together Regional visitors from
all across Asia to celebrate all they
love about Japanese pop culture we're
based in
Singapore um and we pride ourselves to
offer uh three pillar engagement for all
our contents starting from
exhibition stage as well as
concerts I guess what makes us really
special is that we can bring together
all types of events that you see all
around the world and in Japan all
together into 3 days at ala three
days nice nice
nice AFA has grown tremendously over the
years I remember our first uh event back
in 2008 we8 2008 25,000 people occupying
about 4,000 square met since then uh 16
uh years have passed and years we're
happy to say now the event takes over
12,000 meter
at as well as the numbers have grown
from 25,000 back in 2008 to close
130,000 the event as a whole um in terms
of the content that we're offering of
course has also grown tremendously over
the years how much and uh of course one
of our key parts are the concert and
every year we challenge ourselves to do
better
yes next
goals we're very happy with the growth
of AFA over the years um and you know I
guess our main goal is to spread the AFA
brand yeah more Beyond just Singapore
itself and we're looking to grow ala um
throughout the whole region all right
all right we can do that let's do
it the highlight of ala we've yet to
announced the event for this year like
the DAT oh right all I can say is we've
got lots and lots of content uh prepare
last May the quiz question I'm happy to
announce for the first time in our aart
history we'll be holding the first ever
World Tour for Hol life the Hol life
stage 2024 World Tour saw will be held
at ala Singapore this year more details
on the dates and everything will be
announced very shortly I can't wait
thank
you mess for us for us to hollow live
stage 2024 World Tour s members thank
you for your support I can't wait to
have you guys in
Singapore thank you I can't wait he
looks like such a proud father yeah of
the event I
like he really shows like his enthusiasm
for the event too so you know it's
always really fun to work with very
passionate you know individuals
yeah he's not just it's not just he's
not just a father he he's the a
father trying to do something here okay
you guys think and you guys think I'm
the pun Master we got here making puns
left and right
left and right or east and west am I
right b b can't tell
himart I you know what I okay let's have
you got did you take notes of the
numbers the numbers what do they mean
because um it's time to test
you again again are we magically
switching spots in 3 two
one goodness oh my goodness it is my
turn it is your turn to give my turn
tested too now huh oh yeah but I'm the
one controlling the slides so
right you guys let's see worldwide quiz
worldwide
quiz Edition Edition all right let's go
ready yes question number one is ready
why is Singapore known as the lion City
it's known as a lion
City because
uh uh there used to be Lions walking
around well yeah I guess it's probably
like something like you
know yeah like someone someone has to
have like interacted with a lion or
something or they really like Lion oh
yeah maybe yeah in the history of
Singapore
[Music]
final answer what are you going with um
whatever is correct I'm going with
that they really like lions they really
like lions okay Final Answer In what is
the answer thank
you in AC times the prince
s Utama sorry if I pronounced it wrong
he saw a lion when he first found the
island so he named the island singer
which means lion and po which means City
oh and fine text however actual Lions
have never lived in
sing what so technically I feel like I'm
kind of right you know
wait what so
eh lons have never lived wait so did he
see a line was it a hallucination or was
he a
lying sorry next question next question
stop next
question okay number two if someone
orders a fried carrot cake in
Singapore's hul Center what can you
expect to get fried carrot
cake uh
um hopefully it's a fried carrot cake
what you getting but do you get fried
chicken what you
expect cuz I think carrot cake in like a
more Western sense it might be a little
bit different yeah cuz carrot cake is
like the the sweet like there there's
like the carrot bread part and then
there's like the icing the white
icing that's like a classic carrot cake
in my in my
memory well I'm sure this is like a like
a uh it's trying to mislead us because
obviously when it asks us like this that
means it's not a fried carrot cake well
surely there's carrot in there what
could it be
though what how about it's a ah ah how
about it's like um carrots like fried in
oil but like a smashed flat like a
pancake oh oh
maybe okay okay okay interesting
interesting I'm going oh sorry I forgot
to turn it on
again okay
um I'm going to go with car's answer
ah say carrot fried in oil yeah but it's
like a pancake like flat pancake a flat
pancake okay well you kind you're you're
kind of right kind of do I show the
answer yes what is the answer please the
answer
is you get a plate of fried radish cake
radish that's not carrots it's well I
think it's the I I'm only saying this
from um a a Chinese perspective like the
language itself I think it's similar in
dish but I don't think it's the exact
same um in Chinese when you say fried
carrot cake uhhuh you it it also means
like radish the word for carrot and
radish is kind of the same carrot you
add red in front of it so it's like red
radish radish basically so it's kind of
a Mist transation down to English
kind of kind of I guess yeah
yeah is this why like every time I go to
like like restaurants where I don't know
the language of and they have like the
English translation and I order it I get
like something
different but also it's not even a it
doesn't look like a pancake or anything
like
that Quay sounds like cake or so so they
made um so like the texture of it is I
don't again I don't know if this is
similar to the one um that you know I
I've had in um like the Chinese dish but
it does look kind of similar if it uses
uh radish it's kind of how do I explain
it I wasn't a pancake and then they cut
it up someone says yeah it's kind of
like a really thick pancake except it's
hard to
explain I think is it the same is it the
same
as is it the same I don't know looks but
I I have to say this it looks delicious
and I want to eat it
if it's not spicy I'll eat it oh chess
says yes to the same oh okay it's hard
to explain it's like steamed as well but
I feel like I kind of yeah
yeah I'm I'm drooling here it's not
spicy then you're eating it wrong
because you're supposed to put spice on
it cuz it tastes so much I'm
sorry spicy food it's savorite yeah cuz
I just think in like when you say carrot
cake normally you think it's going to be
a sweet you know carrot cake m
but yeah okay well next question next
question oh what is the name of the a a
mascot korei in her um sponsored outfit
of which I will not say the name now get
in the robot
Cali no not that one no I know but I
just thought
it
um um
well who here who out of us has been at
Alpha
before not me do we need some help do
you think it's Miss rocket all right
chat chat help us chat do you guys know
do you guys
know SE
SE SE
SE they're doing a good job at like I
think also just they don't know the
answer for real like a lot of I think I
think I see a lot of sea so it must be
it okay SE oh it was s in the
video was it it was
apparently well I'm the questioner I'm I
didn't need to take notes what is the
answer please next SL
okay cute cute cute it was nice nice
okay all right fourth
question oh the venue where the anime
festival Asia Singapore is held has a
fountain that might make you rich what
is the name of that Fountain oh my God
coordinates please let me just go stand
under there for the rest of my life let
me just shower in that water surely
it'll help do you think this Fountain is
cool are you allowed to like run through
there or is it like off guys tell me
Chad I'm curious cuz how I feel like a
lot of kids would be running through
there right just the just the presence
of it makes you
rich it's is it really that simple of
a
yes if you could name a fountain that
might make you rich what would you know
the Fountain of wealth
[Music]
uh the Fountain of unlimited
resources uh the Fountain of
Gold Lion Fountain here I say something
else
oh that could be a good name what is the
name
please it's called the Fountain of
w recognized in 1998 by the Guinness
Book of World Records as the world
wow it's actually called the Fountain of
wealth
yeah congratulations to being the
largest Fountain I wonder how big it is
it was the world's largest Fountain
pretty big I
assume all right this is going to be the
last question yeah doesn't Las Vegas
also have huge fountains so it's got to
be even bigger than that yeah Las Vegas
is mountains yeah I mean fountains sorry
I don't know we'll see oh okay okay next
question named as one of the most
beautiful airports in the world what is
the name of Singapore's main
airport you guys know the name of the
airport Singapore
International
Airport
lions lions
uh-huh it seems to be you
chy I just okay the funny thing is I
don't know the name of the airport but
I'm pretty sure I know you know how
airports have the
codes I'm pretty sure I know the
code it's hard to forget once you know
it what's theod what is the code sin
isn't it
sin yeah yeah I mean that's I could have
guessed that please give us that
question
instead what is the answer please
answer
is Singapore is not even in
there yeah but then the code itself is
like sin so it's like
true all right okay was anyone keeping
count I was not keeping count no I don't
think we're keeping count honestly I
think it's fine not to keep count it's
like just a good you know good chill HP
stream we don't really need botes here
right that is
true we just got to keep the hype for
all the has negative points I will slap
you yeah know all right before before B
slaps someone in chat we can go talk
about the
next
okay we take it away want talk about
next video yeah okay you want to switch
scenes or uh we can switch when we get
to the quiz okay if we get to the so in
December we have two shows the first one
will be Anime Weekend Atlanta
Atlant on December 12th to5
2024 and and then the second one will be
in comic Fiesta in
koala which will be right before
Christmas December
wow we're so busy holy moly at the end
of the year yeah my goodness so is there
anything anybody has in their mind when
they think of Atlanta Atlanta Georgia
that's
it Atlanta Atlanta anything anything uh
I feel
like no no much no much
okay uh well chat has some things they
say uh Atlantis indeed that's not
Atlantis yeah and a certain a certain
soda is apparently from there I
guess peaches peaches peaches peaches
peaches Peach so oh wait I forgot to
switch slid
sry okay but yes we do also have some
pictures from previous events while
we're there yeah okay then let's show
the
pictures oh that's a cool stage wow
think I see some someone performing on
the stage we've never been to Atlanta
have
we not that I know a
not wow is this like the
vendors W looks mey all the vendors I
always love going to like the vendors
and the artist alleys whenever I go to
anic conventions there's just so much
things to to buy
[Music]
yeah is that
LE is that I don't know I don't know
that's so cool though but yeah they're
rocking the stage that's for sure
yeah very cool very cool but now
what is that is that all the pictures I
think so okay yes then I think we should
do with all this knowledge that we
obviously have we should do a quiz
wow magic
switch Yeah
magic worldwide quiz very knowledgeable
so we shall do a quiz together again
again okay Atlanta quiz we got guys all
right first question let's go let's go
oh what year oh yeah go ahead sorry I'm
asking the questions now what year did
Atlanta host the Summer Games
do they mean do they mean the o l y m
yes I think so yes okay you know what
you know I'll say the first two digits
you say the last two digits 19 there you
go teamwork
this the
last oh you actually know oh damn okay
do you did you know it
Ina yes yeah
okay good job
y
teamwork very nice very
nice okay that was then fast and easy
this is what happens when you put two
brain cells
together I think you got the easier part
though I didn't know you're talking
about sorry next question please Atlanta
is home to the busiest airport in the
world oh how many passengers go through
it each year can you make an actual
guess
uh
[Music]
one billion minimum one minimum
one billion
10 million 10
million is that you 100
million if ena's going 1 billion I'll go
100 million let's see who close billiona
are you saying 1 billion for real no no
no I'll go with like
3,763
okay all right uh that very exact let's
go to the
answer yeah over million passengers
annually
wow that's a lot of
people damn wow that makes me wonder how
come I haven't gone through at same yeah
oh it's quite the Hub
wow okay you guys chat you'll be going
through you'll be one of the 100 million
right if you go see us in the world tour
true add on to that please next question
get lost okay probably very easy how
many gallons of water exhibits does the
Georgia Aquarium have I'm Australian
this question doesn't mean anything to
me just thow out a
number this doesn't mean any what's a
gallon oh I don't know either you can
say it in any anything you want you say
how many okay how many I'll ask Google
how
many leaders you ask Google is a
gallon okay so one gallon is 3.785 lers
oh okay okay divide by three times by
three okay uh close to four lers no
don't close to four going to
say wait all of the exhibits inside the
aquarium is this a known big
aquarium it's yeah that that will be in
the answer more information about that
[Music]
444 Kil of water I don't know how to
judge that I don't know can we um I'm
going to that into laders I'm going to
go with 50 million gallons 50 million
gallons 5 Z yeah 50 million gallons okay
well I don't really know what number
gallons
he
uh what's kiler anyway kiler is just
it's a th I don't think that's real
okay
117,000
gallons wow yeah oh
117,000 gallons yeah oh okay I think
that's a lot of answer please answer is
what's closer 11 million what you I'm
closer I think okay oh no is it B I
don't
knowon I guess I'm kind of
far yeah I think you're both really
far uh it's 11 11 million gallons that's
a lot of water how many gallons did you
say Ena 50 I said
117,000
bro both really but ba is kind of closer
kind of yeah ba is definitely
closer 50
g well it is the largest aquarium in the
United State and the sixth largest in
the world wow damn I love aquariums they
have the largest airport uh in the world
and the largest aqu not the largest uh
Airport P it's the busiest the busiest
busiest yeah damn Atlanta wa whoo okay
next question please
okay when was the first anime week in
Atlanta bonus points for if you can say
where where it it wasn't in Atlanta well
like I don't
know more specifically you know how oh I
see I see I don't know
no guess just guess I feel like this one
has been around for a while though okay
so before 2017 yeah before 201 say
2011 okay you
[Music]
know
1996 same as the summer
games okay
answer answer is it is 1995 that was
close you was close oh my God so close
wow castle gate been around for a while
mhm
wow convention Senai wow
wow thank you
Senai Senai
tax all right SOA you're closer okay
yeah I guess we get a point for that
we're getting
points yeah okay well next one last
question
last is it true that anime week at
Atlanta is the largest anime convention
in the south east is this part of West
Coast East Coast what Coast no
Coast coastless
oh it's coastless this
yes it seems to be coastless
no Coast Southeast corner I see okay
sure I mean they're being very specific
with the directions this time yeah I
think you're flexing again I feel like
it has to be yes yes yes okay
answer true wow okay Southeast
Corner ha is the largest anime
convention in the Southeast with over 30
4,000 unique attendees in 2023 last year
wow mhm mhm yeah I wonder how many are
going to join this
time we got
to better than ever yeah yeah and of
course we also have a special
message from em we Atlanta who wants to
read uh yeah I think I okay while go I'm
reading it I AKA not me but the CEO am
very excited to welcome H live for the
performance this December at anime week
in Atlanta I know that the idols will be
giving their best performance and I hope
that the fans will also give their best
to support them you heard
that
yeah thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you so much for the sweet
message yes This Ss crazy I feel don't
no sorry I'm now it's like hitting that
we're going to so many cities
yeah are you motivated or what I'm I've
been motivated but I'm even more
motivated I will say I was a little I
was literally inable um a couple days
ago cuz I've been looking at my coming
schedule and I was in despair but this
is helping me motivate me yeah I'm so
motivated thank you guys
we
our and of course a week
after a can I say AWA a we'll also have
a show
in comic Fiesta in Colour so we need to
prepare very well for these two double
yeah oh my goodness oh my goodness yeah
we need we need help we need more help
we need help from the ID Girls okay yeah
the ID girls will support us for sure oh
my God does anyone know anything about
qu no i' I've seen a lot of stuff about
like comic Fiesta though cuz it's a
pretty big event yeah I see a lot of
artists they preparing for conventions
and stuff and like comic Fest always
comes up and I'm just like I want to go
see it someday yeah I've heard about it
too makes you really like think these
like big Anime conventions they have
quite the impact on the outside world if
the like one of the few things we know
about kumur is Comic Fiesta
[Music]
yeah I want to try all the food same
spicy food let's
go it's going to be so close to the
holidays too yeah H goodness literally a
couple days before Christmas
holidays no yeah you know calm down calm
down
okay well for the shows in December more
info will be released uh later in the in
the upcoming days so please stay tuned
um there to the event official account
so you don't miss any
[Music]
information y y so I think so far we've
talked about all the stops oh my God is
that it our mission huh is that it
um don't know maybe maybe world but the
world tour hasn't even started yet so
let's see what will unfold in the
future perhaps more things more yeah
okay next week is New York City and
everybody get get yourself ready for the
heat get yourself ready for the
beat maybe you need some stuff like what
could what could they need BS um you're
going to need your ticket for those who
manage to get tickets to the venu you
need your hotel reservation of course um
you need your goods your merch uhhuh and
and and and and what what do what else
do you need H you need to practice the
sword
chant oh the sword chant what's this
we have a chance you want to go back to
the um to the to the no we have a we
have a slide for was we have oh oh I see
okay I'm sorry um in the conert we have
a special chance to get all all of you
guys hyped up um and it goes like this
when we say world is the stage you guys
say
s not s it's sore
sore yes yeah yes I'm trying to do it
okay yeah I'm trying all right here we
go W is the
[Music]
stage
Senai yeah H that was good uh sadly we
will not have any streaming for the
concert as you guys may know I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry we said it before I
know you guys want to see it but the
chant is free for all so we can do it
again that will certainly make up for
the lack of
streams world is the
same all right St all good okay now you
if you sit at home while some one of
these concerts is going on and and
you're like oh man I don't I wonder what
they're doing now just like chant it
alone and then it's the same and if you
really want to feel you know you really
want to be immersed you just got to
chant it during you know the time would
be performing while holding and wearing
our H stage 24 merchandise feels like
bullying we're bullying them people who
can't
go but what do we have what do we have
what do we have
wow so first we have a live stage World
Tour 24 t-shirt comes in three sizes L
XL and XXL second we have a h live stage
world to 24 face towel you know to wipe
your face from the sweat that'll be
dripping down your face from cheering
too much and dancing and jumping too
much um it is the size um I think 34x 85
cm and it is made from
cotton yeah soak up those sweat drops
extra good but third we have have a Hol
life stage world to a 24 pen light with
the size um normal size normal size yeah
and I has a total of 12 penlight colors
so make sure you take note of what color
your ooshi is so that you can you know
cheer them on to the best of your
ability
yeah especially for those of us who are
performing in the Ian second live we
have the same color pen light for both
shows so remember it got that
memorized yeah it's going to be the mut
item you know cuz it's 3 days in a r
yeah same pen light
to so what are you waiting for guys mer
is already on sale right now and you can
purchase these items in our whole life
production official shop online and
don't forget to check the details before
you purchase them yeah link is in the
description or will be in the
description apparently there is plans to
sell them at enemy NYC venues too so
more winful will be announced later oo
okay
nice yes yes so now we have talked about
everything to prepare for the world tour
are you ready for
it
yeah oh my goodness time to practice
more guys my
good next week think next week is going
to be absolutely crazy I can
I'm spending
my oh it's my anniversary next week oh
god oh
yeah I expect to be spending my third
anniversary like this but you know what
I wouldn't have it any other way going
be together you'll be spending it with
us and the fans y let's go yay yeah is
going to be so
czy let's hit it off let's hit off a
nice World Tour yeah yeah let's kick it
off we'll have an amazing weekend and
all throughout the year going to have
amazing shows you guys excited I'm
excited super excited hope you guys look
forward to what we have prepared for you
guys
yeah well any news or updates will be
announced at a later date and there
might be uh similar streams by other
members of the tour in the future the
world tour has just started yeah it's
only just begun it's only just
chant again okay we'll end it with the
chant we'll end it with the chant okay
are we ready
ready world is the
[Music]
stage thank you guys byebye see you at
the byebye
[Music]
he