foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
yeah
this screen
already makes me mad
it's not very high energy well I'm I'm
fine but
such enthusiasm yeah
ah hello everybody
hello
uh first of all uh sorry I didn't get to
do the re-upload yet
uh but I I'm just gonna assume that
everyone's who's everyone who is here
right now
did watch the last Skyward stream sword
stream live or at least partially
didn't catch the end of it well the end
it was just suffering so it's good that
you didn't catch it
yes yes yes yes yes yes wow
wow everyone did I know come on
[Music]
missed the last hour well that's good
I'm glad you missed it
I'm I'm glad you missed it
um
I want to say that
oh I have been
uh generally a very stressed out as
probably a lot of you guys
know because I've been mentioning it but
um it's been reaching levels that uh
worry even myself
and so that
um
uh combined with the game already being
freaking frustrating for like after
seven hours of playing it
already having come across many
frustrating moments until the end of the
game but then the end fight
under the pressure of having to end it
in time for Ina's stream
out of respect because I think that's
just
I mean
I mean I I didn't I did not see the
option of playing over her stream that
was not an option for me so the insane
uh time pressure I mean combined with
uh nervosity and my hands being shaky
and sweaty and and and and the controls
being [\h__\h]
um
yeah all that combined uh ended up with
me being very very very emotional
[Laughter]
and um
yeah uh so the end of that stream
for me was
uh quite embarrassing
um
so I felt like I can't have you guys
see I can't have that on my channel like
I don't know I had a freaking breakdown
meltdown I have a freaking meltdown and
I didn't want that to be uh an archive
yeah
um
I think
I don't know what happened
um
I am I think like I'm definitely like
when I stream games
I
uh
uh like I I definitely do
uh exaggerate my emotions
uh for entertainment purpose but
um like if I would play a game normally
I would just play it quietly and never
rage but
I mean for streams I obviously have to
put my feelings uh into words and and
expressions and that's what I usually do
but on that stream
I was uh not feeling well towards the
end
so I don't feel comfortable with having
that up anymore
sorry and I did
I didn't need to I did need some time to
recover from that
um but uh actually on the same day after
that stream I started doing my whole VR
setup
yes
uh I did set it up a day before already
with Amit but there were things that we
um uh set up additionally on the actual
day but five or six hours prior to the
actual stream there was a lot of
a lot of preparation uh but we'll talk
about that later too we can talk about
VR and all of that
so
um we're gonna fight demise and I was
thinking I was thinking about
the fact that we could make this longer
and do the Boss Rush
but hmm
I
I don't know if I want to do that I
don't know
I don't know nah I don't want to do that
because that means I have to fight that
stupid mole again right
I don't want to fight that stupid mole
anymore
I don't want to fight that ass anymore
yeah so
um we're just gonna do the last fight
but we're gonna get proper healing items
and all that and we're gonna be calm
we're gonna be very calm and
and the the reason why I'm stalling
right now is because
I had both of my joy-cons in my switch
inserted but apparently one of them
didn't load so I'm stalling right now
[Music]
um
foreign
and
um I I watched right before the stream I
watched a video of
uh one of the only YouTubers I watch
maybe the only YouTuber I watch
who plays Nintendo games and Zelda games
and all that stuff
AKA
you probably know because I mentioned
him before but it's embarrassing to say
it so I will not saying yes
so I've watched his uh only only the
fight I only watched the fight and he is
like really really good with yellow
games he's so used to it and that was
not even the first time he played that
uh game but uh even he struggled
a lot with the stupid charging of the
stupid ass sword even he struggled with
it even though he's really good at the
game really good
and it was getting really mad as well
so thinking about how even really really
really good players
struggle with it charging it up
considering that I was already at
freaking at my freaking End of you know
power and energy and everything
with shaky hands and sweat and stress
and pressure and all that I think it was
it was understandable and also
um
some people were like uh I don't know
maybe you shouldn't have been running or
like don't move while charging but no
you can't charge it while running
well yeah I was just not yeah I was
under a lot of pressure it might be
stressed out and I didn't know what I
was I wasn't sure what I was supposed to
do yeah
um but
that I I think it's important to note
that not only I struggled but also
really good players in a really good
condition struggled
[Laughter]
yeah oh man that was that was uh
and what did I read today some of some
of you guys tweeted at me that we should
just bully him with the bug net excuse
me what what
don't tell me that's a an option
what does that mean
you can't we have to try it you can stun
it with a bug net it can reflect the
project what
I don't think I can like
really probably use it like that though
she's strapped wait that makes me think
of the question uh
doesn't this game have like
modes of difficulty and I played on
Noble or something and I could have
maybe set it too easy
was that an option I thought of that
afterwards and I was like wait was there
an easy mode
no
oh there's only one difficulty and then
there's here remote oh okay because I
was like oh for [\h__\h] sake what could
you set it too easy and I would have
probably done it properly
oh there is no baby mode oh okay
ah
Let's uh
quit right because I'm gonna be loading
foreign
yes
okay
and I'll be preparing better this time
uh we I'll go we have another bottle but
um question uh oopsie is this one empty
wait a second
ah yeah that's that's
one was supposed yeah we drank one of
them so what here can I get rid of to
get a fourth bottle the the seat the
small seeds actually I could uh get rid
of right
then get my fourth bottle and then put
um two Potions there
right I think I can get rid of that okay
uh oops what okay I'm playing with the
Pro Controller right now wait how do I
why do I have to go
yeah
you don't need bumsy true true
wait isn't there like a Heart Medal that
I could bring to
you don't yeah I think because I'm much
calmer obviously and have no time brush
I don't think we'll have much issues but
wait where is uh
the cat I don't know how to control the
camera and this one where is the where's
the
statue outside
yeah one extra maybe we should bring the
metal
hello where is it
huh
all the way down no time oh I have to go
for a time portal first am I in the am I
in the past right now or in the future
where am I
go back to the pass
you're in the past then you mean go back
to the future okay
oh yeah because implants yeah but Cruise
wait no wait this is the this is the
present
huh
I'm in
my mind though
I mean that's always the present but
Empires
oh wait why is gross here then did he go
for the portal
[Music]
Bruce is eternal
he was always there
he's a phoenix
am I going for the right door
where am I
oh
it's so pretty that's not where I wanted
to go
I should go for the side door not the
front door back though
the side door leads to a
statue I think
right
this one
nah
I mean
I like him by now but I don't like him
that much that I would say I want to be
friends with him
I don't know why you guys like him so
much no no we did not beat demise
already that's the only thing that we're
gonna do today and then yeah it's not
gonna be much uh content but
yes
[Music]
you said you love when did I say that I
don't remember such a thing you would
have to prove that to me
you start loving him after the game yeah
I think he already did the things that I
would have to love him for by now yo
they got a 20 rupee rupee
why did I start so
low
are we flying with the pro controllers
so much
huh
yeah
you said during the Super Chat yeah okay
I was probably just lying
what about that chest show
them God is cute for that yeah shut up
shut up I know that there's like a side
quest thingy with her I know
I'm not interested in you
okay so we'll get rid of that
oh there's the hard metal heart oh I
have five bottles you
when we get rid of
wait I already have the heart metal in
there wait a second what where's the
difference again live metal and heart
metal
where's the difference
[Music]
life medal is better
foreign
lets you get more heads from grass ah so
that one's useless
zombies
[Music]
all right
I think that's all that we really need
[Music]
yeah bye-bye we could get even one more
oh we could even get one more bottle if
we wanted to but do we need that much
[Music]
so I want one of that I think
and then one more of the far right one I
think
Maybe
maybe and this one I'll upgrade
here's the bottles for guys
[Music]
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yes yes yes yes
[Music]
has Kiana romanced pumpkin girl no
no I haven't but what would I
get rid of the quiver because I guess I
didn't use my eyebrows either
yes the quiver is not necessary
but then we get rid of the mushrooms for
is that sad but can I drink them or like
how do I get rid of them how do I empty
them
mine can I drink them
it used
oh wow sparkly sparkling
streams box
okay
um oh should we now let's get one of
those
so expensive but okay
start a fire today don't stop don't stop
just go your own way
[Music]
foreign
and think about what we put in the last
bottle
what should we put in one more red
potion Maybe
because now I have two Guardian potions
one red one and one fairy
red is good okay I thought so too so
um
[Music]
uh okay yeah I can upgrade that
yeah and I want to upgrade it
maybe one more time
because then I can use it twice
what part of the story are we in the
very end we're about to destroy the last
bus
really this stream is gonna be 95 uh
Super Chat rating
I just want to finish this up for
completion's sake that's really it
I would honestly just throw the game
away and never touch it again if it
weren't for a completion sake
okay
uh
I mean freaking last bus who cares
[Music]
okay now I don't I don't know should I
um if I upgrade the this one does it
just make it last longer
no it sounds expensive
upgrade the shield
I highly doubt that
wait a second am I buying the red one
no okay there we go I think yes
and what was I going to say
I probably I don't have to
stuff to upgrade the shield I probably
don't have it
[Music]
inside the garden potion okay that
probably is true as well
yes let me just talk to you again
upgrade the heart potion
maybe even twice I mean I don't think I
need that much but
and a blue feather you're right did you
not like Skyridge I liked it I like them
but I'm traumatized now
I I did like it
should I upgrade it one more time then
we basically have
what four four hard potions
[Music]
now let's do it
it's just like very fresh wait sorry
sorry very frustrating I want to do it
again
Legend of trunk
become Unstoppable with all the heels at
this point
all right
yeah yeah
get the Haley and shield now
pranking ourselves
and constantly to block him
that was not the issue the issue was me
not being able to attack him
if the shield was the issue I would
think about it but it wasn't
it it broke ah okay once but no
[Music]
and well and honestly I want to try uh
doing the back jump a little bit more
because I've noticed when he hits you
when he hits you and do it as I did uh
parrying him which I have to say I was
really good at even at the end you know
I'm on the first try I might have not
been able to attack him but but me
pairing him constantly
at the point where I was constantly
shaking and crying I would say that was
well impressive of meek
I've noticed that if you if you uh Parry
him
uh then he will hit three times
but if you jump back he will stop
hitting
like if you if you if he uh like attacks
it with the sword and you parry then he
will go from the other side attack with
the sword again you parry and then he
will attack a third time you parry and
that's when he stops but that's like uh
you need a lot of Rhythm feeling for
that and and and timing but if you step
back then he will stop after the first
hit and that's way safer yeah yeah yeah
I didn't know that
um back in the day
I think
we are ready
[Music]
Okay so
safe again yeah I'll save when I'm in
the temple
[Music]
Canada
time to destroy him yeah by the way in
German his name is the deathbringer like
the person who brings stuff isn't that
fun
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh
I never know where the hell to go
no no she doesn't bring death she takes
death
of people
you you bring death upon yourself though
don't you aren't we all deathbringers at
some point
we pray I mean unless unless someone
kills you then the person who kills you
is the deathbringer okay
now that we have cleared that one up
because
I have so many super chance to read you
can't waste time this this stream is
supposed to be mostly a Super Chat
reading
I'll be waiting for as long as I can but
I honestly have to say oh I'm pretty
sure I will not be able to finish
reading them today and I don't even know
if I can go for 10 hours
because I am not
um on my best uh
[Music]
uh condition
yeah so we'll probably have to split it
up
Kiana be like
oh what so let me get my joycoon
[Music]
come on you charged enough don't jump
why is that
is is it broken why is it not charging
that should have at least been
at the middle now
I've been charging it
I think it's broken
you plug it back no that's not even
possible
it's not even possible
joycons break often
eh
I mean it has a green light right now so
let's just do it
yeah it clicked it 100 clicked 100 100
percent
it already did the first time I
connected it over the past two days
and it didn't charge hey but I didn't
like throw it around I don't know how it
could break
I didn't I I don't think I was so
aggressive with it
[Music]
don't go
the tiny gentles
well we'll just have to okay here we go
time pressure after all
Time Fresh Shuffle
how do I do the back jump again
um was it with b and then flip back
wait I'm not ready I want to test the
back challenge
I didn't do it again safe I did save I
did I didn't
I did
didn't you see me standing
Target and beat Target
down here is this there's a statue here
oh okay I guess I'll just save here
I never noticed that one
I ain't Bank ain't
it
[Music]
um
foreign
jump sideways I guess I can do that too
yeah okay let's do this I don't have
batteries
my freaking joy-con is broken I think
what the hell I have to get new ones
yeah I'm ready
practice guy with strikes I don't even
know how to practice that it's like
freaking Kima gurude it just does
whatever the [\h__\h] wants to do
it's absolutely ridiculous
no no I already knew how to do sidestep
but I just didn't feel like using it
because it doesn't feel natural to me
the back step
okay do we need to listen to this again
[Music]
okay well first I will probably fail
because I don't remember how to do
things uh uh
uh
I wanted to do the side steps
let me let me do it
[Music]
um
okay I can't do it
nice
[Music]
Target
it's clicked it clicked is there any way
to check if it's uh really charging like
in in the
in in this menu uh uh wait a second
can I
um ah see that one is connecting isn't
it see it says it's charging
it does say it's charging the other one
didn't need charging so I just
have it here
I know I know that's not that's the one
that then is currently charging it
should be the right one
at the the the the one that's left
whatever okay I'll connect both them
what
we could read some super oh wait that
was the wrong one
all right
I just want to say I had I had them
connected for two days though okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
cat hairs nah
nah
it was connected
let's read some super chats
let's read a few ones
I'll read I'll read a few super chats uh
from Skyward Sword uh the last one the
one before
but even though
I got it
okay
foreign
are these really the first ones
does someone know who sent the first
Super Chat
in Skyward Sword stream
what about Tales of her eyes
of the rise
ah no those are
I didn't read the yeah oh now I'm pretty
sure wait those are
uh I guess that was our
some leftovers
from not the last
Sky ah
yeah sorry my and nothing I say makes
sense but I think it's that one
a few ones that were left over from this
one I saved them in my Excel file
I think because after that comes
Minecraft and after that comes Tales of
our eyes and then comes Zelda again yeah
I do have quite a few left over not only
for the anniversary
dance
oh wait that's Minecraft
foreign
[Music]
responded only if you say please
break that Atlantis was Unsinkable then
Mama Tony decided Atlantis would make
for a good swimming spot
mama told you fact number three Emma
didn't show up in the first mamatory
collapse you ground pounded herself out
of fear
[Laughter]
Mystic has been Exchange number four the
day Kelly decided to take a Hiatus from
reaping as the day Kiana told her about
mamaturi
what
he went to pray for him
Jay
swagbergen Dr Helga stankison Chuck
Norris Jones oh I oh sorry to disappoint
you I don't understand those Mr Casper's
and Dr Helga's Duncan uh
number five oh God I want to Super Chat
a momentary fact about in on the engine
ones but Cosmic Horrors run from
mamatory
one
what what
wait there's not even bgm this is so sad
right now
am I at the beginning
yes and that's double
I'll get it
uh zero six oh foreign
it was roughly a year ago I woke up to
wfh in the morning and today was Darkest
Night at 10 am
foreign
humble game pitch
it lurks below by greybeard games 2D
action-oriented RPG by Dev David bradvic
known for such games as Diablo and
Diablo 2.
I work from home oh
what
you guys speaking riddles to me today
we're back in that day lyrics
now I don't like it
nah I don't like the Aesthetics
be gentle wow okay
[Music]
you guys should know me better you
should know my cakes for now
[Music]
hi
okay
thank you for the pinky it's been a
wonderful it's been wonderful watching
you and Mama until you play Minecraft
together she's not only a Mastercraft
but she was also very funny she truly is
one very cool Mom thank you for making
it happen and let her know millions of
chickens loved having her oh she knows
thank you actually I'm I'm sorry I
couldn't like squeeze uh collab with her
in this week I'm actually also [\h__\h]
busy this week as always and I'll be uh
seeing her at the end of the week
actually I'll be visiting her
um and uh I'll try to squeeze it in
maybe next week Tuesday or Wednesday
which will basically be the last chance
because we're gonna build the portal
next week
mm-hmm
yes and you know also there will be new
outfits
most likely revealed during this month
so
I will have to really squeeze a lot of
things in
out for the reveals Minecraft portal
building
and uh this week called Talk blah blah
so much going on
yeah what did you guys not see the
announcement I mean we only announced it
on the anniversary collab stream I guess
and besides that whole life English did
not even post about it on Twitter I
think right
I think they're
waiting for something until the dates
are actually set in stone
and then they'll tweeted out I think
yeah I think they didn't even so
everyone who didn't see the anniversary
doesn't know about it I guess but
60 000 people were watching so I'm gonna
suppose assume you guys already know
about it
yeah and
the silhouette look fancy yeah
a 70k holy [\h__\h]
and yeah BLD watches I mean that was
something you just can't
Miss
like I think everyone watched it at this
point right
yeah
holy [\h__\h] that was a legendary stream
and I
just later probably but I just have to
look at us
doing like we
our set of Mind mindset
DIY
if if it doesn't work out because of
other [\h__\h] then di [\h__\h] why
like holy [\h__\h]
all of that
made by
like
set up by Hollow myth
and obviously the the people who worked
on the sets and all that but
what I'm trying to say is
there's no there did that was made by us
you understand
we just put it in our own hands
[Music]
yeah
which I think is absolutely amazing
nothing can stop us
oh
[Music]
I mean otherwise
we could have said okay
well unfortunately we don't have proper
3D and we can't be together
in a studio in Japan for anniversary how
often sad let's just do a normal boring
collaboration
where we I don't know talk about the one
year which probably would have been fun
too but instead we tried our best to
make something great out of it
um with our own power and our own money
all of us all of us got ourselves a VR
set
so no
just have to say
bad cuddle kudos to us
and the people who made the sets and the
model and all that
um
Felix sound thank you for the who four
so you shocked me so much I
I'm about to throw up uh four red super
chats are you insane
thank you it's so nice to see you
playing MC with Grandma Tony again later
this month will be the traditional
holiday in my country to visit family oh
and I'm finally going back home again to
stay with my parents oh last time I was
back I only stayed with them for three
weeks and that was after two years of
not seeing them I really hope I stayed
longer that time because this time I go
back I can only stay for three days oh
also time to I think you put the word
Minecraft on the last place you should
place it I'm sad really sad what
I mean the word Minecraft on the front
there's just because I mean the Boba
[Music]
oh did that bother you the placement of
the thumbnail of Minecraft logo
it has to be so somewhere
I tried to keep both of her
boing boing visible
we couldn't look respectfully no
respectful would be if you would not
look at my Mom's boobs at all
so it's good that I covered it up
I wish you lots of fun with your family
it'll be great I'm sure of this
[Music]
ciao yeah I hope you have a great time
hope your family is healthy and happy
and you as well thank you for the insane
support oh lee macaroni thank you thank
you
incredible I don't even want to know
whether you donated for the anniversary
I don't know I never want to see it
is so cool yeah it's it's like I am I'm
I'm um I'm shook how she can make such a
edgy weird Minecraft skin looks so good
when she draws it like she can draw
anything and make anything look good
she could probably make a person in a
lasagna suit
look good
yes
thank you soon Captain something
something
brand hits
Kiana just wanted to say that we all
love you a lot thank you
it was as I always have fun spending
time with you and I'm sure everyone here
feels the same also I may or may not
have accidentally deep-fried part of my
pompadour while working in the kfp
kitchen the other day well plan by the
way is that the the thing that
wait a second on Pandora
you mean the you mean the thing on top
of the chicken head
oh it's a hairstyle is it not actually
in the fan the the the
in German I think we call it come
come
oh [\h__\h] yeah the only thing that comes
up when I Google that is a lot of
uh edgy men
[Laughter]
oh oh my oh my God
but some of these photos are
um
killing me
oh my god do you really have that
hairstyle I mean I don't have a problem
with the hairstyle
yeah it's pretty sick it's pretty sick
yo
imagine a chicken with a pompadour hair
thank you
thank you so much okay I think we can go
back to playing it's trying just fast
doesn't it
um
foreign
[Music]
okay I'm nervous I'm really like right
now in the middle of the fight oh dear
I have a bad feeling we're gonna fail
[Music]
s
oh you've done both of me
[Music]
oh I got it
what was that what was that sound was
that feet shut up why do you look like I
can talk to you right now
do I look like a good time for your [\h__\h]
right now
[Music]
okay I got the size the back step down
though
[Music]
I'm gonna use this by the way
I couldn't use it one day how do you use
it
I'm so slow like I can't I guess because
I have him uh targeted huh not in his
face oh
[Music]
I remember that second try where I
absolutely destroyed him though I wonder
how I did that I just had a really good
run on that second try
[Music]
it's all good I don't know what the hell
is that though we is he doing them
[Music]
yo you got a lot of power
when he does that move I guess I could
have spin attacked him because he raises
his arm he's like he's busy doing other
things
[Music]
oh oh wait does that really like
actually
um
trying to carry I didn't know the old
time last time but people attacked more
often it's actually worse
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
okay come on
[Applause]
[Music]
um
[Applause]
come on
[Laughter]
look at that
again
[Music]
come on calm down
maybe for once charge the [\h__\h] sword
[Applause]
[Music]
it's just it's just it's so easy
[\h__\h] oh
[Music]
I'm trying to charge timing
[Applause]
challenge
[Music]
I'm really bad at this it's good
and look at him look at him next time
wait I want to try to I want to try to
think
how do I use this
don't they are not
wow
thank you
take this
what's chilling now
okay yo
[Music]
what's with the camera okay
[Applause]
oh boy
[Music]
foreign
oh come on
I'm good by the way I'm really I'm good
I'm good I'm good I'm good
I'm good but this is just stupid ass
[\h__\h]
I'm trying to do it
oh come on
okay I'm already
come on
wait
[Music]
come on one more time
for God's sake
[Music]
okay
piece of [\h__\h] bastard dad what a [\h__\h]
mm-hmm
it looks wrong
[Music]
though this is not the end my hate never
passes it is born and you want to cycle
with no end I will rise again probably
has gone unto youth
[Music]
they are eternally bound to this curse
an incarnation of my hatred times
[Music]
foreign
Consciousness has been absorbed into the
master sword and is now sealed away
away
yay yay
yeah
yeah baby
you have done well link
shut up
not a group of course
link
thank you
I think it's over no no no no no no no
no no no
it's not what denial
I'm so sorry Zelda
it will follow you forever
will be there forever
nice growing you do you guys are totally
amazing in this little Adventure Island
to call the legend of course
oh
that's a little joke
[Music]
or not your contributions to our efforts
were heroic you have my thanks
uh well you know just glad I could make
myself useful I'm happy things turned
out okay
hey so things look pretty soon up here
Sean thank you what do you say guys
ready to head back to our own time
granny was really worried about you too
we don't want to keep the old girl in
suspense along she's right there next to
you
oh
thank you thank you thank you guys
hi Leah you're Grace or perhaps you
prefer Zelda what pleases me to know
you're safe
master I must speak with you
she got a double chin yo
[Music]
master link you have successfully
protected the goddess reborn and
defeated demise fulfilling your role as
the hero of Legends
my purpose here is complete therefore I
ask you to dissolve our Arrangement as
master and servants
I would be delighted too
Drive the sword into the pedestal before
you and I will return to the sword to
enter a sleep without end
Master you have achieved the purpose you
were chosen to fulfill please set the
sword in the pedestal and bring the
goddess mission to an end
now Master it is time to conclude
our necessary companionship
[Music]
me
ah yay
it is done
we finished the game
yeah that's it
come on
link
thank you link hear me my purpose was to
obey the command of the goddess and Lead
You The Chosen hero of this land on your
quest
when I first awoken began this task I
perceived it as merely serving my
function as a servant to her grace
however I have come to consider the
information corresponding to our time
together among the most precious data I
have on record of staff oh stop
oh
and now kids
eat Zelda she was like ruining
everything anyway go for feek I ship it
I do not have the capability to fully
understand the human Spirit link but now
at the end of my journey with you as I
prepare to sleep within the master sword
forever I experienced a feeling I am
unable to identify
I lack sufficient data to be sure this
reminds me of near automata
hmm
of my conclusion but I believe this
feeling correlates closest to what your
people call happiness
our partnership is at an end and even as
we speak I feel my Consciousness fading
away
sorry I mean like the thing you know
that they feel you know
before I enter the sleep that calls me
to the sword I wish to relate to you
words that I recorded many times over
the course of our journey
many have said them to you thus far but
I now wish to say them for myself
[Music]
thank you link master link
may we meet again in another life
[Music]
skiing
thank one another do it do it
show her what love is she learned What
happiness is you can show her what love
is
what empa why
come with us
Zelda
Zelda Your Grace you possess the
memories of the Goddess you must
understand why that is not possible
I am a being of this age my place is
here
[Music]
makes sense
I I know that but
[Music]
you must return to your own time I will
take care of the gate once you have
passed through
[Music]
I can't do that you and I have been
through so much together
I don't want to leave you alone oh shut
up Zelda
don't be such a drama queen
come back with us
Zelda at the command of the goddess and
pass through the gate of time I did so
to protect you and ate the fight to
prevent the world's destruction
the last remnants of the Vise aren't
decaying slowly within the sword someone
must stay behind to watch over displayed
his Spirit must not reawaken you must
never be allowed to frighten the world
again
y'all are really not doing a great job
on this kind of stuff you know how many
games came out
after this link
the this is the first one I mean it came
out later but you know what I mean
you know how many times Ganondorf has
revived already
you know
too many
hahaha
this is the nature of the task given to
My Tribe
as a member of the sheikah the goddess
Chosen Gardens I gladly welcome this
Duty
[Music]
[\h__\h] discount salesman
Zelda I shall watch over the Trifles
its power is too great to leave in the
grasp of men
dependence on its might is an invitation
to a disaster
when it has served its purpose it must
be secreted away to lie dormant once
again the knowledge of its existence
hidden from Mortals mortal history
these are the words the goddess spoke to
me long ago I remember them well as do
you I'm sure yes we're done yes and we
are as your name says liberated from
this now
Hallelujah
foreign
skyward Swords
I heard there were motion controls but
they make me go insane I wish this was
in motion controls to begin with
I don't know what they thought of this
when they created it they just wanted to
trigger all of the fans in this world
Hallelujah
[Laughter]
do not despair Zelda you and I will
surely meet again someday
I know
thanks Simba
have a nice life
I guess sitting in this room forever
waiting for the sword to do something
is that Flair's mother oh interesting
Theory
it's flare chica
chica descendant
I like these three people
it's gone hi Grandma
hello
we did it you proud of us oh
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
[Applause]
yo wait what what you guys didn't
realize I thought we realized that long
ago
wasn't that obvious
see I told you we'd meet again huh did
we not know that yeah
they left critical information you did
it
maybe if it if I played this game
without you maybe I would have
not realized earlier I don't know I feel
like it was kind of
[Music]
yeah pretty obvious yeah
I am pretty much
[Music]
because she knows everything
and she's waiting there for us to do
[\h__\h]
yeah also she has blonde hair she's like
Emperor hmm it makes sense
oh
she just forced herself to stay alive
for this
thank you
for everything
well that's sad
Ness
oh
[Music]
that music reminds me of window wake up
music what the hell
[Music]
that's like the the ocean music
that's that's the awesome music
[Music]
the little one the little one in the
background
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
do I need to press something
well
it was it was the first seller that I
played from beginning to end properly on
my own so
um I don't have much to compare it with
[Music]
um
if it's wearing for the motion controls
it'll probably get a way higher rating
from me
although you know I generally like the
idea of putting motion controls in here
and
like you know the sword fight generally
was I and like
um shooting arrows was fine too
and then there were other things where
there were a lot of issues learning
balancing on ropes and
yeah stuff like that
um
but I like that they tried
they tried
yeah the execution
I guess it has been improved in HD
definitely I heard it was way way way
way way way way worse so at least that's
something
but a bit more Improvement would have
been nice I guess is this showing us
scenes that of of Zelda because we
didn't have her point of view that's
actually cute
oh yeah
[Music]
oh wait I wanna watch that where's impa
oh there why was she not with her when
she was surrounded by those bad heads
oh that's sweet
oh okay
okay you're gonna make me cry
[Music]
you just couldn't sleep
foreign
[Music]
bye
dude
yes
[Music]
yeah no um
I know this game has a lot of
um
negative criticism
but uh I think all in all it was a great
set of game hmm
I think the story was fine
uh the pacing was fine the only problem
that really bothered me was the motion
control and the fact that they reused
the same areas over and over and over
and over and over again
including the same enemies
um the same I mean okay I understand
that you reuse box please
[Music]
I'm confused
but
so I understand that they repeat dose
what goblins ah
[Music]
but um like the freaking
um
what do they call that thing
that one that we kept on stealing you
know what I mean
and and the repetition of the freaking
um oh
uh free areas yeah
oh my God
[Music]
Montana
foreign
[Music]
good foreign
Nintendo means that nintendor did you
know their name is nintendor
has an r at the end no people don't
usually see it oh this means that we can
have a Della bgm for Super Chat CL not
the grocery
[Music]
oh God they have the same hairstyles I
feel so sorry for those boobs who gave
them those haircuts
I should be able to choose their own
haircuts dear Lord that's like animal uh
abuse
[Music]
oh link actually really plays the harp
now for her huh how sweet
oh
[Music]
bye
taking a screenshot of that
because it's beautiful scene
safe
what what's happening so I was saving my
screenshot why doesn't she look sad
look around us as a child I always
dreamed of a world below I wanted to see
the surface with my own eyes and feel
the lens one Blaze on my skin
I
I think I want to live here
I always want to feel Solid Ground
beneath my feet
see the clouds above my head and watch
over the Triforce that's kind of sad
that's sad I mean
um
[Music]
what about you link
now let's stay in the sky
what will you do now
I'll go Mary feet wow
[Music]
link will become a YouTuber
not with that face
[Music]
the end
nice
oh
thank you everyone
for watching my playthrough of The
Legend of Zelda
no
Skyward Sword
thank you it was uh well with this I
guess it's kind of 10 episodes long
but I would say we made it a nine
oh let's say officially we made it in
Nine episodes
yeah thank you for finishing here oh
that wasn't after that stream honestly I
was like I'm never gonna touch this
[\h__\h] game ever again
I was I was pretty close to just not not
picking it up again
but yeah I did I did I did it anyway
no no shut up
um okay
yeah no I think it's great that we
played it down the game
um now we can finally move on and play
other games this was fun though there
were many fun moments hmm I had my fun
you know it's not the best one but it
was it was a overall
good game
and I'm sad to say goodbye to my hat
yeah
the other one too this one very sad
and oh and also hopefully I can use the
joy cons again at some point
yeah
[Music]
now I can get rid of uh this logo and
OBS I had it in there for a while
breath of the wild no I mean wherever
the wild is a genius game but I feel
like it would take like a million years
for me
um
it feels like an insanely long game
I do want to play breath of the wild too
on stream but number one I know I said
before I would want to like play it
before going into breath of the wild too
but I already watched a [\h__\h] ton of play
full playthroughs of that
um
uh Speed Run going directly again
yeah no
um I don't think that we're gonna do
that honestly I don't think we can
play that one first
uh I might give it a try like privately
but I don't think I want to do a whole
stream about that
um major worst mask uh well I don't know
when breath of the wild 2 is coming out
we don't know that yet right I mean
probably end of next year or something
like that
I guess
so until then I mean we still obviously
have time so we could still play and
have a Zelda game until then
yeah yeah I feel like they're gonna aim
for like maybe next year Christmas
if not earlier
we will see Wind Waker hey
I love Wind Waker I love Wind Waker
you have a lot of time so we will have
some time to think about it I want to
play Tales of her eyes first and then
Final Fantasy maybe if we finally get
permissions at some point Final Fantasy
or seven or whatever I don't even care
anything anything really I just want to
get into the series
and I also want to play near a replicant
at some point
and same with permissions though still
waiting and other many other Square Enix
games
[Music]
um rides are free oh yeah wait wait a
second
am I going crazy was that like announced
was that announced
no no we thought it would be announced
but then it was uh uh the other game duh
right
the the other uh what would um yes
we were like Bamboozled we were like we
thought rise of free is going to be
announced you but bubbled us
yeah yeah yeah I'm not gonna play that
Bravely Default yeah
yeah but I've been asking for
um permission for uh
um Square Enix games since over a year
ago as you guys know
like I want to play Bravely Default I
want to play
um I am setsuna I want to play octopath
Traveler
all of those you keep you guys keep on
asking because I don't play that see you
I see you yeah we're probably gonna play
it
we probably will Spyro yes Spyro sounds
like fun
yeah yeah
I have the city lying around around here
hmm
spiral hell yeah let's go
to a rock
and there I saw other girls playing it
so you guys can just see watch them like
Enos play through or uh what's bounce
the one playing it
anyway let's go to my office
what did you say about free houses
I already played for why are you
suggesting Fireball and free houses are
you by any chance not aware that I
already played that
was one of my first players
so let me do the let me do the chat
uh chateau
chat
oh yeah
uh I should
I could put the thumbnail for what I'm
reading right now one of those TVs
how about that
but I should write a text somewhere and
I'm reading super chats maybe just above
that's really truly yeah yeah we're
gonna play that one too and actually
that one I didn't remember it as such
because I never finished playing it back
in the day on on the DS but as far as I
know it's a short game isn't it like
what 12 hours or so
could finish it in two streams
I didn't realize throw away it was such
a freaking short game
um
[Music]
the frogs Bean wait I'm gonna put on
some uh music in a moment
we're gonna play Zelda music because
why the hell not
here
[Laughter]
we have so many so what what Zelda
skyward Swords soundtrack do we want to
listen to don't say gross
don't
say it
um
yeah
that one is beautiful
but let me go through
[Music]
I love that one
I want a bit more a bit more
[Music]
kick weaving what's that one like
foreign
[Music]
I don't know about making it into Super
Chat reading bgm
Carolina
that's cute
[Music]
yeah maybe for now we listen to Bazaar
one second
guess much later but that one is up
upbeat I want that right now Bazaar
always team uh Zelda
your show
oh
is that too loud
[Music]
fine but grooves for him later yeah
nah just kidding we played it last time
foreign
[Music]
because I I only ate a piece of cake for
breakfast
and I didn't have the appetite to eat
more than that
at that moment so
uh I will have to prepare some food in
between but guys you know what I did
last night at 3am
and know what I did at 3am 3am last
night
[Music]
I I was I was thinking about making
lasagna but I was like I gotta make
something new one and also lasagna is a
little bit too much work that I don't I
don't feel like doing that so I actually
made a new dish for the first time
that's also really simple let me send it
to General on
um
Discord so I can download it
[Music]
um
no no this one how do I send it there
you go
I cooked
yes I made food
[Music]
it was a simple one oh that's 3am yeah
because I
I destroyed my sleeping schedule even
more than it already was
[Music]
uh because of the anniversary
so
I made
[Music]
I'm good
um wait
[Music]
thank you
and I ate it with bread
but I made a mild one because you guys
know I can't eat spicy food so I put no
spiciness in it but it was so good yum
yum yum yum and I have a lot of leftover
um
foreign
[Music]
I [\h__\h] love corn I love corn
really good could eat it even with
noodles to be honest
what do you guys eat chili con kind of
with normally
I only had bread
uh I mean I had I had noodle soup but I
I decided to eat bread with it well do
you guys eat and live
[Music]
rice oh nachos cornbread
some rice fries
I guess that works yeah
beans and rice chips chips
chips you mean you mean are you British
wait when you say chips you mean potato
you don't mean the snack chips right
chips
what
[Music]
okay
I don't see that as like I only see
tortilla chips as a snack or like
something you eat at the cinema so
just scoop it like salsa what
so intended way to eat it though
[Music]
I wonder
foreign
[Music]
oh wait that's a good idea put it in a
burrito oh
that's a good idea
nice
[Music]
pronounces
ah
[Music]
we don't have so much time to spell
we gotta get somewhere unfortunately we
have a lot to read
[Music]
okay
soon what's AIM thank you for the pinky
I fixed my kfm name at s yeah right yeah
yeah it's correct now I'm just listening
because I'm working today wireless
earphones are good for special agents
wait
special
special agent
are you implying
that you are a spy
[Music]
from the teammates
I am worried now wait I should go down
something on my head I feel so naked
[Music]
foreign
casual clothes
but it's my office so I decided what the
hell are you wearing here but I
shouldn't be in here
[Music]
they off in the office
if I bring in you know some chickens in
here
into my office wearing this they're
gonna be like whoa
[Music]
they probably wouldn't be able to focus
looking at me
I mean I look freaking hot smoking hot
in my uniform too but
but this is like a different kind of
side from your pencil
[Music]
let's just say let's just say though the
the main part my main shift was playing
the game and Super Chat reading is just
you know after after work stuff so I'm
allowed to you see now that makes sense
now it all makes sense
foreign
[Music]
oh
oh I see a lot of uh new super chats
from Malaysia
apparently super chants are activated
there now
thank you thanks for the pinky donkey
and Taylor singing
[Music]
foreign
skip those
for time saving purposes
thank you for thinking
Matthew thank you for the pinky as well
your Diablo story reminded me of the
time I could not beat Battle because I
played a poorly build through it and had
to ask my mom to help me she played
sorceress to this day I saw proudly
saying that the battle was being mean so
my mom beat him up oh yeah I remember
reading the super chat during the Stream
oh yeah that sounds very familiar
um thank you for Pinky too hey potential
the school have started so I can't watch
your every stream I feel so tired and
depressed due to the school can you say
something to encourage me and let me
have the energy to face the task love
potential oh
yeah I think uh school can be very young
exhausting and
yeah sad frustrating as well
[Music]
but but
you can do it
you can do it you're gonna you know what
once you're out of school I can tell you
pretty much everyone says that I think
you're gonna miss school afterwards
yeah so you should make the most out of
it even if it's tough
you'll miss it at some point
um
so
good luck you can do it you can do the
thing
yeah
uh wait I have to translate this name
um
and Translate
[Music]
that's so difficult to read
thank question
what the [\h__\h]
I'm done with you since ages ago
oh because oh right thanks wait
thanks for destroying the breeding of
Santa we are reaching an understanding
you are invited to join bleach Japan's
New Black branch bleeds Phoenix shut up
oh so many new members thank you
[Music]
freaking bleach Japan man it won't let
go of me
foreign
[Music]
to all of you guys
so I'll take that as a compliment for me
Rosie dancing
[Music]
with the red fluff attack
thank you
[Music]
and happy belated birthday thank you for
the almost pinky thank you for using
your Phoenix powers to bring Faith in my
inhumanity back to life I'll try my best
to make sure my children grow up to have
a heart as big as yours oh that's so
sweet thank you I'm sure you'll be doing
a great job at that thank you and happy
happy birthday
[Music]
thanks for the pinky I have to sleep now
but I wanted to say that you're awesome
generally you are so kind to everyone
and streams and your streams are a joint
to experience they are a lovely bundle
of happiness every time keep it up
you're in an uh you are an awesome
person we all support you thank you
thank you that's very sweet of you to
say
I'm glad you're enjoying all my streams
thank you please keep on supporting me
I'm gonna skip the
last chance
[Music]
Smith thank you for the pinky when the
Gen 2 embargo is over can you call your
collapse of crony the cuckoo stream is
in KU kluxler
ah funny
oh
[Music]
wait so the that clock itself is just
called is it not called cuckoo clock
just the cuckoo would just be the bird
no
so it should be cooked I don't know how
to pronounce it
[Music]
I did I like it thank you RP Rana RL for
Danke Schoen atomics 1199
and
um
Sammy is random question is
ah
[Music]
no come Sunny down
okay
bloody bloody diary F incense boys
[Music]
can't stay with the whole stream the
collab with Mama Tony has so much fun
mama told you you are so based PSL love
the TV series The Wire too ah is that
one that my mom mentioned
and hold on you guys are connecting too
much with my mom
you guys should connect more with me
Nacho natural
yes we could do that yes thank you for
the pinky it is close to one year now
that you had your debut I must admit at
the beginning I wasn't sure if I liked
the streams but still gave them chances
and bit by bit Phil fell in love with
your quirky lovely energy and
thanks so far thank you I'm glad you're
staying you stained me I definitely
changed
uh a bit over the course of the one year
so everyone who gave me a try in the
beginning and then gave up on me should
give me a try again
[Music]
I've been working really hard
foreign
[Music]
oh thank you I'll probably turn them on
for a moment after at the very end of
the Super Chat reading
[Music]
been here since day one thank you
thank you thank you guys
and yeah sorry I'm rushing for the super
chats a little bit you guys know why
obviously we have a million of super
chats to read so find it thank you
Patrick
zero nine dancing for the pinky
hi attention today is my birthday and
I'm 26. oh normally I'm allergic but I
just want to say I love your streams
found you in October when I lost my job
and you really kept my spirits up now I
finally got the job I always wanted oh
thanks and keep being awesome well first
of all happy belated
nice
and second of all she made me that was
you know supposed to happen it was bound
to happen it was fate
so that you could get your dream job
afterwards
I'm glad I'm glad that happened for you
congratulations
[Music]
becomes a Diablo 2 resurrected yes
thank you
no
[Music]
thank you
what
[Music]
oh dear interesting Super Chat right
right
so Freedom Christian thank you Jim and
one five one point
yeah
apparently that's what that was free for
you
wonder how that works
my pool share HD thank you soon
thank you for the red super chat I also
heard a bird saying something about free
super chats no
no your bank statements I highly doubt
that those were free
questions
[Music]
it's not for your sentence and they
charged my card it's a scam I
[Music]
am
someone clip it and show it to me
what do you mean afraid what do you mean
when did that even start
where did that come from
[Music]
I don't understand
it's a joke
who came up with that who said they were
free
in what crime context did I say that
[Music]
Coco senpai
cute
Alex and Doug Joseph
Mario's entire family yes this laser guy
Dan cushion Forest Henry Duncan London
why is everyone going in on this joke
joining in on it they're all saying it's
free it's free it's free
Friends food on kitchen L scientists
thank you missed
[Music]
industry
logical
tank residences
[Music]
foreign
at night time I feel like I'm watching
Fried Chicken Koreans love chickens as a
late night snack
it means your stream is sweet
[Music]
I mean I wouldn't mind eating chicken
nuggets late at night I get that I can
relate to that
thank you
Lillian Johannes Hong Dunkin James I am
a
Thomas
King couple dancing Felix thank you
[Music]
foreign
so here's my one percent of my bonus oh
I left the middle out of my last pink
Super Chat so here's that part then you
want the whole of myth girls debutant
that weekend and have helped brighten my
days for the last year well this is
great now pirate Homewood and now I have
absolutely no context
this is
are you here but I mean I guess it's in
the middle of what's like supposed to be
in the middle of like a teddy wholesome
Super Chat just giving me that one
sentence now
[Music]
how did you know
how did you know that
[Music]
too
okay we are we are going through this
smoothly but I'm already hungry
I'm hungry
[Music]
angry
foreign
okay uh I
[Music]
um okay yeah I'm sick of it already too
um
[Music]
I'm ascending
my legs should still be somewhere cause
only my
only my upper body ascendant maybe I can
find my legs
[Music]
I descended with legs only
okay okay
let me set my freaking ass down
however I should have I should have wait
I have to ascend again and go get
something something to eat but what
should I get I have strawberries but I
would have to wash them and maybe I
don't know cut them
and it's not crab food and I have yogurt
with some chocolates
cookie things to put inside
it's more like a breakfast still and I
have I could make a sandwich I could
make I would have to bake the bread
first
[Music]
and when I eat the chili con carne later
at night
the yogurt would be the fastest pull
um but sandwich takes some time
but the yogurt won't last for the coming
10 hours anyway
[Music]
strawberry
um
I will
uh I will get the yogurt and already
warm up the oven for the bread
oh god let's do it that way
okay descending
[Music]
foreign
while I was at it
I was passing by my
a
bedroom and I saw her ears
behind my blanket I was like oh
it's moving
it's movies
I have ascended
music but maybe we should play something
else
[Music]
what about this
oh
isn't that the skyloft thing
[Music]
sounds like it
let's play this a little bit the other
one was so upbeat I need something chill
oh nice
[Music]
beautiful
yes you're good yogurt yoga
[Music]
this one is called
island in the sky
island in the sky hmm what was your
favorite yoga flavor yeah
I wouldn't say I have a favorite one
I like
vanilla and stretch out yellow and um
right now it's banana though banana with
some chocolate flakes
crunchy
crunchy Mama lonely
[Music]
um
yes
yes we killed we killed him
finally only at first try first try
today
I I could have done better but you know
I was I it was I
had to kind of get into the groove first
into the Groot into the groove
yes okay
so thank you
it's on your bonus
that's one percent of your bonus
50 US dollars is one percent of your
bonus what does that mean how much is
how much was your bonus
uh um
five pounds
[Music]
five thousand
that's that's a [\h__\h] nice bow that's
you
wow
what did you do what did you do
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
looking for the top Direction
[Music]
a successful quarter noise
thanks for the red super chat I remember
watching the debuts and seeing some
orange bird talk about how much you love
their videos she didn't impress me that
much A lot when I saw she had Tales of
as a favorite game series why not I
thought one year later here I am and
here you are Tails fans together yes
yes I'm so glad that some of uh us
shared the same interests um
I played this myself yesterday and had
been down on the series for a while I
didn't like the direction it was going
in it feels good to love a tears off
game again thank you so much Kiana oh
I mean the the previous games you didn't
like the direction it was going to
that confuses me because
[Music]
I don't know they always seemed very uh
stable in what they were doing was like
I mean in a good way it was always the
same you know what I mean
but I mean I don't know I don't know
what you mean because Tales of bizaria
was okay A bit darker than the others
but is that really what bothered you
[Music]
um
predictable it's hysteria apparently
yeah a lot of people didn't like it
but I was so excited to see that Tales
of arise
has been uh selling
miles better than any other tails off
game apparently
much much better
right
I I saw I saw the sales numbers
that's so cool I'm so glad that means
that there will be more Tales of games
and they'll continue improving their
games like this I will see this as a
sign
the reviews have been great too
apparently yeah
I'm glad so I'm really excited to play
more of it and see why why it has so
such good reviews I want to play more of
it oh uh have a sad uh
notice for you guys
it really pisses me off but it is what
it is
it's really disappointing
the PS5
and as I told you a while ago who
arrived in my country is the customs and
I was informed about that by my
management
and I don't know how long it has already
been there at that point but
the moment I messaged them per email to
give them what they needed
or I give them information
in German
they told me that the deadline
was like about a week later for like uh
keeping the PS5 there
so I was like okay and I sent them some
information first and then they were
like okay but now we need this and this
and I immediately reacted but I needed
my Management's help to give them what
they wanted and then it was like I was
like the middleman I constantly was like
giving information to management and I'm
giving information to the customs
[Music]
and uh
I gave them like an invoice
from like from my from from cover
but like it was so weird they made it so
complicated they made it so complicated
uh the the Customs because it was
declared as a gift to which it is it is
a gift but they made it so [\h__\h]
complicated and
on Friday
they sent me another email
asking for saying something I don't even
it was so confusing they asked for
something again and they were like yo
but remember the deadline is on the 13th
of September which was yesterday and I
was like okay
and I wrote immediately and I wrote
Emily to management and told them Yo
deadline coming up this is the what I
got from the customs but unfortunately
nothing happened after that
it has not been handled and uh the PS5
has been
sent back to Japan
which is
so
unnecessary and unfortunate
laughs
oh my God so why is it so complicated so
I don't think that it will arrive
anytime soon because first how long
would it take I don't know like
I don't know how fast they sent it back
in these cases do they use Express in
order to send it back or do they just
send it back normally with a [\h__\h]
ship that will take a month or so
go pick it up later then do you
understand what I just said
do you understand what I just said they
sent it back and I was not able to
receive it
picking it up was not an option
yeah that's gonna be a well-traveled PS5
yeah so it's going back to Japan and
then
when I have to wait a while until they
actually send it to me again
then it will arrive again at some point
and then it will have to go for Customs
again
was it because it was a PS5 I don't
think it was specifically because of
that but it was just because it was I
think like because of things like
um
you know
I'm not sure like probably stuff like
who pays the Customs how much will be
the Customs if it's a gift blah blah
blah because the item has a high value
um
and yeah apparently it wasn't declared
the way they wanted it to be declared or
the invoice
was like
it didn't it it it didn't Clearly say
what they wanted it to say I suppose
because of translation stuff
um
[Music]
I saw I don't know man I wanted to play
this with the five that's the reason why
they sent me the
beat up in the first place
and I would love to play it with the PS5
now I'm wondering if I should take my
and I give myself more time and not play
it two times per week so that I have
more time and maybe maybe we'll get the
PS5 somewhere in between
foreign
[Music]
I know a second
is
[Music]
at all
foreign
[Music]
I I originally I was thinking
um that if the PS5 arrives like it
should have arrived this week you know
so I was like even if the the
transferring of the save files doesn't
work I can still I'm still not very
behind on it so I can still like play
privately
um and to catch up
but now it's yeah I'm gonna take another
long long time but officially apparently
generally generally you can transfer
files from PS4 to PS5 save files however
I don't know some someone told me that
they plan to implement the transferring
of files in Winter which makes me think
that it is genuinely possible but not
for Tales of arise currently and they
are implementing that in Winter for
whatever reason
I don't know I don't know if it's
already really possible I'm not sure
but for now we'll just I don't know I
can't wait forever I'm gonna play it on
PS4
I'm gonna continue playing it I could I
I know I could play it on PC too but and
people even say my PC would uh have even
better performance but I honestly don't
think so
I think if I would stream at the same
time then we're gonna have issues like
with Neo automata for example again
I think PS4 would be more stable in
those terms
yeah I think if I weren't too stream
then my PC might be better for it but
if you think about the fact that I'm
also streaming it
it runs great on PC now but anyway we're
starting with PS4 and it's fine for me
it's fine it looks great on PS4 too so
what the hell
it's all right yeah and if I if I play
PC and the PS5 is eventually gonna
arrive then I won't be able to transfer
that's for sure that's for sure you know
[Music]
we won't be able to see the differential
stream anyway yeah that's um
that's something I wonder too if I
switch from PS4 and PS5 is the
difference really going to be that
obvious to you guys
so anyway anyway it is it is extremely
unfortunate and stupid but we will
I'm not even eating
it would mean I would have to stream in
4k which I'm probably not gonna be able
to handle with my internet connection
[Music]
um
I think I need to go on an island
meeting and I have to put the to put the
I have to put the bread in the oven
[Music]
hmm
yeah the hype of using the PS5 well you
know what
because this was such an unfortunate
[Music]
um
happening
maybe Bandai Namco
will will be motivated to sponsor me for
another game once I have the business
five and then actually make me use the
PS5
maybe that will be a good reason for
them to sponsor me again
couldn't we they gifted it to me and I
couldn't even use it for their
sponsorship so
they they would want to make me use
their gift right
because like what the hell otherwise it
would be wasteful
blue protocol wait blue protocol is PC
though
as far as I know
I would love to play Blue protocol
though
um
oh
[Music]
um
all right guys I'll take one more bite
from my yogurt and then I'll go to an
idol meeting
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
it's already uh escaped
YouTube
okay
you guys have to remind me in eight to
nine minutes
to get my bread
[Music]
thank you for two pinkies
we've waited for what feels like she
owns
cheers
[Music]
what is that
supposed to
mean
[Music]
[Laughter]
and for the tales of hoodle game haven't
we and written well written well it's
finally here I'm ecstatic to see you
embark
you could you could have made a joke out
of bark as well
and book I was gonna say Embark like a
dog but
you said in book on this owl New Journey
and couldn't be more proud of our tales
and faster whenever I read your
sentences a lot of it doesn't really
register in my brain because I think
about your puns
[Music]
your love for this Series has inspired
and picked the interests of many to join
alfan and his friends in their journey
to return to the out return the owls to
the force yes because because that is
the main quest
that must be the main quest and the main
goal in the game to bring the owls to
the forest there's nothing no bigger
purpose in this game
you are a runner
collect owl Rena gonna you already know
collect out of widow's bodies
trying too hard
you wouldn't die
oh my God I should put you into the
usual room for these shitty puns
incredible
oh my God
not even gonna read that yellow one
forever
we don't have time for this today
logical chicken dance
[Music]
rice
I love that
thank you soon foreign
[Music]
foreign
s today
thank you for being you and I will
always support utensil I look forward to
the stream thank you for supporting me
and congratulations on your stocks
nice nice please do not throw them all
out on me
please make good use of them but I'm
sure you know what you're doing
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
No Game No Life
Captain Thunderbolts
[Music]
I think I need to sneeze
no I think it's gone
[Music]
um
no no it's gone thank you for the pinky
thank you for the support
thank you so much
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
let's go
oh man I was so excited to play Tales of
her eyes but I was also nervous because
you know I've been telling you guys for
a long time that I really love tails off
games
and um
I don't know also because it's a
sponsorship I just wanted to be good at
the game and so far it's only even two
hours gameplay so I couldn't have [\h__\h]
up that much yet
but I definitely felt some pressure
because I wanted to impress you guys
[Music]
I don't like myself doing my best
yes how could I mean
[Music]
a promo code oh well it's already pretty
late for me to read your Super Chat and
I don't know if you're even gonna hear
this but yeah uh to acknowledge my
participation you can let Bandai namkosa
know about that you bought it because of
me because uh if if you if you use the
link in the description of the tale of
arise stream it's right there
Ezekiel kfb attorney thank you for the
pinky hands up if you want to give
Shield a hug
no no
[Music]
I think I'll pass
I'll give Keisha a hug no no this is
because xion is an electric
you guys don't realize huh break time oh
everyone rides at the same time holy
[\h__\h]
yeah give it a bit more time
shift happens I like your name thank you
you use my link thank you Elvis mixed
with a pinky oh my God where can I buy a
mask like this oh
ah unfortunately you super chatted to me
and not to Bandai so I can't help you
with that
but I wouldn't recommend that mask looks
like it's really hard to eat and breathe
in it Jay and Henry Danger
[Music]
the fire
dominique.com
[Music]
foreign
I'll just put it out of the oven we'll
eat it in maybe an hour
mm-hmm
[Music]
I brought tank is with me again maybe
he keeps on running into me
[Music]
foreign
Island
[Music]
foreign
don't fall asleep guys don't we have so
much to read I need some I need some
company
sorry
stop stop being weird okay
[Music]
oh wait I have to put on the something
this long ass stream
[Music]
yep
la la
are you awake are you all awake
[Music]
mm-hmm
okay
[Music]
he hypnotized by frog Kiana I want to
upload a video where it's just a
close-up of rock yada spinning down
there
I want to just upload it on YouTube
[Music]
she deserves it
so cute
I don't know what it is I think it's the
the pose and the expression
it's just perfect makes you love her so
much
yeah I saw that she uploaded it yeah
yeah
I wonder if she saw the the credits
that I wrote
so there's um I don't know if you guys
saw my credit section
for the anniversary
um stream on Amelia's Channel
I wanted to you know I thought that it
would be too too General too generic to
just write
my fans my Samplers but everyone I just
wanted it to be a bit more personal
so I wrote a free specific artists
who have supported me for a long time
especially since the beginning
especially you not run
whereas there at a time
where I really need it
like I felt like it just sounds weird
but
um yuna's fan arts back in the day
she was like
um one of the few people who kept on
drawing me and I used her eyes for a lot
of things a lot of thumbnails and all
that so
um yeah it was it was uh it felt like
you know
you felt like she cared for me and um
and later on you're not even kind of
stopped
but that's okay but Mama lonely uh
really
draw me a lot and Takoma also
continuously is a a big contributor of a
lot of things my loading screen
and and generally the the chicken
I love those chickens they're literally
the best chickens
so so yeah
[Music]
um yeah I thought I thought that was
free
um probably why why I love all the fan
artists I felt like
they if I were to thank specific artists
and could only name a few of them I
would I would name them
um yeah
and for December is I think you guys
know why I put those specific senpais
on my list
I think you guys know
I don't think I have to even explain
that
I love I love all my senpais
um but those have
uh and a connection with me and they
they helped me or they became closer
friends with me or they were my
inspiration to join or they helped me
when I was really down and all that so
that's why I chose those specific people
I know
cancer statistics
[Music]
foreign
I know
members who I named there even saw it
they probably didn't but
it was just something I wanted to do
[Music]
yeah so continuing
Mr can't speak Spanish
and
um
thank you for two minutes of a chance
[Music]
hello this is my first super chat but
I've been lurking since your debut
watching you all throughout these months
is something that I'll translate Forever
at least out all the things that I love
about you but I just it just wouldn't
hint thank you for being such an
inspiration and for igniting my passion
for drawing I shall continue supporting
you and keep trying my best to make fan
arts also I can't believe it's already
been a year here's to many more fun
years ahead I love you thank you
for the sweet words
thank you for staying around
ever since the day being wow I
appreciate that very much I'm glad
you're still here please continue being
here thank you images
thank you I hope I can give you more joy
in my streams in the future as well my
name is sarodin thank you for the red
super chat
you've given me so much this year Kiana
and now I've met someone in this
community who makes me feel truly
special
it's just a confession
her YouTube name is Randall
and and though our future together is
uncertain we know that right now we are
happy
whoa
thank you for bringing us together well
[Music]
um should I open should I open a dating
service
foreign
[Music]
I'm happy for you
I guess you have to name your child
after me
thank you
good luck don't mess it up
Herbert West thank you for the pinky
so yeah this is our kid chicken oh [\h__\h]
I'll [\h__\h] you up mate
making supposed to be Kiana
is a lovely name yes it isn't it's a
normal name
oh there she is in the chat sending
hearts to him oh stop stop floating in
me
stop
I'm gonna blow you up
I'm gonna blow you up both of you
unbelievable
get yourself a freaking room
get a room
get a room for God's sake
[Music]
don't forget about me
oh
don't forget about me you you love me
too don't talk
I love you Tango are you sure do you
love me more than him
do you love me more than you love me
[Music]
love it but do you love more me or him
I mean you probably didn't even say I
love you yet to him then did you that
would be a bit early maybe
[Music]
I'm waiting for the answer
I'm waiting
[Music]
I love both of you
oh my God
she didn't say
[Music]
what
play unravel
Alexa
[Music]
okay enough of this
Room
everybody wins thanks for the pinky hey
girl you and Kelly were at Calgary con
we're people nice to you too from when I
saw YouTube where two had the longest
line so people were excited oh
really yeah they were nice to us of
course they were
of course
uh yeah it was we talked a little bit
about the convention during the stream
thing
thank you
thank you I wonder wait does this imply
that you were actually there too
or did you just see pictures of the line
were you there too
if yes and I hope you enjoyed the panel
it just you know I just feel like really
regretful that those panels were so
short 45 minutes
I don't know we could only answer like
10 questions then also
well I was their attention wow really
really cool
I think um
the the one that I did with inodo I was
I was killing it on that one I was so
funny in that one
um
[Music]
that was like on a freaking roll on that
one holy [\h__\h]
was it manicon oh
they should have let people in the room
early instead of counting that against
them yeah yeah yeah I guess they had a
reason for not being able to do that I
was uh we love your sign that was
written again
oh thanks say thanks say thanks thanks
sorry
I wanna go visit Canada I didn't know
that Canada has like uh they they
explained to us that a Calgary is kind
of the Texas of of Canada
I didn't even imagine that Canada had a
place like that who
I was quite surprised to hear that
I I didn't I didn't think of Canada that
way
my image of Canada is very different
all the Cowboys lived there
Canadian Cowboys
what about cowgirls do they live there
too
foreign
history lesson a lot of Texans moved to
Alberta for the oil sands industry
brought a lot of cowboy culture with
them wow
no no no I know that Canada is freaking
big and diverse I mean I know that you
know they have like places where they
all speak French there so I'm aware of
that but I just didn't think they would
have like a place like Texas there
well well I really want to visit Canada
at some point
yeah kill back
that's so cool
that is so cool
and I know that they also uh have
accepted a lot of handmaids
so Canada is dope
Canada is really
based
[Music]
oh crap
whatever whatever
[Music]
based Canada
and means tail isn't real are you sure
are you sure about that it could be it
could be real that's the terrifying
thing lucky for the top language and
Randall oh dear
the girlfriend
I second what saradin said thanks to you
I actually met him and all my kfp family
kfb and Sarah they've helped me when
nobody else has tried thank you thank
you so much for being here wouldn't have
found them without you this is too tated
to taste for my taste
I hope you're happy to find
the stuff
don't miss a stand please understand me
I'm happy for you
to send Thomas thank you soon
rennel dankerson
I am a dankerson where I find the
Doncaster and Dell stuff thank you for
the red super chat
hi Kevin yesterday I celebrated my
birthday in the usual room my my one mom
sentence is almost over as well can I
request you to Bonk me and chat as a
birthday gift to celebrate both
occasions
as hot wings thanks hot wings how am I
supposed to block you I'm supposed to
hit my microphone
well how should I Bonk you
how do I do that
a little bit
[Music]
now don't comment about my body okay
don't say anything okay
I have I have
I have self-confidence issues okay
don't
don't talk about it
I I'm already struggling with my body
okay
so
um
[Music]
I bumped you
there you go
thank you delsa and happy belated
wow
[Music]
hope you had a lovely birthday
and soon you'll get out of the usual
room apparently don't don't immediately
go back there okay behave
was that a bunk or a slight breeze what
what your body is perfection true
you seem to be half the person used to
be sharp I told you not to talk about it
makes me feel anxious
black friction
avenge
set nuts
my name is
foreign
[Music]
food
but I'm glad that you left Midway
through because that means you you
missed the last part which was
absolutely horrible yeah nothing that
what people want to see I'm surprised
that they're still like Koreans watching
in a Super Chat reading where I just
read down simple chats mostly in English
I'm surprised
Japanese people too I think there's some
of them at least
[Music]
and thank you
thank you thank you
foreign
[Music]
I need to change the music I'm like sick
of this already
oh no get him
[Music]
um
yes
[Music]
oh yes
foreign
[Music]
yes this is the good stuff oh yeah
cycle
[Music]
country bird country bird
foreign
[Music]
catch the celebration tomorrow please
don't fire me so here's my early
congrats happy one year anniversary
Dental I'm happy to be a kfp and hope
you finish this game and the time you
wish to finish it I did not but thank
you anyway and I hope you watched the
archive of my celebration stream because
it was pretty damn dope
it was pretty pretty damn good but you
guys know that is that a joke is that a
mink
he did say uh he didn't write a funny
Super Chat
that stream was lit right
it was a damn good stream
I I I'm glad you guys
liked it okay I wanted it to be special
so thank you Emily
I left as bankerson
right here right here
thank you thank you
black Virginia
[Music]
and skipping the flash shots noise
you charge fast by holding left bumper
and pulling the joy come back
what
[Music]
Why did no one tell me that earlier
holding a left bumper and pulling joycon
the last bump bumper
oh well oh well hey thank you for trying
to help
thank you
uh Jackson FB language
thank you for the pinky for two pinkies
uh for charging a bow I found for
changing the sword
ah
oh I didn't know that there were motion
controls on that too like in that way ah
yeah
[Music]
happy anniversary one year complete I
used to dislike jrpg's before you and
now I'm having the absolute best time
ever with everyone's thanks to you oh
uncle
[Music]
it's the small things that add on to one
year of fun Sweat and Tears together
with your kfp one year I've been happy
to spend watching your streams and
looking forward to another and even
crazier here your radiant smile improved
things for many including me much love
and thank you for everything from a kfp
beat thank you
[Music]
thanks Dr RPGs and especially tales of
loraz
[Music]
mission accomplished successfully yes
yes good choice
it is a great game apparently so I hope
you're enjoying it and maybe afterwards
you play some more Tales of games
[Music]
wow thank you for the red super chat oh
wow happy early anniversary to my
favorite streamer thank you wanted to
stop lurking for a bit to say congrats
and that I love your work gonna have to
hit the archive though since my little
sister is visiting from out of the state
please don't find me gotta be a good
host and brother too down
for coming by and giving me a happy uh
early early
congratulations thank you for thinking
of me already a reply to that one I
think on stream thank you
Ace free exoding links and looking for
the top 10 questions
this is a random the boss fight fish
1000 danke schoenfree script Danke
Schoen LinkedIn
[Music]
moons
recipe
[Music]
yeah
was going to save my first account to
you for the anniversary stream but why
not show my support now thank you you
can do it thank you stay calm and you
wreck him just like you take care of him
this loses just a buffer version with
less tongue honestly
in some way
despite with demise
was probably
in some way easier
than girl
but I was just not sure like the the
freaking sword charging was just so
triggering
and yeah
yeah
I was panicking
[Music]
if I had the amount of healing items at
that point already
I might have uh
I might have had a
chance but I was already a freaking
wreck
I was already
[\h__\h] mess mentally
so
I don't know
yeah why is he so weak he only has two
phases that's honestly like a little bit
disappointing actually
so weak
I was one hit away the second time oh oh
[\h__\h] sake man yeah cause he was down
on the ground right
if you do that final blow
[Music]
if it hits it doesn't actually kill him
oh my God
I wish I could have finished it the
first time you guys when I re-upload the
archive which I think I'll do after this
stream can you can you please give it
like a view because I know a lot of you
guys already watched it live but it's
gonna be so sad when
it's gonna be the least watched video on
my channel
[Music]
this is playing in the background or
something
it will be so sad otherwise
thank you thank you
thank you yeah
it's a bit weird though because it
basically basically comes out after this
stream which where I finished the game
but the order I'll I'll fix the order in
the playlist
[Music]
you can do it thank you for the red
Football chat I was not able to do it on
that day but hey we did it today and
yeah I think if it weren't for the time
pressure I would have totally killed him
and would have totally done it
oh so unfortunate thank you though for
believing in me
thank you
[Music]
the Kevin Danke Schoen lingles long
Danke Schoen chisels the gondra Danke
Schoen I don't know
for the two pinkies Skyward Sword is
over
so yeah
[Music]
um
that was so embarrassing
that was so embarrassing I don't want to
think about it anymore it's a beautiful
thumbnail
that art makes it so gorgeous
[Music]
okay so there's probably gonna be a lot
of ribs I suppose so I gotta read a lot
oh yeah let me already take a cough drop
cocoa
foreign
[Music]
wait let me tell you how many I have
left
so all of these that's uh
250 52 Plus
[Music]
oh God
foreign
[Music]
oh God
Plus 649.
[Music]
[Laughter]
I mean
I would love to offer you guys
to just read
Reds and pinks names
and messages only and then not even the
names of the others but I feel like I
don't know it's just like
my principle
and I feel like some of you guys will be
disappointed
we can't read them
or
then I mean we would be done much faster
but not even even then probably not but
um
[Music]
yeah but even if they send them
expecting to be read and I think they
know at least that I won't be reading
their messages
yeah but yeah I I will read them
like only their name but oh well
yeah a few of you guys say you don't
mind but
I can't say for sure for the others so
it's like a thousand super chats
let me see how many I read until now
maybe that motivates me a little bit
let me seeing
I read
until now
[Music]
um
wow but well there were way less Reds
and pinks
I suppose
all right almost 500. Auto
[Music]
now I'm definitely save some for
tomorrow
definitely I'm not planning on finishing
it all today
[Music]
but I'm like
like calmly so I can actually
take all of these messages to Heart
of course I want to do it
but my throat is probably gonna die so
let's go take it monkey
monkey thank you for the rainbow
no no not a rainbow but two pinks two
yellows
[Music]
yeah what can I say it's been an
absolute pleasure watching you grow from
a new rookie member to the successful
same body you are today you're truly a
strong and beautiful person
and by that I mean your mind you're so
old what about my body
hey
it hasn't been the smoothest right here
Dem cursed the bamboozling of Susan and
other hardships yeah
[Music]
but you've eventually braved them all
and came out even stronger you always
show so much
you only show so much care for others
beating your viewers or co-workers
thank you
thank you jackets monkey
should I read the
yellows too because they I guess kind of
Belong Together
so I'm glad I found you on kfb a year
ago I've said this before but no matter
the type of stream no matter how it
begins or ends it always brings me joy I
always have fun watching it's almost
like I've been in a dream oh
a pleasant dream that I hope will never
end just know that as long as you choose
to continue to steer this boat called
kfp I'll always be reviewing kfp
[Music]
there's gonna be a lot of these kind of
wholesome messages
[Music]
don't cry
it's been a tough year
a very tough year
thank you for your support for all of it
congratulations on your first
anniversary there are
2.5
million more years left right
how do you come to that number well it's
actually
2.499999 in this super chat but I
rounded it up
um
that's not eternity there are no years
left because there's
eternity left you can't put a number on
that
but I hope you can stay as long as as
you can I hope you will stay as long as
you can
eternity plus one
thank you I'm glad I made it to the
mainstream welcome welcome
thank you for the pinky happy one year
of Kiana must be honest I wasn't able to
watch your Debbie alive it was at 6am
there was no chance I was a week earlier
than 10 am a year ago
no problem I understand completely but I
can't imagine this past year without
your streams thank you for being amazing
plus one percent what
what does that mean thank you
I think it's so defined to not watch the
stream live as long as you're still
there
I'm really glad I think a lot of the the
viewers from nowadays haven't even seen
the Debbie stream unless they watched
their anniversary but
yeah I think a lot of people just bevel
never felt like catching up on that and
that's okay because my stream was my my
debut stream really wasn't it was it was
really decent but it was nothing like
too special that blows people away
[Music]
thank you thank you
thank you guys thank you for watching
the video
how do you think
[Music]
if you watch it though you really I
think you will see a difference in how
how I changed not only you know
equipment wise and all that but just a
difference in confidence and all that
I'm happy and so positive about your
debut there's nothing to not be positive
about
except for the microphone
nothing
I also think
that the amount of Japanese that I spoke
in that stream was appropriate
I I don't
um I think back then I was very
um influenced by a lot of the hate that
I received but I think that's all
[\h__\h]
yeah
there's to be honest there's girls who
speak more Japanese like not
non-japanese
not in whole life Japan members that
speak even more Japanese in their
streams than me
so I think back then the criticism that
I got for that is
stupid
yeah
um and I told him the diamond ones but
that's mostly because I haven't seen
um that many Japanese people in the chat
anymore
but I've seen some new ones popping up
every now and then so
um I hope that they enjoy my streams and
I want to include them in the fun
because I think
that just by speaking a few Japanese
sentences in between it hurts no one it
only benefits people so
why not do that
I just don't understand how there's some
people who like so buttered from that it
just makes no sense to me
especially in my debut I did it at that
amount so that the people because I knew
that would be a [\h__\h] ton of Japanese
people watching
I knew that
that's why I spoke so much Japanese so
that everyone understands
[Music]
I don't know how I don't know how that
was so scandalous
ah
oh man
[Music]
I think it was just yeah the saltiness
of people
it's just them being salty I think
um
yeah
it's no sense anyway uh Kathy thank you
for the red super chat what a great
first year your wonderful entertaining
at your inspiration always pushing
forward innovating and finding new ways
to bring out the best in yourself and
everyone around you I'm truly grateful
to have joined such a great Community
can't wait for you too yay it has
already started so no need to wait
thank you I would love to be a bit more
Innovative though I want to
have the energy and the power to do more
but I have to say
um
currently
I am
very burned out
the past few days and weeks have taken a
toll on me
and I've reached my absolute limits
and I um I tried to not show it
on stream
[Music]
uh but I was
not feeling well able to neighbor today
or yesterday or the day before
and I've been trying to take a break but
I can't for now this week no next week
difficult as well
maybe the week after but then even then
only for like three days there's there's
like always something going on so uh and
even even if I take a few days off I
don't have anyone really to go with me
and I don't want to go alone I need
someone to be with me
yeah rmt actually started besides her
job she started to go to university
[Music]
um so she has no time at all
I stay occasional I want to go to the
beach
I wanna go somewhere where I can swim
I'm just here to the sound of nature
[Music]
yeah but I think about some way I'm
probably gonna just
invite my best friend
uh to the vacation just probably gonna
um pay for her so just so that I have
someone to go with me
now because I can't go alone
I just realized that I don't have enough
RL friends
like RL close friends because I just
don't want to go with some random
obviously
[Music]
she's busy too but she can probably make
it work somehow
so I'll bring her
with me
take jenma I would if I could but she's
far away she's in Japan
the Glorious Nippon land
if only there was a whole life member in
Europe what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I need yeah
the EU pain is real yeah
nipple
yeah
stop it
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
come on
foreign
[Music]
thank you for the pinky this is a pretty
emotional for me but seriously I'm happy
to have been here from the start seeing
you grow into such an entertaining
streamer has been a great experience
happy I was able to find someone who can
brighten up my day like you do honestly
I I I I wonder how it is for you guys
who've been here from the start you must
um
like after after following the growth
you must feel very proud
crap Maybe
that you've been here from the start and
and and followed how how I've developed
hey thank you
oh thank you
I will try to improve even more so that
in in another year later you can be like
yeah School I've been here since two
years ago I'm so proud of you you did
you you improved yourself again
I hope so but I I don't know like I
can't promise
[Music]
thank you
any updates on the membership badges no
nope but maybe we'll talk about it in
the next members stream
which I by the way I think I have to
move that one from Sunday to Saturday
because uh
I have something important uh with my
mother on the weekend
[Music]
and dinner
Oh Derek
why is it
this is does this number have a meaning
365.25 dollars
[Music]
is there a meaning behind that
thank you
for the red oh that's
[Music]
a
year oh yeah it makes sense
aha
oh thank you for that
[Music]
thank you love wow
nice to see you thank you very much
a plus that one fork could act up to the
leap year oh my God
he didn't he did he oh no he didn't what
he loves his numbers doesn't he
oh my God
[Music]
I am
thank you
[Music]
Santa amaris thank you for the rest of
the chat happy one year anniversary
thank you all the love for you thank you
for all the hard work every day for more
time and fun okay if we together yeah
yes have more fun in the future thank
you so let's keep playing thank you for
the right simple chat wow why does it
say no
[Music]
wait there was a ah because I was like
yo the stream hasn't even started what
are you guys doing
stop super telling and he was like no
thank you soda you're like a rebellious
teenager
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
you know
pascara
[Music]
oh thank you thank you
soon
for the pinky thank you my girlfriend
recommended home left to me oh
just a week I got crazy about you I saw
your Clips every day and that made her
so jealous just kidding
it's happy to have you in my life I will
wait for Cafe till death glory to
caffeine
what a perfect example of an employee
thank you I love your attitude thank you
thank you
she's a keeper yeah I think she is
Santa amaris thank you for the pinky
what is Chill is it poof
um no
[Music]
thank you for two pinkies I didn't know
yet about YouTubers till fairly recently
so this will be the first time I
witnessed your debut in life I was I was
but a regular person until suddenly
pentifying
as chickens
[Music]
[Applause]
you're funny about investigation I
conclude that the whole talk
drawing stream waiting for inner
combination
must have must have sparked specs
[Music]
this transformation
that was a that was a good couple of
days wasn't it thank you for the great
content and congratulations on your
anniversary he has no kisses for me oh I
think it's too late
so like I think I already gave you
kisses thank you
I'm glad you have identified as a
chicken
that is the right way to go you have
found
Enlightenment or something like that
welcome welcome to kfp
[Music]
and Mia uh thank you for the rest of the
chat
one of the six oh it sounds
[Music]
awesome
who's that no it's an incorrect order
okay I just passed since the Phoenix
arose From the Ashes you had to go for
hell to be where you are now which is
ironic because you know I go to the
underworld and all that
for the strength of being a part-time
Romeo you have fun and worked hard for
everything and everyone
the bamboozles and other difficulties
you never lost sight of your goals in
the beginning you were a bit of an
insecure Phoenix but you managed to show
us that there is a lot of strength
inside of you and that is one of many
other reasons what keeps me here
yes and also because of the kfb contract
I admire that strength and the love you
put in every day for a year non-stop you
have been delivering happiness in front
of your viewers your creativity on
streams and the fact that you show as
something new every day makes it never
boring you've come so far and you've
already accomplished many of your goals
since your first debut we are very
grateful that you're part of our life
definitely something big would be
missing here without you
we love it will always be there for you
thank you thank you
[Music]
very very sweet of you
it's been a very busy year and I've done
my best
thank you for staying profile
very very happy that you're here
[Music]
Vanguard
hey lazy egg thanks for the pinky
intention one year anniversary congrats
thank you for your efforts and coloring
Our Lives although there were many
frustrations and pressure you still have
done an excellent job I hope you can
continue to be happy you are the best
streamer in my heart
thank you thank you thank you I'm glad I
was able to give you some happiness with
my streams thank you
thank you
[Music]
thank you for always staying true to
yourself thank you for putting so much
work into giving your viewers a great
experience thank you for being so honest
it shows that you really respect and
care about your fans and that is a rare
and precious quality
I do I do
when I start watching last word you
change all the time and lose touch with
what made you special but you didn't
change you just leveled up your jokes
are funnier your karaoke's are better
you're more cool and confident but
you're still the same potential
thank you
I would I would personally
[Music]
um that want to change evil of course
because you guys like me for a reason
but I guess in this one year I only
changed slightly in a positive way so
hey
yeah
thank you changed for the better I'm
gonna sound in such a huge change it's
just like getting used to it
not like I'm a completely different
person right
foreign
yeah
she just got better thinking growth now
you seem happy or overall
am I happier than one year ago
I mean just the fact that I am with my
cats now
makes me happier I think
I think generally yes if I wasn't
[\h__\h] burned out right now
if it wasn't for that I would probably
be more happy
so we'll fix that soon
well I I'll I'll be back to
normal
[Music]
hopefully soon
I will try
um
thank you for coming back
to congratulate me on one year wow one
year ago a phoenix descended upon us
from the adventures we shared from the
bloody battlefields to the stages of
gold it doesn't even say that he's
retired
from hearts that fell to tears of Sorrow
doesn't mean you work for me again
and to the new discoveries the kfb will
stand strong to the days of Glory
forever
[Music]
good
thank you
and God is so sweet I love your speeches
I'm glad to hear one again
thank you thank you
I wonder if you still watch my streams
every now and then
if yes thank you if not then I wish you
the best of luck with whatever you're
doing on the side
thank you for thinking of me on my
anniversary
means a lot to me
Mr casbix thank you for two pinkies wow
cast from One Yoga would be surprised to
find out that it was the cute newly
debuted Phoenix girl who would be the
one to help him finally work for his
social anxieties helping him become a
member of an awesome lovely Community
you're an incredibly good person Kiara I
love genuinely meant every praise I've
ever given yell keeping your amazing and
glorious and extremely fabulous self
haha fabulous
[Music]
I'm thinking of the high school music
song
thanks for being such a positive factor
in my life
[Music]
and it really really cheers me up so
thank you so much for everything
yeah thank you for the pinkies wow and
that will another pinky
I also wanted to tell you that the exact
moment you became my Oshi was the
penguin slide racing Mario 64. I was
laughing so hard because I hate that
stage
hit the one inside
I mean when you hate it I mean it was
not fun I remember it being fun maybe my
traumas maybe my drama is changing my
perception
I mean I mean it was hard and I remember
struggling with it a little bit yeah
yeah I definitely struggled
[Music]
didn't pretty sure you didn't have as
much fun at the time maybe I didn't
maybe I didn't
go watch and you'll see what I mean
Kiana you hated it
hey it's in Super Mario 64. no way
[Music]
that's so long ago
Casino
[Music]
cruise
I only think of happy moments
it's a traumatic experience man
um
shout out to my kfb family who mostly
can't Super Chat my son's Kane nut and
P1 to pay for m
you guys uh have assigned the family
roles to yourselves
my daughter answer me and oh my God wait
this is Randall oh my [\h__\h] god
[Music]
and her husband darf their child asked
you though my grandchildren Sunday and
Sunday and my husband said Rodin
I'm confused is this oldest role-playing
or is the road in the thing that you
have with sir Rodin actually real and
the other things are
uh just made up
we've had this family for several months
oh my God a preach out family ah let's
try seeing you guys in the pre-chat a
lot
oh
[Music]
this is what we do in pre-chat okay
that will be closed from now on
understandable
[Music]
can't do that I can't I can do that
totally I'm the owner of this channel
[Music]
I
am
good is that
[Music]
foreign
open
due to popular demands
don't tear apart my family
aren't you choose the car
I guess you really want people to drive
you don't ya
[Music]
thank you cocoon for the rest of the
chats
Kiana my beloved if one of your hands
passed and you have grown so much you
command an army of chickens a World's
dominating fast food chain and you
invented not a cult you didn't give up
and look where you are you absolute
content machine I'm so proud of you your
voice character endurance art and love
everything about you
you are the most beautiful entertaining
cute Phoenix in the world best best boss
best girl you are Eternal you'll be my
own suit forever I wish you the best for
the future and much happiness I'll never
forget I'll never forget you I promise
you are my idol and you changed my life
for the better you make me smile every
single day for that you have my eternal
thanks my deepest respect to you let's
go and play even higher your potentials
endless
[Music]
kind of you thank you
wow I'm glad that my streams and my
existence brings you so much happiness
thank you
I hope it never stops
um
consider the fact that I have nowhere to
flirt with okay
[Music]
would definitely flirt with me I love
Nancy
I will marry anything
oh but wait does that even mean anything
when she has a million husbands but that
will be her only wife now she probably
also has a bunch of wives doesn't she
anyway I'll be the most special one out
she will love me the most so that's okay
Edward hi
Julia of londor thank you for the
rainbow
think oh yeah it is thank you
okay happy first anniversary thank you
my first Super Chat sorry for being a
look on Twitter and YouTube but I do
watch all your streams I watch your
debut with no expectations and although
I already liked you back then it wasn't
until the legendary Lord of the Rings
went to lungs where I finally warmed up
to you that is so interesting you're not
the first one to say that then that's so
weird but I love it thank you that's
when I knew you were the one why
the one I could clearly call my Aussie
your passion sincerity openness and love
for fans that what drew me to you
because you've been keeping it real when
it comes to giving advice and spreading
positivity to everyone around you I just
want to say how freaking proud I am and
how much you've grown since September if
debuted I think you would have bullied
her no you worked hard to be who you are
now and that's why I can't be believed
so much and how much you believe but
what
that's what KFC believes so much in how
much you believe they believe in what I
believe is that what you're saying
that's an interesting sentence
you've always punched through and just
kept fighting for years being a phoenix
and a warrior aren't just mere titles
they're the reality anyways I'm really
excited for the future I always look
forward to you and play for us practice
and songs lovely Chiara
thank you that is so sweet
um
um no worries about being a lurker
you say you want all my streams and that
is
the best thing you can do
thank you thank you really I'm I'm
really really grateful for that please
please just oh my God thank you
thank you for your kindness
love you thank you you can you can come
out of the Shadows uh more often though
you wanna I want I want for you
winter hand thank you for the rest of
the chat I think think of this as a
payment for one full year of
entertainment best wishes for the future
of us thank you it was not necessary I
do this for free for you guys but
if it weren't for all of these um super
chats I couldn't do this job either so
even though it's for free you guys still
choose to support me not all of you
that's fine that's fine but the fact
that there are some people who do it
um supports my life and my career and my
whole streaming
um environment and all that so without
that I would probably probably have a
lot of struggles
so yeah
it's a
it's definitely
um
it plays a big role I want to say that
[Music]
um it doesn't matter whether you super
chat or not and that is 100 true
it doesn't matter the non-super chatting
audience plays a big role as well
so thank you to all of you all of you
thank you
[Music]
thank you for two pinkies
before this Irreplaceable past year with
the most amazing spicy and lovable funny
hard-working so cute Phoenix in existent
egg egg you're my idol who has preserved
through too many hardships and but
you've accomplished so many incredible
things I've said it before and I'll say
it again I was hooked cool ah
from your first Kiki and I'm glad I
witnessed your journey from the start
your treasured to this world and I don't
want to imagine it without you love your
Kiana always happy first anniversary
when I just realized to change your name
to who love gave me you really like who
don't ya
it feels like it's uh it's Destiny that
Tales of arise Came Upon Us with a with
a owl mascot
ah see this hoodle I don't have to look
for this hoodle is always with me thank
you
Volcan thank you for the red super chat
mate from the fake Australia can't
believe I went to my honesty for you
already time flies by fast when we are
all having fun happy first anniversary
Tanger here to navanya Yo thank you for
watching me for a full year and even
though I stream at mostly shitty times
for you you're still here oh thank you
for making an effort to watch me
thank you
feelings for the red super chat thank
you
five times right to the chat you crazy I
oh I knew it I knew you would go crazy
again
happy first ever a one year anniversary
I know everyone's sending their regards
so I'm gonna keep it short thank you I
just want to thank you to be our tento
and you helped me and probably a lot of
employees for our difficult times you
will always be our attention and we will
eventually all be in your stomach thank
you thank you we love you forever you
know I think
that is the
most
meaningful
statement and proof of love
that you can give me
to let me eat you
I mean it is
[Music]
isn't it or I mean yeah I'm not eating
all of you though you guys are being
eaten by other people personally as well
so
um foreign
[Music]
take me
that wasn't part of the contract oh yes
it was
one day closer to the bucket let's go
[Music]
expert on me I refuse to be eaten by
anyone potential
all right I guess uh I have to freeze
you or something so that you know I
can't eat all of you guys in one day
I will have to put you in the freezer
some of you guys
freezing Frozen chickens frozen chicken
frozen chicken
is that something we could do like
frozen yogurt no probably not um
frozen chicken
I'll think about it maybe we can make it
work make chicken into ice cream put
that on my menu ideas
chicken ice cream
ice cream
genius only tencho can think of these
genius ideas
[Music]
oh
thank you and
[Music]
um
wake her up
no wait wait
[Music]
read that for me foreign
foreign
[Music]
unbelievable
thank you is that a rainbow that come on
come on are you are you okay are you
good
[Music]
Kiana congratulations on your first
anniversary I can't believe a year has
passed already you accomplished and grew
so much in this time no matter what you
are always working hard and doing your
best even in tough situations you're
someone I really admire you got paid
online
uh you're someone I really admire for
that at the beginning I really didn't
watch your content ice you like how you
guys are so blunt about that
at least not until your 300K karaoke you
seem so happy singing and since then I
always try to not miss any of these
streams and I'm so glad I stayed around
you are an incredible person
I love you too Dr Mark
and plants too like like Phoenix like
chicken
you made a great community that loves it
and cares for you you made three amazing
original songs and always make your
content entertaining I'm so happy that
you got into whole life it wouldn't be
the same without you I know for a fact
that you inspire many people including
me your sincerity passion and amazing
talent are the reasons why you are my
Oshi you're always spreading positivity
to your friends and peers your streams
help me through really tough times you
changed my life in more ways that you
can imagine you deserve the best thank
you for everything
I'm not the best at words but I hope it
makes sense it does
good ways very good words thank you
thank you Mom
thank you I really appreciate you
your chickens always make me happy
I don't know why
but
I don't know oh every time I see
something from you
it just makes me happy it just makes me
feel like hey that person is still there
and still supporting me thank you
[Music]
carpet absurdom thank you for two red
superchators
congratulations on the one UK
anniversary before you I never watched
YouTubers engaged in live chats used
Twitter nor super chatted I I I uh uh I
can relate to that and I think a lot of
people in the chat can too all of that
changed after some crazy coincidence
that led me down this Rabbit Hole
eventually to you my Oshi well tell me
about it please know that you are
someone who has made the world a better
place I
was telling me about that and I will
always be supporting you from the
background have an absolutely amazing
day and we can't read the kfb look
forward to a new year review
I wanna hear you start
[Music]
but yeah um
I I wasn't I I wasn't a fan of people's
like live streams either before that so
I mean besides pecula but I would always
watch The Archives so and even besides
pickled I've watched no one so yeah it's
weird it's weird how we whole life made
so many people watch these type of
streams I wonder what it is that made so
many people watch us
[Music]
stop yawning
ah
it has yellow part nine will be up again
um I'll upload it after the stream bgm
change
all right we can do that uh how about
how about this oh
[Music]
best
this might be one of the best musics
in all of Zelda history the The Beatles
theme
[Music]
song
is so good
and we're hearing this in the Wind Waker
too
um
I just announced going to wake up too
[Music]
if only leaked
and again
[Music]
do do
thank you
[Music]
foreign
if you don't buy something I'm going to
send you to the usual room
what do you want
buy something
bye
now
[Music]
take your entire stock on Phoenixville
the frog is not on sale
I'll have one kid or
this is a fast food restaurant I mean
okay this is my office but
[Music]
neighbor is the Frog
I bought a membership okay that works
too
[Music]
employee discount of course
I mean actually you get three burgers so
if you have your employee uh
uh uh cards review
yeah obviously you need proof
and you will have a proof if you bought
the birthday merchandise
which is not available anymore but if
you got it then you will if you get the
full set you will get the the Kiara
designed
um employee card and with that you were
allowed to get free
supplier fast food
foreign
who didn't well
[Music]
maybe you can
draw one yourself
just don't tell anyone okay
just ah
what to me
fake one but just don't don't mention it
okay
don't make a big deal out of it
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
I made her love she liked my tweet she
replied to me as reasons why fans follow
you so I want to thank you for all the
peeps whose day you brightened or lives
you change because of your fan
interaction oh
foreign
[Music]
11 months ago Kitty as power goes uh oh
I remember became a phoenix and you had
the kindest words for her your singing
makes me smile your streams are fun but
your pure gentle heart makes it worth
supporting you thanks for being part of
my life I'll never forget you Vision was
fine okay
well thank you thank you yeah
um I'm glad that uh at least you know I
wish I could reply to every comment in
the chat and every I wish I could read
every Super chat's message and uh like
every tweet that is tweeted at me I wish
but I can't it's just too much but I
hope that with the ones that I pick up
every once in a while
um that you know it reaches the people
and I'm glad it has at least some effect
so
go ahead and unsub from Yango's Channel
it should only be subbed to me anyway
just kidding
I love how you keep streaming just to
thank everyone I have to
oh thanks
Gabrielle for the membership
hire a chicken to like all the comments
like I said my assistant's chicken
no that that's fake I don't want that
[Music]
I want a crispy chicken Bella
Burger King
Burger King please deliver to my home
please
[Music]
she's eating the flies in my office
don't worry she gets food
isn't she cute
[Music]
you know
oh nice piano
I just went on Twitter and saw you and I
missed it
you're gonna miss the credits until now
[Music]
how could you
oh yeah
[Music]
foreign
it's so cute
[Music]
she can be like a rocket like
did you see that mine again
wait what let's go a little bit slower
[Music]
speed
it's so cute
Tim oh he's so cute [\h__\h] frog
yes read your [\h__\h] Subway
[Music]
one year has passed so fast one wonders
where time is gone yo there were amazing
streams collabs and kianaoka original
songs and of course kfb's favorite
tangent streams of occasional cassette
Super Chat reading
thank you Canada for this great year if
there's more here's so many more things
to come thank you I have to say I'm a
bit nervous about the upcoming year if I
can really like
um
live up to your expectations uh the
expectations of kfp uh I hope I can I
hope I can surprise surpass your
expectations
um I think I need a little break and
then come back in full force I'll put my
best yeah
[Music]
greatly though by getting a new outfit
so I'm [\h__\h] excited to show that to
you guys
and I hope you guys will like it
I hope you guys will like my new outfit
[Music]
today
also I wanna make use of the VR more
often
uh I have to say it's very exhausting
[Music]
that the VR I don't know if it's the
same moves above but the one that I have
it feels very heavy on my head
um yeah it's very heavy and and and
holding the the freaking uh controllers
especially when holding down buttons is
exhausting
and can't even move that much because of
the freaking cable
you'll get used to it oh
yeah but I was like oh my God after a
while of at the end no after actually I
think after the first 40 minutes or so
of that stream I was already sweating
uh oh [\h__\h]
oh and at the end I was soaked in sweat
and tears and snot
um
no it's not even about stamina it was
literally just like I don't know the
fact that I was
um
foreign
like fluffy pajamas partially and my
pajama pants were a bit too hot and the
the VR headset being too heavy as well
uh too too hot and too heavy
um and then I don't know the whole new
velocity I guess
um but
and I want to use it more anyway I did
feel when I first played around with it
I did feel a little bit dizzy or a
little bit sick
but the sickness was not much of a big
deal during the actual Stream So I think
I'm fine I think I got just used to it I
don't think I have motion sickness
I don't think I have that
like not at least not always
[Music]
I was I was thinking
what we can do with uh that we could
even do uh on an unarchived stream where
I just play all kinds of idol music
and I act as if I'm on in a concert and
I do I do like chants
I'm not like okay there's there's
different kinds of otage they are the
really uh big flashy moves
which I don't usually do that alone
because uh I was a fan of hello project
and when you're in a hello project
concert
you do you don't do that much
most of the people in hello project
concerts do the dances alongside but
anyway so yeah we can do like dance
streams as well I mean you'll never see
the full glory of the choreography
especially also because of the cable
like when I was dancing Renaissance
circulation
and
I definitely like I I only danced it
with like five percent of my actual
potential because I was also scared of
like bumping into walls and Furniture
because you don't really know where the
hell you are in that moment you keep on
losing track of where you are in the
room it's very dangerous and the cable
limits me as well I can't do turns and
all that
but like like you know still I think
it's so cute and we can do some things
with that we can do some dancing streams
and
um by the way that Sparks that's that
was not a choreography
um there is no choreography to spikes
yet I have a choreography to hinodori
and heart Challenger
so I could show you a scuffed
[Music]
VR chat version of that but at the same
time I'm thinking like I want to show it
to you when like the first time when I
can properly show it to you in its full
Glory
so I'm not sure no but it would be fun
to give you a sneak peek but you
wouldn't see like the details of the
choreo and it's a the choreos are pretty
damn detailed and intricate to be honest
I don't even trust myself being able to
dance it
well with the headset on because it's
like a lot of movement they're they're
my choreographies are very very powerful
um but maybe I don't know I can try but
I feel like I'll I'll be I I'll feel
very held back
okay
[Music]
they don't understand
do you know how to break dance balls no
I don't
we are trackers of dancing definitely
does some monkey things one question so
I have a uh am I got me to buy free
trackers
and two controllers came with the VR is
it possible to add more
trackers like I have one on my waist
and which was kept on flopping around
and I think it wasn't like in the best
position uh which is why I had a really
weird posture I don't actually have such
a weird post shot in real life okay
not that bad so can I get more trackers
like maybe put one like I don't know on
my chest and maybe one on my thighs
because the other two were on my on my
feet
um I wonder if that will make it more
detailed however I guess with the small
Canada model it doesn't even make sense
to add more trackers because the body is
just so deformed
um
I I wanted to fix the the Hunchback
poster sometimes it wants the other way
around too not Hunchback but the other
way around I wanted to fix it but I
didn't know like how I don't know it was
weird my posture on my body was so weird
in in the VR chat it would just be a
waste hmm
and almond tracking was really good
because she knows what she's doing
but I do want to do at least a little
bit of you know like uh [\h__\h] around
dances like I can dance
are you ready or you can dance like Luca
Luca Night Fever
[Music]
it's like [\h__\h] around a little bit with
that even if I can't dance it to its
full potential in VR I still want to
just you know
do get done life I can't that needs some
editing
[Music]
oh we can do that one um
I think that one actually
simple so we could actually make it look
pretty nice maybe I should upload Dance
videos like not only in the streams
maybe I should for some of the songs
that I can actually use the audio for or
and archive it
maybe we could have actual Dance videos
wouldn't that be cute
[Music]
foreign
let's do it although that dance also has
a moment where you turn
doesn't it yeah it does definitely does
hmm I can practice them
[Music]
Night of Fire oh no you didn't you
didn't just pull out that old ass song
[Music]
you don't expect me to do but actually
that's really easy that actually works
nah
no it doesn't because my arms are so
short you won't really see much of what
I'm doing with my arms
[Music]
well I will take suggestions I will take
your suggestions caramel dancing but
that's just boring
the me me dance now that's boring
love and joy I can't oh yeah sometimes I
know above those answers
but that is holy [\h__\h] that is a lot of
movement in that that's very energetic
dance that is a very energetic dance
foreign
[Music]
I can do all these dances
I mean I have to remember them
but I can't do them I can
save beat saber streams do we have a
permission for them maybe
foreign
suggestions you had to sing believe it
no no I wouldn't have
um taken your suggestion guys it was
just because of Kelly
someone said
oh poor people that works maybe oh but
no actually never mind poor people is a
lot of the Nike jumping like from one
leg to another
oh that would be very bouncy with the
headset
but
[Music]
could give it a try could give it a try
I love that you guys know these things
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
that's a little bit different
disco oh yeah
[Laughter]
magnet
I don't know if I can sing that I mean I
know the song very well but I don't know
if I can make a cover of it
okay
rainbow
with one message thank you and here's a
rainbow super chat but you can do happy
first anniversary although I'm just a
part-timer I'll still keep supporting
you thank you thank you thank you so
much that's way more way more than you
should ever give me but thank you so
much thank you
I appreciate it
and Christina Manzanita
help
is that a rainbow
[Music]
Christina
it doesn't have color here in my actual
clothes that that currency is not
recognized
[Music]
it is Christina
pay you
and you just give me that money back why
the hell do you do that
maybe maybe that's been your plan all
along all according to cake
he's just you just drawing emotes you
just take my commissions in order to use
that money on super chats huh
reverse cloud
[Music]
tarantula is not
wasn't that what we're supposed to do of
course of course it was actually
according to my cake
so this will be my big whim I apologize
for my bad English but I will continue
learning because you motivated me every
day a message for the Majestic pretty
bright strong
bossy that's me that's me I was once
told
somebody once told me
to keep my inner light that I had
surround myself with light but finding
light has been hard thank you for saving
me from the darkness it really radiate
warmth and light like a phoenix oh
really
you made this here my days stopping just
days I met amazing people in your
community learning new things I made
more art than I enjoy and I am happy to
be able wait you implied I think that's
a mistake in the English but it implies
that you drew so much that you're sick
of it I hope that's not true I'm happy
to be able to radiant others the feeling
that you shared with me this year we all
laughed cried learned played and enjoyed
together but this is this is only the
first of many more I appreciate respect
and admire using Idol Phoenix and person
always be yourself I'm I am mortal but
the memories will be Eternal this is the
power of takanasikiara fly high and keep
light up more chickens thank you
thank you Christina
thank you I always love seeing your art
thank you for always drawing so much
it's like after every stream there's
another art another fan art from you
thank you it makes me so happy your
style is so cute I really love seeing it
you're really really great
please continue doing what you do
see we love you we love the emotes we
love them
thank you thank you for the super chats
thank you Electro John 12 Danke Schoen
Slowpoke thank you for the pinky
Hulk
I know Kiana the scuffed live stream is
unfortunate which one there were so many
back in the day
and These Wings have been stressful but
there is 250k fans who have their own
unique story with you and accept you the
way you are 250k different reasons why
here is special to the piano fan club we
can do another RTA one day slow
uh what's that about the Minecraft
stream huh
the one where I wanted to do the Nev
wanted to go into the never but I
couldn't
because something happened yeah yeah I
remember that
I was pretty dumb on that day
that was what the shitty PC right
[Music]
yeah once the the one where I uh moved
to General's place used her [\h__\h] but we
realized oh that PC cannot handle uh it
well and then we went back to my place
brought my [\h__\h] heavy ass PC in a
suitcase back to janma's place which was
[\h__\h] exhausting with the monitor or
or maybe now I think we brought no
monitor no no but the PC was so [\h__\h]
heavy oh my God
holy macaroni that was really exhausting
going back and forth moving my [\h__\h] oh
man
yeah but that was no but that was still
my old that was still the old PC before
getting the new one
wait never mind that one wasn't that
heavy but something was really
exhausting I remember that the whole
movie was so exhausting
um
yeah we were going through uh trains
and you know how
how Japan's uh how crowded Japan's
trains can be
little arms well most of the time uh
jenma was um
carrying things for me
but there were other incidents where
I had to carry that [\h__\h] myself which is
uh can't be helped
and always there can't always be
supported by in general but General is
my angel
a hello
what would I do without janma
um
[Music]
you're losing brain cells with the bgm
what no way this is this is giving me
literally Universe brain
typhoon
what the [\h__\h] thank you for five red
super chats are you are you are you okay
[Music]
why now JMT I'm like oh we need JMT
emote
it's so hard to believe that it has
truly been one year and yet here you are
yeah it is it is crazy when I watched
your debut a year ago you watched it
I wasn't quite sure what to make of you
but I decided to keep watching because I
just had a feeling there was something
special about you
you are right maybe and now I'm glad to
be able to say that that was totally
right
you managed to make me smile so much
that I don't think I'll ever be able to
repay for you for it but this isn't
about me this was this is about the
amazing person you are and everything
you've done this past year since Debbie
you've grown in so many ways you seem
more confident you branched out so many
types of streams You've Made Beautiful
music and yet you still remain the
radiant Phoenix with an amazing heart a
bit of myself
[Music]
if you fall harder than any of us can
know and I'm sure we all want you to
know we appreciate it
we love you so much for all the work you
put in just to make a smile as a fan I'm
proud of you and truly hope you're proud
and happy about what you've accomplished
it has been tough but you're still here
and we're still beside you why is that
being so nice may this be the first of
many years that we celebrate
events
[Music]
again
at these times you guys sent these
emotional super chats always
a handle
it's wholesomeness
[Music]
how long can I
good morning
also the inside of my mouth hurts now
already read too many
and yet I'm so far
[Music]
you guys are too sweet
[Applause]
[Music]
no no no I would read more actually I'm
thinking of making a tea
should I make a tea and then drink it
slowly cozy let's wait that reminds me
uh I wanted to you know this this this
new super awesome layout came with a mug
already but I wanna you know make use of
some other things that I received so um
wait a second I got uh where's my
resource
mm-hmm
IX made me some mugs and they're so cute
and you know I would normally put them
on top of these things probably so let
me just be realistic here
these are all denied anyway so whatever
so I'm gonna go make some tea I guess so
that I can go through this without
destroying my throat
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
um
[Music]
YouTube
I put it into my ninety mug
[Music]
cute pink
but it will take a while because this
one keeps the tea hot as long as it can
so it'll take a while until it's
drinkable for me that's why you have to
think
ahead of time
be smart
foreign
[Music]
handy at the time when I most need it
um
[Music]
let's go okay
where was I I had to type on Super Chat
thank you type that was so sweet for
God's sakes some of you guys are
just too kind unbelievable
thank you for the recipe
I'm still here supporting you guys and
we'll continue doing so time does fly
when you're enjoying every single one of
it you've grown so much attention and I
believe you will keep growing even more
thanks for the fun year thank you thank
you
thank you I appreciate the support
I'm glad you're still here really thank
you kfp strong I'm still very proud that
one of my own people was the one who
um provided the don't strive together do
stuff together don't stop is it just
don't stop don't stop
don't stop together right and uh months
yeah very proud that it came from my own
Community
yeah I know I know that you have been
updating ever since then I kind of
played the game again at some point does
does the game have a Japanese version
or is it English only
can non-member send super chats yes but
I currently have the Super Chat turned
off because I have a lot to catch up on
Don't Starve Together is the updated
version oh
I only played the updated one then
I use them with my friends oh cool I
want to play it again and like get to
like like and make actual progress in
the game because whenever I played it or
was that only one time it feels it feels
like I played it two times
[Music]
probably only was one time though
um yeah we didn't get very far because
we're just [\h__\h] around too much oh I
did play it twice oh
oh
that's interesting
one time of mods
in November we played it before
hooray I don't remember that time
but then it's true in both times I made
no progress
yeah
and if if there is a Japanese version it
would be cool to play it like with with
some Japanese members too but I feel
like if they were a Japanese version
they would have already played it in
whole life Japan right
[Music]
yeah that Ian Monaco that wasn't that
our sixth month anniversary
I may couldn't save you guys been dying
uh it was chaotic as ever with all the
move
[Music]
little bgm got me unable to stop moving
oh I feel yeah
[Music]
it's got a low-key tropical vibe to it
doesn't it
kind of reminds me of Super Mario
um
[Music]
uh Sunshine yeah
drumming it on my chair
[Music]
foreign
the year went so fast I wasn't here
since Debbie but I'm glad I joined soon
after you've been the light of my days
for me I can't thank you enough for it
you deserve every bit of Joy that's
coming your way and I hope it stays that
way for many years thank you I hope so
too
I but you know I I I I don't know what
to say
thank you
thank you very much
I'm glad you're still here
even even when you if you weren't there
from the debut you came a little bit
late but that's okay
at least you found me at last
[Music]
thank you for
one red and three pinkies oh my God
I can't believe it has already been one
year since the debut of this incredibly
talented sweet and lovable Phoenix I
honestly can't believe it either it
feels insane it doesn't feel like one
year it feels like less it's crazy but
even though it feels like less it feels
like I've done more in that one year
than I've done in the past 10 years
[Music]
I want to let you know that you're the
reason why these past nine months nine
and a half months of my life have been
such a blast you're bright and cheerful
personality always keep me going
you gave me something to look forward to
and a reason to wake up every day oh I
suppose uh early as [\h__\h] in the morning
I'm sorry about that oh no wait the
other way around late at night
it's amazing how your streams and music
always give me so much happiness every
time I watch them you really are the son
of home life the Sun that shines so
bright and gives life to everything
around it I'm really so surprised that I
uh was able to maintain that kind of
image
because I do have a lot of
moments where I'm sad and not so
energetic and kind of like you know
down
so it surprises me that the general
image that people have of me is being
the Sun
the bright one
because I don't really see myself
like that
[Music]
not really
you always come through
[Music]
I mean I always try to be energetic in
my streams except for now I want to save
energy
foreign
attitude
you're the voice of the group nah I'm
not I'm not that no no no no no
it's good
only a psychopath can act energetic all
the time why that's not true
are you calling pekular Senpai or
psychopath she's not I mean okay some
people say that the things she does in
Minecraft
it's just an energetic bubbly bunny
I really I really admire her effort
always being like that but I wonder like
how she does it and I hope she doesn't
like force herself to keep that up but
you know she's amazing
anyway so I'll say this again I may not
have been here since day one but I
promise that I'll continue to support
you until the end of time looking
forward to many of my eventful years
with you you will forever be my one only
Aussie I love you so much thank you
thank you really I hope I really hope I
can continue entertaining you so that
you don't get sick of me and oh you're
here with your sub account
thank you I've known much love to you
pout I'm ready to kiss the employee
thank you for two pinkies hi I don't
support chat much but your anniversary
is a big day so my first ride is yours I
just want to say that my job has me
working long hours directly with this
big thing and seeing so many sad things
your streams and your energy are one of
the few things that can make me smile
thank you for working so hard and for
being who you are into a happy
anniversary
[Music]
thank you for being there
I appreciate it
you you may be a worker generally but at
least you're there thank you so much
I want to drink the tea
drink some water
[Music]
so I have watched you for 365 days holy
[\h__\h]
can I challenge you to read one of the
longest German word central yes that
word is
nailed it
what a nice anniversary super Chan and
I'm not even joking because at least I
don't have to read
so much more
thank you what does it mean it's a it's
a it's a law
uh about
[Music]
uh
something
that I can't translate
well well well you will forever have
that question in your mind
you will forever ask yourself what did
that mean
you won't be able to sleep either
thank you John B bear
I hope that made you happy
thank you for your love and supports and
stay one you are
not only the John B bear
but also the
okay that makes no sense let me try the
John Bieber because there's a capital B
in the middle I want to see the MVP
okay I can't I can't make anything out
of this let me just say you the MVP okay
whatever
I tried I tried but nothing I say makes
sense ever
I need Google Translate please Google
translate Korean to English because your
name is in Korean and I still can't read
that
[Music]
guidance
it's you thank you
got a Super Chat and Bronx 819 thank you
for the red super chat I won't be able
to catch your stream since I'll be
asleep without sure for sure watch the
Vlog oh I hope you did
that one was great thanks for being
there a few potential you had a great
first year so I look forward to this
year too thank you
I mean this year could have been better
there were a lot of struggles and
um you know because of the seafing a lot
of things were left unaccomplished
no but
I still pre-check I don't know is this
still present I hope not
it probably is yeah no it is I actually
know but uh where it ends the project I
am because I copied it before I started
to stream uh the first part
anyway thank you Bronx
uh you've been around
for a long time so thank you so much
Bronx for all the love and support thank
you thank you very much
crayons are tasty things for the pinky
congratulations
I only joined recently but I love your
positive energy and appreciate your hard
work care if it really feels like a
family to me your streams are the
highlights of my week you might all see
second season let's go
and you'll be and still says I'm the
Aussie and they they've like like they
think of kfb as a family
oh I'm so glad I'm so glad you found
your way in here
thank you for joining kfb
I hope we will have a long long long
long time of lots of fun together
hello one three seven five dinosaurs
for the red super [\h__\h] and the pinky
yeah it's oh no wait that's a rainbow
and never mind that's a rainbow Kiana
it's hard to believe it's been a year
since your video I won't forget the
impression you left on me when I first
came across you I wondered who the hell
is this quirky girl she's probably not
for me
before I knew it I was watching your
streams more and more you grew on me so
much to the point I hate missing any of
your students live
your passion your drive your endearing
personality the way you can just bring
everyone around you into your sphere and
make them feel welcome sets you aside
from others in so many ways be true to
yourself because you have a beautiful
soul the line never feel you and Aren't
appreciated because for me at least you
have brought so much joy and fun in dull
times even if I can't be around live I
will always support you in some way you
light up my world diagonisticiana don't
literally I mean I think I'm in a fryer
right now I just get
this not sure how many kfb members are
in the Caribbean oh
but I claim the title of biggest fan of
takanashikiana here and everyone here is
spark Stanley
[Music]
Arabian yo
that's nice thanks for the membership
welcome
thank you
sweet message
thank you mate it made my heart to go
Doki Doki
thank you
one day one day I'll go there on a
vacation yes
I'm looking forward to it
and here I listened to reggae music is
that is that is that the steroid
stereotype I'm sorry if it is
[Music]
but I like Reggie music there was a time
when I like literally only listened to
reggae music I had a reggae face
ready
it is true okay
is it I mean is it I'm sorry
Frankie is it not ready we're gay Reggie
Reggie
green green God
red guy
[Music]
reggae oh
ranking reggae
okay finally I know how to pronounce
that yeah
how about reggae version of spikes
how about that we need it please someone
make reggae version of spikes
I wonder if that would sound good
[Music]
laughs laughs
I'm blowing my teeth
the kitty
I've been I haven't I didn't try to blow
whistle that that's not what I was
intending to do
[Music]
I love that song
what time
[Music]
wow what time
you say there we go
stupid
[Music]
it's too hot
okay I need to focus I want to at least
read all the pre-chat ones it's been
five hours but we're right now
wait Nene diesel thank you for the pinky
[Music]
there's two months for me to know you
but love is eternal Like a Phoenix right
unfortunately I guess it's not but maybe
your love for me is eternal I hope it is
and you gave me a lot of brightness
energy smile I will keep on keep going
to support you as much as I can I love
you
um
foreign
School
[Music]
um
thank you for the pinky congrats on one
year thank you thank you for all your
hard work and for making kfpl one big
family loved you from the beginning and
will keep loving you in the days to come
let's make this another memorable year
keep shining bright My OC thank you so
ones I will do my best I gotta I gotta
step up my game though gotta do more
than just whole talk
I feel yeah
I want to do more
um I want to organize more big clubs
and I want to definitely do whole
Adventure
um
and I guess
eventually work on a on an album
I have to say my general motivation to
make music is much lower than before
because of foreign
[Music]
but I still don't want to give up on it
because I love making music
so I think I will I will have to
follow my heart
yeah and I want to drink my [\h__\h] tea
why is it so hot
my goal for this year is to drink my tea
laughs
and and I want to put out a single with
a 3D music video
but that would mean I have to do a 3D
debut first
hello bar
yeah I wanna I want to
I want to do a 3D uh music video with a
choreography
um
yes
I've seen a lot of
music videos recently in whole life
popping up not only about the Miss
Empire but the one that uh meal Senpai
put out was pretty damn great as well
[Music]
yeah
I want to do something like that too
[Music]
yeah
Holly
[Music]
well bunch of them already did oh yeah
um
[Music]
thank you
thank you for the
red super jet splitting six orange ones
I think
congrats on one year anniversary Tango I
didn't have enough material to prepare
fancy colored carpet for anniversary no
don't worry about it however I was able
to gather enough material to fill an
orange carpet Lawrence carpet is better
than a red carpet anyway Orange let's go
hope this suits your taste it does time
flew so fast didn't it it doesn't feel
like it's been a year since UW yet here
we are celebrating one year anniversary
I never thought I would be watching
someone for a year long but I don't
regret my choice you were able to
accomplish a lot of goals in such a
short time New Passion and tenacity
drive to reach ghost's admirable you
have also grown as well and definitely
seem to have more confidence than before
your whole summer kind-hearted
personality always put a smile to my
face and brighten up my day I really
appreciate that I'm looking forward to
next year as well can't wait uh what
lies next ahead whatever lies beyond the
future there will own there will be one
thing that is certain I will be there to
give support however I can thank you
foreign
[Music]
sounds like one year
Maybe in my in my brain maybe it's a lie
maybe it's a lie
what
do they say
now let's see let's see what it really
was
yes it says
you guys could scare me
thank you
[Music]
I guess the Katakana was a little bit
inaccurate
[Music]
yes
sorry so thank you for the pinky
Musical
[Music]
Japan
meaning
[Music]
foreign
congratulations on your first
anniversary again I'd like to thank you
for all your hard work this past year
lucky me I get the novelty to say I was
there for your first day of your life
and I'm very honored to have been part
of this journey since it's very
beginning you've become one of my
greatest Joys and I'm really grateful
for everything you've walked a lot of
Rocky Mountains the past year and
overcoming it all is such a great feat
but I rather not have you under any of
that anymore this year is I wish for you
to fly high unbothered by the obstacles
that block your path so we're hire and
illuminate our skies Illuminati with my
dear Phoenix thank you yeah I feel like
you're sending me signals here
I don't know about obstacles this year
but we'll see about that huh
thank you so much for your support
[Music]
oh
well I definitely probably asked what am
I simply for advice once once I get into
the part of producing a 3D music video
I'll definitely want to wanna wanna
really really wonder whether you can
take out what
Kiana thought X's stop working
hahaha
[Music]
that's it
it's so hot
we're getting there
foreign
[Music]
well I'll just burn my insides I guess
weep trash dangers
[Music]
dinosaur for the pinky I think that adds
up to a red one foreign
[Music]
made me smile like an idiot I was going
through tough times when you're giving
me that smile the first time I've seen a
stream was at the start of start of the
love I had for you but and everyone at
kfb who gave me back my smile for that
I'm grateful okay you're not using any
like thoughts and and stuff so it's very
confusing
you may not
you may not see it but you are one of
the best people ever we are so lucky to
have you as our boss even if you intend
to cook us I'm Ben is expressing myself
but I just want you to know how loved
you are and how precious you are to us
you truly are a special person that's
been through so much and yet has still
come out on top of
it that is so admirable
also it's what makes you so amazing this
is the last one I look forward to all
the amazing things you have left to show
it's amazing how far you've come it will
be even more amazing seeing how much
further you can go the love potential it
will always be your amazing past thank
you I hope I hope I will never have to
fire you
thank you so much for the sweet message
and thank you thank you for the red
super chat Tai Chi
Chia
Senza a 500 Redtube and who says happy
anniversary all right all right you want
to make it easier for me don't die I
the one time I appreciate uh super chats
that say nothing or only two words this
is the one time I say thank you
pudding Channel thank you for the pinky
happy first anniversary Canada time sure
flies when you enjoy yourself I hereby
propose a toast oh
wait let me raise my tea
Okay so
May our tears be but a trap in the ocean
of joy and our lives forever be a stable
ship sailing upon the tides of success
[Music]
here come on set cheers
laughs
[Music]
Dr Helena Spanish
thank you for always trying your best
thank you for being the bright and
Charming son thank you for the most
amazing year ever happy anniversary
thank you for the love thank you so much
I hope I can entertain you in the next
year too please stay and support me and
want my growth thank you table Lori
thank you for the red super chat
mwah wonderful video following this cute
verb around huh feels like it's gone by
so fast and yet so much has happened
yeah it's been a hell of a year eh
are you speaking Canadian to me thank
you for putting a smile on my face for a
tough times Kiana here's to another year
of the kfb come by no I have to thank
you guys for putting a smile on my face
yeah it's honestly
it's this way around you guys give me
happiness and joy and smiles when even
when I started stream
unmotivated and unhappy
the time that I spend with you guys
is my happiest time
[Music]
I'm actually surprised how
happy I am right now
because like outside of the stream I was
just like
oh
it was like a zombie
[Music]
I was like [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] that
I hate this I hate that
[Music]
so thank you
I should just stream 24 hours per day
then I'm always happy
oh
Kiana has since tonight
do you know
God again
[Music]
thank you
hmm
let's go let's go let's go let's please
please
[Music]
that's a really old morning Muslim song
wait let me let me let me show it to you
I will I will link it to you guys
[Music]
morning Musa man the peace very old very
old
wait don't play it don't play it push
YouTube good job good job at not playing
it okay here it is can we listen to it
together
us
just let's have like a little break okay
stop
we will play together in I'm here with
my music let's play it together in in
five seconds
go build it
at five at five okay
one
two
three four five
it's so old this was released in 2001.
when you go there
oh you go there
you go there
yeah
oh I haven't listened to this one in a
long time hey
[Music]
this was when morning Muslim was
freaking popular in Japan
you cause it everybody get up
let's get up get up
[Music]
hello everybody
peace peace
you go there
oh hi oh
hi
yeah
let's go let's call it
College
[Music]
I don't know the lyrics anymore
peace peace
[Music]
ha ha ha ha ha
you call that
dude
okay can we stop stop stop stop stop one
more
as I'll send you as a different one from
the group that I uh supported the most
um
I I wouldn't say that
no that's not something I'll send you
guys this one maybe this one is cute I
think
that's a real that's a really old one
too 2005. holy [\h__\h]
it was so cute this is like like they're
they literally that group literally grew
up without a project
they were like what nine years ten years
in the beginning 11 years maybe
and then when they graduated 10 years
later they were like 21 22 and all that
pretty crazy
let's let's listen to one choice okay
in uh at five again okay
at five
this will probably read you out a little
bit but
um
okay one two three four five
that was actually a
used as an anime opening timah song
don't cringe at it guys
[Music]
hi
no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's so cute it's so cute
oh
okay I'm in full otaku mode holy [\h__\h] oh
dear oh dear
wait let me let me show you like the
date I went to a lot of concerts from
them and they're [\h__\h] awesome let me
show you one footage of their uh concert
like this one I think I remember this
one as being insanely uh hype whenever
they sang this one
last one I promise maybe maybe last one
I should make a playlist for you guys
and we just listen but how yeah Emma
does that doesn't she like a radio but
it would have to be alive anyway
okay in five seconds okay go build it
ain't one two three four five you'll
feel the vibes from this hey hey
probably
I I
I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I
hi hi
s
Ada
Mama hi Mama Hi
hi
happiness
[Music]
hi
Chris yes
[Music]
Dad hey
yay
let's go
[Music]
wow
hi hi
hi hi hi hi
Jesus okay we don't know what's
happening we're listening to some music
together
yeah
yay oh my God yes I missed it so much
[Music]
[Laughter]
why don't you
why don't you do stuff anymore why
oh wait this one is so cute I just want
to listen to all these songs together
with you
oh my God
um
oh God
I want to do one more
um
these are all so good
one more
wow which one
ah
yes this one was good
this was a good live concert song
okay okay
last one last one last one last one last
one last one yes
[Music]
okay in five seconds one
two
three
[\h__\h] what
what oh
hi
hi every day and night hey hey
that's [\h__\h] Budokan guys
I I I I
mean maybe
hi
and
hey
[Music]
um
don't cry I think this was the
graduation concert
oh for [\h__\h] sake
hey
[Laughter]
hey hey
[Music]
see these are not doing the crazy old
okay they're just doing like
look at them look at them
[Music]
this is the one that pecora loves the
one that just sang the one of the two
pigtails that's uh she likes her a lot
um
on
every day and now
they throw their towels
[Music]
yay
yeah that's it that's it
why did you guys leave me
without Betty school ball
I lost my purpose
what to live for anymore I don't know
yeah
so I think you saw a difference from the
first music video that I showed you
where they were like really [\h__\h]
young and how grown up they are like
they they did this job their whole
[\h__\h] life they went to school they
went to Junior High School they went to
high school then they went to I think
all of them went to University as well
while doing all of this working so hard
they oh my God they worked they were so
active they put out new singles like
every uh two months or so
um and they had concerts constantly in
between
yeah and I totally understand that at
some point it has to end like you can't
just like they obviously like they had
no proper like I mean
I mean I can't judge they didn't have a
normal childhood that's for sure
but
yeah and for this whole life they
supposedly officially we're also not
dating because in hello project to you
not supposed to date anyone and I mean I
I there's some scandals every now and
then and I'm sure that some of them do
it anyway and just hide it and all that
uh but what kind of what kind of life is
that anyway like where you just have to
hide it all that's that's also not fun
always having to live in the fear of
people finding out about it and to you
then losing your job
um that's just not that's that that must
give you like anxiety problems
because especially if you're so popular
like a grip like that and you get
literally recognized in public and
people take photos of you and they have
like paparazzis and all that that's
where
it gets difficult
um
yeah but the the girl who I supported
the most back then risako she was my OSI
yeah she uh is uh she has a I think two
yeah two by now two children
and uh she has an Instagram where she's
like really being like a legit mother
she really changed like she's there's
some other members of that group who now
um
so do a little bit of music but not as
successful as they once wear and and
other is like one of them who was really
tall she's now a model and actually
being quite successful as a model but my
honestly unfortunately doesn't do any
music anymore but she's married and she
has two kids
um
it happened quite soon after she
graduated
interesting isn't it
but I have no problem with that at all
honestly I just want them to be happy
and
um it's it's always weird to see though
like now she really looks like a mom
she used to be so flashy like she was uh
the the one person in the group who
um uh not besides me I'll be but she
definitely was one of the flashier
members always changing her hair color
and putting on a lot of makeup and she
got criticized a lot for that for
wearing too much makeup uh which is
[\h__\h] and then she had a time where
she gained a little bit of weight so
people criticize her with that that was
also [\h__\h] she's beautiful I love her
goddess gorgeous anyway
anyway so yeah now it's like like yeah
very different so anyway I I I I I
supported them for a long time and they
were like a big inspiration for me
and uh
yeah seeing them go I was not able to
really find an Aussie that meant like
inspired and and caught my eye so much
as Lisa go did anymore after that
uh even though I still like kettle
project and I still like their uh some
of the groups but
yeah
she was so special to me you know hmm
no
I don't know why I suddenly had to go
into otaku mode look for um
uh amber doesn't know about these Circle
don't worry
um
I
had this crazy idea
um
that you know wealthy wolf is actually a
huge fan of Pullman well if he's Rafa's
favorite seems to be pomu in niji Ian
and uh
he I feel like there's like a
possibility of promo getting a wealthy
model
wouldn't it be fun
if we could do VR chat collab and then
both just like I sing a song to me she
sings the song
see that's my vision that's my vision
but she did buy VR recently yo well
let's go let's [\h__\h] go see I can't
make any promises
um but it is a vision that I've had in
my head after the VR chat
because I don't know if you guys know
but Pomo is this uh uh who is very uh
even more of a otaku in the sense of oh
yeah like even more than me because she
knows all the crazy chants that go like
five attackers
I don't
do those chants to be honest because it
was never a hello Project Style too like
in other Idol uh groups they do that but
for hella project it was not so much a
case but I know what she does what she
does when she does it and I love it
so
I don't know I just feel like our
interests align very much yeah I'm a
little bit of different type of I'm more
the the foodie copy type of
otaku which that you call they actually
yeah there's like different types and
they have names so the foodie could be
type of utaku is a type of utaku who
mainly does choreography copying while
uh watching them on stage like in the
concert hall
yeah and most of her project otakus are
that type of uh
so they do love to do the foodie copy
choreography uh copying
type no
copy foreign
[Music]
choreography
so foodie Foodies
food
okay I have to read super chats no more
[\h__\h] around now
foreign
you know it was so funny to me
um but it I really respected and I
really love it when I was in these
concerts uh halls and
um mostly the male audience around me
and um they would they would just like
do a perfect copy of those uh
choreographies next to me and you know
they're like what 50 60 years or 40 50
60 years old years old personally it's
love it I respect that yo your dance is
perfect you got that choreography down
you spend time to learn it I respect it
yeah blast out those choreographies I
love it okay not so many 60 years old
you're old people but a lot of 30 40 50
year old people yeah yeah
it's yo they have good energy and the
passion the passion is insane I love the
passion that they give off when they
dance
oh
and and they dance in like a really tiny
space you know
the you only get like like one square
even less partial view one square meter
it's nothing
yes
they got it
and you they are the dancing queen
Dancing Queen
even with 40 years old you are killing
it oh yeah show me those
moves I respect you very much yes okay
anyway
back
to Super chats
I was not trying to run away from it
[Music]
are you guys still with me are you with
me or what
[Music]
I need you guys mental support you know
oh
[Music]
here noise
welcome
[Music]
right on top why do you want me to sing
right on them
after hearing sing it again I once again
have a earworm
I've been humming it uh today a lot
yeah
you can do it
I don't know I don't know which
uh ongen which karaoke I would I mean
which instrumental I would be able to
use
[Music]
yeah I love that it's a dope song
which which should we listen to face
theme what does that sound like
[Music]
it's a bit too calm
down
ah what is this one
ah Lobster's theme
[Music]
I like it
a bit
home too maybe
what about this
nah
[Music]
foreign
yes
oh I like this
this is turd Bird's theme who is that
who wants that
what is this one
I don't remember that it's from the
stream from the game
[Music]
this one nice
who is Herbert I don't remember
uh Google
Skyward Sword trippered the person
not much comes up
and um yeah an old magma oops sorry
I had to
huh wait I have not met that dude did I
I don't remember meeting him
[Music]
anymore
um
that seems to be a mini game
I didn't mean that dude oh well
[Music]
was it that loud
it is a Super Chat reading okay let's go
planes I think yeah thank you for uh two
pinkies okay actual super chat message
this time it's been a full year now and
what absolutely blows me away is how you
and this community has developed you've
spent so much time talking and
communicating with us being open open
and honest when you come to us it's not
like as a one million YouTuber it's like
a friend
I just come to you as me
[Music]
together we were to make this a place
where all can feel welcome thank you
Kiana for making this community the most
wonderful place to be here's another
bright year with more kfp that reminds
me of a discussion I had yesterday
um
where
how should I put this
um
[Music]
uh
whether or not the
things that people say about me
or others whether or not it's a
positive or negative whether or not that
should
um get to me or not
and I was told
no
if it's negative then no
because
you were playing a character right and
I'm like no
I I don't
so whatever people say about me it's not
like they say it about a character they
say it about me and that's why it gets
to me even more
yeah
so whether or not it's positive messages
like these
or negative messages
it's about me another character because
I'm I'm not here playing a 1 million
subscribe of YouTube uh Phoenix whatever
for you I'm I'm playing nothing here I'm
just myself
foreign
[Music]
accept me this way
thank you
I love you
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
attachment
s
[Music]
so
anyway thank you so let's keep late
thank you for the red super chat happy
anniversary sadly haven't been here
since the start but I've been here long
enough to confidently say that you're a
wonderful person and I'll be supporting
you till the end I love you my Aussie
thank you you guys we just had this
moment with uh where I showed you some
of my oshi's music
and and you you guys didn't used to call
me Oshi from the beginning I think you
guys needed to find your way into this
culture as well but
um it means a lot to me if you guys call
me that because it's something that I
use to describe my favorite Idol and uh
I don't know it makes me very happy it
makes me very happy to hear it from you
guys yeah
nowadays I hear that a lot in the
beginning you guys didn't use that much
foreign
[Music]
we were a bit too shy for that term now
you use it with confidence nice
I'm glad to have you as my Aussie thank
you I understand it now yeah
we started with my tea or give me I'm
done with mine give me yours
[Music]
a cat hair in my mouth
somewhere
can't find it um
oh well it will just now
live in my mouth I guess
oh my God why am I so slow okay I'll
read these fast enough
well thank you for the red so we're Chad
the happy first anniversary yeah what an
incredible year it has been you have
come such a long way and we are on front
and thankful for everything you have
done and we'll do in the future and
thank you for being the strong passion
of divine burning fire in all our hats
thank you very much Peter thanks mate
I'm glad you're enjoying my streams
please support me forever
thanks for the pinky a full game of
piano over already Jesus Christ it went
fast thanks for all the good times and
for always working so hard congrats on
the anniversary and hope that to have
many more great years with you thank you
thank you got some parts of my clothing
now
[Music]
I'm back
[Laughter]
oh
happy one year anniversary yeah fun
streams great memories awesome music and
Bright Smiles hell yeah it all gave us
the strength to keep going through the
tough times let's go for another year
full of nothing but greatness with
radiant Phoenix smile guide in the way I
wasn't there for Holy and debut
discovered it about one month later oh
that's pretty early still your passion
dedication and hard work left a deep
impression on me back then I didn't even
know what Aussie means yet oh right here
there we go yet I already found mine my
favorite YouTuber and streamer takanasi
Kiana
oh thank you
thank you so much
yeah well I think we we went through
pretty much all the technical issues I
can have in the first year and even
though I mean it's inevitable to not
have technical issues
um
in the second year I think we mostly
will be uh
liberated from that uh by the way
speaking of technical issues can I just
say that um first of all the dongle
thingy
foreign
when I opened the packages up and all
that I I genuinely thought that the
small dongles
um were just you know like uh for I
don't know charging like I don't know I
thought it was like an extra
dead because because it made those it
already made sense to me without those
like I was able to use them without the
dongles like like like you have to
understand my my way of thinking a
little bit because the cables fit in
there without the dongle
like I was able to connect it already
without the dongle and the thing is the
they worked without the dongle as well I
just couldn't get more than two to work
you understand like The Trackers that
have free trackers and two controllers
and the three trackers needed this
dongle attached to it additionally which
is like a really really tiny tiny thingy
and
I I
I use it without and it worked it worked
so I thought the issue was I don't know
something
but I didn't think of the dongle because
in general they worked so
they just didn't get I couldn't just
connect more than two at once
dongle dongle
yeah and then the thing is also that
when uh Ina and uh AMA helped tried to
help troubleshooting me I think you know
some like two times or so maybe she
mentioned the dongle but
um I was I didn't even know what that
like what exactly she meant with that
um
um I thought you meant something like
the the the box that I already had
connected or whatever wasn't exactly
sure I thought she meant the cable or
something
and also by the way I have permission I
had permission to ask that on Twitter
and honestly I'm glad I did because
otherwise we would have been [\h__\h]
until the end because we just couldn't
figure it out on our own
yeah I guess it was just too obvious
to figure it out but I I did ask
beforehand I was like I'm in other other
people here do you think it's okay to
maybe ask because I know that there's a
lot of texting Savvy people in my
audience
do you think it's okay to ask and they
were like yeah yeah
it's okay
yeah and yeah those teasers yeah I think
they were pretty obvious anyway
because at that point we had teasers out
already with us as a Wolfie
in 3D it was just black so
[Music]
and it was my first time and I was
setting all that up on my own I knew
that it would be complicated and it was
complicated so give me a freaking break
it was very complicated to set up a lot
of things to connect and blah I have a
[\h__\h] enough cables here
it's a lot it's a lot okay okay I tried
at least it worked in the end
yeah and I was done I was done uh
actually like setting up like an hour
earlier so you know I was done
and then I just ate my pasta
yeah yeah
I mean I'm really sorry that that I like
kind of ruined their surprise but to be
honest the people you how many people
watch this from 70 70 000 people and
you're telling me that I ruined the
surprise for all of them
really
how many people saw the tweet
a couple hundred maybe and they probably
already kind of knew knew what's going
on so what the hell
don't be so dramatic
that's so dramatic and and it would have
you would have known an hour later
anyway
an hour later
well you travel to the Future one hour
ahead is that so bad
and even with that you couldn't have
known how great
what what is coming would be does that
make sense
you may have you may have understood at
that point okay it's gonna be VR but
could you have known that it's gonna be
so freaking dope with all those like
individual stages
[Music]
that huge map to work with
that that was unexpected
[Music]
eat
and the merchandise and the new outfits
and all that kind of other stuff
but it wants to do VR with us all she
said that how would we do that does she
have a wealthy model too or would she
just do it with like
her own body
[Music]
her normal
yeah now now there's like a lot of new
cool things that we can do want to try
out a lot of things but I think
this video did I read those yes I did
okay
uh yes thank you for the rest of
the camera dresses on your first
anniversary Channel you should be so
proud of all of all of you that you all
of that of all that you've accomplished
you've worked so hard though I wasn't
here from day one your compassion for
your fans and the joy you bring made you
my OC here's to many my years everyone
calls me there oh see thank
you thank you big kisses to you thank
you for your support
so sweet of you Daisy thank you for a
recipe chat mwah saying hello myth
forever bless you for not saying more
than
not judging the others but um I
appreciate a little a little bit of a
shorter one thank you thank you
thank you for the freaking rainbow thank
you
uh where do I start here good day mate
happy one year anniversary feels like it
hasn't been that long and when I decided
to follow you it was such a good
decision that I could not imagine my
life without the kfp your streams and
music those bloody ripper songs hits the
right spots every time
your voice is like sunshine that
brightens this chicken life it's like
soft raindrops that loves us to sleep
your laughter melts the heights like
gooey
chocolies chocolates oh God she's
speaking in the weird language to me
with each day endear you to us more
moreover uh you're my honesty because of
who you are and all all the nuances and
such
thank you for your heart yaka in
entertaining us an interaction on and
off of YouTube looking forward for more
Kiana and kfb shenanigans
for burping you if she hadn't we
wouldn't have you our amazing Majestic
Phoenix thank you
the language of the poet
how poetic Yucca what the hell was that
again I forgot I heard that before you
guys taught me before
thank you moving you think you think you
think you thank you thank you for all
your love thank you for listening to my
music watching my streams always being
there
thank you I'm glad to have you in kfp
work ah hard work oh
oh thank you random spy thank you for a
rainbow all these rainbows back to back
it's been five months since I joined KSP
turning to fluffy fat chicken at the end
of this month oh I enjoy every day here
with KSP and watching you stream I
really adore you takanasikiara happy
anniversary you deserve the best please
take good rest after all the hard work
you have done a little reminder do you
remember you promised for singing Karma
for me I'm looking forward to it PS I'm
playing tons of arrest every day since
released ooh it's the best Jeopardy I've
played recently thank you so much for
hyping it up and introducing it to more
people I hope I hope I was able to
introduce it to
a lot of people I hope that
I could help hmm
I'm so happy to see lots of KF peeps sad
playing tails off games can't wait to
watch you play free yeah
I'm telling you do say that too it feels
like maybe I'll add a little tiny tiny
tiny tiny effect on the sales oh only a
small one but still something is
something yeah face thank you random spy
wow did I give to you
catch it
for two pinkies
happy first anniversary I can't believe
that's been a year in this one year
you've achieved a lot overcame a lot
you've grown a lot you're such a
hard-working and strong bird this one
year you've always cheered me up it
might be the happiest year I had thanks
for your hard work thanks for being
yourself you always will be my OC yeah
looking forward to celebrating more
memorable moments in the field thank you
the happiest year really
that's that's quite an honor thank you
so much
you convinced me wouldn't have bought it
otherwise thank you the referral link
yeah I think it is I mean
[Music]
probably still working for quite some
time so go ahead and use it whenever you
feel like it
thank you and
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you for
so pinkies congrats on the one
anniversary piano look how far you've
come you've accomplished so much in just
a year I can only imagine the great
things you'll accomplished in year two
here's to another fun year at kfp Viva
La Chiara I really am glad you pushed
through those early months yeah
but it honestly so much has happened
since then I've worked so much that I
barely remember like those times like
it's it's like it's a million years ago
[Music]
your strength and perseverance is
inspiring and you're one of the most
genuine and compassionate people I've
ever seen the world could use more
people like your attention I might not
might not have been there for you David
but I'm gonna stick by you till the end
thank you that is really reassuring
thank you
I hope you will never change your mind
on that one thanks for renewing your
membership
[Music]
yes I will do my best to accomplish more
Navid I made it
um
please keep on following me and
supporting me watching
above
upon me thank you
thank you for
two four pinkies thank you
happy first anniversary Mama I'm so
happy for you in that year you create
and bring us lots of wonderful things I
learned many things from you like how to
see the light in others whoa
I love your stream and Super Chat
reading so much really makes me feel my
heart poem this Super Chat reading I
really like your personality you're so
creative and full of love my favorite
part is whatever bad thing you face you
can always bounce back like you can be
reborn I'm glad I joined kfp and tell
everyone I'm the one and one of them one
of us one of them us with confidence and
I want to be one of who's you could also
get Confidence from us to make you proud
of me now I'm excited uh I'm so excited
to the day you can bring your light and
warm to another stage I'll follow you
back forever to see more Legends you're
right
uh
thank you that's really really kind
thank you
[Music]
um
yeah I will I want I really want to
stand on the stage not only alone but
with senpai's as well and my gen mates
and maybe cool highs so please please
stay and let's watch that moment
together at some point
speed freak thank you for the red super
chat uh oh wait that's like kind of a
rainbow there's no blue but I think it's
a rainbow congratulations
[Music]
I'm here with you it was a year full of
Great Moments that were heartwarming as
they were hilarious and inspiring as
they were Silly it wasn't always easy
there were a few times when things
looked rougher than normal but like the
great Phoenix UI have shown us that
nothing keeps you down for long we've
watched you fly I Stumble grow and then
fly even higher than before thank you
for this wonderful year it's hard to
imagine what it would have been like
without you and the community you've
built around you you've inspired so many
people I hope you realize that and
you've brightened up hours I hours days
weeks months and now a whole year of so
many people's lives so here's to another
one full of Adventure review boss maybe
May the next one be more adventurous
than the first because I know you with
you it's gonna be a good one I think if
it has to be it freaking has to be
we're gonna go to Japan okay
we're gonna do more
off collapse we're gonna meet the girls
and all that
it has to be more adventurous and
exciting
other lines are right
I will not give up and let loose until I
get what I want what's so tell me what
you want what you really want I wanna I
wanna I wanna I wanna I wanna really
really really really want a free DW
[Music]
I'm with Colin thank you and Kelly's
chicken nugget thank you for two red
super chats
happy anniversary key Adam it has been
an amazing journey seeing you improve
since your W your endless joy and
perseverance are things I deeply admire
one of my favorite streams was you pick
out a drawing stream and I hope you can
continue drawing in the future you
totally feel like an idol to me and I
can't help but look forward to your
eventual 3DW in concert where you'll
have the time of your life on stage
[Music]
also despite what my name might suggest
you aren't always having my Aussie
oh keep on being incredible interesting
true your name is Callie's chicken
nugget but okay I'm your OC
well you know kfp has to has to um
Supply to a lot of people we can't only
Supply to myself
we have to give others some food as well
and you I guess you're in charge of
being countless chicken nugget that's
all right that's all right with me
thank you for your love you guys know
that I feel the um embarrassed and
nervous about my art but I don't wanna I
don't want to give it a try again every
once in a while yeah don't worry I
haven't given up on it completely
hmm
yeah yeah
thank you
yeah I mean those days better artists
than me in whole life but
I still enjoy drawing and I feel often
very inspired to draw so I want to see
thank you for the recipe
although I started watching her life not
long ago I was attracted to you after
seeing takamuri interaction at first
thank you thank you for bringing us the
best stream and bringing hope to this uh
bad year
you thank you yes
thank you I'm glad you found me and I'm
glad you decided to support me thank you
very very very much thank you
Patrick Chen thank you for two pinkies
it is now September 12 2021 10 pm jst
exactly one year since you made your
debut oh
happy one year anniversary yeah I've
seen you grow over the course of this
past year I have laughed cheered and
cried from the highs and lows we've
experienced together you've overcome so
much adversity and hardships already I
believe you are destined for great
things in life and I will be here to
cheer and support you unconditionally
and practically my honestly and to be
part of kfb
I love you guys all of you I love gave
me
I'm so happy to have you thank you
thank you for all the love
Dominique
oh that's a rainbow
where do I even start here
[Music]
where do I start
oh wait oh my God that's such a weird
coincidence because I was singing Abba
it starts here
foreign
young and sweet like Seventeen are you
playing I'm not 17. streaming Queen Feel
The Beat from the KFC Oh yay
you can sing you can live life
having the time of your life
oh see that girl watch that scene being
the streaming Queen
[Music]
nice beautiful and the streaming Queen
hell yeah I am hell yeah
now DM said dmca you're not welcome here
close the door close the door on the way
out the MCA bye-bye
bye-bye
and so you say besides that message from
nice cream Hamilton I'm a high school
student who is preparing for the college
entrance examination so I don't have
much time watching the stream but I love
listening to your stream on the way to
school it gives you so much fun and
power can you give can can you give to
all the examination candidates some
encouragement in Chinese which is thank
you I love you wait one second I forgot
how to pronounce them
yes I can
[Music]
share
you cannot believe in yourself
I believe in you
good luck
[Music]
and good night here's the blessing from
Cafe 2007 on the Discord actually and we
have more than three thousand now oh you
ground my personal regret is I didn't
meet you earlier but I'd love to stay
with kfb and Tanger as long as I can
congratulations of your one year
anniversary oh thank you
happy wait oh that's it oh yeah that's
it
[Music]
fair I remember
I remember
all the support thank you thanks so much
thank you best helicopter ever
[Music]
um
so that this coin
[Music]
don't start hero thank you for the red
super chant happy one year anniversary
Tango it's been a wonderful year to
spend with you filled with tons of of up
and downs on my end oh on my end too but
you've been a big inspiration for
helping me get my life back on track
well while I will miss the stream due to
my job I hope you have the best time
thank you so much good luck with your
job and I hope there will be only UPS in
the future but down Unfortunately
they they belong to life and without
without amps without Downs there would
be no UPS so yeah it is what it is good
luck thank you we're there for thank you
for the pinky since you recently
mentioned my previous board oh my
[\h__\h] God I have to ask did his late
nights that's his inability to talk
about anything influence your style as a
picture when joking of course happy
first anniversary can't you answer many
more friends honestly I was so young I
barely remember that but I just know
that he had a really low voice and was
so sad and depressed and it was an
interesting children's TV show yeah I
did like him though because he was kind
of cool he did speak to me you know in a
different way that no one else could
I connected with him yeah
yeah
and Princess almost over 90 I think
that's it
thank you for the pinky happy first
anniversary thank you for your working
hard and for being you and thank you for
bringing my days your amazing brilliant
inspirational to another year of
depression slaying Excellence from my
Aussie honor to be careful
I wanted to have you although your gum
under the table so
that's uh I I guess it I guess it's part
of like a normal fast food restaurant
huh yeah you're an important part of a
fast food restaurant it's like without
you kfp would be nothing
yes I think we're still in preach at him
pretty sure yeah
uh thank you
um thank you for the pinky happy
anniversary 10 so it's my greatest luck
to meet you I will keep on supporting
you no matter what people like yeah
I will take that as a promise thank you
for your support
thank you hi why thank you for the red
super chat
and a pinky actually happy one year
anniversary thank you for your stream so
glad to know you can too I really love
your stream that always makes me feel
cheerful Viva La Quiana
[Music]
I'm glad you found me please keep on
supporting me I will do my best and work
hard
mmm
as again
[Music]
foreign
ministers
[Music]
one
a Bali Bali thank you for the pinky when
I first got to Novi was I had many
options but I've come came to you out of
all those YouTubers because you're the
warmest one oh I guess because I'm a
phoenix thanks to everyone for my time
when the egg is almost up now because I
was sitting on you huh under my butt
see you outside and happy first
anniversary mama
[Applause]
[Music]
so sweet yeah thank you
thank you for choosing me there's really
a lot of people to choose from yeah you
choose me thank you
my name is Sarah and thank you for the
pinky
hi how's your girl the link every day
you're blazing hot chat with us with
Embrace of kindness roaring passion and
light akin to a warm embrace your
luminous Sun I why are you being so
poetic
and it's never dimming still growing
blessing us with life I hope our love
Stokes your fire too happy when you
Kiana
wow what got you what got into you being
so poetic love it thank you
Bradley Bradley thank you for the two
pinkies
happy one year anniversary to the cutest
Empire by hard to believe it's been an
entire year already but through all
trials and tribulations endured you've
remained a bright bacon a bacon of
creativity and fun for so many it's been
an amazing year with you and I can't
thank you enough for all the smiles
laughs and joy you bring you brought to
my life and I'm so proud to call you my
Aussie I'll continue to support you
until the very end thank you for being a
part of my life love you always Kiana
[Music]
thank you so much for your support
I will never forget the time when you
were a polar Airlines when you became
holy airlines in the free chat of me
flying from Japan to Australia I will
never forget never forgold
Ginger Ranger thank you for the rainbow
starting with a red one
yeah I love that that was so much fun to
read
hey boss what else I think it's been a
year a year filled with smiles laughter
shrieks Shreks
tears and rages a year filled with
soaring highs and disheartened lows a
year you went through with a Grace that
is befitting of a phoenix though we know
it hasn't been all Sunshine for you so
thank you thank you for the sleepless
nights see you you're welcome thank you
for the days upon days of work we never
fully see
thank you for being unabashedly you
thank you for the effort uh to be
vivacious every stream what does that
mean
thank you for the honesty
when you can't be
thank you for venting to us when you
need it thank you for listening to our
wishes thank you for swiftly blocking
chat because we 100 serve it
thank you for being an absolute gentler
is a Precious part of our day thank you
for making me want to get up with the
sun and green today with a boisterous
I hope another year
passes just as joyfully as this one did
Viva La Canada
[Music]
I'm sorry for giving you sleepless
nights but I'm glad you'll always watch
my streams thank you for being here
beautiful beautiful it makes sense that
you want the wedding of our
scriber because this sounds like a
wedding wow
beautiful thank you for all the kind
words
hmm
I hope I hope I can entertain you in the
future too
you seem to appreciate all of me even
when I'm down or even when I vent to you
guys so thank you for that I'm so kind I
wish I could hug you thank you and
you're here
we're here
thank you
[Music]
Jay swagburg thank you for the pinky
congrats on the one on one year Kiara
your 10 is our legendary and admire you
open as an honesty thanks for all the
amazing working care you put into making
this community Thrive best wishes to you
the wonderful Phoenix foreign
I hope it will be a great one and I am
I'm so glad that there's more time that
I can spend with you guys
I hope I hope it will be a great year
let's make it a great one shall we
got yourself thank you for your red
Super Chat happy anniversary boss I wish
I'd been here since the start but
because of your genuine love for your
fans I'll be here for the rest of your
time here we're good and bad thank you
for all the hard work you put in for us
and for being the wonderful person you
are I can only do that because you guys
make it worth it you guys make it
worthwhile I feel like when I work hard
you guys appreciate it and you see the
effort so that's why I like working hard
for you guys thank you guys
thank you for a red Super Chat
congratulations on your first
anniversary thank you for all the hard
work you put into everything you do
you're such a sweet and amazing person
my day always gets better after every
stream I really wish I could have found
you sooner here's some more years okay
don't worry about it
you know that's two people in a row who
say they found me later on don't worry
about you can watch all the archives in
the past but I wouldn't even recommend
it because I don't know I don't I don't
I think I'm funnier now and more
entertaining now and then better now so
yeah but if you ever ever feel like it
you can watch just all of the old
archives
and ask yourself why was she so shitty
at Minecraft
[Music]
foreign
I've only been here for nine months but
it's been an incredible time I credit
you and my kids with keeping me sane
over the last year same yo my cats and
you guys
are what kept me sane
I can't wait to see what the future
holds me too I mean I already know some
things that the future holds
I can see the future
um
I didn't I don't know all the details
but I see in the future and I'm looking
forward to it
[Music]
that's our magical yes
cats
that's really our magical let me eat a
cookie no not a cookie but like a
um
something like a cookie
I need a snack I need a freaking snack
I don't know how that would be a hint
just me wanting wanting to say yeah
oh yeah
[Music]
can't believe Kiana's moving to Texas no
who knows maybe it's clouds are we maybe
I'm going to Calgary
[Music]
not in the my okay excuse me should I
mute myself okay
[Music]
ah wait I forgot
we're doing here no
[Music]
hmm
yeah
[Music]
good crunch
this is the closest we get to as the
market
yeah
sorry for the people who
genuinely like ASMR I'm so sorry to you
guys
foreign
[Music]
before
but it would not be normal is that how
you pronounce it
[Music]
by normal
bye bye
[Music]
PC specs ASMR remember that tonight
we're doing Minecraft
I remember I remember
um
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
I would drop beats I went no
I love your voice thank you
I feel like I would probably get
addicted to it
did Amelia never consider playing that
because if like I wonder if we had
permissions I felt like she would have
played it by now nah maybe not I'm
always not necessarily the music type is
she
does she play Beat saber
it's a good workout
I'm not here to do workout are you
trying to force me to work out
secretly but by trying to you know get
me to do something fun with music and
then it's like a workout and like I'm
like yo
what
[Music]
oh I didn't think this would be so
exhausting
[Music]
gouda wants to okay
um
comments on your ear and more have
become thanks for making kfb a place of
Misfits can hang out Misfits
you're not Misfits I curve my fellow
chickens I see what you did there and
that's just that's really old the club
thing
does have helped me overcome oh one of
my fears I was safe in every possible
way that a person can be Rose Dawson
whoa
I'm glad I could help you thank you
red thank you for two pinkies mwah happy
one year anniversary potential I'm not
great at words so please bear with me
one year ago it seems so silly that I
would be working under Phoenix with
girls of dominating the fast food bag
yeah and yet here I am jumped by her
crank personality and dedication to
everything she touches especially to her
own community no words can express how
much of an inspiration for happiness and
growth you are for me all I can say is
that I am grateful for who you are and
have become here's to one more year
thank you yeah who would have known
who would have known it's only been a
year what would what would your one and
a half yourself think about where you
are now supporting me
[Music]
that one and a half year ago you would
probably be like
come on can it help you go by a little
bit faster I want to have fun let's go
you think Google gaga
confused
now you're living the fun life now let's
go
[Music]
thank you thank you for the red super
chat thank you soon
maska
[Music]
um what
oh wait no no no no Chinese
[Music]
thank you for your support
oh my God
[Music]
foreign
I have a feeling like a gist of who I
can trust and who I cannot trust
until now it has always worked out this
way
um that's good
you come into my boring ass Super Chat
reading huh
[Music]
scored your Discord my like I've had
this weird message I don't know what it
means
my neutral ran out I think
wait I think it actually ran out for
real today
no
problem of course just I don't know what
that means
was it neutral neutral
there's Nitro scabs talk to you know who
who who should I talk to I guess I'll
talk to my manager
Nitro
I I will I will wait does that mean I
can't use my animated stuff right now
can I use my animated
[Music]
can I use it yeah I can still use it
around the past few days oh maybe it has
been reactivated because the message is
gone
maybe it was reactivated the past few
days I saw this orange message at the
top that says yeah you're you're a
Knight trailer so it's running out you
gotta give us your payment uh thingy
[Music]
I reactivated
to wish someone's name to be on the
golden list often when a person is going
to take an important exam oh wait
there's some There's an actual like
golden list where people with the best
results around or what does that mean
that's cool that's interesting oh you
will be on the golden list if I have to
I'll just engrave your name by myself
yes
I'll do it I'll do it for you
well here my name is already on the
golden plate here thank you
see that on my table look at it
look at it
pretty sure it's illegal okay but are
you saying that my name plate is illegal
it can't be
oh
[Music]
my name is
foreign
[Music]
wow but actually that's more than one
that's two thank you
until one year ago you became a shining
bacon shining Beacon sorry I always
think of bacon when I see that that we
as a current KFC employee did not
deserve how you entertain us during each
employee's darkest times have you
facility at each single collab to the
next level cannot believe how long this
has been
you missed the letter I still remember
vividly when you talk about the idea of
whole talk
and how you executed it to New
Perfection from the get girl happy one
year anniversary kfp is one step closer
to World Domination it's pretty cool to
see like how I start
um like thinking about doing something
and then I actually do it and it works
out nicely yeah that's pretty cool
um
it's nice to see a result
yeah thank you very much
big kisses to you
you guys need to stop talking about
bacon though I'm getting hungry always
constantly
the reveal was really cool yeah I
remember the first time I did whole talk
you guys were so blown away by the
opening and the set and all that and
that was like the worst whole talk
debate because it was the first one it
was like a pilot episode
[Music]
got improved so much afterwards
um
[Music]
is next guest by the way pretty
pretty cool huh I was uh
and I was holding back on inviting her
for a while because I felt like I I'm
not even ready for it felt like I'm not
ready for it and I want to everyone told
Trump to be as as good as it can be when
I invite her and I think it reached a
point where you know it's definitely
something to show off so I I oh I have
to stop I start I have to start uh
always I should do it now today can I do
it right now the question tweet because
I've been streaming all freaking day
foreign
[Music]
tweet that I did and then
uh
be that basically
[Music]
this whole talk that idea
that I did quite quite a while ago now
foreign
looking for it
[Music]
scroll scroll
squirrel can take it
I found it
[Music]
now I need to find the question tweet
there it is okay
so Twitter
foreign
[Music]
okay I think that's fine
for me okay
now let's do it on YouTube
[Music]
uh Channel community
find the most recent one there it is
copy
tweeting
Twitter
questions for this week's episode with
soda
[Music]
foreign
I think that's all I had to change
[Music]
image and whole talk there we go
should we post it
foreign
[Music]
already a question noise is it a good
one let's see
[Music]
what that's oh that's that's not a
question
[Music]
okay post it on the community board
let me put that
underneath the tweet on Twitter
English questions here please
there you go
[Music]
okay okay
now let's continue
[Music]
letters happy one anniversary
thank you for the red super chat I can't
believe it's been one year that's 41
million 546
000 seconds and counting of you being
with us wow that's a lot I can't believe
I spent each and every one of those
seconds of you in my mind
oh I love you so much you don't
understand
thank you thank you
I hope you can get your mind off of me
sometimes though
but never forget me and don't miss my
streams
[Music]
so much for your love
I appreciate it
we finally reached hookah Papa's tweet
foreign
[Music]
that I would be oh so happy if I could
get a surprise call surprise call from
hookah Papa uh but I don't want to ask
him on on my own because I don't want to
pressure him to say yes so I would want
management to ask him and then leave it
to him whether or not he says yes or no
and I also understand if he says no so
that's totally fine but just then just
don't tell me and then just surprise me
with it if he does
um want to come and turns out in the end
it was no surprise because I they're
um
they told me about that he said yes
and then I plant him into my schedule so
the surprise was not not much more of a
surprise
um but
I was glad he said yes
yeah cause I can totally understand if
he would say no simply even just because
you know it's it's just kind of like
I understand if he would be too nervous
to like you know because of the whole
Minecraft ship that went down in the
past I can totally understand if he says
no but everyone was so excited what
happened on the call everyone was so
positive and welcoming about it so I'm
really glad and I hope that he enjoyed
it too
um
um yes yes yes I'm glad it happened me
too
yeah he seemed very shy but it was fun
to talk to him
[Music]
yeah I'm really glad I could include him
and my mama in the anniversary stream
[Music]
to me
especially hookah Papa because that was
the first time we ever talked like we we
do communicate a lot to uh like on
Twitter via text
um to talk about you know
things that have to do with work
um but and we get along very well but
yeah we never talked
yeah it made the stream really great it
did it made it so special and he he
provided so much great content
with the with the drafts I thought that
was really really interesting to see
wasn't it
yeah so thank you thank you okay Papa
although you won't see this probably
Sean Ian
[Music]
I think that's at least a pinky so let
me read it I have to believe that just
one year ago you were so unsure of
yourself that you questioned if all that
many people would even bother wanting
you unaware of your potential driving
many people like me to want to follow
you now you have an army of of over a
million loyal fans who would follow you
to the end of the Earth I know it's easy
to get overcome with self-doubt but I
want you to never forget how truly
capable you are Kiana thank you
you have a personality that shines like
the sun sparking the fires of passion in
the hearts of your fans you certainly
inspired me to want to better myself as
a person and for that I am thankful
happy anniversary Kiana thank you for
the sweet words I appreciate it thank
you
thank you thank you so much
[Music]
for a sec thank you for a red Super Chat
well you've already been told so many
warm words and I can only help you won't
forget even for a second how much you
mean for the kfp employees so don't get
upset over small things and take good
care of your health happy anniversary
attention
paying you
thank you let me sleep thank you
lunchbox okay
this is this should be where pre-chat
was pretty much over because I saved it
before the Stream
ah
[Music]
um
so one second let me reorganize my
sheets
I mean there might still be a few more
but they should have come in like
yeah very close
to the stream so
let me get rid of that
I'm gonna move those up
[Music]
oh my God
okay let's see how yeah we have what 650
something left
how many did I reach now 258 of those
anniversary
wow so so how long did that take me
how long did those anniversary super
chats take me those 200 something
huh
where the hell am I
pretty oh my God
but does that not include the tales of a
right super chats and so on are you sure
about that
you guys understand
we're bringing Holo talk
[Music]
uh old Members First Japanese members
mainly
if you have questions we'll move it I'm
sure she's gonna do a marshmallow at
some point
probably surely
[Music]
I'll just wait for that William
okay
let's read some more I'm not done yet I
still have energy I can probably if I
want to I could probably go for 12 hours
but I want to eat some food in between
and also we can
we can more more tomorrow
[Music]
for four to five hours and then read
some budget and the day after tomorrow
as well
[Music]
and what I have to say is that it was
one of the best years for me and also my
love for you has only grown
thank you so I'm going crazy happy one
year birthday
I guess it's somehow a birthday too yeah
continue to be the amazing person you
are YouTube wouldn't let me write
everything I wanted that's right
you can write more on Twitter so if you
want
[Music]
I'm scared that people will get sick of
me you guys know that so it's very
rarely reassuring to hear that you guys
gotta keep on saying that stuff to me
okay please please please you guys I
don't have to know I'm I'm I'm I go
crazy about these kind of things so
please reassure me uh every second day
that you still love me
[Music]
thanks for the pinky it's strange to me
that I spent a whole year in Hell
working for a red rooster
oh Red Rooster
now I work for orange Phoenix and miss
her when I can't catch her streams who's
the red Crystal
[Music]
no no he talks about me and says orange
things
foreign
[Music]
actual restaurant it's not a reference
to something huh
oh that's funny
I miss her when I can't want to catch
her streams I might be a bit attached
but I'm glad I found kfp come visit
upside down Australia someday oh hell
[\h__\h] yeah I'm so ready to go but your
guys is like um
um borders are like so so tough to to
pass you know make it easier for me to
come over and I'll get over there in an
instant
I want only Australia is definitely one
of my top five countries that want to
visit
who I haven't visited yet which I
haven't visited yet yeah yeah
[Music]
sorry I'm I'm weird now do you know
foreign
[Music]
really really adorable aren't
um
and this the other day she posted a
piece of art that was well let's just
say my upper body was only covered with
two big Band-Aids and she didn't tag it
but I still saw it because I follow her
on Twitter
so I asked her to please uh draw
more uh draw me in a way that I can use
it for my thumbnail
why didn't you retweet it yeah that was
that kind of crossed the line I would
love to retweet it but I felt like that
was that that goes a little bit too far
normally I would totally retweet it yeah
those bobots they look so soft like
marshmallows but that's generally Tio
maro's son's style she always draws like
everything looks like marshmallows
[Music]
I mean
um
oh bye
I don't know
thank you thank you for the red super
Chateau happy anniversary your Majestic
Phoenix your first year is complete and
you have come such a long way you've
been able to push through all the high
tips and create many amazing friendships
and memories
hope you have another uh year of amazing
events I love you thank you
thank you I want I wanted to be
memorable
but that doesn't come automatically so I
will have to put my own work into it as
well
thank you thank you
[Music]
hello to your little sister
hello thank you for watching
[Music]
I love you so cute
thank you
crash thank you for the reasonable chat
as well I heard that I was going to get
fired if I didn't come here Jokes Aside
congratulations on this amazing first
year you have accomplished many
incredible things during this time kfb
will be with you for the rest of your
journey salute
say it
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
oh
Antonio
[Music]
foreign
no
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
inflation message but I'm not gonna I'm
sure you'll get a million of those today
so instead I'll give you a brief reprise
reprieve who's happiness or something
silly the other day thank you the other
day I was talk about you possibly rating
the fashion of KFC what you said you
were more interested in women's fashion
and men's does that mean you want to see
us gentlemen and dresses I've done it
before and I'll do it again
oh that's not what I meant
with people dressing themselves in
dresses but please don't do it for me
okay
don't
no honestly I think
I mean something something that really I
think looks good is uh
suits
no need to wear a dress
[Music]
buying a suit and have a suit
you don't have a suit
foreign
I don't know if I'm really gonna do a
fashion that was like more like a like a
joke
um but I don't want to do something of
the community and like a review of
something but I don't want to do the
reveal but that seems like a little bit
too General I want to come up with
something a little bit more original but
still something that everyone can
participate in how about how about I
could I could also challenge you guys to
cooking something again
like a burger
yeah kfb burger I'm like remember the
first time when we came up with
phoenixburg and yaggle burger there were
like a lot of people making it and
posting pictures of that
oh yes and maybe I'll combine that with
me myself making a phoenix oriago Burger
on stream yeah I definitely want to do
that yeah that's one of my plans some of
the things I want to cook on stream are
abruga I also want to make a pizza and
uh I wanna
try to make Eva schnitzel or tonkatsu
[Music]
um
yeah and uh some desserts as well of
course
oh and yeah we should just make a fried
chicken
yum will you make the Buns yourself no I
doubt that I will make those myself I
would need a freaking but I don't I
don't want to get a bread machine
[Music]
because that one time when I uh had the
chance to eat fresh self-made bread
it was really [\h__\h] good yeah Julian
congratulations thank you for your hard
work and the amazing content you put out
I'm sure it helps
it helps and take care thank you I will
do my best thank you you take care too
please
always put yourself first
your health is very important you're not
a phoenix like me so be careful
[Music]
thank you for the reasonable chat happy
first anniversary potential in the past
year and we tend to stream with positive
and energy encourages me impress your
life thank you for all your efforts to
give us the best show thank you but
please don't
overwork yourself
I know that um
especially in
those those kind of cultures where
you're from
like eight Asian cultures that there's a
lot of pressure uh with like work life
and all that like uh over time working
overtime and also you know getting the
best grade and all that so
um I hope that you can and
shut up
but yeah I hope I hope that you can um
feel free and happy and not be too
pressured
[Music]
um so I know it's tough I can I can see
that
how Society might make you feel
pressured but I hope you can overcome
that
and not let it take control of you thank
you Dominique
Duncan C is fully in other words thank
you
I hope all homemade can have 3D life
soon me too wait we kind of did like
right after that stream look forward to
your performance with other Helena stage
uh Viva Lucky had a glory to Cafe thank
you it's it's not the same but it was
already one step in that direction I
guess
it was it was partially so surreal
because
I didn't think it would be possible to
really
have this feeling of being together in a
realm but it did kind of feel like that
like we were able to maybe not like
physically touch one another but we were
able to run around and and follow one
another Chase one another cheer for one
another act as if we were hugging one
another and all that it was really
surreal it was very interesting I never
had that before because I didn't try
stuff like that before like VR chat and
all that yeah so it's it's one step in
that direction it was already great fun
and and really special but it definitely
uh would be something else to actually
meet in RL I I can imagine the moment
that once the internet will all cry
[Music]
the whole life Japan members and whole
life Indonesia members who can meet one
another
so easily so quickly
yeah
um
foreign
[Music]
it's just yeah
I mean
I think maybe like I don't know I don't
know how far away our Australians live
from one another and you know others may
be in the same country as well
uh
but I don't know if like they actually
will take advantage of living in the
same country I think I think there's at
least at least a few members who live in
the same continent now
L definitely something and yet I'm still
alone in Europe how the [\h__\h] did that
happen
[Music]
thank you for the membership welcome
I don't get it
so everybody
no words but thank you I appreciate it
[Music]
foreign
thank you
thank you thank you
root epic one two one three five times
thank you for the pinky happy
anniversary potential thanks for all the
fun moments and all your songs I love
your personality and thank you you work
really hard and we'll keep supporting
and loving you really thank the world
for letting me meet you I'm so happy
for the same thing that you guys were
able to find me
um
was kind of lonely before joining her
life
I felt like not
like not non-existent you know like I
was invisible
and now I feel so
visible
yeah which can be scary very scary as
well but
at the same time it's so rewarding so
thank you
99.99 thank you for the red super chat
happy one year anniversary thank you for
everything you did in your hard work we
through we've been for a lot but one
thing that never changes is that we
always love you
oh thank you for celebrating with me and
being there for me and supporting me
thank you
tiny Delta thank you for the recipe for
Chad one of the two
where's the other one
I don't see it oh there it is really far
up there
okay number one says when I think back
of these past 365 days I can only think
of one word privileged I'm so glad I was
here to witness the tangents that read
them used the inside jokes the whole
talks the Transformations and frog you
collapse your music your art and scroll
up
uh your thoughts and opinions your
dedication towards whole life and all
that entails and everything else you've
given to us this has surely been a
wonderful year and I hope we can share
many more merry years together happy
anniversary Kiana I hope so too let's do
our best Let's Stay Together Forever
guys I do not allow you to leave
you're not dismissed you're not fired
stay yeah thank you
foreign
[Music]
I met my incredible people and you
inspired me to become a more considerate
and heartful person myself wow one who
reaches Health helps others and pursues
his goals thanks for pushing me to give
it my all I'm glad you might want to see
you thank you you helped out a lot with
the whole docomo thing so thank you for
making that happen in the first place
thank you so much I appreciate your
support
thank you
big kiss to you
it sounds to me like the German word for
[\h__\h] which is which is I always feel a
little bit uncomfortable saying it
maybe I should just saying
that doesn't sound so much like yeah
[Music]
dances with Vocaloids
ah
[Music]
um
wait a second
[Music]
thank you
thank you for making us smile since they
wanted you happy anniversary
you've been there
thank you
see you in the next anniversary and
every day in between okay okay
[Music]
you're crazy
happy one year anniversary tangible
thanks for all the fun times you've
given us since your debuted honestly
there's so much already that it's
difficult to remember remember every
single one yeah yeah
but even then I can't wait for more fun
times by hand love your attention yeah
cause every freaking stream there's
always something uh fun and memorable I
mean there's definitely streams that are
more memorable than others but I think I
still think that every stream
um has something special
so it's just like a bit sad that they
just all melt together into one blob of
memory
but at least we're trying to enjoy every
day one after another step by step right
yeah
Alex thank you soon
thank you thank you
what are you doing 400
[Music]
and no words with it
thank you
sleepy running donation is
[Music]
foreign
note to self
request perms for emoji again
because I asked the Japanese surprise if
there is like a game that they feel like
they that that uh I should play in a
Japanese only stream and especially like
games that are that only exist in
Japanese that would make sense
and there's this game that's
um
some Japanese members have played on
their streams before you know the whole
permission thing got very serious
and I would love to play that on the
stream but I don't think we have
permission because I feel like if we had
permissions they those members who
played it before would have played at
the big End by now
but I will give it a try
I love how you message General as your
personality and I sent her the food
pictures that I want to show you guys
yeah it's very useful
because
[Music]
what game are you talking about Uncle
yo I love your art
young Dao thank you
thank you
[Music]
soldier soldier man one one thank you
for the pinky well let's go one year
yeah let's go
Alita thank you for the rest of the chat
happy one year thank you this is
definitely where the stream started
Elena thank you for celebrating with me
[Music]
I appreciate the support
strapping dinosaurs
and it's a magic thank you for the pinky
congrats on one year cancel you're the
best boss always thinking about us first
I hope you can be more selfish this
coming here and treat yourself more
I will try as you you guys if if if I
were able to travel this whole year I
would I would be probably away a lot
I would probably leave you guys for a
lot of vacations anyway so as soon as
traveling is easy again I'll be I'll be
in the air constantly and at the ocean
I'll be even in the air or in the ocean
yes
I'll bring you guys with me with my
Alienware laptop
I'll bring you guys move me don't worry
and we'll probably still take a while
until traveling is easy
yeah yeah
[Music]
no thank you love you too thank you
thank you
Mabel Cipher Danke Schoen Bruno Schubert
thank you for the rest of potato
it's within a year it's been a year
already time to go ahead and give myself
a raise then
you understand the logical I think
thanks for being so understanding and
lighting up so many lives with your
Phoenix Fire Burns love you thank you
love you too you're welcome to give
yourself a raise because we both know
what that means I think
mm-hmm
okay
[Music]
so Bruno
spider
spider thank you thank you for a year of
fun entertaining stream Central every
second of the time you've chosen to
spend with us has been very precious to
me to me as well I haven't felt a
passion like yours in a very long time
wow thank you
I'm so happy to hear that that just
reminds me of you know the passion that
I had for my Oshi back in the day thank
you
[Music]
thank you for the pinky comment on your
one year anniversary attention here's to
many more thank you hopefully yeah many
many more I can live very long so I'm up
for it I don't know about you guys when
I do know I kind of do know you guys say
you wanted to listen long but oh
[Music]
no me no worry me no me not me Nadi
and but but nice catch nice catch
and cheese
I'm so proud of you boss thanks for
spending this wonderful year with us
thank you for spending it with me
especially the people who watch like so
many or almost all or all of my streams
I can't imagine how many hours you've
spent with me
and I'm really glad you like designed to
do that overdoing other things
tough you guys need some like Anonymous
kfb addicts group where you like hello I
am and I'm addicted to Kiana
um but then the goal of the group is not
really to stop and it's just to talk
about it I guess but why would you want
to stop it yeah right
oh I feel like maybe kfp needs that kind
of group
hmm
during the acceptance stage and that's
good you all should accept it that you
can't change it
it must happen naturally
stay addicted to me but I think um for
now that's cool
it's not an addiction as well
[Music]
really
is it the face though I hope it's not a
face I want to be more than just a face
for you
[Music]
no no no no no no no no it's not gonna
be the usual room don't worry also I
want to change the BTM thank you for
renewing your membership
foreign
[Music]
that's the bamboo cutting music oh I
like it it's actually yeah pretty nice
one
maybe that's our last sports music
for me I'll read maybe 100 more Super
chats I'll try my goal is to read
hundred more which normally is not much
but when there's so many pings and reds
it is a lot
and Thomas one G1 thank you for the red
super chat happy anniversary channel
it's hard to believe and has already
been uh a year since debut but by the
way five five free right now let's get
to four five three
thanks for the year uh all the hard work
so put your attention yeah tangents
always a big part of takanasukiyana
and apparently they will never leave me
thank you
[Music]
hello Vlog thank you for the rest of the
chat happy anniversary thank you this
year has been the first decent one
decent one of my out of life thanks to
you thank you so much for how amazing
you've been and I'm so freaking glad the
experience has helped you too proud to
be careful now and forever here's to the
Future yay thank you I'm glad I'm glad
you're having such a great time here
with me and the others thank you
[Music]
I've already said so much but let's go I
still can't believe it's really been a
year and oh nice cafe of this thank you
I love this office
I love it so much
even Excel really works fast he's so
kind to make this for free for me it's
so sweet
both the kitchen and the office were on
my list of things I want to commission
eventually but it would have taken a
long time for me to get to it
because I've been so busy
but then suddenly I had it right in
front of me
without having to do anything
yeah yeah there's a lot of details but
he still says he's gonna add more yeah
[Music]
yeah
I want to put um next time I want to put
some more videos over there I'm gonna
put hinodori and heart challenge out
there in the two screens that I'm
missing
and in the top right screen I mean we
can always leave space for super chats
but
mmm
I don't know gotta think about it it's
because the the gray background kind of
bothered me
maybe we could also
replace it with
like a like a white board
or so
instead of the like not the not the cork
board like that that one can stay but
like a white board above like a tiny one
oh wait we could oh we could actually
have a place somewhere here for my my
weekly schedule
[Music]
maybe like a calendar we could put a
calendar that way kind of where I can
replace my weekly schedule hmm you're in
the room CCT oh that's a good idea yo I
could yeah and that TV up there I could
put my I could put like a live cam of
the usual room
[Music]
but I also want the the weekly schedule
somewhere
maybe it's like a sort of calendar
hanging somewhere but it's already so
crowded I'm not sure where to put it on
the table
um maybe get rid of one stack of these
papers and put a calendar there
or hang it behind me somewhere
like somewhat breathable though so not
it's not gonna work because it's gonna
be so small
top right
I don't wanna I don't want it to look
too crowded you know anyway I wanted to
read super chance
07 hold on
[Music]
John's from kfbank Andreas gracias
for the pinky happy one year anniversary
thank you
bro thank you for the rest of my channel
happy one year anniversary thank you for
all the great times this past year and
for spending time with us on your
Eternal Phoenix Adventure
here's to an amazing second year for my
OC you've inspired me to work more on
myself and for that I'm eternally
grateful thank you
thank you you can't believe I have such
an impact on you guys but that's that's
great that's awesome please please just
just live your life to the fullest
potential
um
thank you so much
thank you for the rest of the chat wow
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
being along the ride has been a pleasure
even when it was tough and it was all
worth it to see how for you to see
how for you managed to come what and
what comes next I can only imagine
here's the number
let's go thank you so much
thank you thank you thank you I want to
take more care of myself in the coming
year though
yes take more breaks I think I messed up
no problem I get I get the message I
want to take more breaks and I want to
go to the doctor
thank you Jacob
102117 Mr shadow
dancers
and Sonic fan 53 thank you
is it a capital I I think so if he X
thank you for the red silver chat
overall happy one year birthday thank
you for all the moments during this year
you helped me through difficult times
into a more years to come really a lot
more years since Phoenix is zone five
yeah yeah yeah but I don't know if you
guys know you guys do die so
I I I'll even have to give you some
Phoenix feathers
Turtles you will have to give you guys
Phoenix feathers or we'll figure out a
deal with the underworld so that you
guys can continue supporting me as
ghosts
Maybe
we'll figure something out thank you if
you
know
thank you
congratulations and thank you for a year
of wholesome awesomeness I'm looking
forward to more from my wonderful
Phoenix plus and all of her friends both
old and new keep up the Fantastic work
Viva La Quiana
forever huh
thank you for your support thank you for
believing in me
and following and watching me I
appreciate it
please continue doing so and I will do
my best
[Music]
um
don't fire me
you're a bit late but it's fun I love
you so much also congrats on that one
year I might not have followed you for
the first two weeks but your Charming
Beauty has made me go camping for life
oh but it doesn't mean you were only two
weeks late that's no problem that's
still like basically the beginning that
counts as you were here from the
beginning yes
you can you can call yourself kfp from
the beginning
thank you for staying here it means so
much to me thank you Lord evoke thank
you for the pinky as well
you're so blessed with amazing moments
and challenges overcome that feels a lot
longer I expected to lose interest on
YouTubers fast yet here I am oh I'm I'm
relieved
oh well thanks to you my dear OC the
stream is the best birthday present I
could have it was your birthday
happy belated birthday
congratulations
oh that that means that you know the the
five-member collaboration will must have
also kind of been like a like a birthday
present even though it was for you
probably past midnight but still wait
were you even awake for that
that was really late
at 2 30.
one 2 30 a.m I think because we delayed
it for half an hour
I was awake for way too long I'll try to
sleep a bit earlier today I was not yet
able to fix my schedule not yet
you know what I'll do after this stream
I'll eat my chili con carne and I'll
take a bath
and then a really hot bath I'll watch
some Netflix in the bath and then I'll
go back to my bed put on like a
um my I have a lavender shoulder thingy
that you put in the microwave I barely
ever use it
but I will try to use it today maybe the
lavender will give me a possibility to
sleep longer and I'll take the the
medicine even though I I don't even feel
like I need it for my pain anymore but
maybe it will me fall asleep so
I'll combine all that
and so maybe then we can sleep at four
a.m instead of 6 30 a.m like last night
that's at least an improvement that
would already be two and a half hours
Improvement
we have a sleeping mask I have that
lavender thing uh that you put on your
shoulders uh I have that and I have also
the same thing for my eyes I bought it
at the same place
I bought it in some like in Japan in in
like a herb
herbal shop thingy yeah it's really nice
but I don't really use it much because
I'm even even too lazy to put it in the
[\h__\h] microwave and it's [\h__\h] hot
too the one for the eyes
I used
um something similar that's a one-time
only use and I bought it in convenience
stores in Japan I used it before but I
didn't really sound you feel like it
made me fall asleep faster it's actually
like a little bit too uncomfortable
because it's a little bit too hot
um I don't know if they have that kind
of stuff in your country guys but in
Japan it's quite popular
you open it up and it immediately gets
hot it's like a sheet mask for your eyes
it gets really really hot
it was too hot for my taste
and I would focus on the hotness so I
don't know which actually has the
opposite effect
oh they smell well they really do they
do they do they do
like a pop hand warmer yeah kind of like
that but just for your eyes with some of
them have like a scent like lavender or
something else to help you fall asleep
or relieve some pain and stress yeah 40
degrees I think yeah
focusing on the happiness
focus on these guys
Focus
where was I
I lost track of my super chat so much
for focusing
[Music]
on here
happy anniversary tension has been such
a fun year fellow of laughing and forgot
Unforgettable moments did I already read
this
I can't thank you enough for all your
hard work and being so genuine I'll
support you for many years to come love
you thank you thank you
I'm glad I'm glad that me being so
genuine
isn't that like too upsetting for you
guys
focus on your nose now on my hotness
baby thank you coffee to the dinosaur
with Dinosaurs
protect the vision apartment
[Music]
for the red super chat thank you
happy first anniversary Kiana thank you
for blessing those chickens with your
presents entertaining streams and music
you set up right in amazing Phoenix
you've been you have been and will
always be my Aussie if that's okay
why are you studying of course it's okay
please please support me love me
watch me cloak I said yolk
foreign
[Music]
much love to you thank you
it's like it
Ah that's completely it's missing the
red one but that's fine
where should I start reading
at the bottom I suppose sorry for the
little rainbows oh what I can afford
don't worry it's still a rainbow
it's a red color just kidding
a couple of words into a family streams
about three months ago it was a very
hard time for me was hard to even get up
at mornings and get to work but your
energy your light you warmth breathed
life into me then I heard your songs
there beautiful and expressively
precious and then you released Sparks
and something changed in me oh
now I have a team again and I want this
dream to come true well it's all because
of you potential I want to tell you my
appreciation for everything you do
you're just being you that's enough to
make any diet day day brother
thank you for your existence for me you
always are Middle top
who dancing between left and right with
Elegance of the Phoenix I'll be grateful
to you for the rest of my life happy
anniversary thank you look forward to
many more years of you thank you I
agree with me yeah
my grandma
[Music]
have a dream again you should follow it
dreams come true I am the proof of it
how far you're in the game I finished it
in the first 40 minutes of the stream
peace
so I just want to send an August but
showing my support but I have no idea
what to write it's been a year a whole
lot changed in a year but I'm happy that
you are still here and are a positive
picture in my life now yay here's my
navigator of the Phoenix
the right here is here of the Phoenix if
you wanted to be
thank you thank you
now go I'm glad to have you thank you
I'm glad to be
a fix fixture in your life
I better be
thank you so much for the love and
support
uh h-l-g-e-free g b v d six is that your
password
is
[Music]
please don't fire
it's okay I wouldn't even have noticed
probably there were too many people
happy anniversary Kiana thank you so
much for all the memories you have
created with us so far and I'm also
looking forward for all the streams to
come in the future me too I want to have
lots of fun with you guys in the future
as well
I hope you stay until the very end
thank you so much
[Music]
because they made a huge thread on past
memories from your streams I had the
most heartfelt emotional nostalgic time
going for each post and just thanks for
all that into tension yo you better tag
me on that one right away
I don't know if I saw it but now I want
to see it thank you
[Music]
jump up
National dive part two donations you
don't have things with a pinky uh thank
you for the membership thank you
one year since I started to learn the
meaning of admiration oh you are without
a doubt one of the best influences in my
life losing only to my eye around Mom
love you
you like your mom more than me but I'm
your mom
I'm confused what
I I take it as I'm your number one
Mission Aztec zombie dancing
opportunity thank you for the pinky
thank you thank you so much for this
wonderful year you have been an
inspiration and a reason to smile every
day for a whole year now and we are all
very thankful
shining bright like the Phoenix and
making our day so much better out
best first I need a little break I think
at the moment I am
unfortunately I have to admit I am
burned out
and I want to do something about it
so I want to take a tiny break
sometime as soon as possible which will
still take a little while but we will
get there and that will I will be better
after that and have my full power to
entertain you guys so please please bear
with me for a while
[Music]
um
I'm here for the special day I have
always been lacking around even if it's
not obvious so I hope you haven't been
missing me too much
[Music]
no
is an amazing year and cheers to many
more Amazing years to come
thank you
it's not like I'm happy seeing your name
or anything
no
[Music]
no no
thank you for the rest of the chat thank
you
mwah kind of happy anniversary although
I can't catch up every stream on live
your streams always show your passion
talent and hard work you always Sparkle
spikes
spin Sparks and fill my days with
positive energy you're my number one and
only OC really
the only way hey
good chicken I love you I'll always be
employee love you too thank you
thank you sir endurance stream of
Hardcore this is this is easy mode just
kidding you know Super Chat reading for
uh almost eight hours is definitely not
easy mode
[Music]
uh but it's just a normal day at kfp
Zulily line thank you soon and this name
looks familiar
[Music]
thank you for the pinky happy one year
anniversary here I am so thankful to
have become a champion boy and I will
support you forever I love all that you
do and are so hard working have the best
day and remember if we endorse you and
we will open and we always will be about
thank you
so much
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you love today
Brian is
dancing Lexington
now time for now
[Music]
okay I moved to another country and due
to the sea I was quite isolated ah
oof finding you when your streams kept
me company since I never failed to make
me smile
screen I'm moving back soon but you'll
always have a special place in my heart
oh I wonder if you did something similar
to what I did
listen that was horrible timing huh for
me and for you
but I hope when you go back
that you don't have too many regrets
about that time you spent somewhere else
it's you know really bad timing but I
hope you can still make some
memories and cherish the time while
you're there yeah
and then
you can still be very happy going back
to the place that seems familiar to me
and to you sorry
thank you thank you coincidence yeah
weird
well good luck moving back
probably very stressful moving from one
country to another
I feel that
I hope you didn't uh uh
um had to say it I hope you didn't I I
hope you don't have too much luggage now
in that fun country
I did I did big mistake in Japan I
accumulated too many new things
it was very expensive to send all that
[\h__\h] back to Australia
[Music]
your laugh tells me something
thank you for the pinky happy
anniversary danger I'm looking forward
to another wonderful year you're the
best show anyone could have sound
though
um
it comes with the food chicken salad is
just chicken food on top of salad not
food
what
you understand that you're not only
arguing with me here
but also we have a lot of people in the
chat who do agree with me that salad is
food
and my regular am I right
tell is what food is shut up
salad is
food
[Music]
happy Monday
oh my God
oh yes
oh salad with
ah Fried
Chicken
there's like this distance uh what was
it can from Canton uh oh yeah having a
brain
cool right now but there's this this one
without with
um
um hello help me
um with a pumpkin seeds and pumpkin oil
[Music]
uh
look it up uh what's pumpkin in German
again
[Music]
hey what am I thinking of
um
maybe it was not
[Music]
a bad candles a lot a bad candle salon
your back handle so that is finished
yes
[Music]
I can't the bar candles a lot now that
can't not be stylish
that is first question
oh yeah oh
[Music]
I'm almost done mommy almost done
sorry speaking I was speaking in Austria
now bye Alexa
so you were telling me
you're telling me
[Music]
hmm
you're telling me
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] yes it is
I'm trying to find a good picture
oh yeah
oh
yeah
ah good stuff
oh
[Music]
look
it's with salad and potato salad and
then pumpkin seed oil so sometimes they
make the the frying breading stuff with
pumpkin seeds crushed pumpkin seeds on
top of it too
as you call that not food then you're
stupid
a little hungry I love that because it
has the freshness of the salad
with that really nice crispy hot ass
chicken yes
never seen this well now we've seen it
that's more than the meat than salad no
it's not no the salad place is a big Row
in this dish
[Music]
yes yes of course
of course it is vegan
duh
okay we're almost done with my goal
uh
I think Furlong needs to go to the usual
room aquining thank you for the pinky
happy anniversary I can't wait to see
what more you'll accomplish in the
future thank you oh wait let me change
the beach in one last time what about
this yeah
what about this
[Music]
oh snap snap
Loveless
[Music]
actually I only have what was my goal
I'm daring finally thank you for the
pinky I can't wait to see what you
accomplished more in the future thank
you I totally changed the order of the
words in the sentence but still works
thank you
yeah I'm there I'm there I have arrived
[Music]
sleepy employee thank you for the rants
of the chat hi can a happy anniversary I
have watched Polo Memphis debut oh you
are my favorite member of home life oh I
really appreciate your hard wake up this
year you make a ton of joyfulness you
are real talented real Idol thank you
that means so much to me
[Music]
thank you
foreign
I already read more than 100 married
people
for the red super chat congratulations
of your daughter thank you for giving us
a wonderful oval horde
who amid the various terrorists she
inflicts on us ha in the usual romance
brought us so much joy and happiness
this last year oh hi Kiana what what
thank you
I guess wow
you don't understand
foreign
[Music]
but you kept me here just by being
yourself
thank you for the fun times and I
appreciate you and give me you oh that's
so cool
yeah you can see how YouTubers might be
a bit too weird in the beginning even if
you're like in the scene anime scene and
stuff I'm glad you stayed really thank
you forgot your super Shadows yeah well
there you go you forgot now you remember
Mr Bones damage and Optimus Prime
dinosaur and Joker let's get to 400
Joker zero one nine five and thank you
for the red super chat to the double
words of a chance happy occasion to my
favorite film ever since I discovered
you and your first Minecraft collab with
Callie on that one I know you would be
my number one so here's my first super
for the good times and the bad I will be
at every stream because love used many
more years of you
wow
thank you so much you've been around for
a long time and you're still not sick of
me thank you I don't know how you can
put up with me but I appreciate it
now thank you you big fluffy chicken
brobe easy loud and proud thanks for the
pinky happy anniversary I'm very proud
of how far you want the other homeless
members have come you guys have
accomplished so much she has a good
health making new memories and my
continued love and support Viva La
Canada thank you yes yes very important
things
I hope I also hope that all the Hello
myth members can stay
and be very healthy and
um experience a lot of love and positive
things only yeah thank you so much
thank you for the rest of my channel
happy first anniversary 10 so I'm a
little sad because I didn't know you
when you debuted oh don't worry about it
that was a mess in the beginning
but I'm also glad that I started
watching you nine months ago I have a
lot of fun and now you have become my
big Lucy thank you for everything love
you love you too nine months is already
a long long time if you think about it
um thank you a very very cute mess I
guess I guess I guess yeah that was kind
of cute yeah yeah a lovable mess thank
you
a hot mess in a good way huh thank you
um
wait you're still alive of course I am
who do you think I am it's almost
midnight I'm Cinderella I gotta go just
kidding I'll finish it up here I have
three more Super chats to read thank you
Donna
I have so much to say so I will divide
into four parts oh where's the rest ah
you mean there's one super chat ah
congratulations on the first anniversary
this July I first learned about Kiana
the ones in kirinuki yes yes yes big
influx of influx of Korean viewers I'm
very happy about it seeing you as kinoki
you had a really happy smile I fell in
love with that smile
oh no there's actually really more super
jets thank you
uh wait a second cutie to the dinosaur
continuation so joined the membership
for the first time although I don't
understand the whole story because I'm
not good at English I feel happy just
watching your stream thank you
thank you also you stream on easy
English and Japanese so I'm getting used
to it see that's maybe one of the good
things that never English nor Japanese
is my uh mother tongue because that
means that I will always probably use
relatively English uh relatively simple
words when I speak the nivo the the herd
the the difficulty level is very low
yeah
Florida and Simon thank you for the red
super chat happy anniversary thank you
for always brightening up my days I'm
really excited to see what the future
will bring but I'm sure it will be fun
as long as you stay the way you are I
can't promise that because I already
changed a lot in this one year but only
for the battle right so
momentum
thank you for being here for trusting
and believing in me
watching me and not giving up on me
thank you thank you
here's another one I think that's the
number three
it's hard to watch the live show because
of the time difference but I tried to
watch it even a little bit I feel like
I'm losing my fatigue watching you
stream oh really that's how attractive
your show is thank you I wonder if some
of you guys watching my Super Chat
streams are just exhausted from
listening to me
I've almost done
I'm putting a Danish and freedom hero
for dinosaur and Dragons fire thank you
for the red super chat one amazing year
with a wonderful Phoenix it's hard to
believe how far you've come this year
you were such a bright shining star no
really you sure
that's a bright bright shining style we
are lucky to have you brightening Our
Lives thank you for being you Kiana I
can't wait to see what the future holds
thank you
I can't wait evil
but I don't have to wait because now is
the future
in one second is the future now we live
in the future see it's amazing it's
fascinating
[Music]
thank you Dragonfire
Jones thank you
[Music]
just wanted to show you some of my
appreciation for all of the hard work
you do and the quality content you put
out I look forward to incoming to the
oncoming year ahead of us thank you
I I'm glad you've seen my content as a
quality content I I mean I wanted to be
of high quality
thank you I appreciate your feedback and
your love and support
[Music]
a wonderful year so far and hope we'll
have even more fun on this on the road
to the second anniversary I hope so too
I hope so too maybe we can even reach 2
million Subs until then who knows
[Music]
try alright and lead your support guys
last
one I think thank you for the pinky I
know I don't know if you can feel my
heart because I only said all these
things but I'm always gaining a lot of
courage and strength from you and it
won't be an easy thing but I hope you
remember that there are a lot of fans
who support you all that's very sweet
thank you I do I don't know
I am aware otherwise I would I would not
be able to continue
thank you
I think no no my fart
SPX thank you for the pinky can't
believe it's been a year already thanks
for all the streams this year every
moment has been a blast feel inspired
and motivated me to improve a drawing
and before I knew it I was I was
casually drawing you at work ah so thank
you for everything thank you
that it sounds very sweet
I hope you can show me more of your
drawings thank you for your support and
your love and good luck
with improving I think you will
definitely improve because drawing is
you just have to continue drawing and
then you'll get better oh don't give up
[Music]
Vincent La thank you for the reason for
Chad congratulations on one year
anniversary thanks for the Triple
performances you have made wish we could
listen more to your Forever improved
singing voice help you get to the wisdom
to overcome the self-constrained mind
and time limited situations oh wow oh
thank you yeah I will I I definitely
want to put out more
um music so please wait for me and
whenever it comes please support
and whatever I put out all right thank
you
[Music]
for the red super gel a Lucas
oh this is the last one thank you for
another pinky I think this year will be
a happy year to get to know you and I
will continue to be your fan lastly
thank you so much for everything and I
hope only happy things happen to Kiara I
love you so much was divided into five
parts yeah you wrote more than you
wanted to uh it turns out
thank you so much for your kind words I
also hope that only great things happen
to you please stay healthy so that you
can continue watching my streams okay
[Music]
fried Phoenix spine
interesting name hi guys baby
getting impatient huh this Covina thank
you for the red super chat thank you
congrats in one year I haven't been able
to catch many streams live recently but
your energy kindness and love for the
kfb employee has been
such a huge influences last year thank
you for all you do and your incredible
personality we love you and
[Music]
thank you
yeah that's a bit unfortunate that you
couldn't watch so many recently but I
hope I help you don't forget about me
okay okay
[Music]
thank you for your love and your support
and I will do my best
forever
yes we'll work hard
and we are at 400 now
so
I will end it here for today
[Music]
how many did I read today
from the anniversary ones I read
oh no well 400 are left it was like
about like almost a thousand
almost a thousand and then I had some
extra ones right from Tales of a rise
and Minecraft I think those were extra
those were not in that number
so no I don't want no need to remember I
I deleted the rest so I know where to
continue
[Music]
I need to go to the title break and eat
food and take a bath and all that so
thank you everyone
for staying with me so long it's been
eight hours
and oh yeah I wanted to put out that
stream until two maybe I'll do it after
eating
and if you have questions by the whole
talk please submit them in the community
board if you have an English one or to
the on Twitter if you have a Japanese
one so that's it
I know
[Music]
um
tomorrow or today after tomorrow
until they're gone so yes tomorrow tells
over rice I'll see you there guys
[Music]
thank you very much for your patience
and all your love and support all all of
these kind words
have definitely reached my heart thank
you
I love you
so my shift is over for day for today
my shift has ended like my watch has
ended alrighty
and in German we say
about guys
[Music]
see you tomorrow
foreign
[Music]