[Music]
you
do
[Music]
me
do
[Music]
so
kelly himself picking up some bread
right now
she'll be there in 10 seconds i'm
telling you one
two three four
five six seven
eight nine
nine point five
i got it and i got the honey toast i got
cinnamon flavored hold on i got cinnamon
flavored you guys and i got regulars
yeah oh my god i did i got i got i got
if you
i mean probably not but it looks like
it's made with brown sugar and honey
and they toasted it all right my
favorite my favorite pan yeah
oh i see i said i see are playing a way
out again
welcome welcome dead dead beats and kfp
ready to party ready we escaped from the
prison we got out of shawshank i don't
know what we're gonna do next
we are on the run according to the game
uh i have to i have two warnings
um actually only one warning
oh maybe two no one warning
um disappears please let me know chat
because i only work with one monitor and
the game is so big on my screen so that
i will not see
when cali disappears please let me know
okay please tell me swipe back
oh yeah i'll call you a bit loud okay
let me turn don't you don't need to do
anything kelly i'll turn you down a
little bit if you say so
yes and then the game audio will be on
once i uh am in the window okay this
time
it's on my channel if you missed the
first part it's on cali's channel if you
missed it also her channel is in the
description
so let's get started do you guys hear
that
uh the the game music now guys do you
hear it
i am watching the chat on my phone
i really need like a second monitor it's
it's horrible
you should get one they hear it ah
because i am not
here much longer so anyway yeah i was
gonna say it might be a bit pointless
right now huh
yeah okay start together let's go
i need to pop out the chat hold on pop
out
pop out the chat there's the chat okay
now we can play the game
would select character we could we could
change the character no if we wanted to
i i guess we could but i feel like
just because we've gone this long with
them already it feels strange to switch
them in the middle
yeah that's kind of nice that's nice i
will say we're not starting from the
beginning right this is continue on the
run okay okay
[Music]
yeah you know i've i've really gotten to
know my boy you know
i i'd feel bad saying bye-bye to him
already yeah
we're back it's raining yeah it is
raining huh
how okay where did we come from
i have uh maybe from up because we slid
down we slid down
right okay um yeah so i don't know
how do you jump in this but the game
started with us looking in that
direction
oh it did maybe we go this way probably
there
hopefully they put up some shields on
how to get away from the prison
why didn't that one shields
oh god is this gonna be like a la
uh how do you call those lava lava ring
labyrinth like a maze yeah you have to
go this is a mace
um great question uh find leo i'm
vincent
well you're right behind me
a right mouse button okay hold on here
you are i found you
yeah oh and we can go up
space to climb okay let me climb
up we go nice
there's uh a bunch of different paths
interesting how big
i hope we're getting the right path
i'll be fine
what a nice day outside it's raining
cool nice wow you know how to do it
already
yeah come on come on
[Music]
yay let go just drop them
thank you there are cops everywhere oh
[\h__\h]
are they looking for us did they already
yeah they realized we're gone we
definitely are looking wow that's not
good
um no right or left probably right
oh god how do we crunch again or how do
we do that again
the game is just doing it for us right
do i feel like but didn't
[Music]
oh yeah i didn't mean quench i meant
crouch i think
that's enough wait game audio too low
um and we're trying to pull that up
look we can hide in the bushes oh dumber
than a bag of whipped potatoes
i need to sneeze let's do it
there you go yeah where'd you go
where'd you go i opened my eyes
yeah i don't feel
i'm still in the bushes see i'm i'm so
good at hiding
that's why these cops have fun
okay so we should probably escape behind
him when he's turned so we need to watch
both of these cops
and we need to make a run with neither
one of them yeah there's one more oh
[\h__\h]
yep he's over there
[Music]
very quickly get into the next bushes oh
he's got he's got something over his
head that's going to say how how close
he is to spotting you
where are you
all right i'm in more bushes okay
i'll see you on the flip side right yes
catch you on the flip side that is
correct i will catch you on the flip
side
for the time being just don't get caught
oh my god
how do i how do you uh run again
wasn't there a dash button
maybe a control review would have been
nice but what am i doing what am i doing
what am i doing what am i doing
maybe i just can't run right now oh my
god okay back make sure all the cops are
going over there
is there a way there there are a lot of
cops around here
yeah are you sure you can't seduce them
or something
probably not i just don't think that
that'll work i probably could have gone
behind him huh
it's fine he's going this way why are
you i'm in more bushes
that's always the same answer
i'm not sure where you are
really only see a bunch of look at all
these yellow arrows
everywhere so many cops please no
shall we i go
okay i wish i knew how to run
it's alright i've got my eye on this one
cop here he's going to turn around
in a minute a bit there are two cops
here
wait hold on hold on oh he's coming
right my way you can take him out
what oh really
got one sir we got one i don't think we
can take it
oh my god did we stop from the top oh no
it's fine here we go again it's okay
we'll just be ultra stealthy and it'll
be okay
i think they'll see us in the bushes
keep just keeping better than expected
oh did it now did it go better than
expected because i certainly didn't see
that
i didn't see that all right hold on my
god this
is a cop coming no just one
yeah but it's fine i'll just quickly get
into these bushes yeah
oh there's one oh look at me don't look
at me i'm shy
oh no way
i barely see him back into the bushes i
go
bye bye bye bye bye bye go now oh my god
no no i think they died we're already
far gone
give up yeah we're already on our
uh
that's right sir oh left mouse button
kill him yeah
get him yeah dummy haha
suddenly give you the prompt to do it
yeah it said left mouse button click and
i remembered my lefts and rights this
time
all right i will follow you i'll get
both of these cups
you get both of them are you sure about
that
i probably can i can save both of them
they should be fine
that's literally where i got called by
the way so oh really
but you were out in the open kiara and
i'm not both at their backs are turned
i need you oh wait wait wait wait not
yet not yet
almost in your bus i'm on the bus next
doors
oh in the bush next to me really okay
cool we need to wait for this guy to
stop peeking though he's being snoopy
yeah wait for him to go away all right
he's going all right are you ready
sorry that was me yeah
needs me i need to go when she needs me
okay
it's uh we both could have planned that
out a little better but you know what
the good news is
we're getting better at this yeah really
back in those bushes and just do things
exactly the way that we did them before
before we got caught
speed run yeah speed run tactics that's
what i tell my chat when i keep moving
over and over again
so they don't get more mad at me all
right here we go
you must be a little risky but keep your
eyes
wide open yes okay
that is that is how killers do
good to know it's fool going uh-oh watch
out
prize surprise friend now
i think we're good now yep
you're gonna take him out again i'm
gonna come back well yeah why not
all right now crouch for a minute
all right he's not coming back so i'm
just going to jump into these bushes
can we get into these i wonder if
there's enough time
yeah it should be fine at least for me
yeah
i'm i'm fine i'm fine but i wouldn't
chance it if this is a deja vu
[Music]
you shouldn't move just yet
all right their backs are turned so let
us continue forward
not those fools actually let's skip
let's just sleep right there yeah and uh
go into the bushes
this is where we were before am i ready
for that
so we just want to move to the bushes
that are as close to those guys as
possible let's wait
where's this guy go what all right i
think we're safe really
because we can just go there from behind
it don't turn around just keep walking
you must work together so which one do
you want kia which one do you want to
wait hold on there's someone behind us
hold on
really oh yeah i'll take the left one
the left one all right hold on there's
another guy watching
we just need to wait for him to turn his
back and then that's our chance so you
take the left one and i'll take the
right one okay
okay i'll tell you when the coast is
clear okay all right looks clear let's
go are you ready
wow what i wasn't god
i want the one on the left okay then
i'll do it right okay we bumped into
each other that was
probably the problem close as you can
and then
i'll say three two one and when i say go
we both go okay okay
all right okay let's see
is the coast clear should be fine okay
ready three
two one go
yeah perfect
how many cops wow there are a lot of
cops around here oh god why don't hold
up they're
pointing behind oh this is [\h__\h]
questions still seems fine here
just stay in the shower the reason why
my reaction time might be a bit slower
is because i just woke up
you are a bit sleepy huh over there
johnson we're gonna need some more you
gotta stay far away from that area
all right this guy's walking away so i'm
gonna go ahead and hit him you're
standing johnson
can i go bud
yeah just don't head in the direction
where there are obviously many police
you come to where i am i'm kind of
chilling there's a guy though he's on
his way so be careful
okay get in the bushes as quickly as you
can
while he's here i'll take a bite of my
honey toast yummy
hi now he's walking away so we may
continue
yes how does it taste the honey toast
really really good
okay so now what we want to do crouch
again
yep i'm crouching oh god
look away there's nothing here you and
your hallucinations
god damn it what a weirdo you should get
that checked
yeah i don't know what he's seeing
we need look away hold on okay
wait let's move back
where
[Laughter]
[Applause]
just keep your head low
you gotta get johnson over there
okay okay save we're going
[Laughter]
i'm fast past this point cali
do you hear my heartbeat it goes
i don't hear it i hate to disappoint you
but i don't hear it
it's so loud keep it moving
let's go as far as we can i'm glad
we don't go too far because if we move
too much we might accidentally get out
of the bushes like we did last time yeah
go past us that's what we need crouch
low keep it low
oh he's walking so we gotta wait until
he goes past us
don't do that what why i'm stuck why are
we stuck here
here let's move this one okay
how did you not see me there though i
feel like that's kind of like
visible pretty obvious you might see you
in a minute wait where did you go oh my
god
i'm already here you passed okay move
away
yes of course you must continue moving
through the game kiara
i'll wait for you okay i'm ready to go
wow wow wow
go ahead good job
yes oh there's no policemen here what
are you i think they
aren't really checking here just yet
we might encounter some more later
though all right i think we need to
climb up here okay i remembered what uh
what dash is
it this shift oh it is oh i think
oh no no no no no we're just uh casually
running always
oh okay just kidding what did you say
you said no [\h__\h] sherlock
they're probably hiding under a rock
somewhere anyway oh no
catch them in the morning do we have to
kill them again one from the right rooms
and
from the left that's possible
i'm not sure let me go scope out the
area a little bit anything beats bean
out here it looks to be
yeah it does well this is going to be
really tough though yeah because i first
have to climb up the rocks and i'm not
i'm not sure at what timing
let's just do it i'll try uh though that
those are cliffside bushes
we're gonna need quick here see if you
can crouch and get as close as possible
i'm going up i'm going up the stones oh
god i can go
you get as close as you can and you're
still in the shadows
and you hide behind the rock first if
you get the prompt to
let me know when you get the left mouse
button prompt yeah
yep uh
you got it okay on three actually it'll
be one two three go and on go you do it
okay
all right ready one two three
go yeah
yeah yeah i'd high five you except you
can't really takamoni's strongest
[\h__\h] in the house
that's right and sure we have strong
strong
b words in in the
in the home we're almost i think
at least it seems like it there's the
bridge back now
of course not i wonder if there's
squirrels around here
lisa senpai and this is senpai
god i don't think they'll find some
fight here
well you can climb on me again okay
we'll do thank you i'll use you as my
stepping stool as i usually do
i don't mind it oh [\h__\h] what are you
gonna do about that steal a car and like
no run along with them just kill all of
them okay ah
god damn it hey let's go that way
we should be able to my solution for
everything what no
it's way too high too risky
i say we take that guy out okay yeah
thanks game for challenge
what no leo's right we're gonna use the
car after we take him out
oh i'll go leo's way go under the bridge
you know what i like leo's way so we'll
we'll go leo's way
hold on hang on
i think we both have to go you have to
go okay i got
there we go let's see
how do we or they're not gonna look up
the lefties are not gonna look to the
right side i guess so i don't think so i
just take him out
no one's looking at us nice
here he goes bye
[Music]
oh you're a cop now
oh you look sexy as a cop don't look
over here
just stay on course then you like you
got this are you only
going spin around you're like moving the
wheel
what the hell are you doing
hey kelly i don't hear you are you
eating potato chips again no
no i'm not i'm hang on just
oh i can turn the car okay i didn't know
i could turn them oh that's the ones i
was wondering
oh is he gonna go away hold on just a
moment
what is falling besides rain it looks
like ash is falling
yeah very strange dramatic effect
can i just run into him and kill him i
wonder um
yeah maybe that's what the full speed is
for but oh full speed
there's another guy over here though so
i don't really know maybe i should just
try to drive around him
i don't know no guys looks like everyone
wants full speed
i can't say i disagree with them i don't
think that's the solution though
it's a great solution here we go oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
i just killed you dude you're just too
much into killing callie
but it's not that was kind of fun though
yeah okay i'm satisfied i'm satisfied
but now we are gonna do it the right way
kiara what really is right and wrong
when it comes to when it comes to
playing this kind of game yeah when it
comes to
finding a way out i guess so you can
just kill everyone though
what are they doing what the hell that's
an easy way idiots
step on it um
who's that speed uh it's just it's just
officer cop man
top man bob smith caught man bob smith
oh i'm a great driver
i'm a great driver yeah
[Music]
all the rocks i mean i made a couple
dents in the car but
overall pretty decent i would say hey
we're alive
yeah we better run away huh because the
car is definitely about oh yeah
for a second oh no the enemies have come
down where are you no they're behind us
no the doggies are coming you're very
fast there's a cliff
oh no leo sorry i heard something wrong
and tapped out of the game
i like how they're all right expert
driving thank you chad
i do pride myself a bit in driving i've
driven many in underworld
an underworld highway
hurry up where are you
[Music]
what why i was running fast
goodbye doggy i'll see you i didn't mean
to keep you in the face but i got to do
what i got to do to get away holy [\h__\h]
are you sure i'm gonna oh you've gotta
catch me button's gonna show up what but
there's a space
touch me
will you let me ah
you really left me hanging mary so i'm
speaking to you except you didn't do
this
again i'm gonna save you this time don't
worry it would have been nice if you
left me hanging
[Laughter]
my man
oh give me that romantic moment that i
always wanted
why there you go
wait does does the timing have to be
like correct now
[Music]
the real version of that famous painting
romantic oh [\h__\h]
oh no look they're mad they can't do
that because they don't have the kind of
teamwork and and um chemistry that we
have they can do the same job right
they'll never understand
but never understand they can yeah they
can't do that sick jump can they now yes
no they cannot oh that's pretty
huh just tell him
this is the deal you either take it or
don't
oh this is the this is the harvey man
that everyone talks about the bad one
this is the villain i think
oh um look take the deal
or stop wasting my time all right yeah
that's not really how it works sir when
negotiating what's up
usually you'll find a nice middle ground
what i just got the call
isn't he supposed to be dead a guy
[\h__\h] up got himself killed by the
guards
and i think i think that vincent wants
to kill him so you decided
oh yeah or no deal
okay no deal whoa
i knew that was gonna happen oh okay
in my deathly crystal ball i saw that
coming
up oh [\h__\h] he's cold-heart
cold-blooded cold-hearted mm-hmm
should have taken the deal damn
why kill them though probably because
it's fun
probably no in my case it's fun in his
case
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
it makes me want to go skiing yeah like
it's been a while i want to go skiing
too i haven't gone since like i was uh
small
wow this is really nice oh okay man i'll
die for a burger
i'm running uh i'll let you know if i
find a burger joint
well now i won't burn when they say food
and i'm hungry then that becomes what
i'm in the mood for now i'm in the mood
for a burger
even though i'm eating honey no oh yeah
now i'm gonna order a birthday
yeah oh yeah cool tell me breakfast tell
if
do you have a favorite burger joint
i like ones where only one of its kind
exists i like the
the one that's called kiara fried
phoenix
that doesn't sound like a burger joint
restaurant fast food franchise we have
burgers
we have the jungle burger we have the
phoenix burger
what are they made of yango burger is
made out of a normal
beef patty but it has a seiso sauce in
it and it has
i think pickles and stuff but the
phoenix burger is a
chicken uh meat with um
with a pineapple inside i know that's
controversial
but it's really good but why is it
called a you go burger if you go is not
inside the burger
well there is also no no phoenix meat
inside the
uh inside the phoenix burger point don't
tell my employees because if they know
that i put chicken in there they're
gonna
panic oh no
oh my gosh all right well we'll do well
i mean you just
told them on stream so i don't know
maybe they'll panic a bit
they know when to not listen and when to
close their ears and eyes
i get it they know they shouldn't know
there's a camp down there wow well
that's interesting to know
but it looks empty whoa
guys don't look at them look at them if
you're not listening otherwise i'm gonna
close you all up in the usual room
okay oh the the usual what usual room
kiara
don't question it oh look that's pretty
species we can eat those maybe camping
vincent oh wait we actually have to
fire catch one fish each we actually
[Applause]
[Music]
is
foreign
yeah okay get a fish no toilets kisses
who can get the charm without nobody it
will be me
vincent really is just somebody's dad
huh
no fishies wait hold on no don't let him
get away
ah no darn it we let him get away how do
we
i'll splash them towards you oh okay
that's one fish each
how about i splash him towards you
no go back to leo go go back to papa leo
hold on no
it's hard we have to light the fire
first maybe uh let's light the fire yeah
yummy grilled fish craft a spear
what does e do oh you're doing it
what ah we have to catch them with the
spear oh i need to get some firewood
make sense we need to get some firewood
so i'll look for some firewood
i need to get some fire i need to get
some firewood i need to get some
firewood
hey this reminds me when me and my
survival mom went into the woods
oh yeah kind of cute
did you build a fire i mean i i find it
hard to believe that you had to actually
make a fire for yourself
i mean we went camping and we didn't
have much
like modern equipment for camping
right but but you are made of fire i
remember one time when me and my
mom we were camping and
i remember i was like really really
small so i barely remember but
i was standing inside in front of
or next to a wild boar at some point oh
and then my mom was just like be chill
be calm
just don't move i barely remember it was
um i did not panic i think
because that's horrifying it is very
horrifying
but we ended up like somewhere we found
uh
oh oh we found we found uh a
boar's bone and we bought that home so
ever since then we have a boar's bone
a wild forest bone no that's a pretty
neat souvenir yeah
okay i'm ready to roast this i
am sick of these fish you got one
damn it you you got this leo you got
this
don't let him don't let him get the best
of you
looks like it's going swimmingly
[Music]
i made a joke yeah i am hungry
i am hungry
come on come on come on how did you
catch the fishy they don't get close to
me
you're just watching me
because if they're drawn to me they know
it's time to die
you can do it they have to stay here you
got this
and then wait for them give it your best
come on i didn't even hit them very
directly don't think too hard about it
uh it's okay one's coming your way just
go for it
he went the other way can you move any
quicker
no hmm
where'd you get it how did you get in
here let me help you hold
on i'll scare the fish away
i almost got one oh my is my fish gone
no my fish is still chilling there
okay let me help you i'll scare the fish
away in your direction
wait it says sit down by fire so i guess
i got it
okay thank you kelly you're welcome
i'll sit here and you can have the fish
that i caught before yeah
yummy oh my god i really want to grill
some fish now
tasty tasty yummy mm-hmm
yeah right on top of like a real fire
like buckets a day
yeah oh leo
well you know it is what it is yeah
sorry for insulting your your cooking my
[\h__\h] feet hurt
what about it's kind of a baby huh vince
is really into someone's dad i love it
somewhere well it's not like we have
much of a choice guy
i am a tough guy by the way what are you
in for
something i didn't do oh see you're
innocent huh
well aren't we all right listen
me too and a kid
alex
[\h__\h] missing man yeah i hear you
hmm that piece of [\h__\h] harvey's gonna
get what he deserves let me tell you
that
so let's go after him together
i'm innocent look vincent i like that
vincent more like vinocent funny chat
i like that yeah tell us the harvey
story venison
i was a regular guy with a boring bank
job
one day my brother brings in a new
client harvey
oh let me guess money laundering
yeah money was easy
but harvey just kept coming in with more
and more cash
and i couldn't handle it it was too
risky so i told him i wanted out
he killed my brother as a warning
what the [\h__\h] after that i lost i mean i
i believe it after what he did to those
two randomly killing him
now but the son of a [\h__\h] pin it all on
me
oh i was convicted for the murder of my
what
i got supposed he didn't kill anyone
after all that's [\h__\h] rough man
except some policemen now yeah yeah that
means that's pretty important
sorry
so uh what's your story with heart yeah
yeah yeah more story time
um [\h__\h] me over that's for sure what did
he do
maybe i'm gonna listen to you hey i
can't tell you my story
we gotta run no it's i wanted story time
well they're really looking for a song
closing in we gotta move
okay here we go again
[Laughter]
no please scare me
i don't want to oh you're gonna end up
carrying me i know it
great depiction thanks chad i thought so
too
figures what are you implying well how
should i put it
you're kind of uptight oh i'd rather be
uptight than a loose cannon
i was about to say that i'd rather be
uptight than complaining about my feet
hurting every two minutes damn
what at least i'm running and you don't
even know how to run
yeah yes you figured it out would you
look at that
you're making progress leo what's that
a farm
oh cool are we going let's go find out
we're gonna go there and ask them if we
can have some
they see them some stuff some money give
us
money
you want milk i want money unfiltered
milk
i mean yeah i like money but
it kind of doesn't have much uh doesn't
have much uh meaning to me
i prefer souls let me help you there i'm
strong
makes the dream happen
oh so pretty
yeah it was pretty spectacular i must
say thank you
today
[Music]
thanks guys
he has cookies and a gun but he also has
old betsy it's an old couple well i
don't want a needle better
we can't walk around like this i don't
like it it's better to get him out of
that
okay who's gonna wear the woman's
clothes
see that barn over there yeah
we released the horses oh horses
that's a large cranium idea nice one
venison i'll be forced to go get them
back
i don't know man
i once again agree with you subdue the
couple
or release the horses it's interesting
because
all of leo's ways are like ways that
involve harming others
sure let's try it okay come on
no but you wanted to go in the car and
uh i wanted to go under the bridge
no vincent wanted to go under the bridge
i chose leo's way because i personally
agree with that
but i don't really feel like taking out
this old couple right now
[Music]
can you talk to them hold on buck buck
buck
buck buck buck buck buck buck buck buck
there's no what happened to your voice
it has to be more like
cheap cheap cluck cluck cluck
[Applause]
you got it i feel like a demon has been
released from me
kelly i think they have a better
impression of you now they like you
i feel sick
are we supposed to go here
[Music]
um by the way can i get some of that
tasty
milk though
can you communicate with the cows as
well
no i i don't even want to try
i just want to release the horses
wait how do we get out of here how did
we get in here in the first place
hold on oh i guess we hopped the fence
maybe there's okay i think we need to go
around somehow hold on can i get some
kind of prompt
here we go oh no i'm just supposed to
follow you window
hold on let's take a nice jog oh that's
that's a good idea
ally help us she's not gonna help you
shut up caffeine please
stay with me here's a sweet little
cow hey bubba can you go ahead and give
me some of that taste you know
we couldn't agree more yeah well you are
hanging out with the cows
i got a ladder oh i know where to bring
it oh wow you
really did work the cow looks cute
i love cows yeah one more pet one more
pet while you go ahead and do the hard
work
okay thank you my action man thank you
very much
action man i feel like like vincent has
like all the big
brain like ideas that don't involve uh
murder and leo is the action man
works better for me but but method wise
leo works better i like wheels
i'm not sure about this but let's
release them number one released
one down two to go yep number two
one of the doors
me open that one can i open it
oh i need you i'm over here i'm on my
way
oh locked what about what
what they're a key i wonder okay let's
just set the whole place on fire then
my first game here's the light this lamp
is broken
oh let's see if i can get it working how
many
immortal beings does it take to uh turn
on a lamp one
apparently that's not i didn't have any
children you tried
you tried and that's what matters
so we got one lamp working i wonder why
that was important in any way
is this one lock two no this one this
door is fine i think
yep huh
why didn't you not orbit the horses time
to scare them let's go oh
they're gonna run out of there by them
by themselves okay
real free oh
it's not going to work i don't want to
do that
hold on maybe i'll scare a horse
nope loud enough
okay
[Music]
fresh grass come on
i don't know maybe something's upstairs
yeah
i mean we have to drop something from up
oh yeah
i got it cool i need you though
all right i'm on my way hold on uh
venusand is on the way right oh you're
going
you're coming from that side where are
you uh other side
can't see okay i'm on my way
i can't do this by myself okay okay okay
that's a crying shame if you ask
[Music]
thank you i got a little southern brawl
spent a little time down
yeah how do you
get to the truck where is the truck oh
we gotta change clothes first
oh yeah i'm gonna go inside here go
inside their home yeah they'll
they'll need some time won't they to go
catch
[Music]
do they have some gucci or prada oh
there it is that's what i would like to
know
give me this hat i'm the purple one
closing the door
i don't care if you have i want the hat
this is the first and last time i'm
testing this no you keep it on venison
i'm
steering i am steering the i am steering
this rifle
okay i've changed and i got a raffle i'm
ready oh did you get old betsy this must
be one of the news
i think you're in the wrong room they
don't have clothes here but they have
butterflies
oh wasting time innocent i want i want
some cool threads
and what would be good i wonder okay i'm
gonna
take uh a big dump once again um
wow i didn't need to know that still got
the logo
he's looking good he likes the way he
looks yeah gotta be confident yeah i do
like the jacket that's something that
i'd like to wear we go down from here
what i've always found these kind of
soothing what right for real
why all of the is randomness
that's cute though or maybe it's just me
that's cute
come over here you gotta escape from the
window i think i'm gonna go smell these
sheets
if only the celebrities were this
comfortable
you want to take a little nap maybe
let's leave
cali i'm outside already where's the
truck
hold on where's it happening are they
gonna come back eventually on one day
uh probably which is why i think i
should probably not be here anymore
venison i know you want to touch
everything we really should get out of
here
i want the gun can i get an old betsy
uh you didn't get one afternoon no where
did you find yours you did change right
i did but i just got it with change
while i was changing
like it came out like the outfit and the
rifle i'm not i wish i could give it to
you though because i
i'm not much more comfortable yeah
that's all right
you're my action man
oh where is the truck get to the truck
we need to find a nice
follower nice
throw horse you want to throw some
horseshoes
yeah where are you yeah vincently i'm
here where
i'm here in the horseshoe throwing place
of course okay i'm coming coming
coming it's almost new years and
horseshoes bring luck right is that yeah
people gift other people horseshoes for
luck i think for new year's
oh yeah yeah you don't know
i didn't know that was a thing i knew
that you could find them in a special
cereal what
see one rowing whole ringer
all right that was bad
jackpot wait they actually give us
blackbody sure
that was pretty decent
vincent all right hold on
what oh you get points for hitting the
pole as well
oh okay i get it now i get it
i must almost
[Music]
what i won why
no i'm doing it again i want to rematch
every match yep those are the priorities
i agree
a perfect throw
i know i know that we we're on the run
we have some angry farm people that are
going to come after us but i'm going to
win
i doubt it
well oh yeah you are now
at the number that i already had after
my first row so
unless i don't miss any i don't get
anything at all
all right let's see what you got come on
i want to watch this
oops
toast oh [\h__\h] while i watch
oh god oh god oh come on why doesn't
give me any points anymore
call beginners luck
what the hell huh
happens to the best of us okay well
let's go
you're called up to me with points at
least get the truck
where is the truck uh i know that i hm
i want to go to the truck but i heard
there's a banjo here
are you kidding me listen
i just i love strange instruments i love
them
hey bessie essie
[Music]
besties
hey you can't say that to the cow that's
so rude let me talk to bessie hey there
bessie
you're a beautiful animal aren't you i'm
feeling i know where the truck is
i know i jessie and i are tight we're
homies
oh but why aren't you just don't don't
tell her about what you want to eat
today
burgers i'm telling you that oh forgot
about that
forgot about that part well that's why
bessie and i are such a good friend
i have a feeling that the truck is in
here because the the lines on the ground
lead to it i bet the truck will show up
if we play the banjo
i need your help again i need some help
okay
come on kelly and let's see our ride
what do we got what do we got
i bet it's super new and fresh and
beautiful
it's not that bad what do you mean it's
not that bad it's orange colored i like
the color
leo is a bit of a prima donna huh
well it is missing i'm sure there's a
spare around here somewhere oh [\h__\h]
i don't know man do you know how to
change wheels
sure be strong um what we could do is
use the body of
of the banjo guitar after we find it
what
what wait what are
sometimes some good music is just it's
just what you need
looks like the car is missing a tire
that bad joe
joke i think i'll lift the car
let's look around it's in the house
apparently i'm
lifting all right
do i even need to lift right now all
right hold on
yeah just keep doing it why not yeah
lettering seems dead
great timing
oh you see anything there this tank
seems completely dry
tank's completely dry we need to do a
bit of
i exploration i'll stop lifting yeah i
mean
it's a good word on the other side of
the barn
oh here a tire at the other side of the
barn
this side of the barn oh
what does this do what are you doing
i don't know this would be useful though
i think
oh
oh there's ties over there how do we get
there
i think i'm you need to hold on to the
hook
and i'll yeah i'll pull the lever okay
just go there just get some pull-ups in
and i'll be here
i'll be in there in a jiffy
[Music]
hey at least he gets the job done that
was very slow
very slow it was quite a bit
sound what do you got here
yeah just toss it
that's a good one i sneezed again
blessings thank you i throw i throw you
the good one down
okay good excellent
how are you gonna get back down good
question you just jump i guess i just
jumped
it's convenient convenient
and now now i have eye lift
that doesn't solve our fuel problem all
right
[Music]
thank you the many blessing
attach the tire oh oh wait wait
two buddies changing me or not right now
it's attached what the hell
i just need to find a lug wrench to
fasten it allow
i have that i did that
oh just kidding i didn't that was a lie
well here's the tool area
but i can't seem to find any tools here
i found the lug wrench
all right that's true
we did it for free there's one more on
there
what i need you wait is that
well maybe that was the only one i need
you
yeah there's only one tire that was oh
huh let's go we'll just do oh
oh we're going straight oh
[Music]
yes we have no fuel and we have no
batteries oh
i didn't let it go did you let it go
why would you let go they fight like a
married couple
i want to drive this time okay oh we're
not driving yet
what is he looking at are we still
looking for
fuel now oh how very convenient these
jumper cables might refresh the box
jumper cables perfect let's pop the hood
and try them
[Music]
what's here
the red one goes to the black one and
the black one goes to the red one hey
the second there's the gasket
yes canister how handy i found the
gasket
yes go refuel that bad boy very
convenient the car rolled away
awesome i got it okay can i put it down
yep okay so first of all we do this
thing i start the car
wow we're learning like survival skills
in this game
yes that's right would you know how to
do this stuff in
in like in the reality i've had to jump
a car before
buggins a day how do i start the car it
was very scary and terrifying and i was
afraid of being electrocuted but
that's silly because i'm deaf i tried it
before
uh go inside get inside the car it
wouldn't land me
are you sure it just lets me do the
thing on the side
huh really fine it's not gonna work
it's not gonna work maybe first i have
to do the gas
maybe i think that you need to do that
first no tank okie dokie
yeah fill it all up yo that bad boy
gobble gobble gobble gobble
now
is that yummy
okay ready turning it on
maybe there we go it's working
this piece of junk we didn't it actually
worked
yeah teamwork sometimes
god have a little face faith oh
innocent is so cute next time
just trust me okay yeah yeah trust me
i'm vincent
no i don't know oh [\h__\h] a while ago they
found out
oh i need your help no banjo i didn't
even steal from
them i feel sorry absolutely thank you
thank you for the truck i hope you get a
new one yes they'll be here any minute
okay i'll go take care of them no just
stay here
it's all right just wait here i'll be
fine oh we're still here
yeah oh uh-oh take
[Music]
hope you're ready for some room two
cowboy shoo
[Laughter]
cowboy shooting yeah
you might even have a little time to
shoot the breeze
you know what that means
i have no idea oh no callie's driving
hey
what do you mean go kelly
it's fine drive-ins to victory in
no breaks okay s button for break thank
you i will never use that okay
okay here we go am i do we have um
infinite
uh the shots what the hell
uh probably
[Applause]
i'm gonna drive more straight i promise
wow
hey
i don't think you really want to ruin
your car like that why are you bumping
into me oh
my god
go go go oh my god their cars are on
fire
leo oh my gosh we're driving in reverse
hey why are we driving because we don't
have any time
we don't have any time i can't turn
around
what is gonna be tight i'm using your
screen to see what it looks like
oh my god it's fine
[Applause]
no you're doing fine you're doing just
fine
wow again not again
hang on no
i need you leo i need you i'm doing my
best for you
the pizza man is here to help too hang
on
i only let you survive if you give me
pizza
pizza pineapple
we're going off-road a little off-road
action
don't die leo don't die
keep it together my man keep it together
oh god oh god he's going fast holy [\h__\h]
chill bro real quick huh this truck
isn't exactly
fast either that's why it's up to you
good job excellent oh my god
it's going way too fast
oh my gosh leo
we're surrounded you're surrounded
yeah yeah no no
i'm surprised it didn't shoot me right
away they really cornered us yeah i feel
like they probably would after all the
cops here
they would not be that nice to me no
they wouldn't
no they wouldn't oh let's see what we
got
[Applause]
i wonder if it's better to aim for the
for the car's wheels or for the person
inside uh for the person inside why i
can't
take my word it's not really an option
for me
oh there's like uh normal people here
too now
[Music]
they're probably like wow looks
interesting wonder what's going on over
there yeah
whoop down the fence here we go
just a little bit [\h__\h] up
[Music]
ordered myself a hundred points for that
one you guys so [\h__\h] bad
[Music]
it's like everyone knows i'm always the
driver
i'm always the driver
no we're not under arrest
come on
i mean it's not exactly a high-speed
getaway but okay
how are they now it was a motor it was
like a motorboat that would be one thing
but
oh that's very calming and chilling
the water is nice it is very pretty
i think we're going to have we're going
to have some nice bonding moments
this reminds me a lot of the rings oh
yeah
there's a scene where they try to escape
through some kind of
uh river but people are actually
following them on the sides of the river
how are they not following us what the
hell oh yeah
how do you know why are you switching
you can just sit on one side
okay you're exhausting yourself you know
what i can't i can't i need to go back
and forth
it doesn't let me do it over and over
again on this one of course it does just
press e continuously i'll show you
whatever we probably should turn around
oh god
probably seven salmon it could have been
a crocodile
seriously yep that's a bunk
oh my god a lot of durability okay well
now now now i've learned the weight so
i'll stay on this side
okay
uh probably it's fine we're fine
with problems no problems no problem no
problem we're looking
forward again okay
i think yeah we're probably gonna switch
every now and then because we might need
power on one side more than on the other
okay
no it's fine we're good uh i think yeah
the other side
okay okay okay
maybe into the right yeah a little bit
more on this side okay
nice
just stay don't chance it keep it on the
right
it's innocent to you
all the way other way oh no
[Music]
help oh my god come on go right
okay focusing
up a sign come on
wouldn't it be fast if i just jumped in
and swam yeah why don't we just swim
try that i'll just stay in the boat
i think we through the worst of it okay
oh we didn't restart from the beginning
[Music]
leo
the boat is down oh my god you're going
oh oh [\h__\h] oh my god at least we're
starting with a full boat once again
and we have made progress that's very
nice of the game
i think the game knows that this part's
a little difficult
no no no no no no no don't hit the rock
this is fine dead ahead dead ahead
what's up
help me michelangelo again come on
i'll never let go thanks man
i'll help you i hear about you playing
in the background
no a banjo to banjo i didn't get to play
oh [\h__\h]
oh
oh it's like before it's like before ah
i got you we did it
i saved your life pally i'm okay
let's yeah thank you for that you're
welcome
that's the second dress jump that we did
the second one
it yeah it sure is
something beautiful about that wow
yeah pretty at least we had a free
shower we were really stinky from the
prison still yeah i would definitely i
think that would be
a good idea from there for them yeah
i know what you're thinking but going
after harvey won't be easy
where the [\h__\h] is harvey anyway but i'm
going after him
with or without you you want to end up
dead
i want him gone he's a cold-blooded
killer
the world's gonna be a better place
without him
that's chill get him
yeah i don't want harvey to exist either
taking away my job you never told me leo
get him what is your story with harvey
oh let me tell you now
before i got busted me and harvey made a
huge score
bank job no you ever heard of a black
olaf
are you serious the diamond how don't
you pull that off
a lot of planning and a bit of luck so
what happened
everything was going our way we even had
a buyer
but that greedy [\h__\h] had other plans
oh flashback
oh that's a nice one yeah i kind of want
it
oh wait is it yellow yeah you don't like
yellow cards
it's not my style it was leo's car
he was ballin
wow hell yeah i was
you got the kids got the rich man shirt
got the goods count it
yeah i do saw there count
let's see if it's all in there one two
three four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven twelve
can't tell anyone 12 million
okie dokie here's the diamond
of course it is you can always trust me
i'm not trusting nobody my friend
uh oh oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
what's gonna happen there you go
what what do you think
is he gonna it's heavier than i thought
it is
nice diamond pleasure doing business
with you guys
you too
[Music]
give me the case what the [\h__\h] are you
doing give me the [\h__\h] case leo
hand it over oh harvey
you piece of shame he's the bad guy
there's
nothing personal he's taking the money
out that's not even
us that is not what business that's not
the definition of business that's not
what business is
you're stealing my car the money and the
diamonds and the diamonds
everything what
you couldn't just what
wow what a rude guy i can't wait till we
kill him i can't wait till we murder
that guy
i'm surrounded by cops oh my god that's
rough
i'm sorry or trust me i suck but they
didn't lock me in for
the murder so for me they know that i
didn't kill that dude at least
hmm so do you know where harvey is right
now
i know one of his guys ray you'll know
for sure
so what are we waiting for
let's go after him let's get him yeah
he deserves it yeah
i'm so excited you want to take harvey
down hurt him
i originally thought the game was really
only about getting out of the prison but
i like how there's like an after story
yeah there's a lot of stuff
there's [\h__\h] to do yeah
i will kill that guy i'm excited it
seems like there's lots more to the game
let's go all right where can we find
this ray guy
don't worry he's gonna be easy to find
but i need to make sure my family's safe
first
of course let's go
gonna be easy to find okay but we're
first checking out my family
yeah yes the same thing of the family
is number one priority apparently so
sugar rash
why is everything the same friend
we at supermarket don't go too far alex
wait is that wait does leo have a son
yeah that's so cute
mom i mean he doesn't act like a dad but
he's he's a dad
yeah what is it oh no
oh did she not know yet that he broke
out
i guess nothing can you imagine being
that little boy
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh wait oh yeah because she told
the son that he wasn't in prison but
just he was like on uh
on some like in some other place but
they were trying to hide the fact from
him that he's in prison
oh he didn't know he was in prison oh no
no for that newspaper yeah sure
[Music]
how do you and your wife manage to stay
together in this line of work
we've always been together
you know she knows me better than i know
myself oh that's kind of sweet
i was 12
when we met at the orphanage oh
orphanage
all for orphans his wife and him
i'm sorry to hear that don't be
i barely remember them besides
i was fortunate enough to have linda
she was crazy you know we used to run
away together
steal ice cream cigarettes [\h__\h]
for romantic looks against the world oh
still is no matter what oh
man that's just how it is
that's a little doki-doki they've been
together since your childhood that's so
cute
this is so long ago it's romantic
i feel bad for not really having paid
much attention to the story now i'm
paying attention to the story
trailer park oh
what are we doing ah we check is my does
my wife live here
keep an eye out for my family oh they do
guess so yeah
go for surprise visit but you know you
know the cops are going to be swarming
the place because they're going to go
look for his family and they're going to
be like hey let's just have a look
around
we should wear them we should wear like
sunglasses or something so they don't
recognize
because we're in the newspaper mr fancy
pants with a college degree in the
banking job
not like never been to a trailer park
i'm here with you now
there's another car we could repair if
we want to do another one of those jobs
anyway let's find you true facts but
this one looks like it might be a little
more difficult i'll level up if
there's a bunch of cards here what the
hell is you doing okay bro
i'm sure you're having a rough day but
i'm looking for someone
a woman and a woman huh i used to have a
gorgeous woman
oh shut up oh here he goes
who cares i wonder if we can find
evidence
a woman huh i used to have a gorgeous
woman
keeps going on and on look at me now
hello
car okay no ah let's listen to him what
happened okay
i lost all i had did you know that the
odds are always in favor of the casino
okay whatever i don't believe him
i don't believe he'll help me
[Music]
where are you is that my wife god bless
no she has a baseball bat oh [\h__\h]
yeah she'll beat you up he better be
back soon
oh man i wouldn't want to be him she
wants to beat up his
her husband oh really
she wants to break his knees nice know
what i did
can i help just husband i put him under
the car and then
all right all right oh god take care
oh my wow she's a bit aggressive
that's good you just do random things in
this game
is there anyone who can actually help me
find my wife just gotta look around
playing some baseball we want to play
some baseball hey you want to play some
baseball with me
oh my god play baseball
hi there hey man
start batting sure thing here here we go
oh i would have to oh i don't know you
can play with those
guys i guess can you yeah go find your
family i'm gonna play some baseball
wait what
i've been through here before damn it i
didn't really hear though
[Music]
how about you dude hey i'm looking for
someone
huh that's my problem a woman and a boy
this time have you seen them so that
probably no
not my problem why don't you leave me
there is such a thing as just being a
decent human you know
yeah come on help me please we've seen
them
they live around here somewhere maybe he
can play baseball he's throwing
curveballs in
what an [\h__\h] tell me something he
wants money from you
oh sorry i was i was looking at your
screen thanks for nothing
get him some liquor get him some liquor
he'll help you
now that's a home run yeah it is a home
run i hit you with the ball
[Music]
america
you talk to the to the guys in here
right uh yeah a little bit now that's a
home run
oh it is a home run i found my i found
my bum where's your sunny boy
he's probably gonna be like dad you lied
to me oh crap
yeah he's gonna be sad you're gonna have
to deal with that huh i probably need
you for some progress now
okay i'll stop betting i'm just gonna
let me go forever
by the way the collab is in one hour
from now so oh yeah it is huh
uh we have like about half an hour left
maybe yeah
where are you i obviously go through
that go for the
that room okay and then go down
okay there i am
i see you all right bye my baby boy
let's go get your boy i'm fine
yeah i have a bad feeling
over here
didn't see that coming
[Music]
god now she she's got your back though
seems good afternoon everything all
right around here
what do you want mind if we ask you a
few questions
yeah i do mind i'm kind of busy here
ma'am
your husband is broken out of prison
cool that's not my problem
ma'am okay i have no clue where he is
listen
if he tries to make contact with you you
let us know yeah
sure oh you really think that off pretty
well
[Music]
she would tell you
i'm surprised they didn't find it yeah
that'd be she cute
i like her shirt she wears a pair of
high-waisted jeans pretty nicely
yeah yeah got a nice body
all right she cute leo very lucky
oh my god reunion i love that the cops
dip out and he just comes out of the
bushes
hey baby hey babe i'm back from prison
alex but that's not very emotional i
thought they were gonna cry and chant
i mean she saw him recently at the
prison oh
it's so emotional that he's finally out
what the hell
why is she not giving money no longer
kiss he's
just a little bit upset yeah just a
little bit
he found out yeah he saw it in the
papers
oh [\h__\h] that's why you don't even open
up newspapers
so i don't read the newspapers
yeah this is uh vincent
it's innocent hey linda
i need to tell you what's going down yes
but first
you need to go talk to alex of course go
talk to your sonny boy
okay let's see how i'll explain that to
him why the hell i was impressed
in your house i'm gonna talk to your
wife
don't feel my wife okay i'm just gonna
hey i just gotta chat
that's a really nice bike alex thank you
thanks
oh how long have you known leo
why alex i guess leave me alone
alex no don't go
[Music]
so uh this is a hab shiki 57 right
a 59. it's really a beautiful bike
what a nice conversation we're having
thanks
leo is getting a bit emotional goes to
the treehouse he has a tree house that's
nice
you get something for me here
i'd like to help i just didn't want to
be weird you needed help
yeah i do he drew me a wrench from the
shed over there oh with the head
absolutely man you're sunny boy ma'am
don't call her ma'am she doesn't like it
wanna throw darts later
oh we can throw some darts if you want
oh we're in darts yeah actually hold on
can we throw darts now i
i know i need to give her this wrench
but here can i just set this down really
i can't darn it you go ahead and throw
some darts i'll join you shortly
all right my boy ran away anyway he
doesn't care about me he started up for
me
yeah oh god i'm really bad at firing
guys um
i'd love to start up your motorbike but
i want to go play darts with my man
right now wow
that's not bad oh
oh let me go start up your wife's
motorbike
here we go here ma'am we started your
bike for you
all right and that's not that
hard rowing dodge is harder
in real life oh i got 80 points
you might even do better
are you feed help got it
now i want a person all righty i'm going
to see my son
oh w
i wish i had a tree house when i was
younger that's so cool
[Music]
i wonder if we need the bike for
escaping later or
just let me up alex oh he doesn't want
you to go in this tree house
come on talk to me i'm just trying to
what's this
and to be with you
hey look your sign is broken
why don't you come down and help me fix
it
all right oh don't worry i'll fix it for
you
leo's got you dead i think i'm going to
need that i mean i
i know that i was
trying to get it i mean i know that i
was saying that venison is
is the dad but leo really is quite the
dad
alex's house oh i'm fixing it for you
maybe you'll forgive me then my dear
friends
oh this sign is beautiful alex you
should come down and see it
oh he's coming down gally
my son
nelly are you alive i am
hello you're eating huh no i'm here
can you hear me yeah yeah oh dad he
loves dad
that's cute oh my god i love you so much
so sweet kidding me
daddy she wants to play best you know
i'm better than you at basketball right
no you're not yes i am
you want to shoot some moves that could
be fun but maybe we should get going
shut up
[Music]
baseball and darts yeah
that's what i'm saying in method i'm
more like leo but in personality i'm
more like
are we playing against my son are you
guys ready oh we're ready
let's go let's play some people against
my son oh
oh my god what uh what what oh my god
what
you and your son what's going on
huh why what is happening wait what
uh i think we just have one one hoop
are we finding a dance in general okay
you want me to pass the ball to you
buddy
yeah let him go
here hey buddy look i'm ready to pass
you the ball
here i'll pass you the ball go ally
go alex take the shot thank you wait
what the [\h__\h]
who's don who's team i don't understand
the team we're in any team we're just
like entertaining him
probably until the police comes probably
until the police come
hey what the hell let me pass it to you
then you gotta take the shot
i'm
[Music]
yeah you help him you're going to be so
weird of vincent
that'd be so strange you're good alex
you're really good
good job alex really i'm your uncle now
you don't have a choice in that i'm your
uncle
yeah okay your natural talent i need
some one-on-one time with my wife kelly
hey beautiful brb well would you look at
that
you guys seem to be getting along all
right
i'm gonna play one-on-one with my alex
he's shooting at you
i'm just happy okay let's play yeah
me too come on here keep yeah let's just
pass the ball back and forth
let's talk oh my god
spend some time with your son we gotta
get moving
this is so weird you know what shoot it
just leave
that's right where's my is that my home
harvey will leave us alone
well he just kind of appeared out of
nowhere like a ghostie
hold on i can play basketball he is one
of these that's the life
leo let's just deal here come on yeah
come over here so you can take another
shot and i can help you and it can be
really awkward going after harvey
he's not going to go get the ball get
the ball
no you need to come over here my my son
my son my son with that [\h__\h]
i need to find him i'm sure he knows
where harvey's hiding
this is my son now
this is my son they work outside
i know but i'm just saying you should
look out the window
because i'd be very worried about
vincent and alex being gone yeah
no don't just yeah me get back safe or
i'll kick your ass
okay i promise by the way do you still
have that piece
yeah yeah we definitely left i
definitely stole your child
why would you do such a thing we're
gonna go play basketball in other places
now
no
oh there you go i got another gun
i guess i'm the fps player in this game
once again
do your best hey look you'll be better
than me
i doubt it oh yeah the window and we are
gone did you see my shots
yeah you were really good like i said
you're a real pro the basketball court
in the back would you like to come to it
we can be a real family your father is
in prison so come hang out with me in
upstanding
shut up it's my son will you take care
of your mom now don't take him away from
me one more game
next time i promise he's my baby
unless we ditch my wife and we just um
raise him together
yeah two dads i feel kind of bad because
she's very beautiful
and seems nice but i think the two of us
could we could play basketball all the
time
but if we raise alex together we can be
like the
the top criminal trio in the world
yeah yeah yeah take over all the bags
and all the diamonds
yeah and we can play basketball anytime
we took a school bus sure this ray guy
is that how busses look over there just
normally
she may be pretty but she has no
basketball skills not like my mansion
this way hey hey hey where do you think
you're going
to talk into this blocked off area silly
i think this is a coffee shop
this is a construction site you can't
just waltz in here sure we can
should we bluff or um threat or bluff i
want to fret him
okay yeah let's let's beat him up or
aura or whatever
you're gonna do what relax don't worry i
got this
what's your name get him leo do you need
my name for
what's your name you're gonna be in my
death note
all right i'm gonna write him down into
my little death note i need your full
name please
see your boss ray once we do that i'm
gonna break
where is just doing his job until i get
the information i need
long and hard about what you're gonna
say next if it's not gonna be hey guys
you're welcome then we have a problem
are you serious do i look like i'm
joking do i
get him leo okay then i hate that guy
so you're welcome okay that was
nice that's a beautiful twist of events
thank you
yup thanks where can i find them it's
easy just ask around
all right larry thank you yeah hi you're
welcome oh wow
did not expect that okay i'll take it
you've got to frighten them really
nicely i guess that's one way of doing
it
yeah i literally just said that vincent
it did
but you know yes being nice can work so
harvey is in here i'm sure it does but i
can't help it
i've been like this since i was a kid is
that toiling do you need three years
oh okay i guess you're um in the toilet
for a little bit i don't know what
you're talking about how's it going here
getting some reading material yeah do
you have a magazine um i will take a
look if i find one
oh that's fine if you don't have one
there's just no point
hey that is so weird
you just said right then wait how do we
do we get anywhere honey
i don't see i don't think
here let's go across the bridge oh there
was a bridge what the hell how did i not
see that
we're in the big city now we are
wow do you know where rey is
no i guess you don't that's fine hello
sir would you like some help or would
you like to tell me where we can't talk
to them again
sorry can i ask you a question can't you
see i'm busy here
i just wanted hey i am busy
where is your foreman gage please speak
louder
oh i lift heavy [\h__\h] man until my back
breaks
broken easy enough you want me to help
you
help me good for someone oh yeah me too
my damn doctor fix my back same please i
need a doctor to fix my bag
please i can't help you either oh yeah
can you can we
can you refer me to him like can you
have a business card of your doctor i
see you have a walkie-talkie
that's right could you reach your
foreman with it
oh my god we can do arm wrestling but
since i haven't seen you around here
before
i like all these minigames
let's go oh kelly
it's okay i'll find him on my own okay
kelly me nobody already
me how strong you are go go go yeah yeah
you can't handle here i'm here i'm ready
for this
give me your hand this is nude
how do
what do we hold it or do we push it i
think it's tapped
[Music]
my finger is getting
all right
[Music]
ugh
most intense collab
i've done this a lot at the arcades
and you have to press the button over
and over and over again
are you getting down yeah you can't
handle it no i'm fine
do you like i'm chilling do you like how
sweaty my hand is when it's rubbing
against yours huh
you like it it's not gonna work whatever
you're trying to do right now it's not
going to work
you like it i like how your hand feels
and mine
inside when they're intertwined i like
it
[Music]
it's not gonna work this is i i will i
will i will do this forever with you
callie i'll do this forever with you too
we can go forever we can go overtime
into the collaboration i mean i think we
both got something out of that
tired arms really tired bosses
i don't know i haven't seen him all day
oh my god
again you know where he is who the hell
are you don't mind him
he's just scared no
what is he scared of heights yeah why is
it always me
always you yes it is oh he just
i've already blown my back out too late
for him right well
oh empty yes it's too late
but get out of here listen let's go okay
on the way
we don't have much time left though i
hope we find another responsible um
yeah end the game today same
oh man i haven't even scheduled the next
stream
yet oh [\h__\h] no [\h__\h] can you explain
this [\h__\h] well uh
yeah it looks like you just spit it out
it's two here
i told you oh is this ray he seems mean
no no i can't
no no no no no no what are you some kind
of stupid i think you misunderstand
[\h__\h] idiot oh well uh
[Music]
go vincent go quickly we're going to go
beat him up
oh guys
i see him that must have been painful
oopsie
and he got the way
oh god this is this is like an action
movie like in a bomb movie or something
that's up to you leo it's up to you
it's fine i got him now he's mine are
you sure about that
i won't i won't i never let them escape
it always ends the way that i want it to
be on the way
i'm in another elevator whoa i like to
take some elevators
i think i was on top of yours that
worked out well
i'm gonna kill him oh [\h__\h] no need to
use that now okay
no there is i agree with leo
he could appear around the corner and
then what will we do we'd be boned
maybe he also has a gun exactly
which way should we go i'll take this
okay i'll take the
i'll go this way you take the stairs
okay i don't think there's anything here
anyway
yeah oh really okay i need to shimmy it
you can join me over here we're just
shimmying
interesting let's see
we can find ray once we find rey we
should probably stop huh
yeah oh god it's really late now [\h__\h]
whoopsie doodle too bad i wish we could
do
this for like four hours or something oh
right
that's what we need to do next time the
next one we need to finish the game
wait no there's another container
[Music]
yeah he's gonna kill him i will destroy
you
let's use that okay we're gonna use the
crane oh my god
do you know how to use a crane no but
we'll figure it out
how do we oh wait uh one has to hold
hats to hold on to it
over here all right probably
what all right jump on
oh all the way okay okay got it wait no
the other way
how do i lower it wait how do i lower
what button was it
yeah here bring it over here
how's that now oh there we go it gives
me something
i go there you go okay
got it ah he wants to stand on it oh
thanks kelly
thanks for the ride let's go let's go
how are you doing nobody knows get out
no i don't see him anywhere i don't know
where he went
keep looking he's gotta be up there
somewhere [\h__\h] oh yeah i'm scared
he's hiding whoa what about that
question oh no i don't need to help you
now pull out the gun come on come on
cut them off we got no time for playing
around here
just kill him whoa
yeah i think we need information from
him though so maybe that's not the best
idea
oh
simians jimmy
shimmy oh no what
what are we doing this is insane
he's gotta move this is insane
it's totally normal all right i'm going
to cut them off i'm going to cut them
off
here we go it's me i've come for you
just as i knew i would party time friend
party time
no no you want to hug me
you're so fine up there i'm dangerous
i'm coming listen leos
[Music]
i can only dodge his feet for so long
don't let it go oh my god no no no no no
what the hell
i'm coming i'm coming i'm coming i'm
there yes leo thank you
hold on we're gonna shoot him it's over
it's our [\h__\h]
got him it's up to you now buddy both of
us yeah let's let's beat him up together
let's beat him yeah
give me the old one too uh oh there we
go
that's fun yay can't fasten your old
dudes
okay real quick this is confusing oh
yeah
i go there don't let him get through the
door
let's corner him let me go yes i need
your help
you could run away from us too no one
can run away from takamoti
yeah now it's time to grill him okay
you're gonna mean
hopefully they make it quick so we can
go to our college tell me where harvey
is
[\h__\h] you i ain't telling you [\h__\h] you
will damage me
okay here we go oh look at this
a gun i wonder what you could do with
this if you could stick it up your ass
you know what let's put it here i think
leo is my favorite
i love innocent but i think leo is back
but i see a lot of different things here
that could make this guy talk
what do you say oh yeah that's it are we
gonna i've got a few ideas
i've got a few ideas oh no or not
oh let's have some fun
a lamp a lamp ooh what does this do
he's about to get a real shock oh you
sure oh
a nail gun oh no
you
get him with him where the money is
should be some useful information
in here oh no if we can't just take his
money and threaten him that way okay i
guess i'll just go for the gun now
you for real do it
i don't give a [\h__\h] are you sure wow
about that that's
nothing compared to what harvey's gonna
do to me go ahead do it well but you
might be dead before harry can do
anything
you can't do it i'm gonna burn you here
maybe you can do it leo
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] me huh how about your dick
i got your money i'm gonna take all 20
bucks in here and i'm gonna go buy
some wine and uh some cheese doodles
that's entirely oh
you're nourishing now always he has a
family oh hang on a minute he has a
family hold up
we use pretty much everything oh there
we go all right here we go
start talking then how can we believe
that he doesn't lie though
somewhere exactly in mexico i don't know
where exactly but he's in mexico
he's got a big mansion there it's the
truth i swear
so that's where the rat is hiding huh
yeah that's where he is
don't tell him i told you you don't tell
me what to do all right all right
see you later hey let's go guys yeah
he's got a mansion in mexico but that's
anyway nice we know where he is very
roughly and very roughly yeah now we
know where to go next
guess we're heading down to mexico then
mexico yeah yeah
together we need bigger guns than this
yeah i think we are huh let's go get a
couple old betsy's
maybe 20. what does it look like
wait step aside
oh oh you're gonna do it the smart way
huh
yeah that's right oh good jump
nice yeah yeah didn't know you could do
it that way
mm-hmm okay
i got a contact that might fly us down
to mexico
oh oh that's the flashlight
maybe oh i got an idea on how to get
those guns
but we're going to need cash cash
[Music]
why didn't we take that guy as well
we're robbing a bank now
true easier places to rob the banks or
like what store oh oh no
leah okay but can you have to say that
you can stop now
i think we can i think it doesn't it
auto save i'm pretty sure that
did it we just need to finish the scene
up so that
for sure i think okay cool i think now
this is where we'll bring it this is
where we'll we'll bring it next time
we'll start off at this gas station next
time so yeah this is a good stopping
point
can a chat confirm that it's like safe
to
quit now yeah it'll save here they say
okay it'll save here should be fine i'm
closing the game now
okay me too yay we did it that was fun
there we go
we spent a long time thank you everyone
for coming to the second part
of a way out we are right in uh 25
minutes
on all of our channels it's going to be
the whole
hello member collab oh no
yeah you got to go do your stuff so i
also gotta do um
quickly some stuff so i'll see you guys
in 25 minutes i hope you enjoyed the
collab and you the next one will be
again at cali's channel so
check that out later guys
i'm here more i hope you remember me
peace
[Music]
you