[Music]
for
KY oh yeah yeah yeah yeah don't worry I
had it downloaded since last
night yeah welcome yo it is
time to play
another Yakuza
game he I'm so
[Music]
excited okay and
it actually downloaded pretty fast last
night anyway look at my cute
outfit I don't know if the artist who
drew this uh is watching um you did make
a separate version where it's only the
shirt but can you also make a separate
version of only the bat because then I
can attach the bat and the shirt
separately cuz like this like it yeah it
moves together very wobbly but it's cute
it's like my the Hawaii shirt that I got
to to Twin with narissa but it's made to
be like you know
cleavage nice
yes it accentuates my
Bonas
beautifully yeah I played the sequel now
it's a sequel and no the prequel I
played the prequel now it's a prequel
this is the sequel as far as I
know it's I guess they are kind of done
with their OG protagonist and from now
on will the story always revolve around
ich did they just
retire the other
one we did play as you can see here in
my PlayStation game list which isn't
very big but you can see we also played
Yakuza
zero oh she doesn't
know I mean k i i I assume Kido is in
this game sure in some form
sure is he even on this picture wait
this screen doesn't
fit
uh there we
go
okay so we're starting a new game series
he's right there there Ah that's him huh
he dyed his hair gray or is it just
naturally gray now no he dyed it right
he's looking so
cool he's literally in front of you he's
lit on the cover yeah okay okay okay I'm
aware I'm aware yeah yeah sure sure but
still ichan is the protagonist right
although they do be
standing back to back so maybe I guess
he'll get much more Showtime than he did
in the previous like a dragon where you
know that's the a cool entrance but like
he wasn't the big part of the
game at all
so that's jordu unrelated to
K twin brother no dual
protag wellow I automatically just have
a a closer bond to Ichibon because I
started
playing the series with Ichibon as the
protagonist oh oh oh did we drop a we
should be back already normally I think
we just dropped a few
frames just just a little bit of weight
has been
dropped uh but besides that it looks
stable oh I ah oh oh no oh
no oh
no
uh oh
[\h__\h] oh
no I think it's oh I think it's back
are you like
that uh and now it should be back I say
ah you say
[Music]
B let's
see probably some more lag now because
of the rout the droppies the drops
I jinxed it
[Music]
on
are we back it looks green
[Music]
again please please be
stable I say I you say
[Music]
B oh there we go that wasn't too long I
okay I think it kind of resets the the
delay okay I was I was about to cry
don't oh no oh no please be stable
please be stable please be
stable please be
stable I don't know I I can't trust it
it was stable during the loading screen
right didn't did it do anything weird
during the loading
screen
I do have it by the window of course
but yeah I moved it around here and
there in front of the
window don't think so loading screen was
fine
right so
weird but I think maybe maybe now we're
fine oh [\h__\h]
gu please let me stream hi hi chunky
wonky
so anyway we're back to being a cat
we're back to being a Yakuza and I hope
this is going to work out let me pour
some water and see if the internet is
going to stay like this or if it's going
to say [\h__\h]
[Music]
you it is time to contact my lawyer and
threaten the internet provider because
I'm losing revenue and I can't
work
but I don't know what the like what the
what the legalities are with that or
well but I might I might
ask oh wow PS5 yeah what was that news
about PS5 lowering their price and then
I see some people saying damn I still I
still don't have my PS5 I still don't
have
one like the I think the headline was
kind of confusing a lot of people
thought they're just ending their life
circle no it's at it's at the end of its
life circle and that's why they're
lowering the price yeah but I got it for
free long time
[Music]
ago what why can't I sue why do I need
to elaborate to you guys in order to sue
the
provider on the second it's on the
second half but
yeah what a deal free from a Bandai
Namco uh and now I'm playing a game that
is not from Bandai
Namco but it's okay I can do what I want
with this PlayStation we're going to I
guess we're going to get into it it
looks
[Music]
fine shall we go
Sega let's go
oh it I haven't seen you in so long let
me smash your head with my bat oh inish
Sho I think let's go with iny Sho what
about the audio last time I think we had
Japanese
right it's got to be Japanese that's not
even what am I even thinking it has to
be say
go say go says call oh
wow oh that's loud is it fine
guys
W fine yeah
okay look at his stance like he's so
determined how I don't even really
remember oh it's kind of loud for
me I don't even remember
uh the end of the game last time and all
that but I heard that there is an option
somewhere to
reminisce
reinis okay I lowered it a little bit
more for you guys as well okay should I
change any settings by the way oh and oh
this is only in case you already played
the game on PlayStation 4 I guess I wish
you would get some kind of like Easter
egg if you played the previous game
CH won chky
wonky ah don't push over the router
please she's looking out the window and
meowing sounds out uh a tad bit lower
than my voice okay that's probably
good yeah like carry over data maybe
like even carry over some items or so
that you had in the previous playr maybe
even my
money you know when in games in like pre
sequels in the prequel you had like 5
million of the currency of the game and
then you play the sequel and suddenly
with no explanation from the game
whatsoever you start with zero again
zero money and zero
level suddenly you're broke
again I don't know probably all of that
oh right is there like uh
subtitles on large wide
okay
okay spent it all lck of the gambling
off screen yeah okay that's a good
explanation uh that the two images are
you oh dear
two what there's
two what
there's nothing on the on the white one
right oh wait there holy [\h__\h] my screen
is [\h__\h]
up I I at this point I can very slightly
see something is going on in the white
one but nothing on the on the left side
oh [\h__\h] yeah I was always thinking my my
screen is [\h__\h]
up
uh but even on my other
screen I can only see it at at this
point uh yeah my monitor setting leave
it as
default
uh I don't know maybe maybe like here
leave it in the middle yeah know I mean
I guess like maybe it looks like weird
to me but depending on your screens it
will look different
anyway h
yeah I need to calibrate I always was
thinking that also in terms of like
colors not just the
brightness this game ises an OB a
feature okay thank you this game is a
work of
fiction wait that's not sure though that
there's something representing real
entities no so one person at
least that statement was only partially
true was it not
o mind the road now wait there are dogs
in the locer out here wait why not nongo
we're out here awfully late is it
foreigners did we choose nongo I say the
meeting was worth it with all the
homeless around these days there's no
shortage of M didn't we chose me H and
tonight marks a big step forward in
solving that who this Japanese people I
suppose you're right but dear I did want
to talk about price did I [\h__\h]
up so they are oh that's that's really
confusing starting the game with English
dialogue no matter what language you
chose
uhoh
[\h__\h] they're in Hawaii yeah but still
like when you choose Japanese it's like
what's going on oh my God what the [\h__\h]
Mafia M
Mafia
how finished oh that sounded like an
accent I like the red
light time for your reward yeah that's a
Japanese person speaking English oh oh
come
[Music]
on sub sometimes give me headaches I'm
sorry but I think I prefer it with the
OG you know
[Music]
Mafia in my Yakuza
game what the
[\h__\h] what is this bugs the bugs uh uh
movie oh my God it really
is the bugs life is that what it was
called I love that
movie
oh my God ants I I understand what
they're saying now because of the
because of me pressing the button
yesterday it's uh saying let's go new
Yakuza game I waited for this for years
too bad I can't really use a controller
because I don't have fingers [\h__\h] when
will I finally make controllers for ants
like me and other insects that can't use
that thing you know
discrimination okay oh it's a finger
what was I thinking
poor ant but if the ant is there they
honestly have some kind of issue with
like sugar or
something at this place is familiar
isn't it we we looked for jobs wait each
one what why are you doing this
job why is he working here
[Music]
hello work contract
why he looks so like put together though
nice
see
[Music]
one has like this
real passive aggressive
smile is he shaking shaking
what is this what is this
interview well you can barely see it
take off your
shirt
or as Ariana grand says yes
and
yeah yeah okay yeah no maybe not that's
a discussion that's really difficult it
depends with a Yakuza ask Yakuza I might
really be
concerned generally like you know if you
had just a tiny ass crime and you know
you were in in prison for a while it
shouldn't be like if it's a like a
stupid crime it shouldn't be much more
difficult for you to find a new job and
go back into you know Society
right so you're part of the
problem there a lot that requires it
yeah in Japan probably
many I love it yeah let's
go yeah be
quiet louder oh oh oh this is really
quiet
huh
eat my words
for well I mean with that attitude
dude you're still just like aaku
oh oh oh
[Music]
oh no he sounded
like like pen he didn't sound so badass
anymore at the
end game too loud now for [\h__\h] sake I
turned it down again a little bit
yeah
[Music]
the
Clapping they're still clapping so
awkwardly
okay did he straighten his
hair
the
orange from Golden
hour golden hours are most
flattering time
ever
her [\h__\h]
yeah yeah okay but why is he working
here
trying to have a normal
life but then turns out he can't live a
normal life here CU everybody knows him
so that's why he goes to
Hawaii orange light pretty orange bird
pretty I
stop I see okay I should get some grub
before I head home grab Garfield either
I go for a sit down place or play it
safe and get a beef ball
kind out of the way but I could check
out the restaurant on Central Street and
go for a beef ball if I ain't feeling it
okay oh wow oh wow I like this I need
like comparison shots oh God the
camera oh the picture wait the picture
looks funny look his
face oh oh okay I need to get used to
this like camera it's like way
to wobbly oh my
God I feel like this will look much
better if I wasn't playing it on a small
PC monitor I should play it on on a TV
screen sure it's great that they've got
someone like me and hello work I'm
looking out for them I don't know am I
really
wow wow splash
splash
oh I can't run yet I think unless I have
the wrong button
anyway
examine Apple defense yummy energy
drink boost defense and I think it's
said willpower oh wait there it is that
that's the button don't think the
restaurants is okay
yeah sorry the camera is like throwing
me
off I can probably change it yeah oopsie
oh oh no oh no move the cursor to
any hover open an establishment on the
map and
press yeah cool I guess it's the same as
before uh in terms of functionality uh
that's not what I oopsie that's not what
I wanted though uh I wanted
this are you okay
ichan
is is he
okay that did he like I don't know get
like I don't know a stroke is his face
stuck like also his teeth look
funny oh my God is he
okay ich
[Laughter]
B look at
him oh my God what who is this he looks
so different too in this
one this is oh my God I'm concerned
about him blink twice if you need
help I don't think he
can increase the bid oh oh yeah that's a
problem with a pretty game like this
[Music]
oh I don't think I can dude
oh is it really
bad cuz this is a compromise so that I
can stream you
know I genuinely don't think I
can yeah cuz we're
720 and then 30 FPS and
2500 bit
rate yeah just just see it as like a
throwback to how shitty my first like a
dragon one stream was nothing beats that
okay I'm just like lowkey trying to
throw you back to that time and then
later on it will look better in the
future if I ever get better internet
again ah yes the sponsored
stream technically still HD yeah I want
to
like at some point they're going to say
720 is not HD anymore it's just going to
be like 480 is now
anyway
settings uh what was I going to change I
the camera right display no
game
uh is it it's horizontal right oh no
that's not I guess that's not this one
this
one maybe minus 5 and then Audio Oh no
uh audio settings oops see let's make
sfx probably a little bit quieter and
then the
music but then we're going to keep the
voices like
this so like this
maybe
yeah okay it's much
slower
hi oh pretty golden hour hey working
hard or hardly working I owe him a
soccer rematch do
I I don't think holy [\h__\h] I'm huge oh
he's just
tiny I'm huge all the way he runs there
so
they're all talking to
me and they're saying the same thing she
says the same thing as that person over
there think of something original don't
let me go there there's a
suitcase
[\h__\h] will I ever get the
[Music]
money is too cheap right now and I'm
going
to so I'll need
more no that's like really not
much
P
us
[Music]
run
yeah he really wants a job man I feel
bad
[Music]
damn yeah and what you say that's
okay oh except for you
[Music]
for I just pick it up it was just five
BS
[Music]
for let's
go shut Up And Take My
Mind our first opponent uh okay how's
this working and use the commands menu
cuz like the fighting in in like a
dragon was very different from the other
uh Yakuza game so I wonder how it is now
select attack to perform is it is it
rounds again
oh it is round
again
uh
okay I do like the round uh combat as
well so that's fine quickly select
attack before a down enemy gets up to
strike them for heavier
[Music]
damage oh okay yeah we had this before
right nice we're
wrestling how do I
BL I don't remember there's probably a
button for
that yeah turn base to select skills to
unleash a powerful ability and exchange
for mental points your current MP is
displayed in the green garge at the
bottom right so where I am recover MP
with basic attacks so by selecting Etc
and use using the appropriate item mhm
skills will activate action prompts
where successfully in putting square or
triangle will increase the damage you
dish
out
[Music]
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah is coming
back I think uh how do
[Applause]
I too bad I don't know the PS controller
that well but this time I I did it right
press Circle the moment you attack to
perform a perfect guard wasn't I really
[\h__\h] at perfect
guards I don't know was
I in a lot of games I
[Music]
am the same move as like a
dragon I was pretty good oh really all
right I was de okay oh all right all
right good past Wawa good for you
okay that's all for now the red go wait
I didn't even get the block the red go
at the bottom right displays your health
points if the party leader HP hits
zeroid It's game over you can recover
health with items so grab a
snack uh if you need to fuel up at last
this concludes the battle tutorial now
you're on your own okay but he's almost
dead anyway get him get him get
him nice we take a fro candy somehow myo
already
hurts he missed oh that's why I couldn't
block it
yeah I guess
so I by the way before the stream I did
I did a stretching routine so hopefully
I I I I
can keep that up for a while cuz I kind
of stopped stretching routin and now I
should do it
again yeah cuz body is in much's
pain level up
y
who ouch no the money
no is he jumping for the
money what wrong with you ich
[Music]
that's not into the
water
oh my
[Music]
God
nut [\h__\h]
dark now he's suddenly
nice they told you
that I remember this place
too didn't we stay in the
house
[Music]
foree
foree damn they can't do
[\h__\h]
[Music]
for
for stop being
[Music]
romantic
spee fore
foree oh my God dramatic
okay
[Music]
foree
fore
H got to grab some
lasaga really want some
lasaga Uber
Eats Dam times of
change
[Music]
oh oh let's
go that's so
cute
[Music]
yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum conven waa what what was outside of
that
convenient oh Saku
Saku eating snacks at the Saku
bar oh oh oh oh oh oh it's like her back
in the
musical
wow I like it I want to Swing Swing
Swing
Swing hi girl what's up cuy
[Music]
Pato hi everybody loves him your suit
looks so good please come back so I can
take it off later
[Music]
oh not that shitty
place why you still living in that
shitty
place
a I show those pictures again what a
cute BN B he has a b
bed know he share it
with searching
[Music]
someone oh good morning
go what a nice
intro who the [\h__\h] gets up like
that so
motivated what don't what doing the best
I
can oh this reminds me of the Cat's
[Music]
game nice looking sharp
nice here's helping Sasaki actually
shows up today guess there's only one
way to find out time to head to work
hello work I walk into hello work like
hello
work banana but I got to pay my respects
first a the left picture too cute
yeah straight
straight so we do get to look at the
picture again what why does he have that
fancy dress over
there I'm taking off now boss young
Master
a all the
memories everybody wants to be my
[Music]
enemy can't believe it's already been
three years since they both passed
oh wait okay the right one I currently
can't remember can't remember the scene
but the left one I think I remember that
one that was really
[\h__\h] sad wasn't that like something
happened we were like outside by like um
like the oceans side or so on like a
park thingy and then there was this like
really really really dramatic scene and
I think I
cried it was like really intense I think
yeah by the water
right that one was really sad he
know yeah cuz yeah he only found out
that was his real dad after he died
yeah yo those incense it's forever it's
Eternal incense right one was stab by
CL yeah but like did we wasn't he like a
like a
[\h__\h] did we actually care about the
right guy wasn't he
like
stupid am I remembering it wrong I don't
even know what I remember I don't
remember
that yeah right why do we have a picture
he has a rais him
okay oh okay toldo and only breaking up
at the same time they call it the great
disolution nowadays crazy they went out
during the peak of all of that yeah you
know lately I've been so busy with
what's in front of me it might be good
to reflect okay is this the
remines yes [\h__\h] yes let's
go yeah I got some time before work I
have two fathers the first being the man
who raised me J kasuga mhm the other is
my yaka father and old boss Masuma who
we always looked up to and we just
didn't get it we just didn't know the
boss was like a lighthouse to me me no
matter the tide he was always there
guiding me to the
shore I want to repay him somehow even
if just in my own little way it's why I
picked this job finding a place for all
the guys left behind in a great
dissolution was the boss's dying wish oh
really how do you know did he tell us I
don't think he told us I was just
assuming it's been almost two years
since I subed thank you I think a lot of
people joined me um during Yakuza like
Fire Emblem and Yakuza is where a lot of
old these old fans joined
me he shot you and saved your life doing
so wait CH will probably remember that
now can't say it's been fulfilled that
well though no sweat though I'll see it
for just you watch boss and this little
piece of [\h__\h]
Mas a the young Master Mas he was the
boss's son and well to me I guess he was
like a piece of [\h__\h] I mean really we
were like brothers far as I'm concerned
the young Master used whatever dirty
tricks he could to move up in the world
yeah yeah
mhm but those fell through heck at one
point he was planning to end it all I
am to think I talked him out of it he
was ready to start over to keep on
living and even then someone took that
away from him yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
the bastard who did it this guy named
Kum ah wait now I now it's coming back
to me Kum oh oh Kum oh
my this guy named Kum tried to escape
but they eventually caught him he got
busted for all the other crimes he'd
committed too and while he didn't get a
life sentence he's not going oh my we
are going to see him again again in this
game aren't
we oh man not Kum I'm going to [\h__\h]
tear apart my PS5 if I see Kum on the
[Music]
screen Kum was a monster of the young
M's own creation most people probably
tell you he got what was coming from to
him I'd rather not see it that way
person no I I want to see it that way
for
sure even now I still wonder how things
might have been if he had survived if he
been given that
chance wait is there no visual of
reminiscing oh was just text reminiscing
I thought there would be
visuals shoot I shouldn't bum myself out
before work like this all right it's
almost time to go got to give it my all
at the office
today oh man I wanted to see some
visuals
[\h__\h] that would have helped me even more
cuz um I I know I I remembered my hatred
for Kum but I don't remember his face
right
now but I think he was a very vibrant
character is this what fuu's bunk bed
looks
like I used to have bunk beds too and
then later um I got upgraded from bunk
bed to like a loft bed both me and my
brother we had them loft beds which are
really
cool very safe spacing space saving
Here We Go Again wa English wow bright
as [\h__\h] that's kind of cool though like
having this big balcony so to say even
if it's messy but this this corner is
kind of
cute the M
speaker
what do it
again it broke
afterwards can we recreate
that no was that just a lucky one oh no
ah it
broke it breaks afterwards oh my
God no let me take a bath I want to take
a bath I'm stinky I'm still wearing the
same suit
man I like this this is kind of
cute what are we on top
of no what is this place
underneath hey hi oh that looks like
it's like a something like a
club pink sh noodle oh oh we're we're
we're on we live on top of a n
show oh wow let's
go how
convenient let me pick that up Oh wrong
button Suffocation bomb May inflict
silence on a group I feel like these
these uh items I never really used many
of them did
[Music]
I wa which way this this
way
I got to collect all the
items it's so nice to be back in the
Yakuza game did you guys watch the the
concert the musical the akisa musical
even though her solo parts were amazing
man like the camera work was really good
wasn't it and the song Choices and like
oh my God everything was so nice your
singing was so
beautiful mama mia wa why am I going
there I don't need to go there
and then the Musical part it was so much
[Music]
fun there's something there in the
bushes oh someone got
hurt natural
herb lemon and you go that comes up so
many times oh it's
you
I stole the show everybody stole the
[Music]
show so fun so honored to be like
involved in
that so why are you on the
floor Nissa would have been proud yeah I
I want to I want her to watch it
cuz she loves musicals she's probably
sleeping needs to watch it what should I
say to
Haman just land her
shoulder I was going to bring her
[Music]
home
for Imagine in the future when Nissa has
fre I hope a Senai invites her
for a musical
performance narissa will be in her
element oh my
God she tweeted a little while ago I
wouldn't be surprised if she drops by
the stream
[Music]
soona way a jacket way a
jacket that's a wicked lover
[Music]
jacket
H and music will be great I know I know
but it seems like such a
big difficult thing but I I do wonder if
like management in general is just
thinking about since this is so such a
nice nice little project if they might
want to do like a big a big version of
what akis Senai does with like whoever
wants to be involved gets involved and
we make a big hole Live
musical that would be so cool I think I
talked about it before but like what if
one of the future concerts it's just
like musical like a musical
concert but that's so that would be so
intricate so much we need a story and we
need so many original songs
then oh yeah I'm sure they would con
consult Aki
Senai yeah
anyway anyway it was a really a great
experience and I was so happy like I'm
happy she chose that because it's based
on a a Grim's fairy tale um where it's
you know uh a donkey a chicken a cat and
a dog which are in in Germany in ban are
like music musical artists they make
music and so I'm glad she chose that
because with her choosing that it's like
like pretty much a given that I will be
included in
[Laughter]
it
yeah
mhm were the songs from the musical
original to Aki's
live I think
so on on that front I'm not really
sure
I think
so I don't
know yeah like rock yeah my part was
like rock a
billy it so
[Music]
fun
I tried my growl again too are you proud
of me
guys the songs were so much fun man so
much fun so much
energy and then also like Parts where I
wasn't involved like for example the the
okou and akis Senai part was really nice
there were like a lot of harmonies too
that were really
[Music]
pretty
yeah yeah thank you thank you thank you
thank you I don't know why they made me
say all these things like baby baby baby
baby rock you baby baby that's that was
a lot of baby could have been something
else I wasn't
sure what I was
saying baby baby baby baby I felt a
little bit
stupid
[Music]
oh was it a foreigner Trope you think so
I'm not sure what kind of um role I was
playing I was
Elvis Mama
Mia was that your Epiphany for GRE
lighting no that was just because I was
watching
um uh uh Home Improvement cuz in in the
last season in one of the episodes they
recreate that
song uh with everybody in the the studio
they like yeah they acted out they have
like a car and and the choreography and
everything Tim Allen everybody's
dancing
yeah so anyway Kasa personality is
represented by the following traes
passion confidence Charisma kindness
intellect and style did we have the same
thing
before refining kasa's personality will
earn him many perks such as increased
resistance to enemy skills and Status
elements as well as access to new
facilities a personality chances an
opportunity to improve kasa's character
different stats will raise depending on
your selections there are also many
personality challenges which boost your
traits upon completion check them out in
the pause
menu we did right
yeah yay okay let's go to work we're so
excited to go to
[Music]
worku you know Japanese Japanese hint
Japanese
advice
uh you know
oh sorry I'll pay for that oh my God oh
my God oh my God god what the [\h__\h] that
looks like someone had
diarrhea
um so Oru orizu is water in Japanese and
you can say uh you need to buy omizu
omizu Kai or something like that
but but it's not always
omu not always wait now I'm confusing
myself now I'm doubting
myself
yeah yeah okay yeah it's right it's
right so for example like you know in uh
in like every Japanese restaurant the
water is free you know you can have like
and often they even have the water drugs
on the tables but that kind of water you
actually call
ohia
oh and it's written with the Japanese
Kani for
cold so you can say oh instead ofu
because kind of I don't know it's
like in that case you can say both but
Japanese people will often say
ohia and that will make you seem uh like
a professional Japanese
tourist oh not
Ohio
yeah it's cold
water given out in restaurants and so
on where where am I what which where
which one which
cubicle I see the map but it's confusing
me H here no
here yes it's because it's ice water
basically just cold
water
is this the same guy from
yesterday are we starting over he got
like a he got a a
makeover
foree
foree just want to give him a
hug
because he wants to be
honest he looks wet and
moist they we
responsible
for Imagine suddenly kiaba coming out of
nowhere what your job will be
shoplifting
[Music]
n is it like a a tester like to see if
the security is is good or something
like that I don't
know I'm sure something like that exist
oh what what where's that hand where
that does he have a fake
hand is that even necessary doing it
like
that like the right hand is that a fake
one oh the girl is
cute they're testing the security huh
that's so freaky oh my
God what a great job for him
pi oh no way not an expensive shop like
this oh you sweaty
spaghetti don't drop it don't drop it
and this one's
rough oh there they are working
together
[Music]
interesting oh my God this is like the
viral
video of I think like a like a Chinese
lady or so
uh really skillfully preventing
fft everybody it
couldn't prevent this one
huh so like I guess the stores the
managers are so hire these people to
check if it's uh if if the everything's
secure enough if they need to train
their employees better or
so oh he's going after them
daughter is it someone we
know well I know
him like why is here in charge does he
have this company which is uh oh yeah
something
[Music]
for
oopsie I bit my
[Music]
tongue
foree
foreign
so what is he going to tell the
companies that where
they and the stop the
stuff and such a open
store hard to
hide
[Music]
for
Dam you must really have good a good
feeling for
[Music]
her
yeah
I gu they r on
it
[Music]
for
fore spee
fore
do eyes his eyes remind me of like
Labrador he's got really
friendly
[Music]
for he does
right
for so
sweet make the world a better
place he wants to
fix for
foree
[Music]
Fore
for
[Music]
foree oh man I want more br and I want
the Bros to be like
[Music]
this I want him to
talk oh my
[Music]
God
for
30,000
[Music]
for then how can we go to
Hawaii five year ex y was a is rough oh
it's for five years that they're like
blocked from
everything okay so it does go away I
didn't think
so someone text me oh it's n remember
we're meeting at survive tonight don't
be late oh shoot I was so busy with
Sasaki I almost forgot thanks Namba
better hustle over to survive
n it's my number
one I I love
number oh oh side quest or
what please
stop what do you say you better speak up
if you want to be
heard huh what are you looking
at hey see nobody gives a crap about
you nah I wouldn't go that far what
hell are you get away from me get get
away from
him and why the [\h__\h] should we listen to
you cuz if you don't I'm going to send
your ass to the
[Music]
Moon W so scary sounds like someone
needs to face punched
in with
[Music]
pleasure
I'll give you
pleasure ring position you can use your
positioning Rel relative to enemies can
make a big difference especially when
using basic attacks okay
okay yeah okay they said try getting
close to bicy see what happens I I know
he's going to use it a triangular icon
will appear when you're near usable
object selecting attack will let you
pick it up and will a as a
weapon
okay uh
uh wait H I thought I had to pick it up
is he picking it up
is yeah I love that I love that so much
I used to love doing
that I one
block yeah
baby I still got got it mommy still got
it this time it actually shows you and
is more consistent uhuh
okay now hold
on select attack and approach enemy
until the target indicator changes and
proximity bonus is displayed you'll
receive a small damage boost when
striking from close range uhuh when you
back to the wall sometimes every
Advantage
counts yeah he's dead [\h__\h] him
what do you want
eh attacks can sometimes launch enemies
backward they'll take more damage when
colliding with walls op or their friends
skills with the knockback quality do
this too that's all the tutorials for
now get your game face
on yeah baby b baby baby baby
baby
baby o let us Yum Yum
Yum no he's dead they're dead forever
thank you forever I'm
dying baby baby
[Music]
baby [\h__\h] man we're sorry forgive
us I'm not the one you should apologize
to sorry about that yes s so what do you
think just let him go better to keep the
cops out of it well I guess you guys
were lucky just know that won't be a
second time oh yes
sir you already finished it oh my god oh
Speedy aren't
you Speedy
Gonzalez you all right you hurt no I'm
fine anyway thanks it's been a while
since someone's shown me any kindness
and know sweat they just pissed me off
as all I haven't seen you around before
just you just get in yeah the other day
all right you know where to come Bridges
you should try over there way better
than
being I never would have known I'll make
my way over thanks so much
pal oh crap I'm late better hurry to
[Music]
survive n yeah the scumbags enemies that
wander the City Bar con representing
their power coming into contact with
them will trigger a fight make sure to
pay attention to their strength
indicators
oh
okay that's kind of confusing it goes
from red to Pink to Red I know they're
different but
still so the the red one that's not
filled out with color is maybe something
I should
be worried
about
oh that's the camp where I also slept
for a while
huh I
remember do you remember no don't go
there it's so good how he interacts with
the world
though red and blue are okay okay
good
yeah [\h__\h] baby woohoo baby bab bab baby
baby baby
baby can I use this
no easy they don't even deserve to have
a red icon above their
[Music]
head
the worms first the ants now the worms
I'm not eating 20 worms per day I did
not press the button okay by the way I
did
[Music]
watch I Le saw a clip of her playing the
game oh my God
guys
easy this kind of
crazy so I'm concerned I I I must talk
to
you
Superior should I change go over
there more what can run through the
bushes let's go wait where is it let me
look at the
[Music]
map this way and then over the
bridge psychos
SC
yeah oh that's like a side quest is it
oh no
no just him
talking
so many people who want to fight
me wait they look like they work at
those those
bars well the ladies spent a lot of
money to drink with them it also works
the other way
around guys look like that yeah hosle
host
never been to one because um in Japanese
you would describe them as very chai and
I really don't like the chai
looking
guys TR as like I don't
know what flashy
gy well like in a very Japanese way
Japanese trai I would say is different
than overseas trai
I remember this
place the pretty boys the itty bitty
boys no not necessarily the pretty boys
but like I don't know the way they dress
up is just not the way they style their
[Music]
hair it's my
gr did his even
[Music]
l
okaye
spark so sparkly
even dropped some foam just now did you
see it I mean I don't know how this
looks with my bit rate
[Music]
but the Chinese and the Korean
right because we had those issues
too
[Music]
for
yeah
have those
eyes the first game I
swear
so
cute fall in love
with no more n for
me oh never mind I'm in love with her I
forgot he was so
flatter wait I'll join I'll join girls
don't go alone to the restroom we go
together cuz we have meetings like idle
meetings obviously can't have a meeting
alone tell me tell me more tell me more
did you get really far tell me more tell
me
more for
Fore
foree say
it
God it's like they were his
parents true
true got to hit it while
it's
spe
no Shy
Boy
foree
[Music]
they all sound
drunk
definitely
problems
let's
roll like a
dad another father figure for
him don't let her unless is she going
into the taxi you should walk her home
otherwise thank you for the Super
Chat oh
she suddenly gets shot now cuz there's a
cut
[Music]
scene huh
cute or she says I have a boyfriend
[\h__\h]
read the room they're not in a
room she can't read the room if she's
outside oh no ich no you don't
understand she was probably like too
flattered and she likes you though
probably how can one not like
you he's so embarrassed he goes to
Li
she's GNA say yes cuz she was too
embarrassed to say it
directly oh I'm doy doing right now I
should have worn my heart rate monitor
oh my God is this like his
first
ever successful date
invitation oh my
God it's so cute but like it's seems
like it's the first time
ever oh my
[Music]
God
fore
[Music]
hallelujah oh my God you hatched oh my
God I can finally stop sitting on you
thank
god let's
go and now he's so thoughtful thinking
deeply he thinking about what they're
going to
do
there we go that yeah
okay how old is he
now
[Music]
go to to date that's like easy like you
know where you don't have to talk much
to
movie doesn't look like it holy
[\h__\h]
dat
coaching well yeah I would say in a case
like this just go on a movie
days and then
maybe mean with 40 I don't know but why
not
for and if both people like singing you
should go to
k he's 47 if his birthday passed this
year what
oh my
God
is like a Beauty
secret cuz you don't get to eat
much going to [\h__\h] up your skin
right you don't get see much and Sun
kind of makes your skin age as
well it's mostly covered from the Sun so
I mean maybe depends
but it's one way to think about
[Music]
it being coached
already wait can I stop it's like I I I
I I I I I I think like you know um
doesn't matter who I meet like even with
whole life members or so like I I'm
concerned
with I don't want to look if I'm the one
waiting I don't want to look too much
like
I'm I'm desperate because especially if
the person is late like I'm desperate
for you to finally show
up and I I want to be seen first I don't
so I look at my phone even even if I
know you're almost there or so I look at
my phone and even if I can sense you
coming closer and closer ideally I
wouldn't look up until you say hey kiaha
I'm here sorry for making you wait and
then I look up and I'm like oh oh I'm so
surprised because that's cute is it
that
making you come up all the way all the
way to me because also it's kind of
awkward I noticed
this before too I would say with friends
as well when when you when there's like
a really long path like when you're
meeting somewhere and there's like a
really long Street and you see the other
person coming from the other side from
really far away isn't it kind of awkward
when like you you already see each other
from like so far away
and you're like like maybe waving at
each other and you're like hi and then
it's like awkward because like where you
already saw each other and you're like
still so far away and both are walking
in normal speed you're not going to
start
running and yeah where do you look like
I won't I'm not going to stare into your
eyes the whole time until we finally are
at like talking
[Music]
level that's pretty
awkward
it's so awkward right so so awkward yeah
star
down I've even had that with like uh
like a supermarket
person is walking up to the supermarket
and like one of the employees that like
I've talked to before and like
recognizes me was like outside taking a
break like a smoke
break and the employees saw me like from
so far away and I saw her too but it's
like I was hoping they wouldn't like do
anything or react or anything because
it's like so far away what what you
going to make it worse don't don't
immediately wave at me but they did and
I'm like yeah I wave back and then it's
like okay where do I what should I
purposefully look away and look like
unbothered and like I'm cool and all
that it's
so many thoughts in my
brain
yeah I'm I'm too too concerned about
these situations but can you guys not
relate to this kind of
situation I feel like it's relatable
right it's relatable right thank
you and then you want to say like Hi how
are you but like at what distance do you
say cuz I feel like some people somehow
sometimes say it too early and then I
got to
scream while I'm still walking like I'm
fine thank you how are you okay I'm not
screaming but it's like we're still so
far away we should have not opened up to
this the the conversation
yet and that's the problem when you
already see each other like so early and
that's exactly why in like Machi a in
like a like a meet up you're waiting for
someone or or or the other person is the
waiting one idea really don't look at
each other until you're like really
close finger guns and head
nut I'm I'm an anime girl yeah I am I am
I am you're literally speaking my inner
thoughts let's
[Music]
go for I guess
so read a book while you're reading to
look
sophisticated no read a
book
oh yeah yeah lean on
something
what I don't want to see you sleep
makes me cuz that makes me feel bad
because maybe that implies that uh I
made you wait for too long and I
troubled you and you fell asleep cuz you
[\h__\h] tired of waiting for me that's
not
good no
no don't
sleep
cuz then also like you know with narissa
it can't even wake narissa up like I
mean how am I going to wake you up like
like um um wake the [\h__\h] up it's time
for our
date thank
you I'm
becoming
make a sign like an airport
sign
she's yeah
yeah no don't look I agree with that
except for
like gazing firmly into that direction
where she'll be coming from how do you
even know where she'll be coming from
no just look at your phone for God's
sake or read a
book take all my tips guys don't listen
to these
guys you got to in this case if you're a
guy waiting for a girl you got to hear
advice from a lady not from these guys
what do they know maybe Adai knows a
little bit more than Namba though
n's giving [\h__\h] advice so
far you just pick a directions there
yeah you just don't
know uh do I sit down and play cool like
n said or do I follow other stand we
definitely stand proud although I don't
like the gazing in that direction
but as long as we don't sleep on the
[\h__\h]
bench yeah yeah yeah
is that going to change like a cut
scene how it
goes
exactly exactly
son I wonder if we turned down the other
one that we chose what would be his
argument to turning that one down would
it be the Gaze that would be scary like
like I just talked
about for both
AR I think sting is
fine but just don't
sleep doesn't really matter that much
let's be real it will be soon
forgotten
unless if you sleep then I don't think
I'll forget
that I don't think I would forget that
one just standing I'll forget about that
but sleeping thing is
[Music]
unable
also I saw someone in the chat before
saying don't go to a cinema on your
first
date I don't know I think it depends on
the person like who you are and who
you're going to be dating because like
yeah if you're like more of if both of
you are more like an active kind of
person more extroverted then you don't
need to go to cinema but I was just
saying this because of ichan being like
really nervous and and and you know
really
really just thinking overthinking
everything then go to a cinema cuz then
you don't have to talk so much and then
you like I I would say go to the cinema
first and then maybe something else
afterwards because then during the
cinema time you can without even talking
just get used to each other's
presence you know and then afterwards
you have a topic to talk about that is
immediately ingrained in your brain cuz
otherwise maybe if you immediately go
and have dinner or something and you're
real if you're really that [\h__\h]
nervous I guess maybe you're like I
don't know what the [\h__\h] to talk about
I'm totally blacking out but if you just
watch the movie you can talk about the
movie and you're sharing that experience
so if do you like if you both like the
movie you can get like really excited
about it and you know have a good
conversation bouncing off of each other
oh my God I'm a genius I should be a
dating
coach yeah movie then dinner yeah dinner
or I I I feel like I wouldn't really
want to go to like a proper dinner
maybe maybe
something like in kataoka for example
you can have like all kinds of snacks
and all that but I I think I would feel
nervous about going to a proper
dinner uh especially for a first date
because I don't want like I mean depends
on what there is to eat cuz like having
a full mouth and then trying to have a
conversation it's like really uh
nerve-wracking and then what if I what
if what if there's like
what if I what if I I don't know get my
mouth dirty and or or I I don't know I
just can't I I have something in my
mouth that I can't chew on properly
because piece of the meat was like
really BL or or or you know stuff like
that like I would have too many worries
about that too so I don't I don't want
to do
that and then sometimes it gets so
awkward you know when you when you're
when you chew chewing and and and and
the other person is also chewing and
then you have like this awkward silence
or if if if uh you know they're asking a
question and I'm still chewing and I'm
like can't answer yet awkward silence
you just asked the question and I can't
answer
it I hate that I hate
that I fear awkward B too much yeah I do
I
do but yeah I guess you just have to
adjust
to I mean you know the other person to
make them feel comfortable if you know
them if you know if you kind of have an
idea a hunch of what kind of person they
are but when waiting for the food you
can chat yeah but like do you even want
to chat like ichan seems so [\h__\h]
nervous but yeah anyway I think he
should go to a movie and then they
should go to karoke cuz I think they
both like it and it's kind of like
karoke is like a a really
fun thing in Japan like in Austria I
wouldn't go to karok because there I
mean there isn't even any karok places
and the ones that are are like big
public bars where everybody hears you
and I think there's I don't know I don't
even yeah I don't think it's a thing
here but in Japan k I love going to Koka
alone or with friends it's the best
place ever there's even food finger food
and all that let's go
k
yeah yeah you got your own
cubicles and then
game what are they going to say about
that don't go to a burger
Place yeah it doesn't have to be
[Music]
fancy
how much spice you can
[Music]
take evenant of spicy
things don't do it if you're not like
good there you go no no no no no no
no I I'm sorry you lost
me not spice but I feel like you should
go to a restaurant that has more variety
in food if it's a curry specified
restaurant it's just
like you know what what if she's not
into Curry right now what if she's not
feeling Curry what if you know the
curry makes her worry that she's going
to like
smell like Curry I don't
know although I love curry maybe on the
second date you could go ichun but not
this time also what the [\h__\h] the spice
is
dangerous yeah
yeah okay NAA give me a good
one yeah go some you always go so you
can make a
recommendation I mean why
[Music]
not it's kind of cute to have some
so
casual I mean yeah
again not really much
variety it's like different toppings at
least they're they're both kind of
inferior C
but definitely don't go for the Spice
option in that
case unless you're
JMA yeah go for the usual people and
just like yeah share share a part of
your
life and and it makes you feel
comfortable probably hopefully it makes
the lady feel comfortable hopefully we
can only pray
[Music]
confidence think both are easy to as
long as you don't go for
spicy
is right and
wrong he get it he's starting to
understand he gaining
confidence the personality point
yeah that's what I was saying like it
might be good for
us so we're changing it after
[Music]
all good thing is he already kind of
knows her pretty well so he may already
have some hints of what she
likes if you don't really know already
know what this is like after hanging out
for years it's over before it even
started
true I'm sure he picked up a lot of
things I'm sure he did oh wait this
CL
[Music]
yeah I mean the [\h__\h] is
fine but it depends on what kind of
place you're going
to I
guess what you mean awful for the it
depends it depends surely it's not a
good day choice for certain people like
if you don't like to sing for
example yeah but I was saying movie
because if you're really [\h__\h] nervous
then again like extroverts for example
they don't need to go to a freaking
movie for the first date they can go and
have normal dinner or go to a bar or
whatever you know or go bowling bowling
is fun I
guess yeah or something like season
specific like if it's like uh spring you
can go watch the cherry blossom have
picnic on cherry
blossoms that's
amazing yeah I don't know something like
that to each their own yeah it depends
like I would I
personally would not mind at all to be
on the movie and K dat so it's really
individual I would say you
know let us go
bowling wrong
game wait that outfit wait wait wait
wait
wait that was so
white white pants white shirt almost
white
[Music]
Jack
I think that will be a Charming effect
to see you in different
clothes but not
those what's Ada's Choice going to be I
want to see Ada's choice
no not not if you don't go to a super
fancy
place really
fancy now if it's these choices I have
to go for the Casual on it might even
look on each
one too white in reality
the shoes give it a nice contast though
the the
[Music]
brown yeah in that case uh there's it's
not perfect but I would go for the
organic one then show me your casual
side
ich I think he'll Rock It
Anyway he went for the suit because the
hemp jacket look
awful just wait might look great I don't
know if it'll see him where is
but he might look good in
it maybe maybe kind of gives me like uh
I don't know white shirt and white pants
on a
guy if this date goes well it's all
because of them n aan thank you I should
get back home for
now okay are we going to buy those
gloves or or just like trying to
recreate that
home of our own clothes oh now they're
gone very
interesting spicy
oh har the metal looks good
though ooh ooh fight fight fight fight
fight fight fight fight fight
fight
Street Punk is only one he's got a
hammer quick yeah yeah before he hits me
cuz that H Hammer can bang on my
head that's fun yeah it's a cute segment
but um I feel like
the this way of starting the game is a
bit on the slower
side
setting me up for a really long
playthrough of this
game especially cuz I had a lot of
opinions on that
one
oh I really I was trying to figure out
the timing but he took his
[Music]
time yeah you agree
huh I'm not the only one nice it'll
change real quick don't worry okay
ah
[Music]
hi what's the button for
the wasn't I able to press the this
triangle to open the map before I
thought that's what I did how do
I how do I open the big map
you triangle
doesn't a touch I was touch bad pad what
I touched
okay
oh good
[Music]
I so how you guys liking it so far the
game in my playr are you guys playing it
too who's playing the game
who played it already he's even
finished you guys excited for a long
long long Series right after I am back
for my break I'm almost finished only
watching
you chapter
n it's like Paper Mario yeah you get
it
I beat it last night oh
okay [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] get up get
up CH 13 how many chapters are
there I wonder if this game is longer
than the previous
one games are always
long
already beat already in my hard mode
playr
oo you like a
challenge you don't really like yaka
this is so this is your first experience
well maybe you'll start to like
it 14
okay
interesting this is the longest Yakuza
game so far oh my God God [\h__\h] I mean
we're probably not going to do many side
quests again maybe there's some things I
can do off screen who
knows
by
this you're literally so copy paste oh
my
God what there's a timing is it like a
ribm game this move [\h__\h] or it just
press it before it's
gone chapter one took you fre hour oh my
God I guess that's actually fine it's
going to be longer for me though cuz
like I I read all the dialogue out loud
and you know that takes more
[Music]
time you don't have to grind much to
still come to you naturally oh why but
I'm not going to do all of
them like in in in some games I don't
mind sad quests and others I
do cuz they're like I don't
know I don't know something about it
just bothers
[Music]
me oh the chairs are
back
nice I'm home and we sleep okay oh yeah
I guess that's what the game is telling
me to
do F all the chapters Nam
what named after Elis Presley songs
she new summons and money oh yes summons
right
oh y he it kind of looks good on him I
knew he would rock anything
really he looks so summer Vibes she
looks like she's in
Autumn cute
[Music]
though so it does change the
they kind of
matching oh we at
Chinese oh no
[Music]
they oh that sucks you should have you
should have reserved that is a big
mistake ah man got maybe we go to on
after all to the
[Music]
Beall in this case
though this is interesting cuz like you
probably end up going to one of your
comfort food
places and then it's like ah can't be
helped I I had the same thing with nabii
Mama on our date in
Austria I was trying my bestest to make
reservations uh in a cool restaurant for
us I was calling so many places and no
one would take us even though I think it
was for the following no not it was for
that day yeah
yeah wasn't it like Chris around
Christmas or New Year's or
so and then we ended up going to one of
my from my teenage time one of my
favorite comfort food places that I
would go to on on the on the uh the
lunch break uh in school time as well uh
called
Indigo and I I said to Nai I'm so sorry
Nai Mama I'm sorry it's not like not
even rustrian food but you know there I
have memories here so you know you can
feel a little bit I don't know connected
to me cuz you know you know their food
is good they have like curries like
Fusion European kitchen Fusion
curries really yummy I loved to eat
those and it was nice eating those again
for me it was really
nostalgic yeah yummy yummy personal
experience I trust wa and love
advice bet she liked it a lot too dude
she added so much spicy stuff she added
so much spicy sauce and powder oh my God
in America you don't need to make
reservations to go to places to eat only
High cles H
really maybe I think it also depends on
whether or not you're like on the
countryside or like on in the city in
the big
city I think uh if you're if you have
such an important date coming up and
you're already planning out everything
Ichiban why the [\h__\h] did you not reserve
a restaurant that's
big
[Music]
mistake
mhm well now we're going to go to eat
beef balls
right sorry I just poured some water and
literally
wow so close to overflowing it's already
over
the over the surface
thingy no
way no no she's looking at something
else else
right that's not what she means no no no
no no that's not what she
means or
game no wait there there's the people
place over there she's looking over
there double phas
such
phrasing first time dat not some loose
canon Mr
Lio oh thank God what would numberi do
at a time like this hell what would
anyone
do it's not that place that's not what
she
means yeah let's just play it cool cuz
we know I know maybe they're assuming
people could choose this are probably
really thinking that's what's happening
but that's not what's
happening wake up wake up
[Music]
it passion man I'm keeping it cool
because that's not what's
happening such that's not embarrass
ourselves
by telling her
[Music]
something
for why are you
[Music]
saying
oh what
[Music]
for not not it's okay you can still
recover from
that hey what about this place my hotu
having a
smoke it's
weird that's not going to make up for
not having food but yeah okay if you're
both smokers I guess in
between uh see that's why you should
have watched a movie Why talk about
another
guy
[Music]
so like a puppy
for that's a weird topic So
[Music]
Random that's so
r
he just completely changed the
atmosphere from a date one to just a
friendly get together with this
topic Can you feel it it just changed
the vibe
changed
see no wonder we're going to Hawaii
after
[Music]
this
Thank God now she's taking the lead
though but thank
God time to make a
comeback why are we starting this game
with a date this is this is so weird
feels like a side
quest nice shoes
oh proper
place kind of empty
though
[Music]
c yeah
you're
you're great thanks a lot guys oh it's
fine it's nice couple has like etiquette
and rul
[\h__\h]
oh didn't this place come up in the
previous game too Japanese food right
you eat that all the
time it looks familiar to
me oh [\h__\h] I can't even read
these even subtitle it in Japanese
though she's flexing her Kani reading
skills never
mind
don't correct
her SAA made a
mistake I guess now he feels less bad
about not being able to read it now
she's embarrassed yeah you make a
mistake too misread something too what's
the best thing to do here misread
Something
cover cover as
in like moving on is bad but also cover
ing like ah if something embarrassing
happens to me I'm not sure if I want to
like you know stay on the topic and have
you acknowledge
it so much like just act as if like
nothing happened especially if I like
stumble over a stone or something while
walking
like make a bigger mistake yeah that's
what you should be doing not
covering although also if it's unnatural
then it's not good either I don't know
let's
cover
it's not a big deal they're like as if
this was such a big deal oh my
God can't let her St away like this it's
not a big
deal how are you going to
come no don't say like that no
no no no I I regret I we should have
ignored we should have ignored we should
have moved on no no no no I feel
cringe
no we got confident though oh man I
know make the way he says it is really K
and all that but in the context it's too
much no that feels
like not like I don't know not
mansplaining but like that feels like
um uh what's the word you're
you're um
not victimizing either what's
patronizing yeah that felt really
patronizing what he's just saying
now like I'm a
child shut up why did I choose this
yeah
[\h__\h] restart game restart game ah sorry
I moved the microphone I hate that I
hate that I hate that yam
stop y
[Music]
please
uncomfortable
took
[Music]
well uh why are we criticizing
him thank you
such a weird
situation
[Music]
they're
oh yeah I was going to say in Japanese
[Music]
like there we go there we go that's what
I want that's all I really wanted just
make a mistake on your own innocently
and then yeah we get made fun of oh my
God oh my
God cuz like even the thing is the
reason why I'm saying uh of course
you're going to be able to know what
what it is because in Japanese um yeah
there's many different ways of reading
Kani especially also if they're like
connected with something you may read it
differently uh but you still can kind of
recognize what it's about because the
shrimp kanji for example will be just
the shrimp
kanji it may be differently pronounced
in the case but you still kind of can
have an idea of what it's what the what
the dish is made of
yeah you don't look very
urishi your facial expression must have
had some
Botox golden hour
again
nice
her facial expressions are kind of
stiff was all right I guess thank God
she already knew you well otherwise I
don't know if this would have gone so
well
is how standing right
now so slowly menacingly
[Music]
walking
giving them enough time to explain
everything they get
it they perfectly
calculated how long they need to
talk
how they still not already
here as if they didn't see this
[Music]
whole conversation you had and now
you're now you're locking
arms there we go
[Music]
fore
he doesn't believe it so
kiss huh what do you know about her
type want to act like her boyfriend beat
him up beat him
[Music]
up I got to start acting like a real
boyfriend what what kind of guy would
make sense for S
joh honestly like number in this case
real down to Earth but we should beat
him up
anyway if she had a boyfriend he'd
probably be a pretty down to earth
dude all right I just got
an I give people
work
excuse me do you not know I am the hero
of
Yokohama
qu should have been a
[Music]
quiz it's not about the money
it's so soft he such a softy right
[Music]
now it's fine to be softy like that but
right now they're so intimidating seem
to be
intimidating a
a I don't believe him kiss
oh are we going to fight the
[Music]
music want to fight too like the good
old
times oh look oh she looks Ang oh the
bldo is is is is not so strong anymore
the bolox is letting letting letting uh
what's the word letting you
know nice just's going to knock him with
a
purse your allies positioning opens up a
variety of strategic possibilities like
knock back chains allowing them to
follow up after an enemy is knocked in
their Direction and back attacks against
enemies who have their attention
divided and many of these attacks
provide extra damage so be sure to make
use of
them
okay PSE
attack I want to use this can I but I'm
too far
away are we good oh
easy took down the boss immediately oh I
can do auto that ble you're right they
did have Auto Battle pressing
[Music]
L2 hold L2 and press up or down and
adjust the party's Auto Battle Behavior
a did I have a
use Y what a
woman what a
woman hone what is that I want to use
that
[Music]
jeez
yeah oh my God I was born for this oh
what's
this what was
that
Ste oh look at us so formal so good
looking
assault I I H I said uh salt ah like ah
salt but I was assaulting them with salt
oh my
god Pocket sand
nice very
convenient ew diarrhea
again
that's why we shouldn't have worn
white what are people going to
think he's not going to change into the
suit is he the the fancy
one that would be funny end up wearing
both anyway
ah this say normal one
cute they did go to game seter I told
you that that's a great
choice yeah just play all kinds of games
and have fun together it's cute and you
can if you're the guy you can try to win
some plushies for the
girl yummy nikan nikan yum street food
let's
go yeah yeah
perfect
oh this
place this place you can't go on a date
to this traumatizing
Place
o
o I'm not going to be
sad and no I said g Santa which is our
arcade but like Game Center is like the
Japanese way of saying arcade that's
what I meant
though I said that I said it a few times
I did I said game
center it still be a nice place yeah if
it
have the
memory forgot what it means to him how
could
you he's so freaked out
[Music]
still
oh my God he's really trying to sell
himself
[Music]
saan would be so stupid to
not give you a
chance and marry
you will you marry
me I didn't think he would actually
no
[Music]
no no
ich no why
no
[Music]
no sat please forgive him he's stupid
but he's he's got heart he'll be a great
husband in the future of course just
turn him down for
now that's so
crazy oh my
God she's not going to say
[Music]
yes
for shut up now stop
[Music]
talking stop
talking
[Music]
she's not going to jump right that would
be
weird she going to say
yes insane what's
happening she going to say yes is
she oh my
God
I mean I mean I yeah
understandable no I wouldn't say
that oh my
God yeah okay now really that has been
enough embarrassment let's go to
Hawaii oh I mean ichan please think
Ian what have I coached you for I mean I
didn't tell you don't ask her for
marriage but I mean I thought that was
obvious ichan the [\h__\h] is that
e
ter for real for
[Music]
real
yeah
yeah I mean you didn't stop
talking she's not mean M mad no but like
yeah
game over he's just like what the [\h__\h]
man what
happened that doesn't make him any less
husband material he would be a great
husband and a great dad
but yeah he needs to be like he just
needs a uh yeah he just needs sance
forgiving this is uh yeah damn [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
oh my
God why we should have told him we
should have told him guys it's our fault
it's our fault we didn't tell him to not
propose H
[\h__\h] I take
responsibility
yeah
yeah I mean it really went well
especially we only got the
screen no one
told
for he said a
lot
everything I I even stopped
listening he started advertising himself
as a great guy mhm
by like
deating maybe I also missed something
maybe it wasn't the getting
married is that what we're getting
at
uh and then everything after the words
made it even worse but yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah oh is it implying that she needs
you to make her happy for a moment I was
thinking that maybe that's what they're
getting at like just it's not even the
proposal no
way I don't think I think the proposal
was the
[Music]
issue it was just a nice thing to say of
course she can make herself happy but
that was still a nice thing to say like
she wants to make even
[Music]
happier we're going there okay
we live in a
[Music]
society I didn't even think it was a big
deal to say that the problem was The
Proposal oh my
God
yeah okay that's where I stopped
[Music]
listening this game is going in that
direction right
now expect it at
all no it's my thir
[Music]
G
okay I mean yeah all these things he
said yeah I guess they're kind of sexist
but uh I feel like it's different coming
from ichan I I don't think
he really
is I don't
know it didn't feel
like that
condescending uh it's kind of different
I've heard sexism come from people where
I definitely
felt like oh that's that's shitty but I
don't know this is this is like really
just caring
and just he's just like trying the his
best to be sweet and that I don't think
he necessarily I don't think he even
necessarily thinks that that's how a
family needs to
work I think he would be totally fine
with her going to work and not staying
at home yeah yeah he's just phrasing it
poorly that's not really what he meant
and I don't think he's like so
strictly um
in in those like thoughts that that's
how a relationship has to be
yeah yeah and also I guess like taking
in account the 20 years he spent in
prison yeah but
still the problem is really just that he
proposed oh my
God
a yeah me yeah now you're asking for a
child who
knows
did are they are they trying so hard to
sorry but are they doing this because um
are they trying so hard to go like this
route that to like show that
ichan just doesn't know the world
anymore or that he's not caught up with
the world is that what they're trying to
do that's I feel like it's a maybe a
little bit of a weird way to convey that
a little bit unnecessary
[Music]
Maybe
what is going
on no why would you take it like
that
what the [\h__\h] is
happening my head
hurts my migraine has not stopped guys
so
bad h
okay I'm going to get a painkiller I
think in a
moment cuz it hurts thanks you guys
seriously don't sweat it you're going to
apologize to her the sooner the better
yeah all right I'll go do it right now
my stomach's still in a notot
though no surpr right there you okay
want us to tag along no I couldn't ask
you to do that you sure well good byby
later I should get a check next week I
don't know if I have time to go to the
doctor but I kind of want
to okay I better go apologize I wonder
if s's at work already I'll swing by the
bar okay fu
let me get
pain
cutest cats
ever they're so
cute they were like oh what the [\h__\h]
suddenly waking up from their
naps like Mommy are you okay they were
looking at me like that
so taking Japan actually Japanese
painkillers cuz I had them lying around
and I don't know if they're still good
but there's no no date on it I think
they're fine I took it uh yesterday
too his
face gosh he's so [\h__\h] up
up
okay okay and a
little
hunger and deleter AKA
food damn it what a shitty
date what a shitty
experience Mama
Mia no I don't think it's that even if
it's expired it can't be that expired
not that
much he's hiding the pain I don't know
that doesn't look like he's hiding
it he's just
um something's something's really
[\h__\h] wrong with
him
I keep on Bing myself with my bat that's
why my head
hurts nah it's okay it's um made out of
really soft
foam
it looks so
funny
yumy
um I love picking up things
man M
yummy I mean I don't like seaweed but
I'm
sure I'm sure he likes
it
and all these foods that I don't like
myself I still think they look like
they're so yummy I wish I could enjoy
them so I can't go much I can't go out
of the blue
circle
what you eating I was eating like a
little like a soft biscuit with like
cream inside and covered in chocolate
it's called milk
[Music]
tender fight
[\h__\h]
love I love how they name the
[Music]
people just an
[\h__\h] circle gets
bigger enemies closer to I know I know
so I want to get like closer but I guess
I can't go get any closer than
that that's fine just testing out my
limits
[\h__\h] was that
sound was there a point in uh
pressing X on each punch trying to get
like a perfect hit and extra damage was
that a thing cuz I've been doing it just
like are the plus two because I'm doing
that I
wonder I'm just doing it automatically
but I don't know if it actually does
anything is it really her make
sure what is
[Music]
her needs to move the
Pluto
foree
really not care is she
playing
pretentions
pretending doesn't care when he's making
it even worse
by
thinking stop talking
it's I can really start seeing that he's
going to Hawaii because he's am so
[\h__\h] embarrassed if he was a Sim he
would die from embarrassment I can see
that timeline now that that's why he's
going there
it seems pretty legit
now stop
cooking oh my
[Music]
God oh my
God
help she she's still not reacting okay
she's also kind of
like
what I hate how she just also doesn't
talk
[Music]
she makes him
suffer for
embarrassment okay then say something
for [\h__\h]
sake okay
good yeah
exactly
[Music]
f
yeah there's like a a slang
wordo which is like a shortening or
combination of the words always Tom it's
literally I guess friend zone in the
Japanese word in the Japanese language
remember
[Music]
zmo but it's not really used in that
sense though not about it like
girlfriends good girl good female
friends they will like be like oh we're
too Dum friends
forever look I got I got Lashes in my
eyes one year
later oh wow ah [\h__\h] my lashes are
stabbing
[Music]
me did he just like sleep through the
embarrassment for a full
year and then
I wanted to read the the where there was
more
written wait how's the club that was
2022 aren't you in 2023 now in the game
they didn't un wait
unre so much for
too
B oh my my God so much for Forever
Friends
girl
huh the
[\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what the what a roller
coaster we were in we were not in we
were in we were not
in
damn imagine imagine him like kasuga you
need to you need
to understand I I fired you a year ago
and you still come to work every day you
you're not working here anymore kasuka
you need to get over it and and and
learn to accept
it you need to stop coming
here he's going to get fired
now oh [\h__\h]
I fired you a year ago cuz you're so
[Music]
cringe there we
go
fire you to cringe one year
later I don't think so should have fired
him a year ago just
kidding just kidding just kidding
damn
[Music]
Dam
why don't they want to get rid of him so
[Music]
badly
he put so much passion and
into to the
work and then you get [\h__\h] over like
this that is disappointing as
well thank God it wasn't immediately
after that embarrassment because like
having those two things happen in in one
go would have been
devastating
damn and can we really accept it like
that there must have been something else
like why why this just happened why I
got fired well that's that guess I got
to say goodbye to
everyone oh just scream goodbye we don't
have to talk to each one of them
personally believe
me I guess we
do hey there son a there her today your
last day that's not really how his voice
would sound
I I just wanted to say thanks for all
your help I know I made a lot of trouble
for you nonsense I I was no trouble at
all best of luck on your future
endeavors Kaz I'm sure you'll do great
no matter where you go hey thanks all
right guess I'll be taking off now
thanks
[Music]
again something happened maybe it was
her trying to [\h__\h] me over for what I
said she did take it really seriously
after
all oh my God the she's just staring oh
my oh my God is she okay she's a robot
excuse me e my son yeah
yeah this kind of s but today's actually
my last day I just wanted to say thanks
so much for all your
help oh yeah I heard the news oh I was
pretty shocked honestly good luck out
there I'm sure you'll do great at your
next job now let me continue staring
into the nothingness that is my screen
sa
yeah thanks have
fun she laugh me
told she was zoning out no soul
left uh pardon me
kiman oh hey I heard today your last day
yeah you were such a big help to me here
you even taught me how to use a computer
oh no that was nothing oh really sorry
I've actually got something I need to
take care of by the end of the day oh
wow that was a sad goodbye take girl off
yourself oh he said
that see see
you was he avoiding me just now oh sorry
I got I got to go somewhere I know this
is your last day and you're trying to
say goodbye to me but I got to go do
something right now before the end of
the day it's still early in the day but
I got do it before the end of the day so
goodbye what and go golden hour
again oh my God what's going
on the cold
shoulder
Clo's job has changed from Hell worker
to
freelancer yeah yeah sounds better than
jobless
freelancer he just jobless now is he how
is he a freelancer he hasn't freelanced
anything suppose once I'm back I got to
let arachis son know what happened from
there I'll need to figure out a new way
to carry on alakawa Son's
Legacy
there's been times like especially for
example when I went to Japan for that
one year where I would call myself a
freelancer but but let's be honest maybe
I was just a jobless no no I would say I
was freelancer but it's saying you
freelancer when you're just jobless
isn't it just a COPE in many cases I'm
just wondering that
now trying to make it sound better oh
yeah I I'm I'm a I'm a freelancer I'm
not jobless I'm a freelancer
I I Lance I use the Lance in my free
time cuz I I am also a larper I go to
Medieval festivals and then I go up on a
horse and then we freely L around that's
what I do so I'm a
freelancer by pressing swear to perform
a treasure honey ah yeah I think we did
this also in the previous game
yeah
Coter I run my own business yeah which
is my life my life is my
business uh sorry
directionally challenged this
to
uh uh this
way they want us to go that
way
forcefully safe
Lancer that should land you every job
ever
I'm more of a free sorter H that's kind
of lame you
don't can't keep up with me I'm a
freelancer
yeah hobo skills unlocked it's funny how
I unlocked this after losing my
job
e what let them look are they still
like did they stop talking about me now
they immediately lose respect for
me wow before y'all were saying like oh
my God he's a
[Music]
hero
DN free
archer right this
way freelance is also called a javelin
yeah fancy fancy word wait I wanted to
pick up something I wanted to run back
and pick up something right there on the
left side damn it he's so
sad man oh now they're going to pick a
fight why is he filming
it
[\h__\h] no I'm helping you start a new
[Music]
life that's why they fired me
they
the Dan of the guy on
the he's standing like
he
yeah oh he fell so
[\h__\h] this no gratitude City let's go to
Hawaii I retire from
life
don't I hope this game is not making me
pay that because I don't want to give
into
that
editing add a few AI
as well while you're
at I'm
viral in Japanese going viral is
um uh like directly translated burning
burning up angel and he was like Angel
like burning what do you mean what do I
look like I'm burning to you or I'm not
burning but but then the English version
is also funny do I look sick to
you
cute he just doesn't get
it sorry he's a boomer he's literally 40
not saying that 40 old people
first
Pokemon now
yaka is this a real
vtuber she has a uh a mole on her BBA
her design is so
cute does she exist for real that they
create her for this purpose I have to
look it up right
[Music]
now I'm looking on Twitter oh my God I
think oh she exists wait there's free
accounts what the
[\h__\h] it's me heok from the hit game like
a dragon infinite wealth parody account
a [\h__\h] hell wait so it's not
real people just making these
accounts be aware of spoilers of the
game
T there's a one that's called tatata
Channel that's also doesn't seem like a
real
one
tat there's like free free accounts on
Twitter uh no that also looks all the
Twitter accounts look like made by
random
people so I didn't I I didn't get uh
spoilered it was just uh yeah Twitter
accounts don't worry don't worry I
didn't get spoilered I'm just just
wondering if this person is really a
YouTuber and maybe also you know went
for an audition to be in the game she
looks cute though
wait you guys saying I might get spoiler
just made me think something that I
think that's what you're trying to tell
me or like that's what I might get
spoiled I think I know what what that
spoiler might be now without even
getting
spoilered and I'm not going to say it so
then hopefully I'll forget it but I
think what I just fought is probably the
spoiler but I'm not going to say it I'm
not going to say it I'm not going to say
it it uh I'll forget it cuz I have bird
brain I mean often my conspiracy
theories were always [\h__\h] anyway but
what I'm thinking right now is probably
really what it is maybe I should write
it down on a piece of paper and then
reveal it later
on in case I was
right uh don't read too much into it I
did did that's the
problem but it's okay I mean I think
anybody could could come to that
conclusion and I didn't I didn't
spoiling myself just
now but let's let's listen to the
voice
[Music]
no why would she do
that she's
cute
the voice sounds like she's using a
voice changer a trama
[Music]
YouTuber [\h__\h] she's so
cute is she GNA appear more
often then once this one
time I I want to see her more often
it's so crazy to see YouTubers in the
game I'm sorry but like oh my God it's
like wow wow wow like cuz like don't a
lot of people play Yakuza games like
people who don't even know YouTubers
might be like looking at this and and
and I mean cuz it's like I guess it's
like anime 3D within an somewhat anime
3D game so it doesn't even like maybe
come across as a YouTuber maybe this is
just you know
like just a cute looking girl not
doesn't come across as a b you know what
I mean because it's like frd within 3D
it's not like it's like a real uh IRL
footage where a vtuber shows up I don't
know maybe she'll say that she's a
vtuber though and then people who don't
know what YouTubers are are going to
look at this and be like interesting
they
should
advertisement give PR give
PR
he
cute yeah Y is
[Music]
photo it's a
different I'm so distracted by her cut
this don't
understand
man should I should I do a stream like
this and expose someone like
this out of
[Music]
Contex just another whole life
YouTu I like how the subtitles are not
the usual subtitles in the game did you
notice this is like literally like a
clip like a subtitled clip cuz they're
stylized sub
subtitles nice
detail
I haven't seen
enough can't be true
yeah it do look like that but
[Music]
out of
cont [\h__\h]
yeah don't give him money for
anything you'll be in a Str
bring it on Mr
Char he's not how was he supposed to
do yeah for
real internet
body
[Music]
oh
pleas stream it
[\h__\h] there's a lot of personality in
every
[Music]
character
oh he actually is a real guy but is he
also like a street
fighter did he also win an
[Music]
audition a guy in the back tripping what
so many
people all
right yeah let's take down right
away
oh
[\h__\h] that's not done the right way
[Music]
and
oh is that
fair okay I got a lot of
uh a lot of
HP and you get a turn and you get a turn
and you going to turn and you going to
turn you're so polite giving everybody
turns like how do I
switch a
d I should have taken down one of the
smaller ones I I get another turn
okay nice so that they can't give me
like dot damage small not even dot
damage no I'm looking ah
[\h__\h] that gives me more damage right oh
[\h__\h]
my you catch these I yeah right I can
knock them into each
[Music]
other wait let's try that
uh like this oh no wait has to be the
front
one ah didn't work
[\h__\h] give me another hit oh no oh
[Applause]
[Music]
no
Dam I was thinking about the angle but I
should have taken down another small fry
again a
now he's already so low on HP maybe I
should kill him now have a lot of MP
let's just do it with
a strong
one nice
okay no way they just lose all power
over their body when they
[Music]
die
this should
work yeah there we go there we go there
we
go I'm
fine nice music
though I'm
[Music]
fine I'm
fine
what do you
want bring it
on wait wasn't there somebody supposed
to film it they're all gone how are you
want to film it should have put up a
tripod and stream
it on the
wall
not a really fair fight though let's be
real
guys
oh
okay
so Miss's afro maybe we can get
[Music]
back maybe I'm wrong with my thought
that I
had I'm just going to say it now I'm not
going to read the chat reaction or you
guys don't even say anything about it
okay but just for the record although
I'm now doubting myself anyway so that's
good let's going to say that Satan is
her that's why she also like just is
gone because she's busy with youtubing
but it it doesn't really seem like her
personality but maybe she's being
manipulated or something I don't know or
it's just not her
who put on the T foil
hat it's good that I'm doubting myself
in
true she's so cute oh my God how the
[\h__\h] did she get 5 million
subscribers
how
[Music]
fore
couldn't you have kind of like proven
with documents and [\h__\h] that your
company that you're trying to like build
up is
legit just it like he took like uh all
kinds of notes and all that I feel like
sue him I don't
know there's some [\h__\h] up [\h__\h]
again going on behind the scenes
only one thing to do let's go
to what if we got baited by the
Hawaii location and we only get to go to
Hawaii in the last 10 minutes of the
game after we clear the whole game as a
reward she's so cute
she's so
[Music]
cute
F your whole channel on
that but she sounded like she's using a
voice so I wouldn't be
surprised
design for
sure
how can the politicians and the police
rely on the [\h__\h] vtuber
[Music]
Channel
for wait I want to read
[Music]
that
like all of these comments are like like
um dumping on kasuga and there's just
one comment that's like so beautiful I
love you thank you I love you Hoka
you're so beautiful heart heart
heart one comment is just
sing
and it's the one with the
suit maybe we'll find out who that
is
spee
fore
the same
thing now I think about it was a white
suit with I
think
very
specific naive with two dos is that how
you
right
[Music]
maybe simping for the
YouTuber that would be so
funny
[\h__\h] yeah we
[Music]
did the original French spelling they
use eyes with double
do wow so beautiful you
guys
[Music]
hold there a good chance some EXA might
still come knocking at Hell work should
stop by to be safe okay
they'll probably tell me
to get the hell out of there but sure
banana
banana so now now we're like getting the
story
started
oops Freddy MS so crazy thank
you those big numbers are so
crazy
banana wait is that why they put bananas
there cuz I always made the banana junk
did they do it for
me
around 40 yeah it's crazy like any all
these numbers sound
crazy putting in a
numbers it's just like especially in
months sounds almost crazier than the
years or it
does kind of
does holy [\h__\h] there we go there's a
40 oh my
God
who hasn't been brainwashed
yet y'all are some old
[Music]
chickens oh
wow
guys yo even 30 or 34 anything that's
also crazy don't worry
guys
but you can spread the good
word so maybe I got rehired and I can
help you
again
no stick together
[Music]
dude it's going to KI it
yeah wait it
landed
[Music]
sick sick trick do you see it it landed
up upward standing straight up
she they did that on purpose so
cute
[Music]
taking the video
man don't freak out you little [\h__\h]
yeah mot not
[Music]
meanse
for where is
s let's just follow the pink AR
blindly I can't believe people change
their opinions so fast on me first I'm
they're hero and now they're
like he sucks he's the worst
really
damn and the issue is that it's all like
out of context
fake
dramatized Clips it's like a hate
campaign it's so sad
that you know you could [\h__\h] someone's
life over like
that poid on power lava
fragments we can probably have like fire
attacks and stuff for
that 22 Mons thank you so
[Music]
much that's where he
lives still looks so different man I
can't
for
you should come join us in
Hawai it's America so maybe the law is
[Music]
different especially because you weren't
even in jail right and yaku I guess
America doesn't give a
[\h__\h] you don't even have to say it like
they would know just go to
Hawaii it's not that easy but I don't
know the game is bringing us to Hawaii
so join the
team
banana one month later
another don't don't smoke so
much oh Korean
Virgil
my
boys imagine they already are wearing
Hawaii shirts and have packed bags and
they're and they're saying let's
go
a aren't they wearing the old
clothes they're wearing the old
clothes it's been like what 20 [\h__\h]
years okay maybe not that
long they're wearing the old
[Music]
clothes they could have given them new
clothes but I appreciate the
Nostalgia
foree
I need pictures thank
you [\h__\h] I don't remember this clan at
all
oh
yeah I didn't know thank God he doesn't
know
either not
[Music]
again
fore
foree
yeah I mean what other choice they
have if they can't go back into
society understandable I
mean you know the guy with the super
long cup sces ah the ones where I zoned
out
for I literally have a bunk bed and a
couch and I'm not letting my Bros stay
with me in my pretty decently big
apartment
I'm letting them sleep on the street as
they just said they're homeless now
too uh I don't think we're
like that big Bros after all
wow why don't I let them sleep here huh
so
rude
we're
[Music]
Bros cut let's
go I am the true
[Music]
bro
let
kiss why is that dress back there
explain keeping
what I got my
B is it
golden
still is he going to make molotov
cocktails
again
[Music]
for
back the [\h__\h] is that weather oh yeah
that very going to be
soon and here we go bring it on yeah ity
fun
with the Banger
Bulls yeah so
epic his
umbrella oh I love
them so dramatic holy
[Music]
[\h__\h] like an
apocalypse oh
[Music]
man oh w we are the
apocalypse I was going to say like this
is
like I was thinking that while they were
walking down there like it's
that it's so epic but like from other
povs this is going what it's going to
look
like [\h__\h]
chuno they're chuni 40-year-old chios
please excuse them I'm a
hero yeah no more
freelancer we don't need that title We
Are a
Hero that was such anime humor just
now
for fluffy hair
[Music]
cute
so weird it's like I'm replaying like a
[Music]
dragon like back in the
game it's like
[Music]
a fight
me you just some random
monster yeah
[Music]
okay are you're right
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah
for what are we saying that they just
look different to
me
ah wait ah wait I'm him right
now
Bel moloto
[\h__\h] yeah line damage here we
[Music]
go looks pretty buff let's o b
breaker
yeah [\h__\h] you
hey you bought a knife to a [\h__\h] bat
and umbrella battle who brings a
knife you little
[\h__\h] yeah only he's seeing them just
once to can prove how how freaking tuni
he is further proof do you need any
more it do be spiky yeah
he I tell you when we're together
nothing can stand in our way we're about
to ra a Yakuza HQ don't get Clocky just
because we took out a few GRS yeah yeah
oh cool he's right with chairman Hino
dead and T in prison who knows if anyone
in the saal clan will be willing to
listen to us stay sharp you
to right okay enemies for the city will
change the appearance according to
kasuga's Wild
imagination What
actually before we do
that our hero might be sword in hand and
ready to face the world but I was
thinking we could use a little something
too oh yeah know that you mention it say
that love magic place over there it's
got some need is this same place yeah we
can buy equipment there yeah same place
as
before sure good plan we're in the area
so we might as well eh no complaints
over here buying equipment and boosting
your St is all part of the adventure we
got the spru things up before we bust in
on the S
Clan weapons and armor can be bought in
stores and become effective when you
equip them check the map to find stores
and see what kind of weapons and armor
they sell by placing the cursor on them
and pressing
[Music]
Square now I was
wondering if this code down there it's
maybe some kind of serial code that you
can use for something cuz surely looks
like
one can I buy one of those cute Chinese
dresses
please
J oh my god
andies oh
de okay what is this for ah okay
I don't
know oh this is for
everybody take number but it has letters
in
it yeah I thought it was maybe like a
game code but no way right no way that's
an actual
game I don't know what to buy is really
that serious like there's no weapon for
me though no this is the weapon for
me how much money ah okay H I could buy
a new weapon for all of us I
guess I don't want to fight with
that yeah let's give the jumbo sausage
to other team yeah yeah who
else the bum boo broom okay thank God
this is a normal
thing [\h__\h] broom I like the umbrella
man and this is pretty good plus
four how expensive 1,000
okay I'll give it to me and I'll give it
to all of us
maybe yo good use of my
[Music]
money think that's pretty we don't need
all of it do
we
I yeah right game is crafting I don't
need to buy new B oh well okay yeah
that's true that we didn't really CRA uh
we didn't really buy things didn't we in
the
past I remember this place
yeah not a soul in sight these days it's
more rare for y office to have someone
standing guard anyway let's head in
least they've got a doorbell right
uhuh I mean there are cards outside
all right what if they don't they're
probably just not going to let us in are
they hey
Bobby pardon me my name is ichan kasuga
I used to be a member of the alaka
family uh Captain kab helped me out a
bunch about 3 years back what brings you
here I heard there's a guy named tasaki
who joined up with you recently I'm kind
of like his Guardian you might say so I
was hoping to like talk with someone who
knows how he's doing I'm very sorry
sorry but any visitors must first have
an appointment that's our policy now
please leave yeah
uh well that that's [\h__\h] rude let me
in can we make an appointment at
least we didn't sort or drop in on them
out of nowhere still that seemed a
little too
short did T forget to mention us I
wonder well kasuka even if we want to
make an appointment we're out of contact
what with up The
Slammer but they must know me they just
don't let me in on purpose cuz there's
something going on
no let me in let me
in I know but even then I won't abandon
Sasaki meaning we're sneaking in no way
there's only the front door I go sneaky
nyyy NYY sneaky like a snake
what's our plan then the place is
covered with cameras there's no PL spots
ah we learned a thing or two about that
already though oh why don't we ask the
people who know this town best who's
that the
US no okay the homeless Camp okay that's
right I don't want to ask them for free
though so we should bring a little
something how about a bottle of sck and
chief would love that bottle of sck okay
drunkies fine I
[Music]
guess say you're forever
oh cute cute the height of Urbane R
party as you walk around you may be able
to trigger party chats with your friends
oh yeah pressing uh triangle allows you
to skip a line in these conversations if
you so choose yeah yeah yeah
yeah it's all as it used to be in the
past very
familiar with the umbrellas I love it so
cute
are we going to hit
him oh yeah one one was being hit
nice he's like a little witch with his
broom so
[Music]
cute like a tails off
skit kind of but uh don't they happen
while you're walking so you don't get
inter dropped it but
yeah I think that's how it is basically
what we just heard right was one of
those
skits yeah we were okay I was like we
got to buy the
socket and maybe something else we you
know this uh food U will be necessary
right we
have food
porn how much HP do we have right now
anyway maybe right now we can just go
for the cheaper
ones we don't have much money anyway
all right let's get it over to the
chief o
[Music]
ni
expensive yeah do I still have money now
I didn't
[Music]
check Pick Up
Artist real person
perhaps
radioactive
radioactive oh my God shut
up
[Music]
I'm a hero I have to save
her this main
story
voiced too I don't even
[Music]
remember
thing calm
down
W need to be so aggressive
R
yeah
[Music]
paralyze e e
e yeah even more collateral damage but
he's kind of
weak his normal attacks are
weak ouch
ow no n
I think I remember we let Namba go
pretty early on cuz he was
[Music]
so
don't don't don't don't question the
weapons oh so going teamwork
why always go for
n he's got like no no
defense level up already level
five yeah I know he's weak cuz he's the
Mage type I know I played the previous
game too
foree
[Music]
radioactive after
what a weird
name that's the new way of listening to
radio not radio cassette
player
[Music]
you are a
hero
she's
[Music]
cringing a
real
no please we need to improve
our
reputation have
[Music]
her does his tongue look
blue
a filter playlist app has been installed
on your smartphone you can add radio
episodes to your playlist using it or
the radio in KAS oh
okay tune in to the radio with Juke
boxes like the one in survive the radio
at kasas H or the smartphone app in the
pause menu the show changes topics every
chapter so give a listen from time to
time yeah I don't know if I really will
maybe once you can listen to radio
broadcast on any CDs you've collected
while out on the town put together
playlist by using C cassette player or
the app on his
smartphone yeah I don't
know
[Music]
radi oh yeah right there was a healing
station here but num's recovered but I'm
not recovered
what yo that Tower was always a
tower oh man I guess things must have
been pretty good for something like this
to get
approved yeah there were big plans for
it but then the pandemic hit right as it
was picking up
SC the construction companies went under
and all that was left to show for it was
a couple of Steel frames oh they were
actually trying to build a house and
then this was left
there and that's when the boys swooped
in and took over the tough bastards that
they are
it's like
a like it almost feels like a fortress
that kid children would build and then
have fights against another group of
children if bleach Japan ah bleach Japan
had taken over the town they never let
the to the homeless folks here I'll bet
this is like their own triumphal Arch
huh a monument to their
Victory looks more like a castle uh if
you ask me no actually where on the
street is they call this place the
castle Key by the look of it I'd say it
fits oh yeah the sea thing also got
Cannon yeah damn so
realistic a castle without the Lord huh
I shall be the Lord oh ah him can I help
you fellas hey no it's been a while
something tells me you're not just here
to see me yep well actually we wanted to
ask you about
something ah like in the old
days so you're planning on weaseling
your way into the S your clan huh just
for this one saki guy look numbers don't
matter here whether it's one or 100
people I just can't let leave the guy be
nice to see you haven't changed in fact
I'm relieved it's gotten been a lot
colder as of late huh oh yeah it has and
now that you're out of the job I bet
getting that suit clean not exactly a
droing the bucket is it oh yeah I guess
not well I know you'll get through this
follow me
okay yeah I know I noticed the teddy
bear n
n
you wanted to sneak into the S HQ to
check up on Sasaki right there's perhaps
a one way ticket you ready to
what
okay I want to see what's that I had a
healing
thing oh sure a little
bit any item to pick up
though oh no
okay I mean I think we're
ready are we not it's probably not a big
deal let me just pick this
up burn ointment okay that might be
useful and here A Worn Out microwave all
right buy some
bit more also save ah wait how do I
save here
or Auto saves anyway not a big
deal that's that's just now that
happened just
now we don't need
to yeah I think we're fine are we going
into the sewer are we sounds like
[Music]
it let's
go stream only 720p yep my my internet
recently is [\h__\h] I'm using a mobile
router so Internet is just really shitty
I also can only do 30 FPS and 2,500 bits
uh kit K bit kmb bit something like that
so yeah currently still kind of low
quality I'm
sorry but at least we're
streaming say uh Chief what is this all
about like I said you wanted the back
door this is it no
oh this looks like the sewage
tunnel yeah in the middle of the wind no
less see I gave you a round you got it
down uh I do not exactly Jazz about it
though are you too
crazy are you too crazy this old heart's
not built for soon we surfing anymore C
there's got to be something
else back into the water I
guess sorry but this is the only way I'm
aware
of guess there's no choice Unreal
Tournament I should have left a will or
at least gone through my bu don't get on
down this is nothing compared to what
we've already been
through h fine whatever di down then dve
the diver Dave the
diver thank you CH I'll be waiting to
hear you oh you got it okay Showtime
here it goes
[Laughter]
oh crazy people imagine IM imagine a
jeser being like I'm sorry it was just a
prank
bro I didn't think you would actually
jump in
there disgusting look at all the
oil it's unreal t
[Music]
don't worry you only s like 5
me here we're right
here and we are very
smelly smelly cat Smelly Cat what are
they feeding you Smelly Cat
smelly it's not your
fault
[Music]
okay and I've actually been recently not
really I wouldn't even say what
re-watching friends again I'm just like
turning it on to fall asleep and I fall
asleep immediately oh my
God I'm always so tired when I go to bed
it's
amazing
amazing but that's why that song was in
my
brain shout out to
phoei wait what about over there though
I'm
curious
item
yeah that's the RPG player in me wait
maybe I
give that someone
to or maybe n n needs it the
most yeah oh wait
that's that's for
attack
whatever can you only fall asleep to old
shows no it's not about whether they're
old or new just like uh I like it to be
something that I already watched before
so that I don't have to pay attention or
feel like I missed something by falling
asleep you
know it's kind of relaxing to just hear
like usually I have it on really low
volume here something why
I
off I've I've like oh gotten so used to
it that I almost like need it
now I need to listen to something
we watching the office right
now the office is
amazing always nice to rewatch that one
too oh no no don't turn why you were
looking at him why would you turn
around makes no
sense oh he's
an item
nice you guys do that too yeah
especially with sitcoms it's just really
relaxing somehow and
just what the [\h__\h] no give me back my
tuna
on that's
[Music]
my that my mommy pack for
me I know I'm not using any skills kind
of on purpose maybe I should use more
skills you keep Bots like my mine in the
background while you sleep but then you
then you fall
asleep and then you don't know what
happened in my stream but it's
okay still giving me a
view
I I got it I got
it please change
his this one looks
fine looks fine why is it only ichan why
did they not realize that face that
they're giving him is like really
unnatural really concerning psychopath
face did I come from here no
right
wait did I ah I
did I'll have to get used to it man it's
so cursed can they like make um a
patch no
[Music]
I'll bring
out F
breaker
sexy
his unhinged
charm yeah a little bit Charming hey
there
myuna or is it another different
one just looking around before we
fight
oh wait ah oh no wait
uh let's attack normally cuz there's an
item right
there yeah explosion oh my God I should
be getting damage from that too oh [\h__\h]
he did he fall down was he actually dead
though
wow
what 28 damage from
burning oh
no want to be able to block all of those
like Bam Bam Bam Bam Bam one day one
day I don't think
so
he can I only upgrade in a
store would I be upgrading I think I'm
fine I don't need an
upgrade upgrade
UPG what are these
[Laughter]
caterpillars oh my God
yeah this is what I like to see in the
Yakuza game
oh dear oh
dear we're going to if we take them down
they're never going to turn into a
[Music]
butterfly we're taking their chance to
become a beautiful
butterfly turn around
d
whoa oh my God
nambo
no oh he's wak against fire those those
caterpillar harded
Metapod are you still alive
man
y thank
you was there something important that I
missed wait I don't even know where I
came from for
here
yeah did I miss
something oh wait that's no that's where
I got to go [\h__\h] so
confusing
[Music]
yeah I looked around here I didn't see
anything
here go downstairs and
swim there's a you want me to get that
huh wait how do I where do I go
downstairs
there's oh there there's a ladder I
didn't see the ladder at
all what there's another
one D must be something important in
there if you want me to pick it up go
back to pick it up safe key aha the key
is right next to the
safe
open passion bandana mysterious cluff
the moment you wrap it around your head
it floods you with a burning
passion okay is that for
everybody four four
[Music]
nice I'll give it to
myself we got to take care of ourselves
first nice thank
you this water again I'm so stinky
yeah if I'm this
stinky such is never going to talk to me
ever again she literally can smell the
stink through the messages I'm sending
her that's why she's ignoring me oh a
clothing item damn it I shouldn't have
bought anything is it better than the
current
one
[Music]
huh wait I understand said that the
shield is defense but what's the other
one Willow oh yeah it's
willower so that would would maybe makes
sense for
n but he needs defense too I don't know
maybe for if we get a new
teammate anytime
soon oh that's it
here a willpower is
Magic and maybe number already by
default has a bunch of magic
defense so we don't need to boost his
maybe I don't
know where are we going where am I
what's the oh you guys also kind of get
lost in this so to say
dungeon this is the way is
it I am a m
now now there we are oh oh that's a lot
of people are we fighting them all at
once okay let's use
[Music]
this yeah yeah stay close stay close
together oh no I'm not hitting him the
other one too
bad whoa wait Na's
dying wow nice block he's huge no no
no I could
see no first death a are they back to 1
HP after the fight I don't remember
[\h__\h] I'm stupid for letting
that who who who good good Reaction Time
wa cuz that's the first time I ever saw
that
attack what how do you act like a
[\h__\h] werewolf
get
up alen thank you thank you so much how
you
[Music]
doing a
[\h__\h] missed it this time I got right the
first time miss it the second time
lame wait can I use this uh thing
no no why did I
miss oh well still big damage whoa
coming out of
[Music]
nowhere holy
[\h__\h]
holy
[\h__\h] maybe one
more this time I won't
miss
mm let's finish you
too okay so look at the floor after the
battle there's some
good okay
[Music]
he still gets exp even though he died
yet on the
floor doesn't look like there's
something on the floor this
time ah and he did go to one HP
ah there it is thank you I would have
been so salty if I would have healed him
before going into this room
nice
helmet another
headgear
wonderful you know what I'll actually
give it to number because he's
so squeezy he needs a
helmet we'll be wearing bandanas while
he wears the
helmet okay I don't know if I should
like buy oopsie buy
anything s Clan and EXC just beond here
once we're in there's no turning back
all set to head in um yeah the tent has
an it
ah yeah thank you Kiara with ch why the
[\h__\h] are you calling me Kiara with ch
What
tent ah ah in uh in the previous
room
I oh my God I didn't see it just the the
cash that's
it I guess
so that's not me that's not my name
that's not my name that's not my
[Music]
name oh I have to save here
ah
K yeah let's go
oh
oh some more
[Music]
water
okay
nice I hope it was worth
[Music]
it see boy always chilling in my
stream European Time
Z
a red
head
[Music]
fake
sorry go for a home run on a line of
enemies uh they're not in a line though
unless we go the other
one let's go for the normal
[Music]
one
I no lines man no lines where are the
lines crany my beloved
a I'm so happy you even love me when I'm
gruny monke damages an enemy with
particularly unorthodox method of
deescalation I need to see
that the new one anyway that I already
saw at
Fu I don't know how that is De
escalating anything
ouch that's
it weak your security is so me and
that's exactly why you guys need Ada's
company we're we're just here to test
your security trust me you need
it we're breaking in and I'm writing
down all your
flaws and here
we typical Japanese office floor
and
nice music going on
again is there something else
there
side room nice not even anyone in
here [\h__\h]
Furniture crunchy I feels like back when
gave you first started no it wasn't
crunchy back then no what was crunching
it was just weird uh
Acoustics what did I just get [\h__\h] I
already forgot was it head gear no what
was it what did I get ah ah another yeah
work
[Music]
Club yeah maybe I'll give it maybe I
will give one of these to
N More normal
defense hoping that he won't be attacked
with magic
attacks
[\h__\h]
this was like so often a thing in the
other Yakuza games we played like us
having to run through these buildings
that are relatively narrow and all that
such a yakusa
Trope actually yeah we even infiltrated
this building before too so that's why
it's so
familiar I spelled your name or I'm
sorry no not you not you
I don't even think uh did you spell my
name
wrong oh no that wasn't even in the
Super Chat huh what do you mean it's all
good I was uh joking about someone
else snaky sons of [\h__\h] you're going
to regret fighting with
us yeah cuz it's a waste of
time thank you for all staying so close
together
what do I need to press
nothing whoa reaction
time on
point you're good Super
Chat all
[Music]
okay I'll do it that way cuz maybe ichan
can help us
right as a follow up or is it only with
normal
attacks maybe it's only with normal
attacks or if I throw him towards
him
yeah I'm in the
[Music]
zone I'm out of the
Zone but it was good enough
collaboration with on the
two you need knockback okay yeah we we
just saw it how it works oh more I like
their
entrance man yakos has such a
game yeah don't move too much
[Music]
[\h__\h] all day
all
dead it's all in my head
anyway in my
head oh no he's got a knife or something
like a knife a
[Music]
blade at least he doesn't look away from
his
[Music]
opponent
with the
bucket a
triple
fin
out let
[Music]
gu yeah this combat is fun I think I
really enjoyed the Yakuza the
typical uh combat the one I had in
Yakuza zero but it's nice to be back to
this uh as
well I hope I didn't forget anything in
the room let me check again double
check anything in the bucket
no no there really wasn't anything there
now you guys are making me paranoid cuz
of that one
time wait what about this room oh okay
there nothing elevator
more we are not enemies guys we've been
for this before come
on did they really not know who I am
dud oh yeah keep on moving e e
nice
position down first might be
loot still
trespassing well they wouldn't give me
an appointment what choice did I
[Music]
have
uhoh where's my perfect
block wait there's still free left of
them I should
have wait yeah let me use one of these
for
you
proximity St not
that good
enough they we going to attack you
either way not and walk true yeah but I
don't know I don't think I could have
walked in because it's
Clos
one doesn't simply walk into more uh s
[Music]
Clan no whatever you can use
whatever box a freaking box don't call
it just a box it's a freaking box
might be worth something a for selling a
wrist watch for selling uh which room
did I not see yet this is where I came
from is it is
it I so confused using cuz everything
does kind of look the
same would have been nice to have like
more poter a
grenade I will catch a grenade for you
I'm so hungry guys this is where I came
from maybe no no maybe not no maybe it
is [\h__\h]
go
this way
no is is
it yeah
okay key what was the other key for I
wonder did I
miss can can a snap make a sandwich I
[Music]
could what like I
actually I've been making myself hot
sandwiches these days I I took
I revived my sandwich maker oh wait are
we in front of a boss battle what are
these hospital beds or like cult beds or
military beds I don't [\h__\h]
know uh I could make one might take like
10 minutes uh I don't know if I should
it's already 9:00 p.m. actually maybe
we'll stop after this fight and we'll
then we'll read super chats cuz it's
already been six six six
hours sex
hours ially said it in German but when I
think
about an English oh man this is why I
hate saying that word in
German uh this has been the um well six
hours
okay and save needs Oney yeah open it
oo down jacket what makes me feel like I
missed uh
a
save oh sorry I'm
stupid o lowers the damage taken from
Ice attacks lowers the damage taken from
blunt attacks sick nice nice
jacket I did miss Stu down for real for
real but if I go back now I'm going to
get so l lost was it good
stuff I'll survive right oh I was
already
recovered yeah I do wish that items
would show up
yeah I'm hungry
[\h__\h]
it's the beginning of the game it's not
going to be the end of the world to miss
one
item although I did just go this
way wait is this the
way a
helmet
wait yeah for you nice okay everybody
has head fear
now it's this way right but is there
anything else to check out
no
okay here we
go who are we going to fight in this
boss battle maybe
Sak
toy maybe we are going to fight wait is
this actual
gear oh wait we also have the
binding okay um you know what both both
of them I'm giving to no he only needs
one okay he got the
bracelet okay I'll get the The
Binding helmet seems like it was a
pretty good find yeah I think so
too okay can't go
there hungry one more
choc
biscuit
[Music]
biscuit don't true oh
he guarded it all
D teach me
how oh guard ah uhhuh
M
spee
[Music]
oh but we did break his guard
right the fur away you target the harder
you let's go for this one
was proximity even such a big deal in
the first one I don't think it was
right really wasn't
I uh he's brought some bodies
in wow so
many
hey [\h__\h]
that kuy
bastard monkey
flip they roll so
far no I should take down the small
[Music]
fry should try at
least come on get it get it get it
right oh hey we did
involve would masty be good I guess oh
was that like thing was a masty
buff a
grenade it's okay
there wait wait this this this is good
this is
good maybe free free of them
yeah oh that was
ideal
he going foru and getting other oh yeah
cuz he's like
uh yeah like a what's it words words
have forsaken
me not host what's the
word not host tank host is kind of like
[Music]
tank
I love you guys I love
you so nice to talk with you guys
again I love
you
you mean it I mean
it of course I mean
it monkey flip and ice cream like a
monkeying what do you mean hacking
what why would you do this to other a
piece of [\h__\h] I hate
you
payback can afford one more skill come
[Music]
on that's
fun why can I not block
attack hey why don't you
help you should have help
[Music]
me it work
work I love you too my okay stop ganging
up on
number
oh we get a key from him
too
lels oh yeah right they rank up in the
class so to say that they're curan I
remember another boss
fight they did usually have like a pre-
boss always
huh we got healed
right oh he's like
please he looks like not familiar but
he's like he's a son of someone we
know he's in that Zoom
call look the
airpods he's going to lose them
eventually s
he's he's kind of
hot sweet
Mas is actor was in Shin
[Music]
Godzilla
he yeah The Stance was kind of
funny oh
wow only two
years that's
fast
fore
foree he's
so and
finally someone who gets
it oh my God was about
time
communication
[Music]
problem
fore you guys seem to be happy having
fun so just let you do
it t TS
KR see you also watch too many
crime
just let
me maybe he's
[Music]
there
all
right then I guess Sasaki went to the
right place
if you got a
job yaka making their own jobs
again taking care of their own
lives taking
charge
what
the what is
this some kind of like Pokemon
plot
for safekeeping or for
blackmailing where we [\h__\h] Shady
[Music]
again it's kind of
weird
many people would use that
in
so are you saying people are bringing
their own like things that they could be
blackmailed with like they're bringing
the evidence
here and then it gets shut Behind These
doors I don't think that necessarily
like makes sense like if you're the only
one to have that evidence
anyway
and
just do you really need to do that like
what if it's papers then burn it if it's
pictures delete them whatever why would
you why would you need to do
that I don't quite can make sense of it
a bit weird logic um you're just giving
them something to Blackmail you with I
don't
really making sure it stays out but then
why not just destroy it why Safe Keep it
why would you ever need your own
blackmail
[Music]
material
Plan B to keep yourself safe by
blackmailing
others yeah I first thought it was
like you safekeeping things that could
blackmail others but I thought now I
thought it's uh people safekeeping their
own
stuff well maybe it's stuff they may
still need could be something they can
may still yeah okay maybe they maybe
maybe it's something they may still need
like I don't know
like like a document that proves
ownership of of
secret offshore bank account or Island
that's illegal or some I guess but you
still need it in order to keep it
running or what I
guess is that they can't find honest
work because of it so they can only work
you know I understand why they made this
whole thing to give jobs like it's great
that they get jobs but I don't
understand the point of the of
this
service you have a c that is evidence
but you can get rid of
it
[Music]
okay the ownership of that plot of land
from yaku would be useful there yeah if
you run a business and your subordinates
are doing illegal things you would want
to keep track but not released publicly
unless they they throw you under the
bus but then again I also think this
like he said it's really expensive to
store things here then if it's people
who have that much money I feel like
they could probably like make their own
little
Vault because they have that much money
just get your own little Vault like why
why isuse a service that's also weird I
don't know man
it's whatever let not
question
not of they're under
[Music]
surveillance
so wants to eliminate all
[Music]
Yakuza
are they doing that so they're the only
ones
left or is it a
[Music]
good
foree
really they surely have a back ulterior
MO
oh like maybe his boss doesn't but he
does
it's like we're passing on an adopted
child especially the music
makes he's
evil
for nah he's
[Music]
evil
for
him someone we
know
uh
[Music]
oh I thank God I'm not the only one
who's like what who again uh ah from a
different
game than God wait seven oh that's the
game we played oh okay I was going to be
like ah not my fault that I don't
know so she like yeah I mean yeah the
name yeah yeah but like no idea what he
did his face doesn't ring a bell
either the douche back that triy to take
ichi's finger
ah wait and then why didn't it
succeed I second
man ah
ah yeah okay the jerk calls me dump all
the time he worked on ichiban's dead U
Captain was friending to cut ichi's
finger in the last first chapter yeah
yeah yeah
yeah the guy I went to jail for
oh okay this
guy this guy sa I went to jail for
him oh that will be an interesting
conversation right
after is that the first time I'm meeting
him since
then
ah ah the young Master is real
dead is this the first time we're seeing
him
yes is he is
[Music]
it it's pretty important to the plot not
even no he was in seven oh oh my God I'm
embarrassed I'm sorry but some of you
guys don't remember
either I paid attention it's been a long
time I just need to watch the cut scenes
again or
so also he looks different like I think
he changed his
hair like a dragon Sawa
shetel yeah yeah he looks different he
had something on his face oh no that was
just that picture he had some blood on
his
face okay no his hair is the same
but
still kind of different
Vibes
yeah you should really watch a
recap yeah maybe I will but I mean so
far it wasn't really an issue just with
this
guy
ah it's only been three years you're
sarcastic yeah cuz fre years is actually
a long time it's been three
years forgive me for forgetting this guy
I didn't forget
[Music]
everything it's coming back I mean it
was two plus years yeah you could just
load up seven and watch the cuts scenes
menu oh no I'll just go on YouTube I
don't even know where do I where did I
play that game did I play it on my
PS4 or on
Steam yeah the game will remind me yeah
in the upcoming conversation
probably you remembered more than I did
see now I don't feel so bad anymore okay
um
Sith chapter 2 Paradise Hawaiian style
well it's going to immediately play the
cut scene isn't
it okay let's watch it or should we n no
no no
no should we watch it tomorrow let's
watch it
tomorrow I have
PC how white
time
okay all right play the cut scene before
no we're going to watch it tomorrow
Gonna Leave You guys on the
Cliffhanger watch it cing with pineapple
pineapple will be a good intro tomorrow
exactly will be good to watch this right
in the beginning
tomorrow
okay then that was our little play time
today do I still have my summer thing no
I think I got rid of
it the OBS
scene damn it the Hawaii shirt would
have been perfect I have to set it up
again yeah don't know where to
go uh where do I go looking like this
I don't
know this place looks like one of those
offices that we're running through a
little bit only a little
[Music]
bit where's the
table what
where is it I may have moved some stuff
ah
around damn
it no let's not go here let's
go let's go just to the girls talk maybe
this
[Music]
one oh
man okay God I have
to [\h__\h] [\h__\h] everything's messed up what
this
[Music]
ahh where do this go where this go ah ah
I think I had
[Music]
it it's because I changed OBS to
720 a there it is there it
is
sure I love this
t-shirt and which one's the
chair all right I have two chairs
because of
Nissa
right okay
[Music]
okay also the
T-shirt I should like if they sent me
the version of like the bat separately
and the shirt separately then I also
might want to get rid of the
arms so that it ends at the sleeves but
don't look at that too much don't look
at it it's an optical illusion I don't
have
forearms and then chat uh there you
go your stuffed chicken is a lot bigger
than ours unfair it's plenty
big
the bigger it is you know the more the
shipping is going to cost and all that
so gotta keep it relatively small but
yeah mine's pretty
big oh [\h__\h] everything's so
confusing where is
this there you
are biblically accurate Phoenix
me not if it's unstuffed yeah but like
sending unstuffed like an unstuffed
chicken plushy would be kind of lame I
think unless it's like a bean bag but
nah but I hope you guys are enjoying the
chicken plushy I saw like some people
put the Hat elsewhere cuz it's like
detachable saw someone put it on their
pet I saw someone put it on a [\h__\h]
infant looks at
Duma
I'd love a kfp Hawai
shirt kfp Hawai
shirt oh my
God but I don't know if I want to do two
clothing items cuz if you remember back
I did tell you or we talked about one
piece of merchandized that you guys said
yeah you want to have it so I kind of
already decided on it for uh birthday
merchandise and I'm still thinking about
other things that I want to
do it would go great with the beach
merch yeah H maybe I'll do it for maybe
I'll do the Hawai shirt first and then
the idol uh happy or anniversary I have
to think about some things then I would
buy at least 2 kfp Hawaii shirts it
would probably be orange guys is that
okay it might be similar to this one
like I feel like the chickens on this
one only like if you only look at
someone's eyes you won't notice that
there's chickens on on the shirt but
then if you look at the shirt you see
like wa what the [\h__\h] why is there a
chicken on your Hawaii
shirt what a weird Hawaii
shirt Hawaiian shirts are supposed to be
brand and FL yeah they are they got to
be
orange Works Orange is great yay you
guys are going to be even more
orange as if you weren't already enough
orangy orang goes well with pineapple
what's with the
pineapples I do I do want to do the
happy I think
[Music]
yeah why would it not be orange of
course of course sorry I I don't know
what's wrong with me it's because of my
break okay let's play some music
[Music]
um Loi I think we need
Loi oh
yeah and then we're going to read Super
Chat to Super Chat
time for a little
while and then I'll go eat my dinner I
skip
lunch man man it's so difficult like
longer streams when the hell am I going
to eat
lunch where did we get to last time uh I
think it was like 54 the number 54 is in
my brain right now did I remember it
correctly that would be
amazing
olizer oh my God I was
right yeah I only ate like two pieces of
toast with um butter and the jam that my
mom made
before and that's it then I was thinking
about eating like a toast like a hot one
with ham and cheese before the stream
but then I ran out of time cuz I was
also stretching and blah blah
[Music]
blah
yeah you should prepare something for
lunch yeah yeah yeah I might something
tomorrow to eat during the stream but
generally I don't know if I start eating
you
[Music]
know some people don't like
it
um this is
stream what what Toys is bae revealing
reminds me of the stream I wanted to do
with like magazine toys toys that come
with like children's and teenagers
magazines that I wanted to do but a lot
of those have like Disney uh characters
and whatever and Barbie and whatever so
I'm like H can I really show this on
stream a small
[Music]
shell maybe we can eat
mik yeah we'll see I I'll get a snack
for sure maybe if it's even just a small
sandwich or finger
food you don't mind me eating on stream
thank
you ah they're going to be toys she
wishes she has she would have gotten as
a child
oh oh that's nice that's a a a sweet
idea there's certainly such toys for for
me as
well although I guess most of them they
like a lot of them they don't sell
anymore cuz it's long long time
ago
um it was of the P World
[Music]
stream
yeah yeah yeah all right put this up
there cute chick
pea okay here we go 54 previously was
giant Apple so we continue with 55 melon
star comes on up with the super jat D
before I go to work out I give Koreans
money powerful kada oo and then it says
in Korean
[Music]
I
think did I read that right what's
P I'll look it
up Pap help
me
[Music]
a broad a b
b it means broadcast live stream thank
you comes on it all very sweet of
you I don't know if you're listening
right now probably not you're probably
sleeping in your cozy bed tucked in and
dreaming of me but I hope you will see
this stream or any of my other streams
after my break again do you remember
me thank you for watching and thanks for
the Super Chat thank you soon Dusty
thanks for the red super chat don't have
to read this all
out you're so nice but I just started so
I'll read it it's okay while challenging
I hope you enjoy your vacation my cute
talented dedicated Kam oi which totally
deserves a break I will wait patiently
love FL thank you so much guys all of
you for waiting
patiently I do I do agree I I deserve
it yeah I I do feel refreshed and all
that so it had a good
effect and I hope Dusty you still
remember me are you still around
Dusty Dusty from the good old
days one month ago feels like 8 years
years
ago Dusty where are
you has there gathered too much dust
it's been so
long oh my God Dusty is not around he's
been covered in too much dust waiting
for me he can't hear
me should we blow the Dust
Away
Dusty are you somewhere under that dust
somewhere dusty please find him guys we
got to bring out the the vacuum
cleaner and the UN dusters the dusters
the fety dusters basically your
butts undust everything and find Dusty
it's an
emergency thank you Dusty we'll get you
back we'll get you back
somehow Dusty in the end his name is his
demise a thanks for the pinky thanks for
the stream T enjoy your break as much as
you can so you can come back with the
full Majestic Phenix power we will
patiently wait and look forward to your
epic return have a great time Al in
thank you for waiting I don't know if my
return was that epic
but I'm back baby we're back in business
and not even shitty internet can stop us
thank you so much for being patient yeah
and for supporting me for fake and fin
thank you so
much Uncle Stone than soon space water
thank you for the pinky thanks for the
fun stream I hope you can rest well
detox a lot and charge your bio
batteries fully my bio batteries may you
feel more well and not think of the of
work for the time I'll miss it yes but
this doing you this doing you so much
good is worth anyway thanks thank
you yeah it did work I feel like I was
charged my batteries were
charged and while yesterday for example
still felt like weird I think uh today
it was like
pretty yeah like usual like always like
my other Yakuza
[Music]
streams
back in the Grove
yeah is all back to normal I was a bit
crazy yesterday today I was more calm I
just let out all the crazy steam
yesterday where my statements yesterday
it weird controversial or something like
that I think uh I made Solid arguments
uh in terms of space travel and all that
yeah I saw nothing wrong with
it razor X Dan video Man
Dan Kuro y Dan Slavic fellow thanks for
the pinky enjoy your break W you very
much deserve it and need it thank you oh
oh yeah well I don't know if at the
time I really needed it cuz I think I
told you you guys I felt like worse one
or two months before but um better then
than
[Music]
never it was a good time thank you for
letting me rest and just ignore
everything for a little
while it was a good time for
me and now now was also a good
time but
recharging
successful
what no I call it
Twitter No I will continue to call it
Twitter it's
Twitter it's always been Twitter it's
been Twitter for many
years you can't just simply change the
name and think that will change it in my
brain it's ingrained in my brain it's
Twitter Twitter is
Twitter now you just hear X really I
know I feel like a lot of people still
say Twitter I say
Twitter your main account is unbun
[Music]
nice use Twitter
and especially us as Birds should
support the cause of it being Twitter
because we tweet we tweet and we beep
and we bulk
[Music]
bulk I press x on it being xed I doubt
it yeah
yeah yeah
yeah our Bluebird that
was executed we pay respect by
continuing to talk to call it the
Twitter Razer X than video man 190 oh
wait I read that uh Super Snake Mario D
thank you hi I recently escaped from the
bucket and gained beautiful firey wings
or Fury I don't like that word it's so
confusing I honestly can't believe it's
it's been 2 years since joining kfb I
want to say how much I cherish the
memories I've made here with you and kfb
thank you I love you K thank you I love
you
too two years
yeah even two years is crazy like we
we're we're so deep in it now three and
a half years we're so
deep it's
crazy damn V tubing is still like such a
fresh thing in the world
as opposed to other things which have
been longer around but it still feels
like so long and it's crazy to be part
of
something that's so new in the world and
you're you're part of this like
development and
experience and I'm so proud to be part
of it and I'm happy that you are part of
it too with me we're experiencing it
together something really
[Music]
unique g d dun subi Allan dangun H
dangun for the pinky T today is my thir
membership
anniversary I've been uh I have had a
very fun ride and I'm very happy to say
that you are my Kami as a celebration
gift could I get a wakeup message to use
as an alarm
clock
okay
wait
ah okay are you ready
ready 3 2
bom wake up
H it is a beautiful morning it's time to
rise and shine get up like our ity bun
with full motivation and then your day
will be amazing let's
go
if you actually manage to wake up like
Ichibon then I really think your day
will be
great just jump out of bed and be like
[\h__\h] yeah yosha let's
G that's the best way you got to learn
from
ichan to be successful in
life one more hour one more hour
normally people say five more minutes
you you're asking for one more full hour
damn I mean I I feel you that's like my
spirit same
same I always need at least 14 minutes
to wake up I if I have an alarm and I
have to get up to do something to go
somewhere I wake up
immediately i' I probably told you this
before but I hate when people need like
like a million
alarms they either set a million alarms
beforehand or they just snooze or
like there's those people who will
snooze for every alarm but also like at
some point they just ignore the
alarms and just let them go let them go
let them go even if they're like you
know in the same room or even in the
neighboring room and I can [\h__\h] hear
it and and you can hear the alarm go off
and off and you're just wondering would
you at least press the [\h__\h] snooze
button
please just IGN ignoring it and sleeping
I'm I'm happy you can sleep with that
alarm going on but would you do your uh
Pro close proximity friend or whoever a
favor and and press snooze or just wake
up I feel
[Laughter]
attacked I may or may not be doing that
sometimes I hate
you I hate that so much you didn't have
to
[Music]
me Ena has answered the chat did Ena do
that I probably complained about it
before if you change the alarm noise
every once in a while it it helps not
sleeping through
it yeah I mean it doesn't help me as the
affected one the
victim and then yeah also another big
issue is that like let's say let's say
we both have to get up and we because
we're going
somewhere and I easily get up like I put
an alarm I I know how much time I need
to get ready let's say 30 Miss so F
minutes before having to leave I put an
alarm but then the other person says
okay I can't I can't wake up that easily
so I'll set my alarm like 2 hours before
or 1 hour for and I'm like great great
that will also wake me up I'll also be
awake I cannot sleep through your stupid
alarm even if you
even if it's I don't know even if you
immediately kill it it wakes me up and
then I'm
awake yeah you give me the win thank you
yeah it's just uh just sucks when you
don't have like the
same way of waking up as somebody
else really
sucks and then I would like sometimes I
I'll just like kind of say I'm I'm
making the alarm just don't put on your
own alarm cuz I know you're going to
make it way earlier and whatever just
leave it to me and I'll wake you up if I
have to one alarm that's all you're
getting but if you leave it to me I will
actually wake you up so I think it
should be fine just turn off your
[\h__\h]
[Music]
phone actually something like
this something like this happened with
me and Nisa and the MDES on our
departure day cuz our departure was like
we had to leave the
room I think it was like at 3:30 or 4:00
a.m. or so it was like a crazy
time um cuz we were catching the first
sea plane to leave the island and still
had to eat breakfast and check out
and I I was
packing um until pretty late so honestly
every minute of sleep was precious to
me and once I finally got to sleep you
know I slept pretty deep and then I wake
up because narissa is making noises she
just kind of got up early it wasn't even
alarm she got up early and then started
doing all kinds of preparations of
leaving that she could have done with
our normal wakeup time that was even
scheduled in our schedule they sent us a
whole schedule of when we should wake up
and then get ready and then leave the
this like Villa Apartment thingy and
then go to the reception and then go to
breakfast like it was all scheduled and
it was more than enough time before we
would leave the apartment but I I just
like I was like half awake and I heard
heard her like opening her suitcase
loudly and opening drawers loudly and
opening doors loudly and I was
like I was secretly fuming hi
Nissa now you know I didn't tell you
that we were just talking about people
waking up others unnecessarily with
their
alarms oh I was hoping that I would
catch you though because I want wanted
you to listen to the
musical the musical of Aki Rosa
Senai did you watch it or did you just
get up you have to watch the
archive I want to know the opinion of
the
musical what's the word
[Music]
suier they were s
shambles
it's okay we're good it was so good it
was so good for real it's going to be
nissa's new favorite musical you just
finished your chores chores course
chores you going to watch
it it's so good you may think that it's
over after like like like a few songs
and then like she does solos no it's
like she it starts with the musical and
then there's some solos of and then gets
back to the musical and then there's
some solos of her and then get it gets
back to the musical and and then I think
there was another solo maybe yeah I
don't know but yeah there's like several
parts which their subtitles
though I mean it was pretty it's a
pretty simple story it was just like
these musicians that are like
man I don't know either life's boring or
people are misund understanding me uh I
just want to have fun like K was like I
just want to have fun but people always
say am so loud when I go W Wang Wong but
then she meets Aki zai who's like
accepting of her and all that and
they're like let's just go have fun in
bman and make music together basically
something like that and then we all
gather together cuz we're all like just
feeling kind of lost or
something for some reason whatever
individually yeah and then we just every
time we meet someone else we're
like
[Music]
no I was done talking about it
anyway I used live TL extension it was
pretty easy to follow what like an
automatic
translator
damn sheesh
technology okay where was I anyway uh oh
yeah here here again thank you I hope I
hope the wake up message works for you
the W alarm clock you have
El black
[Music]
Le rine for the pinking greetings Danel
my birthday merch finally arrived and to
celebrate here's one last thank you for
all you do until you get back hope you
have a nice break oh thank you so much
for your
sweetness M and you merch arrived too oh
my god did you get the full
set I really hope that my merch is
somewhat useful and and I don't know
nice to you guys I hope you like it I
hope you just didn't I I hope you guys
don't feel like you have to buy it even
if you don't like
it ah it just catches live like
translations from other people in the
[Music]
chat oh H you just missed it oh my
God
damn it you you just missed it you were
gone right when I read your super chat
for real for real oh my
god well you got to watch The Vault then
I'm not going to do it
again I like how it's useful and good
thank you I don't think I'll always be
able to come up with like useful things
um some things will always be like maybe
more decorative
sometimes yeah but uh I'm trying to make
somewhat useful things
yeah the bag is so nice and high quality
oh I'm glad you think
so I have no idea what to do with the
bags but they're
awesome did I not give you enough
ideas you can use it for so many things
you can use it as a big shopping bag
instead of like an Ikea bag like if if
you need to buy something big or bulky
or you can use it as a picnic bag or as
a beach bag or as a sports bag like put
some change or whatever clothing change
and maybe I don't know basketball I
don't
know and yeah it's very versatile you
know if you need like a bigger bag and
especially like for example if you go
swimming in the summer or so and there's
this plastic bag inside where you can
put the the wet cloes in there for
example
too
really looking forward to the official
happy
marriage all right I'm on it I'm on
[Music]
it the blanket the towel the plus really
love all the W mer thank you the blanket
is nice isn't it the
blanket the blanket is one of my best
merchandise items I would
say really like that one it really was
great quality and a super cute
illustration I just wish the the towel
would have ended up bigger size I don't
know why it was so tiny how that
happened man anyway thank you resine I
did have a nice break I hope your break
was um
sad your break from me I hope it was
sad thank you so much for waiting for
me SAR thank you for the
redent I use the blanket so much a i I I
try to not really use it I currently
just throw it over the guest bed as like
a yeah just still decoration but when
somebody stays over I take it away I
don't let them sleep with
[Music]
it cuz I want it to not be overused you
know I want it to stay somewhat you know
clean and in good
condition currently wrapped in
blanket amazing I can imagine cute
chicken wrapped in oversized blanket
small chicken in oversized
blanket my banket is getting a bit SC
scuffed because it's getting used so
much oh damn you should have bought
two but I don't know I mean with bankas
they should be pretty like hard to
destroy like maybe give it a wash but
like not too
hot give it a wash maybe it will look
fresh again I don't know
[Music]
don't wash it too hot a chicken bito
chicken
buo so thank you T for the rested chat
enjoy your break W I hope you can relax
a bit during your time off even if it's
going to be hard in the beginning I
enjoyed the last 6 months in kfb t where
are you from I see Euro sign I enjoyed
the last six months in KF very much and
we'll be eagerly awaiting your return in
three
mons all right you're
n you're newbie 6 months oh my God
that's so fresh that's a fresh egg six
what do you mean six months haven't you
been around
longer how can you even have that emot
is that really the six month uh badge
damn Germany
ah
mm
to
I told a Zai let's go to
bman doesn't only have to be bman cuz
like bman is is pretty but it's not even
that big of a city I think so not worth
to go only for Beman I said let's let's
visit several cities come on come over
[Music]
here then
net actual trip with the playcast I just
generally think akis Senai would really
appreciate it like the architecture and
the culture and all that but then again
she's I think too busy um playing games
uh 10 hours per
day I don't know if she she seems really
addicted I don't know if she could
really you know even out of her own will
take a
break I joined after the last do M me up
when I talk to someone the regular wait
a
second wait okay H talk with fans time
once
again
so the last fcal me you weren't a
kfp so what did you just see random
orange people and you were like what's
this and they told you and then you got
interested and you got hooked
cuz that would be
crazy thank God for your curiosity if
that's the case but tell me tell me
about
it tell me about it tell me about
it tell me about
it you do that to people it's happened a
few times yeah but like this
successfully with someone actually
getting so
hooked
pretty much
what for
real that's how it
happened the cult approach works oh my
God my
God I watched a Scientology Deep dive on
my break by the
way oh no it wasn't a Scientology dead
it was um Tom Cruz deep live I
think kfb recruiters are ruthless oh my
God I only watched Hol Japan for oh so
you were aware of allive and you knew
Hol Japan okay okay okay talked with
other Holo fans at the corner now here
we are ah okay so you did have like some
kind of like knowledge about it already
okay okay I I thought it would have been
like kind of crazy if you knew nothing
about it at
all and then we're like okay you know
what I'll check it out and then you get
cooked but thank you for giving me a
chance I'm so happy that you're part of
the kfp crew thank you so much I hope
you'll stay here for a long
time you got to catch up with the the 30
months and so on that the others have
got a rise in
[Music]
status fan was
crazy I wish I could have seen
it
[Music]
what who thought kuo was
Filipino Filipino Filipino Filipino
Filipino yeah stay faster and catch
thank you for ruining or like pointing
out the the logic flaws in my statement
I'm planning on bringing my camera and
my free60 camera to do me this year I'll
try to take lots of videos and
pics okay okay have
fun have fun with that s a kiss for you
perhaps I increas Your Love SK
Unwritten
and thank
you thank you guys thank you Unwritten
for the sweet message
Moonlight thanks for the red chat enjoy
your break K waah wa we'll keep the
restaurants functional and as clean as
possible but you know how it is with us
chickens anyway relax and have a good
time we'll be waiting for the Chipen
mama what do you mean I know how it is
with your
chipkin saying you like can't help but
but keep everything
dirty I guess it's kind of like chicken
Lea feathers and stuff
everywhere
you lose your feathers a lot don't
you and you panic a little bit and you
go flap flap flap flap and then the
feathers are like everywhere it's like
you you use one of those pillow fights
pillows where you smack it against
someone and suddenly there's like 100
feathers flying around I didn't even
know there were feathers inside my
pillow the typical pillow fighted
pillow it's like you killed a [\h__\h]
chicken then and there
let's just say some of us need diapers
see I told you you need diapers why
didn't more people choose Cupid for the
kfp
Polaroid you need it stop pretending you
[Music]
don't we got a sweep of feathers a lot
of Cafe and you probably always
wondering hm I wonder where those
feathers are coming from man they don't
stop coming and they don't stop I sweep
and they still behind me they still
always show up behind me that's weird I
sweep them in front of me and they show
up behind me and then I sweep those and
then they show even more behind
me
weird we are inside your pillows that's
why it's so
comfy or may I say I don't know
uncomfortable because I have I have I
have
pain when I
sleep and I toss and I
turn we don't want to lay eggs at a
random placees that's right because I
gave you guys the skill even if you're a
male chicken to lay eggs yes I made this
mess I created
it anyway thank
you thanks chat you underestimate our
power do I what was this about I do
think you guys
together especially are very strong and
powerful especially if you stack up and
uh put a trench coat over
yourself then you're extremely
[Music]
powerful strong jins strong together
teamwork is
important thank you
Nathan panopticon D rise free d alist d
Brandon D out the wind d
and egg bird thank you for the pink hi K
just wondering when you'd stop being
guest on Tanaka Kyra's Channel I love
you all but I miss my favorite ostrich
too
hey T Kisha Kyra Yellow Ostrich streamer
is not r
she's like a like a
illusion she's not
real or if anything she's
mean you may think you want to see
tanaki sakyra but you really just want
to see me okay you've been living a
life yeah I'm what you really want I'll
tell you what I want what you want what
you really really want is
me it's real to me what for you guys all
thinking you're watching tanaki shakyra
and supporting tanaki Shaka right
now misunderstanding
[Music]
Corner she's really I saw her where
where listen
God damn it egg birt what have you
started again Sky D ziply thanks for the
pinky I love you and enjoy your content
thank you w I'm I'm happy you do because
I put a lot of work into my content
thank you so much
[Music]
Lord oh did you finish it already
comy D
danan or yeah Sian Sian d
Indigo 5 Alpha thank you for the
pinky you did oh yeah a small donation
for your premium economy seating fund oh
thank
you although it seems
like maybe I'm flying business on my
next trip to Japan because it was pretty
cheap
but it's not a direct flight so sad
because now there is no direct flights
until summer again I hate it I hate it
no but it was surprisingly
cheap also cuz they're booking it for me
so I guess they're getting like Japanese
prices in y and then they're like just
automatically cheaper maybe I don't know
if I would be able I book it on my side
if I would really be getting it that
cheaply but yen is cheap h
finally a cheap flight for a change yeah
and I I mean I don't even have to pay it
so that's
[Music]
great get that comfy seed
yeah it's an airline that maybe I didn't
even fly with yet I'm not sure so I'm
going to I should honestly as a side
hustle I should make one of those
Airline testing uh YouTube channels cuz
those do surprisingly
well but people probably don't watch
like like economy or premium economy
reviews usually people want to see the
business ones cuz it's always like so
who oh wow he's showing off the business
class of this Airline and then they have
these catchy thumbnails I I ranted about
this before but those caty
titles that are like so exaggerated like
I can't believe what this airline did to
me so rude never flying with them again
like you know those kind of t
so shitty but I could totally do that
with how much I fly
around on the German
Channel yeah but the thing is I I really
don't fly enough with
business this is it was just my first
ever experience uh on my last trip right
so or last trip or last last trip last
last trip of
it I love to see economy on I've never
been in a plane with different kind of
seats oh
Mar I don't know I would also feel kind
of awkward like in at least in business
class you have like a little bit more
privacy and space so if you take a video
It's
Like H not so awkward but I wouldn't do
it in economy cuz like strangers next to
me I don't want to be that kind of
weirdo taking a video of the seat and
myself in the seat and myself eating the
dinner and all that it's kind of
weird and
unnecessary maybe if you flew more you
wouldn't have no arms hey
[Music]
rude that has nothing to do with
it my flights to and from D this year we
$2,500 so I'm definitely getting worse
for prices
internationally was that a direct flight
or an indirect flight 2,500 for
economy
that's pretty
crazy I think you could have gotten
cheaper
[Music]
flights
no that's too
expensive w oh multicity flight I got
Comfort plus Comfort plus what is that
is that premium economy
basically I still got to get my dumi
flight set up
ASAP yeah uh you should get it Go
Go National flight to Europe during
summer are r
two why was it the price too tall for
economy yeah that is uh cursed you are
cursed my round trip for fifth best only
cost me
$1,190 wow that's really good that's a
good price I think that's a decent
price could still be cheaper but it's
pretty good pretty
good credit card Point redemptions help
a lot if you can use them I still never
a credit card I really need a credit
card for these kind of things oh well
anyway thank you Indigo 5 Alpha than I
appreciate it thank thankfully premium
economy isn't like too bad although yeah
those I think this was probably about
the males flights or was
it those uh cuz we had economy didn't we
and it was still like not that
cheap I don't know no no
no if you're tired you don't even have
to read my name just take my money by by
that time I already read it
so
than you soon okay so for the pinky so
to be a bit more creative at praising
you here is my version I kind of sort of
maybe probably like you a lot and you're
arguably my favorite streamer I guess
have a nice time
off I wouldn't necessarily call that
creative but it's cute cuz it's thank
you thank you Shar for the sweet words
you can be upfront and clear about don't
just say it you love
me just say it don't be shy don't be shy
it's okay to be honest I just want you
to be
honest I'm not even going to put a gun
to your
head picture of a telephone danin Cruz
danan Tim k d yuk D
Al thank you k d d
[Music]
AB thank you for the red chat oh okay
you know what I I I will read this in my
[Music]
brain thank
you thank you so much for welcoming me
back
now
[Music]
yeah I'm just holding a spike bat no gun
today just a
bat no thank you not myself
okay you don't remember you super chat
but you did you
did oh it was a very dramatic Super Chat
too anyway and thank you thank you for
also being so considerate k a lot of you
guys were like so considerate and told
me to not read the Super Chat what's
going
on thank
you fried girl thank you for the r no I
is leaving my poor small chicken heart
will not survive without her Kies nor
her tangents or her calling me a little
[\h__\h] cuz I was being a little [\h__\h] love
forever love forever oh my
God hope you have a relaxing and
revitalizing break uh oh SL cre oh I was
telling you guys to be creative or
what thank you for the sweet words I'm
sorry I couldn't provide you with daily
K keys but you could have played my
Bots and just imagine it was life but I
wish I wish I didn't have to do it you
know but I'm doing it for the sake of me
being around longer and you all
understand that so thank you so much for
supporting me through and
through I am a cheap beep D SP waterfall
D for the pinky don't worry I promise I
will never forget you and never not be a
fan Pinky Promise
indana so many ways of saying it you're
my beloved oi I love you so dang much I
will be there when you return now go in
detox well thank
you for letting me go with such a nice
face
thank you so
much you are all the sweetest chickens I
could ask for thank
you
motion what thank you
D oh my God actually I just realized
your profile picture is so funny cuz
it's it looks like that Pokemon right
but then when you look closer it's like
a person's upper
body with a sixpack
Mar thank soon Damian Ward than soon Cal
than soon kfp Spidey thank you soon Che
Channel than you soon vus thank you soon
oh yeah leaving was really difficult
saying goodbye was so difficult oh my
God yeah it was so weird the first
couple of days to not have to
stream so weird I felt like I should be
streaming Jones than for the py
hi future M oh nice how was your break
did you resist Discord and Twitter
either way I hope you had a great time
love ens myi I did I completely stayed
off of Wawa Twitter and Wawa Discord I
did I mean yeah one time I like you know
communicated with jenma over a different
Communication Service so that I could
stay away from Discord but yeah M no I
really
didn't you didn't stay off while to
completely yeah I
did I
[Music]
did I yeah I used the YouTube but really
just because of the
ads cuz I don't get ads on this account
and I I you know I get my usual
recommendations cuz I always I always
use this account I always to watch any
kind of video so you know my usual my
usual algorithm is on here subscriber
increase yeah I noticed I was notified
about it from you guys
today one of you guys told me we finally
saw a number
change uh it's not
1.5 1.5 anymore it's 1.51
now that took a while growth is so slow
but it's it's nice to see some growth
yay thank you for subscribing
everybody smash that like button and hit
subscribe and maybe even hit the
notification
[Music]
Bell yeah 1 1.51 million
yeah 2 million is so
far 2
million so far
[Music]
definitely unless some miracle happens
it's not really a thing that can happen
this
year with the current growth but that's
okay that's okay I'm just chilling I'm
just
vibing thank you for playing enjoy this
broadcast thank
[Music]
you Million by December don't say say
that
no it's so okay it's okay no need to
rush no need to rush we're chilling we
we're
chilling why you saying High Shield it's
just Aura are you are you having a
shield oh R oh it didn't show me because
of hyper chat
she already
raed who who who who who who who who who
what's with people raing me uh from
Whole
Life whole life rids rare
occasion in my time
zone what the sh sh stream let me
see which one those
stream was it a member
stream I oh wait you can oh I didn't
realize you could raid from a member
stream oh that's so considerate of you
shy I don't know if you can hear this
but that's so considerate to raid from a
member
[Music]
stream oh thank
you thinking thank you for thinking of
me
that is really really
sweet
[Music]
oh we're done playing the game for today
just reading super chatos and cheating
cheating chatting with you
guys oh thanks for the
membership yay and also the membership
gifts thank you oh oh
oh even more yo
20 memberships in total being gifted out
you guys are so so generous wow stay a
while and
listen as we like to
say but yeah I actually uh yeah I just
finished reading the power super chats y
we got over a big
hurdle
M uh then the next is the
unarchived greatest epiphanies of all
time the K stream
why does that one show up before
the the zon didn't I do the zon first
interesting maybe I no I didn't reserve
the chers oh well
whatever F
nail I only see oh no wait this is the
one oh yeah oh
yeah come
okay cute cute this it oh my God even
more memberships oh my God it's worth it
you get a nice deal if you listen now if
you stay and listen stay while and
listen for one membership what a
deal weird that's what came first yeah
well we're doing this
one those were really some great
epiphanies if I may
say and I don't know if I said it so
clearly but like I would get these like
song epiphanies
for example when I was just like sitting
in the in the pizza restaurant with my
friend and eating pizza I they played so
many songs I'm like wait I know this
song I know this song what's the name of
this one again I feel like I can sing it
in the K and people would really like it
and so I I wrote them all down yeah for
the next Koka stream I got really
excited to sing them for you so thank
you for listening oh my God even more
memberships kfp so nice
nice jaob
47 anime food for you thank you for
missing
[Music]
me epic
Gamers Jones naan thanks for the pinky
honestly would watch ourv Dance to
anything in any medium not that we
missed you or
anything thank you why did we talk about
dancing
though thank you so
much while I was gone like there were
like
several like what do you call it in
[Music]
English uh
B uh a what's a a ball a ball but like a
not like a ball that you throw but a
ball where you
dance
[Music]
I guess it's just ball is it just
ball I'm looking it up now but I don't
know it's
[Music]
confusing well in there were so many in
Austria because we have like I don't
know I guess we have big ball culture
ball room culture I don't know and I saw
like other people posting Instagram
stories or whatever of going there and
all that and I'm like it's so nice
actually like maybe one day I'll go to
one but and there was like Austria's
biggest
event most exclusive cuz you pay so much
money to get in there most exclusive
like ball event ever like the world's
Europe's biggest ball event most
expensive ball event was in was like
just during my
[Music]
break it's so famous I don't even know
what it's called
anymore
[Music]
wait what was it
called there's so many ah the open B
there the open B uh op R ball have you
guys ever heard of it open
ball is there a
Wiki so I can tell you how amazing it
is ah there it is Vienna Opera
ball is an annual Austrian Society
excuse me hi Society okay why is it not
written there like that Austrian Society
event which takes place in the building
of the Vienna State Opera in Vienna
Austria on the first day preceding the
Ash Wednesday together with the New Year
concert the ball is one of the
highlights of the vianes Carnival season
yeah and then like celebrities from
other countries and so on come as well
the traditional tradition of the ball
goes back to
1814 during the time when the crowned
heads of Europe and the
aristocracy Aristo
y searched for entertainment after the
Napoleon Napoleonic Wars the first ball
in the Opera House took place in
BL it's really famous and it's expensive
to get in you can get in even if you're
not a celebrity but especially getting
like uh one of
those well I'll show you a
picture
M this is from 2014
apparently and
like I don't really know what's
happening in this thing but like
apparently
debutantes they're they're making their
vtuber debut but like as real people so
it's the real people debut I don't know
I only know vtuber debut so I don't
really know how this is
different but like they come in there
and then in know order to be in one of
those like like seating areas up there
you pay several
thousand
crazy
[Music]
qu it's it's a huge thing
yeah and I think it's not just this Hall
it's like a big building oh yeah it's
it's pretty big it's pretty big people
are like squeezed in there aren't there
it looks packed in those seating
areas still cheaper yeah but I wouldn't
really say it's worth it I don't know
like I was actually like offered like
hey there's still tickets on De on the
evening before or so do you want to get
one they even discounted right now but
it was still several thousand so I'm
like no I don't know this kind of stuff
is not really something I want to pay so
much money for It's like a I don't need
that and the thing is you can get in
without booking one of those seating
areas just but like you know you can
stand around it's still experience it
and then it's like I don't know 600 EUR
or so maybe I don't know 400 600 which
is much cheaper than getting one of the
seats and then you still experience it
so if anything maybe that's uh an
option not shocking that they're all
white yeah I I mean I don't know
that's yeah I don't know where these
people come from are they just Rich
families in Austria
because I
mean I I want you to know that Austria
is more diverse when you walk around uh
outside it's it's way more diverse trust
me this is not a good representation of
what Austrian people look
like really it's
not
yeah I don't know I need to ask my
friend she knows more about it I need to
ask her where these kind of people come
from these
debutantes like I only know about this
culture from gilmo girls and I wonder if
it's the
same kind of culture in Austria if
that's like comparable if I can compare
Gamer Girls
Rory deput
ball don't do dot me one that's like
like where else do you experience this
kind of stuff I I I don't have any other
connection point to it do you guys have
any connection to something like that
have you ever experienced that or a
friend going there or something like
that I feel like it's such a such a f
you just don't get to see as a normal
[Music]
person oh rainbow
attempt no no no right I'm not a
noble I like R's debutant po I think
yeah something very European High
Society wow fany I can't even Dance The
W my friend tried to teach me before but
uh my feet is like I have two left
feet no I'm American but that doesn't
matter Rory had
one I I've worked at a ball before I had
dance classes in wi about but not that
one yeah there's plenty there's like
less expensive ones that you can go
[Music]
to so maybe I'll go to one of the
cheaper ones I do want to just like
experience something like that once
because you can wear a beautiful big
ball gown like I have like maybe one
ball gown and I have absolutely no
reason to wear it you know just no
occasion to wear
it so would be nice to have an occasion
cuz at one time I wore it and and the
the place I wore it to I was absolutely
overdressed I mean I did get some switch
compliments but I I felt awkward cuz I
was overdressed so just go to a wedding
ah I would I wanted to wear the dress
but then it didn't fit the the color
[Music]
code that one wedding I went to in Japan
was we had to dress black or white yeah
so my my cute dress didn't apply and I
had to buy a new one but I I bought it
uh
yeah not not that fancy ball gown kind
of dress I wanted to but I thought it
would be
Overkill Rainbows are hard you tried
your best that's all that
matters but yeah one day I'll learn the
Walts properly and then I'll go to
something like this maybe maybe maybe
maybe and then hopefully I'll hear some
mozard and you know what's going to go
down if I hear some m
rard I'm going to go hyper and I'm going
to zoom around the ball uh Hall
whatever I never went to a prom like not
even someone else's
prom I didn't have a prom and I I never
been to someone else's you know sad
arriving only now miss the game will
watch lat Aug thank you that's fine
that's perfect
welcome cosplay ball uh like a
convention ball i' I I I've been to one
once or twice
but they feel a bit cringe to me I'm
sorry I don't like going to them I tried
but it was cring to me
I still
remember um I think it was that anime
free or something like free when that
was popular and I went to some like
Anime
conventions uh like like ball evening
ball
um you know most people were just
sitting at a table and then on stage
they were playing music and then there
was a performance and there was a a
performer
Group which was like I think it was
literally no it wasn't only guys but the
guys were definitely like the
main prominent thing
and they were all these kind of like
charai guys flashy Gody I don't
know handsome guys but like
like handsome in a way that makes me
angry
um and and and they just had to perform
shirtless and they did some like h no
wait I think they did like free cosplays
and all that before but then I think
this one was that that ice anime with
the
guys I think that was what it was
inspired by and what they were trying
like to perform or so and I don't know
making me cring
shirtless people lifting each other over
this like anime music lifting them like
like they're on
Ice yeah you nice
yeah I don't know what made me so mad
because I don't know okay I don't want
to I don't want to I don't want to
like you know be
[Music]
so salty and and judgmental but um
something about it just made me really
[Laughter]
angry the pretentiousness yeah in their
case maybe I didn't like the
pretentiousness but um that was just
that show group and then generally I
don't know I can't even dance that kind
of
dance and then besides that it's it's
just um those events at least here in
Austria cuz they were smaller ones they
felt like like like those those parties
for like teenagers where everybody's
only on the side of the Dance Floor I
mean me too but um no one's doing
anything and then I don't know it's kind
of cringe I I don't
know it was kind of CR but I felt happy
about being able to wear a cute dress so
H maybe that's my
only my only
[Music]
choice nobody asking anybody else to
dance exactly
exactly like why are we doing this why
are we doing this also like anime
convention After
parties my friends love to go to those
but I [\h__\h] hate them so much I hate
them so much and I'm I'm not going to
talk in detail about why but again it's
kind of cringe to
me I've tried one once and I I really
try to like enjoy
it but I don't even like dancing like in
such a club setting you know I hate
it I can only dance choreographies
TBH I can't I don't really like I feel
like I can freestyle to some extent but
it's like I'm freestyling in a
choreography style you know what I mean
not freestyling in like a club dancing
style that's when I start feeling
awkward and I I don't even want to yeah
[Music]
but and then it's again a setting where
it's so loud so you can't have
conversations with people either and if
somebody's trying to talk then you have
to scream and I hate
that
yeah I'd rather just eat pizza and go to
bed yeah for real for real like
especially after like spending the whole
day at a convention feeling exhausted I
don't feel like I've tried it I've given
it a chance several times and I just
always felt awkward and
cringe so I'm done I'm done maybe I'm
too old for this [\h__\h] I don't know
there's it's not about age really I see
a lot of older people there too but um
it's not my thing I can't vibe in
it I'd prefer to just chill at home
really makes you think why people call
me
extroverted yeah I don't want to be
surrounded by all these people
either
social battery would be dead but exactly
at that point my social battery is
dead and even if I sleep a night over it
it's already a challenge to go there
again on the following day if it's like
a weekend thing that's already a
challenge to do it two days in a
[Music]
row a
pudding you still watching my streams
how did you just ah wait you just got
moved over from sh's Member stream never
mind you're just here cuz of the
raid you are extroverted by B tuber
standards yeah or like by whole life
English
standards but your pink bat is still
powerful yes don't underestimate
it
[Music]
okay enough of that
talk I will go back to Super
Chat welcome Raiders so sweet still
welcoming them
[Music]
now uh where where's my window where did
I stop
reading ah here I found
it that was a big ass tangent
yeah just because Nathan was talking
about dancing and that was about some
completely different
dance dan it over yes yes
yes oh another pinky so close to the
other one oh you you're going to get a
kiss you're going to get a kiss you're
not going to escape the kiss just
because you separate your pinkies m m
you say here comes the cute part but he
showed up over an hour ago ah now even
more so you need a kids come here come
here come here come here come here
naan you need to coach
ichan I think you would do a great job
coaching ichan on how to like talk to
Satan please help him he needs your your
help
please it will be
um I'm sending you like on a work trip
on like
a what do you call this when you send
someone to go to a different country to
do a special
task that's what you're
doing separated pinkies sounds painful
oh yeah right now did you say it looking
forward to the next tension say goodbye
to the previous tangent it's okay to
move on to the next one we we would like
the next one too don't worry you'll
enjoy it we'll have a good
time diplomatic Mission something like
that for example
[Music]
yeah deploy I'm deploying you like in a
gacha
game what
no what
[Music]
now that I think of it did I ever
realize this funniness
about
ichan and
number together being number
one they should make like a a Duo
unit it's called number
one number in English though not n a n
ba and then whenever they get
interviewed M and ask like where does
his name come from and they'll be like
well it's because our group is made out
of me number and him
ichan which is Japanese for first and
number one yeah ichan on its own is
already already means number one not
just one but still you think I talked
about this
before no way it doesn't seem familiar
to me I feel like I had an epiphany just
now but d o d action thanks for the red
of chat Banger after Banger I missed you
like you wouldn't believe
K man really thank
you sweetheart thank you so
much I'm also really excited you guys
like the playlist so
much I'm I'm I'm excited I could
entertain you with good
[Music]
songs number number one yeah it's not
perfect
[Music]
but love love the set list amazing list
thank
you happy to hear that thank you action
18 so much passion do TCH thank you for
the red super chat as well I'm glad
you're back theno I miss miss you for
sure but I also hope you got some good
rest I did just in time for Valentine's
Day and my least favorite day as a
bitter old single chicken but at least I
can spend it with K and kfb tomorrow
glory to kfb Phoenix
power dude you have no idea I
haven't I don't remember first of
[Music]
all let should say I should say wa
didn't have a Valentine's Day for at
least a long long long long
time and uh yeah so don't worry that
doesn't make me any less desirable as a
person I haven't gotten Valentine's
flowers or
chocolates in a long
[Music]
time yeah I don't think I maybe I never
had a Valentine's day before anyway but
um I just want to what I'm trying to say
is does that make me L desirable no you
I think many people desire
me um yeah but just because I I'm not
you know or you're not just because I'm
not or you're not you know active in the
dating scene or whatever doesn't mean
that you're not desirable or something
like like
that so I hope that doesn't make you
feel
less of a of a attractive person or
whatever doesn't matter doesn't
matter you'll rise them up someday or or
they'll rise you up
[Music]
someday
yeah I'd love to get flowers I you know
and I couldn't even stream for you guys
not even that and then I ended up alone
on my Valentine's Day and I kept you
guys alone too unless you went to
someone else's stream and then you
weren't so alone after all but I was
alone I had Nissa at least I guess but
yeah I went to the supermarket and I saw
flowers being sold and I saw people
running around the flowers in their
hands on the streets and I was like
H are these for me I don't know you but
are those for
me no
but nah it doesn't matter it's just
another day and I mean cool if you if
you're
getting courted is that how you say it
but if you're not then it's also
whatever doesn't matter can happen
happen anytime doesn't have to be on
that specific day and all
that
yeah I just don't want you to be like in
a mindset anybody any of you I just
don't want you to be on a mindset where
it's like oh it's another Valentine's
Day where I have
nobody [\h__\h] that doesn't matter don't
think of it as like oh Valentine's Day
is a day where I should be with somebody
that's not
true we live in a
society that makes you think
that yeah it's not a race and it's not
like
a a
competition
so feel feel good feel good and also
enjoy enjoy alone time I love alone
[Music]
time I spiral sometimes but I come to
grips with it that's great I'm happy to
hear
that I find I like Valentine's Day and
I'm single I don't know why oh you like
it that's great maybe because right
after chocolate gets
discounted
[Music]
maybe chocolate is cheaper than usual
discount what a
deal I it wasn't Ash Wednesday by the
way a solemn reminder of human mortality
and the need for reconst Creation With
God Valentine's pagan holiday promoted
by holiday a Hollywood for
consumerism
she
[Music]
she you smacked
it smacked it you were like you can't
control me this Society can't tell me
what to
think you're strong you have a strong
mind let me pour some more
[Music]
water okay where where are we oh yeah so
Phoenix power glor to K thank you so
much do
tag I hope at least for uh White day I
can be there for you guys sorry it
didn't work out on Valentine's
Day thank you do for visiting me in the
hospital for at least
trying
pity thank
[Music]
you fro fro thank you for the red super
chat damn it Tel a banger after the
other we com genuinely we missed you so
much so happy to hear your voice again
and watch me you goofing around welcome
back to froggy waa too waah love thank
you I guess she's back
too she's
she's getting ready to make a real
comeback sometime soon
though she's not quite back I mean look
she's not even moving I don't know if
she's just maybe because I left the
window open while I was gone the tank
actually
froze and she's Frozen in the
tank uh-oh maybe she's
dead I'll try to warm her
up I'll try to put the the tank in the
[Music]
microwave
uhoh yeah really I shouldn't have left
the window open oh my God it's like
still snowing in in into the
room cold and I'm sitting here with my
Hawaii shirt because I can't I don't I
have too strong body heat I don't even
notice but the frog the frog I should
have protected the frog from the
[Music]
snow froggy waa
no did you leave her food even she's on
her own she's an independent frog she
can take care of herself she she catches
her own
flies
[Music]
you think she's hibernating okay she
probably didn't even when I when I wake
her up she probably won't even know that
I froze her by accident
right she won't take renge on me for
freezing her by an accident when she's
back alive
right I think I'll need some extra
bodyguards in the next
weeks
please it's winter there are no flies
right
now it's a no flying
[Music]
zone no that's not lie though I saw a
fly just today or yesterday my cats were
attacking it it flew in and my cats were
attacking it it was a big one
too they're already
around
enough funny hey don't get me that
look may I offer as a volunteer yes
please protect
protect and so thank you for
[Music]
m p thanks for Welcome Back boss and
thank you for the bangers in this K
thank you you're welcome I'm glad you
liked it
now I got to wait for some more
epiphanies until next time might take a
while you missed the streams really
thank you I love you guys thank you for
being so sweet and
[Music]
welcoming so thank you
puno so nice for you to listen in I'm
glad you were able to catch it
fried screw thanks for the red chat glad
that kiaha is back I missed you so much
it just wasn't the same without your
near daily tangents or kiys I was lost
chicken for I bck and yet you didn't bck
back only silence no I fcked you just I
I you just couldn't hear it I swear
almost F like a sapling going oo
Ki a did you guys go oo Ki
but now you guys know I was like even
reading your comments every day so I was
thinking of
you I was thinking of you secretly
secretly just on YouTube reading the
comments to my shorts and all that
that's all I did oh no more just
that it wasn't
work not considered work no I don't
consider it work it was fine
did I miss Koka yeah um but I will
rebroadcast it next week but during a
time that is not
na friendly prop probably or maybe it
will be actually maybe it will be but
just not Europe Europe friendly cuz this
one was Europe
friendly more or
less yeah I don't know what time exactly
yet and what day but we'll figure it out
although probably next week will be
um no schedule
week and
but especially for the rebroadcast I'll
try to put up the reservation as early
as possible so that you guys will know
early
[Music]
enough but wait isn't next week kind of
the last February week no not really
there's another one then afterwards okay
cuz I still want to use that schedule
art one more time isn't it nice it
wasn't even my idea to uh draw like a
like a whole like manga
page wasn't even my idea I just asked uh
I gave like two situations and one of
them was like a mat like uh waiting for
you to arrive to our date
ER kind of situation and then they drew
like yeah free panels
basically really
nice that
artist that artist drew me before
they're really cool artists with a
really cool art style is so
unique but when I look at their art
style all the time I have to think about
their
monogatari fan art because that artist
draws a lot of monar fan
[Music]
art I even have uh their uh one of their
comic comic
Market uh
books art
books yeah with monar Bak monar fan
art it's so cool so cool I love
p and I like that artist already even
without the monat fan art but you know I
like them even more for drawing back at
monat stuff all the time even now like
even now where you know it's not really
that active and they're not really
putting out anything new but hey we got
the confirmation for New Seasons let's
[\h__\h] go I'm so excited I didn't
I somebody needs to like clip for me
that discussion I don't know when we had
it when I was like I still believe one
day there will be new seasons and then
people I remember I remember people
doubted
me we had this discussion before on
stream right sometime and some people
were like I don't think so it's over I'm
like
no I believe it even if it's been a long
time yeah I do think we should do a
watch long I just don't know I think
it's still like too early we don't need
to start yet
or do we maybe I'm underestimating the
amount of episodes we have to watch how
much time it will
[Music]
take wasn't too long ago
really it's never too early to start why
I do want to start it so that it
connects well to the new
[Music]
season but did we have a time frame
besides this
year I don't
[Music]
remember know but so cute so
true how many episodes do you want to
watch per watch long I don't know like
it it could be
um enough to
fill 3 to 4 Hour watch time I don't mind
even going longer but I wonder if you
guys would mind going
longer um I wouldn't even mind doing
like 5 hours 6 hours in one
go we could probably watch a whole
season and one
go probably not the whole season but I
don't
know one episode is usually like 30
minutes
right it's just like not everybody has
that much time right so I don't know how
much I really should do and we'll
probably do it weekly anyway cuz I I
still want to continue doing weekly
members only
[Music]
streams
yeah any my Marone let's go don't mind
it's on if it's on a weekend I don't
know if it will always be on the weekend
cuz I also want to do long RPG streams
on the
weekend yeah I mean we've watched
extended Lord of the Rings before guys
come on 5 hours watch along is
[Music]
nothing but okay I'll try to have it on
the on the weekend maybe we can start
once I'm done with Yakuza or so I don't
know will I be a members next week I try
uh maybe maybe even on Monday maybe
right away on
[Music]
Monday how about every Sunday okay but
you guys you know that probably that
means like in order to be in a Groove
it'll be several weeks of only watch
lungs is that okay cuz like some people
who maybe aren't interesting in
interested in Bak or anime or so or
watch Longs I'm sorry if that's not your
kind of
content are there any people who who say
like they will not
[Music]
participate you don't mind you don't
mind you're
fine
okay you're not
interested I'll pass what
[Music]
really I won't be tuning it but don't in
but don't let it stop
[Music]
you can someone calculate for me how
many streams it if if if uh we watch
everything and then 5 hours
maybe uh but on
average uh how many streams I have to do
to watch everything okay someone calcul
learned out for
me I'll try it out yeah if you never
watched it before maybe at least give
the first few episodes to try cuz it's a
really good
show a
[Music]
classic I do want to consider the people
who don't want to watch it though cuz I
I get it I mean especially if it takes
up so many
[Music]
streams are we skipping opening and
ending um I would but it wouldn't it be
difficult if uh the opening doesn't if
the cuz like timing matching the timing
and all that the ending we can probably
skip but that's not that much time that
we're
saving I'll just sing
along
10 episodes per stream is reasonable
you'll need like seven streams five or
oh
what for all of it or are you talking
one
season there's no way it just takes me
that short amount of
time H didn't you guys say it's like 300
hours of episodes or did I get that oh
no 300 something episodes not 300 hours
of episodes right okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay
okay one season is only 13
episodes and then yeah one is like 30
minutes and if I do five hours
just one 2 three 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 10 okay
then we can round it up to 12 episodes
if 5 hours is like 10 episodes we can
just do one more round it up to six
episodes and then we have a full season
in one go
yeah I don't know where I got that 300
number
from uh it's 13 episodes maybe depends
on the season
right I think we can wipe some of these
Seasons out in one go in one
stream and then I thought it would take
up like three months of member streams
but then it's not that bad and maybe
maybe maybe after watching one full
season I think it would be good to have
one member stream so okay I think we can
do it like this one week we watch a full
season in one go 6 hours the next week I
still do a normal member stream then
next week we watch one full season again
and then the next week cuz then we have
a good cut off
point if each season is to cut off point
then I don't mind doing normal L streams
in between
too
yeah okay we'll make it work let's go
I'm excited I don't really watch anime
anymore but I wonder I haven't rewatched
monuk katali in a long time many many
years so I wonder how I will feel about
it
now you'll need a 300 IQ to follow along
with the sub if you don't speak Japanese
yeah yeah yeah me too like back then
when I watched it I think I already
spoke Japanese but not so fast so I also
often
stopped the screen to read the
everything
yeah but many of these things are not
really meant to be
red you know although yeah well if you
don't need subtitles then you can listen
and read like because there's like
random KI on the screen sometime that
are supposed to like convey something
and if you don't have to read subtitles
then then you have a an advantage for
sure but
yeah it was one of the first animes I've
seen and I still loved it even if I
didn't know Japanese me too me too I was
also overwhelmed a little bit by it a
lot but it was so worth it I paused so
much when I first watch yeah I guess we
can't do that that's the problem but
it's
okay if if there's anything firsttime
Watchers don't understand I'll be happy
to explain to you what the [\h__\h] is going
on if anything is happening too
fast I will be the one explaining for
once or chat will also explain for
sure damn I'm I'm so excited for all the
all the like um you don't you know
nothing or I know everything all those
phrases all those variations of those
phrases I want to hear them
again
y y yay I'm so excited to meet Nadal
again n n my
o just don't spoil the plot okay okay
okay okay I'll shut up I'll be
[Music]
a the the movies yeah I think we'll
watch the movies too but maybe at the
end if we still have time and if we
don't feel sick of it if we feel sick of
watch so many watch alongs or if I feel
like uninspired or so um then maybe I'll
leave it as homework to you but we'll
see how it goes we'll we'll watch the
animes first and then we'll see how
about the movies but it's definitely
like
possible cuz the movies are
amazing the movies were
amazing yeah so good
okay let's go back to reading Super Chat
though now that we cleared that
up where was I ah here Fred screw why
did you send me on this
tangent andless thank you for the red of
chat welcome back I'm proud of you for
taking your time off but I'm also happy
to have you streams again thank you it
was definitely a difficult decision cuz
I
feel very pressured as a content creator
in a stream
um to like keep it up to keep going to
continuously bring content and
continuously try to work work work
work but it was an
important thing to do so and it's thanks
to you guys that I'm able to do it so
thank
you stuck on the grind set for real yeah
[Music]
anyway thank you endless our fun from
now on will be endless
too and your G thank you soon J SW than
you soon for the such a fun C is great
glad you're back thank you I'm also glad
you're back back at kfp I mean you were
never gone right you were working every
day as if I was still there right right
yeah of course you were I believe you I
I I totally will not check the security
cam
footage you to check if everybody was
doing their job no no no I will not
check it don't worry about it don't
worry thank you J SW
B I am a cheap beep thank
you flaming fans thank you Lou Moonlight
thank you for the red super chat thanks
for the K boss I missed you
clap clap emoji you're the best W Ky
love forever love forever oh my God
that's the second time
today thank you so much thank you thank
you thank you for the Applause dooo I
wish I could bow in front of
you no no no no no no no please no are
you mean me watching the
footage huh why why don't you why are
you
hiding
sus we learned where the blind spots are
today not every branch has blind spots
no no no no no no no no
no and maybe you don't even know it but
there's some spy
chickens that I put
cameras onto their
hats before I left which were spying on
you guys on the other
chickens H
maybe got to make you you
[Music]
paranoid maybe there's a Robot Chicken
yeah with with cameras in their eyes and
you think it's like that [\h__\h] water
faucet you just talk to the Robot
Chicken normally you will you have no
idea which ones are the real chickens
and which ones are the fake
ones FR shaved C
[Music]
yeah too bad you guys only have one
brain cell so you can't figure out
what's a faucet and what's a
chicken and what's a
cyborg yeah a pinky thank you so much
for the great stream it's great to have
you back this break reminded me of how
great it is to have you here brightening
our days with your Majestic Phoenix fire
thank you so much for being here for us
T we love love
you thank you did are you sure did you
did you check with everybody you're
saying
we are you guys do you guys
agree is it
true is it true what he
says yes yes yes Emoji coming in in
three two one there it
is I know the latency I know how it
works
yes yes yes yes yes I love you too thank
[Music]
you I knew it I knew it there they are
there's the
[Music]
yeses yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes nice I love
you
do oh my God love
forever Trevor G thanks for the pinky
that's the last one k it was great
welcome B wah wa glad to see you again
finally kfb branches can reopen or
return to normal
reopen they weren't closed were they I
didn't allow that no more secret
rebrands like Taco Bell red R and Sh
Express or
hooers will you punish the poultry
poultry put them on the
menu did such a thing
occur of course
not what the hell what the
[\h__\h] okay seems like I I'll really have
to sit down and check all the security
footage I thought I thought I'd just
like threaten you with it but not do it
but I guess I'll have to do
it
huh
sh
Shina it can't be
helped I have no
choice I have no
choice okay
um I want to go eat food is that
okay tomorrow I'll tackle the comeback
stream super chatos which are quite a
lot oh my
God y
I'll tackle them
tomorrow F I think Today's Pizza day I
have stuff to cook but now I have this
problem again that I don't feel like
cooking afterwards maybe tomorrow I'll
cook before the stream or so and then
I'll have lunch and then dinner same
thing cuz always two
portions okay thank
you w I use tackle on Super Chat a we
ass
attack I was bringing pizza
too we we think the same
things it's like we could finish each
other's
sandwiches what toppings
tuna
tuna I have frozen tuna Pizza in my
freezer it's not weird it's a typical
Italian classic you
know no corn sadly no corn would be
better with corn everything's better
with
[Music]
corn do your cats like
tuna yeah they do
mhm I think I'll just go for basic
Supreme Pizza M
supreme
Supreme
supreme pizza maybe some kind of like
Tik Tok
influencer cuz they all wear like
Supreme clothes don't
they if even your pizza's Supreme oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] don't let them snack on your pizza
no they wouldn't eat that I
think thankfully they don't have those
kind of
weird issues where they try to eat human
food usually not if it's like if I eat
like cereal and I'm done with the cereal
and there's like still a little bit of
milk left I cannot leave the the bowl on
the table they will drink the
milk and a while ago I got like so I
panicked for no
reason I I ate not cereal but like
chocolate those those crunchy chocolate
bowls cereal thingies flakes thingies uh
with
milk and then I was done eating it and
then I just put it on the side and then
I wasn't watching for a moment and then
smoothie mamam mammed it for like 3
seconds I I was like looking away the
other way and then I I hear some Lam Lum
Lam and I'm
like what and there she was and I was
like [\h__\h] like uh chocolate is like
toxic to cats but I I was
like what if this is really really
[\h__\h]
bad so I like grabbed her immediately
away from the somewhat chocolatey milk
which was only a little bit chocolatey
from the chocolate bowls that were like
in the milk you know it wasn't like
chocolate
so I I I panicked and uh I think I
looked up some stuff on Google and then
I realized okay okay it's probably not
that bad it's probably not that bad it's
definitely not that bad it's fine it's
fine it's
fine when I I even though it's not even
chocolate like not proper chocolate yeah
I I I was just
panicking it was just free MMS and I'm
already
panicking cuz like cats MMS are not even
that efficient when they mm there's
barely any any liquid going into their
mouth yeah no she was totally fine
totally
fine oh I think what I did
then I was still kind of worried and I
thought if I immediately feed her those
um liquid cat
snacks then maybe it will
like I don't know like
over
overshadow this the tiny amount of
something like chocolate more like caca
I guess in her
body uh yeah desperation lot just making
sure to do everything I can so I
immediately fed fed her the liquid
catnet and was hoping to just like make
it less dangerous but it wasn't
dangerous to begin with I
guess but yeah dilute in her St exactly
exactly exactly yeah make it overpower
the tiny
amount of chocolate something like
chocolate if that is even considered
chocolate that she took in chist is
averted
yeah yeah D diluted diluted diluted d
looted l
loot
loot I need to give you this advice tuna
and pepperoni and pizza is
a
I hate it when people judge like me
eating tuna pizza or pineapple pizza
whatever so I don't want to judge
you that sounds like something I want to
eat
separately but you do you I'm happy if
you found a pizza that is like the best
[\h__\h] ever to you how I miss K talking
thank
you sounds good m
[Music]
do you
mention double standards no no like I'm
not judging you like I'm not making fun
of you and I'm not doubting
[Music]
you it's not just not common here I will
support you thank
you I want to judge you
but
Hawaiian
pizza it's coming from the corn lady
excuse me everybody loves
corn everybody loves
corn corn is amazing corn makes
everything
[Music]
amazing I'm going use my Italian badge
for pizza advices I thought it was
strange but it's actually good what the
tuna and and
pepperoni
salami we're talking about salami
right that word confuses me so much
pepperoni cuz to me pepperoni are those
like bell pepper looking things but then
sometimes it's
salami so
confusing Pon ah the pon ah the
pon
corn is so good
[Music]
yes Hawaiian pizza o I'm curious about
what that's
like no okay to be honest in German we
say pepperoni with an F in
there but yeah pepperoni so is pepperoni
always the
[Music]
salami do you know the
pepperoni now now I guess I know the
baloni oh we're getting raided but we're
ending no come again tomorrow when we're
going to play um more of Yakuza leg a
dragon infinite
wealth I guess Yakuza is not even in the
title they dropped
it they freaking dropped
it so okay I'll see you tomorrow and in
German we
say
byebye
goodbye goodbye goodby goodby goodby
goodby
goodbye thank you for watching let's go
more Yakuza tomorrow beat some people up
who deserve
[Music]
it
G is doing a c out
[Music]
okay oh
my haven't heard G sing in a
[Music]
while bye
byebye bye-bye