e
e e
oh
oh I guess there was no music there also
is there
no does she have no does she have no
audio feedback on her microphone
uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh how does this
work again I forgot how to do that she's
using she's using the good old go
XLR how's this work
again I forgot about checking
the the feedback W waa are you listening
to my stream somewhere in the other room
1 a.m. tangents 1 a.m. is it 1: a.m. at
your place sorry this is a really weird
streaming time I
know
uh
uh 2 a.m. oh
no headphones chat m i I don't know how
this works anymore wah wah wah
wah
ah she heard me do you not uh stream
with audio feedback of your own voice in
your
ears yes please you don't have to speak
so
quietly W is here yay
why is she
Whispering I'm sh made me Basta she cook
the pasta she make the
Caron with with the love the am
am I think she doesn't want to intrude
but I want her to
intrude H you want you I can't hear
myself yet no you want you want to try
there you go
she uses the headphones that I use like
in my like everyday life outside when I
when I bring headphones to the airport
or
Soto a nice Sony noise cancelling
headphones ah mic monor there it
[Music]
is shouldn't that be it that's probably
it that doesn't work can't hear yourself
now do you hear me
no yeah yeah best headphones actually I
can activate monitoring here
though isn't that kind of delayed though
monitor
only okay okay now you can hear
yourself is that not weird doing like
that uh oh is it too much that's um it's
a it's a bit weird okay
wait is this where was this where did
you find the so mixer is
here oh yeah the mic
[Laughter]
[Music]
one what's your
routine
headphones uh no no I don't think so
that's weird I haven't used a goar in a
long time so I don't
really uh I new to so I'm
not okay
um wait let me I'm going to Google
really quickly go help
us go XLR how
to voice feedback feed
feedback see I I just met laa for the
first time like two days ago and I'm
already at her place eating her
cooking this is going
fast so fast okay how
[Music]
about no that's voice effects Ah that's
my stream ah I can help you I get my
okay sorry guys this is the one thing I
forgot to set up that's actually really
important to
me I mean I'm in Bella Italia
totally no I'm still in
Japan but soon not
anymore
phone
[Music]
oh what what what
are they connect are the headphones
connected directly to the gore yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
H how does this work
again a lot of things
mhm yeah yeah yeah
monor uhuh uhuh here's here's one uh
explanation how to turn off the mic
monitor maybe if we can like go
backwards we can turn it
off uh um select the routing tab yeah
mhm then uncheck so check the top left
box but we have it checked
yeah do we have the
monitor no we have the monitor on like
100%
yeah that did not
work that's Entertainment
[Music]
too maybe I can ask
chpt Chad GPT I've never asked Chad GPT
a question ever I use Chad GPT the
time it dos really doesn't it just make
up answers
I mean it
helps okay I'm going to ask hey CH
gbt how can I
monitor my voice through go XLR go
XLR okay connect headphones done set up
mic monitoring
done maybe maybe it's the routing in
windows I don't know maybe
not he has so many monitors and the
waiter set up I have to like look over
her drawing tablet like lean over it
it's not very comfortable even for me
but I don't know what to set it up it's
kind of similar to what uh what Callie's
setup is like aha system mhm um
n
um test test test test
did CH GPT tell you something useful
it's too much text I don't
read t l d
r um we just we just
what doesn't work I remember it used to
work about no oh
no it's all
on yes ah no
no wait go back
no no no that's something
else let let me test one thing what if
what if what if this is just too too
messed up what if we switch to this oh
now I hear myself oh you hear yourself
yeah I just switched to like the
settings different settings they already
have it like set up like this yeah okay
maybe you have to turn on the uh the mic
maybe it's because now you're very low
okay yeah I I can turn it off not here
oh there you go yeah
okay I mean this is like just default
goex settings so it will sound different
but at least I can hear myself yeah okay
okay
by
bye
bastao
yeah yeah I can I can hear myself that's
probably not like the ideal voice
settings bit quiet still really oh okay
okay okay okay yeah how about how about
now now should be okay I'm like fully in
the yellow you can't tell me this is too
quiet but you know what we need we need
a little bgm it's okay I have some bgm
sorry in the loading screen I forgot
about the
bgm okay it will be
uh it might be loud for one second
[Laughter]
yeah uh sorry
M first you were like oh I don't hear
anything in the loading screen now my
ears broken and now you were like oh
that was so loud maybe my ears are
broken now for real for real M it's okay
everything's fine now so today we're
doing Super Chat reading I will catch
you up if I can
and I wanted to stream yesterday but wow
it really was not going to happen I cuz
everything was also like delayed even
like we were not going according to the
time schedule as as we wanted like we
started around the right time but then
we ended much later cuz like everything
takes so much
time yeah and then I think I was done it
like uh 10 p.m. or something I don't
know even if I would have started
streaming then would have been already
so late so I think this is the better
option even if it's at a weird
time um still better than sitting in the
studio for hours after I was actually so
exhausted even though even though I was
not going to be like streaming anymore
um jenma and I like JMA was like hey but
you can still like once you're done with
this
stuff can you please go use the booth
the streaming Booth anyway and finish up
some work that you have and I'm like
yeah sure like possibly depending on how
exhausted I will but I I also didn't
think I would be that exhausted and so
at like I don't know what time was it
really 9:30 or so I don't know what no
maybe even 10 I think it was close to 10
I was like done and I walk out and and
and I I see Gemma and I'm like the first
thing I say to her is no I just like
cross my arms and I'm like no Gemma no
it's not happening you know what I mean
and she was like
e I'm like NOP
mm no they have to wait I am freaking
exhausted sweaty spaghetti and I it's
late as yeah like um like literally
you f you guys fill up my schedule like
management give me a million things to
do some things will have to take you
know the back seat I guess so to say cuz
I I can't I'm not even at home I don't
have like like my equipment ready for me
to do anything at any time so I'm not
very flexible right now so no means no
but uh after the Super Chat rating oh
bgm wasn't looping after the Super Chat
rating I'm going to um use wa wa's setup
a little bit more uh to finish like some
more stuff that they apparently cannot
wait uh until I'm home for even though
I'm home very
soon they cannot wait but yeah glad you
can actually say no can I can I there's
like I mean like literally though like
certain things are just like not really
possible at certain times I don't have
my streaming set up and microphone and
all that in the hotel so yeah it is what
it is you got to wait you got to wait
yeah yeah I I like I've been like for
hours I've been grinding before I went
to Japan hours hours of recording stuff
to get things done on the deadline the
the few things I kind of have to do now
is like like some little fixes like
little little re-recordings or and stuff
of smaller things
so yeah it's nothing too big but
apparently can't
wait I can wait an eternity for wa wow
if only if only everybody would say that
about waiting for me at least you guys
can wait for me thank you I wanted on my
desk by yesterday okay this is so
unrelated but you mentioning the word
desk makes me want to mention that raas
desk is incredible she has like this
desk that when you push the button it
goes
like down or up however you want I I I
wonder it can probably probably turn
into a standing desk
too you want to want
to yo did you hear that it's so high tag
it wentop a little
bit so cool table go
[Music]
okay there's some noise cancelling going
on so if I don't speak you won't hear
it this so cool I want a table like this
but generally my problem is like for
tables they're like I need a long table
but all these tables they're just
selling them in like basic sizes I need
a long
[Music]
one 4090 disc
yeah yeah her setup is so cool and her
room is like filled with merchandise
with like tapestries whole of Life
tapestries and stuff and some other
stuff but a lot of whole of Life stuff
and a lot of plushes p o k e m o n
plushies so many so many Plushies so so
cool wow wow and there there there was
uh some wa
plushy I I think she has like all the
whole life English
uh the what series what series of
plushies was that one of the ples that
we all seem to have or almost all I
don't know was it all of us but there
was there was yeah friend with you I
think yeah the friend we view
plushies she has like all of them lined
up and the the middle ones are me and
Cali next to each other does that mean
something that um me and cie are in the
middle does that mean
something there's no narissa friend with
you yet right so if there was a narissa
friend with you then she would probably
take the middle
place a new subscriber thank you welcome
thank
you OG tamole fan tamole yesterday I met
Cali yeah cie Kelly was doing well I I
chitch a little bit with her and
inspected like her her
surgery um
thing yeah I was like are you okay let
me check let me check I was like let me
check let me check and I just I grabbed
her hand and I I dragged her into uh the
changing room so she can like show me
privately her knee her knee looks
good and yeah and I I also one of these
days I Met m senpai mon Sena it's been a
while since I'm at M Sena and we chitch
a
lot I was happy to see her and she
seemed to be happy to see me and I was
like oh M Senai you're so cute and she
was like I know you're so cute and we
called each other cute a bunch of times
and pretty and she was like touching um
my head and my forehead a lot I I had my
bags my head my forehead exposed and and
like she was touching my forehead I'm
like I'm like my my forehead I used to
get bullied from my forehead and she was
like e no way no your your Oro is so
Kawaii I'm like
[Music]
no yeah yeah and and then and then uh
she took me to the changing
room and some questionable things
happened uh
yeah
[Music]
she
she opened her
[Music]
blouse can I say this I mean when it
comes to Min Senpai I feel like there's
a lot of like stories of her making
other people touch her boobs and all
that I didn't touch them this time but
like she wanted to show me
something I've heard enough
[Music]
she wanted to show me
um
how how
[Music]
her boobs react to gravity when she's
not wearing a bra so she was like kind
of like taking out her boob but still
covering it with her hand so that I
would not see too much but she was like
holding it and showing me like look look
this is
how and I'm like oh looking respectfully
like
literally uh H oh H and she's like look
look look this is like yeah see this is
why this is why I wear brows and I'm
like yeah uh because we were talking
about me like not wearing wanting to
wear bras because they just always hurt
my back and she was like e how how can
you do that don't your like booby's like
you know and I'm like no no no really
like and then she's like oh because mine
are like this and then she like opens up
and takes
her poops in her hand and like kind of
puts them out of the cup and shows them
off and she's like look look look I'm
like um
yeah yeah sure they they look good they
look like they're really um resisting
gravity to be honest but she seemed to
be a little bit concerned of it and I
was like no like honestly no this looks
wonderful um but yeah thank you for
showing
me it's just good old man
zai I was like you know I haven't seen
her in a long time I feel like and I
thought um maybe we don't have like like
the same excitement anymore when we talk
to each other but no like she's just so
social and talkative and yeah
[Laughter]
it was fun talking with her for the
first time in a while
yeah she's as she's touchy as
ever eh so I touched back but not that
part just like you know G generally just
gently stroking her back or
so don't misunderstand
[Music]
guys
spicy yeah
some things
are going on so ah should I should I
just like I don't want to peack out all
my tangents right away but um I don't
know I don't know I don't know I I could
but I shouldn't but I feel like yapping
right now feel like
[Music]
yapping you didn't show her your I did
not show her no no no I was like waiting
until she was like
gone she was like k k come on come on
I'm like no mm- I'm not wearing a bra
and I am
[Music]
embarrassed yeah Raa is probably also
listen to listening to this maybe maybe
she's getting like neurons activated by
this story and she's like already
sketching something but I'm in front of
her tablet so she has to hold it in
until until she can
draw money said
by showing me the way her boobs react to
gravity yes that's a nice way to phrase
it but I really I really mean it like I
don't know what she's talking about
there's not that much gravity going on
[Music]
really you're taking notes too drawing
sketches on her iPad oh I wonder if L
also does that like you know will like
constantly when she's like on the on the
road or whatever when she's like not you
know at home she'll be like using her
iPad a lot for
[Music]
drawing gravity defying booa well
wouldn't say defying but
anyway uh
ah do you notice something different
this should be the nerfed version but
it's not nerfed as much as I told you so
you probably didn't even notice and
honestly I don't think it's like you
know I don't think there's much Nerf
neration going on where is
[Music]
here oh yeah I think this is better you
know one thing I noticed in the K stream
um that I did
previously I think I was like constantly
like like this
and when I move around like this and you
don't see my full legs I feel like it
looks like my legs are just like
dangling down there when it's cut off
like
[Music]
this because I'm just too wo whoo wo
whoo like if you see like the full
thing then it's not really it doesn't
look like my legs are
dangling looks more natural yeah the
legs the thighs for sure
right I I mean I think it's really cool
cuz I I don't think I've ever seen like
uh F jiggle in whole life before I mean
maybe maybe recently maybe they've been
implementing that but it's definitely
still a new thing
so uh that was that was a surprise to me
I didn't even know that they would
Implement F
jiggle wait I I need to find my right
position
again where am I is this how I was
before
this is
fine so okay okay okay okay I'll give
you more tangents but for now let's read
some super chats because I have to catch
up on super chats I'm just going to I
don't know if this is really the most
recent one that I have to read but um
it's one of the ones with the most Super
Chat so I'm going to be reading
from uh the birthday stream the first
one I
think the first one uh
[Music]
I'll be reading the birthday yeah oh
there's some other stuff to read okay
but I'm not going to read that now I'm
going to just focus on this for now
because you know it's kind of still like
somewhat on
topic uh I don't want to be like too too
late on these yeah and we'll see how far
we get with this
[Music]
huh yeah but thank you thank you for
thank you for letting me use your space
da she has like streams later in the
evening so thankfully I can use her
space she was so so eager to offer me
her space I think I'm the first first
Hol member to visit her place I'm sure
and first whole member to taste her
cooking I managed to eat her cooking
before she's like making a piz with cie
yeah okay here we go we're starting I'm
sorry guys it's like I wanted to do it
in
um this form because why
not um but if I show you guys the names
this will be really small can you even
read this I was just going to show you
the messages what do you
think I'll be saying the names out loud
anyway or do you want me to show the
names
is that
fine okay
okay jaob
[Music]
47 why does it feel why does this why
does me reading super chats feel like
I'm at
home
py Mo thank you for the r chat Y what
pass make you
carbona
carbona I like Carona very much it's one
of my favorite pastas so can you adjust
the zoom level to automa I'm pass in the
screen size
what
what what what do you mean I don't know
what you mean h happy fourth birthday
and H live you continue to be the star
that I'm proud to say I love and deeply
Revere what the impact you have on those
around you are impossible to notice and
they've all been for the better please
continue to be your amazing your your
amazing self our loving Idol thank you
dun is your sweet yeah my fourth
birthday already that's so crazy it will
be my fourth anniversary also
soon that is a lot of time that we spent
together thank you for the sweet words
motion thank you that you're still
around you've been at every birthday as
far as I remember so thank you for
always being at my birthday parties even
though I have not attended a single one
of
yours very
[Music]
one-sided I don't even know where your
birthday when your birthday is I don't
know when any of you guys' birthdays are
that's so sad actually I'm sorry guys um
I'm trying my best to remember your
names and stuff there's no way I can
remember your birthdays but um feel free
to notify me of your birthdays as you do
in Super chats and stuff you know if you
want I will not remember it though so
just so you
know
yeah yeah keep on reminding
me thank you
Mo peab
H Mo
what ah rice all free thank you for the
pinky hi Tel was away meeting a lot of
friends and a pretty lady at the
convention K so I'm late for my paycheck
happy birthday
Tel thank you so much that's so nice of
you uh Happy Birthday to me uh what do
you mean you're late for your
paycheck cuz I mean you were on time for
my birthday you were on time for my
birthday where you not you're not late
everything's good hope you had fun at
the
convention y y I wonder who you met cuz
I I I think I I mentioned I went
somewhere too right I did I go to you
guys know I go to conventions with my
friends you guys know that that is uh
public knowledge and um yeah yeah so I
go too to such places and enjoy them
just like you that is nice that we're
sharing these
interest
[Music]
jackk for
John V
oh thank you for the red of chat wow wow
wow yo tento happy fourth birthday in
whole life I'm in Vietnam right now oh
is that what that currency is it looks
like the the sign looks interesting it's
like a d with an arrow and then yeah is
that Vietnam currency sign ah it's dong
so I'll say you 1 million Dong my 1
million hearts for you wow 1 Mill you
have 1 million Hearts donate some of
them donate
999,000 no
999 9
999 what 9 how do you eh how do you say
9 n999
999,999
right that's weird cuz I'm saying 999 F
I'm saying
twice
9999 that really confused me just now
what the hell
999,999 that just sounds weird how do I
say it in German no
199,999 I
guess this sounds weird I guess I don't
say this number often enough to feel
comfortable with
[Music]
it what am I yapping about thank you
John V bear for celebrating my birthday
are you in Vietnam like for vacation or
just generally now cuz you say I'm in
Vietnam right
now in any case I hope the weather is
good sounds I I feel like that's a a hot
hot place I think it's hot over
there so for personal stuff
uh-huh wow you're so
informed okay thank you John Bieber M
next is marry Pippin with a
rainbow thank you so much happy birthday
Kiana to think it's been four birthdays
already mhm that you've spent with us
now how you haven't gotten tired of us
I'll never know same same to you but
with all the things you do the stories
you tell the effort you put in it's
impossible for me to get tired of
you this past year has seen you finished
tons of series release your first album
plus Cima mhm vlogging in your third
anniversary that was I I really liked
the result of that some fun off collabs
have a football Arc and lots of other of
things a number of these were definitely
not in my expectations not in your bingo
card huh it's still only the start of
the second half of 2024 so while this
birthday will pass there will still be
tons of things to look forward to in the
rest of the year like the Ian concert
and the world tour and your next
anniversary exactly I'm so happy to call
you my Kam oie regardless of time zone
differences you brighten my day and
thinking of things you try and you do
always brings a smile to my face and
makes me proud thank you I'm glad we can
work through the time zone
differences okay this wasn't meant to be
a rainbow when I started but I'm here so
I guess I'm committing oh God I haven't
seen a birthday merch
yet you're right my birthday merch
please bye bye bye bye anyways happy
birthday as well thank you thank you so
much yeah I mean the things you're right
they're like oh
no looking back on the past year as if
it's like my anniversary
but there's still still a lot of time to
go until the end of the year and also
until my anniversary yeah we've been
doing exciting things for like 4 years
now there's just
always always something exciting
happening although right now there's
like a lot a lot of
preparation try to check the time step
to see how much V is left oh you
normally can't catch my streams live and
this is actually for like a good time
for you that is
rare that is
rare but yeah Mary Pippin thank you for
the long long supportive message and the
sweet support in terms of Super Chat
hopefully you liked the merchandise
too and yeah thank you for following my
journey and not getting tired of me cuz
I I mean I would say that's like you
know normal a normal thing to happen
and I wouldn't I wouldn't you know be
surprised e but I'm so happy that you
guys stay for
me
so I have an obligation to stay
too yeah I can't leave you guys
behind I'm
[Music]
here thank you Mary
spin for the beautiful
rainbow and next EDF five fencer thank
you for the red super chat EDF
EDF happy birthday thank you I am
playing EDF at the end of this month I
think mhm mhm EDF
EDF so you seem to be a big fan I guess
of EDF so you're going to be you're
going to be delighted I suppose it's
going to be my first time playing it
though maybe me playing EDF is also one
of those things that you wouldn't have
expected you
guys but here we are yeah you can
pre-order my thing like you can
pre-order the game and then I think it
comes with the WWA I guess or do you
have to buy that separately I actually
don't know um
feels like we're the worship skin
eh I feel like that's a bit different
[Music]
situation okay I am a pre-order bonus so
go pre-order if you want like a big big
but small Wawa decoy to play around with
and it comes with some phas not phrases
like yeah recorded voice
lines thank you so
much iown thanks for the red super chat
and the rainbow actually thank happiest
birthday to the cutest and best YouTuber
in the I hope you have the most
wonderful day ever wa I can't believe
it's your fourth birthday with us thank
you so much for always working so hard
and giving us endless joy and happiness
with everything you do I hope you know
that you're truly amazing in every way
possible possible and there is no one
else in this world that would we would
rather support other than you really we
will always be here cheering you on as
much as we can no matter how much time
passes I know I'm always praising you
all the time but I hope you know that
every single praise I've ever given you
is genuinely from the bottom of my heart
I know you truly are the best love you
forever and always my T oie
yay it is tan oi when you are with your
tan oi B
get
[Music]
it sorry I'm a bit tired
whoa the past days have been really
tiring me out the past couple
days I thank you unknown for your sweet
words I know I know you know
you know I know I know that you are you
know one of my biggest supporters and
I'm your number one and I hope that will
never change but with with you I don't
really have those doubts
so with you it feels very very certain
and stable thank you so much for the
support thank you for celebrating with
me my
birthday pety D Psy D soon J swag book
also rainbow what's happening all these
rainbows it's been a while since the
weather has been this
beautiful happy fourth birthday wa
thanks for being you and continuing to
do cool new things I can't wait for the
next K pop poop to drop wo wo K poop pop
to drop K pop poop to drop that could be
some lyrics and to see all the cool
stuff you've got to work on this year
just a short rainbow for my first and
best and only
oie thank
you yeah I'm I'm working on some new
music right now
um no no it will take it might still
take some
time
um I
think it will not be released until the
Fredy life though
but I
think I think I I figured out
[Music]
something
so I uh ran into my Fredy Liv's
director yesterday just ran into him and
I asked sui
Masen and
[Music]
uh uh when cuz like it's pre-recorded
right and then it has to be like edited
and it takes a while uh until it can be
streamed the 3D live and I I asked and
when we record this and I record my new
song
too can you guys sent me the motion
capture data perhaps so that I can use
it for the music
video
because yeah I could recorded at home
but if I just get their motion capture
data then it will be higher
quality and I might be
using backup dancers this time I might
be hiring some backup dancers so that is
certainly something that is very
difficult to do on my own with my own
suit at
home is tweeting about
me oh I wonder what she's saying but
yeah so there is not a certain yes yet
but um I was told that yeah could be
possible I will go double check but it
could be very very possible and that
would be really convenient
so basically like we record the live and
then there's like maybe like a free week
uh buffer where it has to be edited
anyway and three weeks should be enough
especially when like we prepare like
backgrounds and all of that beforehand
for the music video to like insert the
motion capture data into the music video
and like finish it up in that time
honestly that should work so that would
be really cool if that works out I'm
kind of counting on that
now I hope I hope we can do that then I
can have high quality motion capture
data I mean honestly with like music
videos you can just like take the good
parts from the motion capture anyway so
even if I do it with like my little bit
um a little bit scuffed uh motion
capture solution at
home you don't have to show the whole
thing so you can just take the good
parts but still like if I can get this
one then we can have more cuts of the
dancing more dance focused music video
and maybe even a fullon like dance shot
too like only dancing no in between cuts
like as a separate version and
stuff so I hope this works
out can't guarantee it but I think it it
should work hopefully
ha
yay that would be sick right yeah so
thank you blackb
M the gamer CR thank you for the pinky
happiest of birthday to the most
sweetest charming and hardworking BP
I've ever had the pleasure to meet on
the side of
interwebs you've been a constant source
of POS positivity for me these four
years and I'm so so happy to have you as
myosi thank you very much appreciated
I'm still your
oi so much time passes and I'm still
your oi that means a lot to me thank you
thank you I hope you will never change
your
mind waa number
one waa number
one thank you so much for the support I
hope I can continue serving
you positivity not anything else
just I'm done I'm done with saying that
one phrase I will just serve you
positivity and and and happiness and all
that not the not the other thing I'm
done with that I'm over that that was a
phase that was a phase a good phase in
my opinion it was a good phase
[Music]
phase end of an
era no more you want some
[Music]
I can't serve right now right here
but I I kind of am like damn it now I'm
saying it after all now I'm saying it
but don't you agree like this outfit I'm
I'm I am serving it it's actually
surprising we haven't mentioned it at
all
yet since I showed this
outfit I do be serving
yeah myo HD D take it monkey for the
rest of Chan happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you happy birthday our cute
boss happy birthday to you even after
all these years and more
responsibilities being piled on me your
streams always make me crack a smile and
be happy so thank you w for happiest
birthdays to you thank you so
[Music]
much thank you for even singing to me
and makes me want to blow out some
candles at the end of
that I didn't I didn't uh get any cake
for waa
birthday so just the ice cream so maybe
when I'm back home I can celebrate my
birthday with my f uh fans with my
friends and we can get some cake and
blow out some candles maybe
maybe M I honestly all I
want is I don't even want a fancy cake I
just there's two cakes from like
Austrian supermarkets or even German
ones um I think that are in the frozen
section that I just love so much I could
eat them every
year one of them is the children cake
from Benjamin blooman the Elephant
mascot the German Elephant
mascot yeah and the other one is um I
don't think did I ever show that one to
you guys there's there's another one
that has like um it's like chocolate
cream and uh like Berry uh jelly
jelly on top like a little bit of a
layer of that and like I think
strella is like somewhere in there um
not sure not sure about that one
Speaking of cakes though yo when I went
to um Baskin Robins in Japan they have
like for this whole month they have a
Mario Super Mario campaign right now and
they have a lot of cool
stuff they have like
they have
the if you just order like ah wait it's
speaking
off I just I was going to forget that
probably but laa still has some love
potion 31 I can't forget about it I have
to eat it after I'm done with the stream
she she offered it to me before the
stream I was like n maybe later she
still has some in her fridge oh my God
oh my God uh but tangent on tangent on
tangent yeah um I was actually saying uh
yeah they have so much cool stuff and if
you order just like one like scoop or so
they will will give you like like a
pretty basic uh Super Mario cup not
special but then they have the parfaits
that are super cute they on the parfet
and they're in a special cup one of the
parfet is like in in a green tube bro so
cute and then they put like you know
little cute things on there like um
Super Mario star and maybe a Cooper
shell whatever it's so cute and then
they have like cakes too right they have
um they have like a a cake that
literally to me looks like a Super Mario
Party map I don't know it's not really
that but it gives me that Vibe because
like every slice they're already sliced
and every slice is like different color
a different character like Peach uh and
like each slice has a mascot on top of
them too so there's a peach slice which
is like pink um yeah and each slice I
guess is a different ice cream cuz it's
ice ice cream cake but then there's also
Luigi's Mansion cake cuz they're they're
really promoting the Luigi's Mansion 2
remake
remake right or remas they're promoting
it a lot
here so they also have a cake for that
yeah and and they have like I think
four
four limited ice cream flavors for this
month for like oh a crony crony
raid oh thank you wow quason raid I
don't quason raid is uh
rare cuz I don't stream at this time I'm
[Music]
normally does that sound like her
probably
[Music]
not
no uh I can't sound like her she sounds
too good like you can't you can't
imitate Perfection after
all thanks for the memberships so yeah
ice cream Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum really
cool I want to go again but I don't
think I'll get another chance to go to
batkin
Robins oh may actually
maybe I'm there I could pass one today
maybe
possibly but I'm also getting Baskin
Robins from R cuz she still has Love
Potion FR one she bought like several
Scoops so there's still some left in her
freezer
I'm surprised like if it was me it was
it would already be gone by now I I
wonder if she didn't like it that
[Music]
much yeah yeah yeah cuz I was
recommending it and talking about it on
my birthday stream and then she got
herself the ice cream that I was
recommending immediately she was serious
about it yeah she's so serious about
it I like that she takes me
seriously I need I need uh Koh eyes
underlings that take me seriously I
appreciate that we're going to get far
we're going to get
[Music]
far I like her she's really amazing
she's really amazing La La's really
amazing she's so talented she's fun
she's motivated she loves whole life I
can see it I can sense it I can feel it
and um yeah she's so interesting she
brings you know a new language also to
the to the
table and she cook at a pasta and and
and she's a sweetheart yeah and she
takes me
serious and she's I feel like she she's
um up for anything too and she's cute
she's
cute apparently she
mentioned uh what I said about her the
moment I met her um cuz I mentioned a
little bit I just said that she smelled
rich but I think she also mentioned on
her stream that I also said she looked
rich like everything about her I don't
know why like I think it's that Italian
vibe that just ah I don't know it gives
me
Gucci it just gives me Gucci she did
really smell good and then she I think
she said that she was just wearing
normal clothes which might be the case
but still like you like it's still kind
of you know I don't know it's hard to
explain why did you smell her so much
because like she smelled really good and
I gave her a hug the moment I saw
her and she smelled so good yeah the way
she carries herself it's her whole aura
it's like her whole
Aura and her accent sounds
Rich the Italian accent when she speaks
English
also yeah also sounds
[Music]
rich I don't know it's so weird I know
it's weird the I don't know what it
is I don't know
Exquisite cute cute cute cute cute cute
C cute cute
cute cute cute cute
cute she didn't smell like pizza
no no she didn't but maybe she'll smell
like pizza
tomorrow okay okay enough yapping let's
go a bit more Super Chat
catchup uh thank you ja monkey again and
Travy thank you for the uh two pinkies
which equals one red thank you so
much happy hatching day wava
but that's inaccurate I I didn't hatch
remember my lure right like it's what
was it two phoenixes rub against each
other like really high speed and create
like heat with the
fiction was that
it and then I just like pop out like
there's no egg involved I
think
yeah yeah that's that's established I've
been telling that for years it's been a
while since I told that though so I kind
of forgot friction not
fiction reminds me of something that
I'll have to tell you about at a later
date don't worry I have it written down
on my phone what I want to tell
you yeah M yeah yeah they WRA together
turn into ashes and then I appear yeah
probably like that so I guess the the
the parents
die maybe that's the one way to get rid
of a
phoenix cuz they die and revive but in
this case if you if a phoenix wants a
baby then they'll have to sacrifice
themselves wow that's beautiful that's
poetic they like
rub can't each other so hard that they
go up in Flames through the heat from
the friction but in order to birth
something new they give up like their
own like you know potential to revive
they use their own Revival power or to
create something completely new but then
two becomes one which means
like yeah that would dwindle their
population
[Music]
right but maybe sometimes there's lucky
cases where they have twins and triplets
or so where it goes back up again I
don't
know that's not sustainable
[Music]
okay that part I just came up with today
so maybe maybe we can't we we will not
lock that one in yet anyway let me
continue you've bur it owl
what you've bured owl before I heard it
all before so you can skip reading this
out loud if you want no four years Ki
how would K crazy how it's flown by so
fast but I'm happy that I could be have
been here to with this it this journey
of our always shining
dorky kindhearted cat obsessed
yes sometimes
cocky hardworking
cute it's hard to say it's hard to say
this word really
super I thought said
Superior Superior blunt and ever
persevering Phoenix I'll keep watching
and support you I can never say it
enough I love you my ooshi and now about
Godzilla minus one and Mass
Effect
[Music]
H
somehow I now own a copy of a Mass
Effect
game I don't know what to do with it
guys I don't know what to do with
it why do I have this
[Music]
bruh no I don't want to blame no no no
no
no no mhm a physical one
yeah I forgot what console it was but
probably
PlayStation um pretty please
[Music]
no but anyway I don't know why you guys
always want me to play Mass Effect you
guys are just like trying to to like
Bully me because of my
mom
stop uh but yeah thank you thank you
Trevor G it's so nice to read your your
bird puns again it sounds like you're
back to like your
usual
usual what's what's what's the word
I feel like you're just back to usual
like you seem you seem like re re
rekindled your flame has rekindled I can
I can sense it I'm happy about
that I mean maybe I'm wrong but that's
how it seems to
[Music]
me thank you so much thank you thank you
Trevy but next time don't don't forget
about the how I Was Made I have not been
hatched I hatch you guys but the other
way around no no no no no I am the
Hatcher but not the hatched thank you m
Baron man dang my name is stion for the
pinky you must have been born to be one
of a kind when the planets and stars
were completely aligned no no when the
two phoenixes were completely aligned
when the world needed someone exactly
like you to do all the wonderful things
that you do you descended upon us and
made our hearts
full oh wait I see what's
happening wait
look it's
um yeah four four
different versions of
[Music]
himself With Arms Wide Open you made
this our home you sing You Dance you
make us so proud wait that that doesn't
rhyme what happened you laugh and you
tease and you make us cheer loud oh okay
loud with proud what's with home we do
all we can to follow along with crossr
oceans just to hear your song you're
easy to be with and fun just to know to
H you love you leave people smiling
wherever you go and the best gift of all
which sets you apart is the love that
you share from your beautiful heart
happiest birthday Wawa thank you for
being you
thank you for the pinkies that's
actually beautiful did you come up with
that
yourself oh there some nice
Rhymes beautiful choice of
words very poetic # philosophical
Phoenix yeah yeah straight out of the
heart and straight into my heart thank
you so
much I appreciate it thank you soon
oh three different PE four different
people no wait it's three different
people oh these two are the same these
two are the same actually these
[Music]
two could could you not have come up
with one
more thank you do thank you so much for
the
support thank you for celebrating with
me again kakan thank
you for the pinky oh in English happy
birthday T to I have to stay up late
these days so I participate in the chat
less often it you
mean
ah you staying up late normally makes my
streams like fine to watch but now that
I'm in Japan they're actually like more
difficult to watch huh I'm still
supporting you as always I love you
constant positivity and fortitude keep
up the good work
[Music]
wow nice
English good
job ah thank you so much yeah it might
be hard to adjust s guys but I don't
know how things are going to be when I'm
like in terms of time zones when I'm
here in
um uh August cuz I will stream more than
like now but
in terms of time zones I
mean
I I I don't think I can really do my
usual times because then I would start
like streaming I don't know
midnight and stream all the way to like
7 a.m. jst or so
that's no that's not going to work out
sorry guys but sometimes
uh when I do like long art jpg streams I
would start at
like what what would it be like 1000
p.m. jst so sometimes I think I'll be
streaming around that time too just not
like the long jrpg streams I'm not going
to start them at 10 p.m. jst when I'm in
J
[Music]
jst but there will be some familiar
overlap in times here and there I think
yeah
yeah and maybe I used to do that but
uhuh I'm not going to do that
now cuz I'm going I I say I have more
time to stream next time that's just
because I'm there for a longer time and
like several reasons and projects why uh
I need to be in Japan I like combined so
um I I I figured instead of flying there
every week and flying back after a few
days and flying there again after a few
days I should just stay the whole one
and a half months or so um where was I
going with this
[Music]
statement
uh yeah yeah just because I'm like more
capable of
streaming because things are more like
stretched out like stretched no
scattered throughout the month one and a
half months doesn't mean that I have
like endless free time I still have to
do some things so
I can't do like a
crazy uh time schedule where I stream
after
midnight also I don't know if that would
be okay like for like you know you know
how Finn walls are in Japan and I don't
want to like force myself to be
whispering in my streams so if I stream
past
midnight that should generally be
generally be uh avoided
[Music]
but yeah thank you
kakam yeah I I'll be back soon to
Austria to the usual streaming times but
not for long not for long and next week
as I told you guys before I can't stream
much next week either um so that's that
no but we're trying our
best m thanks
thank Sky thanks for the Super Chat
happy birthday my Kam o I hope you have
a wonderful birthday party and all you
want can be achieved very soon thank you
we're achieving a lot currently and
things are going quite
nicely my birthday my birthday you know
everything felt kind of rushed and
sudden
and but um I hope you guys had fun I
think that k it really turned out really
nicely and it was really fun uh I think
that was the best thing I could have
done in that situation where my birthday
life is
delayed Koke was really nice and it was
hype too felt really hyped to me I was
hyped
[Music]
up and we saw some fun combinations and
the the the song Choices were really
good too considering that it was
an archived
C good set list right I
agree I
[Music]
agree yeah the guests were super into it
too
yeah okay next Juan Carlos rodrig
Rodriguez thank you for the pinky happy
birthday to my beloved Phoenix oie
you're the best and we love you please
never forget that thank you and love you
guys too I have been missing you guys
but I've been doing quite a few Twitter
spaces I hope you guys are able to
listen into them even though they're
pretty
spontaneous oh thanks for the members
message yeah have you guys been able to
tune in to the Twitter spaces
yeah they're recorded so you can also
listen back into them
later yeah you caught
one yeah yeah not really
yeah I caught up on them last night ooh
[Music]
nice yeah hearing narissa a nice
bonus that worked pretty well like
collabing through a Twitter space
surprisingly well anyway thank you so
much for the pinky and your support your
profile picture looks so funny
Hanan Carlos Rodriguez thank you and
James Jackson
D please put this toward hiring a new
text I will I actually will oh um it's
time
for it's time for a tangent because you
remind me of it I needed to tell you
guys what happened
and in the
end it's I I completely will admit that
to an extent it's my fault I just
expected more support from um my tax uh
lady I really thought maybe this is just
how tax people work maybe there's some
that are less um like supportive so to
say and some that are more like involved
and like check up on you but I kind of
felt a little bit over this
time and it's not like the first time
where she kind of loses track of of
like my things and uh yeah so I don't
know if this is normal but so basically
I had to pay my taxes right and she
sends me the the slip the from the
finance department whatever uh and tells
me yeah you have to pay so much uh until
this point of time which was like uh a
month later or so and when I first saw
that like obviously if you get
something I mean some people do things
right away but other people don't okay
and I thought okay there's still so much
time I'm not going to pay this
immediately so okay obviously I forgot
but uh she only messaged me about that
several days past the deadline um like I
would have appreciated if she would have
told me one day before the deadline or
so even on the deadline to pay my taxes
like remind me but I guess that they
don't do that okay okay so um she tells
me hey now you have to pay this amount
extra because of the
delay um but I wonder with the delay if
there's like a like if it Stacks up
depending on how fast you pay it I don't
know um because I feel like I got
notified of it pretty late too but she
tells
me um she gives me a deadline to
pay and and I kind of misunderstood the
deadline she gave me was like 2 weeks
later or
so and then I was like okay I also don't
have to pay this right away and I think
it was busy you know so I took my time
to pay that too but I thought it meant
that you know the deadline for paying
the taxes got extended to be like paid
in combination with the theay
payment you know what I mean the
fine um because I don't know that that's
like in in in whole life it's also like
they give us a new deadline and then it
means just like submit all that in the
new deadline I don't
know so I didn't pay that right away you
know and but I paid it before that new
deadline she gave
me um
but then a few days later she writes to
me
like
uh okay now you are being what was the
word um it was a weird word in English
that I thought I didn't I didn't know it
had that usage
fendon um in German fendon audited no
not
audited um
it wasn't all
[Music]
wait
seizure there was a like apparently
there was an attempt of seizure and I
don't even know how that would have
worked cuz I wouldn't I wasn't even at
home and when I think of seizure that
sounds like someone comes to your home
and takes your
furniture I don't know how that yeah
they tried to seize something
I don't know how but um then I was like
she she said that that happened and that
I'm now being fined extra again for like
being laid even more on the original
payment and for the attempt of
seizure
yeah it's not tax evasion
bro but nothing got like physical
physically seized and so basically she
gave me this new deadline and I thought
that was for the the general taxes too
right so I I waited even more time while
apparently that was not okay and so they
tried to they they gave me an even
bigger fine and blah blah blah I paid a
lot
extra
so it it was kind of up so I
wrote to her like to explain myself like
well okay I think I misunderstood
because the way you phrased it it to me
sounded like I can pay uh the the fine
the delay fine in combination with the
taxes until this point of time so I'm
sorry but yeah that this is really
shocking to me that now I'm getting a
seizure notice like what the and
then she's
like like no that's not what I said at
all you have to pay this I'm like okay
now you're giving me an attitude for the
first time so that pisses me off like
I'm not saying no I'm not saying that
she uh like did anything particularly
wrong but like she could have notified
me of all of these things
earlier if she was like more attentive
to me I need a tax person that's more
attentive to me bro I need someone who's
on top of these things like you don't
have to remind me every day but
if you give me a notice to pay something
one month in advance maybe check if I
already paid cuz like she has access to
it and she does check these things she
does go into my account and stuff my my
finance uh office account and all that
and so like it would have been nice if
she would have especially after I'm
already
late if she could like you know when we
already know I'm late and follow up like
her follow up after my delay until the
seizure was also really late and the
notification of the SE seizure that she
gave me cuz it goes to her not to me
that was also really late like I didn't
know this was happening until like days
later so I'm just like you know I I
understand that like this is like I'm
late so it's my fault and all that but
like I just wish she was more on top of
it so now I'm actually going to switch
because we're just not we're just not a
match no no no no no no no it's this is
not the only thing this is not the only
thing you guys have been like now you
guys are like e you need an assistant
then but you guys have been criticizing
my tax lady before as
[Music]
well what was all the money you prepaid
last year about
uh no last year last year I was paying
for 2022 and 2023 I
think so I already paid I think
everything for 2023
and but we haven't finished the
whole paperwork for that and now I'm
paying 2024 but like in uh four parts
four times a year I pay a prepayment and
then afterwards they're going to like
recalculate it I
[Music]
guess well sorry when I get a
email
when I'm in bed or when I'm
outside that tells me to pay like
amount of
money I'm not going to do it immediately
when I can't get to it immediately and
then I forget that's a natural thing I'm
not the only one don't criticize me for
that that's just how humans
work and I'm really like when it comes
to like whole life work I'm I'm like
overloaded with work right now but
generally I am I'm on top of things you
know I put everything in my calendar I
follow up on
everything um I I'm I'm really trying my
best to stay on top of things but uh I
do have problems staying on top of
things in my real life like that's
definitely
taking like it's it's it's um taking a
hit from how much I'm on top of things
in whole life makes my real life things
suffer
[Music]
basically oh shut up you guys annoy me
now with criticizing that man now I will
just read super chats then I'm not going
to talk about it anymore blah blah
[Music]
blah FR for the pinky happy birthday T
ki our powerful always hardworking
Phoenix thank you for always being being
the way you are funny incredible
talented and just a wonderful Phoenix
will always be cheering for you and we
always believe in you happy birthday
thank you
Dr I've been working hard I've been
working my ass off thank you for
acknowledging that fro fro I wonder how
you feel about having a an Italian in
whole life
now do you like it she's she's one of
your
people she's one of
you she's I hope she does like a full
Italian stream one
[Music]
day maybe she makes an Italian sub
Channel who
knows and then and then just leaves it
hanging for
years forgets about
it that be so funny
actually if she streams twice on it and
then just never goes there
again that'll be so
[Music]
funny I want that to
happen thank you for for the pinky and
the support for being here for another
birthday for me Don for celebrating with
me
thanks for the red super
chat happy birthday to you thank
you thank you for being so
generous H thanks for the pinky happy
birthday
[Music]
K
won n
I we
[Music]
uh I can't read Korean
today huh what does this
say
h Huh oh can you even oh there it
is I was busy this year uh so I couldn't
do anything but next year I will
celebrate your birthday in a big way
what do you mean you don't have to do
anything just you being in my stream is
all I need thank
you thank you so much you guys know what
this
says yeah my oie
ah does it say it in Korean or is it one
of those cases where it's like Japanese
written out
Korean I think it's not I would have
recognized that I think
come thank you thank you yeah no need to
throw some party or
whatever I'm just happy having you guys
in my birthday stream and maybe if you
buy my merchandise my birthday
merchandise that would
be
nice
this El can thank you for the right Chad
happy birthday waa how many years
already I have nothing but grateful
words for you uh for making my day so
much happier after work
please please continue doing your best
being the cutest Phoenix in town and
remember kfb Loves You Forever PS your
Spanish is the cutest my
Spanish when did I speak Spanish
recently I'm trying to speak like uh
more like I'm trying to remember Italian
words that I've learned
[Music]
but then sometimes it when I want to say
certain things it like mixes up with
Spanish even though I know Spanish less
than I know Italian I think but you guys
throw Spanish around every now and then
here and there so like per
and
or like me am more and me more or I
don't know it's like which one was which
one
which one was
which that is like so
confusing por is Spanish okay then per
is
Italian and then T and T I'm like uh I
think T is
Italian
yeah and then uh Kista
and weren't those two similar too
Kai uh
[Music]
ah yo they're so similar
it's it's messing with my brain but
when we went to eat I think okay I think
now I can say because M tweeted the
Japanese
flag um she basically said wait until I
tweet something um but we had dinner
with uh M narissa bi boo
uh Shi LA and
me the six of us and that was
fun and then I was sitting in front of
Raa the whole time um like on the side
on the edge of the table and we 90% of
the time we were having a different
conversation because I was just so
excited to ask L questions I think the
other girls already had some more time
to talk with
l at least most them um and already met
her like Nissa met her before like on a
different date and all that I
think so I was just like super excited
to uh talk a lot of without and I asked
a million questions so we had our own
conversation most of the time and then
and then the moment I sat down I was
because everything was to Italian I was
like and fora and Echo ech love I don't
freaking know yeah I was I was so
proudly saying it to and then the the
waiter also heard it who the waiter was
also Italian
so I was
praised yeah I felt so
proud the pizza
pizza but I need to I I know more
there's I I feel it it's like in the
back of my brain I just need to like um
just dig it out again again
D both Romans languages so they're
sometimes similar yeah yeah yeah yeah
they have so many similarities it's
throwing me off
molto toti toti toti see I just
remembered that word out of nowhere to B
I
[Music]
think uh uh but like the fact that my
Italian was like Hotel
focused um meant also that it's it has
like a lot of restaurant terms so it
helped me like I I don't know how to say
fora fork and knife in like Korean for
example I don't know how to say that in
Korean but maybe they just say like
maybe they say English words just like
in Japanese but yeah the fact that I
know how to say it in in Italian I feel
like that's like next
level that's so a little bit nichy like
normally I don't think you would learn
that so early on like I'm on a huge
beginner's level of Italian but since
it's focused on one specific Direction I
know some words that you would normally
not know On My Level but then I'm also
missing a lot of other
words oh you will be lurking as you
drive home drive safely
please I hear
birds the birds are so loud is the
window
[Music]
open you guys hear the birds I hope I
hope the birds are not going to dox
me they're chirping really loudly what
the hell L go go attack them eat them
sorry boss b
b okay okay okay I what what was I even
talking about yeah Italian yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah anyway we had a good
dinner blah blah blah back to Super
chats thanks for the red super chat no
wait that's what I just read you're
saying my Spanish is the cutest is what
led me to that thank you so much for
your sweet message and your support my
Spanish I I wanted to learned Spanish
one time but now thata is in whole life
I feel like I'm really motivated to fix
my broken Italian so I'm going to work
on that sorry Spanish sorry Spanish or
vanish is what dualingo says
but well I guess I'll vanish guess I'll
die can I Italian
or what's the Italian equivalent italan
wait m
if it's Spanish or vanish what what
would Italian be Italian
[Music]
or something that rhymes with
Italian Italian
or
uh uh no it has a rhyme
stallion what the isn't that a
[Music]
horse uh
it it it's not that there has to be
something
better Medallion o
Italian
Italian can
you how that's a good word but like I
don't know how to use that
Oblivion it's
not that's like similar to like vanish
right like sending you to Oblivion but
don't know how to implement that
whatever whatever whatever I need to
read some chats I don't have time for
this right I don't have time for this
face the
Battalion that
works that
[Music]
works than for Pinky GNA send a proper
happy birthday later but I just heard
about the tax lady L rip Bozo what does
Bo is that a I mean I've seen that word
before but I don't even know what it
means I think you won't be
missed yeah I I I asked
my uh financial adviser if he has a
recommendation so I'm probably going to
go with the recommendation and then like
ask how we can make the switch how that
works oh like a a clown aha
it was the name of a clown
oh Jack for the pinky happy birthday
wa you're my no our son as a result of
you coming to Japan is probably hotter
than
[Music]
usual like the moment when I step
outside I'm not like immediately like oh
it just it takes a little bit of
time I think in August it will like be
the worst and it will be like the moment
I step outside it will hit me like a
brick but yeah it is definitely very hot
and I'm sweaty spaghetti just by
walking uh like for 10
[Music]
m I'm like so normally I don't shower
every day but when I'm in Japan I shower
every day I don't wash my hair every day
necessarily cuz my hair doesn't like
being washed every day but I shower
every day because I'm sweaty spaghetti
every day Mama
Mia it's
[Music]
disgusting for
Moonlight thank you for the
rainbow thank you so much from the
bottom of my chimpin heart I want to
wish you a very happy birthday K I hope
you have an amazing day because you
truly deserve it you are the son of kfp
the son I am your child kfp I am the s o
n the son of you
you are my father and my
[Music]
mother I am your
baby praise the
son no it's there's no typo here I'm
just like I don't
know I want to be your
son H your light allows our eyes to see
the beauty of this world and that's
quite something you make this reality
better and I truly hope you'll never
forget that and if by any chance you do
we'll be here to remind you of how much
you mean to us the shower of Love you'll
get today is proof of that I'm sure I
can't imagine a timeline where I'm not a
kfp I don't know how empty my life would
feel if I don't know about those screams
every time Panic Jo enters the scene for
the most little
thing without that laugh of yours or
your smug he when you do something cool
I don't know if I wanted to create a
more perfect ocean I will just end up
cloning you because there's no one else
I'd rather s for # woke # Yol sorry for
being a little selfish but since it's my
birthday too I'd like to ask for a
certain birthday gift if it's possible
not a race you please sing happy B in
your
shoe happy
birthday to you happy BB in your shoe
happy BB in your pants too happy
birthday to you that's not exactly how I
sang it
usually normally sing sing I think uh
happy birthday to you happy birthday in
your shoe Havey birth in your pants not
B that confused me now there's M account
name in the chat hey
yo sorry that a that's a rare
sight
w
o sorry get distracted
well well well well thank you doing one
night happy birth to you and happy birth
in your pants too
cursed cursed version of a birthday
[Music]
song Thank you so much for your support
very very very sweet of you I hope what
you say will forever be true than m
Jim Tracy thanks for chat happy birthday
K you always work so hard and put your
heart into everything you do truly
caring for your fans and making our days
brighter I'm proud to call you my OSI
thank you for always being you Boss I
hope this is the best birth happiest
birthday ever happiest birthday ever
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you I think it was a great
birthday thank you so much for your love
for being there on my special day once
again as always you're always there
thank you Jim
Tracy yeah than soon I'll continue
working hard and putting my heart into
everything thank you for acknowledging
[Music]
that R thanks for the pinky happy
birthday to the most wonderful
passionate full of love and caring
potential in the whole entire universe I
wish nothing but the best for you the
opportunities and success the happiness
and love you deserve the most love you
always W thank you thank you so much I'm
getting so many opportunities this year
so I think your wishes have come true
did you use a Genie bottle or what how
did you make that happen it's kind of
crazy I'm I'm kind of like getting
spoiled this year in
Opportunities M so much
that uh kind of crazy right now for
Preparation but it'll be worth it it'll
be so worth
it I don't know like if I'll ever be
this blessed again in
opportunities but I'm going to treat
this like it's the last time that I'll
be so blessed cuz you know I talked
about this before basically the more
members join the more the the the pool
of like
like members to choose from for these
kind of projects the bigger the pool
will be obviously so the lower the
chances will be so thank God I you know
got a chance
now yeah got to make the most of it got
to make the most of it so you guys if
you can please go check out the world
tour
go uh carry your legs to The Venue as
they like to say in Japanese
carry your
legs my froat I need a froat candy or
some tea actually it would be
good Fro I'm drinking water but
[Music]
like but I I'll be fine because this not
going to be too long in the end I still
have some things to do and I want to
maybe get a massage afterwards
I haven't even booked it yet but I'm
hoping I can book relatively
spontaneously bu through the wall with a
giant jug of tea who knows if she's like
JMA in that
regard I don't know if she's still
listening she might not
be it's okay it's okay I'll survive with
the
water get that massage I want to oh can
I tell you another thing
[Music]
I my flight to
Japan it it was free I didn't have to
pay for it and uh uh it was premium
economy and uh I was did I tell you I
was in the middle seat I think I
told you right in the Twitter space I
think I told you cuz there's the the
four middle seats right usually there's
like the window seat and then seat next
to the window window then there's the
aisle and then there's four window seats
I sat in the middle of the middle not
even on the middle of the like not even
on the aisle of the middle and the
premium economy this one was pretty BL
so I really was so uncomfortable my body
was in pain and the it just felt so long
but I thought like now my body condition
is even worse than when I came
here and I'm not paying for this flight
so I was wondering maybe
maybe this time I could consider putting
an upgrade bet
again cuz I don't want to like if I at
least had a window seat man but yeah so
I I checked out if it was possible
because if I put an upgrade B bet bid
that's all I'll be paying for so then I
think it's relatively
reasonable cuz previously if I have to
pay for the whole flight and the upgrade
then no then I don't think it's worth it
but in this this case I thought it might
be worth it so I put in a bet and it
already got
accepted so I think it's fine I put the
minimum bet bid bid in uh which like
700 but that's all I'm paying for
that's less than the trip to Japan would
be even an economy class if I paid the
trip myself
so yeah I think it's fine if I think
it's fine yeah for business class then
they don't even have first class so it's
just you know business class I think
it's fine because the the back flight is
even longer than the flight to Japan and
when I saw the hours I was like Mama Mia
Mama Mia I can't do this I have so much
like sore muscles and and I'm
stressed so I just want to sleep you
know I just want to be able to cheap to
cheap to
sleep yeah it is cheap like if you
consider not paying anything else
if you if you consider it on top of
everything else then maybe but I I
didn't pay the flight so I think it's a
good deal what a
deal what a deal I'm excited
woohoo I'm excited to lay down
[Music]
flat yay we take those yeah I'm paying
to sleep exactly I'm paying to
sleep the workout outfit is so good
thank you I know
thank
you what no they've always like been
paying trips where they where they need
me like if I when I record my 3D
Live um like last time for example in
November was it I paid that myself
because it was my own
project but if it's like well right now
I'm not here for my own things I'm here
for
projects that I am being basically asked
to participate in so
yeah yeah and then I am I am smartly
combining like for my next birthday live
recording uh 3D Live recording um I
would have to pay for it on my own but
I'm like extending my trip for like
another trip that is already being paid
and and I'm extending that you know they
already pay for the flly you
know that's why like you know I'm
staying longer until everything's
done but the next trip is also like
several
things so if I flew home each time they
would pay for each flight each time
thankfully I'm actually saving the money
by staying and not going back home each
time I'm saving them money
stons m
Savvy Savvy business
boob yeah I'm saving them money and I'm
saving me sity yeah cuz those
flights back and forth back and forth I
can't it's too much right
now so yeah at least this time I'm
upgrading I don't know if I'll do it
with the other flights but this one
flight I really felt like I have to
upgrade myself because
it's I'm
dying no
yay
Yahoo
[Music]
Yahoo why not move Studio to Austria
well you know I at least have my own
motion capture solution at home that is
relatively
decent not not perfect but decent for
you know I can at least make music
videos and stuff but that's so we have
we have already made improvements in
what what uh when it comes to that
[Music]
that uh where was I uh I think red Super
Chat thank you thank you thank you Mr V
dun Psy dun SLO of Shadows thank you for
the pinky and never year this must mean
we've completed another revolution
around you
Revolution you are the bright and
beautiful sun that all your fans orbit
around who warms us with your here happy
birthday have a lovely day surrounded by
your friends and
happiness okay I was not really
surrounded by
friends uh but still I mean they were
virtually there in the Kadoka stream at
[Music]
least yeah no was a good time was a good
time we'll do it again 10 out of 10 10
out of
[Music]
10 uh what you call that Revolution tion
when the earth goes around the
[Music]
sun when I had to think for a moment I'm
not going to say what I was thinking
about you call it Revolution oh I didn't
know that I just thought about you know
like yeah we our
[Music]
Revolution
uhhuh ah ah they do say like not
everything revolves around you which is
kind of
like a reference to everything revolving
re really wait do they now it sounds it
sounds weird to me cuz I have to think
of
revolvers English is
[Music]
confusing RPM now when now I'm guessing
it sounds for revolutions per
minute or per month I don't
know
per per month or per
minute ah R are cold up because they
spin the chamber cuz they have spinny
bits ah
W confusing
[Music]
T how fast the wheel spins
ahuh Oh I thought it was about the the
solar system
huh how many art revolutions per month
does the Earth you know for example that
too okay well whatever I don't like this
topic it's
[Music]
boring uh you
yeah okay I read it thank you SLO of
Shadows thank very much for your support
and for re re revolting about around me
I guess Revolution revolting re reving
re
rol
re H who knows what the verb is
revolving there it
is
revolting revolving around
me
[Music]
God for the red this is really up
high red thank you keep being happy
birthday K and keeping the lovable you
and looking forward to another year
reviewing k kfp
k hey thank you thanks mate thank you my
my sweetest GD my beloved GD thank you
so much you
are I want to pinch your cheeks
G thank you for your
love
D my sweet Australian
Friend studio ring for the
pinky birthday
[Music]
qu I did get to eat the
quas um it was mid I like the original
more it was like too much I don't
[Music]
know h no giant I really dreamt of like
giant quasons stacked upon each other I
don't know what that was
about but yeah it was made but but it
worked like um freeezing it and then
warming it up again in the in a toaster
oven that's like in Japan they usually
don't have like a big
oven normally even even in relatively
decent
kitchens in Japan they mostly just have
like a small thin toaster
oven which is crazy to me I mean they're
convenient if you have a small tiny
kitchen um they can do a lot of
things but but if you have like a bigger
kitchen then it confuses me Japanese
kitchens they they rarely have a
dishwasher and I don't think I've ever
seen like a western style proper oven
that is like connected with the um the
plates on
top it's just I don't know it's just not
a thing I
guess h
no like Ci has a really nice kitchen I
think like for a Japanese Kitchen but uh
she also doesn't have anything but a
toaster oven I
[Music]
think I've never seen a dishwasher in my
country either see dishwashers I'm so
glad they're they're pretty standard in
Austria and Germany and so on I mean
I've lived in apartments like really
cheap ones that did not have a
dishwasher to
um
but yeah once if you get one with like a
like if it's not a too cheap one just
even mid mid Apartments you usually have
a
dishwasher so not always but
usually now I had to get my own kitchen
so I got myself a dishwasher
obviously but yeah thank God I remember
the times when I had to to wash my
dishes
[Music]
that but I mean you're obviously like
saving money I guess and I mean if if
you don't need a dishwasher good for
you I would get sick of it I would get
sick of
it yeah it's too tedious way too tedious
I'm too lazy for it but I I I always
make sure that like before I put my
dishes into the dishwasher that they're
like properly like scraped off and
everything even like from the cat food
plates the little bowls and like the T
tiny tiny remains I scrape it all off
yeah cuz I don't want my dishwasher to
get up too much and you know who
you know who taught me that behavior my
mom and yet when she's in my kitchen I
see that she does not like so so
properly clean of the remains of the
plates like I do that more than she does
now like she just puts the the cat food
bowls right in there when there's still
like quite a few dried up remains
there even though I learned it from
her actual dishwashers work better if
there's a bit of food on it
what N I can't believe it no no
no better to get it all like
[Music]
gone it's only a problem if they're
fullly but it's like little bits of food
like
no no that doesn't sound right to me
fake news superstitious yeah yeah all
right let's fight those weird Believers
of food remains in the dishwasher ew it
gets stinky and it gets accumulated
stinky and I think you'll end up having
to like clean your dishwasher more
often oh yeah I mean oily residue I'm
I'm sure a lot of my plates will have
like some oily residue or whatever but
like not like actual touchable physical
food still on there that would be
[Music]
crazy anyway what is this topic again
what the
dishwasher topic it's my fault I
don't know why I'm going there I don't
know
why it's because I talked about the
qu qu we're kind of
mid
but yeah it was a nice experiment it's
just you know for my own satisfaction I
felt really salty about missing out on
so many time limited
[Music]
things y thank you for the pinky happy
birthday to my Kam o you have blessed
our lives of your beautiful smile for
another year I wish you even more
exciting events and wonderful adventures
I love you Ki thank you you know I
personally this is so random but I
personally feel
like for
vtubers like in a I feel like in a way
our birthday should be our debut day cuz
isn't that when we're really
born to me that's for virtual YouTubers
especially I feel like that's when we're
really born so anniversary really equals
birthday to
me yeah cuz for you we didn't really and
for me also we didn't really exist
before that
so but I mean it gives to have both
anniversary and birthday at separate
occasions gives us all more merch to buy
and sell
so it's like you know like Christmas uh
being all about like um you
know what's the
word
[Laughter]
money then it overlaps with your G
that's why it should just not be like
the way myth was debuted Mama
Mia to this day I really
wonder why we had to debut like that
only people will will understand who
were there at the time nowadays they're
doing it better a little bit
although
yeah yeah no yeah
better I like how I
think I think I like how did ID do one
person per
day so generally I think that's that's
how Japanese gens do it like that right
so I think that's the best just one per
day like I understand you wanting to
pack it all into a
weekend
but yeah myth was like a marathon even
there was only like we it was five of us
following each other through the night
the jst night there was only like a
maybe two or three hour time window in
between uh where there were no debuts
but generally it was a marathon back to
back
Council was also like that yeah that
that's because for Council it was still
kind of the same management and then
after that you know things were changing
and then we were yeah improving such
[Music]
things yeah it was like for us it was
exhausting and I think for the audience
too it was
exhausting yeah I remember I was so
sleep deprived I wanted to sleep because
ah the whole Marathon Was Then followed
up with the collab too after
all and then I followed it up with my
first solo stream right which
was was it egg the egg
game no F yeah
F and I was really
not not um not my best that was not my
best the
uh
[Music]
yeah I didn't I didn't
sleep cuz I was I was second but I
couldn't sleep for the others debus I
needed to watch all of that and I was
like excited and G
[Music]
so hi The Fall Guys stream I was so bad
I was so bad I mean I'm still bad but
that was a different kind of
bad yeah I was in Japan at the time when
I debuted in Hall life I was in Japan I
was like uh in the middle of a onee
working holiday uh visa and yeah it was
literally in the middle like halfway
through I debuted in whole life and then
so the first six months approximately of
me and whole alive were while I was in
Japan and then I moved to Austria
back to Austria cuz my Visa ran out and
I mean even even if there was a chance
of extending it for the company um which
nowadays is like much more U easy like
they help more with that kind of stuff
then back in the day it was it didn't
even seem so easy to do back in the day
um but I didn't even want to do it cuz I
was homesick as and I wanted to go
to my cats and all that
[Music]
yeah yeah everything is way more set up
now so if if you join whole life English
and you want to move to Japan it's like
easy now pretty easy
now it didn't seem like such an easy
option back when when I uh was
considering it I was lowkey considering
it
but
yeah yeah yeah yeah nostalgic times
[Music]
yeah if I wasn't so homesick maybe I
would have done it but yeah you know I
was I was stuck in Japan for the whole
year because of the corona I couldn't go
home I was planning on going home
several times in that one year and then
I couldn't go a single time so when I
say homesick I mean cat
sick for real and like the first half
year of that um stay really took a toll
on me because the first half year I was
just depressed that I'm wasting
my once in A- lifetime
Visa just
like in
bed cuz of Corona starting the moment I
enter Japan Corona starts and all the
things I wanted to do just were not
possible and I missed my cats and I felt
bad that I couldn't go back to them and
see them and and I just had nothing to
do and I was just wasting my time and
wasting
away and then I found her alive and I
auditioned for it and that definitely
improved my whole situation by
far and I don't even remember this but
you guys tell me that I was not doing
well back then right I don't even
remember that it's been too long but you
guys remind me that I I was just not
doing
well and I I really blossomed after I
left Japan well I guess because I also
okay I was like I finally had something
to do right and it was successful and
fun but I had other problems like insane
Tech problems and then
insane hate problems like you know as as
a huge huge like craziness in the
beginning uh yeah and then the yeah
moving places and then not being able to
live there right away because no
internet and then having to to stream
from elsewhere in manager place but yeah
know that that was good though like
obviously I'm very thankful for that and
it um she wasn't even my manager yet at
the time but that led uh everything into
me switching managers because JMA was
there for me um when my other manager
wasn't just going to see how it is that
that person is not uh a manager anymore
anyway so
yeah thank God for jenma for saving me
but yeah there was so much going on
then so the the full year I was just not
doing
well and then when I came to to Austria
things were you know being surrounded by
friends again and by my cats and having
family
[Music]
around I'm I I've lived in Japan before
you know so for me that really was just
like I've I've achieved like my weep
dreams of living in Japan and and doing
all the wee things there I've done that
plenty of times and I for me for me that
was already before I even joined whole
alive that one year for me was the
original purpose was to just close a
chapter but then I felt like I couldn't
close the chapter because I couldn't do
anything that I wanted to do in order to
close the chapter and then a new chapter
opens that was very connected with
Japan and now I'm like hm well if I
lived in Japan
I it obviously would be good for this
job but I need to think of myself I need
to put myself first my mental health and
you know just make life choices that are
smart for
myself and I think the choices I made
were the right
choices yeah see I'm I'm still like in
Japan every now and then like several
times a year so I can always come here
and do the work things and meet with
people like how how often like if I even
lived in Japan now like who knows how
often I would actually meet with all
these like Japanese Senpai and so on
like cuz maybe I'm not missing out on
that many bonding
opportunities that we might think I'm
missing out on because I'm here a lot
and when I'm here I do meet with some of
them so in the end probably not even
missing out that much on bonding
experiences
[Music]
yeah yeah cuz when I'm when I'm here I'm
actually like trying my best to meet up
with people and it's all focused in like
one short amount of time perhaps but
it's happening what happening I'm
yapping yapping yapping yapping yapping
yapping yapping I should not not Yap
that tangent went really far yeah we
went I I I'm like thinking you know some
some newer viewers might appreciate a
tangent like this not knowing how it was
back in the
day you might you might appreciate me
telling you about these
[Music]
things m
yeah yeah I I do I do think I observed
that
to that the en members or so that live
in Japan uh don't necessarily like meet
up a lot with Japanese members either
so doesn't equal like living in Japan
doesn't equal meeting everyone every day
so
so especially because you live in Japan
you probably take it easy and you're
like oh yeah can meet them anytime
now but yeah okay enough of this yappity
tangent enough of
that um back to topic where was
I uh ah yeah okay I read your call thank
you so much I think I was yapping thanks
to your Super Chat probably thank
you uh Nathan C than pinky hi atten
happy birthday I know it means a lot of
work for you but I'm so excited to see
my Kam oi getting so many or was it this
one so many performances this year or
maybe it was this one that I
read what with the H Ian concert and
following
tour did I read this
I didn't okay oh makes me very proud
chimpin good luck thank
you you're going to you're going to be
somewhere like at the concert and the
tour as
well did you think you're going to
both Nathan that would be
amazing yeah I I did see so many of you
guys got so
lucky Yahoo I'm
excited yeah it's getting closer and
closer yabby
yum soon
TM yeah thank you for the good luck I
will need
it and thank you for wishing me happy
birthday sweet Nathan D very much
appreciated uh yeah let's have a good
time no it's not even louder setup it's
the same mic that I have and it's the
golr that I used to use and it's the
default settings from the G I didn't
tweak
anything it's all on normal but same mic
as I have yeah you you freaking goxlr
haters say do I have permission now to
go back to the go
huh the room yeah the room is like
smaller and seems
[Music]
more yeah it definitely seems like the
uh audio is not like bouncing around as
much as in my
place
no I might just switch it out without
telling you I want to go back to
goxlr screw you I'm going to do what I
[Music]
want think of the soundboard I can make
my own soundboard I can make a
soundboard with um what's it called
the uh stream not stream deck Steam deck
stream de stream deck why are they so
[Music]
similar I'm not part of your
syst going to throw on the
[Music]
ground I can make an even better
soundboard
exactly I I have a stream deck but I
gave it to a friend cuz I didn't use it
I didn't know how to use it I didn't
really know all the things you can do
with it blah blah blah blah blah space
wonderful D for the red chat happy
birthday V I hope you make and continue
to make tons of great memories and to be
nostalgic about later funny because
that's Lally what we just did being
nostalgic about earlier earlier
things and I wish you good luck and much
success in everything and good health
always for you and your cats you're the
best thank you who you my
cats why' you have to imtion my cats i'
I've been like looking at my security
camera to get some Peaks and glances at
my
cats I saw I saw smoovie like uh chasing
some kind of bug or something like
jumping up and running running around
and like trying to catch
it um and then and then I saw I tweeted
about this but
like I was actually I was just like um I
was talking to M and like showing her uh
I was like hey do you want to see my
security camera so cool so I pull it up
on my phone and then the moment I pull
it up I see like smoothie sitting
outside alone and like I'm like what why
is she this is weird something feels off
about this
like can she get back inside are the do
closed
to and I get like kind of suspicious
about it m and then I I turn on there's
like a microphone I can speak
through and I push it and I speak and
smoothie comes over to the camera and
looks up and like whoa and and M was
like whoo wao that's crazy that's crazy
because she was really surprised that my
cat reacted like that yeah yeah she was
suddenly she was like a yo my cat was
like a yo what the yeah and she
looks up with her with her wow Bright
Eyes she's like what the where is
this coming from and then and then I I
messaged RBF like hey is uh smoothie out
there like stuck or can she get back in
are is this on purpose or what's
wrong and turns out she was actually
stuck outside but she was fine she
wasn't out there for too long but um
actually good that I randomly looked at
the security camera randomly because who
knows when RBF would have noticed
otherwise if I would not have said
anything and she was just chilling yeah
she was just
[Music]
chilling my cat senses were
tingling my intuition I was that was so
Random I literally just checked it
because you know I was like I don't know
you know talking to M I was like hey you
want to see you want to see my my cat
maybe I didn't even know the cat would
be there like just do you want to see my
security
camera she's like yeah and we we open it
up it's
like my cat is there
huh what's my cat doing
here catastrophe diverted exactly yeah
that ended well that that was good and I
had a special moment with smoovie where
she noticed me being stuck in the
security camera my voice going through
but the right after that I did like a a
phone no right shortly after that I did
like a phone video call um to greet my
cats and the thing is she doesn't seem
to react to my voice going for a
phone and uh she also doesn't see my
face on the camera
on the phone
camera I mean maybe she does kind of
noce my voice through the phone but she
doesn't really do anything in particular
that would make you think she's like
reacting to it like she doesn't rub
against the phone or anything or look
into the phone she doesn't do that but
she she certainly maybe stays around
like walks around close to the phone but
with the security camera she was like
yo h M no it's definitely loud
[Music]
enough something something was different
there I think it just came from an
unexpected place for her
maybe
okay yeah thank you space
waterful I like it when my my chickens
also like my cats that is very important
to me and my cats are you know an
extension of me and if you like me then
you need to appreciate and love my cats
too as you
know Ro toen thank you for the red chat
with no words to it but thank you so
much very generous of you oh wait space
bful was a was a
rainbow I think H you do so much for us
you're always working hard on and off
stream you always try to entertain us
and make us happy not just for profit
but because you genuinely care mhm
you're D for us when we feel down giving
comfort and advice thank you so much for
that meanwhile you do so many great
things performance stage online and sing
and dance so well organize collabs
events and other things going on trips
create Banger songs play some games
pretty
skillfully PR pretty
skillfully interesting phrasing you're
amazing you know when to be funny silly
and light-hearted and when to be serious
and grounded but you're always so darn
cute you're just so adorable and you
always try to be friendly and
understanding for those reasons and more
you might turn oie to me no one is on
your level you mean the world to me my
role model the son of my world my number
one shees thank you so
much thank you wow wow wow wow my
chickens are yappers too
huh I don't know what the um this means
pretty skillfully seems like an
understatement um but besides that thank
you for your kind words yeah I've been
up to many things thank you it must be
you know hard to like follow around
everything everything I'm up to um but
you guys are very dedicated and I love
that about you guys thank you so
much I raised you to Yap
yeah yep yep
that is
true n thanks for the pinky happy
birthday to my beloved Koshi he it's
your fourth birthday in Hol I hope you
get some time to unwind and celebrate
that in between all the work you got to
do at the same time I'm happy and proud
of you for that work because that means
you're part of amazing opportunities
like the world tour yeah I can't wait
for you to cheer for you uh at the world
tour and the breaking Dimensions concert
keep out the great workana and here's to
another year of amazing streams and
opportuni
clink clinking the
glasses thank
you you're going to both as well let's
go let's
go I hope you'll have the most of
fun New York I'm coming for
y I'm going to go to New York and I'm
going to I'm going to perform there and
and then I'll walk around and and and
I'll be like hey I'm walking here mhm
mhm don't disturb me I'm walking here
and then I'll be eating here and then
I'll be sleeping here and then I'll be
going here I don't know I don't know
what I'll be
doing hey I'm singing
[Music]
ear I've never been to New
York New York
ofai it's a German song where they sing
I was never in New York I was never in
Hawaii blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah
[Music]
blah it's a musical
yeah oh that's how it
goes San Francis
it's too hot now um excuse me I doubt
that uh New York is hotter than uh Tokyo
right now I can imagine that it may be
hot there too but mm it's humid here
humid heat is the worst so can't
be worse
than than
here nuh-uh nuh-uh nuh-uh it was pretty
bad last weekend I I believe that it's
hot but it's not humid
hot and I believe I believe you it's
hot but it here it's
insanely
[Music]
hot it's comparable to Miami what okay
never going to
Miami never going there I
suppose that's
fine thank you
na thank you so much thank you thank you
didn't
you wait
the commissioner of the thumbnail wasn't
that
you or was that someone else I think
that was you right was that
[Music]
you that was you yeah it was you thank
you for commissioning cute
art yeah it's cute
not even for Disney World or Universal
Orlando no I would just go to the
Japanese versions of those theme
parks as I've been there
[Music]
already SP
Ro yeah is this your like your Super
Chat what you were supposed to say this
here forgot to type on my aaspa l I'm
here this time though happy birthday to
my Kam
[Music]
oi can't wait to see another
year thank
you can't wait can't wait well you have
to wait let's take it day by day step by
step thank you for your support good for
you that you added something eh don't
just like leave me hanging with
nothing bottom
fragar wait are you I did I not give you
a kiss are you unhappy about that is
that what's going
on botom frag
pyroar for the pinky happy birthday wao
boss
lady where bear are you like still doing
the tags I feel like I haven't been
seeing them in my comment
sections what's going
[Music]
on are you slacking
oh am I blind or am I just always too
early for you to post them or like where
are the tags the time stamps
huh I was like legit thinking until I
saw you again in the chat or so a while
ago I was like H does we bear Hate Me
Now is we bear sick of me like finally
what the
[Music]
hell he hates
me does he still do it yeah Mama toldi
Mama toldi uses your tags you can't just
quit your job she uses your time
stamps are they still
there the the
stamps okay maybe I'm just too early
okay
[Music]
okay then I'll take it
back R SP the pinky happy birthday to my
wonderful oi it's been an incredible
year thank you for everything I'm
looking forward to the next Ian concert
and World Tour even if I can't be there
uh both the if is the if like a certain
if or is it like a eh yeah I hope you
delayed coner do everything you hope it
will
[Music]
be well it's uh already factually not as
I told you
like something got um something big that
I was planning for it is like now like
dead but that's okay I'm still I'm still
like very very happy with um the way
it's going and uh what what we're doing
and you know it's just like going to be
like fury like standard like I don't I
was going to have somebody green
screened in yeah that was going to be
like the special thing but even without
that it's still pretty sick the set list
is sick and the stage design is
amazing I think there will be some
surprising song choices
choices
yeah andoo it'll be good it'll be good
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
I'm excited I'm excited I'm excited I'm
excited I'm excited I'm excited I'm
excited nonstandard St sign yeah uh
there's a yeah I mean yeah yeah didn't I
get us I I last year too I got a stage
design but last year I was like uh uh I
don't know do whatever
so I feel like it could have been better
if I like actually gave like a theme and
like more suggestions this time I gave
like like a theme and suggestions like
many references and all that so they
created it according to that and it
looks incredible it's
huge
volcanoes yeah anyway look forward to
that RS thank you for your support and I
don't know if that meant you can't be at
both either but um I hope maybe next
time
then onion my onion
m d J1 d o Super Chat coming in wow
thank you uh Pono thank you for the red
super chat happy birthday tento hope you
eat lots of cake and spoil yourself the
rest of the day I didn't my birthday is
on the 7th but yours takes priority I'm
looking forward to see the future plans
and Adventures in the coming year happy
birthday thank you I mean I didn't
didn't at least I ate ice cream I ate a
lot of ice cream
now I want more I
want soon Wawa
[Music]
soon yeah thank you very much I'm also
looking forward to the second half of
this year I'm I'm looking forward to the
results of my hard labor right now and
then the more
calm time hopefully I'm
expecting like after after
September things should be normal for a
while and calm I hope
[Music]
so I hope so at least for two months or
so October November no maybe to at least
[Music]
October
yeah yeah cuz the thing is like now
we're like mostly prepping for like Ian
concert and the First World Tour thing
cuz the first one is like like early and
then there's kind of a break and then it
really gets started with the rest of
the concerts World Tour concerts there's
like a break in between
[Music]
so
mhm so yeah
yeah well we'll get through
[Music]
it yeah Atlanta in
December so I have like no idea how like
what going to what's going to be
happening for that one like what songs
Etc we're just focusing on the first one
now yeah there's dates there's dates
already and everything H check it out
check it out so thank you
Poncho also H yeah happy happy Bel
birthday to you poncho by the way oh my
God oh my God oh my God almost forgot to
say prince of Denmark thanks to pinky
happy birthday K I don't have the words
to express the comfortable Joy I find oh
when I get to spend time with your
streams oh I adore this time with you I
can happy birthday oh oh thank you thank
you comfortable
Joy I like to hear that thank you so
much you give me joy too I want a joy a
joy a
joy
yeah thank you so much for the
support
ad just another D Richard G D ping
Channel d d demon Chef D oh we're
zooming we're zooming but it stops here
again absur thanks for the WR Super Chat
happiest birthday to our beloved T and
thank you for another wonderful year
even though you're so busy you never
fail to make and spend time with us hope
you have a great time in Japan and
everything goes well thank you yeah I've
been taking everything day by day it's
kind of overwhelming
surprisingly more to do than originally
planned yeah um
but oh it's almost over it's almost over
the grind is almost over G
takwa G I am gamb thank you for
supporting me and thank you for
celebrating my birthday yay I'm sorry I
couldn't do more exciting things but I
hope you guys had a good time with it
a a random collusion also with a red
Super Chat yay wa time yeah this was
just the beginning of the stream I
guess thank you random collusion so
happy to randomly totally randomly
Collide into you
again thank
[Music]
you for the
pinky uh K you're an amazing person
thank you for everything you do
I really can't thank you enough I hope
you keep being
awesome thank you I'll try am I awesome
right now I'll try to continue then but
you also must continue you guys are
awesome
too I'm counting on you
Yu resine thanks for the red Chad happy
birthday T another amazing year with you
and kfp you continue to be an
inspiration with your content
performances and general positive energy
hope you have an amazing celebration and
keep up the great work yeah thank you
sir laate good times come on thank you
so much another great year indeed
another a beautiful year and another
beautiful set of merchandise everybody
buy my merchandise Link in the
description I think the merchandise is
really darn good so please go get it
little plug here in the middle of
nowhere Shilling Shilling so that uh
there will be much
[Music]
billing rber
duy the rubber ducky man is so good he
so
good I am going to bathe with it just
like you guys so when you're in the
bathtub with your rubber ducky you can
think that waa might also be taking a
bath at this very moment with her own
rubber ducky
no do what you want with that huh don't
drown the ducky by the way don't drown
It Don't Drown
it I don't see the correlation me
neither thank you rine Happ thank you
for the pinky thank you thank you thank
you D sh
Li and here we have a a
backwards rainbow I don't see that very
often and then I'll read this part uh
Happy Birthday de waha here wait this is
from fire The Elements by the way fire
the elements says happy birthday de waa
here's a rainbow for your wish uh for
you wish you have a wonderful day and
all your wishes come true and
as always I'll keep supporting you thank
you # #
y thank you so
much ah nice nice rainbow seems like a
contrarian rainbow but it's still
beautiful than is thank you m
mwah fire the
elements good old takamori supporter
[Music]
I feel like takam people who like takam
Modi people who are kfp and dead Beats
at the same
time they are in it for the long run and
they are usually they don't change their
oshis
somehow Takami I don't know I feel like
Takami supporters are very
loyal oh you know it
[Music]
girl like they got into this and they
were like I'm going to support takam
Moni and nothing else really or like at
least I'll focus on that and I'll I
won't I won't ever stray away and I I'm
I know what I want it's takamori and I I
like him separately I like them together
I like him on top of each other and
underneath each other and diagonally
across each other
diagonally that this doesn't mean
anything I'm just saying funny words um
just saying that you like us separately
and together either way but
uh
spicy I just mean that yeah you know
maybe you know what I
mean thank you Jeff star uh with a pinky
says happy birthday thank you Jeff star
yay thank you it's up up here in between
the rainbow
thank you for the support and as we have
we have spanheim with the red super chat
happy birthday kiaa can't believe it's
four already here's to 100
more
no 100 no no
no no I'll be I'll be dead uh
don't don't put these expectations so
high but here another example of a
Takami supporter very loyal very
always there can always you know
count on them thank
you see they're so loyal they're ready
to be here for 100 extra years Bruh
Bruh what else could you ever ask for
huh Richard D
[Music]
Danon true and link gaming D in mood
thank you for the red super chat happy
birthday W I can't believe it has been
four years of great memories already and
seeing you as a pillar of the H Life
Community brings tears to my eye cheers
to my favorite YouTuber for now and
forever k key thank
you
yeah yeah whole life English has
grown now of this many members holy
macaroni
really makes you think really makes you
realize once
again it feels like these these these
people feel like my children this feels
like feels like I'm a kindergarten
teacher and these are my
[Music]
Kinders and yeah I I feel I I
feel proud m I am
[Music]
mothering yeah gardening those
Kinders D Senai I have become a dce
Senai yeah it's almost been four years m
m Mia m m
[Music]
Mia m m
trying to hear if I hear some reaction
or
so wonder what she's
doing
summoning waiting
[Music]
for okay sure reacted I don't think did
you hear
that did you hear
her it works it works I can summon the
[Music]
Italian oh I'm so proud of my
Italian I can say more than just the
Pizza
Pasta Italian always
works uh thank you muda for the right
Super Chat very very very sweet of you
and it's nice to see you y you know
there were times where I thought yeah no
more muda but then you always surprised
me and I'm like waa muda still there
muda is still
there thank you so much for the
support don't let go of the Wawa ever
yugen Eugen L Danish sess d o z 176
thank you for the red jat happy birthday
Tel can't believe it's already been four
years first your birthday D the Ian
concert and World Tour and finally the
four year anniversary mhm mhm so many
exciting things ahead mhm this is a
great year for kiaha mhm mhm mhm
stressful stress summer this is like the
most Crazy Summer I've had in whole life
you
know thank you though let's get through
this together and celebrate together and
enjoy every day together hey he he
[Music]
he you know I really like those like
I've been seeing on Twitter like some
memes like
Italian not not like like Italian memes
per se but like memes cute cute drawings
of her like saying pasta I like seeing
that stuff I like seeing angry angry
Italian cute
[Music]
girl we need to anger her more
crayon thanks for the red super chat
happy fourth birthday W another eventful
year has passed you did so much in terms
of music and projects and even became a
homeowner oh yeah oh
yeah that was another Arc that we had in
the beginning of the Year wishing you
even more success in the future today
also put on my armor after three years
of kfp service wow nice nice nice nice
thank you so much WoW armor looking good
on you it fits you so well unlike Egan
aegan Egen from House of the Dragon
putting on his armor he's just going to
fake it till he makes
it you're looking fancy in that it's
like made for you this one's made for
you aan is just like Faking It wearing
someone else's armor trying to become a
different egun
[Music]
making house house of the Dragon
references out of
nowhere valan steel we have something
better than Valyrian steel our armor is
made out
[Music]
of dot dot dot dot
uh eggshells
yay
eggshells yeah eggshells but with a
never right trim
yeah never right is keeping it
[Music]
together oh my that's
cute we stand no chance no I
mean I think you do because you're not
just wearing it eggshells usually are
scattering eggshells wherever you walk
and then if people want to get to you
they have to walk on eggshells and
that's just not very comfortable so
believe believe yeah kintsugi kin yeah
okay never right it's
kintsugi never right uh exell armor so
if you watched my collab of Laden then
you know then you know that's
fancy that's
fancy oh a first the raid now we have a
kaop
raid let's
go
oo W let's go g I don't know if you're
listening or if you just raid it without
listening but um I was saying before the
Takami fans are like so loyal and
they're here to stay and they they like
will always support us separately or
together it doesn't matter but I feel
like they're like some of the most loyal
fans out there it's
crazy cool
stuff but H returning to my super chats
thank you so much
crayons the d s yeah we're we're such
cool sis right we're so cool like Kelly
is I don't know about
me I don't know about me you left out
the spicy bits it wasn't supposed to be
[Music]
spy thanks for the pinky
go feeling
Dan feeling
dank thank you so
much
dingon thanks for the red super chat
happy birthday let's go thank you so
much hey I remember you and another
nostalgic sight to behold thank
[Music]
you what guys she's not here don't don't
talk to her she's not even here it seems
don't tell her things that she shouldn't
[Music]
know we're reading super chats right now
guys and I'm tanging a lot in between
but
[Music]
I'm at LA's place right
now borrowing her
equipment she's an angel for letting me
do
[Music]
that um Mr stitchy D you destroy of
humans D how do I read this
kamasan
d h an an an
[Music]
chicken Broken Man dun friendly
neighborhood
lesbian dun V faction D for the r of J
happy birthday T thank you happy
birthday to you too no I don't know when
your birthday is thank you sometime
sometimes I just want to say it back you
know thank you so
much a legend yeah they they're all
legends y'all all of these people are
legends the it's the League of Legends
literally I'm playing League of Legends
right
now thank you V faction andon star
Creator D zip D for the red super CH
happy burb
wa I wrote it like this is
I I just woke up and my brain is not
braining yet so try to pretend the Super
Chat is super wholesome and written with
fancy words and smartly stuff and stuff
love you why you're the best thank you
no Aris I wouldn't have noticed you
don't have to like defend yourself it's
all good don't worry your super chats
don't always have to be like you know
perfect you know you can write whatever
you want thank you for your support
thank you shly happy bir by to you
too see I said it again sorry that comes
naturally not happy birthday to you but
to
[Music]
me
swords happy birthday
[Music]
thanks for Pinky happy birthday W thank
you thank you so much
Z thank you for being there on my
special day always for me there even if
it's a shitty time thank you destroy of
humans thanks for happy birthday ra
thank you
[Music]
FAA it's little chooo Cho a birthday
kiss for my
chicken arur D for the pinky we're
zooming a little bit now oh that's good
Happy Birthday waa genuinely where the
time go there's no end to the amount of
Joy you've provided us over the years
and the buck doesn't stop there here
let's keep that ball rolling into this
next year too lots of love for my Kami
thank you yeah I was shook I was
shook let me get this table down a
little bit oh
nice like I'm looking up so much cuz her
monitors are up so
high yeah the time went by so fast I
can't believe we're halfway through the
year and it freaking scares me I don't
want to think about
time just letting it go but it goes by
so fast
[Music]
don't we want it to stop it's going
too fast don't stop don't stop I'm going
to change lyrics I'll say do stop do
stop please stop the damn time
[Music]
no don't go your own way don't don't go
your own way go my way go my
[Music]
go no it's not smileage it's idle Master
an old idle Master
song a
classic
mhm you guys don't
know not cultured
enough
oh Flappy Boy Thanks for the red super
chat finally it's no longer bad luck to
wish you a happy birthday honestly I
really do not care about that apparently
it's a thing in Europe but I really
don't care about it hope you like those
four new Co high as your much deserved
present for your fourth
birthday so many eager collab Partners
so many girls sing for their idle die
Senai wouldn't say
sing W Bey couldn't start any better
thank you I I wouldn't say they're sing
for me but I'm glad to see someone sing
for narissa it's like narissa joints
same thing for me and then laa joints
same thing for narissa how is this going
to
continue nice yeah she deserves it I'm
I'm glad she's getting the love
really makes me happy to see cuz she
gave me so much love you know she gave
me so much love and support and I'm sure
by the way that I treated her as a
senpai I'm sure she'll she's receiving
Raa with open arms very gently um yeah
maybe the way I vented and talked to
narissa in the past months maybe the
same way they will do that
too it would be nice if if they were it
could be each other's outlet but but I'm
also offering myself we could do like a
we could uh do a triangle of letting it
all
out a nice ooshi chain yeah it's a nice
ooshi chain yeah keep the chain going
hook it up hook it
up but yeah thank you so much for the
sweet message Flappy boy let's let's
continue to have a good time together
thank you for being part of C still for
another birthday
H triangular venting
yes oi
centipede sure sure yeah it could have
been an ooshi chain but you make it into
a
centipede
sure why
[Music]
not flppy boy M ooh an oi tree that
would be interesting like instead of a
family
tree yeah no it doesn't even necessarily
have to be like a family tree thingy but
I was generally recently thinking about
you know those charts that somehow
haven't seen anyone do in a long time
but the like relationship charts that
were more common I feel
like in the past years I saw it more
often where you know they just like make
some arrows and say and this person
loves me this person this and that I
don't know maybe I should do that
again you used to do those too
oh
[Music]
oh there too many you don't have to
include all of them just like focus on
one like Branch or so I don't
[Music]
know Wicked KN albel dun SL of Shadows
dun the steel d
for
Pinky happy
birthday thank you for the pink Super
Chat happy birthday happy happy birthday
thank you so much for the support
n always always always there for me
[Music]
C thanks for the r chat happy birthday
to the most inspirational chicken I know
W love forever oh my God love
forever oh that reminds me of those
stickers thank you so much wait
what wait
what I guess this is not directed
towards me no I
noticed no I
noticed hey what the
eie what the is wrong with
you I'm not going to give you a kiss if
you call me that clearly a
typo usual room two weeks
[Music]
bye w
w no
kiss no kiss kiss
denied that's how it goes hope hopefully
you learn your
[Music]
lesson yeah yeah that thanks for posting
my lore my
description that says very clearly that
I'm not a chicken or a
turkey
fr0 D retro Ron D Temple
Ty JM I think we might be able to
fin uh I wasn't saying anything I don't
know what I was just about to say uh
nothing in particular
maybe U maybe I'm not able to finish all
of these I just saw how many more Reds
and pinks there are afterwards it looked
pretty like normal like here there was a
lot of non pinks and
[Music]
reds yeah let's not finish it it's okay
it's
okay thanks my CH happy birthday while I
finally have my holiday on the important
day ooh hope you have a great day t
thank you and yet you didn't have it on
the most important day that I apparently
up because I was I released the
merch and did the K on the day after my
birthday I hope you were able to watch
that
too thank you time zones confused
me thank soon for the big big Super
Chat than chocolate insomnia and than
with red happy birthday waa whether
you're Phoenix chicken or an ostrich I
love you all to name will always uh
cheer the hardest for you thanks for
making it a great place for all of wait
so so question
question have you have you have you been
able to resist the urge to watch the new
season
yet have you have you have you been able
to hold back you have to hold back
please hold back don't don't watch it
yet you're waiting for me right it will
still take a long time though
I don't think we'll be done before end
of August or like maybe at the end of
August we'll be done I think I can do a
lot of watch Longs in August until you
watch you waiting okay
[Music]
okay I've been seeing ads I've been
seeing
ads go away must
resist guys you have to wait all of you
stay strong thank you for your support
in these trying times let's occupy our
minds with different things oh oh monat
new season doesn't exist let's just
remember the times how it was before we
knew that another season would exist we
were fine before that we would be fine
now so just ignore its existence just
pretend it's not even there yet we don't
know about it so it doesn't exist occupy
your mind with the
Wawa only
[Music]
nice
nice I'm
tired CH insomnic R thanks for the red
happy birthday T wishing you all the
best to day and all and always thank you
to you
too thank you Sharon very very sweet of
you my Hungarian buddy thank you so much
for celebrating my birthday to
together Crowley than soon rainbow thank
you for the r Super Chat not a rainbow
happy birthday love you cute outfit
today what was I wearing I was wearing
the the dandle right was
I I think I was with the no not the dle
I was wearing the the dle I was wearing
maybe was I was wearing the the jumper
or the the jumpsuit
thingy I think ah no I was wearing the
dle I'm
confused I think I was wearing both of
them on different days
[Music]
stretch
sleep thank you rainbow what do you
think about my outfit today huh you like
this one too H thank you oh my God
stop Tassimo thank for the pinky damn it
a little late but Happy Birthday K I
hope you will have nice day today oh
don't worry I don't think like in this
year for my birthday no one's too late
if anything I'm the
latest there's just no late or no early
and my birthday was just stretched
across like two or 3 days so don't
worry don't
worry no thank you soon UF mod thank you
soon for the red chat happy happy
birthday my beloved oie you are you're
the best always so super hardworking
with such edication thank you for the
red super
[Music]
chat I try my best I try my best for you
guys I want you guys to get good
entertainment and thus I work
hard res 4 for1 dun tremo Rego thanks
for chat biggest birthday blessings my
bright and beloved tent I beseech you to
brim with Bountiful Bliss bottomless
laughter at Beautiful Moments wow you
are bound for Brilliance basically your
breathtaking believe it what is going on
with the
bees what's with the
bees what with the
[Music]
bees they're beautiful it's like oh it's
like they're soft feel like I feel boobs
when I read this like I'm gently resting
my head on top of some Bountiful
beautiful
boobies what I just want to lay down I
think thank you that was mind breaking
breaking thank you
troo or should I say broo oh because
it's my birthday that's why I guess so
my birthday my birthday
okay okay okay people with their cool
English alliteration okay
cool huh good for you that you know what
Toro is doing here good for you you feel
smart now huh you feel oh so
smart you smarty
pants
biter uh CR than Binky happy birthday
from the West Coast W love also Kusa at
rear end
review what review whose butt did I
review keep the idea for another day
although you would still have the best
one but
who whose butt would I have reviewed I
don't even remember this
part ah I did not mess up saying year
end review you guys just hear what you
want to hear uh-huh
thank you
[Music]
sir
Flora in
the
J chip chicken chip thank you for the
red chat come happy birthday T oh thank
you so much
Flora appreciate it thank you so much
for the big big generous Super Chat
no come
on you need to chat fix with pinky
actually
no hey Mama happy birthday since you
already got my love and unwavering
loyalty I guess I can still send a super
as a small token gift hope you enjoyed
your special day thank you yeah I mean
this is a nice extra of course for all
of you guys I'm already already I have
received so much from you you guys don't
have to do anything besides buying my
merchandise he Link in the description
thank you un
Chad thank
Li a happy birthday to me thank
you I enjoyed my special day thanks to
you
guys and Honolulu thanks for the pinky
your second time I
[Music]
think hey ohow Kam I can read
that okay okay okay I think John
patri I'll end it here sorry Slavic
fellow you will have to wait number
21 okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
maybe I could have gone a little bit
further maybe I could have finished it
if I wasn't tting so much but you know
how it is I can't just you know going
like straight through
[Music]
it I'm going to cut it here because I
still have to do some work and then I
want to get a massage before it's too
late
yeah oh and I have to get up relatively
early
tomorrow
maybe yeah I don't know tomorrow I have
one more one more big challenge to
overcome
so I'll be very exhausted but it's also
Shion uh collab stream almost I keep on
like almost forgetting about it because
I have something else really big
important to do
tomorrow cursed witchcraft
yay I already should have a thumbnail I
think so I'll put up the reservation
later later later and then uh the
thumbnail will give away what we're
doing so look forward to
that it will give you a bit more of an
idea what the Witchcraft is supposed to
be what we're cooking yeah thank you for
[Music]
watching and I'll I'll surely be able to
finish this next week don't worry I'll I
catch up on super chats next week I try
I'll try I'll try I'll try I'll try
thank you for watching thank you L for
borrowing me your place I have to go
idle meeting
actually so I'll be borrowing that
too thank you for streaming Mom thank
you for listening in at this weird time
at this weird unusual time appreciate it
guys
[Music]
don't forget the ice cream yeah yeah I'm
still here for a little bit getting some
work done
so okay in German we say a don't worry
it's only 4:00
[Music]
a.m. yeah
only Al in than you and
byebye
bye-bye bye-bye
[Music]
sh
a
[Music]