If you wanna it dive in
Nothing's gonna happen if you wait
Do you all like thrills?
Aren't you get bored with life?
Even I’m excited about falling
That figure is aesthetics
Would you rather choose a life of
Peaceful or Stormy
Ahaha!
There are times in life when you fall
But
if you never fall, you won’t climb
You’ve said it’s like an attraction
Don’t be afraid to fall
Gonna dive in!
BAN BAN BAN BAN BA
BAN RTA
The straight and narrow path is not enough
These words will make you the strongest
Chant it in your heart
That’s the magical word
“HENTAI”
There are many kinds of tears
Painful or Pleasant
I think I’m going crazy
Isn’t it happier?
There’s sometimes we’re hopeless
You can't climb without descending
If you're scared of falling
There’s no up
No way I know my future
That’s why focus on my feeling
I’m the best idol in the world
(NO)
She said you are
''HENTAI''
When we cross the red light, that’s tight
No matter how ashamed we’re, it’s alright
Are you feeling spicy?
I see that you’re horny
Then I will be sexy and lose my mind
Oh no! I Can’t stop my heart beating…
Now I’m gonna drive into shock!
I am crazy about …!
BAN BAN BAN BAN BA
BAN RTA
Down down down down down together
I’m not afraid to bare my soul
We can be strong and never lonely
Can I chant that word?
NO WAY! NO WAY!
Down down down down down together
I’m not afraid to bare my soul
We can be strong and never lonely
Don’t you miss that word?
You can’t say it yet
Everybody say…
”Not yet!!”
Aren't you feeling excited？
Now that time has come
Everybody say “HENTAI”