a
[Applause]
[Music]
n e
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
oh all
right
[Music]
K oh
get
key sorry for the wait uh I
actually oh my god oh wait double
audio uh I speed
ran I speed run the
the
dungeon second level of the dungeon in 1
hour and then it was like 7 minutes to
the stream when I arrived at the last
boss and I thought oh yeah B this might
not make it in time but then I I killed
I Absolut absolutely speedran it and did
the boss in like 4 minutes I was like
oh she I was like really focused on the
boss specifically had some good good
crits and then then I was like okay
let's let's quickly Zoom for
drinklings and then suddenly I was in a
fight
for now ready for third level of dungeon
level the level of the seven star gear
really honestly this level was really
really easy there was only like one
fight that where I was like a little bit
troubled but only because you
know if you have experience with this
you may know what I'm talking about but
in this on that second level there were
these enemies that were like
plant holding people and they like the
first thing they do in the fight is uh
spread like some seeds or po pollen
pollen they were spreading Poland and
that immediately like paralyzes
and uh another
debuff debuffs
them uh and then it debuffed like
several times it would always like
debuff others and I could just unbuffed
with uh with
Satan right away more or less but then
this time it debuffed like kidu and
Satan and then I had to do like pretty
much the whole fight with son and uh da
and that really dragged out a lot and
then eventually uh both of them koed
around the time when Satan and kidu
finally came back to their
sensus they koed but I still was like ah
this is no problem it's going to be fine
they just have to wake the [\h__\h]
up
um yeah those enemies were a little bit
annoying but most of the time it was
manageable it was only one fight only
one fight yeah losing the Healer was
tough it was a big group of enemies too
but anyway I rushed I rushed can be
upgraded to their seven level weapons
which are very very strong ahuh
interesting okay the chat went I yeah
chat sorry sorry sorry I I was like so
stressed out because I was rushing the
dungeon and then stream was about to
start so I was like here so I did the
drink link and then and then the stream
was starting and then I was like ah [\h__\h]
and then and then I quickly uh watered
my plants
and and made some tea and washed my the
rest of my grapes and did all of that in
like 7 Minutes the only thing I didn't
do I guess is go to idle meeting so that
will probably have to happen eventually
during the
stream
ooh speed so
Speedy I have so many grapes too I hope
they will carry me yesterday I was so
hungry I ate like almost a whole bag of
these like chippy chips chippy chippy
cha cha but they're not chips but I
almost ate like the whole actually I say
that and there still a lot
inside and I was still so hungry anyway
and then oh my God actually let going to
get my phone really quickly
[Music]
okay one more
thing one more thing
[Music]
ch
okay hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
ah
okay can I raise this
HH no okay I just want to hear myself
better
if I
sound I going to say if I sound
distorted let me know but that's not
what I meant with
that ah I was just hyped because I was
running
around oh I sound
mled
what wait are we even using the right m
microphone yeah what do you mean
muffled
n
no I
must investigate then I'll listen to
myself
here test test test test test test
test oh I sound normal don't
I sounds normal to
me I S
off hello test test
blue oh it sounds normal you guys are
confusing
me you guys are so confusing
me it's like I'm talking to a f for f CL
what there's no way didn't even change
anything from
yesterday but I do generally feel like I
wish like I I I I I I think I do get the
sentiment but then it was the same
yesterday if that's the
case
um but the thing is I don't know what
would change that
the Noise
Gate
no compress
pressor I don't know does
this I don't think anything is
changing equalizer what is
The
Equalizer equal let's equalize this do
oh I sound I think that made it sound
very
different is this
better is this better or is this better
you know what I
mean
h what you think it's something with the
bgm
dancing dancing giving me the real audio
advice no I don't like this this is too
much more like here and then uh hey hey
hey hey you you versus hey hey wow yeah
but I had it I had it like somewhere
around here if I do like more like
this yeah you like that you like this H
like you like it like that
[Music]
H that is the the high gain right okay
here see hey hey you you I don't like a
girlfriend hey hey you you that is very
muffled hey hey you you I don't like
your girlfriend no way no way wow it's
changing so
much okay that actually solves my own
problems too I think the mid gain what
are the bells though there's High Gain
mid gain low gain and then next to it
there's High bell Midbell low Bell I
don't know what that means shall retest
it high high Bell really
low high Bell really high huh should I
just raise like everything to the
max h
[Music]
well it's kind of better than before at
least I'm pretty sure Nobel is a
priz don't Max sound
well
okay yeah I don't know what the [\h__\h] all
this is
really hi but this is better than before
kind of
kind
of try
screaming I am
screaming don't let me it's
um like what's the
word it's compressed so it won't get too
loud you can probably play around on
your own later in find I always I never
know I always do and I never
know I don't know but uh anyway so today
apparently we're not going to finish the
game I've or so I've been
told
um
you you
guys don't believe in me I get
it okay
it sounds like it's peeking a
bit just like your mom with me last
night
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay um you think it sounds like it's
peeking it's
okay only if
I only if I'm loud right
I don't know it's okay welcome to the
membership welcome back did you like my
joke about their mom so
much don't we
all wait you are our mom self self
self
yeah anyway let's get into this there's
so M oh that's Soo
loud somewhere around here
maybe uh hello chat are you going to
just um not load okay what is it
recently with chat no matter if it's
YouTube chat or hyper
chat guys if your stream lags
today close the
chat that is my
advice and see where am
I H yeah so we are in son drink link
story I think it might be the last one
otherwise probably there wouldn't be a
fight I
suppose one grapple one dude wants to be
grappled but wait wait no no no no no I
want to be the
spinning shut the m 1 2 3 4 maybe
five this one's
safe so
often wow I so often miss the prop on
this
one but it's so
good just scratched by face by a
ow fights are still pretty
loud okay ow ow ow ow that really hurt
that scratch really
hurt it's such a good move yeah and then
so often it also leaves one or two
enemies
Charmed which is
amazing he's weak to gun amazing
she okay but there also quite a yeah
they were like eight levels below
me but then think about it like we're
only two people right now versus it was
like six
people
so too much damage Overkill oh my
God already finished the dungeon so I
don't think we need to grind
today I think
[Music]
mask how dare you touch her inner fire
like that you're disgusting kid
called him omay but they're acting
she doesn't
know how the
[\h__\h] oh she just really into role
play it's probably
really turned on by
that it's the same Glo same voice same
hair
yeah we've been here all
[Music]
along this girl what why are these
people so dump sometimes but then so
smart other
times oh there you go she knows
so she just likes role
playing for the
plot God these grapes are so good grapes
are grap snack
thanks for the membership
gift
thank my mic sounds weird you sound
weird what what do you mean how give me
more Denson should say something Denson
is the only one who gave me like proper
feedback that actually
helped oh did you hear that
what the mic sounds compressed well
that's good radio like yeah that's well
yeah I sound
tiny I was chunky wonky she's doing
funny
things I'm peek okay okay okay well I
mean that's mostly because of
this but then I don't hear myself so
wow
uh
uh I don't know do you like this
more but I
[Music]
think I don't know what's happening I
honestly don't know ah ah ah
ah we good you like
this I think she's zooming I hear her
zooming I just raised up volume overall
are you sure I see it's on on yellow in
OBS here a little bit a little bit for
you my phone
died I sound fine
okay oh there was a little resonance now
there's not there's now less I don't
know what that means but okay sounds
like we're good
okay
hi found
exra extra
[Music]
fore
oh I think since I got a trophy that
means that was the last one oh I have
more costumes to choose from in the AL
you mean probably for son specifically
right we have another
one with
number oh actually so with number the
Bingle board I think was of number yeah
uh I only have one Bingo left oh like
one one one
tile
OMG you're going to be besties
forever last time we spoke now I wanted
to find out the real reason he lost his
job I'm curious about that too
we're just going to get these drinklings
out of the way and then we can jump into
main story don't
worry when's the
wedding these grapes man
she's so cute
game volume
okay
for what
[Music]
what
need for
sounds like he needs a
lesson a beating lesson
need a trip to the hospital to cool
up
sorry we're going to stop him
yeah I know I heard that
peek maybe a little bit less High
Gain what what what
what okay
uh ask her out
he's like
what a really manly
what how do you guys even get that a e
letter
you just get it from
Google that's so much
effort the phone is easier
in
[Music]
German we just
say basically same
thing I guess one more one
more with
him to get like a fighting scene or
something like that do you need a drink
onink no right yeah you nether right
let's sing a song just one
song Yes um there's a is there a new one
is there a new one
please the Z ones might are new I
[Music]
think yeah right I think so too are are
both of them new
[Music]
I love you
yeah DJ k w
c next song
[Music]
is nice announcement here we go
oh
[Music]
beautiful what
I didn't miss
[Music]
it I just felted the
rib let's go
[Music]
oh
yeah it's like an anime opening still
beginning of the Stream
[Music]
he's like doing a weird chant but like
it's not like the typical kind of U
chance it's just like
conversation he feels so cool and then
he's doing all of that in like an
English
accent shab oh D what do you want
the Fone wasn't even there
K like are you insane Kido are you just
crazy in your head is there something
wrong in your
head are you okay I don't think
so he's a little bit drunk I
think even even if it doesn't show in
his
[Music]
status okay so oh wait I got some new
items I I cannot understand also I still
hear now actually I feel like even more
than before I feel like I'm
peeking U but if you guys are not
bothered by it then it's like
whatever um like when I'm talking
louder no actually oh I think I'm
peeking in the mid or or low
range I just uh [\h__\h] everything yeah
it's the mid it's the mid it's so mid
the mid is so mid so I am angry no this
was
still it's the high
belt I don't know I I changed again I
think possibly a little bit
better uh I am angry because can I see
it from here
no then how am I supposed to show it
because she can't wear it
now um I got the Revival microphone
three times in that one dungeon run and
then I got her bag from her main class
uh a laugh bag or or so funny bag funny
bag also three times in the same dungeon
level several weapons Times Free
are you [\h__\h] kidding
me so stupid okay we got a level five
helmet do you have one by know he
does ah Z
doesn't what
happened 10% critical hit rate shees
yeah I can sell him yeah for sure for
sure oh cyber
boots greatly reduces chance of
receiving restrictive status elements
amazing does everybody have five star
boots now okay okay well actually that
was uh good then U did we get a new Jack
oh yeah cyber armor lowers the damage
taken when guarding oh okay so um kid's
breaker no beast beast beast uh thingy
also leveled up one more level and it
said if I guard then I get a really
powerful counter now
so I might want to think about guarding
every now and
then you know what ah but this is the
one with enduring
KO check your skills at Hall happy
before taking the train more
slots ahuh okay okay okay okay I feel
like I already have too much choice
though
um well each one just take this please
thank you take it off of my
hands it did save me before yeah you got
to switch Dragon of do yeah I got to
switch if I want to do that and also I
want to finish the Namba Bingle really
quickly which one's Namba
here it's close we got to finish it I
only have one
left
OMG and then and then we go check
aloha Alo
happy Alo happy k space is very good
right now yeah so I've heard so I've
been
told so this there because I got all the
stats like really high
[Music]
this
jump tou me
[Applause]
oh no I'm going to just ignore you
goodbye than
watching martial arts
competitions I I'll at least read you
the the short version son says she
enjoys watching martial arts
competitions on her days off
professional wrestling
included okay not really my
thing but you do
you wait Flor microphone W wo wo w What
level oh four never mind but it would be
kind of crazy if I found a five or six
star weapon so
randomly
uh now wand last
one taking a trip by train friends
forever oh really I was I was just
joking we oh we're really good to be
friends
wherever yay oh man it's nice that he's
not only besties with Ichiban but now
also with kidu who is ichiban's
bestie
go oh my God it's like a dating game I
think he wants to kiss me on the
bridge some just invited me to kiss him
on the bridge I know exactly what that
kind of invitation means
yo I know it
exactly refreshing
gum uh lowest level is
z so I just want to buy some more
alcohol
please do they wait oh do they not
alcohol in here
Frank well then I'm kind of pointless
but I'm going to get some chicken
KAG homies kiss homies on
bridges that they very much do oh here
there's a aloppy right
there amazing thing oh
cute Al happy I'm supposed to first of
all look at
outfits is it just an assassin or is it
here Yama that's your
default right is this the little
one really girl um think you you're
still going to feel sweaty maybe take
off that jacket like I'm just I'm
serious oh this is awesome yeah swimsuit
honestly I feel like the swimsuit looks
better but damn she's got a a huge rib
cage
no
her waist is kind of low or I don't know
her old wa her whole waist from shoulder
body is very
lengthy I want to give her this
[Music]
yeah okay I think what level are is
26 25 with 30 you guys say I need I
should switch
back ah wait skill
inheritance for Kido I Bond 70 plus oh
no never mind it's not for him what
huh yeah still H oh for you for her I
can do
something
[Music]
um blinding grapple
blinding I think I'm going to bring
this I think I like using that oh two
two extra
skills um
I think this is good enemy area and
power heavy with paralysis I said it
right didn't I Jewel
breaker oh for
who I don't see a jewel breaker
here enemy area
medium I'll take that one
too Dr breaker
ah this one yeah actually I haven't been
using champag splash down ever since
then I'm fine using
this I did huh did you ever give number
a job no oh no I guess I should
have just so he can level in the
background dims
soon oh wait don't Ally
area one Ally oh then probably better to
bring the homecooked
dimsum enemy area medium one enemy
heavy which one which one should I do
like this might be good for boss fights
maybe but usually they have some kind of
like weakness that's either an element
or knife or gun fist is kind of somehow
I haven't I don't think anybody ever had
fist weakness is that even possible
Ascension
okay if you say
so number has
nothing okay then I'm out of
here no enemies right yeah no
nobody's weak to
[Music]
it so that makes me
think maybe not the best choice but okay
it might still be very strong at least
they can't have a resistance to it
either I guess that's the good thing
they're nobody's weak to it but nobody's
strong towards it
either uh so now let's let's uh I think
we're ready to go we're level 40 41 I
think the recommendation was around that
too
[Music]
oh I wanted to buy some alcohol
though where can I buy some alcohol do
you think they sell alcohol
here I think
not because for MP healing I I now like
to just give them one alcoholic drink
and then top it off with like two two
alcohol lower ring smaller drinks I I I
just realized like yesterday that that's
probably how people do it and not just
like take a million of the smaller 10 15
MP
drinks I don't know anything close by
that sells I I should go here anyway to
sell some
stuff and then next doors maybe we'll
get some
alcohol
this this is
so unlike me so out of character to be
asking for alcohol who am I
oh guts booster treasure triangulator
that's
me
pawn I'm here to sell
equipment although I might um keep one
funny bag maybe I'll need it oh wait I
have a dolphin bag too
cute H I'll keep both I got this I think
in the dung and this in the bond
link o they're good
money and I got this also in the dungeon
only need one I would
think uhhuh two of those microphones
don't need those
anymore who needs
these
okay don't sell any of the bond weap you
okay okay okay I'm I'm trying not
[Music]
to probably sell the military armor but
whatever
oh that's
okay H looking good looking good
do we have any of these drops right
now oh I I need to use these things but
I got all of them I think recently don't
worry the gangster one but who's a
gangster nobody's a gang gangster you
mean I can sell it or nobody's a gang
gster right
now Z he's a
chef Oh you mean by default he's a
gangster base
[Music]
defense base
willpower don't
know job XP for your current job
uh gangster cabby assass assassin
assassin we
have and action star we don't
have all chefs are
gangsters show I'm up I should go
too I should go to the
dentist H okay okay alcohol quick
alcohol what didn't I check in here
already ah
man flowers to go ah [\h__\h]
it I have other
things talk to Satan ah man Satan wants
to talk to me everybody wants to talk to
me they're so
clingy people are so clingy
guys no they're not bothering me but um
just
general check
up uh where am this way
oh you aren't in a position to
[Laughter]
judge that's just something we say in
German can't do the thing now can you
guys ah alcohol okay this is
fine 90 is
think
helpful
okay
bye-bye what level was it 40
41 41 wow the dungeon was very
necessary uh
but I think now is also a dungeon
right why is the ocean
[Music]
black so cold let's go to Hawai
ah getting sleepy
[Music]
we're
tring wa radio where is the wa radio
station h
yeah these grapes are so good oh my God
and so healthy
[Music]
wow I feel like I'm skipping things I'm
not clicking anything but like suddenly
we're in the we're in a truck suddenly
we're here talking to Sal what's going
on if Wass to track a flashback because
we already talked to him here didn't we
oh it is a flashback what the truck was
the track to flashback or
this Nono
storytelling this this is the
okay
[Music]
for forch
I know some people were visiting and
picking up
Ma I he said those Nam chores before
yesterday but I didn't realize we were
picking them
up oh
[Music]
why does he not have phone
numbers of these people
like their Twitter or social media
Facebook they must have something
you call them old but they all look so
young so it's not coming
[Music]
across oh why
not some people want to live like on the
outt
or like we in no man's
land are we going to
Hokkaido that much
snow that looks so abandoned as if
geralt ser and Jennifer just left it
behind that looks exactly like that like
that kind of place where they would
be your
geralt finding a new shed be
like which one is it
D no that's not maima that's um one of
the other ones
ma maim look at me
[Music]
you too you
too
oh
o
wow what I glow down but I'm just joking
I I like how normal they look
normal-ish he looks like a Metal Gear
Solid Snake thing
person metal solid gear Metal Gear Solid
metal metal gear Metal Gear Solid what
did I
say what's the right
um pom don't listen to what I
[Music]
say he so handsome that's dle right
my
[Music]
child majima's voice is so old
sounding is that the the same voice as
us
for memory died from my YouTube
chat
refresh fore
[Music]
fore l
okay
fore
for
Fore
foreign foree
oh I wonder
who could
be could it
[Music]
be yeah sorry about
that
fore graduation
incoming
fore
foree
[Music]
fore fore
for
mm
fore
spe
foree
for
what am I supposed to be shocked
family what do you mean his old
family are you saying are you saying
what I think you're saying that the they
that uh uh e might be ichiban's half
brother no right what am
I maybe oh my God I'm making connections
in my
head yeah
okay he already
loved what he
to Wheeling or how you call
it
what that's what I'm
saying
fore fore
[Music]
uhhuh
uhuh that's why that bastard hates me so
much I guess he knows that too from her
from his
mom he thinks he thinks that his whole
life was shitty
because of the father of Ichiban and
then blames Ichiban because Ichiban had
supposedly from his puv I guess a better
life but no he didn't oh he didn't he
just like you know worked hard and just
a positive kind of person like he he's
been for [\h__\h] he's been um stream POV
he's been in jail for what 18 years was
it yeah and he didn't have a mom for
like his whole life so yeah I guess
that's also why he kind of hates akan
too because that's like the other woman
like if if if his father didn't go with
aan then they could have been this happy
family I guess yeah okay now we
understand where all his hatred is
coming from but I still find it's a bit
exaggerated there must be a little bit
more I
think cuz not like ichan had a great
life
[Music]
together you think they'll Bond over
being half Brothers
for
Fore
fore on
who are you saying that
[Music]
to and that's
bad
for foree
[Music]
but I came so far
guys come with me
foree
fore
for
for Fore speee
[Music]
little
bit foree
oh he's disappointed me too me
too oh he's angry huh
is he angry damn he's disor huh
uhuh are we going to fight
them M no they're mad cuz I'm
mad oh
he just I mean come on I
[Music]
mean I mean you got to understand I mean
h i mean he didn't even he didn't even
it was
he come on
oh oh this is so realistic this is so
relatable
[\h__\h] emotional
damage
oh well yeah
we no
[\h__\h]
oh I don't want to fight you
guys we should be besties
[Music]
forever oh
no we made him mad K was passive
aggressive but I say he was request but
not even like he just I mean you I mean
you know what I mean like it wasn't even
like he just
[Music]
he
come it wasn't even passive aggressive
it was just
passive passive disappointment
[\h__\h]
man
foree no no
[Music]
but that was so relatable this situation
is like so
relatable that's why I'm getting
so well
man cuz like we both have issues right
when we're asking for your help and
they're like dude like I got my own
[\h__\h] problems and then you're like
well well [\h__\h] you then for not caring
about my problems and they're like what
do you mean I mean we got our own
[\h__\h]
problems yeah but my problems are I need
your help what you're so mean for not
helping me but they're like well do you
even understand why like oh my God like
you don't understand [\h__\h] ah
oh man they sh off with some big Buffs G
is uh has high as [\h__\h]
agility well how do I nice
music wow violin what I even do they
they they must be so strong let's start
with the spinning Queen maybe no
actually no because they're so
far maybe lower their fertility and
defense he resists it now
should we focus on one or should we try
to get them all one by like one at a no
not not one at a time but like little
bit little bits at a
time CH choose one to focus the yeah
that's what it says here damages an
enemy with leg work that aims at the
vitals May lower their defense and
fertility and he's weak to thunder so
that's actually perfect let's do this he
Don't Run
Away [\h__\h] how can we do this oh it's
canceled nice how can we do this to dieo
dojima oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh okay okay okay okay okay uh miss
being met with a Miss okay can we do
like a nice buff or so do we have
something
um or debuff I guess cuz these are
mostly debuffs
Charming reducing their
resistance now they're already M leave
them Charmed or reduce their
defense
yeah oh I can get out of them I think no
don't out of
[Music]
it Miss did it miss all of
them no it didn't miss um
yeah one of them one of them got it I
think T taer I think got it good good
good
good okay what are you you we uh
only okay only against Thunder
maybe I don't have
[Music]
that lower D wait we want to focus on
one
though which is d
let's do that maybe P mates yeah we
could start with a well he can't call
him so that's
okay I want to make him
bleach first of all that will
help [\h__\h] that will help both me to and
K
you is bleeding let's go perfect
uh greatly if they're
bleeding greatly if they're
bleeding Shadow C
this oh oh okay G is weak against
that
fire okay okay okay okay ah [\h__\h] I
forgot P next time next
[Music]
time oh she dead Dam it I tried to block
oh already cut
scene God I got to press something
right
nice good that was a good punch
so fad maybe this will motivate them to
come with us because they're like oh
fights are
fun this is so fun
actually oh look at her she's so cool
with her
glasses they're all protecting
k a
[Music]
TI yeah I was like where's sa oh she
helping him
up guys he has
cancer for
real oh w w w whoa whoa who
[Music]
whoa okay um
what do we
want do that again Lower the defense
even
more and it's
weak yes full full
full full
prompt
nice but I think the defense thing
didn't
work Cal calm down
kids are F act status
C poor
D oh man
um might need a heal for
[Music]
herself I think only her is
fine game
um is he bleeding over there no ah the
bleed is already
gone
damn next is
Tiger now hold
[Music]
on yeah I'll do it again
there
lag that was a
lag oh my God I can't block these
attacks okay
triple she game is cheating so okay
um May maybe uh this one damage and
increase the part mag uh increase no I
think I'll do this one mli stun I mean
chances are probably
[Music]
low yeah do R2 don't worry don't
worry good no stun but good
damage and then oh die Go's almost down
[Music]
get up can't hit you I'm so wasting him
I couldn't hit him when he was on the
ground
no not
you what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] oh
well still
good okay okay
okay Dao almost dead
die almost dead I like this one cuz it
often crits but I don't know should I do
that
[Music]
or could do this one to boost her
attack heavy too let's do this one oh
wait does she have a skill that does the
KO thing when somebody koos she gets
even more no I don't think she has
that a no this actually she does but
what did k probably
not oh but that's an attack I want to do
anyway so we'll see we'll see we'll see
maybe maybe we're
lucky ah
okay sadly not almost though
almost
can
KO who think go k
who medium heavy possibly maybe even
with a medium what do you
think I know her tag team heals but I
don't think we quite need it
yet I should have done the heavy
one i k
oh that could have done it that could
have done
it PL armor so strong
what's
this bu buffing himself
only oh what you want to have some oh
okay it might have really been uh buff
armor what what what what what
what because they want this to happen
okay where are
you yeah that's why he didn't
die look there's memories in the
background that's why
so we probably can't KO any of them like
in a normal
way one down really not a problem so
far
now TAA is next we
we might need some heal for Z but I
wonder oh we can we can do some GM
[Music]
some ah overtime over
time everybody's so
far maybe maima for last okay I don't
mind but
damn thanks for the membership gift
him plus K is a good
heal you think I should do
this wait this might get three of them I
might be wrong
but uh it it did get free it did get
free of them
okay we're strong against status ailment
too let's
go nice nice
block very very
nice woohoo H oh we can we could call
someone again I guess can
we oh but it's much more expensive oh no
no no cancel cancel we don't need to
call anyone
anymore Tiger Tiger is a in need of a
grapple
[Music]
this one this one this
one this
one this one's
fast I knew it was coming I knew it was
fast but
[Music]
a I can't evasion raised yeah B that's
what it was not agility
evasion four F
Fork it's over there
[Music]
it you say lowest defense but so far it
has only worked one out of two or three
times I
[Music]
think well I'll try
again it would be nice if it works
okay ah defense lowered let's
go
balls w die need of
healing this in that
case I'll do a solo heal
[Music]
him painful
to nobody's having chilling after this
fight well well well if it isn't the
consequences of your
aggressions H wait oh G is right in
front of me we need to go to tiger
[Music]
power medium is honestly not bad and I
just want to make him ble because then
he has a really good
attack that CR yeah there we go that
critically hits him I think if he's
leeding
let's oh did you just
remove everything I worked hard for but
also his Buffs the [\h__\h]
man and now K you st
um who's next
[\h__\h]
no if it was sat on first I could have
like healed him
well uh I I I I can still like get rid
of his ailman uh debuff but I know if I
should just wait for
it yeah he has overtime heal
should
[Music]
I paralysis right there's no ah no
stun that's stun this
[Music]
okay five at least I block three of them
that's pretty
decent
y exciting
go well maybe I could heal
everybody it's not looking so bad
[Music]
H what do you think should
I no
okay does it get rid of
beding okay yeah uh it got rid of it and
Magic is
raed okay you just don't want to Bleed
It seems maybe we can try leaving him
blinded although I want to make him
bleed there's no way he'll get rid of it
again wait yes keep cooking keep
cooking yes bleeding
profusely help me when when do I when
the [\h__\h] was I supposed toess
easy majima not even so strong anymore
he lost his
his his his
power uh so what do we have
wait does
she I know that's Chan that's
chanan chano says the one who can switch
out such has slash resist from armor you
think
so a psychopath still to say that he
never goes
away MAA keeps going after Tito who
seems to resist him and I also I'm also
just good at blocking
okay but yeah that's good he can stay
busy with her I don't mind
this keep them
[Music]
spinning is that really strong on its
own I don't remember 52 52 MP
[Music]
dudeo oh yeah yeah I mean Chito said
who's in the other team who we don't
have here right now and I was looking
for the switch
out skill in in uh son's skill set I was
like oh yeah she doesn't have it get it
get it stack debuffs
uh which
one which
[Music]
one no he's he's bleeding I can't make
him bleed with her but I'll just I'll
just do this I like this
one ah it didn't crit I don't think
that's a crit or is it a crit how do you
know it's a crit is there like do the
numbers look different when it's crits
anyway he's bleeding
so we can do Shadow
cleave yellow damage
okay 681 all right halfway
through oh
oh all right that was nothing that was
nothing majima very disappointed in you
[Music]
sir he resist slashing down oh I see I
see I see that's why I didn't do much
okay um are you still bleeding you're
still bleeding I can can I stop bleeding
I can right it goes from bleeding
profusely to bleeding something else
right I can't I thought I saw it before
that it said something
else well how fast do you think his
bleeding will go
away I can do this one because he has a
status
ailment just one
but
or high chance of causing lead oh oh
this one's also heavy and also status
ailments it's like the the the stronger
version of the flattening pan W opener
ah we're moving the bleed
afterward I'd like to keep the bleed if
possible but it might go away anyway
until it's K's
turn but okay if you say it gives him an
immediate minus L minus free stats
elsewhere
okay I [\h__\h] up though what is Magic
doesn't even use Magic Use
magic
[Music]
man that is so terrible that sucks it
sucks it sucks it sucks
[Music]
stop in your
face
yeah rash
combo ouch not too bad generally both
all of them don't do much damage to me
generally I'm like
pretty feeling pretty sa sure she did
[Music]
um greatly increases your critical
chance anybody weak against pistols
no I'm prepared yeah I can't prepare it
re is good
too much more magical than than my fir
yes yes I remember I was really
struggling with
that can we get them
like
closer no
yeah from from from zero I
think
uh I can do a little bit of a pine
bamboo Plum it might go to both
right it might go from Tiger to
majima Saima to majima
[Music]
but and then even if it goes to my he's
weak against it so it'll be a nice nice
okay but but I'm so going to miss come
[Music]
on okay I got two and it all went to
Saima wait was 471 the total
ow that was not
much that was not so much yo yo I'm
still so
high let's break his jewels J
could I break his jewels can I break
your
Jewels should I
try or one of these 30
35 maybe leaves him
burnt the the burning might be nice
TP what's the prompt oh The Prompt was
easy for 10 and he did got
[Music]
burnt no why not why is my birthday
happy birthday
stris
a over yeah I noticed that too that that
sucks I thought he would get
both can they not have
both
[\h__\h] majima just mad because Dao is like
a younger version of him
now just a little bit just from like
style and
Vibes just a little bit not personality
though um
[Music]
ah I'm coming for you yeah 700 good good
good good good good good yum yum yum yum
yum let him cook oh this one maybe one
here
oh
[Music]
strong might leave him dead for now uh
and when it's uh uh why is she dancing
like that when it's her turn she can
revive him I want to do some damage now
you
know you
know what should I do what should I do
oh
they are
standing what oh okay did 500 to side
and missed on
majima was ah right he was guarding I
didn't even see it okay uh does she have
a survival
[Music]
skill no right no no no that be
crazy I hopefully have one
[Music]
right what
ah there we go we can use the this one I
think full full
HP why
not welcome
back yeah for boss fight where do I get
more of those though I want now that I
used it up I need more of those Revival
items are they at the like the pharmacy
I don't think I could KO him so I'm just
going to go for actually never mind
[Music]
maybe now I'm going to go for this
one cuz it raises her
attack can't KO him
anyway no matter how much damage I do do
you think he's ready for that cut scene
fight oh yeah he totally is
you guys made me worri just now saying K
needs a heal he's
[Music]
fine oh oh [\h__\h] wait he actually he did
I actually he did need a heal I'm going
to cry if I die we just can't let
him y
y be
H it be H one more time him
[Laughter]
okay
St doing me a big
concern I was mashing so hard thank you
thank you that was so clutch
oh I was
desperate um this should be
good I was like oh we don't need heal
but actually I didn't realize that we're
going into that kind of fight
afterwards only HED four really majima
really you might as well just go back
into the shed right now maima you're
you're disappointing me
let's load up K with another
[Music]
heal majima dis majima you're
old go watch some anime in the CH majima
or go play some Yakuza
games okay uh MAA was weak against fire
the but her fire attack is really weak
so not even worth it I doubt we can char
AR him
so running out of mp2 let's just try a
[Music]
crit here
we didn't crit still good
[Music]
damage how old is maim like
60 he does give me a little bit older
Vibes than uh k
ooh no MP but all I really want to do is
this
anyway MP coming soon ah no bleed so
sad but it's okay we're we're going to
be fine his evasion is going to be
annoying
though
she that invasion is annoying but I
have't attacked that never
misses skill never misses ignores
enemy's
guard should I just do that but I have
so many strong fire attacks that he's
weak
against maybe buff with
kidu all right why not don't don't walk
away don't you walk away
now everybody's attack race everybody's
not only k
critical but if they miss yeah that's so
sad if they
miss
um who's next ah s is next she can
heal I'm going to give him a burn
now
burn burn burn why
not why
[Music]
not ah no MP
[\h__\h] nah I think that's
[Music]
unnecessary I want to save my team I
just do
[Music]
this he's doing ninja
things oh no do I have get rid of them
[Music]
first but she needs she needs MP too
we're in the recovery phase of this
fight sad they're much
weaker how much not just one hit right
like a normal hit is probably not enough
right let's try to do some AOE with Kido
or so soonish soon soon soon
he didn't have this move and keep on me
W I don't know where the [\h__\h] he picked
that up
but
he's he's learned something
new okay next is
[Music]
K maybe maybe she can take one of these
down what do you think let's try with in
collaboration with
want to help yeah I thought so okay easy
easy easy
easy and he can do like a little bit of
an AOE
perhaps [\h__\h]
yeah wait did the, 400 go on to the tiny
little clone and it missed on maima
no that would have been such a great
great
crit you piece of
[\h__\h] oh that's going to hit hard yeah
1,200 that's what you get yeah ooh
attack buff nice nice
nice weak weak weak weak weak yeah I
still think he's weak did you just see
that did nothing that was
like that was like a fly in my
face that's all I felt
[Music]
I don't know her attacks I wish she had
a stronger fire
[Music]
attack got up he resists
it if only we were behind
him well I'll just go for this one might
not be like extreme damage but
Invasion yeah that's what's going to
happen godamn
Invasion he's he's weak but his invasion
pisses me
[Music]
off but
K is about to
unleash another big move
and you cannot run away from
this
try I want to take you back to Tokyo
2,894 I he sits there
[Music]
okay oh his evasion is
gone his evasion is
gone this is probably a really fast
one hey you want me to do human grating
um gr him right back when an enemy Gres
you grade him right back damages them
with a high chance of okay oh we can do
that this one is no prompt right the
rainbow ones are no prompt I think
or were they did they have a prompt it's
a good cut
scene does it have a
[Music]
prompt looks like an
instrument no promps
okay oh no no that's gore that's just
Gore oh not with ma now I feel really
bad oh he's almost
dead he's so dead head oh it's
[Music]
over that was actually kind of
disappointingly
easy kind of disappointingly easy it
just took a lot of
time it's over oh that was so
easy a a
expected a bit
more those stupid plant people in the
dungeon gave me more
trouble yeah it's good though it's good
that we're not struggling it's good we
we're
prepared
up level
up oh big ass bird
that's
me you new attack so
guys oh
he needs to
[Music]
rest I feel like that fight was
story-wise
so
unnecessary like they just wanted to put
a fight there
they were so they felt so attacked so
easily it's a guy thing it's a Yakuza
[Music]
thing that was fun
yeah was nice to see them
[Music]
for that coat looks like a lady's
coat maybe it's c
[Music]
that's not
true not at
[Music]
all he feels guilty
you're going to clean it up
[Music]
oh
man then come with
[Music]
me that's it
yeah that must have been it but that
also implies again yo I knew you weren't
going to come along cuz you guys suck I
just wanted to fight you one more time
but I knew I knew you weren't going to
you weren't going to disappoint me
anyway I knew it just came here to
fight they're like what did you just
[Music]
say they really did not take
yeah
[\h__\h]
maybe maybe we need to get rid of
YouTubers
guys maybe YouTubers are curs to
society YouTubers ruin
everything I'm sorry for ruining your
life guys so great vtuber
disolution down with the vtubers down
with the vtubers
down yeah okay maybe it's only a a
specific a specific type of
YouTubers or generally a spe specific
type of YouTubers could it could have
been a a non vtuber too could have just
been any YouTuber who just makes their
whole
Channel like the playground of putting
out scandals of people to ruin
everybody's reputation and lives yeah
okay then maybe YouTubers are allowed to
survive and continue doing their jobs
y y
woohoo well anybody whose Daily Business
is ruining other people's
business need to
go well you guys are all noticing now
I've been running around for days now in
the
city
foree that's
SE now
[Music]
I want to get all of these really
quickly can
I I heard it's dangerous over here
though let's
see T CH
speak he's looking at me though he
doesn't care about you he's so SM ch ch
cute I want to give him dog
food ooh
soundtrack oh it's not in here
[Music]
what a gorgeous
view yeah just one dog says K every time
I look at the sea memories of Oka keep
flooding back into my
mind oh man I want to go to okina
playing with the kids catching fish for
dinner I want to go you know the other
day uh which which artist I think it was
was it Me senpai's
artist I saw their tweet
of I think like Oka they went like
diving or or just snorkeling
maybe somewhere in Okinawa and I saw it
I was like oh my God I'm so interested
tell me like other fish they're
interesting and so
on I think in the moldes there's
definitely a bigger variety but from
what I saw it looked pretty cool I do
want to go to I've never been to OK I
lived in Japan for 3 years
never been to the south of Japan like
not that far I've been to somewhat
close uh uh area but not not down there
and yeah inava is like super
hot and like it's like I I would compare
it from what I've seen to Hawaii Vibes
it's like the Hawaii of Japan
I really want to go you think Oka has
more tasty
fish this compared to fishes in tasty
but I want pretty
fish no but they they still certainly
have like uh even if the fishes are not
as colorful maybe they they uh
definitely have like you know
interesting stuff like turtles and stuff
I want to check it out OK for next
vacation
maybe well I think it would be cool to
go to Okinawa uh with a group of like
Hol
members maybe next time even when I'm in
Japan a bit
longer
maybe maybe
maybe yeah that would be dope I should
get my diving license until then then I
got to start now how long does it take
does anybody have a diving license in
the chat I know it's kind of rare but
anybody how long does it take to get one
how many like
lessons I don't of course you don't I do
really vas yansen really I don't I I
don't think you would lie to
me tell me how long does it take a week
for advanced diving I got an army
oh oh that's a thing you do in the Army
I do it I took two weeks for me but you
can have it Rush oh really oh it doesn't
take much time at
all I've been going diving dive training
for
[Music]
years oh interesting exciting I got it
when I was in
Thailand like oh I guess they have yeah
Ocean
true but I got to do it in the
[Music]
lake it depends on classes like two
weeks on average if you go fast and then
you have to schedule the actual license
separately
ah but yeah the good thing is if I do it
in Austria it will probably be a lot
cheaper than in any of these places like
Okinawa or
so well Thailand is a famous spot for
people to get license
really I doubt anyone else in H has a
diving license to well yeah we can just
go snorkeling but if I go to okav you
know then I wouldn't want to miss out on
at least one solo dive then even if I
got to go without them I I'll go with
like random people or
so oh can I go alone well I I need to
borrow the equipment hey even if you
have a diving license do you still need
to go with like a a guide
person can you not go alone I
wonder never go alone yeah I mean yeah
it's probably not really desirable
anyway unless you have the Dive Master
oh yeah surely they have rentals all
over I wonder how expensive it is anyway
anyway
anyway anyway oh I got to do remind me
guys I got to let's try to get license
soon
TM
within it's almost
May let's get it within May the waters
might be cold though oh no oh no May
June
is
yeah that'll be
good 50 bucks for two tanks 3 hours dive
in Shallow 10 M Water 10 m only
the [\h__\h] I want to go 30 m 50
100 I'm not going to go to too t too
dangerous places no worries I I'm too
much of a chicken to hang around sharks
and all that anyway I just want to dive
in more chill
Waters I want to become Wawa the diver
yeah I'll become the DLC of Dave the
diver
GAA no I'm staying away from GAA she
scares
me samian chambles no don't go cave
diving I haven't thought about it so
don't worry but I don't know does it is
it interesting if you say it's dangerous
then you mean caves that are completely
underwat or caves that are only like
half on the
water completely on the water does sound
indeed
scary C diving where if you guys all say
that there must be a lot of videos on
people dying while doing cave diving
like videos as in
reports I guess I'm going to go down
that rabbit hole I've I've seen videos
of people you know dying in like normal
like uh not water cave diving but like
the the crawling through
uh dry caves so to
say but I don't know about like under
underwater
[Music]
caves lots of stories spelunking
splunking that sounds funny I think it
was called something
else but anyway yeah the NY putty cave
incident for example that's
terrifying absolutely terrifying
I watched people die okay that's not
what I
mean I I watched like yeah the document
documentaries on
that so anyway playing with the kids
catch you fish for dinner a life of
peace and content content oh content
creation let's go if only I could turn
back
time even just for a little and here I
am now sounding like an old man my age
is catching up on me oh man
K look look I'm so
strong level six and level
seven oh I want that
treasure give me
[Music]
[Applause]
wait wait I was like wait I'm also wait
never mind I thought I was still like
level 35 or so never mind I can handle
this I don't know why I panicked so much
we're good probably maybe
maybe I wish I could could get oh
there's one what there's so
[Music]
many can you go over there
thank you thank you maybe I'll get him
yeah I think I'll get
him higher level than
maim
[Music]
I'm seems like you have a
says um K don't
die you s Baka don't die
[Music]
wait a moment
[Applause]
a
[\h__\h] that
worked maybe that wasn't the oh ideal
way to do it but it
[Music]
worked oh we got raided by by k y p Mor
the one and
only I guess that was
uh raided the wrong stream what do you
mean did she not want to raid me RA her
the Raiders the freaking Vault what she
raided the freaking
Vault ah she raided the wrong
place what
VOD you can rate a
VOD huh I don't think you can do
that
accident uh but I was going to say you
guys just come from
like a VCR finale thing right wasn't
there today was like a
finale
right well you know what I want to
do kind of want to
call
him that hits everybody right yeah I'm
spending so much money let's go
[Applause]
building oh yeah I wouldn't mind playing
rust again if Amit would be
there Amit was like the only one who I
really am and and Ura cuz wasn't I also
kind of late back then joining the rush
party I'm in wa
were taking care of me a little
bit heaven
sounds like a
fgo
season or
game anyway thanks for coming dead beats
we just did something really cool in the
story and now
we're I don't know what we're going to
do next actually good
question
kajima what do you want
what do you
[Music]
want just
Sho why do all your party members have
the same jobs as mine I thought they
were fitting
I don't
know
ow but they're going to reach max level
of their uh classes soon so I might
change them
[Applause]
soon St St St stun nice we stunned like
almost
everybody ooh the rage she's raging so
hard she might rage quit if we're not
careful I she going to die like for real
R quitting as I'm
dying soon
TM great mind think Al like cute so
this this all right let's clean up
here
[Music]
die dub stab we love dub stab at G
area of
effect
ow you don't you do you don't why
not aren't we all vibing to this very
very fitting even if you listen to
Dubstep in your free time at least
during Yakuza I would
say it's
making it's a great addition to the
atmosphere stop dying son please
[Music]
W what why are you not
dying follow
up why not nobody follow up everybody so
far you guys I had crazy
dream I was actually really excited by
it for once having a supposedly good
dream so H Fest again again Hol
Fest my second Hol Fest related
dream and we had some like it was uh on
on the day we did rehearsal apparently
on the same day as the real concert and
I was like backstage and we had some
special guests
and and and
and I I go backstage and I see
there's like it wasn't really clear in
my brain who who they were um but there
were some famous actresses from
Hollywood that give like Mean Girls
Vibes like that kind of actress at least
one from Mean Girls I think or so or or
or some something like that they kind of
looked like that but I my my brain
wasn't clear on who they were
um but they were there and they were
like special guests and they were like
oh we heard the rehearsal and H yeah it
was so good and and then they said
something about Maran tonet and I don't
know what that was about and then and
then one of them pointed out that I'm
the one who can speak German and so they
spoke a little bit of German to me and
I'm like yeah oh my God that's me wow
these famous people they like me that's
so
cool and then I kind of offered to show
him around and stuff and like hang out
with them and I said I'll be right back
and then and then I laughed a little bit
and and and then I I found a cat which
was at the same time one of our special
guest actors like a person actually but
in this moment it was a cat for some
reason and I I had to transport the cat
oh wait wrong he I'm so confused with my
ts s might
die he might
die there was some cat and I had to
protect it and transported but it was
like freaking out cuz I had to transport
it through the Holo Fest
Hall when there were a lot of people all
over yeah but then anyway so I don't
remember most of this anymore but it was
fun because there were cats and some
famous actresses and they were
cute I need to stop
transing brain
empty brain so empty
[Applause]
our very first tangent
death but it's going to be
okay it's going to be
[Music]
okay yashi
y an action pack
movie but I I needed to get the business
done the cat business done before I
could go back and meet the the cute
actresses so
that was a bit stressful and I don't
think in the dream I ever saw them again
wait I should heal
myself what do you think brought on that
dream no idea this time I have no idea
cuz hame is quite a while ago at this
[Music]
point I don't know why those actresses
were in my
dreams that is weird
me
here this fight is taking too long cuz
he had like a million
[Music]
minions he's strong
[Applause]
dud he stuned her too so she can't even
heal herself all right all right it's
tag team
time enem is next again I hope you won't
kill another person wait that wasn't
even that much damage but my evasion was
buffed and it helped me rather
let's
[Music]
go I never get all three of
them
[Music]
never this is so
R I don't want to heal her but I have
to how much does she need maybe a quas
have a little
quas oh her KY skill right could have
used that oh
well oh my
[Music]
God huh
oh that is so going to kill him extreme
power already and then even more if is
bleeding eh what I expected more than
that you little piece of
now I can
[Music]
detect if I lost this battle just
because I have my guard down I had my
guard up when I
was uh in that boss fight
and now we get a nice reward first
one
oh going to sell
that this might hopefully be a better
one
okay all of your base stats increase
[Music]
forever
willpower normally that would go to
number
[Music]
I guess
we increasing will power maybe makes her
heal
stronger or we keep it until the other
team's
back for
[Music]
now I love this
song
O Copy
[Music]
it's a bit expensive but it low it
doesn't make me drunk and it still heals
a
lot
ooh 250 is almost too much coffee
assortment for a
[Music]
gift should I get these anyway might as
well nice stuff that you're selling oh a
b
way I know poy L never tried it I just
don't drink coffee in
[Music]
general taking for a spin anywhere
there's a wheel
Bingo
wooo son he likes Ferris wheels who
[Music]
doesn't sell something
else oh
flowers might as well get some new
ones I'm here for
[Music]
interactions nice radio too bad it's
only these two
songs fisher of
men the fishing p
with
Bingo Sunny often goes to the fishing p
with jungian apparently he gets pretty
chatty when he's there hey
cute
H got to be careful there's strong
enemies over
there is there a restaurant here too
no h
ah wait it's over
[Music]
there son he overlooked and I am under
looking even among so many son he sees
something unique in each and every
flower her admiration for them is pretty
endearing
how do I take this picture
again
uh wait maybe I put get closer
or I always forget
[Music]
wow I'm want to roll Z always for really
examines his brothers that may be why
the shopkeeper who remembers his
face wait you
mi can you make
me prepare
items
[Music]
yes entire party yes I think the 100 one
is
okay Prem let's make just
uh these
ones yeah I just maybe one of these
and then one more of
these
nice nice these would be great too but
I'm missing
pineapples oh no mango in this
case mangoes we need more mangoes do
sell
mangoes the [\h__\h] get those watermelons
on my face
[Music]
do you do the same stuff oh
H hute
gifts
[Music]
um I want to go to that book but there's
a or memory there's a strong enemy over
[Music]
there don't stop
heyo oh oh I did it full name ion so
it's a maritime museum that's pretty
neat ah wait I've been
I've been in there before in this ship I
think this in
yukama yeah I think I've been in
here I just noticed this
now wait I've also been over yeah why do
I why did I not notice this last time we
played like like a dragon number
one it's a long time ago
M Maritime Museum that's pretty neat
yeah having a museum in a boat about
boats is amazing yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah boats always make me think of uni a
ship building town that faces the stto
Inland seat
ahuh oh wow it's
pretty k a quite calming Place
surrounded by the Sea and mountains I
can see how hard got wound up there it's
also the place where I was officially
declared dead oh though I always think
of com to as my hometown I I think to
think my life would come to an end
elsewhere I guess it's not all that bad
it's a good place to rest in peace yeah
but you're not actually resting in peace
there
[Music]
dude run run
run nice you got the
memory there's another one over there
[Music]
careful careful careful oh it's
here I've lived in Oklahoma for 4 years
but never been on in that boat do you
recommend well I mean I say I've been in
it but I didn't make use of the museum I
think m- oh the ferris wheel yeah that
view wa this is so to
I don't know if it's worth
it well I haven't experienced the museum
now this is quite the stage I bet they
use they put on shows with this much
space I wonder if it's possible to build
a ring here a
ring what just imagining a ring still
gets my blood pumping after all that's
so random
dude why would you think of a wrestling
ring
here what I am the one the only dragon
mask of course course I only started
wrestling for taichi's sake but after
that strange turn of events I actually
fought in the ring while I was in fukoka
against a real wrestler that was a long
time ago at this rate dragon mask will
Fade Into Obscurity I forgot to drink my
[Music]
tea man damn it in that case I'd like to
wrestle one last time it'll be the
retirement match of the decade and if
possible i' like it to be against TIY
now that he's all grown up give him
something to remember me
[Music]
by my tea is
cold I only got like two sips of it when
it was
warm dreamss
[Music]
[Applause]
W thank you thank you oh thank you so
much son's been wanting to add some more
plant life to K uh maybe someday they'll
have their own little farm
a w
[Music]
it's Bingo time baby I'm just addicted
to getting these conversations to fill
out my
bingo pet wasting food
[Music]
a I wasted so much food last night and I
didn't even want to it wasn't my my
intention for people who don't have
Twitter or didn't see my tweet yesterday
after the stream I did end up ordering
food and then I got something very
different uh from the same restaurant
but oh like three or four times the food
of what I wanted and not even one I
wanted
so yeah I mean I one in some way I was
winning cuz I got way more food than I
paid for but in another way it wasn't
what I wanted so I still ate a bunch of
it
but oh I got full so fast so it's also
like fast food so it can't really be
warmed up no no no no no sadly
no sadly no it was a weird order whoever
ordered the order that I got
honestly weird taste was like a million
chicken nuggets and a vegan
burger I never had a vegan burger before
vegan
Patty and then also a lot of fries
yeah yeah million chicken
nuggets maybe was for a party not it was
weird CH just really love chicken
nuggets I guess s was a firm believer I
never tting food apparently he once
pulled off a triple axle just to save a
meal wait that's a wait that's a
different way of saving
food that sounds like there was some
food falling from
somebody falling down dropping their
food and you did a triple axle to to
save it as in catching
it no no leave me alone leave me alone
leave me alone
high
maintenance let's
goo s found a four Le Club but said he
was happy with his life and would rather
someone else have it he's got a
surprisingly big heart
a what does that have to do with high
maintenance you'll never know
[Music]
okay pretty
satisfied but there's another one here
[Music]
is it
upstairs
yes maybe we can buy some cloes
here the back
shop
Bing can you record a short video
announcing the return on phop for
Twitter with your Bal sound
maybe pyo's bag is sturdy enough to fend
of a knife apparently it's designer but
something tells me the knife proofing
was her
[Music]
idea
ooh six
star I need this stuff anyway
huh
[Music]
ooh am I in need of this
already I can't afford it at
[Music]
least no special effect kind of mid okay
I'll just get one
set just one
set or maybe maybe that's all I want
maybe that's all I want
thanks we can get the dress a great
jacket
great check it it's for
[Music]
ladies there you go a bag well that's
perfect that's
a I'm like there sugar daddy oh God but
that was thousand yen was like eight
bucks seven
bucks a cheap bag for being in the store
like that
[Music]
oh by the way when I was saying his
jacket his uh coat looked like a ladies
coat it was mostly just because of how I
guess he accentuated his waist with that
belt besides that it does look like a
normal men's Cod yeah was fine no hate
no
hate oh guess we'll go to KAS
apartment yeah his figure was is very
accentuated showing off is very thin
waste 600 fire damage rocket launcher
yeah that's not
bad but that's really not bad
y y all story time
oh are they changing their mind or
cuz that's
over or someone's stalking
them he said I not oh no that's when I
was there did somebody film it and put
it on the [\h__\h] Channel on YouTube no
you you were supposed to stop
[\h__\h] yeah no that is a voice changer
she stopped to use it so now
now
aan that aan took over and is using
voice
changer oh joh I'm going to rip your
head
off no this is going to cause some big
misunderstandings
for
[Music]
God damn these
YouTubers mhm
for so sick of your
[Music]
[\h__\h] who the it's the [\h__\h]
go [\h__\h]
yourself wow even normal people are
[\h__\h]
[Music]
uhhuh did you also see us fight and then
leave those threee dudes behind
[Music]
B them report them can we not report
that channel on YouTube for like slander
and
[\h__\h]
for
yeah information
[Music]
case h
yes yes they will
[Music]
oh live
stre I they GNA
[Music]
all right we're going to no that's a
trap n that's actually a
trap don't you think that's a trap cuz
like they know we're watching this so
obviously we're going to go to the
Salia uh Clan office as well oh so
obvious but like we're still going to go
he went with that
knowledge got to beat him
up got to beat him up beat him up
[Music]
but they don't
even they're not even thinking about it
being a trap it's so obvious that's my
first
thought why are you guys playing so
dumb I don't
[Music]
know
meow
Maga can I change this oh I can add
songs
here what is Daytona USA
what
this I can't hear it no
[Music]
preview only in
Japanese let's listen to the radio I was
told to listen to it anyway
to six Let's Go
Radio
oh what's this
ah is this like
the English
[Music]
version well it isn't from
Hawaii and doesn't have subtitles
probably right aloha kakaka
aloha
aloha aloha Al
okay then then maybe this one
instead
okay yeah
okay
uh St
[Music]
is the
playing damn Cofe machine's busted again
oh hey Aloha welcome how's it sun up or
sun down it's your favorite Howley Mike
hula for another episode of seg waves
kicking things off with some good news
everybody give a warm Aloha our very own
DJ PP stew is returned from the Land of
the Rising Sun hey that's right brother
took a trip out to visit my cousin to C
and now I'm back top knot and all and
that reminds me we got fans all across
the globe so to all of our Japanese fans
out there this one's for you Amen to
that cuz I got a lot of love for the JP
first off the food out there is as good
as they say the curry what ACC is this I
was all over Tokyo Island boy in the big
city Uptown downtown underground malls
Temple the back front alleys you name it
you know P the one time I was in Japan
back in the 80s there was a lot of real
estate flying around change in hands you
know not that I was in the middle of it
or anything I was actually on a huge
budget but uh good thing I wasn't on a
huge diet cuz one of the things that
stuck out to me was the fast food way
better than the states or at least the
mainland service quality presentation
tell me I'm not crazy here PE I don't
know my the portion size over there I
got to order the same thing three times
times just to get full well then why not
just order three different things ah
figure of speech Howe oh I'm yanking you
buddy anyway you had have tried some
fast food over there so what do you
recommend for all our listeners out
there where was it you were staying
there uh kamaro oh I was place man but
in kamaro let's see huh for fast food it
was between wild Jackson wet kitchen and
smile Burger I remember smile Burger I
don't know about any of those other ones
though ah wet kitchen's new it's
like in terms of food plenty of soup and
Ice hold on wait a minute are you saying
that soup is not a food soup is if you
don't it's a drink something a handan
like one beer don't it yeah it's
true no this a
food they don't even have a soundboard
yeah so boring boring yapping about
food we'll listen to more later
I'm sure they have nicer topics
to oh
already you guys in the waiting room
uhhuh
uh-huh
for Fore
[Laughter]
he's
dead
oh 60 80,000 people
watching
[Music]
no 200 200,000
she
thoughe
fore spee
what is gonna
say is she hogging the
phone why is she holding it like
why is she holding it like that we can't
watch properly like the other people
around
her
[Music]
for they're just
listening I'd want to
[Music]
see for
he's reading a
[Music]
script now we're watching
fore
[Music]
foree
fore fore
fore for
who the [\h__\h] is paying for that
[Music]
oh it's like
tweets that say
like oh two birds with one stone thank
you
ab and
Yak as long as all the Yakuza and other
dangerous shitty people disappear then
it's
okay they're just like excited oh yeah
get rid of those [\h__\h] yaku [\h__\h] him
get rid of all of them
par
is that
legal didn't we didn't we say that like
didn't we already come to the conclusion
yesterday that one country can't give
their nuclear waste to another country
for
disposal and then yeah
now they're announcing it publicly what
what yeah wouldn't the US government do
something they will make it legal yeah
okay but even if you got Japanese
government on your side do do you think
they would have US Government on their
side
too I don't know just P kind of
power I don't know realistic that
is but we're just going to ignore
that
[Music]
formali the same comment
are we just waiting for them to
endam and leave the
building thought we were going to
interrupt
them
for
B
[Music]
this why revived them
yeah you're just changing the name
doesn't change
the Who You Are
music really
hot why are they naming it that what's
the
point just so that I don't have yakaza
in their name
anymore but
hello what's I guess they'll probably
explain to us what the point is
remember
that electric Balo
you were
saying
remember that group that murdered the
founder the former Governor of Tokyo
yeah we're going to let a Yakuza Clan
Rebrand to that it doesn't sound so good
does
it
son you are the spinning
queen young and lean only
17 I don't know what the actual word
there was
great right I know I know I know I know
almost all of them half
dead a young and free that was
it let's go let's go let's go
combo son has the best moves she did
yeah I do I do like a lot of them moves
yeah um
[Music]
oh oh it's just cute oh oh hey there's
even more people waiting there in the
back and one is uh shirtless
topless do I look like a baseball
or what
that AOE was so
sick now we getting
series you survived it
somehow you were probably just out of
the
AOE easy peasy let
how weak are
you very weak Y what next next
round oh
oh maybe we can get all
sir we got them
wall as if they didn't just watch what
went down right before
them you should not all stay in one
bundle
charm good really good uh Spin to Win
strategy
collateral
Dam and ah another one collateral
Dam and here we go this one's a bit more
serious I
[Music]
think don't don't move
guys time
all right all right all right they were
about to move
away got to be
fast no he might why are you running
away oh they're all oh my God even the
boss is
Charmed even the boss is
Charmed stream
Charmed grapple
[Music]
oh well I'll go straight to the boss and
whatever sometimes I can hit those
people on the ground sometimes not ah
[\h__\h] oh
well some love who's not in love with
Sony I'm in
love I am so in
[Music]
love actually probably can just do a
normal
attack H comi comi com okay
[Music]
tring
be
cute not so
[Music]
bad when it starts out with them on the
floor you can just kick them how what
what button is kicking them
I'm I I I hate that attack I can never
get the PRS I'm I'm done with
that I don't want to use that
anymore let's try
this what are we getting agility lowered
okay better than [\h__\h]
willpower triangle square and
circle H it are you saying in that order
triangle square circle triangle square
circle or just I know that those buttons
are the ones that make damage if that's
what you're
saying are you saying it has to be in
that
order triangle stoms down
really really I feel like I was pressing
triangle
[Music]
what we loaded oh wait that's evion
never mind you good you
good wait he resist [\h__\h] I was acting
too fast but what about the fire what
about the
fire oh is that whisper
lag why why why I'm playing on a [\h__\h]
PS5 oh he's Charmed from like the whole
battle
damn why why why why why why why why lag
why lag
though this dude is a damage SP well he
was also really unlucky to be Charmed by
[Music]
me
for and you think the PS5 is weak than
my
PC I thought
this that fight was easy too I need to
get weak
have you tried pushing instead of
falling baby's
pushing that' be
funny but you guys didn't even try
pushing
this feels very
familiar great
Lo waste my time
no go back
there not
there ah he went
back ah man it only got
one the back one
[Music]
too of course it does almost all Y is
the game you fight at the
headquarters I didn't play so many so
it's like for me I didn't know I don't
know it's like that
[Music]
common at least it was blind that's fair
right I would say so
too n
nice don't want to waste my mp on these
dudes ready to die he gets his together
critical hit rate
raise you think that's going to help
you I where his bones break
nice this whole location is such nice
Ambiance he's so
pretty you finally made it was getting
tired of waiting could have come to me
for
Fore let's [\h__\h]
go hold hold
one is already Charmed we're going to do
this
anyway okay it lowered the defense of
that dude probably not even so
meaningful but oh
[Music]
well yeah
yeah if that dude stops moving
[Music]
power every bit
helps yeah you guys are Charmed by me
too you just don't realize that it's a a
deep
why would you not want to be chared by
me you're fine with it
right yes of course you
[Music]
are let's lower his fertility we love
doing that don't we and he's weak to
electricity
right, 300 we got a crit
baby but we did not lower his defense oh
surprising
[Music]
huge huge damage huge huge huge
damage nice
follow wo motion Matrix wee look at that
[Music]
steel
he was that enough it doesn't have to be
all the way right just on my
side
sheesh I was mashing so hard I became
mashed
potatoes sorry so I I I always think a
bit too
late
um what was it electricity I don't have
electricity for
yall too bad
I guess I just have to say it ask for it
and then he does
it I ask you kindly to please
bleed he's almost there
nice
kick nice follow
up if sakan is the one who takes you
down then you must be really
embarrassed oh but she's not okay only Z
would have followed
up just wanted to give Z the time to
Fair
okay some nice Treasures War
gos War God's
Keystone 1 2 3 4 5 6 seven you make me
feel like
11 K-pop reference that's seven star for
son a jacket said to have been won by an
Unstoppable F
FAL
yo
sick she gets a [\h__\h] uh seven star
jacket did I count that right yes I
did be before everybody else get like
six star jackets he yo chance of agility
buff at the start of the CH
amazing are we going to get more of this
please hi do we have to
fight seems like I don't have to fight
all of them out here oh oh was that all
of them did they just come together oh I
think they
did Tools
in
sick
sick two per
chapter optional but if you want to
grind
chap so Sunny is just like the first
one we don't have many chapters left and
what about the other gang on the other
side of the globe
[Music]
there also healing for every buff you
get is very broken
oo are at the end of their respective
dungeon
uhhuh a you mean oh like the oklahama
dungeon at the end of
it
well I don't know if I can get to
that we're probably already so strong it
would be Overkill to get seven star for
everybody
probably that probably
unnecessary CU how many levels do those
dunge have I finished the second ones
how many are there three if it's three
then
[Music]
okay more than free would actually be
kind of crazy
nice ah okay only one more no that's
okay I might be able to do
that F in particular is really good for
him laxes the timing needed for per
cards reduces the
damage well as long as we don't switch
back to
Hawaii by the end of the stream then I
can do the Kido one
but yeah it really
depends really
depends
no DS but those a post game you know I
don't usually play post
game you are the spinning Queen but
there so far apart boring boring
I think it's s just after this oh well
understandable it's been a
while y
y y yay
[Music]
next week by the way besides Girls Talk
girls talk is happening but in another
Yakuza stream is also
happening but um generally I think I'm a
bit busy next
week
so
uh I I might have a lot of short streams
or
yes not going to be so
much at least two days
off probably probably just two I I
probably can't get myself to take more
than two days off
but we'll see but don't expect 50 hours
gameplay next
week that's not going to happen we all
know that
I want to get some stuff
done you
know wait I should have healed
S I don't know I also want to record all
those shorts for
example all the shorts that I want to
record
and the the n and theik so much to
[Music]
do you can't right to me thank you
you yeah the dances I can't forget about
them ideally maybe I'll record them
tomorrow
already tomorrow is Monday
right I want to play all's game too that
that will be one thing that's coming
this week I'll play all's cute little
game
with I think the release was uh delayed
to 22nd but that's fine cuz I think
Monday is
20it no Monday is 22nd maybe I'll do it
on on Tuesday yeah days with all on
Tuesday
[Music]
perhaps yes I could have killed them
maybe I didn't miss
no in a few
hours I want it does it cost money or is
free they say is it on Steam do they
show the price on
Ste what do you mean strike so what are
you talking about
you talking about the
P
$7 okay that's not
much
what no just
normal thank for the membership
the the V of the
F oh guys if you if you have a streaming
ticket and for some reason you didn't
watch the VOD of Fest yet oh
nice um then here's a reminder it's
ending
today good to know
today today today
today
today yo these weapons holy [\h__\h] we're
like legit in an RPG
game
like s jacket yo we straight up skipping
six star and going straight to Seven
Star what is
this so
Boost Physical attack damage at Max HP
oh
yo good that I did not buy equip like
new jackets and stuff for everybody like
the six star
stuff if there's a heal then there's a
boss I think or they're just being super
nice oh you're about to begin a series
of battles
okay a one on two stream
with yeah I don't know what
about I wouldn't know what
about I'm always open for uh invitations
though always I told them that
too if you ever want to stream together
just you
know oh
oh the phone
guy
coward that reminds
[Music]
me won't happen won't happen I have plot
armor the the the book
club oh they're scared are they they
don't have much
motivation unlike me the book club I
have a small group but it might be good
this
way and it's funny because the group
basically consists of
two popular pairings
now but I don't know if uh it's
realistic to do it this month still
probably
not must probably be within May or
so not even worth killing him right now
now you know what let me focus on the
boss a little
bit wait where's the
boss you supposed to be the boss the
boss out of this group I guess okay well
then you don't think they
read
well well it is in inde not them but I
mean it's not completely out of the
question that they would join a book
club is
it what is
this let's inflict bleed
first didn't go to the boss sadly
nice manga is
reallying I just I think right
I just wanted to see how much damage
that
does count too
KY is
next maybe that will just die on his
blood yo boss is bleeding let's
go rocket launcher is that a rocket
launcher or
is
or what
I missed cuz I was looking at my sound
thing I'll give you that one but that
was the first of these kind of prompts
that I've ever
missed I didn't even have much of an
impact too bad too bad for you
[Music]
nice I can see into the future
hting those around
me can take a little a little bit of
action of
the oh no he's dying what what are you
trying to
do trying to have me blow my nose in
that piece of Club he saying my nose is
running you want to help me with that
that's so nice of
[Music]
no you you probably wanted me to the
paint not going to happen [\h__\h] 19 months
thank
you super long extended
Katana White
St you going to you going oh dude you're
going to hurt your hips you need you'll
need a hip replacement if you do stunts
like that be care
careful what are you
doing what are you doing old
man you just look funny to me and now
you're on a
rampage Clan
Lieutenant okay that was kind of cool
I'll give you that bro than he's a movie
star holy man oh
see yeah that reach looks
insane
medium oh that's good this
good expect a bit
[Music]
more strong these dudes have decent
amount of HP holy
[\h__\h] are we having a sweet little fan
meet and greet
here I think I should finish one of
these
smaller fries that are almost dead I can
[\h__\h] I
can't glory to the men
okay nice
[Music]
B damage are you making fun of her
damage it's not too
[Music]
bad I need to call someone really quick
can you guys please all hold for a
moment it's important
nice just using some
shortcuts look thousand damage on those
dudes only took like 1/4 of their or
one/ third almost of their
[Music]
health not all the thing is I wonder if
he's going to call reinforcements when I
get rid of all of his dudes maybe not
worth it you know maybe I should focus
on the boss but I'll I'll try this here
really
quickly missed
it now I wasn't talking to you you saw I
was calling Kumi talking to the people
the dudes in the
suits maybe the help will be fewer h
H he's more and more moving away from me
I see I see you want to have your
crch son he handles I see how it is
you're literally asking for
it weak to thunder I see your order
is CR
stumps do you call a male crotch also a
crot
this is a question I had in my mind
yesterday good that I think about it
now yes
okay was just
wondering
[Music]
um oh that's interesting pressure cooker
slam
what [\h__\h] oh I didn't think there would
be two okay
I I don't know I thought maybe that's
you know you can only call it crotch a
crotch when there's nothing in between
the legs I thought
maybe I thought it was maybe like that
but no okay
okay English is not my first language
excuse
me oh he's really gey ok
let me tell you a funny Japanese word
like internet slang just I mean I
haven't seen anybody use it in years
but there's gyoko and then there's
gyoko is like abbreviation
of OKO is just like U so angry and then
geki is like extreme so geki is
extremely angry but then p is kind of
like the sound you make like f doie doie
Etc when you're angry like you're going
boom boom boom boom and then model I'm
not sure what the model is for but it it
gives it even more intensity
okay I thought kab was extreme I
speaking of
oh want to try this just for
[Music]
fun
wa it's like a
movie how much
damage oh this round h p oh oh oh oh oh
Gore all these K me things are very
Gore oh
oh that's not even so much
damage nasaki is next
might want to heal
K I don't think he's going to go for him
but probably a good idea to heal
K uh where is he
there yeah epic screen nice the the the
cool cut scene makes up for
it oh
um I want to finish the dude can I get
[Music]
both oh
well I was trying to get both and then
he moved so I was like oh Now's the Time
got to be fast and then he moved faster
than I was
moving couldn't get both but it's okay
Miss click kind
of all right Mr n
[Music]
electricity I don't
have
[Music]
electricity
P oh almost a th000
damage ow there you go there's our
thousand
[Music]
I don't
remember one enemy oh she
found it's
okay where's my paralysis
though paralysis
[Music]
uh my brain how long have I been
streaming 4 hours I feel like today like
yesterday was just so much yapping
yapping yapping yapping and I was just
getting bored but now all of the
fighting like choosing the right attacks
is frying my brain in a different
way
uh yeah very full 4 hours
today has his R2 ready oh okay next turn
I'm going to let him
attack
um do I have something that lowers his
[Music]
defense lower their
attack might do that
though might try it
oh well ah it didn't
work wasn't worth it his R2 is not
ready but the circle is complete I guess
it's still missing like a one pixel or
so
huh huh why is it not
working oh yeah I'd love to have chat go
for these stup
tiny useless time waste
battles they're so long I'm necessarily
long damage sponge even even when I'm
[Music]
strong is I really missing one pixel
to
in mhm mhm
[Music]
mhmm
wa there it is J it's going bling bling
K
shiny and
I can't say
anymore let's try this you guys were
pushing hard for Dragons as
s what even even
this3 ,300 and I missed two
proms out of nowhere wo wo wo wo
[Music]
W damn
it I'm so not ready for the fast
boys I'm so not ready
let's prepare
him for's final
hit no not even worth he's almost
dead I was going to H to okay we keep it
for the next fight
right oh man he died so fast there at
the
[Music]
end mad
Hustle
for getting a lot of essence
attacks
noise
oh they're not
here no one got
[Music]
away ah
so it was a it was a trap uh in the
sense of they said they were going to be
there but that wasn't the place where
they were streaming from at
all they just ah they were just like
wasting our
time I knew it was going to be
H oh I was pre-recording
what my stream is pre-recorded too by
the
[Music]
way what's outside
are they catching me
outside walking over his dead
body uh you're not supposed to fil dead
people no they're not dead cuz K never
you don't
[Music]
worry oh if they're [\h__\h] s sticks I
thought we were done with
those oh my God this [\h__\h] ass
chapter but they're so annoying I hate
all these people they're so
like they they're
like they want those scandals they're
thriving from the scandals and there's
like it's like there's nothing there you
think there's something there because
all you believe is like this cancel
culture stupid drama baiting YouTuber
stuff yeah that's all you believe you
don't even listen yeah what the actual
[\h__\h] this is all like [\h__\h]
everybody's falling for it
everybody
damn yeah they don't have a mind of
their own they just follow the popular
opinion and that's a a big problem
toai Promised Land Promised Land
Promised Land promis Pro that was only
one of my songs did I sing in k
Rescuers Our Heroes
[Music]
to
read maybe it doesn't exist maybe is
doesn't
exist now island is just
America random just America as a
whole
foree
fore
for there you go he's
cooking
[Music]
for we're back in
Hawai
fore foree
[Music]
I love him he's my
I guess so
[Music]
I think yamama is just kind of like he
gives off tund Vibes so
strong come come hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
oh did I just hear a cat
jump they doing gymnastic or
what kind
[Music]
of I want to get cookies can I get
cookies d in my bedroom on on my next to
my bed on my night stand for whatever
reason who knows how they got
there I no totally wasn't eating cookies
at 2: or 300 a.m. at night couldn't be
me could not be
me it was me
this movie jump scared
me wait
no she didn't jump in front of me she
was just
suddenly around the
corner all
right I got the cookies cookies butter
cookies with chocolate
cover on
top covered in
chocolate the the ones I'm eating a lot
recently actually I should go to Idol
meeting
too I feel it I feel
it ni should go huh M bu
cakes I can buy them I probably have a
lot to
spend little Meo oh yeah
I don't me
good me let me m though m
come e
movie I'm
back I gave her a
hug
you thank
you just getting
comfy okay s s
[Music]
fisherman yo these cookies are bumb
I still love milk chocolate the
most rather than bitter chocolate or
dark
chocolate so
good and white
chocolate Okay um thing is I don't know
how many seashells I want I have
5,200
discs I there they
are how many do I need probably like oh
I can't even afford that
many I should check what am I even going
to make
though what am I even going to
make am I going to make
something what
look I don't even know what I
want uh currently he's still an aqua not
are we even going to leave him or not
that's another
question see I finally got an empty
cough dropped
in currently we have
this um for this we don't even
need the seashells where did we need the
seashells
what
for
maybe yeah we should just collect them
you have no idea I have no idea
either oh where are the SE shelling
let me just buy them when I'm realizing
that I really need
them but I can also just collect them
let's let's go to the beach beach let's
go to the beach
beach and get those conversations and
collect some shells just for when I need
them let's go get away
hey I need to learn that song
nice
[Music]
oh maybe he
did oh let's
go that was actually interesting so I
listen to that it felt very relatable I
don't know
why bir
feet this is WWA I need to feed the WWA
always make sure to feed your WWA
guys egg thank
you I love those jumbo
eggs those are actually helpful are you
guys selling mangoes or
what dog food you're
welcome Bast bases
buddies Fortune ah I remember you get MP
region accessory around the midp point
oh okay I should check it out I haven't
checked it in a long
time
buties it was a mix of me trying to say
besties and
buddies nice Flex
what are you selling
guys you sell M guys no why do they only
where the [\h__\h] do I get M
go can I make anything at all oh wait
you're not the one you're the one so
confusing I can make a a tea that kills
one person I don't want to I don't want
to I don't want to thank you
there's a fruit market in this
city is that so
wait you're welcome bye wait there's
your conversation over there that needs
to be had
ooh
Al where'd you
go she
despawned did I kill her
no not quite we talked about wishing on
shooting stars at the park teach's
wishes to get good at tongue
twisters really really you have no other
more meaningful wish like healing Kos
cancer or
so I don't know man that's just not
it that's just not it where's the beach
this was not the beach
oh
here guess I got to go
here H Irish W watch
what
what what do we want just pick up some
of these
conversations wait what how does this
work there's a there's a speech bubble
here what is this about what is this
speech bubble about
here but how do I make it happen or do I
have to get into that uh tram bus
thingy are all of these side quests well
now we we're finally getting to see
them
H is there one that's worth
doing I
wonder anyway
seashells do I just where do I find them
are they just on the floor or do I have
to ah I have to die for them
right a that's so refresing holy [\h__\h] ah
a it looks so
nice actually I was
thinking I saw one of my um old
friends was like in in the what was it
called the
French
uh
Browns am I thinking of the French Ruby
here what is that I think she's there I
think that's what I'm thinking
of but it looks amazing holy
[\h__\h] Geral
carala are you confusing me let me
check it can't
be
ah no no no no no completely different
you know
that it's yeah that one it's
beautiful are you friend okay that I I
think I looked it up and that's how that
came into my
mind but I wasn't sure where are the
seashells
guys I only got seaweed
you know I'm not into
that 420 was
yesterday
s
okay
now but anyway it made me think oh my
God I'm so sleeping on the south of
France I need to
go but Mo
home with
home neat French YouTu
friend or
French
colag one
day French member please
what
oh well I guess it doesn't have to be
friends just anybody in Europe I'm
sure somebody would go with me right
where these sand CL sand sand
sand than one
I have to like stop on
it oh there's a bunch
here yeah I'm going to put it on my list
of places I want to go like it looked so
good
[\h__\h]
no didn't we do this
before lifeguard
Duty what was I saying
oh yeah top of France let's go oh what
this is also side quest have I not seen
you before as well oh it's just a fight
okay
you
[\h__\h] very self aware coconut
St even more
self-aware
H what are you on fire I don't have
anything good
here
H just going to shoot you
maybe or yeah
yeah I'm sure a lot of people would want
to go with me I do have one friend in
Fr
[Music]
one Haven ah here oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] yeah I need to oh y o
y I stumbled into the fight with no
gear at least we have decent weapons oh
no no yeah hang hung out with her
Paris oh wait no he does not have a good
weapon cuz they're Shar in it
ah not the first time I did this
oopsie come on no don't don't hurt
Al
please
no please please have mercy I know I
made fun of you
[Music]
I didn't mean it like
that he resist
water
a come on thr those coconuts Fight Fire
with
Fire weapon with air mail it's arriving
I have this feeling it's right
here I've got a
feeling that not it's going to be a good
night
uh whatever I don't care what it is just
give me
something
you lowers the damage taken when
guarding recover
[Music]
HP
mhm ooh nice five
star that's
okay oh wait what
happened ah I switched
okay Square to F yeah I guess I could do
it that way but they gave him no shoes
because they don't want to take it away
from anybody oh
[Music]
okay 1 2 9
7 what do you
have yeah this is fine the protector is
fine it's strong enough and please give
me back the weapon thank you maybe next
time we get back to Kio will will we'll
switch him back to his uh normal class
anyway
so he won't need that Katana
anymore yeah Dragon of dojima he did hit
fdie he did
oh
nice good for him I am so proud of
him okay we got it do we got it do we
got
it what do we need to improve this a bit
more yeah
possibly
uh wait I CH an our team so we can take
this for
example even though I know the life
jacket is really nice but yeah we're
going to be
fine I always
alive five star five star five star oh
wait and then we have a we have a full
we we should get like a combo
Set uh thing for having all the Cyber
stuff on us by the way maybe a
better um maybe there's a better
accessory for us what is this by the way
oh uh that might be good for like uh
Tommy Maybe
M this is not bad greatly reduces chance
of receiving all status alements I kind
of like
it what do you think I like
it stus elements are
annoying especially when it's on our
strongest
fighter
H they're both ARB guys you did give it
to
ET this one
oh the team healer yeah would be useful
on the team healer too so like if team
healer gets paralyzed she can't heal
so but yeah um this this
not oh uh what was it what was it what
was it what was it this
one is pretty
sick what do you have decreases MP cost
that's fine in
theory defense br br br is there
something better this is on Satan Satan
is not with us now right so we can take
it but then I have to remind myself to
give her something
[Music]
else job XP job XP
nice
attack
yeah the
insults I'd like to have two of those
athletic
ones that' be
nice that's
fine going into a huge fight with onear
equipment that is very likely to
happen well let me eat
here sorry I was in
first thank you for your
[Music]
understanding sparkly
knife sparkly knife he so slay with W
knife the one I had on
one of the oh the
Penguins funky tongue
girl very funky tongue
girl what that tongue
do probably said that before too her
didn't
die is there something in this toilet of
course there
is
e
e what is that supposed to be
what does this word mean
AA what does that even mean get carving
Tomy let me check for Tomy
zawa I want to get those
bingos hey
hey hey hey you
you I don't like a girlfriend
toilet
tracker I'm I'm just clean a toilets I I
I I'm
innocent sorry I came a bit too close
come
on I guess I mean something discharge
are you saying it so badly oh my
protection or is it really this vague oh
nice
outfit hey you Katie on the beach is
this Katie Barry the woman
[Applause]
only no haai girls are Unforgettable
uh leafy skirts and coconut tops yeah
yeah
yeah it's working
guys we just made it
up West Coast R present what could that
be Coast where's Hawaii is if anything
in the
south of
America
where no Bingo though so sad Tommy seems
like he's good at working with what he's
got said his next project would be wood
carved bear oh W west of
Usos see what I told you guys these
coconut trees do drop something else
like you told told me and then I I I
told you and you didn't believe
[Music]
[Applause]
me
Mos did I get that conversation how do I
get this
one let's get them
all no leave me
aloney hey where is it in the building
coconut trees produce everything you
could
imagine what do you
have ooh nice a bar a beach
bar some good stuff M chicken fingers
thank you very much this is why you guys
don't have fingers yeah did you ever ask
yourself why don't we have fingers you
used to but they always cut up at Birth
to produce chicken
[Music]
fingers that's how it is
we did and this is why yeah you use that
fingers we live in a society where your
fingers get cut off can you believe it
and this is why we must Rebel Aloha
start a
rebellion no more fingers cut off never
again what are these things what are
these are these presents no
used as a dart oh this is for like some
class uh or is it just this like mini
game y yie don't my
yoes I'm so sad I have to bring you guys
the truth like
this anyway I'll go do some story cuz I
don't know what else I'll be
doing throw BS
say how much damage they
do
um what was I about to say so sad
anyway I will get you your fingers back
I will I will buy all the chicken
fingers in the world and I will get
Justice for you guys
[Music]
he's coming
no I never had chicken feet
before but that's the next epidemic for
chickens fingers now feet they're
preparing to have you
guys like feet less by 20
by 2029 chickens all over the world
won't have speak
anymore you heard here
first yeah your wings too there in
danger
too your B is in
danger he has a knife I have a surf
oh my God he
so okay your no
problem let me show you my real power
now that I have my equipment
yes wo
okay anyway the lesson is guys you have
to stay with kfp cuz I'm keeping you
safe the it was too late for the yub
ubis I couldn't have you keep your
fingers cuz I rescued
you don't don't ask too many questions I
know I
also uh sat on you when you were an egg
don't question it it's it's the thing is
like it's Evolution it has to do with
Evolution you know let's go it started
out with you guys having
fingers because you were once
[Music]
dinosaur and then and then they took all
the chicken fingers you know H and and
then Evolution slowly F okay oh they
don't have fingers then maybe they don't
need to be born with
fingers and
does eventually you started being born
without the fingers so it was too late
for
me but if they keep on taking the wings
and the feat and
whatsoever your breasts away from you in
the next years one day you'll be born
without
it classic Evolution yeah that's that is
exactly how evolution
works that is exactly
[Music]
it so as long as you stay with kfp I'll
protect you we will we have to
conserve conserve Evolution and the form
of the chickens that you are now want
some
[Music]
this what the [\h__\h] am I talking
about well I'm just preaching the
truth you want to go back to being a
raptor you want to well if anything
staying in kfb is your best
[Music]
bet to becoming a Raptor return to
Raptor take
this you pra the orange
Messiah yes praise me more
[Music]
more both are great
option but I choose this
[Music]
one you waste to
G nice
agility no I'm not drinking energy
Wings even last time I noticed the next
day when I cleaned up my dad's the
energy drink that I drank that time it
was still like 80%
full I thought I drank like good amount
but
no so not the
case it's not worth it you're almost
dead dude I'm not going to spend 30 mp
on you am I maybe I am
I fear the day when you'll finish the
full can yeah it might just be in that
uh getting drunk
stream among us but I don't know it
might not be that kind of Among Us it
might just be a normal
one it happens at
[Music]
all I will be coming lighting I I might
actually start like lighting up yeah
yeah that is so a high possibility
[Music]
honestly I'll become radioactive if I
drink too many energy
drinks that's really what I feel is
going to happen you know my prophecies
are always
true W
prophecies a
you're so nice we're gathering in the
[Music]
middle oh we
know wait how because he's guarding
whatever I'll
force
28,000 28,000
active dinosaur
stream what the [\h__\h] Tak brainwashed
much oh no he was born into it born like
this are you a Haku
my God
[Music]
such
freaks are they going to
Suicide
Y no so dumb please guys never join a a
cult besides KP
oh they knew it was coming it was like
something
implanted insane
what kind of explanation are we going to
get for Bryce's
psychopathy we got kind of an
explanation a good decent one for
aan how we going to explain what the
[\h__\h] is up with
Bryce but he's just a cycle that's what
we thought about
they might have some explanation for
Bryce
[Music]
too I think it's just evil
maybe I kind of want an
explanation cuz like what the [\h__\h] is
like
H they could totally take insir Iration
from like real cult
leaders how they became who they are
just like very very very
self-centered but that alone is not
enough take notes from kfp
no yeah in the end it's just money and
power mhm
anyway I think it's time to get out of
here back to yam until things cool down
a little yum yeah
yum
anytime uh can I help
you wow his
eyes police
policia pling flames of M uh oh
everybody in Hawaii seems to have gone
mad
what come
on it's like a virus
[Music]
spreading crazy [\h__\h]
why the [\h__\h] CH say what's wrong with
you are you are you just manipulating
the team again manipulating what no
what's the word what's the right word
won't do this this is going to hurt wait
that's not what I want come at me come
[Music]
on
maybe maybe this is the right word just
try
me oh please
check this
out manipulate I feel like I'm thinking
of something else it works but I'm
thinking of something
[Music]
else when you just dare
to infiltrate and make them sabotage
thank you
that's the
[Music]
one sabotaging me once
again those brain warms are taking over
all of
us oh that's pretty weak actually we
need a new weapon for
him oh it's just because never mind it's
just
because he was
guarding sexy froat slitter W I like G
never mind that's actually
not doesn't sound so cool and I'm about
to say it
anymore like getting my my gut punched
or so would work but nope that doesn't
work that just doesn't work
these guys are they all the same as
takada we got to keep moving for now oh
but wait
[Music]
Moto oh we're
running ah are they there
no it's all in my head
guys it's all in my head where are we
going good fortune ah the fortune slips
can I go am I stuck here now could I go
to the fortune thing
now I think I'm stuck
now running from my rning
my this is not
enough ooh I want to sing that uh in my
truck
[Music]
all all running my head R my head R my
head really pissing me
off last night and they brought up like
a song like again and again and again
and I was like oh this is perfect for
the next truck
stream I put it in my Spotify
playlist what was
it is this it's so good I think you guys
know it too maybe not by the name but if
you listen to it you'll
know it's
uh ah two princess by Spin Doctors do
you guys know that out L if you listen
to it I think you you realize what I
mean so good I heard it before but now I
finally know the name do you have
something I
want sound
familiar I wouldn't know it by the name
by the title either to be honest thank
you for stopping by I used to have that
CD oh back when CDs were I
had another
one take a break tattoo album was called
200 kilm but I was in the wrong lane
what kind of album title is
that
Aloha thank you no
need what a crazy
title but was the title that but in
Polish
maybe it sounded better in
Polish welcome give me something give me
egg
egg they're not letting go maybe if I
gave it something else later
what why you not letting
Go Let It Go ah oopsie not polish oopsie
where am I
going a what's up take
[Music]
a
slow
200 that way probably I think I got
the pronunciation down
we need to keep out where the [\h__\h] do
you want to go
what where you
going Oh I thought that was the
exit
oopsie I thought that was where I was
going that way I saw
[Music]
it take a break
what's the side what's the side what's
the
side stop saying that I'm going to make
another song out of it well stop stop
stop
[Music]
please I can't hold myself
back okay we're out and now we go here
let's take my
scooter take walk
[\h__\h] that really intense music wait
wait can we we have mangoes now can I
get a can I get a
uh can I get a
uh oh wait wrong can I get
yes
yes I can get two of
these yes thank you that makes me so
happy I got
the what where are we going ah [\h__\h]
Direction fruit cup is love fruit cup
for Te meals yeah big team
heal although for big team heal we also
have skills honestly the MP ones are
almost more
important but this is nice too to
have maybe if healer is eh maybe if
healer is like out of order we can't be
sure who's the enem now let's see clear
which ones oh we're just okay wait so
you want me to go this way
okay but there's enemies
everywhere
sorry get ready for
[Music]
this what do you mean scooters have no
rules stupid
the reason I drive my scooter is because
it is scooter there's no rules to
scootering my way
down ring in the middle of the
[Music]
over
here
no why' you got to call the
[Music]
backup you're so desperate a
oh nice they weren't even weak to it oh
nice follow up Tommy I love
you after seeing you do like 1K damage
you look so weak with the team that's
what I've been thinking and feeling
too I strongly agree do you think I can
get
both this angle it's it's kind of
hitting
need weapons oh it kind of did yeah yeah
yeah I thought
nice you making fun of
me you want to get new
weapons I should I go
crafting I think right now maybe the
game won't let me
really kind of got to go somewhere
which then I can
check
afterwards oh you want me to buy them I
guess I got to buy them anyway as a base
right what are you scar what are you
scaring at I'm a bit railroaded I don't
know what that means but I'm just going
to use it the way you said it
cuz sounds like you're using it
the way I'm
thinking mhm I
see learn something
new blah blah blah blah don't get smart
[Music]
I don't really like her skill set so
much right
[Music]
now but it's just because I have to like
think
again also it's too bright I can't
[\h__\h] see the markings that
well we got all of them scattering
a I still go back to the mall and buy St
yeah should I is are we are we going to
get in trouble otherwise if I keep on
going this
[Music]
way this is going to
hurt what are you
were where
death woo
PE aren't all Surfers buddies why is
this Surfer attacking us aren't y'all
like so chill and like everybody's got
to be
[Music]
buddies
that or is he you went surfing and my
surfing don't surf in
my tast this m Turf you know
surf
what get it cuz Turf I think means like
this is my
hood we will cut through the front of
Crystal Aloha gets to little [\h__\h] from
there most of these prob kind of guys
the local so more should be sa
with
this so it
he this
way
H bird bird bird bir bird bird
bird I need to buy bird food I'm out
what if I meet what if I meet a chicken
in
need hey
back no go
away no I'll take you
down scattering of
flowers flower
power oh yeah that's decent
mhm even better if they were weak to
fire but they're not you give it your
best sh I own your
asss come
really we are weak you think I'm stupid
[Music]
game is so
bright I cannot
[Music]
see what you were there I didn't even
see you
there burning to death in the Hawaii
heat very
realistic I
assume give it your best
[Music]
try I probably could have just the
brightness
but it's
okay it's
[Music]
realistic screw you h
close what is this damage I'm two levels
above them and okay
[Music]
I oh my God my my my my my armor is find
the weapons what are they four stars or
no they like minimum five stars
right nowadays that's not enough
anymore they're four stars oh [\h__\h] of
[Music]
them give it your best
try me [\h__\h] should be fine is
[Music]
ooh for for
for oops sorry um
now now I kind of know what I want and
what I need to do um okay so for example
not you uh for example we currently have
this we'd want this or this even if I
can even get
that it says what does this mean times
zero and then here it says nothing can I
not make it maybe not a raging goddess
sword you want six
stars what does it mean when it's
like not even the number there
and okay usle short
sword would be good and we need a lot of
rainbow crystals which will probably
cost me a
lot ah I need to upgrade the shop ooh
money spending okay okay write it down
you suckle short sword
and a brave General
axe
okay you short sword brave youu brave
youu
brave
and
professional board
hey you suckle Brave
professional aim five stars for now six
stars you know you want to
use five stars after
all um Brave General X was in a
mall I mean I wouldn't mind doing the
five stars first I feel like that would
already be a decent Improvement
yeah okay in that case it's Bamboo Leaf
board
bamboo
k great
Axe
right yeah Bamboo Kitchen great
Axe uh if I'm just going to do it right
now m
M uh how does it work
again
uh this shop probably
has the thing for Kuno wait is she a
kunoichi bamboo k what are those weapons
is she a she she is right first finish
the plot lock
okay I'm just scared that maybe the
fight is going to be too
difficult whatever comes at the end of
this she is
okay I'm confused there's so many
classes to keep track
of I walk like a truck hey
you in
curves
hey where are we
going okay
hey I'm going to
you no leave me
alone please it never works for me never
I want to use my
segue oh leave me the [\h__\h] alone leave
me
alone Bring It
On don't run into are you serious is
that the
problem I don't think so you're joking
right I don't got all day you think I'm
a fool
[Applause]
this going to
[Music]
hurt n it's okay it's just free unless
they call for backup then I'm
in bring out the [\h__\h]
tuna and even that oh my
God even with the tuna
[Music]
cannot even rely on the tuna anymore in
this day and
[Music]
age
okay BR it
[Music]
oh thank
God n dog is
disappointed a good old nard
dog I don't have a
grapple I can only offer you a knock
back is that
okay
no are you going to keep the same CL I
don't know I guess we should go back to
hero is that the best thing to do at
this
point if we're bringing back kid to
Dragon of dojima is it best for Ichibon
to go back to his own class as
well I don't really
no it's his signature
yeah it's it's best class okay is he's
level is he level 30 now on his
uh almost oh one more level for all of
them and two levels for
e eel
he right I need to go to the Post
Office that's also thing I need to
do
tomorrow
perhaps it won't let me go there Eva
where the [\h__\h] do you want where to go
for the for
here
oh promising aloha
okay thank you thank you
bye wait this is not bringing me
where I wanted to go but I'll give the
doggo some
food and I probably never see you again
but nice jump that was a sick flip that
is that was very cor that is 100% a
coron probably got to go
below and then through the building on
the on this level here
no just behind it I
guess leave me alone leave me alone
leave me alone leave me leave me alone
leave me alone leave me
alone oh they're falling they're running
they're running me ready for
this level 3 freak they're not even poly
not
related basic normal stupid sussy BAS
[Music]
are you what do you
want I like how sound he makes when he's
aiming I can't even make it I can't even
recreate
it it's like between
how do you make it he's breathing in no
no I don't think
so
stay oh what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] it sounds different when he does it
okay let me through let me through
oopsie get out of my
c
m here I go again my mind how can I
resist you
M exp is exp but yeah these are pretty
low aren't
they they are dying in their minds
they're dying for a greater
cause forget you win next time this is
going to be so
disappointing what a waste of
tuna over
here
no I'm so close to just throwing a smoke
bomb I swear you're all
almost you're done we just need new
weapons then it's going to go smother
[Music]
get I don't want
to for these no
bodies also they should let me do
Showdown throw down
[Music]
whatever
L2 at this point with red
enemies let me do that don't let me do
it blue is already such a long time
ago smack down smack down is the word
come up you think I'm a fool BR
It screw
[Music]
you
nice until Level
505 I don't even know if I'm ever going
to reach
55 somehow I doubt it
[Music]
I'm so bored I'm so bored
guys talk to
me talk to
me ah he has no GR
Apple have I eaten yet only breakfast
and grapes and like two
cookies nice weather
today airline food accidental accidental
big meal I already said it was really
mid
sadly a grapple
Doo my only grapple cost 30 MP
no movie wake you up she's still waking
me up um these days but uh she's
actually way more patient like she let
me
sleep
usually usually she wakes me up 1 hour
or so before I went wake up which isn't
too
bad it's really not too bad and then she
will meow a little bit but then she will
stop and let me sleep that last 45
minutes or so so we
good
soon yeah although I wouldn't
say that Yakuza is connected to that in
any way ready for this
do
matter
[Music]
no I'm your background music w w radio
once again I know I probably have to
fight the other no everybody's gone oh
they cleared up everything cuz I feel
like there was two groups of enemies
there let's she still uh today no
yesterday also I think she was not
around but overall there has been a a
surge surge
surge in my kitty
C trying to stay close to
me so cute am I right where are we going
oh
here and now
Smack That Booty Smack That Booty and
smack
okay what
else oh yeah of course we can't go there
blah blah blah uh we have to go through
here but no there's so many enemies in
here
here I think here I'm kind of are we in
the shopping
mall wait can I buy [\h__\h] here where was
I going to
buy maybe not for ichon you know I don't
know cute Aloha bikini and
[Music]
stuff around I know you be gone in
summer don't even mention it you're
going to make me
quiet I don't want to think about
it you leave me alone help me
Aloha help me they're all out to get me
please protect
me hello
happy are they level 30
yet
no hello happy I'm not very happy right
now a you a running from
[Music]
me sorry it's just really a pain in the
ass right
now dis guys would be nice
[Music]
yeah what for here
move [\h__\h] get out the way how how are
we being like hunted down
Hawaii so annoying let me take a
taxi stop following me what do you
want what what
what
whoa what are you what are you staring
at
right back at you what are you staring
what are you st no what are you staring
if you st if you notice me staring that
means you are also
staring you have something cool
no it's the revolve
bar could make
some only
free oh good
damage what's
happening
nice nice
oh don't don't don't you dare don't call
don't call for backup drones are
okay you stole that move from it
damage is okay
what what
what am I
no hey I didn't nothing
come
get okay hey damage is
okay last stretch okay I feel like I'm
running a marathon now okay okay you
motivate me I am
motivated [\h__\h] that reminds me just
because I watched Cody Co yesterday I
watched this Cod Co video and he talked
about some famous YouTuber or so doing
like a marathon running the whole length
of uh Africa the whole length I
think and then some [\h__\h]
idiot
uh [\h__\h] idiot
joins in the last like
minutes but you know they're filming all
of this making an emotional video it's
really oh hello Raiders it's really
emotional and like wow boy moving
moments cuz they're finally at the
finish line and then this dude joins in
the last two minutes and runs in front
of the main dude like he's being he's
already being followed by like a lot of
other people I don't really know what
this who they are what they're doing
there but okay he's not he's not running
alone okay but but suddenly some
unrelated dude joins and then finishes
like he just he just decides to like
scooch in front of him run really close
to the dude that YouTuber whatever he is
yeah fans joined for the last stretch
yeah this this random guy maybe he
thinks he's a fan but he took he hogged
all the attention he was like running
like he was the main act and then you
know there's just like Finish Line where
you run through like the the the the
thing that when you touch it the
ribbon and
he runs like 1 cm in front of
him snatches the
ribbon and ruins the whole moment this
dude was running for months or
so I have no idea like who these people
are but even I was pissed off what do
you have you say oopsie
see
kitchen I'm looking for
this so I guess I'll H even if we um go
to back back to main class for Ichiban
and kidu what do we do about the
others should I is it should I is it
important to return to the original
class the others is as you want
H okay I have lots of money and even
without upgrades it's already so much
better oh
present D cute maybe lowest
this why he's like my best body
hey I remembered guys I
remembered oh I get some cool rewards I
guess damn if I do the
photos all righty Ain
a Tommy and SII have good base classes
kunich and house are good desperat and
Samurai are good m okay then I'll keep
her as a
Kuni I do really like Tommy in his
current class even if you say his space
class is good I don't even remember what
it was I had taxi driver I don't know
but my image of him in this class is so
strong I don't want to change it
anymore he's he perfect he looks so good
with those fickles and doing the dongle
dongle stuff
happy with
that as pyro
dancer tomy's best classes host e but
you know I think it's not um like seeing
how well we did with the other team
now uh I think it's not so like not so
I can't even think of words anymore I
don't think it's that seriously serious
serious serious
important uh that we have to min max
even the classes from
my from my experience and impression so
far it seems like we're
good right we can just do whatever we
want I just want to make sure I'm not
doing something completely stupid if
it's like the meta to switch back to
your original CL class at this point
then okay but if it's only the meta for
Ichiban and kidu then okay that's what
I'll
do okay okay you guys give me confidence
have
confidence shut up dip [\h__\h] is such a
funny cute word dip
[\h__\h] oh I thought the battle was
happening they're like goddamn locusts
what why hey Al there what's up more of
them no look where we are H wait that's
kind of where was to
go D my fortunes let's go there trespass
inside the temple I don't know if we're
really
trespassing oh that's a very special cut
scene something's going to go down
oh Triple A budget
[Music]
is like losing his
mind there go I knew something was going
to happen
MH wait what's this music A J I thought
[Music]
I don't need another dude in my team I
need no
one now he won't join anyway I didn't
say
M he's just
being don't we feel so bad for him like
he doesn't get to fight he just being
pushed around like this
yeah he got
demoted what the [\h__\h] is that
hole it's a freaking black hole
did they dig all the way
to
Japan wait they they made a hold to
Japan didn't
they head
Howe
wow if only we had a
climbing Boulder
F chunk didn't load
uhuh
ah
[Music]
for
sense
fore
fore fore
[Music]
me
spee
fore
he uh uh no thank you uh stay on the
computer uh or fix my it things uh no
like what we're like what we have like
one chapter left or so dude you're
[\h__\h] late to the party quite
[Laughter]
literally uh no need who the [\h__\h] at
this point I better be so worth it like
is he like really extremely
powerful cuz if he's not then who
switches out at the end of the game
their main party that they're so used to
fighting with they should have added
them
[Music]
earlier Str and to were clearly only
included out of expectation and not any
real reason for the story yeah they
don't really play a really important
part m
he's the storm that is
approaching she's Port so now he wants
to join that's what it seems
like yeah does he have good
equipment K if I may we would be wise to
restock our supplies
oh don't you dare join the party so late
and now order me around and call the
shots shut up you have no saying
this I say when I need to buy
supplies this just seems so
like who are you I know you and yeah you
know I have no problem with him as a
character but the fact that it's like so
late like what what do you want it's so
weird n aren't you hot in that good
question I suppose I spared no time to
change really what are you wearing on
the KN huh what you must be wearing
something
underne right right there's something
underneath so you can take off the
jacket right or are you saying you're
naked underne which is also really funny
if you
are give us back on no never I'm
sweating just looking at you hly it's
only going to attract unwanted attention
as you go hey we didn't
wait what if you're going to give me a
glow up if you act actually going to
take off the
jacket I wasn't aware my attire was so
problematic
oh
oh okay don't be embarrassed we should
resupply anyway like you said we'll get
you some new friends while we're at it
wait are
you are you saying we're just going to
change his equipment but not his actual
visual appear
appearance come
on or are we going to get him a Hawaii
shirt Street's quiet if we're going out
Now's the Time okay
so this is where I wanted to go right
the story led me right to
it what I get 56 points
wait
what what this not worth it what do I
do or
H I need to buy an order and then what
what do I do with this [\h__\h] does it get
better do I need this to like make a
better one or
so I don't want any of this oh maybe I
do what is this H recover and
pee okay well I don't know if I want to
wear it
TB wait I can't buy
this
why
uh what why is this one at the top now
greatly lowers the damage taken from
fire
attacks
okay oh I bought the other ones already
ah I was so
confused ah
H gr lo I already have
this now all my points are
gone what's the next one
funer Mama Mia do I get minus points for
collecting bad fortunes or is it just
whatever that would be funny your total
is zero points because you collected too
many bad fortunes oh
no you get one for bad fors
not
okay H it's time to craft ladies and
gentlemen uh but so we bought the one
that we need
for our Kuni I think o full men party
not in
Taki's
house who Do You Think You
Are the
[\h__\h] the
audacity okay uh what am I doing what am
[Music]
I so we have the US short sword we need
rainbow quals which I think we can buy
at the dungeon
right oh two level he's two levels
below also it needs the it needs the the
one single empty cough drop tin that I
have oh
man wasn't he your homie yeah I remember
him but like he's
late I have no interest and then for him
we'll just make the sport because then
we'll
or what that that freaking cough drop
how do I get more of those maybe I'll
get more in the next dungeon or
[Music]
so it would be great if I could make the
ultimate
exra metal bed
huh it needs a
huh this needs the hero bat and I threw
it
away an enemy drops them oh okay okay
nice nice nice
nice 100 100 of the eeral exas
no but this damn this one needs the
freest star metal bat this one needs the
one star herob b as a base well
anyway okay okay okay okay
okay I'll just do it step by step
otherwise I can't think we'll make hers
we need rainbow crystals okay so we go
to uh Hawaiian hunt I think I I think
think I can buy it
there yeah I think it does pay off to be
a
hoarder in this
game now now you want me to fill out his
Bingo too see this is another reason why
you should not have him join this L into
the game I'm not going to work on his
[Music]
bingo oopsie no no no no no no no no no
this
mistake exchange
exchange thank
you what do we got uh what did I say
rainbow
crystals right how many damn it brain is
so empty it hurts
expensive m
hours I wonder you
know like I might have to go into this
dungeon to get more discs to make all
the weapons and stuff I need to grind
stuff we'll see how far we get I'd like
to get everybody like geared up
and then do a little bit more of story
but if I can't get geared up then I
can't
continue but I might just buy the base
weapons the six star or five star base
weapons and then that should already be
an improvement for
now ah right I need to invest
oh just one level I
wonder oh we're done with investing
anyway
good okay this better be worth it we're
going to keep her as a Kuni so it should
be okay
[Music]
kumas secret a masterpiece forged by a
renowned swordsmith the blade melts into
the dark light like a
crow interesting
attacks and weapon skills May debuff a
random enemy
[Music]
stat sounds good then upgrade a little
bit
[Music]
maybe seven for now
nice and a branding oh I can't all right
cuz it's from 10 onwards whatever it's
fine for
now and okay what do we want what
else I wouldn't mind keeping him but I
can't make the empty cough drop thing
anyway but if I just buy the brave
General
Axe and let him fight with that we'll be
we'll be fine I think for now
so I could make this one
though how strong this has a base of
138 uh let me see how much the brave ax
has as a
138 brave brave brave where where how do
I know even where is it
13838 where Where is the bravex
H there's just so much I have to switch
around
and no that's not where I want to
go
no yeah I know I have to buy it first I
really don't like the system
[Music]
like what's this what's this
class po
geod dance no py dancer it should be
there go here or
here I don't think it's that shop what
was it called what did I need
brave brave whatever it was it was Brave
right be the best
vacation is not
upstairs it's upstairs
right
hey this of stuff was only
faster but they don't I think they might
still have it was it
here hopefully I don't know where else
get
it can somebody look up where I get the
axe if it's not
here
Aloha I know it's here the brave General
axe plus
140,000
bucks
yeah Merry
Christmas this is your birthday present
and your Christmas present for this
year thank you for stopping by you're
welcome and then a
nice
surfboard six star
surfboard probably also somewhere here
um not on this floor
though yeah I'm going to make him a but
he he does need one more
[Music]
level I mean buying a six-star
surfboard yeah that's obviously not
worth it uh I could buy a five star for
that one level it's just so painful you
know it's just so painful
oh it must be there
yeah I do you have
Valerie why don't you come on over
[Music]
Valerie
valer do I would they be
here I
don't I didn't
have I did not
have [\h__\h] but it was a good
thought or are they just not there I
think they would be there
ah
Valerie it was a good point let's see
how expensive that five for it
is uh you only have the six star or
what everything's the same price uh the
[\h__\h] he only has a six
star thank you very much sh is only star
weapons was I going to get was I going
to leave uh other CH or some I also have
this question in my mind are our teams
going to merge like soon and then I
won't have all these people in one team
anyway and then it's not worth it like
or do they stay separate until the end
of the
game they won't merge okay cuz if I have
like nine people to choose from I'm not
going to give them all great equipment
okay andachi if he stays a
samurai maybe we buy him a six star
samurai
sword this weapon was okayish now though
right oh it's the
same I could buy this buy the bat oh
yeah head of time I'm which which one
uh this
one is that what I need to craft six
star
b
y current current current Ali weapon is
okay should I get this is this thank you
very much
that's the sound allery
makes I just got
it uh right
here super
aloy for the Supernova
bat need another empty Clough drop tin
or I make one of these you one the wait
I have what I have a herob
bat so I could make this one too this is
even stronger I could I have the herob
bat I need just 10 electric crystals
which are easy to get the empty cough
drop in I would have to get for this one
anyway and I saw the shark fin shark fin
being sold somewhere else anyway in one
of those shops I should make this one
that one's even
better I'll make it I'll make
it not today though
probably so if you're not selling five
star whatever I guess then we'll have to
suffer here
until Level 30 and then yeah
well this is really wrecking my brain
right now
but cuz if I move on in the story now
and he turns 30 and then I don't have
anything to
replace he probably stay
any it's in the another shop where is it
where is it where is it is it so this
one we just this one we just checked out
is it in here
uh
no bra wreck I'm a train wreck and my
brain is
wrecked
H in the VIP section what there what
there's a VIP section you mean in this
shopping mall you mean the the what
I wish I I wish I could change
floors item Pack DLC does it give me all
the base weapons or what or is extra
stuff what you looking at this game is
hurting
me this game is deleting my brain cells
right now I don't know why it's so hard
on me today maybe cuz yesterday I also
played so long it's too much me
too wow buying deal
[Music]
see well now you make me
considerate yeah I played before I
started too call it the day m no no but
I feel like I'm kind of like in front of
a wall right
now where is this stupid
[Music]
ass six
star um
fre star gear no no it also has a five
star but that's a six-star board huh
does it have the five star
board five star surfboard is by the
alohappy
oh is this
one let's not buy the Alo Happ
uh how are you guys feeling watching me
just being
[Applause]
so brain
empty I'm
feeling confused wait a freaking moment
dude how much more exp do you
need I'm not going to I'm not going to
get W I'm not going
[Music]
to buyid
where do I see how much exp he needs
until his next
class I'm overthinking you're having a
chill time how dare
you it's not a show [\h__\h] I'll bury
you I'm I'm going to take all of these
people down
stop moving stop I said stop
moving it missed on the one that's weak
to it oh Mama Mia oh D you're a big dude
how' you get so
big he's got no element on his
weapon h
cheaper than New Gear pound me no but
like
no what the [\h__\h] are we
[Music]
why are you guys so in
syn I think I'm burned out from this
game right
now
wow that didn't happen the the other
weekend why am I so burnt out from
it a
cereal I never heard that before that
you get bigger from cereals usually it's
like eat your veg
what the [\h__\h] why are you doing this to
me knife
twister why I don't have the patience
for this right
now what go [\h__\h]
yourself pure
aggression this is part 10 you're
telling me I'll need another another
[Music]
apart
spee speee
okay so
this
leaves the idea of giving him a
surfboard
behind I can now focus on getting him a
bat the thing is though for the bat I
need you need to tell me where I get
that cough
drop where do I get more cough drop tell
me now please on guy
drop in
Yokohama
no no way no what the what the [\h__\h] am I
supposed to do until then with him I
guess I do have to get him a surfboard
to just get over that
hurdle or or switch him to to hero and
buy him a a a bat a temporary
bat
no oh my God see why my brain is
breaking see why it's
breaking sujon sub story hell
no I almost forgot he uses a bat
normally give him a temporary
bat poort enemies drop them is not
easy they're in the DLC DLC they're in
the DLC how
many where where is this information
where's this list of what you get from
the DLC I might buy it I'm losing my
patience let's end them for today the
the stream yeah sure but I want a game
plan um a strategy
there's a couple on the store
Page can I buy
it
wait how to buy what else does the DLC
give me
wait how do I get out of this game again
wait uh PS5 button
okay where is the shop I don't ever use
PlayStation I
hear I'm offline damn
it
oh I haven't connected the
Wi-Fi
uh connect to
[Music]
internet
uh you guys have to you have to go
through with this with me with you have
to suffer with
me don't look at my password don't look
at my Wi-Fi
password connecting to access point I
hope I put it in
right I suff a with you any day of the
week I love you I was a level
55 with ultimate weapons and armor and
the final BS still hit very hard
prepping would be good to avoid future
frustration wow ultimate as in like
seven what I have to sign in I don't
know my [\h__\h] password please don't
ask me for my password for the
PlayStation store is there a password
oh I have to update my system
software Okay
1,187 g No
1 187
GB password is I love
kfp you're better off just grinding for
them at this
point really you think
so I want to see what else it gives
me we should
check how much is it Anyway how
expensive is
it 6 minutes this is a big system
software update
huh it's pretty big they drop with some
patience I don't I ain't got so much
time
this is like a small break so I think
this is better I'm not sure
um if
I'm I I I'm going to look at this DLC
and then I'll make my next decision I
currently can only handle everything one
step at a
time I need to look and then
decide
yeah I feel like w could beat the rest
of the main story without grinding well
I definitely need weap
weapons but now everybody except ichun
has a good
weapon even if some are not
upgraded
yeah so we have like what one more
chapter or plus this one we're currently
in but then the last chapter is super
long or is this the last chapter that's
just super
long super duper
this will end the Final Chapter okay and
the final is really long okay no
problem no
problem how many did we do today one and
a half or so or
two can't
remember the DLC has a postgame dungeon
with an absolutely amazing line by kidu
you are not getting me
to play post game no you should know
better that doesn't work on me just for
one line uh just a oneliner m that is
not even such a good
bait you need to offer me something
better look it up on YouTube exactly
those kind of things can just look it up
on YouTube
shopping W is window shopping system
software update restarting
PS5
[Music]
okay oh we're so back it's
installing who 100
hey yo oh it's
restarting can you buy me a
PS5
no I'll tell you the line next stream
because the has a boss refer you haven't
seen oh okay do I need to restart this
PS5 on my own it's not oh there it is
okay
yeah yeah yeah EV every once in a while
I remember I didn't even pay for my
PS5
shees there's certain sponsorships which
are
just
goat absolute goat hey I just get a
black screen let me I think this has
failed
[Music]
me let me reopen this capture s
Ware yeah
bam they are just
so uh what's the
word what's the
word generous and goed both
GG that's why I kind of feel like you
know cuz I love them so much and I love
tals that's why I feel like I need to
play the DLC on stream but then again
I've been thinking maybe I
shouldn't
maybe maybe I'll play it on my own time
I don't know I wonder how long it
is some of you guys played it right
already any estimates how long it would
take me you're the [\h__\h] Ambassador
what you don't
know have to go now goodbye thank you
for coming
you finished it 100% only 9
hours took me 20 hours well you probably
100% in it took me 25 hours but I did
everything I think I might do it on my
own just like as a Feelgood wa
game then I can take my time with it but
I don't know at the same time I don't
know I feel like I owe it to them cuz I
love
them I want
to I want to support them oh come on
don't I don't need to install a dual
sense wireless controller device
software go
away go away okay PlayStation store let
me in what am I looking for like a
dragon like
oh I see the game okay like a dragon is
a DLC like to be found
here
add-ons like I Dragon infinite
wealth set
extra or there's like oh oh oh
oh
H I guess the most expensive one what is
in
here 20 uh level boost thingies five
this many many
boosters oh these are just boosts
okay but there's this material
one 200 pure steel Electro lava ice
rainbow GE oh a shark fin five shark
fins there's no none of these cough
drops in oh wait there's two different
ones wait which one did I click
[Music]
first tint and fish
tentacle squid T tentacle
Taco
tentacle
[Music]
costumes
oh
H spoiler can I get D to fight in my
team or is it just he's going to h i no
no they were oh they
were un oh
oh outfits for
everybody this one
has what the [\h__\h] is this I don't see
cough drops
[Music]
anywhere
H was it perhaps a
mistake Miser understanding
information oh they removed them what
the
[\h__\h]
why was the
what what wait there's
more there's
more was
this sujon and
[Music]
Resort special jobs there's like a what
is this rugby linebacker and and Tennis
oh
oh ten is such
[Music]
cute
cute DLC job
cute what's this A what
this
mhm what is this RGB
ichon new game
plus a
bonus dungeon new trophies
outfits outfits St Island something
something songs blah blah
no he the classes man I should have
gotten DLCs from the
beginning yeah no they don't have it
they don't have anything whatever I'm
done for
today if if certain uh Yakuza know it
alls saying it I'm saying it in a
positive way want to tell me what I
should
do what's my best options now to move on
although well I need to do the dungeon
right that's one thing I need to do off
screen I'll do the
dungeon and I need to get my equipment
in order but the the cough drops are in
Yokohama so I can't get the cough drops
just get five star for now five
star
bat okay is my screen gr on purpose I
was looking at the PS5 store if I was
going to buy something I thought I
should probably hide it I don't know
what it
shows but never mind I'm not buying
anything no stuns today for the PS5
store five star good enough okay you can
get them in Hawai kind apparently a drop
in the area where asak asks you to fight
him at the
pier apparently there's a place where
you can easily Farm cough
ohuh okay easily I'm a bit late
poter a bit a a bit late a a a bit that
is the understatement of the century
Mama
Mia save yourself the trouble of going
for a whole dungeon and fishing it will
save your
sanity
what
what what but I what are you saying I
should not go through the dungeon
well you're later than jungi I thought
that was
impossible I'm so brain empty I'm so
fried I'm fried Phoenix
fried Phoenix oh my God the
prophecy the
prophecy no I think I got to go I
think brain
empty has been
foretold
um I just I just I M
who am
I
um
[Music]
um to
tomorrow no no stream
Tuesday days with
[Music]
Ollie and
uh
huh
uh uh
uh Friday
Friday H
uh
Friday Friday
finale
Yak Saturday members and girls
talk oh maybe not both maybe just
one members I don't know I don't I don't
uh I don't
know I don't
[Music]
know I got it I have to
go I have to
go
goodbye I have to
go to go my brain hurts
thank you so much for
today it was fun until they fried my
brain and honestly it was fun until we
switched back to
Hawaii I have to cook because my meat is
going off
today I think it'll be released on time
yeah yeah the delayed line timeline time
it's
already like in a few hours as you guys
told
me no leave me alone don't leave me
alone don't talk to me now about such
things I'm going to go I'm going to go
I'm going to go I
sorry sorry leave me
alone leave me Al
bye-bye I am now going to
ascend or descent into madness do you
normally Ascend or descent into madness
I think you descend
right leave K alone
honestly that's that's so funny but I
watched like a documentary about all of
that and then it made so much sense and
then I couldn't make fun of that anymore
not that I ever really did but uh that
dude I forgot uh the name but uh it just
makes so much sense actually I should
go you don't even you do you
even yeah Chris Crocker was the name in
side
like knowing all all the [\h__\h] that was
going down at the time and making that
connection
now like at the time I I was like small
small teenager I think so when I saw
that video I was like what the [\h__\h] is
wrong with this person it just seems
like actually it seems kind of acted out
it doesn't even seem
real but now I understand everything so
much more m
honestly that was
genuine like
that's Chris
Crocker
understood what was
[Music]
up before most of the other people
did anyway I should
[Music]
go my brain is logging off goodbye
goodbye that was also in my brain at the
same
time leave me
alone leave me
alone leave K alone leave me
alone
goodbye
goodbye see you on
Tuesday when it's Tuesday that's when
I'll see
you uh
okay
[Music]
sorry sorry for small small brain cell
small smaller brain cell
[Music]
no brain worry
okay oh honestly those switches are
really annoying cuz like now I'm in this
position where I want to farm an item
but they only have it on like the other
side of the [\h__\h] Globe they should
make it possible that any items you need
for crafting are available on both Maps
just like the [\h__\h]
seashells oh my God that is not planned
very well so
inconvenient
M I'm mad I'm so mad
or or let me switch yeah I thought that
at some point maybe they'll let me
switch around freely but they never did
wrap it up it is possible at the dogs of
Hawaii where I am now am I in Hawaii
yeah I am no way okay stream M and yeah
stream Kima
please during during uh the
Monday both on YouTube and on the uh
streaming
[Music]
platform near the pier in Harbor
Street
okay oh
[Music]
press for to pay
respect for not here go to Kima
now please wrap it up no
[Music]
is someone dreaming
nope nobody's
[Music]
dreaming I'm the only
one I have the
Domino no the
Monopoly of
[Music]
H
byebye okay you rate the MB I mean if
cie can't raate a
VOD no I don't think
[Music]
so what was up with that