[Music]
Ko
De
[Music]
DET
De
[Music]
Hahahaha Oh, he's a teacher, he's a teacher, he's
not a teacher, but hey, I just happened to be here.
Hello, everyone.  Is
everyone gathered together? Everyone is fine right now, Masukane-chan. Is that
true? Please, please, sensei, please take attendance.
Well, I'll go. Then, I'll go from the white group's
A. Eiroha-chan, I'm
hungry. Please,
Nera-senpai.  Hello,
hello too, thank you very much for your support,
Kanata-san, I'm here, my niece, my niece,
yes, my niece,
yay, tomeyou, tome
you
[Music]
That kind of candy, meme-
chanme
Chaname-chan, hey, hey, I'm here Hey, Okaela Yes, Hello, please take care of me. Thank you for your support. These members are on the phone. They are the people who will break up and become A. Yes, yes. For B, Choco-sensei Awa.
Iriori.
Zu-chan is Koazukizuki.
Thank you, please. Captain, hello. Captain. Hello.
Hello,
hello.  I
wonder if I should go? Yes, it was Lale-chan today, and I'm sorry that I got a little confused.  Do
n't do anything wrong when you look at me.Since we look alike, we would like to cover Nema Raden-chan's
flight as well,
so please look forward to it.Everyone, it seems like
you and your seniors have lost your horses, too.
Well, Raden will be appearing in Holomen Hunting,
but I'll be
taking his place in that role.
Thank you very much. I'll be acting
as a hunter, and the fight against Maki has
yet to happen. I'm not going to tell you what will happen, so I guess it's a secret.  I'm looking
forward to seeing what will happen during the secret battle. Will
Kanata be wandering around alone? Will someone
come? Yes, I
want to see her working hard all by herself. She's wandering around alone and
taking everyone's camera.  Maybe
Oh, I'm telling you to do my best and hit me.
Maybe there's a spy here.
What a spy, really, I'm like a messed up spy
. There's Matsuri Senpai.
Oh, I'm telling you to leave. He's right
here in the White team's waiting room.  It's a classroom, right? We
're all waiting here right now. Okay, so we're
going to have a competition. Who's here
? That's right. Everyone's here. That's right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Everybody's here. Okay, so we're going to have a competition. Who's here? That's right. Everyone's
gathered here. Okay, ok. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
There's a signboard sitting
there.Where can I put it
?I
wonder
where I can use it, but I can't
place it.  It's like, I have no choice
but to do that
.
[Music]
Hey, Polo came to scout. Everyone's here.
Well, the scout group is coming tomorrow. I guess we
should go scout somewhere else.
Which one should we go scouting?  Red Team I
wonder how everyone in Red is feeling right now. They're all sleepy.
Yeah, there's no one there. [Laughs] It's starting to get really bad. Terumo Riguro-san and I were having a lot of fun with each other. Hey, I can't
get the signboard in my left hand anymore.
I'm sorry, but the signboard
may have been on all day today, and I ca
n't get it.
I'm glad I can't get it, but I can't get it. It's true, I can't get it, but
everyone's holding it up. Seriously, it's
too bad, but is it okay to carry it in a competition?
No, maybe the thing reset will be completed, yeah, maybe
when it's
infected.  As
expected, the author did his best and taught me everything. I
wonder if the author didn't have any intrusions. No, it's
true. Oh, it's terrible. Is it
true? Is it true that Minecraft created it? That
's amazing.  What's this?
[Music] I'm
listening to something. I
don't know.
I don't understand cameras.
But I can hear it. I can hear something. It
sounds like Subaru-senpai's voice,
but it's not a misunderstanding. It's a misunderstanding.  I heard you, I
heard you. Okay, then I
think I'll call out to you. Well then, everyone, I'm
very well called. Thank you very much.
Entrance begins. Entrance is the entrance announcement. Okay,
everyone who came in is not red, so I'm
going white.  It's white, Merle Meme is red
Meme
[Music]
It's there, it's there, it's
falling.
[Music] It's a
genius right now. It's really lined up. It's lined up with the
red. Let's line up the white, too.
First of all, mom.  Yoko Niko
11th row Okay, so next,
everyone from the white team please come in.
Ah yes yes yes yes
yes yes
[Music]
[Applause] Yes, that
's a powerful white, that's great. Lastly, I'd like to receive a compliment from that yellow team.
Okay, that's
okay, Kashi-chan, you're hiding, and you
[laugh] are
on camera, too
.
Why are there such neat lines? The white group is
too beautiful. Let's go with the serious frame. Serious frame,
serious frame.
If I can win the frame, I only have a pink signboard.
Well, it's true, I put it together. It's a yellow board. I
mean,
there's no white board, right? Even the signboard. So,
first of all, I'm a member of the Hololive movement.
Hello everyone! Nya, thank you so much for coming together. It's been a lot of fun. I
'm sure you've helped each other, both seniors and juniors, and you've all worked hard in practice up until today.
Since it's a real event, I hope everyone will give it their all and come out victorious. First of all, everyone should have fun, and then we should aim for the win.
Everyone, please have fun.
Thank you very much for your support today. Please.
Please, thank you very much.
Next, we have received a message from the president of Cover Co., Ltd.
[Music]
Click here to see the video.
For example, it's gymnastics. It
's not in the plastic plan. I
don't do it properly. I'm
tired.
At today's sports day, let's cooperate with each other and
do our best until the end. Thank you very much for your
support.  I
hope you will pay attention to me and support me. Mamoru Mamoru and other
members,
please be careful. With that, I would like to open the meeting with you. You must be suffering from a
mental injury,
or the principal.  Kokasa, the
person who is being used as a stooge in a fistfight, channel 1,
please, Mr. Masu, I'm going to go,
please, do your best, please, do your best,
good job, I'm the most serious in the
serious category, so
please, please, please.  Please do your
best.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very
much.I'm starting to feel strange in my ears.Mr.
Wish
[Music]
[Laughter]
I wonder if I'll do it Has Has Ka Mon C'mon Has Has Has Has Sus Good Good Good Sensei I think I'll do my best Good luck Good luck Okay, let's ask you to play the role Mr. Player Is that okay?Yes, then please.  As members of Hololive, all of our players
use sportsmanship to take over and fight with the teacher.Cute,
cute, November 4, 2023 Red team representative Virtue
White team representative A yellow representative Bells
Ye
[Music]
[Applause]
[  [Applause]
Okay, I
'm sorry for the loss. I'm
sorry. Thank you for throwing.
Thank you for shining.
[Music]
Special Excuse me. White Team
's
All Competitors Channel White Team's Competition  I'd
like to ask you about the channel.The
sound quality of Ria's sports day is
a bit poor.The real Kia
is round 2, so I'm wondering what the
channel is like.I'm the only one who is in the
first round of hunting.
That's right, that's
right, that's right, that's right. I'm going to go to the white team contestant's channel. So, uh, Ame-
chan Kaneri, hi
, hi, oh,
hello. Do your best,
layer team fight.
Player channel
[Music]
Good luck, old man.
Good luck.
Good luck, Gluck.  Good Luck It's Good Luck
Completely That's Good Luck That's OK
Totally Good
La That's the third Kaela right Yes that's right Yo
Kaela
Okay Good
[Music]
H
Hellouptoyouguys
PleasecarryThe
Gdoit
doTeamWhiteTeamYes
TeamI
[Music]
NEXTAll
HUNTING
righthandhaveleash
ofCAPhave
onokWewill
WIN
wehaveKNoNoNo
PleasenejnejnejIbea
sweatygamerTooLate iepneedtobe
competitiveTry Yes
happen rightrightI think okayWhereismyMy teammates shouldwegoinNoright okayfineJANOT SURE mckon the
Well, I heard that the fugitive running away has
become this channel.It's
difficult, it's difficult, it's difficult today, it's
difficult today, I wanted to do this exercise,
which is the first thing I wanted to do.  The
first thing I wanted to practice was the first thing I wanted to do, but I couldn't do it.The thing I haven't been able to do is the first thing I haven't been able to do.It's true that once I get through this and that, I can do it.Okay, well, I hope you'll do your best.  is a hunter and the white group
all run away yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes that means everyone is a contestant right?
Only
is
yes
Yes Yes Yes
Hello Hello
Ah Areyou
readyIam
readywelljust
Again
[Music]
mayun
I Are
you
readyI am readywelljust Again
[Music]
going
SorryI
for
[Laughs]
byareyou
running
aroundThankyoufor
lettingMeOnYourHead
earlierNoProblemI
appreciated that
Prezi Ah Mizuo Senpai
Mizuo Senpai Kyuri
Kyuba
Kyu
IstuffWhatstuffI
[Music]
know
think
damagemygodIeven
throwStuff
inventory
lely
M
SKY
ClearBeautiful
Day
people
REGismy
nameEnglishNonot
[Laughter]
iun
okayNoyouneedto
saveyougetStuckOn
TheSpider
WebDirtyPlayDirty
TrickNo
No
Sorry
noAllTheEnglish
members
White
WOWDETMarewe
supposedtobeplaying
inHereIguesswejust
separWeGbe [
Music]
doingI
think
SHCanweBreakOut
anywaycannotIthink
H
No
komWhyareyouare
youI
[Music]
knowto
protect
to
[Music]
time
thisCageCagethis
CageM
crampedokayFIVE
F
Onenice
okay
allthat
means
ME
OUT
pleasLetMeOut
Free
USNowYELLisitor
WhiteWhiteIthink
afterthis
WeYes, bewhiteand
Y
[Music] It's
okay to cheer like this. Wamodawa. They should give you a bonus with Mooplus. No, you must be working hard. The bonus is right. Yes, it's right. It's nice. It's nice. It's interesting. It's fun.  Hey, I do
n't think there will ever be anything like ``Catch Goal Live English'' again, but I'm sure it
won't be the same one twice or three times.I think
something like Indonesia or ``Catch Me'' will
probably happen soon,
but there are also tall people.  I guess it's possible, isn't it? You'd have to
bring someone who's tall. To be
honest, I don't even remember. There aren't many people over 160 cm, so
everyone in Hololive has to be very careful. It's
small, so we'll see what
happens.  Wow, 149 is a pretty good lie.
Yeah, no, the most common ones are
in their 150s. I'd like to interview everyone from the white team.
Yes, the first game is Eneli Saiie,
Kaera, and A's 3.  I'm a member of the Kaikai group.Yes, I'd
like to ask you, Mr.
Hunter, the
second trial.Ah, I'd like to introduce you to the second hunter.Yes,
Captain Noel.The key point is,
and the person from the other side.Yes
.  Well, all the players of the white team, can you
hear me? Can you hear me? I
can hear you. Yes, yes, how are you? We
have enthusiasm and a strategy.
Well, we'll
catch
everyone for now. Well, I see. It's us, this is the second game.  I'm
going to catch it now, and I
'm hoping that I'll be able to get it before someone wins.The money will be too much as it's decreasing.That's
it too.It's power.It's quite surprising.I'm
going to get through it with power.  When I
saw the title, what did you think? I
thought, oh, what about my
senpai? I was wondering who the cutest member is that Mimio-senpai would want to protect,
but yeah, that's right.  I
was included, Nemi-senpai No, I don't know if that's true. I
wonder if it's too narrow. I wonder if that's the case. I wonder if I'll continue. I
believe in this. I believe in it. I believe in it. That's why it's
strange. Yes,
please do your best.
Good luck
Yes, you're welcome.
Yes, so-and-so is doing the voice.
But, thank you very much. So,
everyone, please stand by.
Thank you very much. So, all you
have to do is enter. This is the
1000th one.  I was
so embarrassed that I looked at you. I'm sorry,
Mr. Noil. Mr. Kia, please
go back to the original channel. I'm
sorry, it's okay. Please do your best.
I
knoweedtoreadthe
categoryWe
cchickIknowWeGoing
rightJALetdo
thisokayIfamiliar
theMapWecanGetStuck
inaJELLYlike
substance
GOacrossICEand
SN
[laughing]
PRTeam
GO
JELLYIwanttoeat
itonethank
[music]
youy
Ilike
[music]
that
IsAlwaysGood
Ideas
[laughing]
youVOICESJUMPJA
JUMPSpace
BARDET
okay
SHIknow
[ Music]
Times
okayKill
DIS
[Music]
ONE
IR
outfit
shortThis
Man this
have shorthair right nicenice [Music] [Music]
ikke [Music] min [Laughter] JA But actually, that strategy was power.  No, no, no, but it might
work. I see.
Well then, let's go to the interview. Hello, hello,
hello,
hello, hello,
hello, it was difficult.
Difficult. Yes, it's all
difficult. It's difficult. It's difficult.  If you touch the sign,
yes, touch the
sign, OK, touch the sign, OK, OK, Koro Kids, I got it
Holo Kids Hololive Kids Holo
Kids are difficult at the beginning Holo
Kids are in it Holo
Kids Sususu Holo Kids at the beginning Oh Holo Kids Festival Hane
Ero Ga
Matsuri is Nokino Kids
What's wrong with the shrine maiden?  I thought she had a big sister feel,
but it looks
ugly.I wonder if it was a problem.It was a nice
fight.Thank you, yes, thank you.  The group was able to catch two people
PRjust
Mariho Nankore Emari
Okiwa
see
seeneedcckthesign
AgainI
Thinkfor
yokalso
even
[Music]
wor
prut
ONEJAbutsaidThatShe
wasconsideredshort
butI is
shortthingisIknow
arewetalking
aboutdefaultoneor
non
timemaybe
maybe well
[Music]
Hey, Punopuno Problem
Yes, it's No Problem to No Problem. You're so angry, aren't you? You're so
angry. Come on, come on out! Look, there are some people who look so pitiful like this.  Tayoichi, what kind of situation is this? I
really want to do this. Open this door,
open it, and close it right away. I'll
do this in front of the closed door. It's so
nice of you to let me in.
Live,
live,
no.  There's a smell of earth in my heart.It
smells like earth.It smells like earth.It smells like earth.It smells like earth.It smells like
earth.It's like, what are you saying?Let's turn it off.It's kind of heavy.Is it a
little bit?
I touch it.  It's too brainy It
's so cute when it's lying on its side.It's so cute
when it's upright.Oh yeah, yeah, that's
that.That's so
cute.It's so cute.You
can sell cushions like this.I'm sure
this is really cute.  It's so cute,
but you're selling it. You're so cute. You're so cute. You
can't stop being smart. Yellow, yellow,
yellow. Let's
run away. I'll do my best. I'll run away.
I'll run away.
[Music] I'd
like to go to Korea.  No, no
, no, only the fugitives, only the fugitives,
touch the fugitives. I'm entering the fugitives on my own.
Maybe I've already entered them.
[Music]
Za
Even Mamoru
is hiding. It's crazy.  I'm a
newbie. I'm a newbie.
[Music]
[Music] I'm a newbie. I'm a newbie. I'm a newbie. I'm a
newbie.  Hey, I caught him, but he totally ignored
me. There's
no way that could happen. Wait a minute,
leader. He caught me, but wait, leader.
158 I'm a little sorry. Hey, I wonder if it's an
aura. It's safe. I'll
hide it, hide it, chocolate.
165 That's right, hide it, hide it.
I'm in charge.  That's
why I
caught him once, and then he caught me again.
[Music] I'm sure no
one will catch me.
But I did.
[Music] I'm sure he's
polite and courteous, too.  No matter
what you do, it's neat and clean.
Various complaints are happening, and bad things are happening. Yeah, nice, old man, nice. Ajie did
n't get caught, Zunezu, Gem-
chan, and Gee, but it's true that Azusan will definitely
be a member.  It's in, it's in, it's in, it's in, it's
in, and it ran away, so it's cute that it's a little more self-aware No,
it's cute  Chan, you have to run away too. I don't
think you'll get caught, even though you're so neat.
Yellow was really strong. I
caught about 100 yellow, but it was dangerous. That was
amazing.
It's not a battle for leader, it's time to run away again.
Yes, you've made an entry.  All of them
did it. They gave me this.
Ranran
Run away, run away!
When I was a big sister, I was the leader
[Music]
and a woman who had the ability to get into the big sister's room. It didn't
matter, I wanted to be chosen.
Don't say it.
Well, it's true that my height wasn't chosen right.
Well, I guess it's
because Polka misunderstood me. I
was able to get a little closer to the cage, right? It
's quite narrow.  I
really don't like it. Once you're caught, you
can't run away during the game, right?
During the Hunter game, that's right, until the next game.
[Music] Do
your best for the rest of the game and run away, Mio-senpai.  No,
who's going to think that? The next one was Mia, but for a moment, that's right.
There's a possibility that something like that or something like that will change, but no, there's a completely different possibility.
If I do this, I
want to be protected.
[Music]
Everybody's in a tight spot. Everyone's doing it.
The place to enter. It's a little
creepy because the slope is about to overlap next to Zion Tepa.
But it's
weird.  I don't like it, everyone is
looking at me, I can't help but stare at
them, so cute It's so cute that
they're standing side by side It's cute Hey, someone please line up next to me too
Ah, that's what happened
Reset, the reset begins
Oh, let's do it one more time and do it all over again  Do it all over again Kaooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo I do
n't care at all, but Subaru-senpai
's nipples are gone, uh, he's got them.  How
many of them have you heard?
Two? Of course there are more than two. No, it's not because birds
are eggs. I
mean, it's become something of a specialty,
but I wonder if it's a cat. I'm so lonely.
My debut was in 2019
[Music] It's been a long time since I entered the
year,
so I'm
not safe.  2019
[Music]
Good year, I was able to get away with this.
This is bad. This is bad.
But now run, run, run, run. There are a lot of
artists who have gathered at a frightening speed.
I had the impression that No-chan was releasing quite a lot of albums.It's not a private station.No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.The
king was arrested by the police and
was interrogated.There
's someone like that.Ah, that's not Ronnie.Who was he to
arrest?  It's
true that I was
arrested. I do
n't remember being arrested at all. Surprisingly, I have
n't been arrested yet. I was so nervous that it
fit the theme of [music], but I ran away
.  [Music]
Great
[Music]
Han,
please move the rest.
I understand, do your best, bye-bye, do your best.
Okay, okay. Yumata was
arrested. He was arrested. He was
arrested again. It's because he was arrested. He's
arrested. It's Korea. It's Korea.  It's a country, it's a country, it's a country. I'll give you this
as well. Hey, which one is Korea?
Where are you looking right now? I'm
giving it to people who don't know. I'm giving it to people who are in captivity. I'm
giving it to people who have it. I'm giving this to them.
This is the candy Choco-sensei gave me.  It's
really surreal to see the shots in Korea,
but Noel-senpai has such a great sense of lighting and photography. I
get it, he won a lot. He's eating a lot of food.
It's a shot of him. He's a regular. I
hope he does his best in the second race. Good luck.
Do your best, cheer us on, and cheer us on.
Kia,
do your best. Wait, wait, I accidentally shot the drug.
Wait a minute. The mouse is
drenched. What's the situation? Why did you
just use the disinfectant? You accidentally fired the drug. It's terrible,
mouse.  The
mouse
got so wet, it
was
so
cute.  It's looking down, it's looking down, it's
moving, it's moving, it's moving, it's cute, is
n't it?
When I woke up, I might have been an engineer.
No, I've just entered an entry for a fugitive. It said, ``You're the one who
gets taken away and disappears. Stay strong, do your best.'' I
didn't realize it was a book that said a dangerous white brawl had begun. Eh.
Subaruzo's one was taken. Was
it the sound of you?
Or was it just a bar? Look, it's
starting, it's starting. I wonder if it's going to start. I wonder if it's going to start.  Do
n't worry,
go ahead and catch them all.
[Music] Do
your best, Barre-sama. You're the first one to come in. Do
n't do it. It's okay. Let's put it in. It's
expensive. I'm hiding here. I'm hiding here.
[Music]
Really.  I can't fit into the guy who's in the corner, he's
hiding in the corner, so if it's not
as expected, I'll lose,
but it looks expensive, right?
[Music] It's too
early, Moko-chan, it's all right, it's all right.
Who is Moko-san being arrested? I
can't see her name. It's called
Naekari-chan. It's expensive. It's expensive. It's
expensive. Yeah, it's expensive.  It's
good to catch cotton.I
just wanted to go there.I wonder
if the people of my tribe have ears.I
wonder what those ears are.  I guess it's just the ears. That's
right, Fana-senpai's horn is not so obvious. It's
not my fault, it's okay, it's okay, everyone,
catch it!
It's okay, it's okay, I'm
using it. Some of you are really using it.
11 is really good.
So let's
go. I'm gone. No, Mel-
chan is nothing but a fool. Mel-chan is just a
senpai.  No, no, no, it's different.
I'm in the red here. I
'm trying my best. You're so nice. Nice, nice, nice, nice. Nice, nice. You're
close to being nice. You're very Korean.
There's a best record. There's a best record. The best record. You're really, really good.  It
's
amazing, isn't it 2 next time Karawa Ayoshi Nice Nice Ah Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nast is in the way, please disappear Ah [Music] Hahahaha Ah Awesome
What's going on with that one from earlier? Wait a minute, it
's too much of a photo of Choco-sensei.
[Laughs] I
just took this. I'm
going to send it to Yatsuba. It's
too much. Ah, where is it? Ah, the smoke from work was so good. The smoke is
so thick.  Yeah, I caught a lot of it at the end. Yeah, at the
end, it's mostly blurry. Most of
the time, it's just floating, but the
ears are surprisingly few. But I was
a little surprised when the seniors were looking at my ears. I
don't have an image of that.
Well, I guess that's right, everyone is
dumb.I
wonder if that's why they don't get too much attention.I wonder if that's why I don't like it.But when it comes to judging beauty, there are quite a lot of people who are dumb.That's
right, Mio-chan Kamio.
chan It's like something other than that, it's a bonus stage, it's a bonus stage, it's true, it's a runaway.
It was a little hard to catch them when they were all gathered together. Hey, it's dangerous. Hide it, hide it, hide it, hide it, and someone got caught. But they hid it and hid it, and they were about 0 to 2 years old. That's right, 4 people too. You
can catch them.  It's okay to be caught, be careful
[Music]
Hey, you're caught, you're caught, you're caught. You're
hiding it like you're being lazy. It's
not your hair, it's your hair. It's
erotic. I
'll protect you a lot. It's true. I
have silver hair.
[Music] I'm
sorry it was the same.  I'm sorry.
[Music] I
'm sorry.
I'm bored. I'm free. I'm in trouble.
You can catch me if you want. I've
got a chance here. Go
ahead, please.
I'm going to ignore you completely.
Why didn't I do anything with my name,
Matsuri Senpai, Matsuri Senpai, Matsuri Senpai, I'm not
sexy,
that's sexy.
[Music] I was
really a little surprised, and I
'm glad I hid behind Taiya-sama. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.  I wo
n't say
it. I'll explain it to
you. Remu-
chan is disappointed. I'm here. It was moved without permission.
It's back.
PER moved without permission.
[Music]
Right?
Who's winning now?  I don't know, I don't
know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
know, I don't know, I
don't know where I was, Enu-senpai, sexy Ah, yes, yes, this
is Ha-chan, Nose-
chan
[Music]
Number 1
Sexy 1 Sexy 1  Ban
Seque
Nono No Nono no Sexy No
Sexy Eh Sexy, but there's no time to
wait here. Please wait and wait.
Oh, there's Kaessika
Caella sexy Kano sexy Sexy Sexy Sexy is
yourself.
[Music]
It's cool, it's cool, it's
cool, it's cool, it's cool
, it's cool, it's cool,
it's not sexy, it's cool, it's glossy, it's
glossy, it's glossy, it's a butt day, it's a
butt day.  I saw your butt a little while ago, but I
was in Korea, so I couldn't catch it there,
so I guess it wasn't sexy. Well, I guess sexy wasn't sexy enough. I thought
sexy was better, and I
wanted to be caught.
Just
in case, I can't tell at first. It's true.
So, I don't know what's going on, so please
close it. It's yellow. I want everyone to do their best, and I
want the other teams to run all the way to the end.
That's why I said yes.  So let's aim for the next competition Let's
move to the follow-up venue Evil please
please Please go to the middle or middle
[Music] Let's
go to the Acekans stadium where it's completely dark Let's
go to the next venue flow up Good luck
Upsaroor
[  [Music]
Floor
Amazu is missing, so English is
bad.
[Music] Let's go, let's go, let's go. Do you
say it in English
? School
School School Sue High School
High School Floor Up Follow Up Floor Follow Up
Stage 5 Follow
Up Stage Ro Rooftop  I wonder what it is on the rooftop What do you call it? It's
high ground. I wonder if it's high ground. Why don't you say
that you don't know what high ground is?
High ground
up I'm all excited about the passion Roof
top Luft Roof top To the top
Lulu Luft Go Gold Go Go Luft Top
Proof  Top Okay, let's go.
Lid, I see. It's on the roof.
Howtogo, I see. Howto
up. Now, what's that? It's interview time for all the contestants.
I see. I see. I see
. Good luck.  Do your best, try your best, but that's it. I feel
like I could have been on the phone with her at all. I wasn't too
nervous, but it wasn't that bad. In
fact, I
was really grateful for Chiara's presence. Thank you,
thank you, Shine and Passion
Ing.  I've
been looking up English for Repassing English, so I'm
going to spread the word a bit, but I have
n't used it even once.  I
heard that they usually
say "steak", "chicken" and "pork" in English.
Well then, I'll do
my best to convey that to you, Pifpork
chicken, Pifpork chickenki, I'll
forget about the chicken,
so I have to shout this out to my senior. Is
it beef, pork, or chicken? Beef, pork, chicken steak, steak,
steak, steak, beef,
beef, beef.  Fire Beef Bifa Bihu Fire
Steak Steak
Ah, I
'm hungry.
Someone said they were hungry. I'm
hungry. Oh, I'm hungry. It
's about 7:30, so it's dinner time.  That's
right, that's right, that's right, that's the case with the overseas group, right
? It's different, right? It's time, my senior.
Ah, 33am, uh, 3am, 33:30,
3:30am, not 3:30am.
Yes, it's not 3 a.m. Yes, it's the middle of the night. It's hard to
wake up all night. Good morning,
okay. Good morning, it's amazing. It's raining. Even
if it's late at night, thank you very much.
Senkyu Sekyu, it's okay. I
drank coffee. I drank coffee.
Nice coffee.  Nice Coffee Nice
Coffee Caffeine Caffeine is Important
Caffeine Minister
Caffeine Caffeine Let's
Go What's up with English? A
great person once said that if you just say Let's Go, you'll be fine.
It's true.  It's okay to believe in great people,
but Gozaru I-chan is throwing a trident.But it seems like Sui-chan is the only one
with creative authority.I
heard that's why she's popular.She
throws tridents, right?Oh, maybe that's it.
But I was on the other side
of here, editing Holomen Hunting
in creative mode,
and yeah, that's right, there are some traces of that left over, like
when I was practicing and flying.  I've been
throwing a javelin for about three days now. It
's an anzuru. It's in my hand. It's a try. It's a cunning
. It's a try. We're
fighting each other and my seniors are like, 'What are you doing? It's
okay, it's okay. I'm creative, so I'm going to come up.'
What are you doing?
Once upon a time, I went crazy and said I could do this.That's
true.I can't pick this up.I can't pick that up.I
can't pick that up.I took a picture of my teacher.
Please don't tell me about Teruhiha-chan's star reading. Please don't say it to me. Please stop saying it.
Channanakasu-chan is clearly reflected
. I put some of Trident's handmade marks
in Gypro.  I was
just checking the smell. I was also taking pictures.
It's gone. It's gone. It's
gone. It's gone. I'm in shock. Please
do it first. Ah, that's
right. What should I do? Don't stop.
What should I do?
Well, I guess it depends on how things turn out in the future.
Well, it depends on how things turn out in the rest of the day. I
'm going to lick my jackets. I'm not going to lick my jackets. What do you think
about this?  I'm
not asking you to
lick me. I'm happy
if you lick me. I'll deliver cookies.
Cookies. Cookies. Cookies. Cookies. Cookies. Cookies. To
everyone. I want to deliver them to everyone. I want to deliver them
to everyone overseas.  I want to feed them,
right? That's true, too. I
want to tell the world, after all, I want to tell them
. I'll take a break from streaming for about a month and
give them away for now. I'll
go to training. Let's go to training. Let's go to training.  Are you
going to
give it to Karamui Ame-chan?
Cookie present Cookie present color
Cookie yes cookie color is coming, coming It's coming
5 more seconds Let's go Chichiwa Chiwachi Let's
Go Robo Collets Go do your best Roboco-san Do your
best Do your best The
fight is good, oh so
beautiful  One, it
's tandedozaru. Practice, Akami. It's not that fast. Bi-chan looks really good. Bi-chan, you're good at it.
Do your best, Roboko-chan. It's Roboco's turn. It's okay, it's
okay, it's finally number two. Now,
nice, nice, nice.  It's all right Ah,
okay, okay, it's okay, I can do it now I fixed the startup
and now I'm
guessing it's probably a checkpoint and it feels like I've returned the points I see
Yes, yes, checkpoints are important
Yapaoi, I'm really competing with Sui-chan.  It's
true, it's true, it's great, it's great, it's great, it's great, it's great, it's great, it's great, it's great, it's
great.
No, this is really good. In the remaining time,
Pi is wearing it. It's true. Sui-chan is amazing.
But the 1st place is
very fast. Bibo is too good. Ao checkpoint.
Nice.
Sapoko,
Senpai Pokopoa, but I managed to wear something.  I can
go to the top of the viewpoint.
This is the point of view, I can go to this point. I can
go this. I can't go. I can't go. I'm
looking from below. It just looks from the bottom.  They
say you can go if you touch the signboard,
but it's a lie. It's the first time I've heard of an infected person. It
says "Entry" on the right.
Ah, I can go up, I can go up, I can go up, oh, it's
true. It's so amazing. I'll
chase after you. I didn't know about this place. Now, I don't know about it.  I
didn't have it, but Imaichi I feel like I got a close-up of it. Wow, this is amazing! It's true, everyone. Why are you all
floating so much? Did
you know that everyone's heads are floating
? Only their heads are floating. Pain, pain, do your best. Yes, it's
wearing clothes.  It's so nice that you're going to the store, it's nice, it's nice, it
's nice
, you're on your way to winning the book, you're
calm, you're stubborn
, oh, that pink one is sleepy.  [
Music] Do your
best, do your best, do your best
Sui-chan, do your best [Music] Nice Sui-chan, do your best, wow, this is so tough! Do your best, Sui-chan, do your best,
Sui-chan, do your best, Sui-chan, where is Sui-chan? He's
pitching amazingly with Raiden.  I'm so cute. I'm
looking forward to seeing you. I'm going to be a photographer. I'll do my best to become a photographer. I'll see
if I can do it. After all, it's from the fans' point of view. It's cool, it's
cool, it's steadily rising.  It
's not going up, it's going up, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's
good.  Just a little more, just a little more, let's do our
best,
that's nice, nice, nice
, nice,
nice, nice, G
G,
good game, good game, already!
I'm clapping with all my might. I
like this, everyone, everyone has cleared it. It's
amazing. Something strange is coming out.  Oh,
this is amazing.
Oh, you must be nervous. Yeah, yeah, okay. There's
something strange about the screen. Something is wrong with the screen.
This is what it is. I wonder if there's a chat setting or something like that. I wonder if
there's a controller or
something.  Hey, I don't really understand. It came out.
What did it come out?
Wait, I can't get off this. It's
a little something. Shift. Shift. Oh, it's a shift. I can
get off with the shift. Just in case, the shift is
fine. Yes, a
severed head flew off.  It's a little
surreal to see it come out. I'm sure it's going to come back with all these infections. Oh, it's back, it's back, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, tae. That's amazing. It's a bit surreal. I didn't know there
was a mode called Spectator Mode.  That's amazing.
People in this normal human state
can't see our heads. It's true that when they look at us from below, they
can't see it. They didn't see it. They didn't notice it.
That's why I thought it wasn't there.  I
can't help but feel that my existence is no longer a nuisance. I'm
back. I can't be
forced to go back. I've been writing about it one after another. I wonder
if they've been infected since the beginning. I
wonder if they've become infected after they died.  It was like when I
was looking at it from a dead body. It was like
leaving a ghostly body.
Eh, Next Kiara, I'm
rooting for you, Senpai. I have to do my best to cheer you on.
What do you do when you're cheering for people here?  Let's do
it, let's support each other in English, fight fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, Kiara-chan, do your best, it feels good.  That's why I practiced, so it's good,
good, good, good, I've
reached the point, it's so fast, it's so fast, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so
good, it's so
good, it's so good, I'm the
only one of you who has already gone 70m.  It's
too early, the checkpoint is too fast, wow,
wow, the checkpoint is too fast,
wow, I can't go there, wow,
it's too smooth.
As expected, I was
really nervous when I practiced flying in the air.I was
thinking about what to do, right?If I didn't think about
what to do, I
wouldn't have made any mistakes.
I don't know if I make a mistake, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know. Um, I
'm going to go up again. I'm not going to go up without chopping eggplant.  It's amazing, it's
amazing, it's so easy, it doesn't make any mistakes, it's really nice, it's a
brain mistake and it's come this far.
Okay, that's great. Which way are we
going? It's going that way. It's going that way.  But I
can go there as fast as if I had already decided on the route. Going up is really fast, really fast. It's
too much. It's
not nice. I tried to go back down. If I
fall here, the checkpoint will drop considerably.
I'm sorry, no, I'm not going to fall, Chiara
, I'm not going to fall, I'm not going to fall, it's difficult
Hey, maybe we'll make it to the top here, too. It's really big,
it's
so amazing, it's going to be really bad. Kia, do your best
at the end.
[Music]
[Applause] That's
amazing. It's so cool. It's
amazing.
[Music]
Too
nice, nice, Kia
[Music]
Nice, nice, look at how nervous you were
. You're starting to give in. You didn't seem nervous at all. You
were moving, but you were climbing like an RTA. You did
n't stop.  It's nice, nice,
nice, nice, nice, nice, too good. I
haven't scored 2 or 3 yet. It's not even
half yet. It's not even 150,
so I
waited about 90 seconds for the sake of being lazy.
Let's take a look.  That's right, that
character is fast
, isn't it?
Oh, I'm sorry, Nya-chan and Chloe
had a good fight. It's true, the black fell, and the
black was amazing. When I thought about it, they died. It's
difficult, isn't it? It seems like it's hard to get a sense of distance, though.
Kira, I really practiced,
so it's the result of all my hard work.It
looks like I practiced for a long time yesterday.
In the end, the yellow one is in second place, or the yellow one is in second place.
Wow, there's only
one more step left. No, it was just one more step.
Hey, it's already
flown. I saw the amazing moment when Daa-chan dropped it.  I was
cut off in an instant
and I fell. It was a really great battle. It
was amazing.
Nice chiara. It was so nice. It was chippy. It
was crackling
. Like a beautiful bird, it was flying like a beautiful bird. It was so nice. It
was so nice
here.  Also, it looks like the points from the second match will
be added up, but since
we had a Watsu finish, I think our
follower points are probably the highest. We were
in second place a while ago, so there's something.
Even if it seems like it's not possible at all, it's not possible at all, it's very likely.This point is being distributed now.If the
one on the screen over there
is a follow-up point, the white group's
points are currently 20, so the number one
point is now.  Now that I'm here, I'm
probably going to be number one. I
wonder if I can catch up. I'm so nice.
[Music]
Nanai was so nice. I'm
back. It's still the
same. I'm interviewing Kanamai. I'm still like that.
White group.  Only in our white group, both of us
are properly eavesdropping, right? We can go all the way to the top,
like a mountain, like a mountain, like a mountain.
Tanaiyano That was
amazing, I didn't make any mistakes. That's so nice.
Nice. The white team is currently in first place. It's
white 40, yellow,
38 red, 37.
Nice, nice. Nice
spoiler. You're
strong. Nice go, do your best.  Degozare, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Well, I have to do my best.The
pressure is on, and I'm
going to do it slowly, but I do
n't want to give up.I don't like the pressure, but I don't like the pressure.But it seems like Chisen and I don't have a good pair.This
time, I teamed up with Ra-chan.  Is that why you asked for it? I do
n't know yet. Thank you for your
hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. I'm looking at you mom. I'm
going to say yes.
So,
1st place, yes, that's what it felt
like earlier. 3 points, 60 points, 52 points.
Only 3 points left. Good luck with the 3 points.
Now, let's move on to the venue for the next competition.  It was
announced
that there was a jump from that. It was announced. It was announced. It was
out. It was out. It was out. It was out.
White was in 2nd place overall. There
was still a 3 point
difference. 3. Yellow was 63. White 6.  And Kiara-
chan,
that's nice. Thank you Taore. The game is serious.
Gugugu nafanafanafa. The two of you are so
cute. Don't
do it. Don't do it. Don't do it.
Do your
best. It's the end. I don't want to do it. I don't want to do it.
Enter on the right.  Where's
this? I'm going to go with this. I'm cute. I'm so cute. I'm so cute. I'm so
cute. I'm so nice. Nice, nice. I'm so cute. I'm so cute. I'm going to
ride on top of her.
If someone rides like that while holding a toneku,
wait a little bit and see if the general is in the top or the general is
in the top, so it's the one that gets clicked.If you
don't enter and if you enter, you'll
cancel and you can try again.  [
Applause]
Will that person from Hosk come?
Will that person from my pair come? Is that person
there? Will he come?
So
I wander around everyone, I
want to eat some food, so I'm hungry, I want to
summon something,
please release the naka-shogun.Oh
, okay, I
know that
Oh
[Music]
for
Ae Kano-sama
Where, where,
where, where, where, where, where, where, where, here, everyone
is here, everyone is getting more and more angry, it's amazing. This is so small that I can see where you are,
here, here, here, here, here, here, it
hurts. Is it okay to go? Is it okay?
How do you stop it? It's the same in that book,
just press it one more time just P
Ook
just nice nice nice nice
Aoyo I
mumbled too.
Wait a minute. Did you
say that in that outfit? He's
wearing a suit. He looks strong.
Suit suit.  I
made it. You look nice. You look strong.
That's better. You look too strong. It's okay. You wo
n't be charged a huge amount of money later. It might be
okay
. Thank you, Okayu-senpai.
Thank you for your wishes.  Yeah, it's
strong, ride it!
Taaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah
Aoka-senpai,
thank you for coming. I
'm going to ride. I'm going to
ride. Ka-senpai is going to sit on top of the senior I was riding in. I'm going to ask you to
sit in the chair for a while.
Okay, I'll leave it to you.
Thank you.  I'm so
happy, I have a mo on my ear, but it's on my butt. It looks like there
's a chocolate corner stuck in it.
It's the leader. It's
better to fit it together a little bit. It might
be really hot.
This is my senior's horn, and it's stimulating me a lot.  I'm sure I'll
win.Hello,
NekoMataOkayu, thank you for today.Thank
you very much.Thank
you
very much.  So,
please, please teach
me how to do it. I want to lead you to victory.
Please, thank you
very much. Yes, let's do our best, everyone in the white team, we'll
do it. We'll do it.  I'll
do my best.Okay,
then finally I want to ask the Kigumi group.KigurumiGuruGumi-
gumi or Kumi-gumi's group Hey, what's the strategy
?I wonder if everyone in the white group is going to get angry.I think they'll
get the best kill after all.
Well, 1 point will be added. I don't
think so. I'll defend and probably attack. The
opponent will focus on me, and everyone will be
able to wake up the one who approaches the general.
Oh, I think it's more likely that people who are close to the general will do more and more. It seems
like the weaker ones will be more likely to beat up the weaker ones. I
can see their part, so I
wonder if it's the person who wants to do it, please.
At first, you'll be near the general and when you see 1 heart, you
'll attack. It's
more scary than Rika. I
think this will probably be a voice chat between that pair, so I wonder
if that's the case. Is there that kind of
voice?  Chat voice I
think there is a chat name, so now that I
think about it, there is a real place in the middle of nowhere. You
can't get it unless you cooperate with everyone. It
looks like the general is going to protect you.
Oh, the general.  Neji, let's
do our best, we'll do our best, but we're both
being targeted. I think we should go cover. If you
find us, it looks
like we're going to be picked on. If it starts to feel like we're going to be attacked, then I
think we'll probably have to move from here.  Oh, let's go
Let's go Let's go
Oh hello hello [
music]  [
Music] Let's go let's go [
Music]
Let
me
[Music]
JAiiYeah Let's go Let's go
for
Lastof
see
YeahTryBEST
beonepun
dageME
MEMOVE
andiiovONEonlythat
OnlyYouand
ATTthe
Yeah Yeah
Yeah
[Music]
dage
Nnnnnnn
IknowwhyIReally
Love
[Music]
thetheHold
upHold
upafter
prinbe
prin
[Music]
know
areyou
goingor
Princessdone
done I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll
do it  [
Music]
see
Need
[Music]
okok
ta
tite
[Music]
Nice Ah
Oh
done
seeOhYeahOKfine
[Music]
OKLetseethenext
announcementaresing
nowOhNoahSee
Ok
Oh
[Music]
Yes have
REG
MayOKandwhereare
[Music]
you
OK
back
SWORD
Wood
Oh
okay
[Music]  [Music]
H
know
GU
[Music]
J
May
[Music]
A
Igo
for let's go hard ten
o
[Music]
going
oneone
[Applause]
one
KOk
LetSE O
Dopry
goodliketheTeamthe
TE
okokok
F
AllIsLastOneMore
[Music]
SCTeam
WIN
Turn
[Music]
know
ONE wa
more
[Music]
are
OK
[Music]
knowsee
people
Ihavepeopleonmy
hand
Lisa
Mice do my best
[Music]
people
pleas
[Music]
MOVlittle
cred
OKthink
rck
me
May
best
know
anyTurnpeopleATTUS
Yeah
MaybeONEHEART
[Music]
ONEThisisthis
is
Nai Nai
Nai
Fafa Fa Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice
Nice
O Oh Miko Miko Obe
Ya
[Laughter]
OK
Nachi
O
310 O
[Music]
Go Go
killskills
kills
[Music]
Hey know
of
know
Su
agressive
[Music]
Nice One Nice
One Looks
Againkills
killskills10
1097 Nice One Nice One Looks Againkills killskills10 1097 Nice One Nice One
Looks Againkills killskills10
iovYeahMaybeIknow
maybewejustneedto
wait
RES
Oh
goa
[Music]
Gogone
10g Eiame-chan is also a 10
kill overseas kill machine
Killma was amazing Nemidayoe It's
amazing  We did it,
no, this is amazing
. We've had quite a lot of fun. 41
did it. We did it too. 41 did it. We did it too. Nice,
nice, Nasu. Nice, no,
escaping is important. So it's
nice.  1
Killna Nice Nice Nice Suki If it
wasn't for that one kill, I'd be at 40.
Yeah, yeah, that's right, it's important, important,
important, nice. Nicely-
chan is
strong, very strong. Strong, Su-a-chan, Roboco-san, the pair was also
amazing. Nice, Nice, I was really surprised.
Oh
wow, everyone is doing a great job! It's amazing.
Nice, nice,
nice. I wonder how this is
going. I wonder if we've gone quite far. I
think we've made a comeback. It
feels good, it feels good.  In the second match, it was number 2,
maybe number 2, or something like 25.
Red was also strong in its own way, so it happened
many times. I'm sure red was strong. Well, it was
amazing at first. I
wonder what's going to happen.  I'm scared,
and Momo and Hime are both shaking and trembling. Mu-chan, let's
do our best. It's okay, we can win. It's okay, it's okay. It's okay, we can
win. We can win. During practice, the
yellow group dodged me for about a minute and a half.
However, I would like to say that they would serve that kind of food for some reason,
but I'm seriously reading this,
but the
content of Lome Hunting has changed quite a bit
since the update came out, so I guess the menu has also changed quite a bit.
Yes, that's true, that's possible, that's totally
possible, yes, that's
possible, that's possible, that's true, that's true, that's true, that's true, that's possible, that's possible, that I
want to win, that I want to win, that I've come this far,
right?  I
felt like I was getting greedy, but somehow I was
starting to see a victory.I was
n't
trying to tear it down just now, but I just tore it to pieces.  Do
n't tear off the skin, do
n't tear it off, that's so wild,
take care of it, you're
muscular, you're proud of your muscles, you're so proud of your thighs, you
look so good at the end 41
Ki
Senpai Miko Senpai turned bright red from the glue
[laughter]
It was too strong. How was it? The number of
kills was amazing. Who was the one who got the most kills
? Kia was also amazing. At the very end, I'm
sorry, but I defeated Su-senpai twice, and I
defeated him once.  Who was the one who was
being lied to? There were a lot of people like Kara, it was
huge, it was
amazing. That's why the white team was amazing.
But at the end, I'd like to say a little bit about Nekomata porridge.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Please give me your thoughts.
Yes, yes.
Thank you very much. It was a pleasure to play with you all. I will
continue to support the White Team.
Thank you very much.
Thank you also disappeared in an instant.
[Music]
Thank you very
much. Thank you, too.  I'm doing number kills,
so it's totally different if I had it. I
worked hard. I tried my best. It's going
to change. So, thank you very much. It was really fun. It
was really fun. It was fun. It was fun. After this.  There's
a lot of pressure in competitions. There's a
lot of pressure. There's a lot of pressure.
Let's relax and hope. It's okay. It's okay.
Everyone who can do it can do it. It's okay. It's okay. It's
okay. I guess it's okay. I have to
protect the princess. Even if I have to protect the princess, I'm a
princess.  Even if I make a mistake, I can catch up with the relay.The pressure is
terrible, it stings in the world, and it
stings in the spider too.I'm
climbing the ivy right now.Everyone is climbing the
ivy, and I'm in a hurry to climb it,
but somehow I'm getting better at the ivy.  It's nice, I can do
it, it's difficult, isn't it? It's difficult, it's not good. I
told you that when I heard it today,
where did you do it? Well, it looks
like the scores have been tallied, so I'd
like to take a look.  Here are the specials for the total of the three games.
Red team did their best. It's a little
bad. No, the red team has 46 points, the red team has 46 points, the white team has 38 points.  It's
all
good, so let's move on to the second half of the race after Nema.So
let's
go to the next one.Okay, let's move on to the next race.  Let's do our best, do our best,
do our best, let's do our best, let's do our best, let's do our best, let's do our best, let's do our best.  Do your
best, Oka-tan has entered the princess race. Hime-hime seems to be strong. If the princess is number one, then the strong-looking princess is the one who is the strongest. She will be crushed by the strongest force, and she will go on tight. Thank you very much
. I
want you to go on tight.  I wonder if they're going to shake hands? I'll
do my best, I'll do my best, I'll
do my best. It's so cute wearing a tiara. I
thought Jo-chan was crying. I
thought she was laughing. I was so surprised by the way Hime-chan laughed.
[Music]
Yeah,
when
love
knowhappTearshapp
happ
happ, that's good.
[Music]
[Laughs]
Why is Eka-chan smiling like that?
JustJust
My,
play with your own 3D
Yeah, you
were laughing, yeah, it's fun
, aren't you
streaming KOh
[Music]
Yeahlookat
myamIhave
OpenPARTY
PARTY
Oh
snak
B Yeah
pry This is only the first round Yeah, it's supposed to be Yeah,
it's scary It's just one round One
game  There's pressure, pressure,
and I'm kind of nervous.
Well, I'm going to participate in this because Kana-tan is a princess,
and Mei-chan, and
Azuki-chan, Azuki-chan, and Kama-chan. Unana, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru, Naru.
Well, I've done cooking before.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's
right. I did it myself, so I had to cut it, cut it, etc., and there are
various processes
involved. If I can't share the roles, I'll lose money.
Time is running out. Cooperation is important. Cooperation.
Yeah, yeah, that's true
. But on the other hand, Minecraft, he's been doing this for about three years,
and
he thought, oh, you can cut vegetables. I thought so, too. Yes, you can
cut vegetables.  That's right, I thought, ``Oh yeah, there's a knife.'' There's an
item for cutting boards, and when you
click to open it, you'll see a knife, and if you put it next to it, you'll be able to
cut tomatoes, carrots, potatoes, etc. Oh yeah, and beef, too.  When you put it in, it
turns into ground meat.It's meat, Yakiniku meat, special,
so it's really amazing.That
normal salt doesn't cut it, but this time it seems like it's special salt.Ah,
that's the kind of stage it is.Oh, yeah, that's right, you
can do it.  That's amazing. There's
definitely a possibility for Minecraft. I wonder if they
've done any kind of setting or something like that. I'm so
impressed by this, but
from Kara-chan's point of view, it
seems natural.  Maybe
that's why I'm smiling
[laughter] I'm
relaxed
[laughter] I
laughed Kakoa
Mamama You're
kind
Thank you, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do
your best, I saw you on the road the other day.
Well, here we are, so you've just
arrived here Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go,
you can persevere, we're going
smoothly, we're building a foothold, even if you're impatient, it's going
well, hey, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's
fine.  Oh, oh, case, it's so
slow, it's so smooth, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's really good, it's really good, it's
good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good,
it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's nice, it's
number 1.  It
's
brown. It's made of wood. Oh yeah.
What's this? This is also a
new stand. I guess what they're making is this.
Oooooo What was it?
It was the one you just made.  No, I don't understand at all. From here, I
don't understand. It's white and white and pink.
This is so sweet
. What is this? What is this? Why?
What are you doing? What are you doing?  I wonder what they're making. I'm really
curious.
When I was practicing, it looked like a homemade hamburger.
Yes, it's a homemade hamburger.
What does it actually look like? What are you
making? What are you doing now?  I'm
cutting the giant. I'm cutting a vegetable. I'm cut off the vegetables I'm cutting the
vegetables, I'll do my best, do my
best, I'm going to do my best, I'm
going to have fun.  Wait, Isuna, you
're already up to stage 5.
Good luck, but you're only at stage 2. No, but red,
strong, red, strong, but fast, fast,
fast. You can go,
go, go, go, go, zombie.
This princess is a gorilla, that's right.
That's right. This princess, our princess, has 50 ki of strength.
That's why I'm so sorry. Do your best, try your best, do your best. One
chan, one chin, one chan. There's one. There's one. There's one. There's more and more. Wow, it's
coming out.  Let's do our best, let's do our best.It
looks like the final boss,
but
something in the back isn't floating.It
looks like it's really strong.
Do your best, try your best,
boss, do your best, do your best, but you can
still do your best.
3 seconds,
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
wow wow I wonder what you
were making I'm
sure I
'll ask you about it I said
to Lo the white one I didn't understand at all, but if it was that
certain feeling it would be brown  I don't know what it
was. I don't care. But yellow. That
was amazing. That last catch up. I
was so close to the edge just now
. It's not my cat. What happened to me yesterday and
now?  Who it was, I couldn't figure it out in an instant.
That was wrong.
Hmm, I'm so nervous. I wonder if I
can go fishing for flowers at this hour. I'm
not doing an interview. I don't even think I'll
just
go there right now.  Air conditioner It's an air conditioner, isn't
it? It's hot in the room. You should open the room. Let's avoid it. I can't live without an air conditioner. Yes, but I don't have an air conditioner at all in my house in Austria. Yeah, but what about the weather?  It's quite hot in the summer, so I
'd like you to turn on the air conditioner, but I usually don't have an air conditioner in my house,
so it's so hot that I can't think of anything.
Unlike Japan, they have to be great.
Even if they say no to chocolate, they'll act quickly.
If it were now, I'd keep the image quality on all the time.
Oh,
and
Air
Conditioner Love Lala. I wonder if they're compiling the data right now. Is it an inter-county tally? This Tsuji is
here.  And at the end, I'm
really weak at actual performances, so I'm scared, okay? I can go, it's
okay, it's
okay, I'm scared of the actual performance. Yeah, it's okay, but I'm going to be the first one with Lissa-chan, so I'm going to be
super nervous.
Yes,
you're right, but it doesn't matter how many times I've done it after that.
Everyone can fix something, so I guess I'm going to admit that I made that mistake.The person who
feels the most pressure is
probably the last one, Iroha-chan, the last one.I'm home
now, oh, go home, go home, go home, go home.  I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I
'll give it to you, and I'll pass the baton.Ah
, it's an ordinary person, or something like that.Somehow, it's somewhere in
the middle.It's not
okay, I want to do my best, but I don't know about the
real thing.  Because sometimes you
can't do what you used to do, so I
understand why you get anxious, right? I guess the
points in the relay are high after all. I wonder what it will be like
in the last competition.
Even now, the red team is probably pretty big.  I'm in the
lead, right? That
's
right. Every time it goes up, I get the impression that it's going to be high at the end. I understand. It means that a reversal is possible. So, let's take a look at the scores for the Etsu race.
Yes, the red team was in first place, so it's 30 points, the
white team is 20 points, and the yellow team is 10 points.The
red team is a bit amazing.Maybe the
red team will be strong in 2023.I do
n't know yet.It's still strong, so I don't know.
So from now on, let's
move to the end of the next competition trace.
Aoshi,
Oisho, Tire, come, come, chacha, etc. I was sent away
without
permission.I was sent away without permission, and everyone went home.Ori-
senpai was an amazing cook.It
was very fast.What was he making?What was he
making?You can tell by the rum.  It's a
lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, kantara,
lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb, lamb.  Actually,
I'm
sorry for losing it.
What's up, Tsurugi-chan? I'm sorry, tomorrow.
After this, the Spring/Summer East Relay will be held, so
if you're going to participate in the Reel,
please move to the Eshiro-gumi contestant channel.  I wonder if I'm being blown away.
Excuse me. I see. Before Nodoka-chan's announcement was made, the contestants were called out. I see, cutting-edge technology is cutting-edge technology for a moment. It's surprising and easy to understand, so it's helpful. I
'm going to investigate and go to Ohana. Dash.  Let's
go, let's go, let's go, let's go, it
's better to enter, right? Well, if we
enter, we can get a book, so we can
choose who we are, who is white, here we come, we've
come, we've come, we've come
Kitaki-san, are you okay? Right click.
[Music]
Yeah, the entry list is number 8.
How many numbers are mine and Ame-chan? It seems like it's
in the middle with the memory group leader,
right? Yame-chan 5  Layer number 5 No. 5 big hey
Anonymous This and that Anonymous is 33
Okay, I see. I wonder
if I've been able to enter with this. I've done it. I've
done it. It's
nice to say that I've been able to do it.  Don't be too weak, it's okay. Can we
go? Oanca, it's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's
okay. It's okay. You'll be nervous. In the end, you're right.
Ah
ONE. Ah, I've
made the entry. Ah, I'm done. Ah, but I'm already at 9.
Music]
Onana,
nice, nice
, no, this one-chan, this underwater diving.It
's the order of the contestants.Okay, the first layer is
Eneri.Okay, next is Choco Sensei, the third student.Mui, the
fourth person is Captain Noel.Then the fifth layer is
Ame.  However, the 7th layer is Azusan, and finally,
as people get to know each other, it feels like people who are used to Minecraft gradually come in. It
feels like they're about to catch up.  So, let's
do an interview. Yes, that's right. I
bought it, everyone in the white team. Good
morning. How about it
?
Well, who should I talk to? Nada, ah, then, ah,
Iro. When I noticed that Ankage 5 was in Game 5, he
became an anchor.  I
think it's because I'm fast, so I'm saying that I'm trusting you. No, it's great. It's
white. I hope you get first place.
Do your best, do your best, do your
best. Thank you, Zhang. Yes, then.
Finally, Niyabikuri-san
[laughing] Wow, I
just came back from Hana. Welcome
home. I just got home, and
when Sora-chan was confused, I
didn't hear her say, ``Open book, open book.'' Oh, I didn't get it.  I'm a man and a
woman who have had embarrassing and embarrassing experiences.Okay,
let's do our best.The water
is so bad here.It's just luck.We were at the bottom at the beginning.Let's
do our best.Let's try our best.Let's try our best.Let's do our best.  I
fell in.
But here I am, the water is so loud.
[Music] It's
okay
. I practiced nervously, so I'm holding my breath. I'm
starting to get into a mental state.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay. Do your best. It's okay. It's
okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.  Yes, it's
Korea today, it's okay. Remember, it's
okay. You're really working hard. It's okay. It
's the end, so it's a casual ending. We'll
laugh at the end, and then we'll
eat some delicious meat.  Let's go,
let's talk about the chocolate line, Azuki and the chocolate line.Oh yeah, that's right,
meat yakiniku.  Come on, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, you're good, you're good, you're good, you're good, you're good, you're good, you're
good.  It's
okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.  I was rooting for you, but now I do
n't understand myself.
[Music]
Oh, do your best, do your best,
oh,
oh, oh, oh, so tense.  Do your best,
do your best, Ini-chan's Ini-chan, you can
go, it's okay, Don Don Don Do, Do Ya, it's okay, dodge it, do your best, trust me [Music] Do your best, do your best, do your best, do
your best.  Let's
go, let's go, let's
go, let's run,
oh, fast, fast, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, bad, bad, bad, good, good, good, good, good, good,
good luck, Kara-chan, do your best.
Good
[Music]
Gogogogo
Go, go, do this, get sucked in
[Music]
Go, nice, nice,
okay, finally, do your best, do your
best, do your best, senpai, it feels like you're going to hit me, it's okay,
right? It's okay, I'll hit you properly, it's
okay.  It's okay, it's okay,
let's eat, let's eat, try our best, try our best, try our best,
try our best. We can't do our best, Nana. Yes, we can do our best. Go,
Roroha,
okay. Where's the food? It's okay, it's okay, it's okay. It's amazing, let's go, let's go! Let's go!  It's good, it's good, it's nice, it's nice, it's nice, it's nice, it's nice, it's nice, it's a nice fight
, it's nice, it's a good run, I was nervous, I
worked hard, I'm all done, I
'm good, I'm strong, I'm good, you're strong
Hey, I forgot to eat Oh, it's
okay.  Yeah, I'm hungry, I'm hungry. Let's
eat a lot when we're done.
[Music]
Yes, nice run, nice
run,
nice run. Nice, yeah, yeah, nice. I want to eat some meat.
[Music]
Eating meat, let's go. Meat, yes, yes. My heart
hurts.
Thank you for your hard
work, Japanese sub-sub, I want to eat. I'm going to eat all the good food. Reluctantly, let's all eat shabu-shabu. Shabu-shabu. Beautiful shabu-shabu. Beautiful shabu-shabu. Let's go and make shabu-shabu. I'm sure the
chocolate line will pick up my dick and take me.  Give
me all the chocolate Let's
leave it to you Sensei I'm very good super
nice
Yeah Leave
it to me
Leave it to me You did your best
[Music]
Please You
did your best in the interview You did your best You did your best You did your best You
did your best Thank you for your hard work You did your best Well then, I'd like to
be the anchor for a while Iroha
Let's listen to the story one more time. How was it?
We were the best. From the beginning to the end,
everything was okay. It was okay. It was okay. It was
okay. It was okay. It was okay. It was
okay.  There was a time when I wanted to be overtaken, but I
ended up in 2nd place. It
was a great race. It was a
nice fight.
Thank you, sir. Are you using it? Are you using it? Hey, how many days are you going to take a break with Yoyoyoke? Tao [Music] I'm tired on the way home. I'm tired. I'm a grade 1 student in the exam order. It's amazing, it's already amazing.  I
lost, you know
, tears. I'm
glad you're such a sensitive person.
No, I'm in 2nd place. I'm in 2nd place. Did you think you could get it? I
tried my best. I tried my best. Everyone, I
tried my best. I tried my best.  At first,
to be honest, I
had the feeling of having fun, and I was like, ``I'm going to do my best, even if it's difficult,'' but I didn't
expect it to happen, so I didn't understand until the end.I
said
yes at first, so I'm going to use this phone.
Everyone, please gather in front of the dais.
[Music]
First of all, I'm from the school.
There was a stinking wall in the house, and now there was a wall in the house. I was
surprised to be trapped.  We've
been sealed away. Now we're locked up in this school. I'm
shouting a lot and my throat is a bit
rattling. What's more
, the white group is beautiful, beautiful.
[Music]
Hey, what are we practicing? This is what we're doing, so it's okay, group.
It's a mess.
[Laughter]  ]
Jou Yeah, after all, I feel like I'm going to have a tonality,
so I'm going to match the tonality, and I'm not going to lose anymore.
That team seems to have a completely different color.
Boruka:
Well, I'm
doing well, and I'm
doing a Suma,
but I'm doing a
lot of work,
and the
ceremony begins, and I don't know
what to do, and I hear that growl, and I don't understand it at all,
but yeah,
everyone is really cooperating with each other.  I
tried my best and it was a close battle every year.I
thought it was really worth watching and it was amazing.Yes,
that's true.In each case, there
was drama, or rather, there was
drama.I think it was a drama, including the practice.But,
yes.  I think it was really good.Everyone,
my mom is not home, so now I'm
going to come over.It
made me feel a little nervous.It's great.It's
amazing how strong you are with one word.It all
calmed down all at once.I want to
But everyone has begun to properly bow down.
I'm scared of the feeling that things are going wrong in our relationship. I don't think so.
Yes, that's fine. Well then, everyone, can I ask you if your voice is
being heard? It's being heard. I
'm hearing it.  So,
before the closing ceremony, I would like to say a few words to
everyone who
supported Nechan, A-chan, and Nodo-chan, who have been using voice chat a lot for this competition.
Thank you
very much, thank you very much, thank you very much, thank you very much, thank you very much. Thank you for your hard work. It's the
voice of heaven. Thank you,
thank you.
No, thank you again this year.
Your hard work and individuality are overflowing
Thank you very much for your cooperation.Thank you very much for your
cooperation.Thank you very much for your cooperation.Thank
you very much to all of you for your cooperation.
Thank you very much for your cooperation. Thank you, everyone. I
'm sure it was fun for all three of you to participate, so
please do your best until the end.
Thank you very much. So,
everyone, let's move on to the
closing ceremony.  First
of all, I would like to give a closing address. I would like to ask Ms. Samiko, the chairperson of the sports day committee, to give a greeting. Yes, yes, everyone, this sports day was
fun. It
was fun. It was fun. It was fun. It was really fun.
Good job everyone.  Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Every year, I'm
thankful that
Goro Live has gotten busier and busier.
But still, I'm glad to see everyone coming together like this,
everyone working together, taking the initiative to call out to each other
and help each other.  You know,
Miko and the others have already seen it all, so I'm
really, really overwhelmed with emotion
every time.
Thank you very much for your continued cooperation.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you, thank
you.  Thank you very much for giving me the opportunity. I'm looking forward to talking
about the newcomers,
en, and other memos in the future. I
think it would be great if we can have more interactions and make Hololive even more exciting, so I hope you'll continue to support us in the future.
Yes, yes,
yes, please. Thank you very much. Thank you, Tsuzuki-chan.
Yes, everyone participated again this year
and did a great job.
Thank you
very much.
Thank you very much.Next, Subaru is now
Subaru as well.As a
result of that contact, I have been able to see various aspects of the team,
but
all the teams are working hard.
Well, I'm sure we'll see some results this time, but I
think it's one thing that we all did our best together. I
think this big gift will become a treasure, so I hope that we can make use of our bond in the future.  It
was really fun to watch. Thank you very much.
[Music]
Thank you very much.
Nice Peach Nice
Nice.  I
would like to make one presentation in the order of 1, then 100, then 10 or so.Now
then, Mr. Samiko, the sports day executive committee chairperson,
would you please make a specific presentation?
Yes, then.  First of all, I'm going to announce from about 1.
Okay,
so here
's the door. You can see this. The red team is 8, the
white team is 8, and the yellow team is 6. I want to see what the
picture is, what's what, what's scary right now.  Announcement It
's scary, I don't know
yet. Okay, then let's continue. We announced about 100 first. Yes, yes, 106 is here. Go ahead! Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's so bad. I still don't understand. All of them.
About 100."  Well, please, please, it's dangerous.
No way, I'm going to go to the end, everyone. Please,
please, please, let's announce about 10 at the end.
[Music]
Wow, that means yes. So, what,
what, what, the winner is red. Red 158, white,
138 yellow.  I got 106,
but it was a little
more, but I understand.
[Music] It
's Rito, and the second place was 138 points, and the third
place was 106 points, making it a group.
Well done, everyone,
did well. Well done, well done. Good job, everyone.  I'm
glad you did.Okay, so I'll give the
awards.There's going to be an awards ceremony.Well,
everyone, I'm going to give the same medal to the yellow group.It's
Geo.Okay, well, I'm going to go ahead and present the yellow group
's athletes and teachers.  Hassu Kana Habe
Chanbe-chan, please come to the front Please
come here
Please Hassu Well then, for third place, please give me a
medal How about points?
Congratulations on that! It's amazing! Congratulations on that
! It's amazing how you're wearing it! It looks like you're
wearing it! Next up is the white team with a silver
medal. It's a golden medal.
Please don't follow me,
Tachimoe I'm a little
looking forward to it, but I'm excited. It's an amazing medal. Congratulations to the white team.
[Music]
What a great medal. Congratulations on the
cute medal.
Congratulations.
Thank you.  Thank you
and congratulations! I
want to see the medal.
Thank you and congratulations.
[Applause]
[Music] I wonder if
this is Hololive. It
disappeared so quickly.  There were so many
missing diamonds, but they
disappeared in an instant.I'm not saying that it's okay.I'm going to blame
Hololive Daidokai 2023 for the above.Thank
you everyone.Thank you very much.  I'd
like to take a commemorative photo at Seksan, so I don't know
what to do. Let's
take it on that stand in the middle over there. Yes,
please. Yes, it's on top of the front
. Ok, let's move. Kamokamokamokamo. I wonder if it's somewhere.  I'm
in a game where I can't go back. Is my
husband okay? Kanata is
dangerous. Everyone is lined up in the upper right corner. This one can fit
in too. Yes, this one can fit in too.
Lee,
Sorry,
Lee-chan, is that okay?
Yes, it hasn't arrived yet.
It's on us too. Everyone's lying. They're lying to us. Oh, it's
true. I'm so happy. I
failed once, so I don't have a medal.
But seriously,
[Music] I ca
n't help it
. It's not like that. If I try it one more time, I
won't lose my temper. It's okay, it's okay. That's
definitely the case.
Mel, yes, I can go.
Wait a minute, senpai, that's it, senpai.
Please take a look. I was able to touch it.
Thank you,
thank you. Thank you, that's good. Okay,
everyone. Where should I look at that little thing right in front of me
?  I wonder if it's okay if I look at Koro-
san. Koro-san. I'm looking
at Koro-san. Koro-san. Hey, he's flying. Taaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
There's someone here. Cameraman.
Yes, everyone. Can you see it?
I'll take a picture.
[Music]
Mermerka Mercari
Hey, hey, hey, who threw it? Who
threw it now? Who threw it this year? By chance,
someone threw it.  Hey, we're all
throwing
things, throwing things, here we go again. Hey, don't throw away the trash, take the trash home with you. You
can't see the box.
Thank you very much for the squid. Thank you to that listener who
helped out with his and his comments.
Thank you very much to all the staff for your continued support.
Thank you.  Let's
go, Holo
[Music]
[Music] Let's get along, let's
get along
[Music] Bye-bye, bye-bye everyone Bye-bye everyone Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye Bye-bye-bye-bye
[Music]
Bye-bye
Eeusu hun Wow Fu-
bye-bye
[Music]
Adeo
Ade
PatiforLast
Tapafor
Last
Yabai A
Howto
partypartypartybeI
go
Party
Fire
this
[Music]
with Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
]
What
thanyouso
muchSUAll
[Music]
Of
guys
[Music]
ト
Hey No
way
YE
OK
Not
EnoughHold
On ah
oh
bye bye
Rishi seesee
Baba
[Music]
し