[Music]
so
you didn't see that did you you did not
see that
anyway didn't see anything
no no
[Music]
good evening hello oh
it is time for the nintendo direct
of e3
[Music]
thank you for the super chat thank you
and for the membership welcome
and it starts in 10 minutes
uh i hope you guys have it already if
not let me give you a link
uh wait
i mean you can watch it in on the other
channels as well if you prefer to watch
it in german or japanese or whatever but
manage your song
thank you for i was just about to put it
there but
uh you you uh
[Music]
um so yeah we'll be watching it in
english
um no audio no the
video as usual in our watch lungs
i know nintendo it does not allow
showing the nintendo direct
here on screen and we are aware of that
and have permission to stream it
by just reacting to it and just not
having
it on screen it's all good no need to
worry guys
we got it covered and we are ready
the thing is though is that
japanese link really
oh oops ah i need to reopen the
chat window
is that the japanese link maybe maybe we
should
put up the english link in my son
if that is the japanese yeah i know the
japanese tends to be a bit different or
like
sometimes a little bit longer
uh we'll be watching it in english
jen masan only she moves
i need to open the comments again close
the comments accidentally where are you
where are you just
chat pop out welcome back chad
i can see you i can see him now
did it did it did it change
the link change yet otherwise i'll do it
i'll do it
yes okay thank you
thank you jmt jmt and
let me let's i will let you guys know
that i
actually never ever have watched
uh e n e3 ever before
can you believe it i watched nintendo
direct
like the yeah but i know what's in
you guys are so surprised me too yay
i i don't know i knew about the
existence but i never really
no really i don't know never real never
really paid
much attention to it um
and i guess i would um no i don't know
it was not the time
zone but i just never oh
i don't know i just i i wasn't ready for
it
uh my body was not ready for it i
uh even if i watched no and i watched
never
saw anything from it but i did watch
other people's direct
reactions to nintendo directs
[Laughter]
and that's about it
nintendo director our bodies are ready
we are ready
yeah i heard uh up until now the past
few days there hasn't been
um much for my interest
like i asked you guys if there was
anything that
could interest me and uh you guys said
no
but hey today uh later today there will
be also
the e3 presentation from bandai namco
and maybe
maybe there's something for me there
maybe more tales of a rise trailers that
i haven't seen before
i mean that's already out there they
bandain uncle can
not make it any better they cannot
surprise me anymore i think with
anything like super
amazing because i already know about
tails level rise if they would announce
something else tail self-related a new
tesla game that is absolutely impossible
uh but yeah tenth of a rise is coming
out in
september the ninth which is why we
already know about it so
i don't i don't know if there's there's
a foreign
isn't there already information about
the next ninokuni
um you know what i did see and what
looked cute
was uh ace ace attorney uh
something regarding that chronicles
i don't know that looked kind of cute i
know ace attorney
oh yeah besides that i don't know yeah
ninokuni i wanna play ninokuni
i wanna play it i wanna play it
i i watched there's a movie right i
think i watched the movie
four minutes to go five minutes oh for
everyone who's watching this
uh in the archive i don't know how
you're going to line it up with me i'm
just going to say
exactly when it starts because right now
we're staring at the screen
that's just you know the banner and
that's it uh i guess i'll just
let the archive people know whenever
there's
like something starting yeah
but i think most of y'all are just
are just uh so excited that you're gonna
what you're you will be watching it live
with me
i will try to be hmm
do you guys want me to be mostly quiet
so you can focus as much as possible on
what's going on or
or hmm should i be
should i be not so not i i mean i'll
probably want to
i'll probably want to hear that
information so
be quiet no no no feel free
okay okay i'll just i'll just go with
the flow
if there's something really important
sounding like especially for breath of
the wild
too then i'll shut off because we want
to know all the details about it
okay
i know i know that most of you say do
whatever but there's also a lot of
people
i think that are like kiana shut the
up
but yeah you're also here for my
reaction i guess i'm here for your
reaction
i don't know if my reaction will be that
crazy because
i don't know i i
i'm generally not like following
all these kind of things up that close i
just
when most of the time most of the time
like for example with what was it
eldon rink i didn't know
about that until the other day when it
was when the trailer came out and
everyone was
excited about it on twitter i was like
oh so that was a thing
never knew about that
so i don't know anything about anything
at all not very informed
about two minutes let's go and also
we've been reading super chats after
this is over because this will be what
40 minutes
uh we will not be watching the treehouse
because that's much longer
yeah three hours that's a bit too long
or maybe you know what you know what we
can have it open in the background while
while we're eating super chats oh
oh actually that sounds interesting yeah
we can do that it's gonna be the same
stream right
it's not gonna be a different stream so
we can just leave the window open
yup okay
okay i'm ready what sounds off
collection
he's hoping for a tails off collection
you mean like
several games in a bundle for
the switch oh you know what would be
i i played tales of berseria on
i think i played it on playstation
but it's also on pc right is it also on
switch bezaria
because if not they could maybe like put
it on switch that could be maybe an
announcement but
no way they probably what is this dario
on switch
i played it i don't i just don't
play it on pc it's not on switch
oh do you see that maybe they could put
it over to the switch
uh what do you call that what's the word
for that
uh uh
uh what 10 seconds oh my god a port yes
yes they could port it to the switch
let's go have tomato maybe
maybe wait let me make the window a bit
more
bigger for me maybe full screen
okay full screen let's go
no sound from my side watch it on your
own
pinned link in the comments is that here
reading pending to major 17 please note
blah blah blah blah blah blah so that's
what i see
archive people if you want to you know
line up with me
oh logo moving logo moving
there we go
oh god
oh
okay
i thought for a moment they're gonna
announce the pro right away
oh are they that's so early
this hair is so shiny
oh not yet okay you got nice hair the
left guy
the takahashi got good hair
you must have watched it washed with
gravy oh snap snip snap snap
sorry my fingers are sweaty right now
there we go
oh what is this
oh wait is that it looks like world of
warcraft no
way that's going on
oh i noticed dude i think
oh wait that's a super smash brothers
[Music]
arcade thingy
oh oh is he the new one that was a
very sudden announcement not very secret
surprising okay no wait
he just froze down into the lava
dude
oh that's that's kind of
wow holy what
we need to play smash on my channel once
i've always wanted to play it with you
guys on stream or with other girls
but i'm like really bad at it itself
probably even worse than in mario kart
so by smash bros ultimate ex-chicken
[Music]
he can just fly and now he comes back up
now he will be coming back up
there we go so cute
[Music]
yay
surprise
is that is that the character that you
guys were hoping for and and and
expecting
to come i
heard people wanted among us in smash
no not really but okay not expecting but
even better
oh
oh chiara for smash
i used to play super smash brothers on
gamecube i have never played on the
switch before
um i need to buy it i don't even own it
but i'm gonna get it for you guys
i'm playing on gamecube and i would
usually play
uh zelda most of the time i would be
playing zelda because i just like to
play cute girls
he does fit in well into smash
oh oh
i am main zelda oh
he's buff
he also looks like he could show up in
in yakuza
[Laughter]
that we have been playing on my channel
headlines oh this is
this is this is uh this is the thing
oh wait no it's not the thing i thought
that was uh the thing
life is strange oh wait it is
i don't know the art style looks no no
no no no it's not like
life is strange we look at it is that it
i have a strange anime
oh that girl yeah that's the girl from
the new one right i never played love is
strange
oh the anime was just for fun ah
the games are coming to switch they
weren't they were not on switch before
cool let's play it on my channel someday
i've been very curious about it
wow
stylistic choice
september 10 one day after 10 level rise
i'll be busy i'll be very busy
can't play immediately
uh-huh
cute
i watched i watched the movie gardens of
the galaxy
that's all i've watched that's marvel
related
llama
where is it so nostalgic
i played like a really old worms game
when i was younger
oh that's cute
that looks uh very um
laggy sheep
oh oh what is that that looks cool
wait that reminds me of
audience feel
[Music]
oh
i like it i like it
what is that sims
university university simulator
university simulator
bananas donkey kong
[Music]
what is that who are you
what is that
that's so cute that looks so old
that must have been on what gameplay
enough with donkey kong
i feel like i played a similar game
before ages ago
maybe it was this
cute you deceived me with those bananas
mario well never
i'm ready for my first round
that's from nintendo 64.
no oh they're putting stages from the
nintendo 64 into the into the new
mario party wait
i heard
the face moving thingy
i know those levels i know them weren't
they also on the gamecube though because
they seem so familiar to me
that's fun that's fun
looks so familiar
oh wow
cool cool wait that's a new game
boy party superstar is that a new mario
party
is that uh
metroid new game it's not a dlc
it is a dlc ah that was just the name of
dlc
okay new metroid game
a snap snap stamp
oh
looks good
it shoot shoot it
it's dangerous
there is a sound delay on my
presentation
do you guys have it too
same uh-huh
i tried dread looks very cool what is
this is that metroid
always a side scroller oh like a dungeon
what's it called again that genre
dungeon crawler
no no no that's not it what was it again
a metroidvania it makes sense
wait does the name metroidvania come
from metroid
[Laughter]
is it because metroid started the whole
genre
holy how revolutionary where there
was not a
a castle oh yeah
that's interesting i would like you guys
to explain that to me later
cool seems like something you guys like
never really been into metroid before
though oh
august 10th august or
8th october on it that is uh
wait which one is it that's very
confusing for me
october probably yeah august would be
too early huh
that looks really good
oh
those look dope
familiar franchises return a nintendo
switch
oh just dance
never played this game ever before
but youtube recommended me a video on
how
just dance is being created
with the characters uh with the people
the actors on the
dances on on the green screen did you
guys get the same recommendation
oh yo
let me play that
unicorn
what the yeah you gotta do
cruising
oh coming huh
goku
i guess this is a jrpg and i love jfpgs
but it's not my
not my favorite series
golf
oh i heard this was actually pretty good
if you like golf
you know i would look super cute in a
golf outfit
just want to let you know birdie
they called me nice britney thank you
thank you
victory talked to me in the nintendo
direct i'm so honored
wow i don't know how i deserved that
mention
but okay okay
nintendo direct thank you for
recognizing me
acknowledging me
usually that's a phoenix wasn't that a
phoenix
usually they call me hot wings because
nice birdie is okay too
that was a video that was that's why
they gave me a shout out
[Laughter]
whoa that looks cute
it's more of an anime style than the
monster hunter that
came out recently
cool is that just more story based than
the recent monster hunter
because that's what i did not uh that's
what didn't really catch me
about the new monsanto is that it's
just fighting
oh they have they have
since this is number two i guess there
was number one they have a
rpg focused
uh series as well huh
cool
big egg
july 9.
that's very soon i guess this was
already known
oh oh
oh
ah
is this warrior well that's cute
you guys told me about that before that
i when i was asking for shorter games to
play on stream
interesting didn't know it's that kind
of game
is that for switch because i think when
i looked it up it was like
the
oh two people
nice because the other games are
on platforms i think that i couldn't
have used
oh september 10 as well
oh i'm gonna get that one i'm gonna get
that one
oh magic fingers
oh oh is that like shin megami
oh
she looks cute or wait that's a boy
because of boys on the phone got
nice eyelashes though
different dimension i know a lot about
that
another tokyo
wait there was a girl it was a girl
hot oh she's doing the naruto ring
wait no it's a boy
whatever
oh
move they'll be like okay i'll join you
okay shut up already
what the hell
it's a demon
that is pretty cool
was this is this a new announcement that
nobody knew about before
november 12 oh end of the
year
yes yes oh cool it leaked oh no
but in general it's a new thing coco
wait atlas wasn't that
wasn't that uh the one we cannot stream
oh danganronpa i watched the first
season of the anime
yeah that's actually the anime i watched
the characters from that anime
oh wait is that a port
yeah no i did like the anime back then
when i watched it
hmm a port uh huh again i'm like a
minecraft villager
no i'm not okay
[Laughter]
for real
interesting
[Music]
what
what's this fatal frame
maiden of blackwood which is cute
is this a new announcement
horror
but it looks so cute i might play it
cute
spoopy game but but
cute main character
some even today do maternal
didn't like gouda play this before
or anyone in halloween
i'mma played it i mean kelly did ah
interesting oh we are skateboarding
daddy hook
wait that's the one tony hawk game i
played
i think no i played this one
maybe is that the one that was on
gamecube
yo let's play this guys we all did
well i wanted to be a skater girl she
was a skater girl she said see you
little girl
what booby-trapped dungeons
wait it really said the same thing in
the subtitles
booby trapped the game looks good though
who trapped the boobies free the boobies
oh mario
hmm
we already know about this but uh
this is this can be played with others
together right
collaboration game
yes ah
single play only
oh it's just it's single player only oh
that would have been cool as a
collab
orange star nation is under attack
what is this you guys know it you guys
are excited about it
you guys are so hype nostalgic
oh oh
gameboy advanced classics oh
that voiceover was good the female one
age of calamity
they gotta stay bamboozled us
okay and now now you show us breath of
the wild too right
right right
right oh
i like his t-shirt
we're gonna be streaming dad
ah wait no pro controller
wait how am i gonna stream that
how i'm gonna play that it's a bit
difficult
wait does this pro controller work
should wake okay
because i know there is motion control
yeah yeah
yeah look forward to my playthrough on
my channel um
i didn't play the og
what's that
that's so cute
that is so cute
so cute way you can actually play it
it's so cute
a clock game
i love it oh that's
so cute here we go what
you guys are faster than me chad is
earlier than me
indeed
true
i'll be quiet
oh what is that
outfit
what the hell
oh new weapon i love the soundtrack
what portal
makes climbing up those mountains easier
huh
that's it that's it
well that makes sense
oh yeah that's cool
that it's in disguise as well because i
felt like what the hell that's like
skyward sword
thank you as well for watching
nice okay
uh i would have liked to see more
about about the birth of the wild too
wait wait there was also no title
announcement right
and no nintendo pro announcement
this is trey house now
yeah okay guys we're gonna put in the
background
do you think they'll show something but
nah no way they won't show
rev up the wild right in tree house
uh no way okay ah
i'm gonna make it more quiet
okay sure but should we have because
we're gonna read super chat shouldn't we
have on some kind of
background music otherwise it will be a
bit lonely
anyway anyway thank you for
watching this together with me i always
wanted to do some kind of like watch
along with these kind of
gaming presentations and stuff so thank
you for spending your time with me
and it was also my first e3 i might i'm
gonna privately
be watching bandai namco presentation
later today
i think i i i was thinking a little bit
about streaming it as well
but it would be
overlapping with the ttrpg stream and i
guess i'm just gonna
um i'm gonna live tweet
i'm just gonna fangirl privately and
also because that that way i can do
some more stuff privately and focus on
it today
um but yeah
treehouse watch long no i'll ha we will
have it open if you can i'll
have it open in the background you can
do that too if you want to
oh gosh why it's so hot in my room um
but we'll be reading super jets because
i have some left over
well what are the highlights of this
nintendo direct obviously breath of the
wild
uh smash
but taken is not like not nothing i'm
particularly
excited about yeah for you guys uh
metroid
shin megami looked very interesting and
uh
monster hunters stories maybe perhaps
advanced voice for you too oh yeah and
warioware just because it's going to be
a great game for streaming
fatal frame ah indeed indeed
yeah monsanto stories that has kind of
like more
like the the aesthetics of it is more of
my liking than the
uh most recent monster hunter and also
the
the fact that there it's focused on
stories is also more of my liking
that is that is more my cup of tea than
the other
i keep on forgetting what is the monster
hunter rise right
i bought that and i played it once
that's a bit sad
metroid in treehouse right now
development history
all right let me i'm feeling very
like dried out and hot
and hey i mean i did get a shout out in
the in mario golf
so that that's quite exciting
that must have been the highlight today
hi junkies you missed the nintendo
direct why did you not watch it drunkers
oh yeah exactly yeah i love you
i love you i love you
guys are you ready for some super tags
because i don't
i don't think there's gonna be uh
anything
i mean from what i've seen in the brevit
well bro
for the wild trail i don't know i want
to re-watch it
closely the the whole sky thing is dope
that's dope and the portal thing
we did not see that before right
that is new too damn and i liked his new
outfit
yeah but i still have never played
breath of the wild one
however i am watching right now the
third
full playthrough of it i've watched two
full playthroughs of it before and now
i'm watching the third
full another streamer
slash youtuber so in some way i have
experienced the game
fully three times now but
never played it myself
so it's almost like i don't have to play
it myself
or yeah i might have a lot of knowledge
already
um if i were to play it for the first
time by myself
play it for us that's a long project
but i don't know if we run out of games
around
winter time um then we could play it
like to prepare for breath of the wild
too
for the release ah i guess it's not
gonna be released in
in in early 20 to 2022
evil right it's probably gonna be like
summer maybe
maybe summer the earliest
i would guess
um the the zelda games that i played
were
a wind waker and
a little bit of twilight but i never
played much of it my brother played most
of it and then
i played a bit of it but it scared me a
little bit
wind wake up was my my favorite
uh ocarina of time i just watched a full
a full playthrough of someone else
um yeah wait was there anything else i
played
but i wanted to play um
that that that that the other one that
got pointed to switch what was it called
again
what was it called again spirit tracks i
watched the full playthrough of spear
tracks
when you always i watched the full
playthrough of majora's mask
link's awakening yeah i never played the
lynx awakening og game so i do want to
play it on
uh on the on on on the switch at some
point
um no i did like midna i did like her
but twilight was so dark that back then
i i i don't know i felt like not not
ready for it
oh but i do love zelda games
why not play them i don't know but most
of those games that i just
mentioned like majira's mask and all
that i just didn't have the access to it
uh i would have need and i needed i
would need to get
myself that console um
travel princess is scary yeah
i love watching them being played by
someone else
um i think you are ready
yeah i think i would be ready to play it
nowadays yeah yeah
um majora's mask was way scarier
i definitely enjoyed watching um
other people play it yeah because they
know how to play
well yeah they definitely played it
better than i could ever
but you played diablo yeah and back in
the day when i played diablo 2 i was
also way too young and therefore could
never
uh fight that first who was
who was that lady in in behind in the
fences outside
who was the lady that i i never got
passed
who was she it was not on dario it was
not on dariel because i thought it was
on dario
we figured out yeah it was blood raven
that i could not even get past because i
was too scared
i was a little little girl okay i just
wanted to play the game
because it looked fun when my mom was
playing it yes my mother played
able to all the time she liked it a lot
my mom is going to be so hyped up when
the
remake comes out because she was she and
my sister as well
when i told them that when they started
i was playing diablo 2
um remake alpha on my channel a little
while ago they were
like really really jelly they were like
i want to play that too
i want alpha xs 2 yeah
so wait when is that when is the release
date for diablo 2
remake wasn't that announced
the other day yesterday or so
what was that did you guys tell me i
forgot again
family of demon slayers september
september 23rd
[Music]
all right my family is gonna be playing
that and me too
oh so i guess for september
since we already have tales of a rise in
the beginning of september
starting later on we will
be adding diablo 2 to that i think
because i'll probably be
zooming for tails off i'll be playing it
four times a week probably because i'm
so excited for tails of a rise
and then we can add diablo to remake to
to the list of games that we we will be
playing on my channel
for tensorflow rise i might play it
every day
you know normally i always have a jrpg
going on on my channel
um but uh or one
one or two but we usually don't play it
more than one or twice
once or twice a week but for tesla
variety i'm sorry but you have to bear
with me i'm gonna be playing it every
day
i'm too hyped up about that i you know
my favorite game series ever is tails
off
i love bandai namco and everything they
create
and tails off is just the bestest and
i've been waiting so long for a new
tails off game
i've been going crazy
it's about time um
so um you know what i will not put let
me let me write a little note because i
will not be putting on music
let's the people who want to listen to
some music you can turn on your own
music today and the people who want to
listen to the
tree house you can listen to treehouse
in the background okay
let me put up a note
it's kind of nice to have this in the
background it's like a podcast
oh my god reusing something old
i'm not getting an energy drink i am not
getting another drink
and still listening
to tree house
no btm today uh
is that understandable kind of have to
keep it short
usual
it's so long
like that yeah okay wait let me change
that's better who is drilling
someone's drilling here make him stop
let me listen to my podcast
oh
samus i used to always say samus
hello hello chocolate
new cutie what's up did you hear that
did you hear that
what's up what enjoyment will pronounce
it like that give me a break
[Music]
yeah the lady's voice is really nice
really soothing
huh super tattoo
[Music]
so super jack reading
uh
what no keep that you like my
unicorn style popcorn and drink
isn't that cute
yosho what did you thought of the games
announced this e3 which of the
you may play a player from dua too
uh and diablo 2. um
and why are you aware the other e3
announced games i
i didn't watch my like anything of it i
only know what you guys told me so
i don't really know what i would play
but yeah from what i've heard there's
not much that is of my interest
oh yeah skyward sword holy of
course skyward sword
uh and and you know we already mentioned
it
maybe maybe not she might have been
tendency probably not gonna work out
because of reasons life is strange
yeah yeah that is that i mean i would i
wouldn't say that that is an e4
announced game because it has been known
before right
but yes uh
elden ring maybe yeah
i'm open to i'm open to being
into playing ellen ring eventually so
let's open up those super chats
we have to read the ones from yesterday
shouldn't be
too long and i got something to do after
the stream
so we're not going to drag it out too
long even but it shouldn't take too long
are you guys listening to music now or
the treehouse
what's your choice of entertainment
background
entertainment or just me
treehouse bgm or me
treehouse museum you treehouse treehouse
treehouse link it's the same link that's
in the in the comments it's the same
link they just continue after the
nintendo direct with the treehouse
just me oh
oh thank you
yo i'm scrolling down the yakuza super
chats right now
um
tomorrow sorry tomorrow's mystery collab
oh
announcement
uh
announcement coming 25 hours before
so in a few hours actually
ah
where is this beginning of these super
chats there we are
found it
what hints da
no hints you don't even need hints for
that
and let me get the thumbnail
oh shh what was it
yakuza
[Music]
um sad that we couldn't finish it before
my vacation because now there's gonna be
a big
break in between the 10th episode and
the last episode
unfortunately but it is what it is
huh
youtube did a guru good
did it do that for you guys too
unfortunate but understandable yeah okay
you don't even know what i mean with
gurukul uh when it goes like guru guru
then that's gonna oh again
i guess it's my internet all right let's
let's read the super chat let's go
early in your whole life career you did
a life or two
stream i thought it was cute and fun
would you ever consider doing one again
you mean regarding the same game or
regarding any other game
i think you probably mean regarding
another game
um hmm
and wait for which game could we do it
we could do a yakuza white futilist
including the the guys though
wife and husband cheerless of yakuza
maybe tails off
oh
maybe i'll think about it christophe's
duncan
i've been avoiding the yacht streams for
spoilers but i checked in over the day
and i loved watching you play my
favorite casino game
your increasingly manic reactions for
hilarious what do you mean with
manic what do you mean oh
felix congratulations for what
wow you met your family nice
quarantine over congratulations
is that something to congratulate but
but yeah
it's it's done you did it
good job good job for being patient
i'll get to you a bit later that sounds
scary
i'll get to you later mr felix style
you just wait there hubble and thank you
felix sound never mind i'm getting to
you now from a past super chat
feeling for the red super chant
tantra i missed the beginning of your
stream yesterday because i had to get up
early however i was surprised to see you
were still streaming when i got up i'm
glad but at the same time
yeah that was because we streamed for
nine and a half hours
yeah understandable i'm glad but at the
same time
just make sure you have enough rest
after the long streams no worries i
think i got enough rest after i'm not
sure how much it was but definitely like
seven
eight hours or so
[Laughter]
nine and a half hours stream just just
just
normal no even nine and a half hours is
not that normal we usually do six to
eight hours
[Laughter]
yeah thank you for the support felix
thank you as always
for your loyal and generous support yeah
stop also a red super chat thank you
thank you
hi my kikity queen i like that i hope
you're doing well i haven't been to a
tent of the past few days because of
lack of energy sorry for that to be
honest i could use a hug from my
imaginary feelings wife
ah no problem come here
come here wait this is so wait is this
gonna work uh
yeah come here oh there you are
you can't see my hands but
[Music]
i hope you feel better soon
ah i get that lack of energy that's
totally fine take your time to
regain your energy but if you
you should try to i don't know maybe go
outside go have a picnic outside or
drink some smoothies get some um
get some sun vitamins and some fruit
vitamins and stuff into you
and and that should you know give you
a different kind of energy back but it
should maybe help you to get back on
track
no don't drink cats
no different kind of smoothie
i should i should personally do that
more often too i do i i do
drink a lot of smoothies these days but
not cats but going outside is something
i need to do more often
as much as i like to ignore that fact
but
uh apparently apparently the sun gives
you energy
whatever i am the sun bird so
i give energy to myself no
no no no don't put you no no p axios no
no he's not a plant
like you you should be the one
that says yes kiara go outside and now
you yeah now you're working against me
you need vitamin c go get it
on the treehouse super
you didn't want me to read that did you
all right i'll stop
there because i understand the situation
thank you kaka for the pinky
[Music]
elbido thanks for the thinking
to all kfc employees we need to secure
our pension fund
so please stop attention from any
gambling activities at all costs see you
in archive later
oh don't worry i did not gamble
yesterday
it's all good um
i don't know that's the first time i
hear about the pension fund too
but yes i thought don't worry that that
was all
just in-game money not real money it's
okay it's okay
i'll be the language and apple pencil
dancing
no that's not but okay thank you anyway
come to me now
kiara you are my vitamin
now we were just talking about vitamins
i'm glad you say so thank you
soy gao thank you for the red super chat
ma
kamiya thank you i appreciate it
thank you so much hope you're doing fine
and i hope you enjoyed the stream
yesterday maybe you're here right now
too oh yeah your hair
hello did you like the nintendo direct
was it exciting it was pretty
pretty good it had a lot of pressure on
it because everyone was like please
nintendo direct save us from this e3
what a game over in the house
hydration oh oh that's
i need to remember your name you you
send you're sending a lot of super chats
these days
you need to remember this korean writing
right uh google translate
korean
[Music]
this person is sending super chat daily
recently
is
[Music]
i will try to remember your name going
to take a while probably
thank you best girl aqua dankeshan apple
pencil thank you
go to the grocery store by harbor and
yokohama make lunches at the survive
part the lunches are very good
ah yeah i by now i should have a lot of
cooking ingredients i should
uh i'm aware of the lunches um i will
try to remember next time but we're
pretty much
at the end of the game
i love you thank you love you too
that's a bit late at this point
goddammit
doctor c eq duncan
you enemies will know through fear if
you bring out the hatties and fan
oh i don't think anyone drew a hatison
fan for key arsenal did they
my first gaming handle was a nintendo oh
and i love nintendo games
yes me too me too nintendo
is uh also my favorite gaming console
always
daisy danger tai chi thank you thank you
for the red super chat again
[Music]
thank you thank you taishi always so
supportive thank you so much
but write more in your super chats
please
what am i supposed to say
slow dangle
[Music]
thank you
um
[Music]
g'day mate how are you with the cuties
this seems so like i heard it before
you're giving me a deja vu but this is
just
your usual greeting isn't it
here's for your vacation the only the
one i sent before
pinky got sent to the void with me
when we when we did an experiment before
oh
enjoy the vacation with rmt and world of
warcraft and play on the side
i still didn't open up my new laptop i
need to see if it works and stuff
who's going to look up the cutest on
your vacation my best friend
i actually asked her to like live in my
apartment
instead of just coming over to feed them
because i want them to have like someone
here
as much as possible so that they don't
feel lonely
yeah and so she'll be sleeping over
and actually living here yeah yes yes
yes yes
thankfully
thank you
i'm excited for the vacation i can't
believe today in one week i would be not
here
i'm excited and i'm honestly i probably
won't be streaming much at all
i was planning to to do to try maybe
like one short stream sliver.io
if i get it to work but even if i don't
i don't care anymore
but i would be gone for a lot of days
you guys guys gonna
miss me
but there will be a song cover coming
out next week and
can i just say
i already i already said recently
that yoona yuna is making the video you
know yuna also made the video for aiko
toba
and wawa world and the art and the video
animation and she's making it for my new
song cover as well
and i asked her for a really simple
video you know how some
song covers like king and
you know all of those they they usually
have some
like like like the the covers copy the
video
as best as as good as they can the
original video you see how there's
a pattern in these videos right so the
sound cover that i'm doing
also has something like that going on
like copying the videos
and uh i just asked yuna to do that
because it's like super super simple
but she sent me a work in progress
yesterday
and it was way more than i asked for
she went all out again it's
she she just went absolutely crazy with
it
she's crazy it's way way way way way
more than i asked for
and expected so it's it's so good
it was just supposed to be like you know
a filler for my vacation
that's it but now it's becoming into a
really cool thing so i wanted
i want this the my singing to be also as
good as possible
yeah look forward to that it's going to
be really good
again
[Music]
these japanese when japanese people fill
out their red super chat it's like a
wall of text that slaps you in the face
[Laughter]
about the shogun thing because the only
japanese i know is joking and kusa i
didn't mean to lie please forgive me
then
[Laughter]
that is that is uh two
interesting words to know i mean i
understand kusa but
why do you know shuken you should know
something like konichiwa or
or genki or so shoken by the way
let me tell you guys when you come to a
stream let me teach you
um let me teach you stream manner
japanese stream
manner okay if you if you come to a
japanese
streamers stream for the first time
and you want to say something people
usually
say i am shoken i am the first time
viewer shook in this
uh to that viewer in the chat which is
written with the kanji
uh hatsu for first time
and me for looking or ken for looking
mm-hmm sure can yeah you can just copy
paste what the japanese viewers are
writing right now shogun this yeah
that is a japanese streamer
matters
then then they'll think you're one of
them because you seem to understand
japanese perfectly
yeah exactly exactly that means i am not
first time viewer
meow hello hello
baby hi baby
yeah yeah yo
baby i love you we've been cuddling a
lot
today no i've been trying to help her uh
get rid of all the hair she's been
shedding
no no no not shocking shopkin is like
food
ticket i used to say
my pronunciation of shogun was bad back
in the day and i used to say shopkin and
people thought i was saying
food ticket no no no
no no no no no
[Laughter]
all right continuing did i give you a
kiss
there is it there it is can i speak
english properly please scott you liar
i just told you the meaning and you used
it wrong
so you can no
love super tangent reading uh
[Laughter]
it is it is indeed a super tangent
reading always
patrick and dangerous
looking at yakuza the new turn-based
system is so cool the environments
resemble japan so much i love these
interactions kiara looking at new yakuza
these
stairs though yeah the stairs were
fascinating to me
i i mean you gotta you gotta respect the
details
yo yo my my my treehouse just doesn't
move anymore
it doesn't move it's just it's just
loading
let me refresh ah there we go
they're talking about mario party now
my connection is really bad right now
apparently
it's so not good oh my god
i think it's better now
so do i understand correctly this is
support from the mario party of the
nintendo 64.
it doesn't load
but some of the stages kind of
but as a dlc right um but some of the
stages i know those from the gamecube as
well so i got excited
maps and game modes
[Music]
uh iphones 19 dangerous
is that the same name again uh no it's
not
i need to learn how to read korean
because like
it's not as they don't have that many
signs i could
actually really try to remember it
what they have like 20 20 something
right 20
20 how many is it
so then i don't have to use google
translate all the time
at 48. oh oh okay well let's still
that's still reasonable eh wait 28
no one here who knows
oh yeah 24 48
eh 14 vowels
10 consonants that sounds like someone
who knows what they're talking about
okay so it is
24. oh easy
easy yeah 48 is japanese with hiragana
and katakana no
okay del star dan kishan uh
we met the man the most important of all
of them and to me he was nothing but a
bodyguard
i was very unimpressed by his appearance
well everyone else was like sam
it's him the legend i was like
he to me he looked like a guy from the
matrix
with his glasses and the way he looks
like he looks like the
mate i'm like a matrix guy
[Laughter]
can you believe this burp i'll tell that
to coco senpai in hello talk
then i met her husband and he looked to
me
like a normal bodyguard from from the
matrix
agent smith maybe
stream actually no you know what let me
do it now because before i
freaking forget should we do the holo
talk tweet
okay uh
wait let me get let me try to find the
one that i
like a template home talk
questions whole
talk questions
because i was gonna start getting
gathering them today
right i can't find my
[Music]
can't find it
oh
okay so first i tweeted in japanese
guys if you have english questions
please post them on youtube
and
wait okay
so
[Music]
senpai
i'm always running out of letters in
these tweets it's
so annoying i need more letters twitter
give me more
so and i would like i would like to add
um
a lot
[Music]
um
uh-huh one letter too much one letter
too much
maybe get rid of that exclamation mark
yes
and then whole talk thumbnail
where did i save it
there it is looks we actually look
in this thumbnail when we're lined up
next to another you will really notice
how similar we look actually we both
have orange hair we both have purple
eyes
[Laughter]
and we both have big badonkas she has
bigger ones but still
okay uh in
english questions oh wait i'll
do that later i'll just do that later
on
now let me do the one for the community
board
uh channel community
i wish and let me make it very clear
that we don't need all those repetitive
questions
holo talk caller talk call the talk
there we go
questions for this week's episode with
coco senpai can be submitted in the
comments of this community post for
about 24 hours
please keep some things in mind um
try to avoid generic questions and i
always think what is your biggest goal
blah blah
no but most importantly
no questions about
graduation reasons
and plans for future please
because we won't answer them
here um and i'll keep doing it
for you and well don't try to ask any
questions
um no questions that will be answered in
a negative way we want to stay positive
remember the goal is to
get some deeper knowledge and
understanding of the japanese helens
because
[Music]
okay it should be fine
okay almost done adding the thumbnail
now
nice okay will you talk in english and
translate to japanese's wholesale no it
will be as usual because i want a
japanese she has a lot of her main fan
base is japanese so
i want them to understand it as well so
we're just doing it
as per usual although who knows maybe
maybe coco senpai will just also
speak a lot of english in between
okay done
okay the post is up now
so if you already know what to ask
you're welcome
to post your questions there now english
questions here please you sure
[Music]
and now back to super chat reading
back to super chat reading
thank you for hosting contention no
problem i felt like i
i am you know i didn't want didn't want
her to
leave her life without me having done an
interview with her yet
i will not let you go before i get an
interview
um but uh i planned this by the way
before the but before the announcement
was made publicly so
it's not some people been have been
wondering if if any other guest was
like rescheduled because of this no no
no
i didn't did not have any guests lined
up before i made this decision anyway so
it was always planned as coco senpai
yeah i just knew it earlier than you
guys so i was able to plan ahead
freedom looking for the top dungeon
some people were really mad that i was
actually cheating yesterday in the tests
in yakuzank
sorry i thought i thought i thought you
know might as well
use the possibilities that are being
given to me
i read one one comment that was like
really bad but also like i didn't even
know this was possible for god's sake
something like that um
i had to do it without pausing
thank you happy
late a little bit late birthday to
marvin
why blackwell thank you soon randomly
sanctioned randomly
[Music]
the key to blackjack is to memorize the
cards on the table
all players and predict the odds of the
dealer drawing a 10 face card
card counting is illegal but okay in
video games
if the dealer is showing a 2 to 6 it is
common to stand because of a high chance
they have a hand with 16
or less regardless of how good your hand
is if they're showing a 10
it's a high chance they have a 17 to 20.
oh i see okay cool
thank you for the information thank you
for the pinky as well
it's not illegal casinos will just kick
you out
yeah i see well
i um i i hope we won't get back to
blackjack in
yakuza anymore because we want to stay
away from the addiction
stay safe jason duncan thank you also
for
pinky hi kia i hope you're enjoying the
yakuza series i would recommend playing
zero if you enjoyed the series also have
you ever tried picking duck before
you should take someone to review here's
some money for it
congrats on the new kfp employee thank
you
oh new cave point which ones
um
i think i've eaten
picking duck before me but i don't know
when i'm not sure actually
the egg i used ah
that's so cute can it make another egg
or is that the only one
the egg um
yeah uh
yeah playing another yakuza game i don't
know how
how like when i would do that because
you know i don't really have time to
play games
off screen and i'm not playing to play
not planning to play another yakuza game
this year
because there's always so many other
things i want to play
but maybe someday when i have free time
maybe i'll get to it yeah thank you for
the recommendation
[Music]
m
where are you going eating mike tysons
it was not full muslim by the way
very good very good very very um
child children uh friendly family
friendly
right evan christopher
ellis thank you thank you
very much
not my favorite game but my favorite
youtuber playing it always makes it fun
to watch
thank you thank you the people who have
been watching my yakuza playful i think
a lot of them
are big big big fans of yakuza but i'm
glad that you
watch it even though you're not that
much interested
in it thank you for taking the time
and supporting me what is your favorite
game then
are you in the chat now
thank you soon anyway for being there i
don't think you're in the chat right now
but
i'll see you again hopefully in the last
in the next and last yakuza stream
yeah you you gotta be there everyone's
gonna be there for the last episode
eating mike tyson's oh i almost read it
oh my gosh
and thank you for one red one and one
pinky
[Music]
yeah i just want to first uh say thank
you and i appreciate you with the news
of kidyokuku leaving i had a
terrible thought of you one day leaving
i hope this is
in the far-off future so it made me tear
up and become very emotional oh no
i first fell for you during your taka
monica live on a way out oh
you have become my idol my favorite meat
over and the big reason why i smile
every day
i wish to continue supporting you
however i can be more lucky
that is so sweet thank you i mean yeah
um i understand the thought and and
but don't worry i just it hasn't even
been a year i just
joined i got i got many
many things ahead of me and uh
we just have to do our best to live in
the moment and enjoy it
together okay
thank you for becoming part of kfp and
supporting me
thank you for letting me be uh your
entertainment source
and your idol and your favorite yata
bring back golden juggles ah right that
was a thing
danke shin atomic ada atomic adam duncan
[Music]
i got done swimming at water park and i
kept chatting
key every time i went down the slide
around
what nice i like that
thank you for using all across the
world
thank you
thank you i reacted to it during the
stream
but thank you again thank you so
russian soldiers have nowhere to eat
open up a kfn restaurant in moscow
don't we already have one open
open it up make one build it you're
welcome to build one
it's like it's like almost like open
what's it called
open um what's it called when you when
you
uh and you know open source
is that what it was called open ip
free real estate that's also we could
say that yeah
yeah if you wanna kfb in your country
you just have to
stop dreaming about it and then just
just
just make it happen in your brain just
imagine it and then it will be there
yes and then you can just
you know celebrate and promote
the kfp of your city and your country
don't let your dreams be dreams like
a dancer an apple
[Music]
do they still get tagged with art of
ashes yeah why not i mean if the
if the artist who uploads them will do
it why not
yeah that would be nice because then i
can find it
did you convince yourself when
or are you about two are you supposed to
sounds exciting a round of astute lex
lexington the lion dancer you
commissioned someone special
special special
is it for my birthday
motion
is you lagging or is it me i don't know
my treehouse presentation is lagging on
my side but i should be fine my stream
should be fine
it's still mario party over there thanks
for becoming a member welcome
my little fbi really the whole time i
feel like it's just sometimes
i don't know yeah that could be because
of my internet right now
yep happens sometimes
and lexington the lion dancing and
that's it for the super chats from
yesterday so
we'll be reading the super chats from
today and then we're done and then i'll
go do my things
i thought
let's go looking for the top function
what do you think of visual key music
and fashion i was really into it back in
the day i was the same kid and also
yay really sink it
and reap what
visual gay i had a friend that was
really into it
uh i personally was not really into it
i i knew some songs and some
bands but i wouldn't call myself a fan
mm-hmm
the cats who begs in the
let me open it in the night ah
thank you soon the mario who undoubtedly
appear in this presentation is a fake
the real mario and family mysteriously
vanished after one of your
super mario sunshine streams
[Music]
no
oh thanks for telling me you smuggled
some stuff into the usual room so
i'll send my guys to take it away from
you go
guards take it away from you i'm going
to get a stop
elvis and i'll be the dancer naruto's
[Music]
foreign night eater dangerous
duncan star fox nothing right nothing
about star fox right
damn i was kind of like i don't know
hoping for it because you guys were
hoping for it
i played starbucks on on gamecube
um the one with the hot chick
the cute girl jay taylor thank you so
much
thank you for adding the english reading
to it that's very helpful
yeah crystal crystal's so sexy
and brian sixteen action
please shout at the top of your lungs
throughout the entire presentation
sorry but it was not that exciting so
that was not possible uh
chaos night dancin
fantasia never got a proper western
release so getting it would be awesome
um that is that is true wanna play the
updated version that ps got later on
that would be nice yeah excessive boots
dancing
hey kevin hulang tangashin
what's the status on the custom keyboard
i've gotten super into them because of
being inside so much the past year i
hope you've had fun of it
no status at all i got a lot of
recommendations from you guys a lot of
you guys linked me to like famous people
um but i don't know like i don't know
about
i don't know i don't know about
contacting them
i i don't know maybe i'll
maybe i'll get to it once i've got my
chair and my desk
um maybe after that albedo
who are you to take over my youtube
algorithm i've never seen your channel
yatta we're on the youtube algorithm yes
yo youtube what up thank you for once
for being nice to me
on the korean youtube yata fight guys
and monkey man danger
metroidvania a port mountain of metroid
and castlevania is a 2d platformer game
with a focus on exploration
new areas can be explored by back
tracing when
new abilities are unlocked is that not a
thing for castlevania
so okay i wanted to know what is the
difference between metroidvania and
castlevania
castlevania it is a metroid venue
oh that's the game huh
metroidvania is the genre
oh oh okay
oh so metroid did kind of really like
create it in some way huh
someone said technically technically it
was zelda though
hey
[Music]
that's so cool that is so cool because
they got like
they got all this um um
i don't know they made it they made
history somehow
why do you know german because uh my
first
first language is german because i was
raised in a german-speaking country
motu account named
yes australia
uh
[Music]
but you wrote nothing into it why
let me give you a kiss though is that
okay
you're gonna give you a kissy come here
thank you
thank you for your support i appreciate
it very much
hope you're enjoying the streams ah
our new fermented mask night 93
and double youtube tags from dan kashing
nintendo really came through with some
gucci stuff i'm glad you enjoyed it
dominique david anger dan kashan
was fun watching the direct review thank
you mrs duncan
monkey ball hype oh yeah you guys are
really hyped about that
no actually the other one the adventure
thingy or whatever was also really hard
surprising like some games that i
had no idea about you guys were really
excited about
thank you wikitunes wow wow wow thank
you
chaos donut duncan the thing i look
forward to most when you play sky with
sword is your voice acting for groose
okay okay i'll do my best i'll see what
i can do
nostalgia and then
yeah advanced voice yeah yeah that one
elector john 12 donkey should incredible
[Music]
what would it take for us to get you to
play the new metroid game
um i don't know i look at it
again when it gets released and think
about it when
at that time i wouldn't like completely
say well i'm not playing it at all
we could like we we could even like give
it a try for one stream only
if we wanted to yeah but i i got a lot
of other games that i'm more excited
about
in the in my queue
but yeah i would be i would wouldn't
mind trying because i think i
i remember playing a metroid game
on the gamecube like a little bit
i think i'm pretty sure i remember
something like that
but that was metroid prime yeah
but it was uh i i i think i wasn't
really
playing i was just running around i
think my brother was playing the game
maybe
you know back then i was just starting
games and not doing much not getting far
not never
never finishing them yeah that was the
fps yeah that's not a metroid
uh yeah yeah yeah right that's not the
metroidvania
yeah okay yeah see i kind of like the i
liked that one probably because it was
not a metroidvania
but i'll give the metroidvania a chance
as well maybe
i can't promise right now but i'm not
against it
[Music]
refreshing the super chats we're almost
done
[Music]
okay
um
two of them actually wow
sorry mom i was so busy today that i
can't even send my super chat before the
stream
i'll watch the archive when i get the
chance no problem
take your time
or or don't watch it at all you don't
have to it's just a watch along it's
just a react along nothing too special
i think you can skip this one i'll be
having less time this week to watch you
sorry i'm so sad
but on to the good news i'm out of the
quarantine and finally met with my
family i'm quite emotional for a lot of
reasons right now so i'm gonna go shut
up and go to bed while i still can
don't let me spoil the fun here no
problem
good night i'm glad you had a great day
i'm glad it was
fun for you and enjoyable
i hope i hope that you'll have a lovely
time with your family
[Music]
thank you for your support thank you
was a nintendo and i love nintendo games
yeah i think the same is the case for me
my first
hand was definitely a nintendo 2.
yeah those are the bestest game boy
game boy color game boy advance
game boy wait what was uh it was
was there a game boy classic
any yes obviously but for the nes i was
so young that
i don't know i played it but i don't
have much memory
wait there was no classic yeah just a
game boy i guess
i remember bringing it bringing my game
boy
to school i remember that
and i was especially excited about
nintendo ds
the first one i was playing in 10 dogs
on it
and sims there was a sims game for that
what else did i play on there
huh i was i was drawing a lot on that
chat thingy
yeah okay pokemon i guess i don't i
don't did i play
pokemon on nintendo ds yeah piktochat
i was drawing on that one that was fun
did you play since the way same way you
do now i don't know what you mean
with that mystery dungeon i don't think
me
thank you so much for the pinky don't
mind me i just wanted to send some love
to you and all of cafe
oh click on this that is
very kind of you i think everyone
appreciates that thank you
so much i wish the same for you
[Music]
thank you wait let me let me get
you for the red super chat um thanks
thank you for happiness and joy viva la
yara also first read super chat oh
thank you since it's your first one let
me also give you a kissy
very good hello thank you so much for
your support
thank you thank you i'm glad that you're
here and enjoying my streams i hope that
you will stay here for a long long time
don't have a choice anyway
the spam and the nintendo
stream is
is crazy but that's what i thought but
i guess my stream was just way way
behind
still still in mario party and now i
just refreshed and it's actually
something else i guess that's why
everyone is like
no this know this show this and this and
this and this
when the when the stream was ending
and i minimized the window it showed
like 900 over 900 thousand
viewers did it at some point get 1
million or did it
just gitty giddy not reach 1 million
because that's the highest view count or
like
live view count i've ever seen yes it
was over a million
holy holy
one million live viewers
and if you could if you like um add the
ones on the nintendo germany
channel and then the nintendo japan
channel
that's that's even more i wonder how
many they had
damn
oh ah uk
exists as well i mean
don't take it out of context
you can't nintendo you can't exist as
well
i already see it someone is uploading a
clip that's two seconds long it's just
me saying
ah uk exists as well
thank you learning both english and
japanese now hopefully i can understand
all the conversation without google
translate someday
good luck i wish you the best i'm sure
you can do it
fighter tj
russia plane rider slope is dangerous
i love your energy your personality is
so much fun you've become one of my
favorite features of the time
thank you so much thank you i'm happy to
hear that
um
i am japanese i'm sorry if i make a
mistake i'm studying english because i
want to see your life
i still don't know what you're talking
about but i want to be able to
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
german sounds so powerful
that's just because i am powerful has
nothing to do with german language
captain corncob duncan ginger ranger
[Music]
uh slightly unrelated but i recently
learned that the phoenix enemies and
final fantasy mystic quest are called
hot wings
but you might find it amusing that is
amusing
excessive boot thank you
some other examples of metroidvanias
include guacamelee
and oriental blindfolds oh
ori is something i will play at some
point for sure i promise you that
because it is made by
people of my country
yes and i know it has a very cute
um but emotional
story very sad story and i i appreciate
that
i know it's a really really great game
from and i
i just want to support such a
masterpiece
from my country yeah
yes yes ori is made from people of my
country
australia
uh wikitones thank you for the red super
chat
danke i saw a clip recently about you
hoping to be the best bridge of for
whole life after coco senpai sadly
graduates
i know it's hard to choose to feel phil
but as i said when i first met you
you're already one of the best
ps sorry i've been away but i'll be
around more soon enough oh
thank you i guess you've been busy with
something else i'm glad you're planning
to come back
yeah i i mean people have already been
calling me
a bridge between halloween and homeland
japan i'm happy about that
and i'll do my best in the future
and and and yeah try to step
into her footsteps er or shoes or
whatever how do you say that
in english in german we say yeah
well i don't even know what do we say i
say auf wiedersehen but wait wait wait
almost
right and bridge soon and bridge
already ambridge uh
i love how for you guys it's like almost
like a reflex that i trained onto you
when i oh i preach when i say
in german we say you guys automatically
have this reflex
to say avidasin
[Laughter]
i love it i love it that's funny
thank you wikitools glad to have you
back soon
thank you for your support thank you so
much
crystal burial chrysler barrow
oh yeah uh was that the game i was
interested in
i'm glad you're interested in uh austria
ascending definitely recalls vintage
vanilla where stuff all in sphere of
grim gram wrong i hope you will play it
um i'm i'm interested in nfds yes yes
don't know if i would do a full gameplay
on my channel
but i've been like
sad about not being able to have a
first time experience with autumn sphere
anymore because i played it through
before
because i really liked all golden sphere
um there's also a similar game that came
out recently
lost epic that one i also wanna
give a try yo
i never really paid attention to persona
i'm sure it's a great game series
but i never paid attention to it and you
know what i'm kind of happy about that
because i wouldn't be able to stream it
anyway and that hurts me if i
if i see a great game that i really
really like and really piques my
interest
and i can't stream it now that upsets me
now
and but shin megami tensei yeah we
probably wouldn't be able to stream that
evil but it also looks very interesting
maybe maybe someday i'll play it
privately
you know there is actually like a big
chance that i would do that but
at the moment i got no time looks great
though looks like a great game series
both of them
gizelle dancing thank you
um thank you thank you i wish you the
best too
and i got really used to it but yeah
pudding channel
british money oh thank you
what's that was that really necessary
they'll start
[Music]
let me give you an angle kiss
go away go away okay
why did i why did i freeze there come on
anyway anyway
uh people dance and
sky dancing just like when you
hear when when we hear you say usual oh
my next one is room
oh yeah
the usual
thank you this is it guys i
will be doing some stuff and and uh
hoverline decoration maybe
live tweeting bandai namco uh
presentation
thank you for spending your time with me
tomorrow is
mystery collab announcing soon in
announcing in three hours alrighty thank
you so much
for watching together with me
that was fun short stream
two and a half hours
[Music]
um
prepare your questions for the cuckoo
senpai in the meantime
[Music]
thank you guys for watching and in
german we say
cheese bamboozle
we do say cheese as well in german no
did we say alvita's in
what oh i gotcha i gotcha
cheers yeah just just
choose the trees bye bye
[Music]
in
do
[Music]
you