[Music]
[Applause]
welcome to my first lesson today we are
with K and Pie hello k
let's
go oh my
God would you like to introduce
yourself see
[Music]
um yeah wait what else do I
say um um how do I say uh what what was
it again uh I am I am Phoenix can I say
that somehow M of course you can so to
say I am you say
EO mhm and then you have to say uh you
have to say Phoenix is
f f oh I like that that sounds nice but
yeah in uh you have you also have to put
something in between so the
a yeah
or or Una Una so la is the the Phoenix
and una is a phoenix
good job good
St
[Music]
y can I can I flex uh to you I have like
I I try to remember all kinds of words
mhm so I'm just going to read down my
list M so you have a rough idea of the
words I already no okay okay that sounds
good to me okay it's not that long don't
worry and I feel like probably there's a
lot of words that I don't remember okay
so it's like
and yeah he knows a lot of time you you
bus him well the lesson is over then I
have nothing to teach you yay y we're
done bito we're done bito yeah yeah yeah
no it's okay you know a lot of things
but today I hope I can teach you
something extra something more than that
yeah can I ask you this is this going to
be like um a series that you do with all
kinds of members or are just we doing
this we'll see if someone will ask me
why not we can do we can do finals at
the end
finals I can put you um on an exam at
the end of of the year and see you oh
yeah cuz like I don't know how serious
we want to be about this but I I
remember a while ago I asked you to
teach me Italian in the street right but
I said can we do it like a biweekly
thing or
so like every two weeks or so we have a
collab where you teach me more Italian I
mind I wouldn't mind I would that if I
if you want to make it seriously I can
do that but people might get I don't
know maybe it's weird if one gets too
serious about it h this should just be a
joke stream I don't know I don't know I
think other people could take the
opportunity to you know uh learn some
it's as well why
not I mean I have a lot of you know you
know K Senai uh can can I just go k
today because you are my teacher it's
I'm your teacher so I'm going to call
you K today yeah yeah yeah yeah I I
don't mind uh wait I feel like I knew
the word for
student ah can you give me the first
letter
s it it's really similar
wait now I have to think of the Japanese
word
say no it's
stud ah easy that's not I feel like I I
learned a different word uh maybe uh
aluno Al know it's similar to
student oh okay no student is
okay yeah would you like to
start yeah so all right mhm so uh K do
you know that um Italian language has
actually um gender for every single word
you know that yeah so yeah that's a
little weird but it's just because we
differentiate for some reason the
article um so like in English let me get
let me get my my my pen mhm oh in German
we also have uh like a genda for every
word and it's weird oh yeah right like
school is female and car uh is the
what's it called not not male and not
female it's D AO d
a train is
male yeah yeah we have very similar
thing very similar thing to Italian so
in English we use the for everything but
in Italian to use the article uh we're
going to
use
or
depend
right okay okay you know that already M
can you say m and yes perfect
and and mhm
perfect well she know a lot of
things so good and you know um I mean of
course we already mention that but I
explained for the chatin as well
um yeah everyone this is a big class
today you got to learn yeah so many
students so many students hear me out
guys so if if you are in DB and you
don't know if you should use ill or La
you should check the end of the word
right ah
yeah so for
example so it's like the boy right oh
yeah but if we change the last and it's
of course a boy but if we change the
last letter it
becomes M and now it's
[Music]
yeah now it's
fale ragata is the girl and Ragu is the
boy yes wow yeah it's prettyy simple
pretty straightforward but now I have a
question for you K yeah what
about
v v v is La what about what about
fich that was Phoenix right it's laich
yeah yeah yeah
yeah it's laughing
to but it doesn't have the a at the end
right you're like you're like how do you
know so this is kind of an exception I
think um uh I'm not quite sure
either but I think it's an exception and
you know like you're going to meet a few
words that end with e like I or
E and those are exceptions usually or
those are plural but we go into it
later okay okay then another example
Pomodoro is il pom right
yeah yeah good
job what about um I have an example for
you actually right there what about this
what is this do you
know I only know G because I am G person
I knew it that's why I put this do well
I probably know it I probably heard it
before uh what's
do yeah I I can can help you I can help
you okay please okay this is
car a car car
meat what what do you mean me do
you I thought you meant c a r n
e it's car wait but car is also Italian
right for
meat car car car yeah car with with r is
also is meat yes that's another one
right okay okay okay so car and car yes
car it's the car and they're is meat
they're both ill
right
no no
so
is yeah
but
it's see we found a great example of how
Italiano is very confuso I know I think
you just got to memorize those words
there's nothing really you can do about
it because yeah you know is this an
exceptions how do I say s this in in
Italian
capois good job good job good job good
job
yes car car car does like this I think
[Music]
pasta oh so cute okay ah let's see what
else Sensei Sensei oh yes yes yes yes
what's jetpack in Italiano jetpack is
Jetpack no we don't distribute packs
that means that because jetpack does not
exist in Italiano so you have to stop
asking her jetpacks don't exists in
Italy stop asking her for
jetpacks I mean they I think they
exist they don't this is how you can
finally make him stop asking Basta
finito no b no it's okay dude it's okay
they
they they have to they I think they're
just very bored
yeah it's okay they can chase a dream
right M A with a jetpack they'll Chas it
with a jetpack
yeah don't give any
jetpacks my teacher always used to say
that like the whole time really I don't
even think she was Italian but she
really liked speaking Italian I kind of
say that in Italian all the time aot
yeah I
kind yeah I'm thinking so Al means
so yeah so so so so so so
yeah
it's so
so at the beginning of a sentence
usually right yeah we say that in
English as well we say a lot of so so or
like
like I guess like I
guess ah yeah yeah yeah yeah we say that
all the time mhm yeah I learned it from
my Italiano teacher in school in hotel
school so I know a lot of Hotel specific
words and like restaurant specific words
a a little bit helpful when I travel
when I travel to Italy I travel already
like I think three times to Italy this
year oh my god really just this year
yeah or yeah I think so or two times in
last last year also two times or so but
yeah I tried to use a little bit of
Italian when I'm there I believe I
believe next time you're going to go
you're going to speak fluently yeah I
feel like I know many more words but
when I'm there then I forget it because
I get like nervous to talk anying cuz I
don't want to say anything wrong I know
but you know I think it's cute if you
try
no one say that you're bother anything
don't worry about it
oh
pie
pie are you back oh yeah I'm back I
think she
exploded hello hello hello hello she's
back she's
back where have you been
oh huh huh are you going to bathroom
without my permission huh without asking
to the to the to the
teacher hello hello hello feel like my
internet is dying a little bit but I'm
here I'm here I'm here I think we're
take your time don't worry about it it's
good oh good oh good so no no not skip
our skip our class no we not skip a skip
of the class right no I would never skip
my Italian class yeah K if you have to
go bathroom you have to ask me politely
any okay how do I ask so how do you ask
wait
well yeah and how to say I have to go to
the bathroom do you
[Laughter]
know Kaa Kaa means what AA
ah what
Whata ah B yeah B KOA you have to you
have to you have to
say but that's like isn't that am I
asking like where is the toilet when I
asked that yeah you can you can also say
like can I go to the
bathroom and in that in that case you
want to say excuse me which
[Music]
iszy mhm
I remember
that oh that's too long I know excuse me
it's
szy can
it's so usually uh in Italian we don't
say the subject you know that wait and
right with d and oh I can type S i i
sorry I can't I can't I can't I can't do
that I'm bad I'm bad at
writing she saw nothing
okay um
so so you say
[Music]
scoozie excuse me P it's yeah it's like
wait I'm I'm going to put this in the
there you
go but we don't actually say
e i okay yeah we like to cut out some
words yeah yeah so POS is I
can she was too quick she was too
quick my Discord is killing my internet
but I went to the B I went to the
yeah you can you can go to the
bathroom
put you got to better note this down
because I'm I'm not going to explain you
next time you got to tell me no I to
say no you can't you
remember the whole sentence now yeah
that's how it works
but don't SAR in my
class don't SAR in my class oh my
God I didn't
[Music]
know can you say Basta finito when I say
bito don't say that ever again
I'm sorry okay it's okay if your
connection I love when you say
that that's to know let me get a sip of
water
Aqua Aqua Aqua Aqua is water aqua
[Music]
which
cat son son
pink yeah yeah
[Music]
yeaha
mhm yeah you're like an
orange and you are M strawberry cat how
to say orange in Italian
cat no that's the
truth
aruh yeah AR
close close enough very close very close
good job how to say how to say
pink
pink yeah yeah yeah how to say pink
[Music]
oh pink pink Rosa
Rosa someone suggested to you
but you know we're we're all in the same
classroom they're also learning and I
mean if a different
student don't suggest to when she's
interroga it's teamwork it's
[Music]
teamwork passing notes class okay now
some more notes
get don't talk into my
class I pass a note to you guys I pass a
note to
[Laughter]
you she didn't see she didn't see who
who what what
what no okay listen I have homework for
you
now
already no what what is our lesson
already over you get at the end it's
it's something in between the lesson
it's like a test how say already uh I am
a pink cat and no actually the opposite
I am a
orange orange cat
and is a
pink pink
C high level Italian already
big cat how to translate this well you
didn't teach me big that's something I'm
going to teach you
now yeah yeah yeah Grand good
job mm
[Music]
got okay let me teach you
something in
Italian you want to say the subject
first
before the compliment you know
before
um yeah that I don't remember
so yeah so you got to
say you can do it
[Music]
adjective adjective so you have to say
the subject before the
[Music]
adjective
yeah
so correct
correct do I need uh do I need
La um you want to say a orange cat so
instead of La you have to say a is
translated
in
or no sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry don't worry take time don't worry
take time
how do I say she is like cuz I said e
can I
[Music]
say and then I go already to to the
other word big cat yeah okay now let me
help you on that let me help you on that
so uh because we have two adjective
right I'm big pink and big at the same
time I would say Roso Grande Grande no
because Grand Roso is more like big pink
mhm mm right I would say Roso
Grande
oh so you want to say
[Music]
okay I don't know normally my internet
is not this bad I don't know what's
going on it's okay maybe you can uh
don't I don't know don't look at the oh
I can try to change my
don't SAR my
class you I just heard you like Scream
the moment I said L you like no then it
cut off and I was gone that's swear my
CL wait I'll try to instead of streaming
I want to try to one second oh yeah can
you make the quality lower or so maybe I
will take L of my
internet what about what about this I
got I got I better
maybe
[Music]
okay where were we so I was explaining
to
you about the adjective so you want to
say
uh
Grand M Grande is first and then Roso is
after cat mm
Grand
bra
perfect chat is correcting you they're
saying it's Rosa not Roso because Roso
is red and Rosa is pink yeah told
Rosa yeah you're saying Rosa I said
Rosa Rosa Rosa it's pink Rosa it's
red okay okay Rosa
good she's so good she is so good she's
Unstoppable
okay we have Rosa also in German same
writing mhm Rosa you say Rosa it's also
pink but like it's usually more it's not
a hot pink it's more like a m
marshmallow pink oh how you say my kind
of pink in German M your kind of pink I
mean it is something like it's a mix of
the the sweet and the hot pink I don't
know hard to say I would say I would in
German I would say pink because we also
use pink
oh I see interesting but this is the
enti lesson so yeah let's
go I want to teach a new a new word
are you ready
yeah what is it ah goat
yeah oh you know how to say goat any I
can teach you teach me okay
so go any time
is
kaaa exactly
andaa for
laa
laa yes and yeah I guess you can get
very good cheese
from the goat yeah that's actually nice
yeah and I want to teach you something
related to that do you know that in ital
we have a tongue
twist with this animal and it's oh no
yeah it's time above I'm going I'm going
to show you show you the English first
oh uh above the bench the goat lives
below the bench the goat dies is this
just like a way to advertise above and
below stream above
below I am
predictable the goat maybe the goat is
hidden somewhere in the song Maybe maybe
maybe the goat wrote the lyrics maybe
yeah I wonder okay D destruction
here no destruction and the Italian
version
is
[Music]
is you got to say to now
[Laughter]
who bad close
enough it's uh yeah you say it a little
bit aggressively can you say it more
gently sorry I'm a very aggressive
teacher I guess
I wait you should do like Italian
ASMR really gently and sometimes maybe
aggressively but also then again
gently I need to be a tough
teacher so that's why no you don't need
to be tough teacher I will listen to you
anyway I like to be a tough teacher
though okay that that's what I want to
be okay MRE MRE
okay
[Laughter]
um that was funny
um how do I say my mother
M we don't let me think like we don't
usually say mother we say mama no
actually no actually you're right we
probably say m i don't don't really use
it
much it's very formal I'd
[Music]
Sayo do you
like it's in your logo I noticed there's
there's a cucumber in your logo there's
a cucumber because uh for some reason
chatini likes it I don't I don't know I
don't personally like
chat
but
no
no okay I will eat oh my God but they're
sending so many I know they're obsessed
or I can make so much cucumber
salad no what about zucchini zucchini
sounds like an Italian word now that I
think about it yeah I'm okay with
zucchini is zucchini an Italian
[Music]
word is is zucchini an Italian word I
guess so it is loan from Italian where
zucchini is the plal masculine
diminutive of Tuukka in Italian
masculine tukino is attested early in h
per
do you in Italian you say
tukino
um we it zuk Zina zuc zucchini zuc zuc
oh my God I never thought about it
before that it's it's definitely it just
looks like an Italian word to me but
yeah it is it is Mama
MIM Mama
M good job with the Maro the Marino okay
zucchini on Pizza
[Music]
okayi ah zucchini on Pizza is okay but
no cucumber yeah good I've seen pizza
before that has like you know the white
sauce and then top with like thin
zucchini yeah I think it's not something
I eaten very often honestly
usually
e how do you like
[Music]
pizza uh oh wait I knew the word for
pineapple I know you were waiting for
this not
you
ananas
Gran Oro
[Music]
repeting what
repeat very good and then
tuna another just just tuna nothing else
h no like usually maybe with like
there's red onions on there I
think right sometime but just
H you're probably thinking of uh those
small what do you call them
again yeah no I know
tuna yeah also like just Margarita is
very good margarita is a best but it has
to be napoi Pizza
see I'm I'm agree with you best I agree
with you best pizza comes from napoi m
I hope one day we can go eat together
Pizza in Napoli yeah I mean we kind of
did
already right oh
yeah I mean we we got yeah actually
you're right it was it was pretty
napolitan Pizza no pretty much me and k
k we went to eat pizza together and it
was pretty um actually it was very um
very legit not
but so Big W yeah it was very big that's
a that's a Italian style and Mama
ordered so many starters and we were so
overwhelmed oh my God I was expecting so
many starters because like I ordered one
but then they got like I think three for
the table and because where are so many
people so many and then we eat so many
of the starters and then we didn't have
hunger anymore for the pizza I think
uh so yeah the um the owner of the
restaurant wanted to impress and Italian
so they got a lot of a lot of food with
us it was nice though yeah it was nice
it was good we can go again
again anyway let's go back to our
class okay okay please teach me more
mhm let's see so next thing I want to
teach
you is
um let me check okay so do you know how
to make the plural of words uh that's
important
think um I think usually it turns like
into e like uh like for example I don't
know
um maybe CRA turns into
Capri no damn
it no no no let me teach you so when I
say e i mean i in the English
pronunciation but yeah let's take
theu for example right
andu rata raata
so this is uh
male this is fale okay so um when you
want to yes when you want to uh make a
word plural you change into
RI RI instead of the O you put the E
this is the I but I say e because in we
say e yeah me too I say it too like that
oh okay and then the a you change it
with yeah
Capo Capo so CAA is
C good job what about the article before
though yeah yeah you learn to my old
Italiano
teacher I think so good yeah I think Le
is like the same for both uh male and
female you use it for both right no no
um so to
sayi instead of
e you want to say
[Music]
e i remember yeah this
isi and this
is example so I said uh IL cell so IL
cello becomes e
perfect and for becomes for yeah perfect
what
about mhm e mhm it sounds weird GTI no
it doesn't sound weird GTI it's perfect
good job GTI
okay they call me gato
sometimes gato oh yeah the cat with the
with the butt they call
me guys wait for the wait for the day
when she becomes
3D okay no no you are under pressure now
not me
okay okay um more
Grand yes
grand
grand I really like your pronunciation
of words I'll be honest
yeah I like how you say things it's very
cute I like how you say
things cute oh I like
Italiano I like
kaha I visited I visited so many times
already cuz my mommy she used to always
bring me to Italy cuz she loves Italy
and she speaks Italian probably better
than me for sure I mean she forgot a lot
of words but we should you should uh do
collab with my mommy
Italian collab with Car's mom can't wait
for
it I'm down for
it
yipp
Mom Mom
collabs okay let's let me give you a few
more words just to
practice what about
[Music]
it the
dog well huh it's already a at the end
so maybe it just stays I don't
know maybe it stays it no it becomes
e yeah same thing goes with
car e carne no car we mentioned it was
fam La remember oh you're right it's the
bambole
[Music]
effect and in plural
is
perfect he's so
[Laughter]
goodoo okay now I the few words that we
can let's see oops
oops you so
nothing I think those are words that you
already know because you know your your
level of italent but I think those are
General words that you can sorry General
sentences that you often use right you
already know all those though right
[Music]
hello how are
you
wait no don't look at the no I'm not
looking I'm not
looking I forgot because I'm mixing it
also with uh uh Spanish I always like
Wonder wait which one was Spanish and
which one was Italian right it's very
similar yeah
perfect and then second and
then no you would
say stop I am fine ah stop B yeah okay
okay okay stop B
and please wait in the in the sense of
uh like per or yeah please it's like so
okay we use that all the
time
uh yeah both is good actually
or was good or it
Wasa uh Kaa means
what yeah but you taught me that before
oh no no no it's because I was confused
I was asking your question like you said
um
B and I was like B
what it was a question for okay I
thought you were saying that's how I can
ask as well no no no no I was asking
question because I wanted to teacher to
say the whole sentence instead of
saying then I can also
sayh
uhhuh perfect and you can say
e left and right good
job she
[Applause]
so so good
I prepared also um some EDI idioms is it
correct to say that EDM EDM no you mean
okay you mean Ed I don't know IDE I
don't know how you say it
either I don't know idms probably
IDE IDE you got got the mean you prepare
some EDM though above and below is kind
of EDM
yeah a little
[Music]
bit okay okay okay now I'm going to
teach you
some
idioms
okay do you know this ah Polo
poly wait idioms what what does that
even mean is that uh sayings like
phrases yeah like phrases we say um
like mhm yes just yeah phrases
phrases yeah I understand okay yeah yeah
yeah
so this is something that is very
popular we say I I personally say all
the time I really like saying
that and it's translated in to make the
chicken laugh
oh make the chicken laugh it means to do
something so ridiculous that it will be
even that it will it will even make the
chicken laugh you know
H like I give an example right in
English um that excuse will make the
chicken laugh No One Believes it
wait say the say the English one again
that excuse would make the chicken laugh
No One Believes it ah so when something
is really ridiculous yeah very
ridiculous like super is this going to
be a test
[Laughter]
yes is it
and for context I give you also a new
word today R means
love reader is laugh mm CH
laugh okay
capoo job next
one I think idioms are important in a
language because it makes you you know
feel
more I no you get to learn something
that usually you don't get to learn on
books but I just imagine like me sitting
in Italy in a restaurant and then
something weird happens and I say to the
waiter so
randomly i e am I
right that'll be so
Random like what what what did she I
think will be very impressed really
yeah next one
is I like I like this one this one is
[Music]
silly yum yum yum yum this one
is in
[Music]
English in English you can say uh to
have ham on your
eyes and the
meaning is to not say what is obvious to
be blind I think we have a very similar
saying in German too really yeah sounds
very similar similar tell
tell uhuh to have H on your eyes to be
blind to something right in front of
you how do we say it in German we say
something also like do do you have
something on your eyes I feel like we
also say something
specific Tom we say Pomodoro we say do
you have tomatoes on your eyes oh really
white Tomatoes though that's
cute yeah I can
say I think if it tell me that you have
tomatoes on your eyes I would be I will
bring you to the
hospital because I think like you're
going to you're bleeding from your
eyes oh no oh no please
no wait
where um
[Music]
I I like how you say it can you say it
again
[Laughter]
again one more time
okay one more
time now I like the last part the
most okay next
[Laughter]
one ah
another a mhm a means to have is on the
test so a pasta
means to have your hands in your in in
the
dough oh wait oh is it when someone's in
trouble no it actually means to be
involved in many things or activities at
the same time or yeah like
um I'm going to give you an example you
you use like a pasta related idiom ideum
in it in
Italy cute but pasta in this case means
though ah okay
okay in pasta
mm what's uh ah Mone is hands yes M ah
Le so was it original
[Music]
La Mana La
Mano Mano yeah that's another
exception one hand Le two
[Music]
hands I know L yeah I know it's a little
it's a little weird that's wild yeah
that is a little wild wait wait
le le are you taking notes this is going
to be in the class yeah are you taking
notes I'm not the only one doing a test
yeah I want to do it kfp words mhm you
can't take my notes you can't copy my
notes guys I'm not giving you my notes
or my homework no no
no okay being very busy with something
like
oh let me give an example like uh Joan
always always has his hand in the door
with thousands
projects
Joan Joan I don't know Joan I know I
just invented a
name oh May
K Mor always has her hands in the D with
a thousands of project okay translate
that in
now a is like to have but how you say
she
has um
[Music]
ha
mhm
yes ha means she has it's similar to
English in that
way instead of a completely or yeah so
let me let me write down so
Mar oh let me make it
[Music]
bigger you call her
you call her by myy do you call her Mory
you don't call her Mory I call her cie
but like some people I feel like most
people call her
cie some people call her only Mory but
it's I feel like it's funny I like Morty
like why would you why would you say
Callie if she has a very short
moring cuz Callie is
cuter I like Morty
wait so do you do you actively already
like call her Mory in
collabs yeah really no I'm
self-conscious I feel like a lot of fans
maybe call her Mory but I feel a lot
call
her no sure but I feel like co-workers
maybe call her Cali more often and then
fans call her Mory more often I am a f
she here I
a she's here
hell I know the answer it's Forest what
are you talking
about get into this class right now
she's a failing
student she doesn't know what she's
talking about don't talk to other people
like
this be polite this is only
talk you'll be next Callie you'll be
next don't worry I'm I'm willing to
teach
everyone you're such a
Mor what does that
mean okay so Mor Mor
Mor wa you
forgot the article Le uhhuh Mor
Hal in
pasta yeah and she literally already did
when she made pizza with you
exactly she she literally put her hands
into
pasta amazing making these things come
true as
Destiny yeah yeah I loved it you like it
is silent is it silent what
the H yeah
it's yes it's it's like it's quite like
silent h we don't say hot okay sometime
I do though I don't
know sometime I do
anyway subtle it's a subtle it's very
subtle mhm okay okay okay okay Capo
Capo okay and then
I have one
last i e EDM for you that I think is EDM
EDM okay Anda
EDM oh
p
is maybe it means there's many fish in
the sea no no
it means to feel out of place or
uncomfortable in a
situation ah so very relatable is uh to
be a fish out of
water ah I see I see well that surely
feels very uncomfortable for the fish I
imagine yeah sah can you say it again
can you say it again
s oh I'm so unsure about the
pronunciation I
say can you please say it again so I can
get my pronunciation
[Music]
right for
say again sorry one more time I'll get
it right this time you're best stent Arn
you I know I just want you to say it
more because
[Music]
your
okay
fish what's what does it
mean is to
be okay okay like it's um to be a fish
out of the water so for it's
um it's
actually fora but um in Italy s in
Italian we uh we cut a lot of words at
the end so instead of like saying
fora we say
fora makes sense M but you can you can
also say fi it's also
correct fi F
daaa okay dala because it's da which is
from and then laa which is the
water MH so
daaa
together okay
oops good job and now from here we go to
the next
lesson cat like
fish yeah
yeah what
T
yeah ah or maybe salmon depends ah you
like
Tona
pza but only like with with pasta and
with pizza I like T the most but when
it's like on its own like you know like
grilled fish or so on its own then maybe
salmon can I can I can I tell you
something yeah every time I eat tuna it
tastes exactly like
PR H I don't know if it's just me but
every time I taste tuna I feel I I feel
like eating the P I don't know why it
feels the same oh interesting it's like
maybe a weird Jean that you
have I some people have that with like
some uh herbs wait okay can you one
question you know when I say in my
stream I say uh I like uh like tuna
Pizza mhm they're like what are you
talking about that's so weird because
like most of my viewers are probably
like from North America and they they
it's not normal there to have tuna no
it's very popular tun tuna and onions
are is a very popular pizza tell them
tell them it's normal in Italy right
yeah they don't even know about pizza
with fries they think that I'm weird but
it's actually a very common and popular
pizza I mean that's that's I
mean let's go back to lesson but pizza
with fries is more like for children
right for okay what if I what if I have
baby
taste leave me alone okay I like
it it's actually the only Pizza I ever
got in my
life oh my God kind of well thank God
they don't have like uh uh fries on
Pizza on the menu in the restaurant we
went
to no I would have what would what would
they think of you it's normal maybe they
would think nothing it's normal okay I
understand that it's like a you know
like I mean even here like some people
eat like ice cream with fries but it
just feels like such a meme food no it's
great it's it's actually tasty and it's
very
popular it in the chat
please you can't believe it exists and
it's like a thing but but then you
should accept the pineapple as
well it works really
well anyway let's move on on the next
Mommy
Mommy uh mommy put about the pineapple
do you know how to
Mommy
what pineapple is very deast in its own
thank you yeah I like
pineapple wait wait wait I forgot did
you ever have it
before like on pizza
I'm not going to tell you she she looks
so I had this feeling that she wants to
like kick me out of this classroom I'm
about to end the
lesson okay please no but it's it's nice
it's
refreshing okay you know what you know
what skill
[Music]
issue wait M MRE MRE yes see
um I want to ask
you
um I mean I'm not asking about the
toilet
Ito um okay
Google can you
[Music]
tudge uh
mhm
okay please show it on stream okay okay
I'll do
it oh wait H that's okay one of them is
Margarita um that's not just show just
show the first
one oh
[Music]
okay I want to know what you think yeah
your your uh voice kind of lowered a
moment ago can you hear me yeah but um
this this this wait maybe I'm touch
something can you hear me now this yeah
okay that's
better yeah I made H okay this is a
mixed Pizza on the right side is uh this
is before baking it but is a tunel with
corn and mozzarella and left that is
just uh I think yeah Margarita basil
corn and then on the side is corn corn
corn corn corn corn corn
corn do you like corn by any chance I
love
corn yay yeah corn is so good so good um
so you it actually it was so
good so you made like half is is a
margarita I I I I can see with corn
margarita with corn and then yeah the
SEC the half is like tuna and and onions
yeah red onions and and a and a a circle
of a circle of Love
am um um let's
say let's say that it was a stroke of
Genius
it's a stroke for my
heart um I'll make it for you you know
what please visit me in Austria sometime
and I'll make you
pizza I I'll I'll I'll be honest with
you I hate onions and tuna both okay no
problem what about
corn corns on
Pizza
yes okay but not that much like not the
not the circle of summoning some Spirit
here just like just maybe like here and
there that's fine I mean but this is it
was amazing because you know I I I have
a proper pizza oven so you know it got a
good like
grilling Grill taste and why you make a
pizza that I actually
like well okay that would probably be
the other Pizza I made the margarita but
um the margarita look good though yeah
right I mean on that picture it just
came out of the oven so it it was a
little bit too watery I was still
learning you can show the margarita too
if you want it looks yummy I'm going to
cut it one cut cut the pizza
I want the pizza now my the
pizza it looks very Yumm yeah it's messy
because it was too um the the I think
the cheese was too watery still so it
the left side especially looks kind of
like very weird but it tasted so good it
tasted kind of almost like napolitan
pizza yummy yeah I the texture looks
good M yum yeah I didn't do it in a
normal oven I did it in a proper Pizza
Oven that you know finishes the pizza in
like 2 minutes yeah why it gets so hot
it makes it in 2
minutes okay I definitely want to try
your pizza C and let's go come over come
over European off collab I would like
that maybe maybe I I can even make you
one the fries on top really yeah what do
would you
actually of course I'll make you a
margarita with fries okay then okay then
yay but then you also have to try my
pineapple
pizza I haven't asked you to try fries
on
pizza but I'm asking you as your Senpai
to eat my pineapple pizza please I'm
asking as your Sensei to don't make
pizza for me we finally Apple
[Music]
okay we'll see about that we'll see
about
that basto basto okay next lesson K are
you taking notes that's very
important okay
so that's about
um let me grab my my beautiful pen again
I lost it pen
bra how about more
[Music]
pants le
le M but that's
pasta that's that's why they called pin
because they looks like
pan what what what
what oh my
God mind blown mind
blown the more you know so wait so
there's like without context you
wouldn't know if they're talking about
the pasta or the
[Music]
pen yeah I mean I mean you written the
same way yeah yeah yeah it's written the
same way but you kind of get it like
you're not going to say I'm gonna
eat P like it's it's obvious yeah but
but I mean if there's no context then
you don't know like if they just write
down this word say p without context
though there always needs to be context
okay okay
okay understand capito
capoo pass me your pen pass me your pen
hands over pasta instead of a
pen here one pen you know okay okay you
know what now that now that we talking
about this why speakers dying right
now I
know what what are you dying for what
they
dying Spanish chatini I don't know
what's wrong They're
laughing maybe p means something else in
in Spanish something bad something bad
anyway let's move
on Spanish and everyone
else I see okay so
yeah
H see do you know wait I'm I'm taking
the the the picture one second give me a
moment goodbye goodbye Pizza goodbye was
nice seeing you was a nice lunch
break okay I found it so do you know
about
oops Yeah Yeah Yeah R pasta mhm you know
how those are
[Music]
called far far a
far yeah yeah yeah I heard it
before um does it mean ribbon
no you know what it means you can you
can try you can kind of get it though
from the shap uh like a uh
candy no what else
it kind of butterfly butterfly butterfly
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah oh my God oh my
God oh my God oh my God far that does
sound like
butterfly yeah
far far beautiful means wait butter
means
butterfly
cute so Nai mama is faral Mama
oh make
sense
Mama cute
nice cute ah bow tie is
farino
cute farala in single okay
far far
far mhm is butterfly like a
butter
capoo mhm
mhm okay next I want to teach you a few
rules about the Italian language if you
okay with
it so uh yeah do you have any question
before we move
on and
[Music]
raising up my
teacher no
[Music]
[Laughter]
don't make me
blush I shouldn't love my teacher should
I oh no I mean I mean I
mean I
mean I'm lagging my oh wow wow I'm
lagging you made my heart
Ling I made myself
I this is something now hi what is it
so yeah yeah it
means I love you
yeah but also I
[Music]
stand I like I
like you e also means I love you ah Volo
bner means yeah bner means like good and
Volo means like want yeah but like in
the
context um
T is used for your like number one lover
[Laughter]
so okay
H I accept
it yeah with passion we have passion
with a lot of
passion but if you don't want to say TI
to everyone you can say t Ben for your
friends M so
everyone yeah
yeah well I I I guess okay someone like
Ollie would probably say the to everyone
because she has the passion to has a lot
of VI
yes but but I say it just to
you thank you just kidding probably
honestly I'd say it also to a few other
people but okay okay I I I got to be
honest I got to be honest I mean you
know n side
wait it's
okay it's okay to love multiple people
it's okay yeah it's full of love we have
we have um
M yeah Love Is Love is up there where
the faral
Flies
[Music]
yeah I I I at least I'm the only teacher
you love and you love in this way
maybe yeah I mean that's yeah probably
yeah although
me
Indonesian anyway let's move on okay so
this is about
reading so I want to teach you the
difference between
these oh yeah okay please remind me and
these and is that a is that a g or or C
these and these oh okay so G mhm this is
a g yeah sorry my I cannot
write I don't know how to write anymore
anyway I would say the GI I is G yes
like in B joural correct and then the
ghi probably is just G
correct the c i the chi okay uh looking
at my yeah for example key y so C hi I
is uh-huh uh-huh and then C I I also
sometimes uh UNS sure but G because d g
d d
exactly
wow we
have G okay so Gigi becomes g g
yeah no no no she's geeky for
me she
CeCe is chi chi and
chii and Chi yeah yeah
yeah no see we need some differentiation
so it's going to be gigy and chii this
is switching switching it
up first it was g g and CC now it is g g
and Chi it's it's
g no Ki
okay and now next step that's a little
bit more difficult what about the
difference between
these
and
these Lee Lee Lee Lee g is silent
no GLE no maybe not silent what G is
correct but this one becomes ye
kind of
like ah okay well yeah we become silent
but the L also becomes silent okay yeah
it becomes
like yeah like like
a
okay okay okay okay okay okay perfect
skip skip the G and the
L sorry
oh skip skipa skipa the the L too yeah
so for example um let me
think
uh did is this
word this is a
flower a
it's pronounced
g
[Music]
g yeah
g g g are lies in
English can you say it again
g
g that's a bit complicated but is g g g
g per m
are the lies in English lies Lily in
English you know li like the white
flowers yeah so oh so this is one
specific flower not any flower yeah any
flower oh look at
the your em is so
cute good job guys so UC they're so
educated look at
them they're so cute
okay I love chatini I love chatini too
they're
nice when they L for impossible things
like jetpacks anyway flowers I want to
teach you this word do you
know flower M do you know how to say
flower I feel like I
know but I need to be remembered yeah
it's
fi Fior mhm M oh yeah I heard that
before I didn't realize that was flower
anymore uhhuh
yeah F but that okay that's already
plural okay so is it originally laora no
Fiora is one
[Music]
flower but it's the same thing with uh k
mhm no flower has to be love no f is
male in German also
flowers
female oh really yeah is it flowers in
German blo blo the blo oh cute like
bloom
yeah yeah wow
okay
okay eori eori
yeah
perfect and I I will have you know that
I was the best uh in my Italian class
even though we were all pretty but
I was the best out of those shitty
students I can't tell you were very good
honestly I'm very surprised so how many
words you
know honestly you're so good good job I
probably know more but I just need to
remember I think I know a lot of uh
breakfast items
and yeah Hotel words yummy what's have
you ever tried a Italian
breakfast I mean I think I did it's
usually a ATI mhm
right and I don't know maybe orange
juice no probably coffee coffee coffee
coffee coffee coffee coffee coffee yeah
yeah it's got to be coffee but I really
love how much Italians love C because I
also love
qu yeah we we like caretto and
cappuccino for breakfast m i remember o
i remember on the day when I left uh
Venice I remember I got myself a piping
hot uh uh uh Jam not chocolate jam
cornetti it was so hot like the the the
jam inside was so hot maybe they just
made it you know it was yeah it was
fresh they was it was like heated up and
then I waited for my my little boat to
pick me up and everything was flooding
and I got my feet wet but my cornetti
was very yummy
yummy do you dip the cornetti into the
coffee yeah you do yeah H H I hear about
people doing that with like a hot
chocolate but coffee huh yeah it's like
it's like not prople coffee it's a
cappuccino no oh okay so with some milk
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah maybe you
wouldn't dip it into an
espresso and usually espresso is too
short to dip things
inside true oh my packet AR or so
M
please yummy I love
caretto are my favorite breakfast I
cannot miss I miss having Italian
breakfast I am since I'm here I just
thre it up keep the
breakfast oh do you remember the
cappuccino with cereals that I talked
about yeah No One Believes Me when I say
that it's it's a thing
though why the One Believes
Me it
works I need more Italian to defend
me ketti cross originally from Austra
what
really I think I love
coretto we
I'm not sure maybe chocolate I kind of
like ketto with chocolate but also cream
like costard
[Music]
cream also Jam is good I don't know I I
think the best ones are the the
the um the qua with the action
Nutella
yummy love your accent thank
you I hope you guys guys I hope ches are
learning a lot of things from today's
lesson everything is going to be on the
test yeah the test oh no yeah the
test sorry they just they delivered my
hellofresh package but like a day late
so it's probably not good anymore
because the all the all the cooling ice
probably already melted so my meat my
car is is
hey don't swearing my
class stop swearing my class oh my
God my meat
[Laughter]
dead huh it's okay I hope your M will be
okay maybe not maybe it's gone maybe not
it's okay I will make pineapple pizza
mhm enjoy your enjoy your pineapple
pizza okay I'm ready for the test oh you
want to you want to have a test already
okay oh I thought I was getting a test
you can get a
test okay let's do a recap of the things
we learned today okay okay okay don't
look at the
chat what about looking at my
notes no
[Applause]
no no not no T no
one yeah I know it's
difficult okay let's see it's going to
be easy what is this where let me just
get the picture again
sorry
in CA who that not not the ca yeah what
is is
this the
article mhm and
plal e
e yeah good
job this one easy easy easy okay next
[Music]
one what
about this ah CA
no is your final
[Music]
answera
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
what yeah
[Applause]
he didn't even ask me and I bring out
something that's wrong
[Music]
uh good job feels good man feels
good good job
kada okay and
now
[Music]
translation no not
first one by one hello how are
you is good
morning yeah but I want to say a nicer
word is so
short and so
yeah and then
szy
a difficult one difficult one
you
[Music]
it she's so
strong smart she's so smart thank good
job why why do you have the check mark
chatini to approve and
to where do you use that normally all
the time huh
wow they oh there this
[Laughter]
approv they can approve and not approve
things H you give them those rights huh
very nice of you they have no rights
they plushes but
um they can just Express their opinion
sometime oh okay yeah illusion of choice
wonderful I like it we have a similar
thing at kfp illusion of choice m
what what you what are you going to do
with your
chickens well you know the usual room
exists and um I I like to put them there
for some uh well torch a relaxing time
to re-evaluate what they really think of
life you know if uh K of fried Phoenix
maybe if kfp maybe gets some chatini to
visit uh and i' you can send me some
chatini who are badly behaving uh-huh
and and then it becomes KFC oh is that
any chatini yeah yeah yeah send me some
over if they if they really behave B you
better behave from now on we have an
agreement now we shaking yeah yeah
yeah
KFC kfp becomes KFC with
chatini it's
over yeah be careful chat very careful
if if Mama has enough of you and she's
bito for last time then you go you go to
usual room from W she will borrow she
will maybe rent some rooms yes yes okay
next next next question K the test is
not
over okay I have to say uh I am
[Music]
uh big
cats
um
uhhuh
uhhuh do I need do I
need do I need
La yes so no this is um so la and it's
the right okay it's Uno
or
okay this is without pink so I guess
it's just
[Music]
Grand yes it's correct it's actually
correct yeah um I was thinking like
sometime you can also
say but I think it both works so don't
work okay okay okay that works uh
Roosa
mhm um another thing I want to mention
uh about
un so
it's uh
a uh but um if you want to say like if
you put a
word that has like
um oh my God how it's called
um this uh
ah I see I see I see if it starts with a
a consant a consonant if it's start with
a cons I mhm yeah uh you can avoid the o
or e in the front and you just say
un instead
of okay yes yes yes yes understand but
if you have a if you have um a word that
starts with a Vel m
you want to say or for
example
um
anra
anatra anatra is uh
duck duck
okay
anra uh there is an extra rule I want to
add to this mhm
and it's that's a little bit more
complicated uh but if the word starts
with a
bubble and it's a femin it's a it's a
FAL mhm yeah you got to put these little
things at the um the apostrophe the
apostrophe at
[Music]
the yeah yeah yeah yeah likea
yes similar similar but you don't do
that if it's uh male M yeah I think I
remembered this long time ago somewhere
in my lessons I learned this before okay
so no apostrophe
no but
the wait huh wait H so eh it's because
it's because like you supposed to
sayra but like you remove a you just
remove put do you really use un with G
should it it's not un Uno at all no you
don't say uno uno it's
very it's like
Uno we never say
uno okay
so we don't really say uno but you say
Una Una is more
usedo
exactly un ca
unaa una you want to say una when it's
fale um but un if it's male usually ah
okay so it's un or un it it really
depends like now that I think about it h
yeah now that I think about I really I
don't actually know when you use
Uno I'm conf I'm confused a little bit
so it's okay like knowing your own
language uh grammar is sometimes more
difficult than knowing a different
language yeah like it really depends on
the word because now that I think about
it like a student you w't
say un
St you do say
student h
[Music]
it depends it's confusing actually yeah
I guess that's that's really something
you will get into when you learn it more
seriously actually pay attention to
this it's okay
yeah how
about yes perfect
[Music]
okay okay okay I think I'll study like
better like why we say un
and next for next time How f
is f because well it starts with an F so
and it's female
yes okay yeah I mean yeah I roughly
understand good job it's feeling you
just just got to get a feeling for it I
feel like I think there is an actual
rule for it if I remember but uh I think
I'll stud and the second letter of the
word matters
too somebody said maybe
[Music]
sto Uno if it begins with st or that I
feel like I heard that yeah when when I
learned it in school really s or Z or s
t and z s and z
oh mom makes sense so oh yeah so Uno St
because with st but what what Italian
word starts with
zet zanzara but it's feminine so it's
zanzara which is mosquito or Dino Dino
Uno Dino yeah you're right oh there we
go now we know the rule we figur it out
no but
likein Zino I say un
[Music]
I say unuk I didn't say
uno maybe unuk is correct
[Music]
unuk I don't know my own language I'm
sorry it's over no that's fine yeah
right Zina is feminine I'm stupid
maybe yeah it's okay yeah it's because
the English language confused you maybe
with English also I don't really speak
much Italian anymore nowadays
A then then we have to speak more
Italian together of course anytime you
want to
practice are you planning on ever doing
a Italian only
stream and n no I don't know
um I want to hear it just do Italian
ASMR please Italian ASMR please I'll
think about
it maybe I'll think about it it's anmr
sounds good but we'll
see see there like please please please
I
know it will be special it's something
only you can do I know oh I think I'll
think about
it okay and Alora and let me think let
me think about what else did we learn
today
[Music]
um we did a little bit of progress not
bad well you taught me egm but they're
very difficult you don't really expect
me to remember them by heart I don't
expect but I thought it was funny to to
teach you a little bit more but wait I
can maybe remember the meaning of each
yeah makes
sense like the the chicken one was when
something is so ridiculous that it could
even make a chicken laugh yeah and I
also picked one one because it it remind
me to
you I wonder why I'm a cat obviously I
don't know why I would remind you of a
chicken no never you definitely if I
remind you of a chicken then looking at
yourself you should remind yourself of a
chicken
too M makes sense I would say yeah of
course beautiful
chicken a pink Rosa Rosa po
Rosa okay let's see how to say uh I
like something something right I like
like something how you say I like me
mhm how you
say I you say uh I don't
like
no but you were very close very close
very close M I knew this before but I
forgot okay is just going to add n at
the start of the sentence
ah oh mhm something something I see I
see I see I think in German we do the
same but we add it kind of at the end
blah blah
blah
oh you put at the end we put at the
start okay non me P okay why don't you
make an example of things you like and
things you don't like hm
[Music]
how about
the what's the word for
SP p
m oh okay I teach you how to say I don't
like it much like yeah very much very
much so I
don't like very
much Chad is judging me for not liking
spinach but it's just like spinach on
its own and there's like a a food in
Austrian cooking where it's like a a
little like a little little dumplings
and in the dough there's some like
spinach in it which makes them green I
like those and they serve them with like
cheese
sauce yummy spinach dumplings I feel
like maybe I see something similar in
Italy before too oh yeah I think uh I I
mean I we we put spinach everywhere
honestly personally I love spinach to
them uh in with the meat and the
pizza no no not for me makes me want to
throw
up is me okay I don't like very much
[Music]
is
okay
me and then you
uh per
I
think or I mean I mean I don't
actually I'm not
super like
100% you say
either buto is more like
[Music]
I depending on the context I think but
it's like at all I don't like it at all
so you say I
don't like I don't like very much
like yeah you can use both it really
depends okay
mhm you can say both
[Music]
so
correct because spinach usually say
spach in Italian you say spinachi which
is plural you know you never say it
like one yeah so you want to say
n because it's
plural wait I'm going to pick this and
one
p no because this is
plural I should have used a word where I
can say something in singular
what else don't you like
mushroom that's also another thing we
usually
say PL
plural I think when I even when I say it
in English I will always say these
things in plural I don't like mushrooms
I don't like I think it's because in
general you don't like mushrooms not a
specific mushroom that Mak sense yeah I
think yeah that's probably just normal
to always say plural
m okay but okay then maybe how about not
food
oh n me P do you like the
rain I mean I kind of do like rain okay
let's pretend that you hate the rain how
about math I don't like math ah okay
Mathematica oh la
maatic wow that's so long do you guys
don't have a shorter version to say math
no so it's always
Mathematica Mathematica wasting time by
making it making it such a long
word
uh perfect Yi
do you like
Mathematica wait what was your what was
your least favorite subject in school
and your favorite
[Music]
subject let me
think that's surprising cuz you're a
creative person I feel like a lot of
creative people struggle with
mathematics I actually really enjoyed
math when I was at school because it
made me feel so good to solve problems
and equation and stuff like that it it
really made me feel like powerful you
know like oh my gosh this actually works
let's go and I was very happy yeah maybe
I would have felt that way too if I ever
got anything right but it was just
frustrating I could never at the moment
something Clicks in my brain and I
understand exactly how to solve the
problem it may me feel so powerful I
don't know I
like yeah makes sense um I don't
[Music]
like
maybe
I oh my God were you just good at
everything no I was bad at everything
that's the problem
oh I was B everything actually I was B
at everything but
math oh really
yeah like okay so in in Austria like we
also have of course our own language
German so were you bad at Italian
too no as a subject no not really I
think I was like very me because my
teacher used to ask us to write a lot of
of like stuff for Daya like um po not
really just poems but like actual
stories and yeah stories essays essays
yeah essays a lot of essays but I really
don't like writing essays what about
science and physics yeah physics I
didn't like physics that's that's one
subject I really didn't
like same same same I was bad at those
two I was bad at math science and
physics biology you like biology I love
biology yeah biology is fine yeah that's
fun it felt so felt kind of
simple H what
about uh do you did you have
geography I kind of had for like the
first few years of school and then we
didn't start we didn't study geography
again did you history I loved history m
i
orang the way the way the way my teacher
asked me to learn history was about
remember like she asked me to remember
every single
year by memory like the test was about
okay when that thing happened and when
this thing happened it made it so
boring and then like after school I
started to watch a lot of like history
channels and a lot
of yeah I started to watch a lot of
those kind of documentary and and then
after that I started to learn more about
history but I not really in the school I
really didn't like my
teacher yeah yeah okay it's like I mean
nothing against teachers they're just
trying their best but yeah if if you
don't Vibe with the teacher's way of
teaching things then no no matter if you
have
yeah it will be it will be difficult to
learn that's also why I liked
math you like the teacher the teacher
was great now that I remember probably
that's also why I liked MAF because she
was very nice with me and she
really like she was teaching in a way
that she made it funny to learn a was
she your favorite teacher in school yeah
she was my favorite teacher a she
wait in Italy do you have grades 1 to
five or 1 to
six one to 10 actually one to 10 yeah
one to 10 10 is the best I'm not getting
a repeat of that joke but uh one to 10
what yeah we do have one to 10 score the
best is 10 so 10 is 10 is the best is 10
oh best is 10 uh six is like
sufficient five is like you're in
trouble four is you're so bad three is
like you haven't even tried to study and
I never I've never seen someone getting
like two or
one yeah I mean what is the minimum
requirement to pass a Class A six six W
what about
you and for us like okay so in Austria
we have one to five and one is the best
five is the worst and as long as you
don't get a five you're usually fine oh
really yeah if you get like a five on
your
final uh like the thing you get the
certificate you get at the end of each
year if there's a five in there you I
think you don't pass yeah you don't pass
the year so you have to repeat the whole
year so for is safe M for is safe yeah
oh really that's good though yeah and I
think in Germany it's one to six and
with a five you can maybe still pass but
I I find it amazing that there's one to
six 1 to 10 I mean in Italy because
then like what's the if you already
don't pass with a five what's the point
of having 1 2 3 4 five so um cuz you say
minimum is six I think it counts on the
average
of everything but like as I mentioned
never seen someone getting an actual one
or two I've seen three I got some Tre
sometime oh but I you got some free too
I got a tree yeah where in what subject
French oh friend mhm I haven't oh oh
yeah you know that I actually
studed German as well oh how long how
much
was please I I'm am so
ashamed I said like how many years 3
years and three years yeah and it was so
bad what was your grade I was bad how
what was your grade like
five so it was it it was not something
you didn't really
pass
yeah it was bad yeah German is difficult
French too like you're suffering get
remember at some point I could speak a
little bit of German like a little bit
now I don't remember anything it's been
a few years but like well maybe we
exchange and next time I teach you
German be nice I like that I mean I
don't know I've already like taught a
lot of members German oh really uh yeah
it's been a while I don't like being the
teacher so much but we can do it again
we can
[Music]
students yeah because I can finally lean
back and let others do the preparation
cuz usually I always do the prep
work I hope it was good enough for
you yeah yeah yeah very good I love
talking
Italian next time we should talk in
Italian
only simple today oh next time I'll be
more tough oh God okay yeah I wouldn't
mind doing it again you know getting a
little bit deeper yeah I can do that
next time Italian only no no no no no
no oh I remember like in school like for
English it was fine when the teacher
would say that even
communication between teacher and
student has to be English too but in
Italiano we can we barely had any
knowledge a little bit at the time you
know I
remember like speaking a little bit in
Italian with you is going to make you
remind a few words and like it's going
to also learn make you learn new words
yeah I think so too I'll I guess I've
been paying dualingo money for like
years and I never use it so
no just automatic subscription renewal I
should use ding a little bit just you
don't have ding anymore you have panta
y green Al replaced by
Grand Rosa
bra yeah would you like to learn
something before we go like um something
like do you want to um ask me something
specific
or do you have anything in your mind
that you wanted to learn
today or we can also
start with the verbs like basic verbs
like uh to be and to
have that was awesome my lesson today
but I didn't want to push too
much wait um what wait what I wanted to
uh teach you uh the two verbs that to be
and to
have
yeah yeah let's go with that because I I
think I know them but please remind me
and of their
forms yeah so this is
present yeah
pre present mhm yes so to
be to be or not to be mhm m
[Music]
is MHM so in it we want to
be
e
mhm to
say to
ah what's that L is Lou or
Le is like Lou he or her
mhm Senpai no not
Senai not for me at
least
Lou
L
mhm Lou
is uh
he and let it her uh she sorry M mhm mhm
M and then we
have um
no
no which is
we oh yeah oh
yeah uhhuh uhhuh
uhhuh mm son it sounds familiar m
so e it's I two is
you there's probably no need for past
tense there's already too much yeah
probably we we keep the past tense next
time yeah no it's we boy it's you again
sorry it's a bit
messy L is Day Day
o
soundc yeah verbs are I think are the
most complicated thing in in
Italian yeah like the a is so Random the
a feels like what are you doing there
there's not even an S involved in this
okay let's try some sentence
okay okay
k k
is very cute
mhm and then we going to do another
one um he's more
cute is
[Music]
um a
teacher
uh and then we can do K
kfp
are um cooked
CA the kfp no
actually kfp are uh very
nice you're saved for today guys just
today and then another one can be uh
you are
uh you are
beautiful there you go huh let's
translate well well
well so should I say the name and not
like
she or should so you have to you have to
say the name this time because like we
have a she which is implied right yeah
so
k e
mhm MTO
Kina is male Karina good
job M Kar yeah perfect now I don't know
the word for Teacher actually do I uh I
can teach you um in that's a pretty long
word
in yeah I'm going to I'm okay there are
two ways to say
teacher oh there are alwayss multiple
ways to say a word
so either you
sayro yeah actually Maestro too you say
[Music]
Maestro or maista depending on the
gender or you say
[Music]
in in in my school we used to say uh
professor as well which is MM which is
probably the
the easiest one for you maybe to
remember which
is but I like
my or
[Music]
fun say pretty long Maestra is okay
mestra is okay Maestra is short and fun
MRA that sounds epic that sounds
actually prettyy epic I like it you can
call like
that so now
good he's so
good what about
kfp
kfp this time it's plural it's
loral
uh
V but wait wait uh in thinking in German
the order was
see day which one's day which one M
[Music]
mhm
is is
is you need
help yes okay so it's l because they are
L I'm looking in my notes chat not at
you
L Lao okay okay p no
yes M
nice we can translate nice with
brav
[Music]
bra okay okay okay okay and
then you're you're you are so we're
talking directly to one person right
yeah you talk to me okay to
say no Bella
okay
yeah no Bella Bella Bella sorry the way
the way right it's so weird cute
[Music]
okay nice
words ni W I will become the best best
Italian speaker of all life
English maybe the second ah okay yeah
probably more realistic realistically
speaking oh yeah Bonita Bonita
Bonita
Bonita somebody wrote Bonita what was
that Spanish I think Bonita is Spanish
espan no no no espan
itoo we need we need a Spanish to teach
Spanish to us I I I can I cannot speak
um Spanish I can I can understand a lot
of words and I can pick up a lot of like
context but um I'd say I can understand
like 70% of everything but I cannot say
a single word yeah I I can imagine yeah
cuz they're very similar words very
similar yes yay okay and then we made
sentences to
be to be or not to be to be or not to be
do you do are you going to memorize
those words for next time because we're
going to have a lot of sentence
for like you know to be it's very
important probably all right we're
serious okay yeah let's
go okay I'm ready I'll be there I'll
show up to class A that' be nice I can't
wait to teach you more thank you oh
thank you for teaching me Italiano
beautiful language of
am I'm happy that you like
it I really like
Italy I want to go to Italy again can
show you around that' be nice yeah show
me around a city I haven't been to cuz
I've been to a bunch now we can
definitely find something that you
haven't seen I think I've never been to
like Sicily
or
so those are some good places I would
say I'd love to go yes of course let's
go oh Milan yeah I don't think I've been
to Milan
either I've been to
Milan
yeah last year I went to Rome and this
year I went to Venice and
Remini oh nice Remini
nice yeah Mei is so like
[Laughter]
random oh and bolognia but not really I
was just at the airport what's your
impression from
riny it's cute and small and fun and uh
yeah I like all the like little I like
the restaurant strip like then you can
walk by and find a nice restaurant at
the atmosphere it's quite nice but I
mean I'm sure the south of Italy has
nicer beaches
[Music]
M yeah you like to the beach I love the
beach I love the beach I want to live on
the beach
y' can can you can you can you
drive
no can you
drive I can
drive I don't believe but no no no no I
I can drive but I don't
drive yeah you don't sound very um
confident what do you mean by that hey
you you know it I feel like we talked
about this before anyway you're just not
like my teacher is not reliable in the
car I see well we get the TX
okay yeah show me the nice beaches
because like all the all the like
popular places in Italy there's just so
many tourists and it just you know kind
of I know too crowded and it makes the
beaches not so nice anymore sadly yeah I
have a few places that we could go
around she is the car why are they
saying the car car because because I'm a
cats okay big cats means big car
[Music]
yeah you're a dork I'll tell you that
bring you
around became F1 are
Ferrari oh we have some I guess we have
some we have our countries we have some
good race car drivers oh you know M
Shuma I know
Shumaker yeah very popular
yeah ferari Ferrari well okay if you
don't do you have you don't have a car
right now right you don't have one so I
technically have one with my mom uh I
see well if it's not a Ferrari then I
don't want to drive in it oh okay it's
got to be a Ferrari my mom has a very
small car ah small Ferrari is is very
small car f is
expensive well come on L get me a nice
car and then we'll drive around Italy
ital yeah I can't I can bring you uh
with a bike do you like the bike like
biking is it a Ferrari bike no h we can
maybe we can share uh a
Ferrari no I don't want to waste on in
that car it's not wasted it's a Ferrari
I I I don't want to no I don't want to
waste my money enough no no ducatti
ducatti no those are expensive ah bike
ooh Italian bike yeah ooh bikes are fun
you know what I like I like
um yeah like uh Lamborghini no no no NOA
vesa I like vesa oh yeah vas are cute
they're cute I like vesa
okay I have to learn how to see I don't
have a license for anything but I have a
license let's go k oh okay so I'm on the
back I see yes being on the back of a
bike is very terrifying but also on the
front honestly okay the where I got to I
Will Learn I think I think driving a
vesa is like for an Italian is maybe
like how skiing is for an Austrian yeah
very popular it's like a national sport
that everybody knows yeah honestly so I
can probably trust you with that I I can
learn all right all right that sounds
fun okay we can buy a little cute besta
a pink one maybe a that be cute cute I
need to be I need to see
this nice oh okay so H I feel like we're
probably ending right so can you teach
me how to say I'm tired
or in your
Cas
because yeah I'm going to write for you
so every every single word has a female
version like every single like ad
adjective yes oh my
[Laughter]
God yeah it just sounds like I
stink let me let me
no let let me let me let me
[Music]
no means I am Eep ah you are
okay so
B
not yes good night I go sleep again have
a good e q thank you so much for joining
today's lesson you have been a good
student despite you wearing in my class
next time I won't forgive you um yeah
this is the last time if we do one
stream specifically where you teach me
Italian swear words I won't do
that we have a huge vocabulary but I
won't teach you any what if I teach you
German swear words then that's fine
sh yeah sh we exchange come
on no in
[Music]
my but German swearing is okay no
swearing in my class
K but you said CH s a moment ago because
I am
Italian h
that makes sense no I'm not sure about
this
logic yeah I hope you're going to have a
good rest I go eat as
well okay okay thank you so much now I'm
glad we had our first final finally our
first one-onone collab I was so I want
to say one note K I'm so happy that we
finally collabed together yeah said that
like when you girls debuted I it was so
I was so busy I'm sorry I was uh I was
in the pasta my hands were in the pasta
money and past no problem money exactly
honestly I was I was just very happy to
you know to to do anything with you I
hope we're going to we get to coll up
more we and and and we I hope we get to
learn moreal together ah see see see see
see mhm
see more more more more more please I
want to learn like swear
words okay maybe I can teach you one
swear word every every lesson oh okay
okay what's the swear word of today MDA
you already said that ah damn it no new
one you already wasted wasted your your
your SAR ticket
[Laughter]
she she's
misbehaving no she misbehaving a
bit anyway thank you everyone for
watching thank you kfp Andi for coming
here I hope you guys have fun with us
and thank you everyone I'll see you soon
[Music]
for e
n
[Music]