[Music]
l
sorry I moved my microphone
[Music]
like oh oh yeah right probably a bit
quiet it's fine
[Music]
wait I'll mute
myself oh I found The Sweet Spot I think
more or
less yeah it's just the
the static noises depending on where the
cable
sits
ah
hello hello
[Music]
hello the crunch of tree yeah yeah
taste good maybe for next I have a
feeling I already know what to do for
the next thumbnail 50 memberships Rama B
what's wrong thank
you opening
I 50 so
generous isn't that one membership costs
five
right no 250 wait how much is my
[Music]
membership
how 250 that's $250 us you crazy Ram B
thank you I never think about it that
way but I
should I should think about that more
often thank
you ram where are you in the chat say
something mama why what do people what
are they thinking when they do that
what's in the back of their mind tell me
I want to know more about the psychic
the psych the psych hey wait you golden
even what the
[\h__\h] are you more of a lurker because
like
what
what golden if you golden at this point
that means you're probably around since
more or less day one well you have to be
pretty much well thank
you it tell me let's do holot talk with
Rama
B what do people think when what's their
thought process when they send so many
memberships I want to
know yeah within the first two weeks of
whole life english's
existence yeah crazy hey see I'm waiting
for Rama B to write something else but I
guess I'm right with you being more of a
lurker cuz you don't want to communicate
with
me
[Music]
why they wrote God damn it it's hard to
hard to
see should change my YouTube chat to
four years a yeah you are Lear right I
knew it I knew it that's crazy like to
think about this there's there's people
who watch me for four years but and
maybe sometimes they send crazy gifts
but not even that often but when they do
they hit
hard and then then it's like wait wait
you're golden like what where have you
been
where have you
been um my
life oh
my where have you been all
my where have you
been my
[Music]
I want to do another
stream oh [\h__\h] sorry uh even though I I
don't know what's no I didn't drink
anything with
coffeine actually I would have loved to
have another nap even though I just woke
up three hours ago
three and a half hours ago excuse
me but I watched a little bit of uh the
archive to check the audio and I'm
surprised it didn't sound at all like
what it sounded to me in my ears I I
should have turned myself louder for you
guys normally I'm I'm it's like always
hard to hit the balance and I had this
feeling from my experience that
uh like on OBS it should just be pretty
much on par like the desktop audio and
the and the and my
microphone but no not this time it felt
like my my voice was kind of like behind
you know what I mean not not behind in
timing but behind
in volume so with the songs that were
like maybe piano or so that was fine but
the other songs that were a little bit
surprisingly hard to hear for you guys
huh yeah but the layering the layering I
don't know you can't do anything about
that noas I don't there's nothing where
you can change you have compression turn
off I
don't it's it's maybe it's not as strong
as it could be
um where do
I what is what is this
I no that's something
else you know you know I love my
compression I love my
compression let me check the Yamaha
software if there's anything there I'm
just checking if Quiet Sounds uh get
turned up louder there's definitely some
compression
there yeah the interface is not very
user friendly I really don't understand
this at
all ah FR oh I found it
I have flum in my
[Music]
Thro do you guys hear anything
changing is this another problem with
like I don't hear it the same way you do
[Music]
no a gas
Le anything sound different no right oh
man it's so oh
wait I don't
know I don't know what
the volume is
changing you don't know if I was just
doing it softer who knows oh aluda oh my
God see you're also I mean you're not as
much of a lurker as r b maybe but a
little bit of a little bit of a lurker
no actually not you're not really a
lurker you you quiet around happy
birthday
happy
birthday to
you happy
birthday in your
Sho happy
birthday in your pants to
Ala happy
birthday
to you
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah I realized I can turn on reverb And
Delay here at the same time that's
fun thank you guys for so being so so
being sweet yes uh English myth
speaker okay one day I will get to your
Super Chat and read it properly but that
day has not come yet
uh wait chat why are you not on the
screen you're late to your shift no wait
you are you're just not where you belong
to but that's okay we're going to turn
on full screen of the game come on come
on come
on I have headache I have a headache why
do I have a
headache maybe I should take a
medicine I should take medicine you
clocked in and then you clocked that's
so funny that's a funny that you say
that because I think I I I noed a new
trend of words maybe I should like you
know uh use it as like when I find a
word and then I learn it and because
it's like the thing now in on the
internet like skibby I found a word
seems kind of new like New Slang listen
listen do do do we have a little bit of
delay somehow so when somebody says
something blah blah blah blah and then
somebody says clock it exclamation mark
I think that's what I saw like someone
kind of say no what what what what not
talking about SK I'm talking what clock
it clock
it what
yeah it's not new but I just saw it for
the first time like but twice in a row
today and I'm like people say that now
when they want to approve like agree
with something
[Music]
but I don't hear people say that maybe
it has come back you know what I mean
maybe it has come back and you say you
say it's old but
maybe
maybe it is old but it came back maybe
even skibidi has been around since
Medieval Age you don't
know maybe it's just come back
now yes see first time I heard it too
why is this thing not showing on my game
capture card screen
H clock it but I don't really like the
sound of it to be honest so if you guys
are not saying if you guys are saying
that's not the trend right now then I
will gladly accept
that because uh it doesn't sound very
trendy to
me I'm in a good mood
but I don't know if for how
long I can't guarantee
anything it did we play like this last
time did I not do full screen wait no
maybe I didn't do full screen tell me
chat was it like this oh okay yeah cuz I
had the logo okay then
let's do it like
this where's my where's
the there it is ah shut up I
Elgato just
[Music]
man why is Elgato such a little [\h__\h]
elato so did you guys see Twitter what
happened on
Twitter did you
see oh I'm breaking my Elgato what the
hell did you see with
YouTube I feel like they replied because
my tweet had 25 I didn't even know it
had 25,000
likes um so they were like okay I guess
we can't ignore this man I guess we got
to ask them what is their
problem
H thanks YouTube I didn't even tag them
no I will say when you tag YouTube for
something they usually reply and often
also if you don't tag them they usually
write to you and then they'll be like oh
we can help you
um but I didn't need I mean I do but I I
can't be helped you can't fix this
situation
YouTube you can't fix
it it's not you it's me
YouTube oh wait elato elato is bitching
around give me a moment to
to grab it and shake it and choke it
into
[Music]
Behavior ah there we go I got
it ah wait I'm I think I'm going to get
a painkiller it's not that bad but
[Music]
what
did you hear
[Music]
me I just went into
my no yeah did you I just went into my
bedroom to get some pink colors and both
of my cats were were curled up I have to
say people always talk about cat loaves
but I think the best form of a cat is
not loaf loaf is pretty cute but I like
it when they're like a cinnamon
roll like and even then there's like
sometimes my
cats when they're rolled up especially
chunky wony I feel like she will have
this she'll she'll be a little bit more
like a snail than a cinnamon roll cuz
she will have some some volume on her
back and so it will be a mix of Loaf and
ball rain uh what ball and cinnamon roll
it's like a mix you know hello open open
up painkiller why are you not
open um H have I not used these before
Oh I thought I used them
before okay I'm so cute and now T wony I
found her oh like in so to say in but
more like on top of my laundry basket
because the laundry basket is full and
now she's just like on top of it which
looks kind of funny it's like that's not
really what she was hoping for
probably she probably wanted to be more
like hidden in
it but she's not hidden at
all mhm
M do your laundry yeah I should that's a
good sign the cat is like an indicator
ah the cat is like the thing in my
dishwasher like the thing that
floats you know what I
mean if the cat is like
visible very visible that's when you
really should do your your laundry if
she sticks out of the laundry
basket
[Music]
so if I see cat do laundry laundry alert
system
indicator
indicator ah man amen amen to cats man
amen and I planning on playing this game
today I was but now now I'm just
like let me change into a t-shirt
because this is too
hot don't worry I had a t-shirt prepared
right next to the desk cuz I knew I was
going to get
hot so I don't even have to leave the
room
yeah this is the
shirt the
shirt my whole
life wasn't so serious yet about
double-checking their English writing on
their official
merchandise because this was before
whole life
English no I wasn't toplet if anything I
was too
hot too too
too too too well
dressed okay
so I waited to play this I was getting
so impatient because I can't watch a
certain others you other YouTubers
videos on this game if I'm still behind
it's crazy how fast he catches up what
the [\h__\h] so we have to get ahead like
quite quite ahead de so that I don't
have to worry about well we play this
twice this
week oh twice that's right as always and
one more
[Music]
thing so I've been announcing the
members that are going to be in my live
and you may have
accurately um
H what Ian ah that one uh you may have
accurately um what's the
word
it what's the
word nah not predicted I mean whatever
you you may you may have
understood that uh I will have to do
more than
one uh uh
announcement per day
perhaps um if I want to announce all of
them because there's two row but fact of
the matter is I forgot to take proper
like introduction pictures with some of
them so some of them are just uh
like screenshots from the performance
itself
so some of them are groups right so
right now I don't I have like for this
one big group I don't have any like solo
one-on-one pictures with the members I
just have this group pick which will
spoil the whole group so it should be
fine if I'm not announcing one by one
each
time um but yeah so far I've announced
narissa and wiu nisu nerissa and ru wiu
yeah yeah yeah yeah just grab the
picture no it looks weird I don't know I
have a few good ones I'll post the good
ones first and then the biggest like
group spoilers I'll post those closer at
the
end yeah and maybe I'll post one after
the this stream I I'll probably have
to yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah no
no it makes no sense because like
ideally I'd still want to keep the group
a secret I don't mind spoiling the
guests but I don't want to spoil the
group you
know please check out my Twitter to be
on top of everything and now we play the
game oh yeah we were right uh before
jumping into this
thing awesome keep the rest a secret I
could keep some a secret but there's
definitely no point in keeping the top
row is secret so we will all just
pretend to be surprised each time I show
you a
member game audio might be
loud okie
dokie how about
[Music]
now let's go lemon Chan
um
h i I
um I I
[Music]
can oh I I can create an entrance
here stand back Zelda I've got to
thanks
Tre
thanks see morb that wasn't as bad as it
sounded for my throat don't worry oh
what is
this I can sense my friends here they're
trapped they're trapped in five areas to
be exact if we rescue them all I don't
think this was how it sounded before
more like this if we rescue them all we
can fix this
Rift oh yeah as per usual oh my God I
want to do this like Super Mario ball
jump
here why can't Z not do that W what a
loser okay let's go ride
[Music]
first oh never mind I guess I'm not
going right to this
place it's interesting
par oh there's there's one over there we
can just make a a bed Bridge
easy this is this really sucks like
having to go through all of that man did
they not
think did they not
think they certainly didn't
think when they made
that awful menu that's probably the only
critic
ism is that
W oh I can swim oh let's
go nice okay the Octo rocks
are in my way how are we going to tackle
them ah attack
B my face I don't want to because like
that's also not really
efficient yeah I'd prefer them to have
like a different system
tph that's okay yeah at least two lines
like one line of
enemies or and one line of normal
objects I don't know and then there
should be an option to get rid of
things
bruh but one could also like go into
this menu but that's too annoying that
that's also not
ideal yeah
anyway binding them to other buttons on
a d-pad would be nice still only have up
and right used
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah one could perhaps
see I'm not can't I have to really think
about what I'm looking
for oh oh no
what happened to you all right let's go
in here is this a whole dungeon
again is
it I don't remember how they usually do
things oh you want to do you want to not
like hello do you just ignore people
that's so nice of you okay I'll hurt
myself it didn't even
work it didn't even work the way I
intend
it all right got to get my own fish
no all right this way
[Music]
works my own fish is
better all
right um evil fish we have the same one
right but how about we send the
shark
yeah he's so aggressive he's so angry ah
bomb
[Music]
fish
yeah W elect this wait this right now
gives me Dave the diver Vibes I feel
like I'm in Dave the diver especially
because of the electric jelly fish man
those are the
worst I hated the electric jellyfish and
Dave the
diver h
do you want to be wait I already have
you why would I waste my time here to
fight
you the same one
right wait yeah okay they're immune to
their whatever I'm not going
to there's no
point um probably no point in finding
that one either that's just the the blue
one right no yeah you don't even get the
um you don't get to copy the shadow
monsters anyway
right what am I going to
[Music]
do yeah yeah okay what was the point of
this whole section
here for me to die it
[Music]
seems no
go no wa wait wait wait he what wait
wait wait wait
wait it seems like that was the point
here attack before I die in here oh my
god oh I I have
to back into the
water no no come
on okay oh I had to oh what now that
makes more sense good job little
boy I thought I could ignore it because
we already got some Souls down there in
this in this little section down there
so we got two threee yeah we already
have threee two in here and one
outside huh yeah I should
rest all
right so you know all uh yesterday was
my day off and I was like
procrastinating a
lot and then I did something that was
procrastinating but also at the same
time it wasn't so I think it balanced
itself out I decided a few days ago to
make everything like brighter the the
room that I have my streaming setup in
it gets pretty dark
need an extra lamp or so or a brighter
lamp but it gets pretty dark in general
and which is fine I don't mind that uh I
don't need it to be too bright in this
room that would probably be not good for
my eyes or so anyway I don't
know um not pitch dark but you
know yeah um and so I thought well
generally like I don't really like that
so many tables
like all tables are freaking black
always I want more interesting colors
but the interesting looking ones they're
usually pretty small so whatever I just
bought white leather mats that are
supposed to be used for uh your desk
anyway and because my desk is currently
two desks put together to shape an L to
shape like an L
table um I bought two of those m and
then um yeah so yesterday I cleaned my
whole table I was so much like random
like letters and
then bills and [\h__\h] on here and a
million other things and so I cleaned
everything I I decluttered the whole
thing
and uh then I
disconnected uh like my monitors and
stuff so I could reach under them and I
had to like basically like how to say
unscrew through like my microphone that
is like clamped to the table and do the
same thing for like my phone holder I
have another clamp for that and this and
that it was it was quite an Endeavor
yeah so that I could empty the whole
table and then nicely lay the new Lea
mats on top so that I could cover the
whole
table yeah and I did
that uh
[Music]
I did that ah I did that and then it
looked really nice yeah especially now I
I have the the white mixer from
mint yeah the Yamaha ag8 in white it
looks so nice and now I have some
brighter key caps that brighten it up as
well and yeah everything looks quite
nice now you know my PC case is also
white remember and my switch dock is
kind of white it has like a um Animal
Crossing case thingy that's like pretty
white with some icons on
it yeah so it's getting brighter and
holy moly this changed a lot and then I
had to rearrange a few cables and stuff
so I I cut some cable binders because
otherwise first of all I wouldn't have
been able to
reach uh like yeah I I wouldn't have
been able to do some things here if I
didn't cut some cable
binders um and then and then and then
I uh oh yeah because things were in
cable binders I didn't want
to like for example there was this one
time after my cables got binded I wanted
to switch the microphone cable to test
out if some issue was due to the cable
so then I had like one unplugged
microphone cable stuck that still
hanging there in the cable binders
because I didn't want to cut the whole
cable
binder right and I had the same issue
with another one or two cables that were
just hanging
there yeah no I didn't I did not cut
into a cable no no no no I'm just saying
like I cleaned that mess out as well
yeah and and then I I re arranged some
things on my table and also I finally
plugged in things the right way like
somehow
my what's it what's the razor headphone
USB dock it just wasn't working because
it wasn't plugged in I
guess I don't know but now it has a spot
where it works and I turned on like a PC
and monitor light again like a monitor
it's like a lamp that hangs on the the
monitor but I didn't feel really feel
like I wanted the light above the
monitor where it's intended to be put I
wanted it to turn the other way against
the wall because that area was so dark
anyway so now it's lighting up the wall
on the height of my monitor and right
above is my YouTube play
buttons hung up on the wall and now
they're also being kind of lit up which
looks really
cool yeah
e o we
W wait oh I I wasn't sure what you meant
what that meant you mean this game oh
okay you beat it well nice you can help
me e o because in German we say not W
but B which is so much faster so much
more
efficient and no lot what what do you
mean apps I always do light mode on apps
you usually but uh yeah but my setup is
more light mode now you might want to
say it that way um um so anyway I'm
really proud that I like did it because
now it looks so clean and nice and
decluttered and everything and more
light and it looks nice and then in
connection to that I thought you guys
might want to
know my USB issue has been resolved not
yesterday but like a couple days ago uh
before the myth collab I think I did
that I did that
alone because I always had a
feeling um that it might be from my
cintique
because like
some like whenever I would draw on my
cinti it would also always be really
weird like weirdly disconnecting itself
and and then the the my my pen would
work on it anymore and it would always
throw me back to the other monitor
without the monitor turning itself off
though the CTI did never turn itself off
but it just like kind of disconnected my
pen and I thought that was weird for a
while um but I had a feeling this was
kind of being
weird um but even when I like you know
troubleshooted during the stream and
like disconnected and and reconnected
the cables it didn't fix the problem and
even when I wouldn't move anything I
swear when I was just like sitting there
in silence not moving anything it would
still randomly randomly start doing that
so that that really makes you wonder
like what is going on um but then I uh I
tried troubleshooting it properly and I
I um installed a program that shows me
all the disconnects and connects of the
USB but that was
confusing
because it showed all kinds of different
ones
it wasn't very clear to
me it was not very clear not as clear as
I was
hoping um like it would show me the
slots uh named uh where what
disconnected and some things would point
to
cintique Wacom tablet but some things
wouldn't so I was like
H but then I would again I would try
like disconnecting the cable from the
antique Wacom tablet uh and connecting
them and moving the Wacom around cuz
it's on this like arm mounted arm and it
wouldn't really fix it and then I
figured you know
what
the
um
RBF cable binded my setup a while
ago and the cables for the
cintique he bound them around the
cintique boom arm or so however you call
these like mounting
arms and it looked to
me like it was very tight and
restricting so I thought well this looks
nice but let's cut the cable binders and
then I saw the cable binders made a
little dent on one of the threee cables
there's threee cables connected to the
cinti
going down to the PC and when I cut the
cable binders there were several ones
and there was a little dent on the cable
on one of them at least that was very
visible
and yeah just generally the probably the
tightness and the Restriction of how it
was so
restricted was probably an issue because
immediately after I undid the cable
binders the problem was gone
[Music]
uh so yeah I fixed it but the solution
was again quite a simple
one oh yeah do I have to go over there
or just up I wonder I'll go up for
now I just wanted to tell you that I
fixed it
yeah many cable binders had to be
sacrificed
I didn't have to replace anything
yeah yeah I figured it out y now I don't
have to hear that [\h__\h] anymore and now
when I draw on my cintiq now the thing
with the pen stopping to work
also fixed fixed fixed fixed
[Music]
fixed I did
it no oh I want draw more because of
that no shut
up there he
is he'll go back to normal just like the
others if we can fix this
Rift I believe so too our Studies have
shown that all right we got five
yippee we found all my friends in this
area now we can M this
Rift you think it's not easy huh
tree no no guys just just just
acknowledge that I fixed it don't make
this more into something that it
isn't thank you acknowledge please and
acknowledge that I I made my setup so
pretty it's so clean right now and
because of the leather mats being so
clean and so pretty
um I brought out some coasters that I
normally don't use because I never use
coasters shame on me but now I put
things on coasters on this table so that
it won't leave a mark on the lever mats
I wonder if it would it probably would
even though these are made for desks I
don't know so yeah yeah it's super
refreshing it really is refreshing and
it's like satisfying and now I want to
do more um I want to I want to make
things brighter I wish my monitors were
all white I don't know I don't want to
replace all of
them just to make everything wider but I
kind of want
to but even if I replace the monitors
then I still have the cintique which is
black
so I think nowadays there there's a
white scentique maybe or there's at
least different brands that make white
ones yeah yeah I was thinking about it
too if I if there's any like
decals at least for I was thinking about
that for something
else but I don't think there's there's
probably no decal specifically for these
monitors but can I paint
them spray paint is there specific paint
that could work for this thanks for the
membership welcome is there specific
paints Maybe
but I could imagine that for the
cintique there might be some kind of
decal as you call
it any plastic
paint I'm not good at painting I mean
like like painting things where you
don't want to go over a border like on
on in in in uh programs on the C inside
you know digital art then I can do it
but IRL
difficult I just don't have a good
reason to replace my monitors they're
working so I I want to be like cuz we
live in an economy and and the society
think of the economy I can't just
replace these monitors just because I
want them to be different color
not in this
economy that would be that would be so
wasteful unless I sell my old monitors
maybe
secondhand yeah see I could do that and
not not just throwing them away right so
I could do that but anyway my friend ja
the powers with me
Yi oh it's not very
much but thank you did change color it
looks
so what's that looks different looks
[Music]
moldy sorry I'm yapping so much today we
have we have not made any progress so
far not really at
least I got to eat it be before it grow
mold
[Music]
I Tred off
wa last
night wait what the hell was that it was
it was weird I was sick she was
streaming I was in the same room kind of
talking and then she turned like she
turned on like a webcam
and just [\h__\h] turned it on me close
up and I'm like no wait no no what the
[\h__\h] I'm I'm sick first of all I look
like [\h__\h] why are you exposing me like
this way I was screaming when she just
wouldn't stop what wa what was your
issue yeah it was weird
um weird we were going to go fly
somewhere but to different destinations
I think but we both had to go to the
airport so she got us a car and she had
the chaur put my luggage in and and her
luggage in and so on and then she sat in
there and somehow there was another
person I don't know who but then she
said sorry W there's no space for you
we'll bring your luggage to the airport
but you have to get there on your own
and I was like wait a what why what come
on like surely there's space in there
still for me like what about this seat
in the front next to the
driver and then the driver you know came
out and helped me like get some space in
the car but it felt like waya just did
not want me to be with her in the
car yeah this is all a
[Laughter]
dream dream
way kind of
mean yeah but no I still liked her it
was
weird anyway
swallowed up by a rift my goodness dread
don't be so precious now Frank is
Haring who's calling who precious you
with your friendly
gills Str what's wrong with my papa
hey what's wrong with
you it's like he's stuck back in there
then I will unstick him how how you
going to do
that he has one of the p and Ste things
[Music]
a a
cute that's it that's it it couldn't
have played like 2 seconds more more
Mama Mia that's a that's a cheap
performance did that
help
I'm I'm okay now thanks to
you
Yi well the music of the SE allers
frantic thoughts into a deep
[Music]
calb that performance Good As It Gets
huh I know
right Chief K
[Music]
Chief what's wrong
darling it's Lord dabble jabble he's in
the Door Co huh right then let's
go dabble
jabble hey wait for
me and
me MH me
yeah who are you
anyway I am Zelda the princess of this
Kingdom okay at least
he I know I've heard a name at least he
reacts to it kind of knowing the
name but still not acknowledging that oh
oh you must be the princess oh my God an
honor it is to me what's what's wrong
with these
guys h
H
Kar don't give me a new name that I'm
never going to
use well Zelda I owe you a big thanks
but that's got to late I need to catch
up with Sashi Kush I owe her a big time
too sing
around he's of higher rank than
you is I mean
is he though because like so
Hyrule is the whole Kingdom right and
then the Zora Kingdom Etc isn't aren't
they Under the Umbrella of the hyru
[Music]
Kingdom actually I'm interested to hear
the answer let me know let me
know
correct I think so
too
H are I think so seems fractur py is
just a castle on his home yeah but
that's like the main like the capital of
the Kingdom but they still they still uh
own not own but like rule over the all
of the you know right it differs
depending on the setting well but then
even then they would still know me I
would assume uh just by being close to
the hyro kingdom which seems to be the
center if anything of these King
kingdoms if there are more
kingdoms gudo are definitely their own
Nation yeah but they should still know
the name like normally you know the name
of the royalties from your neighbor
kingdoms if you are also a queen or what
whatever at least anyway there they go
again that music she played was pretty
nice she performs better by herself
[Music]
anywayi where are we
going I guess I'm just going to go to
the
okay from the seedor
ah oh here I can can't do the thing that
I did in the rift are you kidding
[Music]
me I don't think I have this one yet
let's go get it oh wait great it's in a
position where I can't grab it are you
kidding
[Music]
me how the hell do I get out of this
water
come on
[Music]
now did I go into this cave before
surely I
did no I didn't
[Music]
easy evidently not I like how you say
that could have made bed stairs yeah but
stupid huge brain
smart so
[Music]
smart
Okay the same but uh not quite can we
jump oh oh okay oh okay oh okay oh easy
easy
easy little bit messy on my behalf but
it worked
out mhm
[Music]
uh now we don't get to be in the
water
uh
wait
[Music]
oh I can't reach it from there
uh okay we need to keep it on that
height because I don't think we can get
it back up if it's down there
once but I still can't reach it
oh
ha there we
go little bit weird but
okay 100 yo we never had a silver rupe
before hey
[Music]
nice we need a lot of money in this game
I
think okay cool cool cool
cool well
then if I didn't go there yet maybe I
should explore a little bit here before
I run away again have I have I really
looked at
everything besides that cave Maybe not
maybe I
[Music]
didn't did I miss anything else
stupid octo wait do you call them octar
Roo in English I
forgot Golds are 200
wow where do I
get is that the one I killed before or
what did it just fall down finally oh I
did in my absence I almost got
[Music]
scammed
okay how do I get out of here let's just
teleport um how about going here and
then going further down from there
have you guys been playing this game are
you behind me or uh in front of
me how is it
going ahead behind past me cleared it
already neighor didn't play ahead so I
can watch you very
good in front pretty far I'm just enough
ahead
okay okay just watching me oh that's
fine too if you don't plan on playing
this game
ever I personally think it's a mistake
but as long as you watch me I cannot
complain # vul # yolk after all
[Music]
did I see
everything I hope
so
oh that
guy that guy I don't recognize him
uh don't think I talk to that guy let me
fight this
ugly ass spider I don't know we what man
having so much Choice also gives you
this issue where you think too hard you
don't have to think so hard but like too
[Music]
much just counter it with the same
ones
ow what the hell which one mine that's
not mine right cuz I can okay
good now let me focus
on getting up
[Music]
there
yooo hello for you
hey he hey and hello Acorn ging give it
a go a fun snag and fun your bag
Gathering acorns is never a drag L saai
is this you in the game
all you got to do is pick up the acorns
that I scatter about if you're fast
you'll even get a prize you'll get one
try for 10 rupes what do you
say uh sure
okay mini
[Music]
game okay six acorns in 40
seconds all right all right all right
all right all right all right uh 40
seconds that is that a lot
or a
[Music]
little
wait wait uh I need to get up
[Music]
there wait for me wait wait for me wait
for me wait for me I'm going to die ah
what it's not over wait wait wait five
out
[Music]
six wait go I see one
okay holy [\h__\h] I made
it like
yo what 35 seconds are you sure that was
literally on the beep oh was it not was
the beep just when I wait did I still
have 4 seconds I thought that was the 40
of
[Music]
seconds do you get anything better from
this oh yeah hey anything that's worth
it
though cuz I don't know if I want to do
it again is this worth it
yeah that was just the winning sound and
I thought that was the it's Times Up
Sound his
[Music]
whistle yeah I should
heal someh worth it but not all the time
[Music]
you guys not know try exploring up here
might be something
around up here was I not here
before I'm walking on water
[Music]
genius
build what look I've been here
before I
haven't thinking of some other place
that was
similar if you're in a bed trying to
heal a go I I know I know but that's
like too much of a b too
much oh
Riv horses did I get Riv horses before I
don't think
so see
[Music]
horses I talk to
you I think
so
[Music]
okay Landing up with this guy ah the
river
[Music]
hores a a seahorse movie that sounds so
cruel and not really
tasy
E I mean I can do it
but that's so
[Music]
close yeah sure only for them that's
tasty but not for me I'll try it though
there they
are
[Music]
easy what can you make out of
that okay it looks
adorable rapid smovie oh probably faster
swimming huh yeah swim faster than
usual going to make
these potato juice I've heard is a
thing it is climbing
smoothie don't know if I'll ever use
that but it's just for the sake of
making more that we haven't made yet
have made this
before have I have can you make a but
like pure butter smoothie is that
something the salt Sal I'll
just ew butter butter and
butter W salted radiant smoothie W with
the salt on top that's like a cocktail
that's what they do for the
cocktails oh
reort a serving scul the special spy
glass makes Smooth ingredients and
monster Stones appear a little more
often when you break objects or defeat
[Music]
monsters
yippe mhm you want me to make more I
know I know I know oh interesting what
do we have on right
now the swim speed up M I think for now
I'll still wear those until I'm not in
this area
anymore how about
that okay now let's same for
the cave yeah cuz
they I would think they are
there but maybe I misunderstood I'm not
sure sometimes the main
quest as we had the same in the gudo
village a gudo place uh it will it will
show a place where you don't have to go
anymore why I don't understand c not
cave is that not the same thing
[Music]
are these guys protecting something
there can I squash
[Music]
them maybe
not call you
Liara I'm Ki not Liara
[Music]
oh little child
here
[Music]
this doesn't really look like it would
do anything but
okay oh dable dable the island of the
East he went towards the island of the
East
oh is it here I kind of went here
like without knowing okay but
nice that was TR wasn't it what's he
groaning
about oh
no what's happening to
him I need a bird
because this other bird is bullying me
oh well now he gave
up let's see let's talk about the
pecking order my friend you know who
you're messing with you're messing with
a mighty mythical Phoenix yeah people
call me a chicken but they forget well
you're welcome to underestimate
me [\h__\h] around and find out yeah that's
how it goes that's how it goes my
[Music]
friend maybe I'm going the wrong way but
I want to
explore oh
stamp let's
go stamp the first stamp of the new
page low budget stamp
card I'm an Elvin princess right now I'm
I am a phoenix playing pretending to be
an Al princess I'm sor sad to
say honestly but is
the but I am proud to be a
phoenix need to
[Music]
heavy he seems
fine are you again yeah you can kind of
tell we're in the real Jam
here my son and see they're both trapped
in this cave my son wondered often I
just come here to find him when Double
Trouble stor Chief was nearby during the
confusion she sensed my son was in the
cave she DED inside to make sure she was
he was safe and wh bam thank you ma'am
this pile of rubble fell here smack dab
in front of the
cave what am I to do don't worry keep
Cal I've got this never met a pile of
rocks I couldn't
move you come on and play
is your set and done maybe there's
another waiting sight I'll figure it
out don't
[Music]
worry oh wait there's a on the map you
can see yeah yeah yeah the other
entrance he could go through here too if
he knew about it he's a fish
did you drink a Red B I
didn't I did not and I had a feeling
that I would be too
tired but I'm fine for
[Music]
now
thankfully it's so dark should I bring
my my angler fish and control
him
wonderful uh-oh
yeah yeah yeah it's so good to
like okay that didn't go perfectly but
if you hold him you
know hold them hold
them okay it doesn't work so go of these
fish but oh God I'm
dying but you can control him better
it's ah I I I why did I wake this
fish but I've been here
well I've been here
before what the
hell that's where I got the angler fish
anyway wait before no before you talk to
me let me
sleep yeah I entered the other way I
guess it wasn't it wasn't open uh it
wasn't closed
yet those
um those stones are new I
guess it's okay everything's going to be
fine help is surely on the
way you
promise I'm right
here e the Highland did you truly manage
to swim for all those monsters to reach
us quite a capable one aren't you we'd
hope to get out for
here can't take the child into those
Waters we need another means of
[Music]
Escape just let me sleep first Mama
Mia they don't know how to appreciate a
hero and let them do their thing
[Music]
it's so hard to fake snoring can't
believe that people actually just do
this automatically when they
sleep I guess I also rarely do it but
like if I suffer just trying to recreate
that sound
choking how are people doing this on
their own when they
sleep how does the the human body
just let people go through that that's
it doesn't seem
natural let me eat the
[Music]
chocolate cuz I mean the human body
forces us to brief automatically right
so it's it's generally smart enough to
do things that don't kill
us but then why does it make
us
[Music]
snore shut up I'm talking about other
humans we are just you you are just
chicken
yeah autopilot breathing not optimized
it's not
[Music]
perfect after all these years how long
has Humanity
existed
H and we need a patch it's so bad why is
nobody updating our system their
system 500
100 at least 4
[Music]
you guys don't seem so smart after
all wow
okay but no surprise you guys are
chickens
y now will this experience make them
think like oh my God maybe we should
work
together because for whatever reason
this this is like an emotional moment
just paying you back for saving my
friend oh
[\h__\h] I feel the Laugh In The Air rightel
now when did you get here
you're right son look we can easily go
outside
now huh you're safe child there's
nothing to be afraid
of there's nothing to be afraid of sorry
I forgot how she talks for a moment the
poor kid frow it to the face to scared
for
words oh let's go
oh that was
sick good trumpet M do I love the do
D now they both hurt each other play
solo and realize how how much of a good
effect they can have on other
[Music]
fish pure oomph
it's got that
oomph oh okay
wait I want to read that but the
chocolate is just so
[Music]
good I'll admit it drag that performance
was
magnificent who could have guessed that
your music could help one of my
people don't forget you helped one of
mine too just repaying a dep I didn't
get a chance to say but the way you
played was great and honor to hear
it oh my God I'm feeling
butterflies maybe there's some kind of
parasite inside of me we feish get a lot
of parasites don't
we I I can I can um
I don't know man I'm not going to say
[Laughter]
anything um every now and then dread huh
how about we put our scrabbles aside and
help each other
out I was about the say the same
[Music]
thing then we're agreed and when you and
I work together we're strong tide that
LE all well
hot what what Zelda what why are you
ruining the
moment what's that you need us to
perform at Lord jabu jabu St your name
was J yes we're in deped to you but we
must focus on finding Lord jabu
jabu tell might have the right idea
don't going to his thing oh really I saw
L jble jable swing back nor while wait
why why he talk like that now I saw L
dle dle swiming back North while you
were stuck in here could be that he's
gotten tired out of out after his
Rampage and gone back to his D that
would make sense Lord chuju r moves
around this much H we will grant you a
request let's be on our way immediately
we will meet you at Lord Jau jabu
stand wonderful finally we're doing the
thing that brings me f ahead in the
story it's a s an accent at least I'm
trying to do
one do you like it honey do you like it
honey H honey darling
darling thank you for saing my
boy oh
my oh my
[Music]
all
righty where is the
den do they want me to go here again or
is it was it then this one is that what
they mean probably right
nor shut
up why you ride it like that what's your
problems what are you trying to
say what are you trying to say what you
trying to say that's how the dwarf's
talk in rings of power what are you
trying to say
say what are you trying to
say what accent is that some scsh accent
that's how the
[Music]
new episode is it out already I it's not
what was the date there's like a the
last episode I'm waiting for it too
now I already said I didn't drink an
energy drink today wait I think I'm in
the right I I think I'm in the wrong
place what the
hell Boozled maybe we got to go here
after all
guess that's what they meant of D I got
to go to the
Dan that's cool side quest in the
village yeah
later what what's all that about what is
it
about uh wait side
[Music]
quest oh wait the flying
tile ah and G we can give that
back wait what you mean one that I
have't accepted said
yet maybe that's what you
mean eight episod is
out stream cancelled got to go watch oh
my
God oh
God the seventh episode was
crazy like holy
[\h__\h] I I'm excited for the this next
episode oh my God oh my God
on hello who else is watching it can you
confirm episode 7 was
crazy oh my
God they put all the budget in episode
seven surely there's some budget in the
eighth episode as
well it was super thank you yeah yeah
thank
you man that
crazy a great crazy [\h__\h] man I'm not
going to spoil but woo yeah see people
are saying second season is better right
second season really ramped stuff up
there you go guys give it a chance come
on it's really good mhm yeah K my boy he
feels more like a dwarf
like the way he acts his personality and
his face honestly to me gives me dwarf
or Hobbit actually not not I didn't mean
dwarf I mean
Hobbit his face gives me Hobbit
face it's not a bad
thing it just didn't quite give me um
it's combined with the personality it
didn't quite give
me you know he reminds me of
billbo both because of his face and his
personality
could I just talk myself
hey hobit cold you're right thank
you I like the repercussions of
everything it was
insane the moment oh okay I'm going to
try to say this without spoilering just
being vague but you guys the ones who
watched episode 7 the
moment where uh Kell brimo comes back
in with the
guards and then they surround him and
then that happens I was
like oh [\h__\h] oh they're so [\h__\h] what
holy [\h__\h] you know what I
mean yeah you know what I mean
right it's not a huge spoiler at all no
no no no no no no
no there's a lot of stuff that happened
in that episode but that moment was
rough like in a good
way
I I mean
I
yeah I wonder will in rings of power I
will probably learn
how Sauron goes from human
form or like properly bodily form into a
ball will I learn that in this
show judging by the the progress of the
story no but they have two more seasons
planned that's way later
I
did in the prologue of the
movies the IE finger it's only from the
movies what are you saying you're saying
it wasn't in the
book he's still person up until is
defeat by Isel ah that isur battle that
was in the prologue I remember that yeah
yeah yeah but how do they make him into
ball
in the book he's not an
eyeball
H the eye was justos to
moving what in so in the books what is
he just a spirit that's like all over
the place or does he still have a
humanish
form it's a metaphor oh because he's
watching over everything but does he
have a body
though or is he just like woo everywhere
like God
I really gotta read the
books you never see him in the book well
that that's because there's no pictures
it's not a picture book
bro might have a human because he
tortured golum golum said he saw saon
with four fingers
only interesting allegedly met him well
we can't believe what the hell Golem
says oh my God that's s
run oh Jambu Jambo did return
here you've got to get for the store
right we normally perform here to open
the way but it's not so simple
now uh one of the altars upon which we
perform is broken likely by Lord Jau Jau
we can't play together until it's
repaired
and both got Rubble on
them chill out guys oh this one I can't
ah I bring
it oh where are the others there's one
in the water is
there uh well well
that's can I solve that easily yeah yeah
ah okay I thought I'd have to do some
silly tricks
here but that's
fun lets him perceive sour in ways
others
can maybe yeah they even plan to have sa
show up in the movies in the final
battle but it was scrap
what well you know the thing is though
that I I I I thought
but like because I thought sour was only
ball in the movies I thought when I saw
the ball of
numor they probably have a proper name
for the balls that I
forgot I was like H are these balls
inherently evil or yeah the
paner is it what's what's up with the
Palante they're from elves right elves
make the Palante
[Music]
but so Sauron became a pantea right in
the movies at least so what does this
mean is what I was
thinking for the Unseen realm wow movie
team was right though having a physical
s in last battle would have been
lame I guess so like suddenly bringing
him in would have been weird
maybe sour used a palum
tier he has one
oh Saron just had a you mean
Saron I got to rewatch no I don't have
to I watched it plenty of
[Music]
times I'm fighting the troll in the
black gate that was supposed to be
Sauron oh I don't remember the fight but
interesting cell brimo is in the shadow
of mortar game
oh now I want to play
it now I want to play
it no know it's like a peak of human
development
G and aror were bigger
stronger okay perform come
on been yapping too much need to make
progress
oh it's going to be good this going to
be
good oh they're performing to one person
just like me and the past depressing
oo
ooh
[Music]
oo that's so good
more
M that's really good more more the
trumpet was so good I know it's not a
trumpet
but why sound so
[Music]
different
fun well you weren't half bad
[Music]
I playing in time with each other I
don't get it they played together last
time too we changed now there they've
got the hots for each
other there is some kind of chemistry
going on there and it's not the kind of
chemistry you learn at school my
friends I'd like to apologize I behave
terribly I hope you can forgive me
Kara I feel the same sorry for
[Music]
everything we didn't mean to hold you up
that the door is now
open of course I sh them I thank the
Lord if there would be um
uh like a a continuation of the story I
think they would make the lore so that
they those two have babies
[Music]
100% we never have gotten this far
without you we only big time let's go in
to see Lord T tble yeah together I don't
know if you guys should really come with
me I probably should go along hey
wait big mistake Pro
probably we ask you that you return to
what our friends have every to
us oh I have an idea playing
music yeah do
it uhoh you're going to make him mad
probably
now he's still angry that doesn't make
sense something's a little off here huh
a little things have been a lot off ever
since she started acting
vies the way that big fish looks Sala
it's got to be another impostor Among
Us
amongus now you mention it that would
explain everything who said anything
about
Theus that round thing next toing that
she can't see it but he can oh
[Music]
I have no idea who you're talking about
but well I'll take your word for it
that's only as fank face that you can't
mess with the Dora and I bet giving it a
good fuming and trumpeting will fix all
your problems
too I find plant red let's all dive on
in there
yeah for real you guys going to join
me oh really
I'm time to fill lest fish
no of course you guys going to be
[Music]
useless cut off by an invisible wall
once
again I can make an entrance into the
rift directly behind that big fation but
only specifically there and nowhere else
because that's what's going to be the
biggest isue so that you have as many
problems as possible that's more
interesting for the game you know so
first get the fish out of the
way all right oh my God what is all of
that that you have just spawned shall I
spawn some interesting things too should
I do my PE
hat my PE hat can reach these M right oh
wo whoo whoo are you eating the boat or
what no oh he's he's eating the dead
fish oh no
that's
concerning now go for the big fish can
we go for the big one
Sharky oh [\h__\h] too slow what was I
supposed to do there I want to should I
go into the fish maybe and then attack
him from inside I wonder if that's
a that seems awfully long I feel like
maybe that is what they want me to do
what do you think
guys I'll throw a bomb fish in that's so
smart yeah
ah but before I throw bombfish let's
throw Chompy wpy one more time oh Chompy
Wy is going for the
big oh I have no link energy by the way
that's not very
good can i h i can only throw in once
yeah okay that work o now I get some
link energy oh wait
[Music]
oh what what what was that what was that
what do that mean ah ah
ah he's spewing it out [\h__\h]
uh okay ow
chaos look at
him it looks so funny
cute
funny
very oh wait
uh like oh yeah oh wa I forgot sorry I
was I'm going to be so slow
[Music]
wait no no no no damn it
yeah I'll be ready I'll be ready this
time
sure
yay my shot is doing me
f let's let's get closer
[Music]
oh that's
it nice no second
pH h no no second
face well that was I guess not not a
dungeon boss so this is
[Music]
fine that was almost a Tim what's his
name Tim Taylor Tim Allen
almost at Tim Allen
reaction yeah yeah yeah good fight
though but pretty like typical kind of
gimmick that you see in a lot of Zelda
and other games throwing a bomb into a
sucking big thing yeah B that was
terrifying know what I'm sorry sorry for
all of
this P I'm sorry too RMA all this
because you RMA RMA
[Music]
Lima all this because you left my to my
defense seeing you safe brings me great
joy think nothing of
it you guys are the reason for me even
thinking about anything like that
without you guys I would not like even
understand understand what ligma is all
about it's your fault you guys have
poisoned me this culture has poisoned
me
Ro it works quite
[Music]
well uh wait who's talking who's Inova
again hey m look like you and cush patch
things
up boy you missed a lot didn't you we
ended up helping each other out H we
couldn't have done it without Zelda
[Music]
here
M it's amazing where go oh yeah
delightful how fortunate that we were
gulped down by Lord Jambo jumo are you
saying that ironically bro
but if this little Jaba Jaba was the
Imposter where in this world is the real
one inside still let's
go water temple question
mark let go let me go let me go in let
me go in let me
go let's go guys yippe
why am I so excited what's wrong with
me yeah yeah I know you can create an
entrance here you told me before the
fight very
clearly usually the hardest Temple let's
see about
it I'm in a good mood today maybe
because I had a day off yesterday should
give myself more days
off I've been watching a lot of Sims
videos videos yesterday and today
kind of have this urge to play Sims but
I genuine genuinely don't
think that I
can you know play it as confidently as I
used to as I told you
before oh bubble K bubble bubble bubble
K is that like are those things up there
can I pick them
up
Wonder just do it no should just play it
chill what do you think about Enzo Eno
actually is coming out soon like at the
end of this year right and I uh watched
a video about the character creation and
wow you know what I think I will play it
I think I previously said that I'm not
that interested but I'm kind of
interested now just because I think at
least for one stream it will be uh like
interesting people will want to check it
out and I want to check it out out
so what's this
place so let's do
it so I'm going to I'm going to go and
try ask for
perms
but who's the publisher I wonder if I
can get perms
easily we'll
see
bro can you not
[Music]
okay different
idea my good
old platform of
Boom character creation hype
yay yepe I shouldn't maybe I shouldn't
have jumped off so
fast ask for sponsored stream usually we
don't just ask they come to us speaking
of I think next no oh next next week I
have a
sponsorship that is kind of
[Music]
interesting oh is also kind of last
minute but I'm glad to receive it it's a
game
sponsorship I think it will be
[Music]
interesting but yeah I mean enoy is
welcome to uh
welcome to sponsor me but I uh doubt
that's like usually you know when we ask
to play something then that's not going
to result in the sponsorship oh no my
Shark oh no my
Shark there you
go what oh no just because I said just
wow or so no it's not world of walk
sponsor why would they sponsor me must
be so Random they don't need to sponsor
me it wasn't the hint did you guys
really think it
was oh nice this track is
crazy good shark whoa what are you
doing a weird shark
what
learn what do you mean
learn water
block will they just float and not fall
down bro that's
[Music]
crazy what that's not it it doesn't seem
to work the same way I can build it on
top which perhaps that's us
what they want me to do
here okay can't that would be too op I
guess being able to build it like
floating
L but
wooho
what oh oh I was like is there a hole
there like why would I fall down no I
was just out of bounds got to be
careful huh here it works I guess as
long as it's attacked to another water
block or or any block for that matter
let me
see uh
wait yeah probably any
[Music]
block I want to
see this part first
maybe no
no or is that a
shortcut just like Minecraft how is it
how is that like Minecraft there's no
water blocks like this in
[Music]
Minecraft but this is quite interesting
so that's a cute boat all right I'm up
here now I guess I could have gone from
the right side
[Music]
too yeah yeah yeah I hate it when they
hit you it doesn't do any damage but it
always feels like it
does
what um
f do I have to fight that
one because he just is so far
now hope that's not going to be an
[Music]
issue this thing is fly leaf I shall
name it fly
leaf I'm so
[Music]
sick me without
when I was looking for sad songs I found
a lot of like in my research just for
inspiration I found a lot of like Emo
songs again kind of want to do like an
emo cut
out I know it's been done here and there
before by other members but I want to do
it
too I used to listen to a lot of that
[\h__\h]
[Music]
man please do don't roll back but like
emo cut is different from what I did I
mean that was kind of emo too in its own
way but you know you know what I mean
right yeah I could sing fly leaf I could
have a good excuse I always feel like
fly leaf is too Niche but a lot of you
guys seem to know it it's crazy I feel
like in Europe nobody KN really knew it
but maybe in America they were quite
well
known oh damn how what do I do about
these
[\h__\h]
wait never heard of them definitely new
to me oh when will you get your golf
email huh maybe an idea for the future
huh honestly not a bad idea I never
thought about
that huh and I was kind of running out
of ideas like for this I have I have one
like now finally in the making for
2024 but it will obiously not being
released with in 2024 cuz we're still
still not even in the sketching
phase um what am I looking for Dam it
water
block but for 2025 then maybe
interesting oh yeah yeah you got the
right timing ah now come back but be
careful no no no no no oh yeah you got
that one right again good
job oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] go
away it's a long since I heard fly leaf
I went to a fly leaf concert in high
school oh that must have been sick sick
I'm so
[Music]
sick what was the other song that I knew
quite well of
them that I saw in this like Emo songs
popular Emo songs from 20 the the 2000s
to 2000 10 or so
playlist alive is that a strong name
yeah that sounds somewhat
familiar there's just two songs that I
know of fly leaf I think just
two ah now you almost add it buddy you
almost yeah there you go there you
go
it's uh difficult burp uh-oh
yeah yeah yeah go give it to him show
him who's the boss
yeah so proud of you little
buddy fully yeah okay now the more you
guys say that the more it sounds
familiar to
me how's that go what's the
M all right
fine I'm kind of feeling lost where am I
okay okay what is that place over there
for maybe I come here later honestly
thanks for the membership welcome the
fly leave uh the talk about fly leaf
convince
you what you going to do about that H
you can't go through here unless there's
water oh can you oh [\h__\h]
unfair oh
careful there we
go there we
go he's above needing water op too
op by the way I got Plucky Squire um
perms and maybe you saw k AA started
playing
it well I hope she likes
it hope she's enjoying it it's a good
game from what I've seen she loved it is
she already finished crazy
lady crazy
lady okay these are quite fun these
blocks and this whole gimmick that you
can create out of it oh hey what the
[\h__\h]
Lord jable
jable what happened to you death
perception is yeah I mean that's
fine it's not quite my
issue I like
this what what what enemy will we be
facing in any case he hat fly leaf will
always work
well [\h__\h] stop pulling my fly leaf just
start singing emo song
I'm so
sick St it
Escape frozen fish Frozen
time are they done yep so I'm going to
sleep hi K hello how you
doing when Kyla plays a game she really
plays I really play games too
[Music]
hello Heal
Me
Oh isn't this one of the people we're
looking for is it he'll be restored to
noro once we take care of this
Rift where that supposed to be but I
don't want to go in here yet
[Music]
oh well we can't forget about that but
we will probably have to go there and
here and there in the other dungeon we
also had to exit sometimes and do stuff
outside again so it's probably fine
right yeah I'm a gamer yeah I do a lot
of long hour streams thank you you
believe in me I like
you I sense my friends up ahead they're
not just in my head Trust
I hope there aren't any monsters in
here I hope there aren't any mon girl
are you new
here what we've been through already I
think should have kind of painted a
pattern and what we've seen outside and
all that girl what what's wrong with
you of course there's monsters up
ahead not paying
attention you gamer real right I'm a
gamer
girl I'm such a gamer girl I have gamer
girl headphones although not the ones
with the cat
ears oh come on I just entered
here oh that was a cute scream scream
some more
Zelda who did that scream who's the
voice actress cute
are you all right what's wrong with you
e oh I guess you can't just go back up
here can you Zelda I will keep on saying
things like that to trigger
you I feel like I maybe I could with my
water blocks but
[Music]
yeah but sure we'll do it
differently or with a bird like I don't
know uh uh
uh attach yourself to a bird let them
fly you up I don't know so many options
you
know oh [\h__\h] wrong button uh what What's
the button
ah some oh [\h__\h]
uh sometimes you forget the simplest
things
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] that was not very generous of
them cute it's like d the DI all over
again they also before the boss fights
and D the diver the the things also like
first swam up and then did a scream and
you know every time before you fight
they did such a funny thing yeah yeah
yeah yeah this is this is like big time
Dave diver
core you this to just section two they
had sections like that too but it's it
was more like faster Dave the D was a
faster swimmer than
her oh
no oh no
ow we good we got a good oh that's why
oh no never mind I thought I had to pull
it back but no not at
all and
escap yeah
yeah
[Music]
easy yeah it was pretty cool pretty cool
I wonder we might get another section
like that I have a feeling they're going
to throw that at us
again these things are too powerful now
I shall use them to my
advantage
ow the [\h__\h]
crabs they move too
[Music]
fast I can't
wrecked nice
when in doubt nothing beats a ground
pound guys haven't we learned after all
these years from our wise detective the
one thing that we should
have you know brought with us is nothing
be the ground
pound hey here we
are probably the real entrance yeah yeah
yeah
yeah so this there
[Music]
speaking of I wanted to clarify
something that I said in my K stream I
feel like you guys understood what I was
trying to
say um for promise I think it was a
great idea to merge and um I think they
work so perfectly now Council was great
too but like the the you know having one
single member without a generation
really and then a generation who just
lost a member it just made sense it
worked well and they had good chemistry
and they were already doing a lot of
things together um but that was also
like the merge was like early on still
like merging anything with myth or
changing its name four years in or at
that point more than four years in to me
feels wrong and even if it wasn't 4
years in just because we're the first
generation I feel like for the sake of
uh like IP and identity and history
that's why I think myth should never
change its
name and never merge with anything yeah
I don't know who we would even merge
with but you know what I mean right for
promise it made sense and it worked out
really
well
yeah so so so so so
this yeah it was perfect
I didn't want to imply that that was bad
or anything obviously I just don't think
it's the right thing to do
for uh myth these are we doing something
with statues again I can put up my own
statue here on the button no or doesn't
even have to be a statue but here how
about an
[Music]
elephant one button ah we have do we
have to fill up the whole thing ah so
that we can maybe reach the top up there
is it unreachable otherwise
[Music]
oh
oh well for now that's probably the
right thing to
do no misunderstanding Corner exactly
yeah Council RIS was even a thing when
they were still five huh yeah we just
always like put them together because
you know at the time it was myth console
and Iris
and yeah it's just it's just
becomes like
that yeah
yeah and then they just made it
officials it was sweet it felt
[Music]
right yeah
yeah even though Council are iris's cooh
eyes Council took good care of Iris huh
I think yeah they always vibed really
well
what is that bomb fish there for is
supposed to do
something uh yeah that's not what I
was hoping you would do because now I
don't have a platform but I'll just get
my water
block is that a new outfit no it's just
pngs attached to my
body but yeah speaking of the outfit so
would you guys like does it make sense
for me I mean I I'm maybe not as
hardcore into that kind of stuff as b or
M but I mean actually I had this whole
face where I really wanted to have like
a emo hairstyle and all that but my mom
wouldn't let
me but instead of an emo hairstyle I
basically just had way too long bangs
and I was like this this hyper
weeb um but I did listen to a lot of emo
music like fly leaf or Panic at the
Disco and [\h__\h] like that I don't even
remember all of these uh groups
anymore
yeah yeah honestly I think that's a good
idea a dark outfit the the alter waa is
pretty dark but it's not casual enough
for me to wear in those
ways so yeah maybe 2000 uh uh 2025 yeah
oh yeah four blood inspired four blood
yeah [\h__\h] yeah let's get something let
Maybe can make it very similar even to
the four blood outfit because that was
really
good that was really good we all love
for blood in this house you know we do
attack one more
time no you guys
suck well while you guys are distracting
yourselves
n n n
you know what I was thinking the other
day cuz there's a bunch
more really nice K songs these
days wouldn't it be so cool if we had
a like
um mini album or
something in collaboration with k
like for blood and all the other songs
from K like wild card and the new on
that they've been
releasing covered by me but like in an
official way and a streamable
way like I'd love to do that
honestly a full album with K's already
released
Songs but covered by me because they are
already mine no
four blood I think really the impression
is too strong from my
cover
n
n ply I'm going to die I don't want to
die can I place a bed on Water I can
right I remember again
H like vocal and do no title plus oh
they had something like
that just thinking makes a lot of sense
doesn't it can I sleep here without
you right fine I'll sleep
here behind
bars can student cover Studio 3D
H I don't know maybe one day right now
I'm not really
uh you know
struggling with finding new songs that I
would have to resort to covering old
songs that I've covered before in
freedie but yeah one day would be cool I
wouldn't
mind I would not be opposed to
it k doesn't usually have this many good
ideas back to wait wait wait what what
what what else like
what what
what what do you
mean what
the leave me
alone got to do something pisses me
off no don't go for the go for
the yeah thank
you I take care of the other ones too I
wouldn't mind
[Music]
emo I get Emo outfit cover true I guess
yeah I'm I'm a genius today but honestly
every
day but I'm on a roll
[Music]
sometimes ah what ah ah
ah good have [\h__\h] killed me
where do I
respa okay that's already
happening bro that's a rough
room what okay this fish is gone though
it's so generous that this is a one Echo
block quite
generous go for the upper one don't go
don't don't go for the bombfish thank
you okay good
[Music]
job oh thanks for the Super Chat oh oh
thank
you from uh prob
probably the great Brit
Briton thank you appreciate it
appreciate
it you guys don't even know you say I'm
having good ideas now but I'm having
good ideas every day I'm uh a few days
ago I messaged the
girls uh asking them um who wants to
participate in the New Hollow bag
stream
[\h__\h] for
them because we got a lot of new members
who haven't shown me their bags yet have
to see what's
inside show me what's inside
[Music]
[Applause]
H new girls now with new bags new bags
to be seen new bags new insides of bags
Hello shark are you ever going to do
something you know I know I can Target
them but I think he would go for it on
his own
no not
necessarily P my back while we're
added wait which one's mine
[Music]
mine died I
guess the
hell give me a lord jabu jabu Echo
please what about what do I choose how
do I choose one that's further
away like it's hard to determine what I
really want I'm telling you what I want
what I really really want look
ATA oh taking the train is like in
Germany first a truck drove in a bridge
and later a bomb thread at Sals Transit
what
what crazy well happy
[Music]
birthday well you made it in the end
right so all is good question
[Music]
wait I I don't want to be killed
again do
[Music]
something
good yeah happy birthday I'm glad you
had a good time and enjoy
yourself wait are you from Germany cuz
you're I know you were German speaking
but I I don't know you were just
visiting Austria and I hope you enjoyed
it hope you had a good
time hope you had some good snitel and
maybe because it was your birthday you
needed to eat a cake so I hope it
[Music]
was I want to eat s now
H how do I choose okay guys genuine
genuinely is there a way to choose
switch between what
I'm what I'm
[Music]
targeting do you
know Belgian chocolate cake or that's
the wrong chocolate cake the wrong
European chocolate
[Music]
cake it was that easy for you to get it
right but you got it
wrong I think it just Cycles you just
retarget until you get the right one
that sucks what the hell with an
oversight in any other game you can
choose the target like in literally in
the previous Delta game you were able to
choose your
target so like it
R okay like retargeting when they close
works but often it also just targets my
Pokemon when I obviously don't want
that
BR yeah that's that's that's pretty
bad come on
took him a while to get up on his
level all right
[Music]
uh there we
go almost a sced as a targeting in GTA I
don't even remember did I struggle with
that the Sharky the Sharky can't reach
me at this point
oh that's a
challenge you call that a
challenge
crabs honestly not
sure how about
some
oh
um so far we're not
winning I I think it's like not enough
space to slam him with a hit him with a
ground but
wait oh yeah you actually did
it okay this way work
ow okay now we're in the water ah but
these do go in water so that can also
bring me back up thank you
and a what was
[Music]
that um
H
nice kind of hard to see with the
perception there we
go nothing be the ground
pound yppe GTA 6 hype
indeed I am excited for that
too but still got a long time to go but
we got we got games to play until then
no need to
worry bubble C bubble bubble bubble C
bubble bubble C
help what what are these I can't even
copy these what are these
for you're just telling me to use my own
old statues or what is that what you
want I guess
so they're too cheap to give us new uh
new statues but thank you I guess I
don't want anything to spam
my uh my echo choices I could just walk
on it
oh it's the statues here that make me
think
man guess I'll
die is this where I've been for it looks
[Music]
same develop is crying right now yeah
developers is it's your
fault you did
this you did
this don't put any decoration there it
makes me think one should know takanasi
should not be
thinking it will be the end of all of
this
[Music]
so that's apparently
faster but it's
[Music]
annoying well now it's
dark away wait should we I mean we
probably will never otherwise drink it
do we still have a smoothie that makes
me glow we
do but I almost feel like
it's a waste because we could drink it
just when we need energy recovery
urgently it's just a minute I don't know
this is like I'm going to be hoarding
these I'm already hoarding
them oh RPG game feel like
a oh good job on that
jump I'm the one to jump
in be bio Baba
bio why
bio Lincoln
bio has link energy yeah yeah that's
what I'm saying like hm
[Music]
see now he didn't even attack the one
that I was targeting but I'm I'm fine
with that because that's not who I
wanted to
Target um yeah that's not the right
timing
Sharky that's not going to go so well
either yeah
there we go who's a good shark you are a
good shark you are a good
shark you've been replaced new
shark can I go up or here ah
chest a
another silver one my favorite Rock link
You
by funny
I was so close to singing some linkoln
Park but I was like ah this is going to
be better for an emo
K not a sad
K cuz there was some linking Park in the
emo playlist that I was looking
through what was that song that I was
going to
sing
remember I don't normally listen to Ling
par though do they want me to turn it on
or off cuz we had both so
far maybe on this time oh there's one on
the water there's one underwater so then
that's funny then I guess it's
off Breaking the
Habit num no it wasn't it was not numb I
think
I don't know wait
[Music]
what Ultra hand
oh so we do have to turn him
on all
right I just like so it being on the
water is maybe supposed to tell me
that they're supposed to be
off cuz you can never turn that one on
can you but apparently you
can you also were stum same
same oh that was
fast the other room because I died was
more
[Music]
Troublesome okay now I guess I'll just
stand on it
[Music]
this reminds me yesterday I also fixed
my cat drinking
fountain I bought a new pump and then I
replaced it now they got a proper
drinking fountain again so they go like
slurp slurp
slurp so
cute W the mechanic now all I did was
buy a new
pump which is half the price of the
whole drinking fountain so I was
considering just getting a new drinking
fountain but this one wasn't so
old I because it wasn't so old I
literally don't understand why it
broke it just my mom just told me it
stopped
working okay and I tested it and it it
really isn't working anymore but like
why this is sus why is that
there wrong wrong wrong wrong could do
it oh I can't go there oh what H
ow at least it doesn't hurt when it's
[Music]
self-inflicted getting them to like new
things doesn't always work
[Music]
but you
know this economy oh wait what am I
doing why do I want to cut off my Air
Supply do I want to
die now that
R
[Music]
Ben
tomorrow Italian Le's
[Music]
hey I was um thinking while I was
watching L stream a little bit
today CH and L Dynamic is so
funny it's a little bit
more like rebellious and uh
cheeky than what you guys do to me
and the way L reacts to the
[Music]
cheekiness quite funny why is this Stone
there ah because I want to lift them
back up I could also make them boom I
could make them go boom like here I
probably have
to
right K you're riding it with a
c like a
[Music]
Italian it's just a face I would hope so
for
you I hope so for
you I am I am not Italo I
am
austri what how do you say again I'm
mixing it with
Korean that's the wrong placement
probably oh it
worked austri
[Music]
I need to refresh my uh Italiano
tomorrow I'm
[Music]
dying where there's so many paths bro
let me go back up first because if
there's so many paths down here then
that means the the path above was
maybe extra path oh ah but ah maybe
maybe that's for later cuz I can't reach
it but what about
here
Wait you guys don't need Jack packs I
already told
you I believe wait here I believe you
can
fly I believe you can touch the sky with
your chicken wings my underlings I
believe you can fly
just believe in
yourself wo wo that's
pretty what nah I won't get it that
easily the master the key like just here
now already
really BR
really you don't need to shut the [\h__\h]
up
you have wings uh you were born with
wings what do you think that was
[Music]
for unless this is chatin is asking for
them specifically from
me but
chatini I cannot give you
anything ow it's got to be from laa
directly if anything you know
don't finish stalking
[Music]
me what the
hell this is difficult
ah okay well that's good but could you
not at the same time have exploded the
boxes oh God I need to heal
again try to fly on the water I'm like
unsure what things work on the water cuz
some things do and some things
don't but at this point I'm committed to
the bomb
[Music]
a green
bean what green bean a come
on ah I won't be that won be too
far I'm going to die let's
go could have grabbed it oh [\h__\h] I don't
I think
that oh there would have been an air up
here too bit
closer sometimes you just forget about
the simplest things like Ultra hand in
this game like what you can touch and
what you can't
[Music]
touch oh no I'm I my HP have you guys
seen my HP
bro okay stay up here I guess I don't
have to go down there oh all is okay all
is good my shark is doing it hey look at
the sh go getting every timing right
this is like when you cross the streets
and every freaking traffic light is
green for
you no many how many streets you cross
every freaking traffic light is green
that's how that felt thank you shark
good J who's a good who's a good job oh
who's a good job yeah you go back into
your
ball good good oh dear
not something that will trouble us
that's for
sure send a new one I don't know
why um well in this
case I don't know but how about my my
grandpa nothing beat a
groundpound Yoo
[Music]
imagine waging her
tail
yeah she might get excited if that
praise was for her but no it's
[Music]
not no it's not can I oh that's
invisible invisible
[Music]
ceiling the way of ground p ooh there we
are that's yeah I knew it was a way
back oh but okay you're going to you're
going to be this annoying to me
now I wonder if I
[Music]
can okay now it's like in this weird
half tile placement I guess I whatever I
don't want to do it like that anymore
[Music]
fish water dungeon starting to be yeah
living up to
its
reputation there we
go we had to do it that way right
yeah water dungeons be like
that I've been there it just reset
itself right I don't have to go there
again this is just my way
back we good I
think now we got left because we only
have one more button to activate and
then it will lead us to the end okay not
so bad like some of the rooms are like
because of the enemies a little bit
difficult but generally you can get
through this dungeon pretty fast
huh now what does this remind me of what
uh Froggers frog froggy Froggers
what what's it called
again you fought the same thing froger
I can't can't manage to get on the
platform ah ah no please leave me alone
no no why am I so dead anyway why didn't
I
sleep don't get
killed what am I going to do without
you oh
bye time to sleep I I I seem to forget
to sleep a lot
frog copter was so fun
too yeah lowkey frog copter Vibes too
remember when we played frog copter in
last frog
week and that was the game with the
developer showing up and like putting my
colors into the
game mine and some others like Ena and
Goa I
think that was so sweet
[Music]
oh was that spin frog did I call it that
was two different games
huh need more games where the de shows
up in chat so I can scream death
[Music]
took me a while
to perceive first of all on what height
that
was I don't know why but when I went
grocery shopping
yesterday I bought the simplest salt
crackers ever you know the TU took
crackers I didn't like them that much in
my childhood because they were too
simple you know you want those snacks
that are less simple but they were fine
everyone in a
while but now yesterday I had this urge
to like I appreciate some simpler snacks
these days I they could use a little bit
more
salt bacon flavored ones what oh and no
the craziest
thing this is the first time in my life
that I bought took crackers willingly
voluntarily by
[Music]
myself and it was just such a
random urge that I had
right and so I'm sitting in
my living room with my
iPad some Tu crackers right next to me
and I turn on the newest and the last
jet leg episode of their current
season and they're like in Europe you
know doing their jet lag thing and so
randomly too while I have two crackers
next to me that I just bought in this
episode they show Tu
crackers they just randomly one of them
buys Tu
crackers yes Sam finally won I was so
excited I was I I'm usually always um
cheering for
Sam I was like what the [\h__\h] like out of
the million things that could show up in
their show and that I could be buying
especially cuz that was so Random I I
never bought this
before what are the odds subliminal
messaging coincidence I think not yeah
but I was kind of
sad you
know you guys know by now what show I'm
talking about right
it's a really
high high production value YouTube
series
um we're usually the same free guys but
sometimes they have a a guest from some
other YouTube channel um they they use
the world as their uh Playfield
playground and they play like hide and
seek and all that kind of stuff over
countries um and yeah this time they
were in Europe again but like in Central
Europe uh covering Switzerland
Italy uh
Austria and that kind of area and I was
so excited to see that Austria was like
covered very well this time in their map
but they basically didn't go to Austria
at all this time it still ended up just
being Italy and Switzerland most of the
time I was excited to see some Austria
representation but so somehow they just
managed to dodge it completely it made
me
sad
yeah but their next season they already
spoiled it and they're in Japan again
for the next season and it seems like
they filmed it this
summer man they should they should
invite me as a guest but how am I going
to be a guest I'm a be but I really like
the
show
man can I be a guest somehow how would
that work
I really like their show it's so good
it's so fun and I want to recreate it
like a little bit they have like
different kind
of
um Concepts like generally it's like
kind of the same concept but then they
change it they switch it up a little
[Music]
bit it's really good it's really fun
I'm still trying to figure out what's
going on
here if I were to have no link energy I
mean there's surely other ways to
activate that right can I just twist
[Music]
ow yeah okay I
can it's hard to come by in here though
what are you talking about
[Music]
about let's do water
blocks no on top on top
no
[Applause]
[Music]
no I'm sure it works
guess it doesn't work but it works here
I can just
okay okay how about up
here wait a
[Music]
second why does it keep on this
appearing
what of cuz it's
flowing
[Music]
ah one more
ow
what no that
[Music]
way this is not I could just use beds
but wouldn't that be
boring ah
[Music]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] but I I could just beds but
I also just want to
destroy the boxes
[Music]
first wait why did I use the expensive
one
[Music]
anyway will this now be on this on the
right height
[Music]
sometimes you know jumping is good
enough oh and it already activated it so
that's good but I was hoping maybe from
that height I could shoot an
arrow but that would still not be enough
height anyway
[Music]
so let
me I don't know I don't know
[Music]
let me think a little
bit it's up so
high it's there's surely a really
simple way can I send an enemy onto the
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah how did you know
Smart
Cookie random W Japanese yeah cuz I saw
Japanese in the chat and I need to
remember you know usually they they are
there but they're just not writing much
because I'm not speaking in Japanese so
they feel like they just shouldn't speak
or so I don't know but they're always
there and I want to appreciate them for
still watching even at the shittiest
time
[Music]
I've definitely been speaking like 90%
less Japanese or 95% even compared to my
debut
times it's just well generally there's
definitely less Japanese people in my
chat than there used to be so it's like
less of a
[Music]
uh what's the
word prompt there's no prompts for
me I I I have a hard
time I have a hard time too
randomly suddenly speaking Japanese to
myself it feels like I'm talking to
[Music]
myself an incentive yeah
summon them like crony
does why why what do you mean like crony
does I can summon them like y
does yeah it definitely got to me back
then like I got so much hate for just
you know translating what I've been
saying uh a little bit because the debut
stream was special in me translating
more than usual after the debut stream
it wasn't even that
much it just feels so weird
because there's you know a lot of people
who speak way more Japanese than me in
their
[Music]
streams I don't feel like thankfully
they don't get [\h__\h] for
that but I I don't know I I stopped
mostly
why are we here why oh wait because okay
we can just walk through
here we have reached it for real wait do
we get a mid
no I didn't fight Link in this
dungeon what did you think so far in by
this going by this
[Music]
pattern we would fight Link again in
this dungeon and get the bomb for
link but we're already at the main
Master
boss rest first well it's just half a
hard but
yeah well yeah thank you guys you guys
are always very
[Music]
supportive yeah we did right we didn't
see link when we entered the dungeon
unlike the other
dungeons a I thought he would show up in
every dungeon at least on until we get
all the items but then I was also
thinking like doesn't that limit how
many dungeons there's going to be to a
pretty small
number
a thank
you my free tongue oh she e e e e
e e that reminds me of people who have
split tongues and I really hate that so
[Music]
much someone I don't know if I should
say who because was uh I don't know if I
feel like she talked about it but
someone showed me someone's split
tongue yeah okay you do know yeah
nissa's
sister oh maybe I already told you about
this but in the MS n was like on a video
phone call with her
sister and then like we showed each
other like we talked to each other right
and then I I saw her sister's face right
through the
phone and I saw the tongue and I was
like I'm so sorry but I really
can't that gives me like Shivers chicken
bumps on my
skin no it's not a bit it's real
tell us
more I mean I know there's you know some
people are into it and then there's
other people like me who get like
freaked out by
[Music]
it oh God just speaking of it I'm so
sorry she's really nice and all with the
tongue the tongue what that tongue
do can't I'm so
sorry no it's not that's just
[Music]
been you guys thought it wasn't
real no she really has it it's not a
joke or
anything the tongues are so
great I mean you know I'm I'm glad you
can see it like
that um I just
can't are we going to have like a
sucking mechanism again or what do you
think we be dealing
with what could it be a jabu jabu lord
jabu jabu well then he's probably going
to suck again right I'm going to take
the shark though for
[Music]
now something something
water
disconcerting I forgot about something
what is mean oh that thing look at his
eyes wait it's a
snail got those alaka
eyes vo you're
funny you look so funny from the like
frontal frontal appearance is very funny
oh what you can't do anything to him
wait wait wait I don't understand and I
already know that this is it's just for
now I just have to probably Dodge oh now
he's chilling what's wrong with
him what still doesn't Okay do I have to
become
[Music]
link [\h__\h] can I even shoot the arrow on
water yeah go for his back yeah that
looks yeah cuz it doesn't have any shell
on it I just I'm I'm still I'm still uh
observing what are you going to do oh
what are those from your tail but you
lost your tail
now you good buddy oh no
[Music]
oh all right all right all right all
right okay here we go here we go I don't
have much link energy
but oh just what oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] sorry I
thought it was over already so I I tried
to transform back but ah ow
can I tell the shark to go for it
[Music]
back yeah go
oh
oh probably too late okay I got one
hit come on oh wow
okay I mean wow it's giving me a lot of
time what but that's it what what are
you doing what's happening with the
water what is that for am I
escaping where two where
two did they get rid of the water
because now I can't use my [\h__\h]
sh how am I supposed
[Applause]
to huh I wait I don't
[Music]
work you gave you some link
energy yeah P had good choice
right
good what you going to do what you going
to do when w comes for for you B boy B
boy
my PS can't go for water right oh
God it's
already wait now I'm going to do with
this
link oh he's on the ground y
y that it's
[Music]
fast the vortexes looks so scary what's
the vortex you mean the
[Music]
tornado should try to get
closer don't a bad
idea is fine it's fine
fine
ohow thank you
[Music]
uh I don't know wasted ow
but it's
okay will ah will he actually
not move on if I don't get all of his
bubbles in one
[Music]
go and the big
one please wait for me please wait for
me please pleas wa for me please wait
for me he went so long he's like please
hurt me I'm into that stuff oh okay all
the water gone we're going to do one
more round or what
no h
got that wasn't bad that was way better
than my last boss
fight I was fine that was fine fine
fine so look at all the lemons that I
could eat they're very disposable guys
it seems don't worry about it when I eat
them could make lemon cake
lemonade
lemon uh salad
dressing lemon
fish lemon chicken so many things I
could make with those
lemons lemon don't M lemon
jam to put literally
everywhere thank you sorry by the way
the fullart yesterday I uploaded the
wallpaper I didn't immediately want to
make another Community post uh to spam
that away with the polar W thingies
but now I can probably post it my friend
Shar some of their power with
[Applause]
me more
yay I feel like I can do even more now
will we get a fifth
or ah he just removes one from all of
these like all of them or just these
ones you're showing
though and that's if it's just the ones
showing what what if I didn't have I
just randomly selected what if I didn't
have one of them surely it's like all of
the some of them so what it's randomly
selected let me choose what if I I don't
use a lot of them and then like what I
would have liked a removal on my PE hat
for example what if I only have like
some of them how would it select them
and that's not
nice that's not very nice
bruh that sucks nah that sucks you
should let me choose at
least you get
like then you kind of get punished for
getting everything
like I heard something from my friends
while mending the
rift something very obvious once again
they told me that this was the largest
Rift they've ever
mended one of us realized that ribs
could get big like this if we are unable
to do our job it's hard to say that what
would have happened if you hadn't
defeated that monster
Zelda that's probably the end of the
world there's not really anything else
to do in the still world for now so
let's get back to your world
up it applies retroactively Al you mean
that if you don't have one of
these it will always bees are not
randomly selected so if you don't have
them you have to get
them well that's weird too I think I had
all of them though hide
[Music]
container
okay water dungeon
complet we did it we did it we done that
we did done that did you we
do yeah yeah
yeah I don't know about these
rewards Z's back what's with Z's
back what
about that big fish was in the S world
with the rift gone I'm sure he's fully
back to
normal are you sure hopefully what if
that's a flag red
flag you know D and I are more like the
KN we're close in
age we care for our Villages maybe we
should marry huh yeah we squabble maybe
we're F similar so we argue over the
latest details but that's kind of hot
yeah now we know that rora and Cur can
get more done
together like make baby but maybe what
we really learned is that we got too hot
this so you
did are good friends usually huh we're
not young lady what are you saying shut
your k
[Music]
in any
case allow us to express our gratitude
Zelda we owe you a great
[Music]
deal oh
[\h__\h] oh is that a good thing or
what chief chief drown Lord J jba has
returned to the Cross Fall's
[Music]
Plaza okay thanks RMA yeah
let time for celebrate
yipp did you open the treasure chest
which
one
huh wait is that me without my hood did
I is that the first time I se myself
with that I got a bun
cute what was that again why does that
sound so
familiar a
dip
W
cute so [\h__\h]
dumb you call that you King guys look at
him what is he doing
oh it was a drink a sweet rice drink
wait did I have it maybe I
[Music]
didn't oh is that normal
behavior
uh what what what what what what are
these looks they're giving each
other huh now they're vibing
what he's a god oh yeah right not
well it was nice to hear that Zora play
their music I could have listened to
that whole thing I want a perfect way
for the Chiefs to make up after all of
this and make out
right where am I
oh oh you there I need directions wait
who's he
again he looks familiar ah isn't he a j
right I might oh
oh the right
one
yeah from the castle from the
beginning I found myself at Sea after
reg getting my senses and heard the
music coming from here do you know the
way to
hoc wait a second
[Music]
you princess I'd never have guessed to
meet you
here what what the hell is been going
on what can't believe all that happened
while I was gone and so Minister Lea is
at this blueberry person's home right
now then my first order of business is
speaking with Minister Le immediately
[Music]
Phoenix
right oh well then where does that LE us
we took care of the Rip but didn't find
your father S I think he's dead oh no
maybe it's a good time for us to head to
Newberry 's house
[Music]
too what did you just say what did you
just say about my
dad be more careful with your words will
you not
funny little
[\h__\h] all right uh if there's still a
side quest I didn't do uh in the village
and I want to do it and then we'll leave
also did I miss some treasure in the
dungeon or
what wait I should I could check if I
just look at the map damn it I forgot to
like check through it ah damn it also
the ah damn it there were some outside
things
that hey but the but the rift is
closed wait the rift is closed I can't
what
the can I reopen what why would I want
to do
that that's so unlogical
that's just in case you forgot something
but that just makes no
sense game
logic how do we reopen this Rift
guess I just walk
in uhhuh hi Lord jabu
jabu what's
here there secret here by the chance
no okay but I see
do
that just stinky fish
[Music]
water this is not human or elf
friendly not made for people like me
all right all right all right all right
all right so but e does it bring us okay
I was going to ask if it brings us into
the dungeon or into the still
World lemon Chan lied to me she was like
uh I don't think we have anything else
left in this world anymore
liar here what about that H and what
what about that I thought we' get there
if we're just you know traversing
through the the dungeon
turns out
no oh now you know previously we didn't
have these
yet now we have them in the beginning
already
but I'm too stupid to plac them
properly or maybe I'm not maybe that's
just it just doesn't
work there we
go stop okay right
side are all the enemies gone
no that would have been too good to be
true I'm just going to dodge
him as much as I
[Music]
can
okay trying to speedrun this where are
we now okay
I hold maybe we can n we probably got to
all go got to go all the way there I
wonder if I could have made it easier by
teleporting into
somewhere in the dungeon and then just
walk out of the dungeon
entrance please don't say yeah
because now piss me
off no please oh bully bully bully bully
bully No Bully No Bully No Bully no ah
go
away no
com
[Music]
no oh no
can't waste my time with you guys too
much take
[Music]
this they give link energy back so
that's
good okay where are we all right all
right all right all right
[Music]
wonderful
okay we got to go left
probably do you want to see a Zelda
change to this in Smash game or think it
would be a
separ wow but they're never going to add
more characters anymore but maybe new
new Smash for new
Switch switch
2 oh almost most definitely what do you
think would be a launch game do you
think Pokemon will be a launch game
because by the time that comes out I
feel like it's time for a new uh Pokemon
game but I don't recall Pokemon being
launch games usually are
they 3D Mario but I don't want the 3D
Mario I don't care much about
[Music]
mostly third party always every three
years in no November
November Mario Mario Mario Prime 4 okay
well that's interesting but you also
don't think that Super Smash Brothers
would be a launch game
[Music]
no damn
it I was wondering if that would happen
so now we know I could um wait I have an
idea oh but no they always going to
stick to each other
[Music]
yeah the last one as long as I just jump
it's
[Music]
fine what are these cute
boats I like
them okay what's in here probably just
money now that's so not worth
it but okay I'll take it for completion
sake
[Music]
you could sell the seahorses oh are they
good money
[Music]
uh oh yeah what was what was that anyway
did I go
there isn't that weird what is
[Music]
that maybe nothing in particular maybe a
shortcut so you can build
your is it a shortcut should I go
[Music]
down what's this
for yeah top camera with the right
joystick if you press
it sometimes you you'll be able to see a
bit more clearly
[Music]
fin oh
finally
[Music]
H I'm honestly kind of glad that we
didn't find that before until
now because the one time I died in the
dungeon I feel like that would have been
a
waste to use it
there the way I died there you know
[Music]
a you have snacks I have those really
simple took
crackers salty
crackers yeah okay how did I get
here beds beds and Sh beam
H okay now how do we get up to the last
treasure chest I guess I got to go the
normal
path to get up
[Music]
first how long have they so cute to eat
I have so many I bought like an extra
large pack like volume
pack they're
[Music]
cheap we have landed on the island
yippee
what am I hearing is that one of those
Shadow
monsters zooming around waiting for
me
yeah 50 rupees so did I forget any
treasure inside
no no inside I mean unless I'm blind
tell me if I am but it looks to me like
I got
everything so how do I get out of this
how can I how can I go to the there we
go now hold on now she knows how to do
it too much power in my hands guys too
to
much
yipp W our completion
[Music]
is okay side quest we can go do the gudo
side quest
first so that I don't
forget was it in the Oasis or was it in
the
city maybe OES
oh I didn't even see the
Blom I'm such a lost
cause where's my tile
[Music]
why does
she why does she want to see that I mean
it is kind of special and cool you I
guess
so I got to show you a
bunch wait has she seen it now okay all
right now that I've seen the Tes with my
own eyes I can share what I've learned
with my boss Mercy B you've been a huge
help please take this as payment for
your
assistant my friend accent is so good
come
on H
help my boss is a leader among the gudo
with
responsibilities she doesn't leave down
much she does make a point of
researching in the ruins looking for
useful things to bring to down and she's
so incredibly selfless I aspire to be
like
[Music]
oh sure she's great but you should to be
more like
me
Zelda the princess who has taken it upon
herself do not be rescued by any little
linkings no more no no no now she is her
own hero which kind
of teaches you
about how women don't need to be rescued
by no one anymore nuh-uh
cuz I mean it's always like this in
games and TV shows and movies the damel
in distress who needs to be rescued yeah
yeah we a strong independent
woman hell
yeah wow I guess it changes my whole
perspective yeah I hope it did it should
have no Peach too though peach got her
own is this the year of
Nintendo trying to
be they're trying to say something
they're trying to say that they're so
deep now they they know that women can
protect themselves because peach got her
own game where she's the protagonist and
fighting on her own wow girl bosses
Nintendo is all about girl bosses
now that's pretty cool yeah mean Samos
yeah yeah yeah yeah
sure but finally after years and years
of these franchises having these ladies
go out and do things on their
own that's pretty great Nintendo took
you a while but it's cool although I I I
personally I mean I don't think
that um it's not something that I feel
like they must have done years ago no
not at all because honestly where am
I huh because
honestly you know you don't have to
think so deeply about thing sometimes a
game is just a game and sometimes a a
dump little princess in a game is just a
dump little princess in a game and that
doesn't mean that women can't do certain
things it's just a cute little setting
and not everything has to be so
scandalous and super
meaningful and Peach is fine as just
being you know the one
character that has to be rescued from
Bowser that is fine
I think that's totally fine but them
switching it up like this is also fun
because just from the stand uh Point
View point of
view of a fan of a franchise where it's
always the same for years and years it's
just cool to see
things switched up it's a good
opportunity for them to make the fandom
feel like it's fresh again cuz they
they're changing things h
yeah yeah yeah so I don't think that
just because it was always like this
that doesn't mean
anything doesn't mean that Nintendo
doesn't think that women can be
strong is this the other side
quest I went
[Music]
there what what what's the other
Quest is there really another
Quest it's an Adora Village damn
it I'm overthinking my
thinking
what I probably just realized that non-
Nintendo people didn't understand why
the hero of the games wasn't in the
Game's
name I mean that's to me that's just a
joke to me that's also perfectly
fine if they see it as The Legend of
Zelda rather than the Legend of Link I
mean it always resolves about about
Zelda and Zelda is quite the legend even
if she's not fighting just by existing I
mean it's it's a whole legend on its
own what am I what am I looking
for I here
[Music]
well not that mean not every game needs
to have
what the protagonist in the
[Music]
name Spirit track oh yeah I think I've
watched a play through of spirit track
before
have you ever played the Green up time
yes I have but I was very young so it
was kind of
scary and I didn't play it on my own
really it was mostly my brother
playing but one day we'll play
it on stream
fully scratch my head over the
protagonist being someone else I wonder
if I ever thought about it like that
when I first got into it I don't
necessarily think
so like going into the game I don't
think I was that
confused but I definitely had moments
before ever playing a Zelda game where I
also just automatically assumed that the
that link is called
Zelda yeah most
likely my mom's being R she's standing
at the pool in our house talking to
herself something about monsters oh [\h__\h]
she's she's impostor she's going to feed
me to monsters wait no that is isn't it
still I'm sure she's very disappointed
with me I can't swim yet I'm just too
scared to try please you got to help me
could you check on my mom that person
over
there
no wait where's your
[Music]
mom this your mom yeah oh my it's Z
right I've heard that you rescued those
who got in the maybe you'll help me with
a personal matter could you bring me
some monsters I'm going to use them for
something let's see first I need a
monster that looks like a Sinister fish
a Sinister
fish which one does she
mean I would
say
maybe oh okay
wonderful clonk clonk
clonk this one was a tough this was
tough enough for the job but it's not
getting very shiny yeah what are you
doing it helped me learn more about what
I need to know now can you bring him
once it goes boom
yeah she abusing these Fe should I
really be supporting
this this wasn't good enough either it's
not getting dazzling enough ah you want
the ah she's looking for the glowy fish
which will be the third one that I'm
showing
her but then a shocking W talking
jellyfish monster yeah yeah she's she's
going to be asking for the this glowy
fish
[Music]
right very pretty shifting colors and
patterns oh oh no wait maybe that that's
maybe satisfying enough
At Last I did it got to say it turned
out well too now to see my song Come
With Me
Oh did she make a little boat or
something to help him
swim I'm
[Music]
not what oh my daa please just hold out
your hand how
[Music]
cute she maybe she'll give me one
too so I can swim faster but I already
have a charm that makes me swim
faster
a so sweet of the mommy he was so
worried so concerned for
[Music]
nothing look at him go maybe with a
scale you can swim upwards the
[Music]
streams well done I always knew you
could do it swimming is fun thanks Mom
ah
Placebo Cy Cy you never know in this
magical
world if it was just placeable she could
have she didn't have to put that much
effort into
it a see I get the same one how cute
that's pretty pretty pretty
[Music]
pretty
interesting what a crafty mommy you are
dive time
up
aha yeah that could have been useful in
the
dungeon so do I have all quests here
now I hope so let me know if I don't
otherwise I'm going to see where to go
next where did she tell us ah yeah cuz
we got to go
[Music]
there thank you for everything you thank
you my mom just thre me in a pool and
teach teach me how to yeah seems to be
the way to
go I mean you can just throw in a
freaking toddler infant into the water
maybe not an infant but a toddler right
wouldn't work with an
infant but they would just swim
automatically
wait what yeah they
float what I saw that in videos or are
they are they
wearing Des
no
what s in
videos yeah yeah they have the instinct
to keep them afloat why are you guys why
are you guys so
shocked what they swim like
automatically
what it's a very unreliable end
dangerous way to teach swimming well it
generally it seems kind of
terrifying but apparently it works I
phrased it scarily
okay it's why water BS work oh well I
mean usually water bsts are not in such
a big body of water so they can
immediately get out of there
no is that really connected
doesn't work always really okay don't
worry I I don't really think I would
want to do that
ever it just seems kind of yeah
scary anyway how did I do his voice
before uh I think I made him talk really
fast so despite Ming up those Rifts
there's still no sign of the king or
link that was probably not it but
whatever IAS my king where could you be
uh your your persistence has paid off
but your your persistence
has I don't remember it's been too
long your persistence has paid off
princess thank you for taking care of
those Rifts that leaves but one large
Rift the one located in hro Castle only
one large Rift left
really all right that's the one that
took these two as well as his
majesty I'm magnanimous King is in a ref
even now and while we stand here
yammering away those frauds are walting
around in the castle General right calm
yourself princess Mr luberry M Mr
le as high General I cannot stand idly
by what is it you intend to do then take
action I'm going to expose the true
identities of those imposters tainting
of Love
Castle he's going to like land himself
on the rift again maybe wait General
right for the
[Music]
L we weren't even done talking that guy
can still along can
he well back you mentioned you yet to
fight Link I hope he's all right yeah I
haven't seen him in a while now cuz he
wasn't in that one dungeon so I'm
guessing you'll head to the castle too
then those fakes are after your head
princess so please proceed with the
utmost caution let me upgrade please
I'm missing two where why don't I have
more feel like I'm
missing a bunch of them could have found
more
maybe NE Roy Jenkins time yeah okay so
now I've been a little I got to be
honest I've been a little bit spoilered
uh for this
region uh well I mean this I guess no
this part I've explored but um I'm a bit
spoiled about this
region
because D tendo couldn't literally
couldn't hold his horses and before he
like after gudo before he went to jble
Waters which is what you're supposed to
do he explored this whole
area
yeah yeah you can get a horse
there you can get a a freaking horse
[Music]
there go to Lake kyia for second
accessory Sal where
oh
okay well we'll go to like kyia and to
the ranch I guess for some exploring and
maybe getting
some uh extra of these blue
stones
hopefully no leave me alone leave me
alone
[Music]
right let me get
out my fly
[Music]
LEF clean up here easy
don't
stop don't stop your wheel buddy that's
what I got you out
for I'll get that
later I'm mowing
alwn guys it's going to be winter soon I
feel it the air is I mean first Autumn
but the air is already so
cold and it's been getting so
refreshingly cold and it's getting
darker earlier I love this
but depression Arc incoming because this
weather brings depression all going to
be so
depressed but I I don't know I like the
atmosphere it's been so cold that I
noticed my blankets didn't warm me
enough last night so I'm going to switch
to my winter blank
ASAP are you too high
[Music]
up this one already got me sick e what's
with your immune
system autum is the only season I like
really what about spring then but I'm
excited I'm excited to see I'm excited
to see my house uh and my garden in snow
again because uh you guys know I got it
in like when did I move in in February
right I think in
February the snow was already like
melting maybe y but I remember when I um
was like getting my first look at it and
when I uh got the keys because I didn't
move
immediately I remember I saw like the
whole garden covered in snow and made me
so happy to see it was just so
pretty you told us to remind you last
year remember for
what what for what remind me for
what the Yeah smoothie is always so
motivated to go outside I wonder if
they'll still like to go outside when
it's like super
cold snowing for the vitamins oh what
you he a bunch of you guys seem to
remember something like
[Music]
that
huh the vitamin D so that I don't get
depressed vitamin D's Nuts
bro well I guess okay think of the cats
and
snow I don't
know movie lik going outside but snow I
don't know if she will put her paws in
the snow I would be happy to see it
though yeah vitamin
depression now you guys should take it
too you guys should start taking a too
now
then to avoid winter depression a little
bit let's see if we'll be happier this
winter what are you doing here great
ber ah is that what gives me the
slot she doesn't like K she's beautiful
really little island in the lake is
suspicious
[Music]
okay you already have to take it all
right let's all try to be happy all year
long
yeah got vitamin La really that works
for
you avoid crippling winter depression
it's go
I like when the world is cold and dead
you like that I mean yeah I like the
atmosphere too but it unfortunately has
this natural effect of depression on
[Music]
you where do I want to go this is like
kyia is
it a this island maybe ah there's a cave
here is she in there
[Music]
let's see what we
here maybe it's an extra dungeon with a
rift be
interesting I like winter when it's good
snow I don't like sleep or wet snow but
that reminds
me uh the the
py was it no the myth the myth collab in
the myth no what when was it you know
recently when I got some girls I think
it was in the myth collab to like
consider coming to Austria in the winter
time and they were so excited about
it well immediately after the collab uh
I I I just mentioned like oh yeah so by
the way I'm serious about it like
anytime you can come uh I'll welcome you
[Music]
um it immediately became a uh like oh if
anything maybe next winter
you
[Music]
know of course of course I knew it I
just knew it I was like yeah that
doesn't sound very
realistic I don't believe
it but then when they said next I
thought well but until then you'll
probably have forgotten about it or
something else in the schedule will keep
us from doing it so I don't know if
that's ever going to
happen I think it's more likely that
raden will visit
me or or am on her own but not like you
know several myth girls at
once
yeah how cold does it get in the window
I already talked about that in a myth
col lab it depends on if you're in the
mountains are not
Etc yeah I'm fine with just one of them
visiting or
so but I just wanted to mention it not
that not that you guys from that
motivational talk they seemed quite
motivated not that you expect anyone to
come over this coming winter it's not
happening
[Music]
can't believe m is all talk wait what I
just got easy access here I thought
there was maybe a rift or
something but it looks
pretty oh she's cute
what what that's the prettiest Great
Fairy that they've ever made in a Zelda
game I think usually they're all ugly
[Laughter]
or just very overwhelmingly
huge why is she cute this feels
[Music]
wrong they I feel like they always
should be much cuter but now they
actually made her
cute I speak the truth a problem with
that I guess not for you giant ladies
she's super sazy oh
see
um oh are you the one that woke me up
dear you little [\h__\h] how dare you I
don't know who you are or where you're
from but you're a diamond in the raft
and with just a bit of Polish you could
be a diamond with the
stuff but what approach to
take I've got it what if I increase the
number what she doesn't seem sassy the
number of accessories you can wear yes
we must be bold there ing are you ready
to begin your adventure of
[Music]
style yeah okay but I also want to chat
more with you but
sure how can I refuse your most
heartfelt wish to be more St that's not
my most heartfelt wish that's just the
wish that you're pushing on to me but
sure but I won't insult you by doing it
for free of
course the trouble with a free service
say you're always waiting for the Bill H
I don't believe in waiting so I always
collect my fees in
advance 100
okay how I adore
rupes as promised I will enhance your
style thank you Dipple
[Music]
your accessories limit has been raised
by one you can now
[Music]
wear more accessories than ever before
now go into out into the world and show
off your accessory
[Music]
success oh well my gift is increasing
the number of accessories you can wear
there's no sh path to CH St my
dear for a few few rupes of course so I
guess I could get even more now but I
don't think we really need that
urgently I will equip this at the same
time and yeah we can always go back here
for fairies
[Music]
now my phone voice from hotland
Miami you remember some stuff huh that
stayed in your brain that stayed with
you won't ever leave you
huh don't you dare don't you
dare
ah damn it I can't spawn it like that on
them cuz they're in the
[Music]
way okay okay okay okay
okay 300 500 oh my God yeah I don't
think that's worth it right now but I
wonder
uh was it just bre of the wild or are
there usually always more than one fairy
in the
[Music]
lands there usually is there's always
multiple okay okay
okay then I wonder what the others will
give us
[Music]
there's an opening here
what what I can create an entrance here
stand back I'm going to
morb I I I'll I'll mute uh the lemon for
now is this what is this oot has six mm
has five what about what about Wind
Waker where even any fairies I don't
remember
any what free areas I guess we just get
a little bit of extra lemon
[Music]
energy if we do
this
[Music]
optionally come
on is that spawning them endlessly oh
what oh my god oh
that's kind of dumb wait a
second come here come here try
me okay it wasn't spawning them
I there are great F wind really I don't
remember them at all what did they look
like
[Music]
yeah I could have grabbed them
too but you know that's just boring
sometimes it's funny but I don't always
want to resort to that hey
yo why is he so dumb why are you
throwing those spars that they're just
going to fall uh Bonk against a
tree think
piggy think
[Music]
really should come here when you already
have the water block
bro bro
bro first of all we're really having
trouble of these
directions second of
all keep on falling
[Music]
down wait can I go in is there something
in there no okay but that was the third
one
[Music]
I like these big bodies of
water
[Applause]
water ah ah ah oh no no no no no no no
maybe I have to fight him
ah shy once again it's your turn I Rely
so much on
[Music]
you dep perception
go get him go get him protect
me protect your creator
takiar there's a sussy place over
there Ah Ah that's the
one oh I can just touch it like that
there we
[Music]
go of course Metro Prime 4 is on my
list
but they they were they will release it
on the normal switch I guess right but
I'm sure they will release it
immediately on the switch to as
[Music]
well be what well digal games no wait I
I heard um even physical it has a slot
for switch one games so it'll be
compatible MH so there's no need
to um bring a what's it called uh not M
remaster what's it called again when you
bring a game to a different
console what's the word again Port oh
yeah so there's no need for ports I
would
assume can I wonder can
[Music]
you are they going to let
you you know that switch Nintendo switch
online thing that lets you play all the
old games if that will be
possible like in on the switch 2 as well
when you log into your Nintendo switch
online membership or if it will be
different
thing I would hope that the Nintendo
switch online membership would work for
both the old switch and the new Switch
that'll be good
otherwise that'll
suck
mhm yeah hopefully so that's gone yipp
but getting rid of the rift here it
would have been
nice if it would have created some
something now it's just an empty Island
like they could have put like a treasure
chest or something there
[Music]
no interesting
what have I
gained I actually didn't look did did
the lemon get some extra lemon energy
for sure it did
[Music]
right oh
oh a double what's ah finally I find
something yeah and two crystals I got
two crystals
too a chest with 10 more dumb seahorses
anything y'all I feel like it should
have just like revealed
something or even a person an NPC or
so I got 11 now I can get an
[Music]
upgrade everything carries forward yeah
that would be great that would be
great thaty
[Music]
very um
user
[Music]
friendly are we still swimming in Lake
kyia or is it something
else where am
I
[Music]
aha okay then I'll go to this side
you missed that
Crystal wait should I talk to her again
I met her you did oh sorry I got so
jealous that I blacked out for a second
um so where did you see
her in a cave on a little island I knew
oh only I could swim there well I at
least feel bit annoying when she has
face for letting me know how to learn to
swim it's not that difficult or make
yourself a little boat or or hire a
boatsman get yourself a
boat boats boats
boat get yourself a nice
boat there there he
[Music]
is do it
swimming armband side
quest where
what what are you saying did I miss it
is it does she give it to
[Music]
me o what you saying
flying T could be do I have to give her
something she didn't seem to have
another Quest seemed like that was kind
of the end of
it
oh it was a
j oh it was a j the not guy Aon
Gathering give it a go fun snag and fun
to bear gaing Acorn is never a drag all
you got to do is pick up the acorn okay
where will they be this time will there
be enemies
again okay okay oh
oh that's
fine no problem 22 seconds
no where are you
going I guess they not even
attack oh wa need did I miss some by not
diving
down
no
easy they barely try to attack me I
think you're fine even without a shark
helping
you
huh do you want me to do it faster bro I
can try with this one I can try but 18
if you do faster how fast let's try
without spawning the shark maybe I'll be
faster maybe he wants 15
seconds let's give it a
go spinning makes it go faster even on
water wait dud does a speed thing stack
can I take a smoothie a speed
smoothie h and no wait wait I have an
idea cuz I'm diving and swimming I need
uh at least one of them but what if we
take both of them and then I do wonder
if it if the Speed Stacks does anybody
know like this
one I'd be disappointed if it doesn't it
doesn't Okay I just don't want to waste
[Music]
it w
oh it
no oh but look at my
wa like 11 seconds or
so
shees 1255 that's under
15 that was lighting okay now we get our
bonus
oh okay okay okay okay okay I appreciate
that maybe I should do the other nut
challenge as
well that's a different kind of nut
challenge uh in
October not November yet should I do it
right away
n maybe next time oh but I wanted to
go yeah maybe when I get the warp point
of this
map wherever that will be
[Music]
do they ever give hard pieces these nuts
guys notice but
using oh yeah I've seen them drop rupes
a lot but I don't really like the
crows maybe I should use them
[Music]
desert
um does it work with the Alber trolls
[Music]
too or does it have to be the
crows no no
no
well the fire
ones are not the best opponents yeah
they don't they can't even touch them
[Music]
game no no long
no
what a to the
[Music]
yall hey they got a fly Le out here
oh it's your
family but I'm not going to let you see
your family not that easily going make
you kill your own
family oh it's up so
high it has been killed by its own
family it did not end up killing its own
[Music]
family no don't get bullied by your own
family you got to fight back now I have
a good reason to kill him there we
go ooh it must have been very
frustrated at that point it was just
filled with rage and the urge to
Revenge
[Music]
avenge all right
I think that spot over there is
extremely
suspicious that was
[Music]
obvious o warpy warpy point warpy
point get some money here with all the
grass
[Music]
I can't stop there's so much grass I
want to get rid of all of
[Music]
it
stop ah do
[Music]
something no why you going that
way okay fine
stop making decisions on your
own let me do it come down come down
cheeky little
brat all right I'll replace you
now lawn mower simulator
[Music]
activate this where are
we oh wait that's not at all where I was
hoping to go
oopsie I wanted to go down down down
down down down down down down down
down I we'll go
[Music]
now ah there it is on our left
is the
ranch it's time to quit horsing around
guys stamp R also to find here wonderful
another
[Music]
Stam yay L LA Ranch
I think it's the
same hello there's
CS time to stop horsing around and cow
around Mo ah so cute I saw a picture
today on
F of a cow with a cat head because it
was like referencing a picture of a cow
on a TV cut off by its head just by the
screen cut off you know and then the cat
is peeking peeking out on the side of
the
screen and then somebody made fan art of
it so silly so silly don't worry it
wasn't actually cut off it was just like
the scene the framing had the cow cut
off on the
head can you imagine what our hores went
missing we look all over but we can't
find it
milk
chickens oh how have I long for
you well what can we do with the
chickens can I maybe how do we anger the
[Music]
chickens it won't
attack can I control the chicken no what
how do
I how can I anger the
chickens don't look at me like
that you can't Echo the chickens for
some reason why not what about the
car I can lift them
but it won't let me it won't let me lift
it anymore
why
H oh notic our music box didn't thank
you it plays really pretty music let me
tell you it's a priz for our black races
black races are little contest we hope
here oh so this is like in the gudo
desert with
the
um that one mini game that we had where
we got a sparkly item that we don't know
what to use
for say my artst bed yeah that seems to
work with you guys oh oh welcome to H
Ranch I'm afraid we're not oh yep distro
horse ran off can you help us find
it
easy I unfortunately know where it
is I just can't get out of here just
can't seem to get out of
here it was
somewhere um
is
it where am
I oh it might have been here I'm not
sure anymore no I I I'll
Trust I think it was on the left
side oh there's a there's a cave we got
to go into it
[Music]
later must have been here is
no ah Maybe there in the
[Music]
water no that's a hard container that I
would like to put
[Music]
this don't let them bully
you come
on put an end to
this Zelda she's getting her steppies in
for
sure I need to use my treadmill again it
hasn't been used in a long time I mean
obviously I can have the excuse of just
not having been at home for like 1 and a
half months if not more if we consider
the Italy trip as
well so now maybe perhaps you know it is
time to activate the machine again
[Music]
this can help with the winter Blues too
really oh we could build our way up with
[Music]
the with the water too but this might be
faster and easier
actually Yay
did we just get a new heart no right
it's just uh it just healed back up how
many pieces do we
have we need one
more okay now where's the horse a maybe
it was down
here might have been there we might
passed uh by the cave again if that's
the case I will go in there it
is hide the CL
[Music]
Treasure Chest could be a hard container
maybe
speed nice oh he dropped like a oh
that's a different
one
huh I should not have learned it it's
just it just takes up
space Oh yeah this is a hard
[Music]
container it's not but this is fine it
was a pretty easy
cave stream hard container yeah if you
guys would have streamed hard container
more maybe I would have a hard container
now oh wait a second why is there a
second level
you can kind of miss
this ah it's like you could probably get
into this cave
from is that not doesn't that look like
um ah ah maybe you can only fix that
from the other side there's a stone
there that you can move is there
not or was that just decoration
[Music]
uh sorry what
I I did the order
wrong
I well I guess there's nothing at the
[Music]
top leave me alone
wait
okay so would it be
here I feel like it would be here but I
can't see anything and maybe maybe
they're just trying to confuse
me but wasn't that weird the second
level that's
[Music]
Weir it's not like there was anything
worth anything
[Music]
anyway yeah but I don't see any stone
that I could pull out and it didn't
react to
ah gosh all these monsters
here
infested Mama
Mia I can't even ground bound them I
hate
[Music]
this
something you're not doing it right ah
this is where I think yeah there it is
there it is
I walked past you I'm so sorry horsey
you were probably thinking ah I'm never
going to be
rescued all
right how
about
[Music]
beds we're on a horse
scene press a to mount the horse out to
move tilt opposite from the rest in
which you're moving to stop okay I need
to drink
you didn't know where the horse was were
you looking for it and you couldn't find
it
ah it's a bit hard to
maneuver
okay horse girl
alligations I was thinking about horse
girls because um today I I saw this
video of
someone drawing uh a horse on their hand
or so I think it was on their hand and
they made a really funny video no it was
on their cheek and then they when they
looked the side cuz it was like drawn so
that was the side profile of a horse and
when they look to the side uh their own
teeth became horse tee and it look so
funny you saw it and I was thinking
should I send this to moay or so I don't
know it look so funny the teeth looks so
funny guys
[Music]
I I may have liked it so maybe you saw
it because I because I liked it or so we
don't know because Twitter doesn't show
us such information
anymore thanks
Twitter
so the guy in green s his link well the
funny thing is you can't even say that
anymore because she it's not like she's
wearing a green
cape it's blue
[Music]
yeah there's a few horse girls so I
wasn't sure who to send it to and if
they would like
it Twitter is like so [\h__\h] like that
video too like there's so many accounts
recently that just Spam I mean I mean
there's always been that but I feel like
there's more than usual uh accounts that
spam like Tik Tok videos or whatever and
then the most annoying thing recently
there's so many spam accounts now
replying to everybody's tweets
everybody's
tweets Mr elen didn't you like want to
get rid of those spam boxs
H and it's like somewhat uh like they
they their AI kind of like reads what
the Tweet wrote and then reply to it
nicely so you can kind of sense a
pattern in who who are normal users and
who aren't but sometimes it's a little
bit difficult and I like I try to block
them all because they like spam all my
[\h__\h] replies of this
[\h__\h] but it's difficult sometimes I'm
not
sure but usually usually yeah if you
look at their profile they all just like
all their replies are like
replies that reflect everything that has
been written in the original Post Yeah
there's just so much [\h__\h]
spam yeah you can't block them all
because every single time you tweet
something new ones pop
up there just so many it's so annoying
honestly I miss our spam bots in on in
the YouTube
chat where are my
xxx.com
whatever lady
where are
they I missed
them those are fun hot girls in my area
are are there just no hot girls in my
area
anymore what happened to them what
happened to the hot girls in my
area oh
man yay so wait if I understand
correctly can we can we borrow them now
and leave with
them they're migrating cuz of winter
where
[Music]
to the hot girls are
gone so we have horsey now but I don't
know if like we get off once and go into
a cave or so if they'll actually stay
with us I think not can they jump over
this they
can that's good
so ah the wants me to go to hro Castle
not I'll
um is this region cut
off I don't want to like explore areas
too much that you that the story the
main story doesn't want to explore you
necessarily because I don't want
to go there if the game will make me go
there anyway eventually this seems to be
cut off by Forest
side quest down
there
where ah you
[Music]
mean was
it here
[Music]
right uh the the pretty aona looking
horse that one I know they won't give
you at this moment of time maybe later
[Music]
I'd like to get rid of this Rift
please can I activate
this while I'm on the
[Music]
horse okay
hot girls graduated
[Music]
no yeah this one I know I know I kind of
just ignored this guy cuz I thought ah
this is probably for
later but hey now I opened up the path
for you without you even having to ask
me
wow w
[Music]
welcome thanks for the
monies
[Music]
MH this thing really reacts to the grass
huh the moment it feels grass it's like
I need to become La lawn
mower lawn mower
yeah has lawn mowing
instincts
cute is there a hard piece that I didn't
get yet no
okay it's its real purpose
H seems like
it so wait is my horse still there
waiting for
me
yes but I didn't go into any cave so I I
do wonder how that would
go hyal Ranch hyal Castle I ran that way
I came from a different way sure what ah
I just uncovered this path okay oh
there's an opening
[Music]
cool he y' hi
peace uh how do I get off
again okay
[Music]
um attack before it before it shows it
spikes you idiot is that my
[Music]
own no this is so dumb this is so dumb
not being able to Target what you
[Music]
want d d d no I don't know that
D I need to
sleep good night
[Music]
chat the danger noodles yeah she kept on
focusing on the danger noodles
[Music]
man maybe one more
okay pick up the heart no I can't just I
can't just do that and then run away
that would be too simple too easy extra
heart y let's
go is that
[Music]
sus where's my
there what I swear I didn't know that I
swear I didn't know that I just know
that this sometimes is a
thing in suspicious spots of
dirt yeah even if there's no way to dig
yourself down into a cave or so uh if
it's suspicious it might give you one of
these blue
stones 20 Crystal
[Music]
St did I leave my horse
oopsie sorry it's easy to forget about
you
somehow I chose the horse on the
map in case I you forget at some
point okay what was this forest does it
have a name
no
weird a weird
forest forest forgotten house
forgotten I don't remember who I even am
uh what else should we check out or
should we just go to the castle what do
you think
guys well we definitely should go back
here once
[Music]
right that's why you got the okarina in
Link to the Past is the same
spot was it
recognizable link wait link to pass is
the one where I played the Remake
right some of these name games are too
similar
man upgrade then Castle yep yep
yep thats aw Dam
it level three
ooh thank you now can you oh okay I
[Music]
can m
maybe my sword is it 10 you can't do it
now you need to do more research than
get on it get on it old
man don't waste my time I got all these
crystals the dick SP reference
[Music]
is SNES game the I probably I probably
watched the play through of it but only
these names are too similar they're
confusing
me a couple of these I I think mainly
link to the past and what was the other
one I I just confused
those links Awakening yeah yeah yeah I
confuse those too much so is my horse on
the
map it is
there so it just stays there I wonder if
you get an item to call your horse
sometime a whistle or
[Music]
something wait can we play the mini game
now do I need to bring the horse inside
or can we just play it
[Music]
please milk I don't want to buy
milk how
much fresh milk I don't need
it I think I have enough but like eh
game maybe she's not the one that
initiates the game requir story progress
ah okay okay okay okay okay
yeah that probably is the case uh oh my
horse is back here now ahuh
[Music]
interesting how did it decide to do that
when me entering a cave and warping
around didn't change its
location
H okay I guess we'll go here now maybe I
should have activated the warping
point I felt like it was too early
[Music]
guys I don't know if that sus it's got
to be like one tiny spot of a dirt now I
feel like I want to ride around one more
time and have an eye out open for these
tiny dirt what is that looks like out of
a tailes off game why it's so fast W who
who
who stop chasing me oh my
God if you get that wolf Echo I
wonder I wonder if that you can Traverse
the land fast with that one I feel like
that's the one I saw in that video
why are you running because he scared me
Natural
[Music]
Instincts bye
[\h__\h] oh cool looks like a m
[Music]
thank God there's
no uh Arrow count like thank God I don't
have to buy arrows they're all magical
wolos
Echo they are Speedy boys how expensive
are
they oh wait wait where is it
the end of my list probably
[Music]
yet okay it doesn't have a Target so
it's just
chilling
[Music]
okay what's
this wa holy moly that's aggressive oh
well too bad you can't jump up there you
pushed him up there but you can't go
after him
[Music]
now wow it's like it dashes
through
W Treasure
[Music]
Chest you like the Wolves watching you
live from work
oh how's work
going is it bearable today wait I don't
have this bird yet do I
[Music]
ow not the dangerous
snck wait wait wait wait
wait no
[Music]
okay you forgot about
me I got a potion s but you know I'm a
[Music]
hoarder in this economy I can't just
drink my
smoothies I got to spend 10 bucks per
smoovie to make him and never drink them
makes perfect sense right for the
economy
sometimes you just got to do what's best
for the economy so let's get those birds
though because uh I can't accept not
having the
bird it should already be damaged come
on wa well okay yeah cool he she just
spreads
everything everywhere am I supposed to
pick all of these up eh oh wait there's
that I already have one
here
gu why are you
where are you
[Music]
going
yo
PL five of them okay
[Music]
all right let's go to pyro
Castle now we can go to pyro
[Music]
Castle no no leave me
alone what do you
[Music]
want water block is a great Echo yeah a
quick way to get up maybe I'll stop
transforming into link all the
[Music]
time good job good boy who's a good
boy who's a good boy where are where are
we
[Music]
okay that looks like a pretty big
rift big enough to give me like an extra
Rift world to go into but I guess not
this
time ah the nut guy okay we've done his
thing is this door open for me wait are
they all right somehow I even though
we've started the game in hyro Castle
somehow why I don't know but I just felt
like when I go to H Castle now it will
be like in gra of the wild like only
enemies in there trying to kill me but
no wait I mean these people do want to
kind of kill me but they're not
monsters hi waa
hello welcome once again in the waa land
why don't you believe me look at me
listen to me behold me clearly you can
see that I'm a
general it's just as I said General the
imposters have taken control of our
kingdom the king told us to be on the
lookout for bosses like you wandering
around you oh wa I get a real deal don't
tell me the password I
love the password he doesn't
know that's right the king's on the
password if you're who you say are then
you'll know
it I
see Lily the fraudulent King is trying
to frame the frame us as the
imposters this is preposterous the FRS
have all maneuvered
us they the real left and right but
these people think they're imposters
this is kind of a mess thanks for
stating the
obvious all right let's up the king the
general and minister is in the castle
are fakes FR
phonies right let's revise our strategy
let's just kill
[Music]
him no n the
rift has it enlarged oh no oh
no W that's okay that's suddenly very
big what what made it suddenly grow so
big oh
no oh
hello oink
oink a couple more no problem oh all
right yeah no problem oh no the C on the
rift it's p in what should we do should
have listened to
me pull it together your soldiers of
Hyrule so soldiers what is your
duty protect and
attack yeah pretty much protect the
people correct you know your duty well
now then brave Soldiers of hyru guide
all of those who are fleeing to safety
I'll seek out anyone else who's been
left behind together we'll protect our
people all and now you listen to me
good
job it's like their instinct when
they're being yelled at and told to do
something this is terrible princess
you're the only one who commands the
rift please rescue those who have been
taken I'll help with the
evacuation
easy fight the abyss yeah as always hang
on
what
below bro why you got to make it so
complicated
again mhm uh-huh okay well at least now
you're not expecting me to go
underground with you uh so easily
through the freaking ground again thank
you for your
consideration obviously go for the ones
on the ground
you guys like this thing I don't like it
this one this one can cover ground
and air everything except
[Music]
water get out of here get out of here
stop moving stop moving stop
moving my God
[Music]
what it bus up quite nicely we can stay
link for a while very good look at that
that gets me Ong ground but can I still
walk into the
houses o oh dear oh no oh no I would be
so [\h__\h] scared too
chickens but that looks like a yummy
Burger on on the left side m
scared you poor dear it's going to be
all right come let's
go
yeah
okay easy princess this child was left
behind for now I'll guide him to
safety sure lemon way underground no no
I know where I know no need for hints
well
thanks that end
carpet looks like a
[Music]
lemon
maybe maybe they all know something that
I
don't fast travel points
ah oh
oops was it out here
yeah
CA almost missed
it even though I was planning on
activating it
[Music]
what about here is is the General in
there yeah oh no he's the way he's
holding sure I don't think that's a
human the way you're carrying it it just
looks like a freaking Matos mat
matrioska
uh oh this place completely empty
[Music]
let me sleep for a
moment princess Carrie that was not a
princess Carrie I guess because she's
not a princess only
I would get carried like
that but don't get carried carried
away we don't want to be carried away
like those
others we want to
[Music]
stay here we go here we
go caves and Wells it seems they got
everything that they had in tears of the
Kingdom to satisfy us
[Music]
stand back I'm going a
more having a giant purple portal in the
backyard probably not good for property
Val
yeah unless you're like gondorf for some
some creature like that then they would
probably appreciate that and would like
like to expand on it that's a
map I wonder if there's any like hint on
there hello mhy mhi you're not going to
move
huh G on dor all right water blocks help
me out here surely it'll be
useful you want to fight me
[Music]
first I'll just these
shitty fats what a waste of my
time look at these Twitter bird
[Music]
cute wait
oh I blocked oh
[Music]
okay I got to become link more often now
like they're they're really
annoying and they do give me a bunch of
energy back so
hello
hello fight
me a
[Music]
aggressive turkey
noises you think you could type that in
chat and not be seen by me huh right I'm
going back
once cuz I want to
explore some
more something in
here a half eaten
Burger I'd like to have that tph
today so
far I've been awake for maybe 7 hours or
8 hours now I only had a a breakfast
with like corn flakes and one banana in
the Corn Flakes like I I cut I sliced
the banana and put it into the Corn
Flakes with the milk I like to have that
kind of breakfast
sometimes it's a good combo yeah
feels more healthy than my daily
chocolate
quel I still have Bice s in the
fridge
bro I would make it for my lunch but the
moment I end the stream it's already
kind of dinner time with how much how
long I
stream yo look at that
oh but
now is this like a shortcut if you
wanted to you want to go real
hard of course
sweet sweet
mustard corn corn flakes with banana
it's good
yeah just works so
well chocolate's healthy too I kind of
got sick like after eating chocolate
quasa for
like over a full week every day I got to
switch it up a little bit and then I'll
be back to the quos in No
Time Zelda be like me sleep wake up
sleep wake up sleep wake up so relatable
this princess is such a princess of the
people with such relatable
issues having trouble
sleeping sleep twerking no oh she's not
twerking she's a princess she wouldn't
twerk butter I Can't Believe It's Not
Butter it's radiant
butter even
better sleep twerking in my dreams I'm
sleep
twerking did we miss
something what about this area it's like
shrouded still should I go back for
[Music]
it you
bastard I'll go back because I don't
want to be missing out on
anything yeah that Island over there
maybe beds I don't
know there any better
[Music]
way oh
wor can I put this thing here no but
what if I put it here ha
I feel so smart guys I feel so
[Music]
smart I
will I would have preferred I don't know
blue stones
[Music]
maybe that's not going to work
I wish I could place some
diagonally how many more can I
make are they sell for good money or
maybe I should just sell them huh don't
think I'll catch up to the time for bed
no
don't but okay
understandable please watch sir archive
gyy nice the W
[Music]
away can't stop me that jellyfish won't
stop
me nothing can stop me should I get that
rupe what an annoying position you're in
okay we're getting
there feel like we are there
[Music]
yeah I I have this feeling we're going
into hyru dungeon now but surely we're
going to come back at some
point we're probably not going to get to
explore the whole thing
right I have a vacation now I can stay
up as long as I want oh nice
vacation
Yi something about this feels even worse
than what we've dealt with before Zelda
let's be extra
careful yeah the music already gives me
a bad
[Music]
Vibe we'll probably meet
link even if he's not here at the
beginning I have a feeling we got to
meet Ln
[Music]
right and maybe gon is there gon in this
game I mean there was like this monster
but it didn't look like what did we see
Ganon that didn't look like
Ganon oh well hello there
[Music]
good bully good
bully in the very start in the very
beginning I already forgotten but I
don't think that really looked like much
like gon oh it's a pig H I guess Ganon
is a pig by default
huh wait this is the I know my room is
over there wait I think I can learn how
to get my bed now because I did see that
you get to learn her bed so maybe maybe
now's the
time hey what the [\h__\h] what happened
with my room I was going to learn my
bed
what my
cat the
[\h__\h] okay never mind we're not learning
my bed maybe after we fix the
rift Ganon is a pig G of a human okay
okay yeah yeah yeah well he has taken
all kinds of forms in the past so not
surprised I the king
[Music]
so your father was here all
along somehow conveniently just your
father didn't get like teleported into a
different Rift and just stayed here H
well don't worry Zelda once we meant the
rift he'll go back to
normal yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah will he
though will
he interesting
[Music]
Baba I yeah yeah I know he's G though
but I think we're just saying human to
reference any kind of human looking
form Another War
Point has it already been 5
hours already 10 p.m. huh
[Music]
isn't today Thurs
day where's my did they deliver my hello
beep
box oh what what
what why did you teleport me into a
different realm the shadow
[Music]
realm that's it you don't even have to
give me hearts for that that was just
some stupid
bats wait I just realized it's a stealth
section That was supposed to be stealth
all right um I just realized I can take
these
off
um just wear that and that I don't know
for now we don't have anything really
useful besides
that more Hearts appear and more Monster
items and whatever appear
ah okay he's back again that doesn't get
rid of
him stealth it
[Music]
is I could use the pot now but this is
pretty easy so
far is that guy on the right going to
move
somewhere well maybe maybe will'll use
the P just to make use of it also if
that guy is stationed right at
the exit I
[Music]
guess we probably have
to what
wait are you going to stay like that
okay what if
wait uh let's wait until he faces
completely opposite are you going to do
that ah maybe I've gotten Too
Close ah oh okay we're fine we're
probably fine yeah yeah yeah he's pretty
dumb wait isn't this we started out here
didn't we when we were doing prison
escape can I
I remember
[Music]
now and we were doing stal with beds
mostly cuz you could have done it back
then with
these uh pots but I did not think of
[Music]
that oh [\h__\h] oh
no I jumped it and I picked it up into
of jumping into
[Music]
it I I I can't I can't believe you
guys where's the hearts huh
Dam so do I get back to the beginning
please tell me there's a midpoint
because I went through that one section
ah
thank
you wow generous oh they heard that [\h__\h]
no no
no we don't have to do it again
[Music]
hey I can leave about
fighting
what what what's the
[Music]
point I didn't think you could use the
portal
[Music]
okay um let's just move it
silently and then get the pot and get
inside instead of lifting
it then we should be
okay just a
PO the turn around no yeah
if
but I guess I got to
quickly jump out of
it well he turns his back on me
[Music]
okay I just aart
bro bro there's no portal now
[Music]
attack nothing but a pot bro
chill why why is it because um the first
time I
used I I'm in one of
[Music]
these uh every time you're in a second
time from the same enemy maybe then
thanks for showing us all the punishment
fights you're
[Music]
welcome I'm just trying to get some exp
in this game where there is no such
thing as
exp go
away please oh now you bump into you
changing your rhythm
no is that endless cycle of me not being
able to
pass oh
no okay that's that changed their Rhythm
definitely but they're looking away now
both of
them okay that worked
out now we wait for him to pass and then
we move one of the trees
[Music]
away
okay what about him do I have to go up I
think I have to go
up I don't want to
experiment maybe going up would have
always been easier
uh what about that
[Music]
guy
maybe oh
[\h__\h] I right they uh I could break
something and make them go somewhere but
he didn't move much
huh I forgot about that they taught us
that before wait why why are these not
breaking
what are all these bats doing here
now oh
[\h__\h] uh wait more like here
please run run run run run run yippee I
think south portion should be over now
i' hope oh my break s not not mine the
one is mine wait
what
impa impa
[Music]
no we have to save her but at least
she's not dead wait did they put her
into a prison
cell you did huh how dare they that's so
disrespectful did she ride a
diary hey she's she's the one who helped
to escape from the dungeon the rift took
her too she'll be back
toah thanks for reminding me again and
again yeah I was going to read
[Music]
that after the princess escaped from the
castle I was captured by the soldiers
and thrown into a cell I was outnumbered
I did what I could but in the end I
succumbed to
them cumbers I keep hearing people
shouting find her find the princess from
the Halls which me means that she is
still safe she has not yet been found at
least I can take solace in that the
soldier spoke of a rift disappearing
being mended the princess must have
managed this yet I worry is she injured
is she overextending herself for the
sake of the Kingdom she's worrying so
much she's do
posting I am frustrated here in this
cell being unable to do anything pray
for her safety don't worry I can handle
it the castle is in an uproar could
something have happened to the princess
or could the enemy be making a move I
must find a way out of here so I can
warn the princess that seems to be
it
hey oh what that part wasn't there
before
H this is just caree about Pi possibly
so possibly quite a fitting reference
yeah a a
connection you mean hack voice is that
what you
mean
thanks
I
honey honey
[Music]
honey honey honey
what's
up
[Music]
[\h__\h] they don't give energy back they
Su can just stay so far from them wait
he doesn't even see me
[Music]
op blink
K Link Link do Zelda and Link Link so
powerful so
untouchable I don't like these being
floating
around but I don't have to find it
huh what are all these pots sing
here twool treasure
chest in exchange for fighting some
shitty bats
really is one of them a fake
one what
[Music]
pumpkin that's a funky
pumpkin oh this rain
floral nectar okay wait what about the
upper level should
I what there's threee treasure chests in
this one
[Music]
room no please
no okay monster
Stone all these treasure chests didn't
have such super special things
okay not bothering with
those all
[Music]
right no I don't really remember that
now was the first time they're asking me
to actually do that I feel like there's
other ways how I could maybe do it but
okay uh
oh it just shoots it
um H that works it just I just can't
really decide where to put it it just
shoots it wherever it lands and Bs
against is that so what about this
[Music]
one wait
yeah first time I did that well it
really isn't necessary usually
so go get him go get him come on don't
disappoint me don't disappoint
me such a
[Music]
disappointment what are you doing
you know if if only I had a chicken Echo
surely everything would be
better
what I have an
idea but well okay wait
[Music]
um like just act use
it oh my God it almost kill and then W
wart my experience wish you could kind
of like change the
angle
easier okay that's pretty
[Music]
straight good puzz
soling now you praising me after
roasting me in the steals thing thank
you what the hell is that what is that
is it Blowing Me
Away not how I blow you guys away
right doesn't again want me to use
things in a
distance I don't it's going to fly there
anyway so maybe not oh give me give me
give me give me give me give me give
[Music]
me go away go away
what does that do it didn't feel like it
was blowing me
away knock
back
[Music]
K
what okay it blows me away a little bit
so like these narrow paths are difficult
to tr to
Traverse can I cancel that out if I put
uh bring out my own but I don't know
it's kind of annoying I don't know if I
want to do that I'll just shoot
[Music]
him ah okay the wind does block the
arrows but that will not be an issue for
[Music]
me I guess I could have just like I
could have just done that and then moved
them
you guys are probably thinking that and
you're like come
on can I make that
jump pot mother ah pot
indeed I still kind of believe I can
make the J maybe even as
L
par what is
this yep some TR game to you
[Music]
huh you can Uncle them blow out them
candles wait I get
it don't die Zelda
please wait oh oh
no first of all I want to sleep but I
I'm thinking they probably want you to
put one of those things on that
platform but you can also just
shoot
him if you wantling there's so many ways
to do
it you're on speakers what did I say
something did I do something weird did I
[Music]
moan that a
buster is that a reference
to Arrested Development
[Music]
look at his flips look at link of
flexing they're
acrobatics what was the point of this
stuff what's the point ah never mind
okay I see I see I see in this case it
would be nice to use it
because you can probably push them off
yeah
you can stop now
thanks but here how would have would
have turned them off but they would
still live and not be pushed
off
[Music]
h no
stop they should make it so that it
doesn't affect
me jump why holding
one what it turns itself off though
sometimes but
[Music]
okay wait
no I can't jump it it makes me throw it
yeah ah
why you why why why why why you make me
try these
[Music]
things let's just do
beds let me look at the map by the way
we didn't miss any treasure so far right
cuz I didn't wasn't able to go here yet
W there's water there so
many mhm mhm
[Music]
apple is this
uh like these candles make me think this
is like a church within the
[Music]
castle I
now what do I do about you guys eh
where's my
[Music]
there you want the you would say I
should take the left C first
[Music]
H
Peppa will I not get anywhere here okay
can't
see I hope the enemies don't respawn
when I come
[Music]
back
yeah I have a song for Peppa yeah it's a
hello project song Too morning I think
it was was it was it was it or did they
just cover it
oh my
God okay this is flowy
water do I want to go down
[Music]
first not bobbly water pretty much same
thing I also don't like
it do you guys like the new members well
paper it were so cute you know the only
thing that I asked uh in terms of
costumes was um put one chicken into B
Arina costume and make it look really
embarrassing so that was on
me I hope you appreciate
it yeah thank you
L for
accepting was kind of late I think
already in terms
of uh
[Music]
time where am I oh wow that's
a that is quite the ridd but I'm on the
right path to the treasure
chest go for it
oh I took off with my diving
things oh
well
hey the more I look at it the more I
love it it's cute right it's I asked for
like um like a sewing machine and
everything so that it looks like I'm
making the costumes for you just like I
was thinking of you know some um what do
you call what do you call it again like
a calm neighborhood in America suburb
suburbian mom and my children are you
and the suburbian mom is making you know
all the all the costumes herself for her
kids that's basically the situation that
we're
in
yeah best
[Music]
mom yeah but the chickens weren't
supposed to really enjoy it that much
but I mean
[Music]
n Only the ballerina chicken is I guess
a bit unhappy but the others seemed
pretty happy with their costumes so
they're not embarrassed they maybe they
should be more
embarrassed even if it's a cool costume
I feel like kids would often be
embarrass about whatever their mom makes
for
them okay should I explore some more
over there or should I
just it doesn't show
anymore what is there a chance there's
something interesting
there even though doesn't show any more
treasure uh-oh run out of a
uhoh I'll go there
[Music]
anyway
okay I don't know what I think I'll be
finding but
I wish those crystals would stay
on
okay maybe that's just another path
[Music]
through
although yeah okay I already have that n
okay there was no need to
backtrack except maybe diapers diapers
is where you draw the line
but all I want for you guys is to be
able to you
know move around freely even in
environments where you're not supposed
to be pooping and peeing
everywhere cuz not everybody likes
that and chickens you
know not not well sophisticated enough
to be
using real human
toilets do you do you
know
Mom you guys
really hate
diapers is it some kind of trauma you
guys have huh what is it with the
diapers
PTSD it's humiliating
he no you look so cute and diapers why
are we another self segment
[Music]
eh I stopped early
enough no no
yes it started so early good job
good come on go
[Music]
cing unbelievable
diap for badges fifth year chicken and
[Music]
diaper I just go straight oh maybe I
can't go straight
time to
un yeah can you
[Music]
pass no no okay okay he'll forget about
me thank God
okay thank God he wasn't smart enough to
go around the corner
[Music]
okay isn't there
yeah how to what is
this why are there these
tiles I don't
[Music]
understand ignore it no chest for now
ah there's a button there all right all
right there is a button do you think
that'll react to the ground pound
machine probably
[Music]
oh God oh
God we're
fine oh
[Music]
no sorry I leaned very far back back and
sunk into my
chair are we supposed to go up
or oh I blocked this path huh I forgot
that you should just maybe do that to
make things
easier
okay another stealth section
survived can the notebook of Echoes
connect to a furniture store what are
you talking about
let me change something with the sound
[Music]
okay okay
ah ah I'm back I I went through here and
then okay that brought me
there a cuz otherwise if I would have
just swam across I would have understood
that can't go up there can I at least
not that easily maybe I could have eh
should I have was that the way back the
way that I
[Music]
took
so enemies gone enemies gone on what
[Music]
this here
first behold the power of four bits
[Music]
he I love the peaceful music every time
I become link
makes me feel like I don't need to save
link after all I can just be my own
link he doesn't need to be
[Music]
rescued climbing lots of climbing maybe
now is a good time to drink my climbing
smoothie but
ah didn't see that coming
[Music]
honestly haven't used the little spider
in a while was it this one not the other
one probably the other
one
yippe further
please oh
[Music]
okay no
no why why do you push me down why do
you hate me
[Music]
sorry what wait I don't understand what
I'm doing why did I why did that one
[Music]
disappear maybe cuz I touched
it see now now I'm doing
[Music]
fine wait a
second okay no could not have hooked uh
onto the top here unless I started the
thing from here
wa I feel like I could have skipped this
by building some beds over the
[Music]
top like couldn't I have just built like
myself some stairs here I would hope
that you wouldn't have enough
Echo uh to make enough beds otherwise
that room was
pointless oh a golden one oh [\h__\h] yeah
what is
that I changed my
wait I don't have so much link energy
otherwise I would just turn into link
[Music]
ow it's time to take a smovie
guys how
about a this doesn't give me HP
[Music]
oh I stopped moving I wonder why there
we go fixed
it I drank
one wait how how
about I feel like it's almost over but
I'm going to drink
this yeah to fight
this there we
go but finishing it as link Zelda makes
it a little
bit easier and faster less
painless wow ball and chain
Trooper okay that's a stupid
name come up with something more
interesting like dark
nut oh room to the left aha aha
aha how to get to this room dig maybe
from above to go down
masi a frogy we can jump more with this
oh I sto moving
again we can jump higher with this
that's so
cute
frog this egg Frogg and egg hey that's
literally
like telling you about Wawa and froggy
Wawa
[Music]
is that higher I guess that should be
now as high as link can jump and then
while I wear it link can probably jump
higher too
[Music]
hope this room is M for me and a key
frog egg key Ada frog key Ada FR wow wow
wow wow
wow basically if you play an A game
if this was an AC the game if we mix
these free items in a
um what the word the the the
pot what would come out is
me these threee
items so
true a cauldron not a blender a
cauldron come on now wait is
[Music]
it well first of all I just realized why
can't we already go to the master that's
kind of short but then now I'm wondering
like how to get there but since this is
the sand
room uh I'm thinking to dig my way
through the sand and see where that
leads me especially if I dig like close
ah wait there's
a I didn't see that I like my idea
more H just hold
it it's the right height and it doesn't
hurt me oh
[Music]
oop I expected money maybe some more
money in
here
Apple I've seen better treasure rooms
honestly hyu family kind of
[Music]
[\h__\h] kind
of greedy
that can't be the real treasure room
kind of
mid
NGL
so is that
it seems kind of small kind of short
maybe that's just because I sped through
it what would you say guys would you say
that was short
yeah seems to be boss time unless I mean
maybe that's not the end of the dungeon
maybe we fight Link and then there's
another weird section that we didn't
know about and then what wa this G on
music that that wasn't throughout the
whole dungeon was
[Music]
it maybe just since I have the master
key right I think the music changes when
you have the master
[Music]
key will we fight Link again I think
yeah fly leaf is my
goto okay it's king and the other
imposters
oh my dear daughter you have done well
to make it
here you've worked tirelessly toand
quite a few
Rifts I find that
vexing so I'll put an end to you I'll
use my Monster's power to be rid of you
once in
all whoa what the
hell what you become one big monster who
wields that I assume
how
big a big like Soldier yeah that's oh
wait Ganon
[Music]
Ganon it's that blue monster I thought
link defeated
it no that isn't the same monster defe
it the power used to create this monster
is the same as the power we used to
create
Echoes this monster is an echo
[\h__\h] I'm not some kind of echo I'm G
The Demon King who Reigns over the
darkness of this
world no one can defeat
me crumble to dust in the wake of my
dark
[Music]
power speed
what's G on
really you but the heart is wasted you
[\h__\h] idiot now when I need them there
won't be any hearts on this
field ow ow ow ow ow let me get the
heart
[Music]
really giving a lot of openings but what
if I run out of energy
huh what
[Music]
then
ow that just another weird opening he
gives
me oh Phoenix said no okay um I'm
burning
no energy is energy should I just yeah
refill it what if I didn't have anything
to refill I'd be kind of
[\h__\h] that's not much but let's drink
that
wait w
[Music]
okay okay okay where did that come
from
oh I I I keep on forgetting to turn a
[Music]
lot no we can
probably oh
sorry happy count
turkey feel fre to destroy one of those
thank
you okay good energy good energy good
[Music]
energy no just a little bit you just
needed a little bit more then I could
have opened the pot without having to
lift the finger there we go
[Music]
okay round two round three actually I
think wait
[Music]
I'm scar
no tennis what am I supposed to play
tennis with
[Music]
him
how
how how
no with his um with Link's Shield or by
hitting it I guess okay
okay
ow right that's I mean that's a thing in
every Zelda game somehow I didn't think
about
[Music]
it ow
just like when I was a
[Music]
teenager what if I turn back right now
ah no I
going I can't do this now bro
I can't do this
now
all yeah give me the birds cuz I think
the birds spawn the enemy
[Music]
oh just one more hit is all it
took till the next
[Music]
B are we going to do the same thing
yeah I can't give me a break
bro I can't no give me Birds give me
Birds this is not
enough does he do one more
time like one more often than usual
Now give me
Birds no give me
Birds I don't have I don't have any give
me Birds give me Birds give me Birds
give me
[Music]
Birds what wait
that would have been so easy for him to
[Music]
dodge that would have been so easy for
him to
Dodge thank
you thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you one hit one
hit give me energy I need HS
bro oh look up fire
bird oh I could have I could drink but
it's like man I guess okay no hoarding
no hoarding H okay wait wait
wa oh no oh no [\h__\h]
[Music]
thanks for the
rain you just a witnessed to sorry a big
spoiler you just witnessed a gun on
fight not the end of the game don't
worry by far not the end of the
game but an interesting time to raid for
sure Mama
Mia that was a a nice tennis
game G game shocking I know right yeah
we're very far from even the middle
apparently this game is pretty long huh
now if much love to you you're so sweet
you're like a very
mature um adult version of OE if you
think about it it's like you're so w
look at this Glory you're so supportive
and like everywhere and chatty right but
you you don't like you know you're not
not
like not like OE was like oh my God
Senai you're like oh my God Senpai thank
you
right it's
like relaxing support yeah Ollie I love
it I love I love just generally people
like you and Ollie it's so wholesome
sharing all that love and support and
those sweet words and no it's not C it's
not catch St I love Olie for who she is
and I love herb for who she is it's just
different types of
support a more mature support and a more
energetic gy
support Hol red love oh you know what
Ollie and Herb should do a
stream where they just
like what's the word uh what's the word
what's the right
word not yet simp yeah gush gsh that's
what I was looking for a gushing stream
fangirling
stream you like my I know you were
listening the whole time you're so
sweet the freak what what do you think
about it a gushing fangirling stream but
like specifically over I don't know
whole life songs whole life members
whole life
streams can you imagine imine a watch
along of like any kind of concert or
like Frey debut or anything like that
like a big stream and the watchong
watchong is um hosted by Ollie and
Herb
[Music]
a s
cast you want to watch long past
concerts you want to really we got to
get those
Blu-rays M oh
also we got to bring like risu and Herb
together oh my God wait oh my God now
I'm like oh I'm looking forward to the
future because like you know how lisu
blows everybody away with her singing
every freaking fest
concert now it's not going to beisu uh
alone anymore I mean there's always
people blowing people away but Arisa is
always like like people should people
should know by now that she's a great
singer but somehow she
still manages to surprise everybody with
it every
time imagine like a followup a set list
with like I don't know luu and then
after her herb and then after her Su say
we're going to
die her new tune yeah yeah yeah I think
that song uh it just recently got its
music video but it has been uh performed
in last
Fest um this year
in March so there's a life performance
of it uh is that Blue-ray already out
probably
right so one could look back on it right
that was in the last F right Lis sang it
there I think oh yeah isisa there Isa
too
ooh ooh o I hope one day they're going
to have a unit song either in Ian
concert or in the Japanese fist where
the unit consists
of nerissa and Herb we have other great
singers but I think nerissa and Herb's
voices will be really nice together and
they just like visually compliment each
other so
much
yes
yes blood
Raven where are my comedians yeah what
the hell we're getting more and more
great singers our our
comedian uh
what's the word the roof roof in
German we won't be known as comedians
anymore want to sing with it would be an
honor yeah I mean yeah of course
like reputation yeah not only singers
joined yes surely there were some
comedians joined too but there's just so
many powerful singers man
yeah more than make up for the comedy
part I guess so if you see it like that
[Music]
oh man that
name that's like maybe one of the best
or
worst uh Duo names I think it's quite
good it's quite good
both the best worst
name I love it anyway what let me change
my ghon voice back to my tree
voice uhuh uhuh my friends shared some
of their power with me see herb I can
voice act too this is all coming from my
throat I'm doing
this can you do this kind of place H
with Reverb natural Reverb in my voice
can you do
this I want to
see try to Top
This my friends shared some of their
power with
[Music]
[Applause]
me I feel like I can do even more now
really really more of that just removing
the
cost I don't
know I don't
know be me I
I'm it's not too bad yeah but
like out of all of
these I don't even use any of these that
commonly U maybe the new golden Knight
sometimes I will use maybe like getting
the golden Knight and then immedately
having a a discount is nice but I still
don't have a discount on my most used
enemy fly leaf yeah still nothing on
that
one try K but when you say katos you're
probably thinking of someone else I'm
thinking of katos from Tales of
Symphonia but I wouldn't even know his
voice
what does it sound like I don't
know y fly leave please come on my lawn
lawn
mower yeah you're thinking of God of War
huh turbo lawnmower so all of reach so
sad anyway we got five crystals maybe
now they will let us upgrade again
probably cuz we proceeded in the
story so that blue monster was an echo
yeah and I don't seem to be able to
learn it
no I wonder if that means there's
something else capable of using the same
power I do you think all the monsters
that have been capturing me and my
friends were Echo too I don't know what
kind of questions are you asking me I I
don't know the answer to this it's all
pretty confusing right now I'm sorry I
don't know more Zelda I'm just a
lemon stop bullying me I want to figure
it out but you're comes first with the
rift gone he should be safe now so let's
get out of here now
y will he really be back I hope so
there's no weird twist right don't get
it twisted but we got another heart
container let's
[Music]
go cute
my okay wa I want to look at this a
little bit
this
part outside of the rift what is this
normally I wonder this
[Music]
room let's go to
Daddy oh
what I was literally just looking at
that what the [\h__\h] is
that link really link he's sping in the
shadow room
s with a
[\h__\h] wooden B stick while I'm
leaving no wait Happ to
no why didn't I like press cancel on my
thing on me flying
away ah
bro yeah that was a really real
protecting me in a way a good that he's
what does that remind me of what movie
or anime or
game like kind of what do
that what what does that remind me of
fighting like getting sent to
this Shadow realm and fighting really
weakly in it in that shadow realm feel
like I've had that before somewhere no
no no no not Yu-Gi-Oh not ff16 not ji
[Music]
no
h what could I be thinking of not
Yu-Gi-Oh I don't play or watch
Yu-Gi-Oh I also didn't play Kingdom
Hearts
Never Never play Kingdom
Hearts this is the one time you you guys
are not guessing what I'm thinking of
even in its
vagueness magic why
magic wasn't there something like this
in rise up was there I don't think
that's what I'm thinking of should make
go
Bei yeah that's also not it I give a
very usually I give you guys a vague ass
description even more vague than
this sometimes I just say oh no uh I'm
thinking of this game I played when I
was a child and all that's that that's
all I have to say and you already know
what I
[Music]
mean yeah we're not on the same
wavelength
today this one is more vake than usual
no that's not true T Rock I don't know I
don't think so whatever
anyway did he get captured or something
what should we do
Zelda oh oh man
welcome back Santa
[Music]
Claus where am I the castle Everything
feels
hazy oh I recall it now I was B into a
rift oh my dear daughter you saved me
thank
you we can't actually read your mind
after 4 years you
can't what have we been doing this for
all this time eh I've been training you
guys for what what has happened to
theing to my kingdom in my
[Music]
offence I see you have put your own
safety at risk you've done so to protect
our people to save
hu we've done two dungeons today and
some extra stuff damn 6 hours I p.m.
feel like I could play for another 10
hours honestly
but tell up my Brave and sess self
selfless daughter I'm so very very proud
of you well
done oh you
mesty are you all
right help Intruder me stop it
now stand down soldiers have a closer
look it is my daughter Zelda
oh now you don't think I'm an impostor
or something or that the king is an
impostor or
anything now I can really get you to
believe me so easily 12
hour I crony and I talked a little bit
of about tunic T niic yeah yeah yeah I
told her
oh yeah she she told me she's going to
finish it or try to finish it soon I
asked her where she is and she's still
she not quite at the end I guess I don't
know but I told her be careful at the
end it might get frustrating there might
there you know there's some difficult
bosses here and there but especially at
the end I barely remember but I think it
was rough yeah and the golden path I
told her there's something like a golden
path and it will make you insane but it
will be worth it do
it yeah I'm so happy that she likes the
game someone else who appreciates the
greatness of tuning
[Music]
but felt it was worth it I don't know
it's been so long that all my trauma has
kind
of just
yeah I don't know what happened to it I
don't remember it
anymore but also maybe the golden path
wouldn't have been so bad if I wasn't
like already eight or 9 hours in to the
game on that day that stream was already
so
long maybe it wouldn't have been so bad
if I was in the beginning of the stream
or
so you converted me to tunic and I've
evangelized EV what do you mean I
converted you to tunic to like in tunic
or
what it was super
late but princess Ella was one creating
the roofs wasn't she
wello my daughter creating the Rifts
what the [\h__\h] are you talking about it
seems to imposter posing as me has
spread some damaging untruth that you
guys just so easily
believed dumb [\h__\h] I'll clear up the
misunderstandings please go rest for now
my standing Corner you've done well
thank you
Zelda thank you thank you for thanking
me now I can get my bed yeah and my cat
is
back impa oh my God I wonder if my cat
after coming back from the dark silent
world has been affected by it
somehow I hope not wa I need a cracker
I'm getting
[Music]
hungry there was a lot of cracker I
pushed a whole cracker in
[Music]
I chewed
it I'm enjoy the game of
course the only download game I probably
didn't enjoy too much was um not wind um
oh motion
[Music]
control Skyward Sword yeah but I mean I
wouldn't say I hated
it what was my writing of it in the end
I
wonder it was just like rage so much
Rage with the [\h__\h] motion control but
the game itself was
fine but oh my God remember all the
times we had to go into this [\h__\h]
hole in the ground
and had to like you know the the Chase
from the thing with with the nail or
whatever that
was how many times would we have to do
that [\h__\h] it was so
annoying yeah they imprisoned boning him
back the demise that was that was just
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah the seal
mhm that was like my worst memory of it
besides the boss fight but the boss
fight is just that just sucked because I
was tired and all that and
stressed but the demise was really [\h__\h]
no matter what state of mind I am
[Music]
in ah the demise at the
end oh wait I'm thinking about the was
that not called demise cuz you guys were
saying
demise that seal is that also the demise
I don't know but the boss fight yeah
when when your motion controls are
stupid then you're
doomed it's just
salt the imprisoned my he is also
demise
mhm thinking back about that oh my god
oh so bad
but I mean it seems like they really
improved their games since
then oh that was more like a onetime
thing sometimes some games they just you
don't know what happened but the
recently the recent Sal the games in the
past years have all been decent um no
big huge like fuckups like that
[Music]
you think Skyward Sword is better than
bre of the Wild
what
what hot take that's a hot
take oh wait you're just saying that
because of motion controls maybe because
you're in
motion are you just saying that for the
joke crazy
kind of crazy T
princess I'm sure it was better in t
princess I had it but I didn't really
play it cuz it was too
scary skywood sword have actual dungeons
birth of the wild have only one dungeon
copy pass I
mean I don't think it was that bad I
mean people also seem to complain about
it not being classic dungeons but I mean
it's to me it still felt like a dungeon
and I didn't play it but I watched four
full 100% playthroughs of it including
all of the
Crocs CS so it's basically like I played
the game
basically so yeah I don't
know I wouldn't criticize it like
that no I played it shut up I played it
by watching it like four
times if not even maybe even
five the hardcore one too like a normal
one 100% And then a hardcore one 100%
except for the I think only for the
first one the normal one only then the
coks were fully
[Music]
included I I lived through with for Vi
cariously
duh I played it
yeah Master T I find it interesting that
I can see you now where I was not able
to do
before and I know that the princess has
been safe because she's had you as her
guide so now that I can see you I can
say this to your face thank you for
everything wa this is
emotional motion
mention I've been wondering for a while
what the I hate this Trope where there's
characters who speak the English
language or whatever so fluently but
then they don't know these like stupid
specific words like what does a you
mean really
such a stupid
Trum what does love mean what is
love so
often for
real such a stupid TR man I can't
[Music]
even everyone keeps saying thank you to
S
them oh my God I can't
oh well it's an expression of gratitude
which makes me really wonder why you
understand English so well but you don't
know what this means kind of weird well
I've been both happy and relieved that
you have aided the princess so to
express that feeling of gratitude I say
thank
[Music]
you I'm only helping Zelda selfishly so
that I can become a big lemon again but
I'm glad you're for
helping already waking up then
[Music]
princess is this a
butterfly you are here well I'm glad to
see
it tree told us everything about
us Oh you mean
the you mean you the king and someone
okay
about how you faced extreme evil putting
yourself in Peril all to save us to save
your kingdom this feels like the end of
the
[Music]
game but wait link we could just n
honestly you could end the game here you
could be like H who cares if link is
still in there
whatever I literally just forgot about
him even though I saw him 5 minutes ago
you pushed yourself princess but you are
safe now I think about how small you
once were the baby and I look at you now
oh how you have
grown there I go getting myself all
worked up again oh I'm so very Overjoyed
to see you again princess well my
apologies for disturbing you so soon
after waking but I bring a message from
the King he requests you to come to the
throne
room once you fully rested I will go on
ahead we be
waiting I kind of want to hear what K
who listen to streams as of the story
based on Creative I don't even do it
that often I don't even change the
dialogue that
often I feel like you would still get
like an accurate idea of it
yeah I know I know about the bed you
don't have to tell me I've been telling
you
guys I want to learn the cat
[Music]
guys you
bit wow
fancy oh [\h__\h] takes free I need a
discount on that
one pet the C I can't I
can oh it's so
bright being a lemon is Canon
yeah non Canon gon non Canon gon non
Canon Canon is non Canon gon show up
hello are you here we're playing a game
of Canon and he's somewhat Canon where
is non Canon Canon I always have to
think of non- Canon Canon when I there
you are
yipp yi yipp yi I always love when you
guys' names like just mean
something that I can connect with
something
else non Canon Canon
y yeah I just needed I just needed to
make sure that you're here good good
good good good
good my name never comes up space
waterful honestly that can definitely
honestly we've already like if you the
the silent World kind of is like space
and there's we've seen some waterfalls
there actually already showed
up oh T I trust you got some rest now
then we're all
here it is time for us to discuss the
next steps Trey informed us earli about
what is occurring in Hyrule through your
hard work and determination the lar have
been tended to like chicken tenders so
peace has not been restored to hyu there
is work yet to be
[Music]
done oh now they can all hear her right
the gon we thought beneath the castle
was an echo he was created so it's
possible that the monsters that captured
my friends were also Echo like Ganon but
are you saying that there's no real
Ganon but maybe all those were created
by a big real G I don't know
initially I DED that everything had been
at the hands of that monster Canon that
following Link's defeat of Canon we were
seeing the after effects Adobe After
Effects not sponsored of their battle
but three you believe we may have been
facing a different enemy all
along link saved El from this mysterious
fo but and Link was captured oh link I
hope you're
safe youy
the gun we met along the way with no
counton gun all
along never mind you wanted to say the
same thing L are opening up all across
high again oh not again three of them at
once this time probably at the top of
the map where you haven't explored
yet no why are these Rifts appearing as
I just said at the top of the map where
you haven't explored yet like alen
volcano far and Redlands and holy mount
lanaire
considering those locations and it could
be what what what is it
s those Regents connect directly with
the Prime energy
what with the what
now the Prime energy a source of power
beyond our understanding left behind by
the goddesses the knowledge of its
existence has been passed down for the
royal family since long ago but I forgot
to tell Zelda I for those three raes
connect to the free goddesses and in
turn to the Prime
energy Metroid Prime
[Music]
spoiler totally not tree Force why they
just like
oh oh wait if you didn't say that I
wouldn't have expected that but it makes
sense yeah I mean of course we're going
to see number tree Force M it's just
still the Rifts are targeting those
areas very
specifically this my mean the RS are
natural occurrences but are being
created by someone that's impossible all
these voes are very similar huh but then
if that's true the Prime energy could
end up with the
Enemy oh there are yet more Legends R
Shadow Legends passed down by the worldy
family of IAL when evil stries for the
Prime energy a wise Priestess and a
courageous hero will appear together
together the priestes and the hero will
rent this evil asunder probably with
some really light glowy arrows I don't
know maybe light arrows whatever you
call them our Priestess and a hero oh oh
that was
him Zelda has gotten rid of many RS
could Zelda be the Priestess of the
legend the Legend of Zelda and Y
she must be but then who is this
[Music]
hero wow he actually guesses it perhaps
it is a swordsman
link come to fera mentioned that link
able to move even while in the still
World he's also been fighting the enemy
all on his own seems like he has plot
armor if link is the hero then that
means both the Priestess and the hero
have indeed appeared so Fox
no we're not [\h__\h] that's a good sign
Well's been captured by the
enemy Zelda meant the free Rifts in the
regions collected to the goddesses this
will
FL our
enemy in order to stop the enemy
completely however you must do even more
than that you have to find the hero link
and the two of you must join forces and
bet not fighting together my daughter I
would not approve of such a thing anyway
yet I've only never wished for a
peaceful life for
you but it seems that fate has other
plans you are the Priestess of Legend
the hope of hyu I'm just trying really
carefully not to say the title because
if I do that the credits will roll and
the game will be
over we will do everything in our power
to support you on this most dire Journey
but we will stay of course in the castle
where it is shav and coffee while you
goow out in the world duh
Minister laughter you are to continue
working with lber monitoring the Rifts
General R lead your soldiers to contend
with the monsters across hyu but Zelda
will still have to end up fighting them
all anyway on her own it will be like as
almost almost as if you didn't
exist
okay time provide Zelda with the
garments
garments wait I can take my Cape off now
huh I can but will
I I won't do so with Hast TI fresh drip
let's
go come with me
[Music]
princess please give me new
Tri oh
cute I got ponytail now I those pink
pants wow those are puffy
pants is this like I mean that looks
very similar to other outfits she's worn
but I don't think she had this type of
uh tuni car with uh these coffee pants
before is
she she confirmed what
why yeah it's very similar to a green of
time outfit is
it the fan out of her new outfit is so
good really I have I don't think I've
seen
any but yeah she had her hair open last
time she wore something like these in
previous games with the pink
[Music]
tunic but cute although I lik her bun
too but it works better with the
ponytail here these are your ancestral
vestments passed down for the royal
family they will be perfect for your
needs as you continue on your
quest I imagine the enemy's ultimate aim
is to obtain the Prime energy we do not
yet know the enemy's true nature but I
fear that hyrel is in grave danger as a
leader of H will and the prestes of
Legend please do what you must to
protect your
kingdom this is a perfect spot to end
for today
huh look at
me look at
me I want to see again there's no like
good look at me
it is time oh you have a side quest for
[Music]
me pass ah you've been raising me in Ste
ah ah okay so we didn't do this but if
you talk to the um in in the in the if
you try to get the White Horse over
there in the thing in the farm they tell
you that this is the only horse you
can't get because uh someone's been take
uh like putting it in their care or so
uh that that's the one
[Music]
I thank you you've been you've been
doing that for me thank
you and then with that horse we can do
that little
game oh
wonderful wonderful indeed
wonderful that was fun I can't wait to
play more guys
am I in the middle of the game now
that's so
sad
man I do want to make sure that I do all
side quests in this game because there's
not that many and I do want to stretch
it out more so let me know if I ever
miss any
quests just five more hours don't tell
don't say that that's not
true there's new quest in some of the
towns oh okay we got to check through
that for
sure you can get a new outfit on the
mango game now to a new
outfit new
outfit to replace what I'm raring
now these Quest are different as it's
Del
oh check your room oh my
God what what's in my room now I just
came from
there maybe my old outfit hung up no
wait uh what there's nothing
[Music]
new but I mean I mean I think we saw
that portrait before and looked at it
for a moment but yeah it's
uh wait but so is that an ancestor of me
and not
me I can get up
here cuz like I'm wearing this for the
first time cuz he explained it to me so
that's not even
me bro no one tell her yet what
something about the cat
huh what is it what is it wait my my
horse is there
too so many spoilers
[Music]
bro what my
mommy mommy is that what you weren't
supposed to tell
me it's okay we don't we don't even
[Music]
know no
no there's no secret up
there okay no
[Music]
I will kill
you just spoiling me
no can't be true can't be
true
no
no I hate
you I hate you I hate
[Music]
you well well well did I save already
double save
[Music]
baby
so this game is so cute I know he's so
good more but my throat starting to hurt
or like already hurts from all these
voices a little bit H it's already late
I need to cook the food uh tomorrow will
be on l
channel for an
italio italio
lesson so much fun Dela game so good I
love Dela
[Music]
game like I like I like I like
[Applause]
man was a good good stream good day good
mood I appreciate you guys watching
and had a good
[Music]
time wait it's sitting on my head was it
always sitting on my head when I stand
still for too
long
cute don't get too close to me I'll eat
[Music]
you you had a good time too yeah more
collapse of Mario who what I'm a big fan
of those ears yeah huh
[Music]
really don't you have like these kind of
elf ears too I think you do don't
you the ear talk reminds me I just saw
something today cuz I I didn't
know I watched the Steven Co bear video
from like literally today or last night
or so and and he said he made a
joke about uh a
bear uh like there's some kind of bear
event and then the bear has like [\h__\h]
up ears that's why it was named after
Cole bear and then he shows and points
out his ears that one of his ears is
normal and the other one is not
normal and and now that she showed it
I'm like all right it's actually not
normal but I never noticed until
now colar step coar has one ear that's
like uh I don't know
they don't zoom in so it's hard to see
but it's different from his other ear he
usually keeps his head turned one way so
you don't notice it honestly like I I
watched a lot of cobbert videos in the
past and I never
noticed H but now now I can't un see
it why did he mention
it I remember people mentioning it like
15 years ago H I never knew
yeah I mean there's no issue with it but
I'm just surprised I never noticed cuz I
mean that's a I guess that just means
it's not that noticeable and not that
obvious until you know it
yeah he's def inite
huh oh that sucks you always got to like
oh man I know sometimes when one of my
ears gets kind of clogged up and I can't
hear always kind to like oh that's so
[\h__\h] that's
rough not hearing in one ear that's so
unbalanced you want to always
like turn the other way please speak to
me on my other ear thank
you
[Applause]
man how I never no this
right what that's so silly that man I
they name the [\h__\h] bear after him
because of like a messed up Ear
oh man but he's joking about it I hope
he doesn't mind I mean he's old enough
to probably just have no issues with it
[Music]
anymore but I want to assume that just
because you grow older doesn't mean that
all your
insecurities uh go away but I would also
I don't know I feel like he probably
chill about
it but I feel like I'll never grow out
of my insecurities
H he's definitely self-conscious about
it well he did joke about it but then
again I don't know that doesn't
necessarily I I joke about things that
I'm self-conscious of ah depends some
things that like things that I'm super
self-conscious about I don't ever want
to talk about just to hope that people
will not like pay attention to it but
other things that I'm self-conscious
about maybe if it's not too bad I'll
joke about it but I still don't like the
fact of it like I joked about you know
my clock reading
skills I'm self-conscious about that but
now I'm making a joke out of it because
I'm an
Entertainer yeah when other yeah when
other people joke about it it hurts like
you can joke about it but then even
others joke about it m but he's he's
probably okay right he seems very chill
and
yeah I've made peace with my shortcom
that's great I'm sure whatever you think
your shortcomings are others might not
even see his shortcomings
anyway can't read out loud very well
because of my dyslexia so many people
have
dyslexia
[Music]
crazy talking about stepen be reminds me
I watched this whole deep dive about H
what are they called again some other
two late night talk show hosts one who
completely stopped now but had this like
legendary well-known show and then the
guy you guys probably know when I st
explaining yeah yeah Jay Leno and Conan
where Conan replaced him once but then
Jay Leno was so salty about it and kind
of got him got Conan to quit on his own
uh again like this whole messy story
that was quite
interesting I didn't know anything about
that because I was I don't know how old
I must have been but I surely was too
young to pay attention to American late
night shows at the
time you watched it too are we watching
the same channel huh I like that channel
it has really good deep Dives but but
the way he talks it pisses me off after
a while watching a few videos is fine
but then more and more you watch that
guy the way he talks oh my God it's
so for example he will he will say
things like this uh but it's Hollywood
drama so don't worry about not being a
were lol jeno has cool a lot of cool
cars it wasn't even that long ago yeah
remember
that every sentence yeah Patrick CCE
that's the channel late night talk shows
are a thing of the past I [\h__\h] hate
that t of voice
lall no matter no matter what the like
atmosphere of the the
sentences and this will go on for one
and a half hours or so if the
documentary is on the longer
side clock or not clock or not I think
it's cool you can get thousands of
people to watch you and you make a lot
of people happy you really built a
strong name what clock not Oh I thought
you word kind of lowkey talking about
crony and I was like why are you wrong
chat or what you mean the time rating
thank you thank you thank you thank
thank you yeah something like that he
kind of has weird
inflections I'm sure he can read
normally H or speak normally but when he
reads off of his script for his videos
that's just how he thinks he should talk
the whole time
[Music]
no don't talk don't someone talk like
that to wa during the next meet and
grade no
don't you like it when I do it wait now
I I can't I can't 100% recreate
[Music]
it yeah it's monotone and
rhythmic I feel like it
appeals for a certain amount of videos
but once you watch too many of them the
more you notice it like you become too
aware of it you focus on it and then
it's just really
annoying but it's like how a lot of
people talk in their like YouTube shorts
or Tik toks or whatever kind of similar
when people are like explaining things
and [\h__\h] but that's short ass videos for
that it's kind of fine for like over 1
Hour
[Music]
[Applause]
videos I don't know not every sentence
has to be like that makes sense some
normal inflection inflictions what
in but yeah BL blah BL
[Music]
o I got a a Holo B
submission been getting I have I think I
have two now I gave them like a
deadline uh which is not that close
anyway so they still have time but some
some are early
I appreciate
[Music]
it is there anyone who a never mind
okay all right all
right you guys are
[Music]
anyone but you're not just anyone of
course I'm not talking to you
guys you're not just
anybody
Riz That was supposed to be
Riz do you feel
[Music]
it
guys oh my God we're so close actually
holy
[\h__\h] to my 3D live oh I got to put out
an announcement do you want to I'm just
going to put out another obvious
one do you want to be part here I'll
I'll I'll make one now while I'm on
stream let's
see it's just going to be another
obvious
one I don't have that much time left I
got to start doing the not so obvious
ones
soon next announcement number
[Music]
three ah okay let's do this one because
that one's obvious and I have a a two
two people
selfie not
[Music]
selfie too bad these kind of spoiler the
stage design a little bit but whatever
I'm probably more cautious about like
worried about that but there's really no
point in being worried anyway anyway I
guess okay this one
perhaps I'll cut it a little bit into a
square so that you don't see too
much but I'm not using the um
Holan stage as a base this time maybe
you
no yeah if you look at it you would
probably notice um but yeah last time I
used the whole English stage as a
base um but I I really wanted to use a
stage that has like a middle stage cuz
the whole life English stage actually
has a lot of things that don't even
function properly like those middle
stages that go up uh they still glitch
out to this day so it's like we have to
choose the angles wisely angles that
don't show the uh bottom of the stages
the ones that go up and stuff like that
and you can't
show ah the first time I used it I think
during my Fredy deut we couldn't use the
function of them like going up in the
first
place so yeah it's it's
like you know and I really wanted to
have this like middle path the runway so
I'm using the Japanese stage this
time yeah we can use any stage we want
want I could even use the ID stage if I
wanted
to okay guess
[Music]
announcement wait get let me just
I want to get the buy
Mark there we
[Music]
go
uhhuh uh
what should I write in the
[Music]
comment
right I don't
know uh
oh wait you don't know yet what uh
so I got Conan as a
guest is nice
right no it's not it's I'm not no I'm
not
[Music]
okay
oh wait I'm quoting the wrong
[Music]
post need to quote the main
post and then put in the picture and
then drop
it here we
go zoom in a little bit there we go okay
are you ready it's going to be such a
surprise wow such a big surprise you'll
be blown away
[Music]
guys 3 do one
ala
what
OMG but there's a little bit of a
spoiler in the uh
cap
[Music]
so yeah first Japanese member
H but you probably don't recognize any
more Japanese member in The Invisible
roow so it must be somebody sitting down
right but you cannot really
tell you can't really
tell the second row is really hard to
tell too bad was
my game is on that's
[Music]
fine but I'm going to do at least this
yeah oh my switch time is kind of wrong
but close
enough you didn't expect more Japanese
members sick sick yeah yeah I got to say
this live uh was pretty damn cursed I
had so many things go wrong song songs
had to be changed members had to be
changed
uh everything was yeah
rough
uh yeah I'm like coros some coros I I
really wanted to learn them like earlier
but some of them had to be super last
minute like on the last couple of days
before the
recording
so this one was really
[Music]
first like there was one song that I
planned to do that wasn't like it was it
was going to be a cover song but it
wasn't released yet and that was also
like a bit of a problem because it kept
them getting delayed
mhm so then at some point the the staff
was like H we maybe should replace this
song and I was like yeah I
guess yeah
because like if it gets delayed so much
that it would be released after my Frey
life that would be a problem because
then I would have to cut the whole
segment out of my life and then it you
know it would be missing a
song
yeah yeah ah there were a lot of issues
a lot of issues this time it really felt
so cursed and stressed
ful but it's finished the product is
finished I have the opening too all I'm
all I'm missing is the ending but I'm
going to put up the ending as a members
only content
because with the opening it's already uh
like an hour and maybe two or 3
minutes
or maybe an hour and 1 minute I don't
know and then I'm adding of course like
a normal w loading screen a little
bit yeah yeah yeah like there's an intro
not a did I say loading so there will
there will be the typical lava loading
maybe for two or three minutes or so and
then there'll be the intro which is also
a couple minutes and then there'll be
the live which is pretty long on its own
so I'm excited
[Music]
yeah so hyped me too me
too
yeah so many k for give that membership
so more people yeah yeah I wish I could
do like a members only whole like
concert section as well but really it's
so difficult unless you do it live if
you do it live
then you can really do a lot more songs
and all that just in one
go but yeah sadly having it pre-recorded
will ensure a lot of
quality but it will like yeah a lot of a
lot of the time will be sacrificed of
recording time will be
sacrificed maybe one day I'll do like
some live sections we'll
see but you usually it's always like
kind of assumed
uh seemingly like they just assume um
that I'm going to just do it pre-record
it and not be there uh you know for a
live section which I'm fine with that
I'm very fine with that I don't mind I
prefer it this
way it's a choice though like it's a
it's a choice but I don't
know maybe one day h
yeah so okay I'm going to uh see you the
day after tomorrow on my channel again
for my uh I'm not going to read CH today
W to want to go now why I want to go why
I want to go but W I also want to play
more
zela but W I have to wait for zela
I have to wait one more day one more
Dela I was I was kind of even
considering
um like put putting this stream one day
early yesterday when I woke up I was
like I want to play Dela maybe I'm maybe
today day off and yesterday Zelda but I
resisted because you guys would have not
gotten
much uh ahead of time
notice but I really like and I really
enjoy it so far it's really fun and now
that zala has got new drip and I'm kind
of feeling refreshed even like
wow yeah and we freed all the hyru
castle people as a big step I thought
that would be at the end honestly I'm
surprised we did that now um but now
we'll we'll check out the north of the
map wherever it takes us the day after
the yeah the day after tomorrow so hope
you'll be there make sure to catch up if
you are behind now or if you're like
around the same make sure to get ahead
of me quite a bit maybe two dungeons I
would recommend cuz it seems like I can
always do like two dungeons per stream
pretty much quite
easily yeah good stuff good
stuff or one and a half
depends are you ride to the north yeah
oh oh my
God I could watch the last episode of oh
now oh
[\h__\h] oh
God I don't know if I'm ready for it
mentally because that's that that will
be the end of it for a long time again
[Music]
no I'm excited you guys are not so
excited and that's okay except for the
three people or so that have been
watching it
too how long was it between this season
and the one before I want
minimum a
year how long was it maybe one and a
half I'm curious
too the season is so good it's actually
good yeah thank you make those people
doubt
themselves going to watch it right now
let's go two years it's was it two full
years you watched the last episode last
night let's go did you like it 2 years
oh my god
well I'm still waiting for another
umbrella Academy not no that that's not
the one I mean uh Wednesday cuz Umbrella
Academy just happened still waiting for
a new Wednesday and a new one Piece
season so next year I'm surprised they
still didn't do a new Wednesday season
maybe 2025 we'll have Wednesday and uh
one piece and uh I wonder if Wheel of
Time could be possible 2025 maybe end of
2025 a new Wheel of Time season
they took quite a long time with the
most recent one and then Witcher Witcher
right I mean people are not looking
forward to it but
Witcher when is Witcher going to
[Music]
happen oh a Yakuza show in October you
mean 2025 October
right her taste is still
affective you little [\h__\h] which is not
cancelled what this year end of
October what where is it on not Netflix
right may still be okay but yeah not
going to be good well they're definitely
not following the books anymore it seems
from what you guys
say Amazon oh okay cool cool cool
cool so yeah there'll be enough to like
lead up to the next season of things but
everything takes so much time people
their special effects man they can't get
enough
event a Warhammer 40K series what was
that have you watched shun shun is so
weird it was so good and then somehow I
was
interrupted to watch it because like I
had no time anymore and now I just can't
get back into it
but I'm like missing only two episodes
or so Henry Cavill is working on it
what yeah I really liked it I should
just finish it honestly
maybe maybe after I finish rings of
power like one of these days I'll finish
shun I'm sorry I know shun is really
good it's really
good Oh you mean he left Witcher for
what that's what you mean with working
on it oh h
M I'm sorry I just kind of moved on from
it because like I got too busy I had no
time to watch it because I was like when
I went to Japan and all that I had no
time to watch it I was always tired when
I had time to do anything I was just
tired I needed to sleep and then I just
got over it I just didn't think about it
anymore what
happens I'm not actually watching those
shows yo I'm just falling asleep to them
like immediately when I turn on the
office or anything like
that give some time to Anin son okay
okay okay okay I will I will that last
episode that I watched it was just
shocking that was just [\h__\h]
up that the one thing that traumatized
me the one thing you know what I mean
the thing with the like where they uh
you know they un alived
yeah because someone touched the bird
that was so [\h__\h] up yo can't go back
to that anymore can't go back to it
anymore after witnessing
that don't touch bird or you
die rough man rough important to learn
like what do we learn from Shogun learn
another
language one language is not enough
people will die for you not being able
to communicate yeah I watched Vikings Z
had a lot of [\h__\h] up stuff
too misunderstanding Corner can end like
that bro very badly very
badly what
okay I'll go now no
Ragnar
Ragnar oh yeah ragn is
good his son is [\h__\h] like the biggest
little
[\h__\h] anyway I I'm going to go I'm going
to
go sorry had fun and thank you for
watching can't wait for more Zelda I'll
see you soon
tomorrow do you want to learn some
Italian with me and see tomorrow on
louder
Channel well I be I'll probably talk
like that the whole I have to hold
back I have to talk normal I will I will
only talk like that whenever cuz like
they you know likea for example
appreciates it when I say her name like
that because she says that's how you're
supposed to say it
um so whenever I speak Italian maybe
then it's okay to talk like this a
little
bit I can't help it I can't help
it I hope maybe I'll do a little bit of
Italian dualingo before I get into it so
I can Flex a little bit just to remind
myself okay German we say Al in and in
[Music]
um good
night
bye-bye
byebye bye
[Music]
bye imagine if's ending catchphrase
would be
and we
say that would have such such great
Synergy with in German we
say
oh oh yeah but I use that in froggy
week don't I wait do I I say a ribit dir
do I do I does she I do she
do and she's Italian
frogy what do what do I say in froggy
waa we say in froggy we
say are we be D do I even say that maybe
I just say arit Dy and call it a
day AR ribit Dy ah Ribbit
Dy ah Ribbit D just lets it
rip rib
BL
[Music]
wait I want to I'm going to
raid wait for the r
[Music]
ah there it is didn't show up byebye