[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
expensive assistant
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
this is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
hello
come over onion
what's up
hello everybody
how you doing
ah
nice to see you all welcome to the
Stream
yeah no my voice voice too quiet
oh
really
too quiet
distant distant
distant Chihuahua
what do you mean distance I sound a
little tired uh I'm I'm getting I feel
like I'm getting sicker
foreign
[Music]
yeah
ah well first of all this dream is uh
sponsored by epic seven thank you very
much for supporting the stream
um I mean it's more more like the sound
cover is the main thing I have I had I
set up two screens I have two screens
right now so I might be looking here and
there
um yeah did you guys listen to the song
cover always with you it's kind of like
a theme song from the game
and me and crony
were asked to do a little
you know
a little cover of it it's on my channel
came out like a couple days ago I think
on the third year
30th
uh of December so a couple days ago if
you didn't watch it yet then why not
please check it out
uh
did you listen to it
lovely cover yeah it's a very very sweet
and calm pretty song
gives you I think it has like
what kind of winter Vibes but I mean
maybe I'm getting manipulated by the
music video
that is
kind of
in a winter themed with like Christmas
lights and everything it's very very
pretty
um
originally I mean crony were gonna do a
collab stream together on her Channel
where we talk about the music video
unfortunately it didn't go according to
plan and once again it was a very very
very very very very sorry but uh I don't
wanna like
make this stream uh negative I'm doing
this here to leave it on a positive note
so we're gonna
um do exactly that
by well a little bit talking about you
know the song cover I guess but also
um
also playing the game a little bit
because I was I kind of wanted to look
into it I didn't have to
um but I wanted to it was
um I don't know who's interested to look
into it
um hope you guys are too is a game that
has been around for a while
and is
available of course in all the app
stores
but I'm I'm playing it through um
BlueStacks right now just so you know if
anything looks weird to you or so
um
sorry guys
my throat is not in a good condition so
please forgive me for
sounding horse or so
[Music]
um
I've been having some
more coughs and also cough attacks in
the night
um please winter
stop it's ending me
Winter's ending me
um but yeah
um Gemma made me a lovely tea take my
warm honey I'm dead so I'm drinking
thinking the whole time
[Music]
you guys not you guys don't hear the
audio right
uh uh the audio from the game
you probably don't hear it do you
no
interesting
interesting interesting
I'm having audio problems again but
while I'm trying to figure that out let
me just talk a little bit a little bit
about the song cover
um
so
uh first of all in the beginning we
spoke a little bit of Korean
well crony speaks
um beautiful fluent Korean but
um me not so much
maybe some of you guys were wondering
why Korean because
that was maybe kind of out of nowhere
because the the song itself the lyrics
are in English right
yeah
um I think it's because the game
originally
if I'm not wrong comes from Korea um
yeah so as a little little I don't know
what's the right word uh
[Music]
I can't find the right word but it's
just it's just a little
a little greeting
to all the Korean fans against because
um I guess it's even more well known in
Korea is it is it the game
um
call back
not quite tribute maybe yeah yeah
[Music]
you could call it that it should be
yeah and uh the song I really like the
song it's very pretty it's where we cut
calm and soothing and it has a very high
key throughout the whole song but I
personally really enjoyed singing in
that high key
I thought it was quite fun I I
I generally like it but
uh yeah
I wonder
if if it sounded good to you guys hope
you hope you didn't think that our
um high-pitched voices were making your
ears bleed hopefully not
yes I highly like it
um
yes
was it good
it's also like a really good opportunity
for me to collab with Cody otherwise I
didn't have anything in planning to do a
song collab with crony so that's a good
good opportunity
very special
I've played E7 for years
with whale for Halloween
well I don't know anything about
something like that but for now and
there's this song cover that you can
enjoy yeah I listened to the original
um they sing it with like several people
and it's really cool I'm assuming that
the original is sung by like some voice
actors probably
like people who give voices to the
characters in the game probably
yeah yeah I assume am I right
just saw a lot of cute people
singing the song in Korean actually so
it was translated to English
oh yes okay I was right
um it was already like subtitled back
then for the original but yeah our
version is basically just that version
if you're appear in the game I'll make
sure I'll make you into
a
I Champion team what does that mean I
know what that means but I'm guessing
that means that you'll treat me well if
I were if I were in the game
so yeah you guys should check out the
song cover we put a lot of effort into
it and
um we it was at times when we were both
sick but like at right afterwards we
both got sick
and
um
this was not the reason why we got sick
but oopsie
but uh
it was a pleasure it was a big pleasure
was a big honor
and I was I was really surprised because
like I saw BlueStacks uh
BlueStacks is on my mind right now
because I can't fix it I saw um epic
seven doing a collaboration with espa
which is a really really famous
Korean K-pop Idol group you guys know I
have a Fang for cute pretty
the girl Idol groups K-pop Idol groups
uh so I was like what what this feels
like this feels like as if
me and espa were
like performing at the same concert
and we were together in a in a gakuya
what's Kaki in English
hey you can even pull one of the
characters right now right
we were
through performing together we would be
like backstage right now together this
is what it feels like even though we
have absolutely no interaction together
whatsoever
but yeah um if you don't know the idle
group well then you maybe don't feel so
passionate about it as I do but I think
a lot of Kpop stands
I feel very passionate about it and it's
a really cool Idol group and their
members were made into characters in the
game and they made like a really cool
promotion video and all that yeah Karina
Karina right now you can pull her maybe
we can maybe we'll get a chance because
um the game is apparently pretty free to
play user friendly
which is nowadays
such a rare thing like almost
non-existent thing in uh gacha games
right they all want you to pay a
ton of money and not this game
apparently
so now I would like to finally figure
out where the audio is not working
because it worked before
down there
hello
yeah yeah I know I know I know
do you have it well I have the blue sex
side panel out
yes
why
his own volumes and there might be uh
but they're on like I hear the audio
it's just not going through OBS if
that's true
you guys are you guys helping me are you
guys helping me
nope epic status is insanely friendly
when it comes to free to play players
just save up a little and you're sure to
get whatever you want oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah I heard that you can even
re-roll uh 30 times in the beginning
referral ring in my description Link in
the description check it out check it
out check it out
yeah you can re-roll 30 times for to get
the in the beginning to get what you
want and if you still didn't get what
you wanted after that then there's an
actual function in the settings of the
game to reset the game so you don't have
to like you know do it otherwise but the
installing the game no thing lets you do
it and then
yeah you can try again for another 30
tries
[Music]
this is very very kind yeah unlimited
very well works they encourage rerolling
yeah see like what
other games they're like
no no you have to install the game if
you really want to do it and we don't
really want you to do that either
because just take what you can get
um
I don't really know what what I'm
looking for though so I'm not gonna be
re-rolling and
foreign
[Music]
how do I do this
audio
but here you see the I actually started
the tutorial should we just play without
audio actually I started the tutorial uh
already but then I was gonna finish it
before the stream but then I thought
okay maybe you know what maybe it's
nicer if we played a little bit together
and learn it together yeah and Just Dub
it yourself it's like nice Christmasy
music playing right now no not really
Christmassy I'm not sure but the
background is definitely Christmassy
hmm
see I hear the audio
and I've already been playing around in
Windows I swear to God this overseas
streaming setup
is making me mad
let's see any any smart people here
you can play other music no no no no no
no no no no
I don't want to
and emulator yes
maybe it can't
[Music]
um
yeah but it's I'm trying to capture
desktop audio
not even like
in no experience
maybe maybe you should all become
streamers and then you can
learn it
yeah it's currently being window
captured let me try a different way
foreign
[Music]
gaming capture does that work with uh
hope it might work
does that work
oh
with some ads yeah no the screen would
be black but wait maybe that Windows
thing would fix it the thing I learned
yesterday
oh that's not even a thing
oh
oh it disappeared
it disappeared after a second
um
he's playing for One Source only you're
not going to be able to hear it huh
what did that say
and it seems to be a smart person around
here
speaker icon for blue steps Android host
is not muted
no it's not I hear I hear the audio
at another audio Source yeah I want to
try it out right now
I forgot how to do that because that's
not really something I usually do
no I'm not gonna do this as myself
OBS requires some fine tuning with epic
seven
ah
um
what if I do this
in any case
I don't think a different capture would
work
let's just play with that audio
also
okay no I don't like that though I don't
like that
no I don't wanna
I think I might have to do
with me using an extra screen or so
Maybe
and then the audio kind of weirdly going
through that
could that be let me try to disconnect
it
could that be
yeah because the extra screen screen
does have speakers
let me unplug it wait wait um
oh
some of my team may have spilled on my
laptop
worth it
if the audio
hit the audio plays
[Laughter]
okay
I mean the monitor is off now
uh I don't I don't see
I don't see the audio reacting now
hmm
okay
I sound a bit better no that's just
because I'm leaning forward
okay here we go whatever
we have to get started at some point
oh
a source in OBS needs to be the desktop
a destination needs to be the Stream
it's the seven of epic epic seven
did you see my my jorks epic seven at
Epic 7 P.M I'm very proud of it
yeah I don't know how to fix it
I don't know how to fix it
I think I'm I was in the middle of doing
an adventure
oh there's sound I wish you could hear
it
so
I have to go to the sky Breeze Forest
guys follow me
I'm gonna choose this girl because she's
cute
let's go
oh a boss will appear in the stage we
best be careful no
[Music]
no in this dress
please protect me
act four to Tyrell Castle
all right we found your garden so now
it's straight onward to Tiger Castle oh
my Adventures aren't any ending I'm sure
Sir Charles will punish me if we go back
to the Royal Palace luckily if you had
stayed at the balance there'd be no
reason to punish you once you come all
the way out here
it's exciting isn't it the air of a
covenant after 20 years finally woke up
Now isn't it time to be punishing me we
have made we have to get to the Palace
super quick everyone is waiting for
Wrath
GoGo she's so cool look at her look at
her little kitchen knives on her back
I love them
okay attack
you can't escape that's what he said
really yeah
okay so it's kind of like round based
it doesn't that you can you could take
your time if you wanted
but I guess once you have it all figured
out then
I need to do my best then you can go
zoom zoom zoom and there's Auto Battle
but if you do Auto Battle then you're
gonna like Miss items that are on the
screen showing up like Treasures
and uh
armor items
I'm just getting started the road to the
Palace is complex and inhabited by many
monsters please ensure that you stay
close behind me
understood I make sure to protect either
and everyone else let you focus on
Guiding us to Syria
I wonder who will protect whom for real
she's the one protecting us she's the
strongest
there's a new function called pets that
will collect uh items oh well there you
go
Coolio it's nothing let us go let's go
go next go next go next run run
get ready
no
oh they like eating humans and now you
can do like a special attack
go oh maybe I should have used it on one
of the enemies that had more HP
hmm
[Music]
eyes okay it's okay who knows that one
would have probably not even died
so better to initiate
one first Dead
is already
close to dying right right
I'll give you a rest she says what a
kind way to say I will kill you
am I helpful now do you like me yes I
love you who is who is this person gives
me notifications about other people
got it
that was like a Mana Shrine right now oh
boss we won't we won't boss Monster's
portraits have a special border and
their house is displayed on the top of
the screen aha
they're stronger than normal monsters so
we have to be careful okay Sir Charles
said when finding bosses Elemental
relationships aren't bothered oh here we
go that's when they started explaining
the
relationships the elements to me okay
okay
teach me I think you said in every life
form on this world belongs to one of the
five elements fire ice Earth light and
dark I can't even do my cute voice my
throat is so
oh
fire ice Earth light and dark okay okay
I can get some of those ice is weak to
fire
Earth is weak to ice
I was probably exactly that order right
yeah I guess light is weak to Earth for
whatever reason
dark is weak to light and
fire is weak to dark
or something like that
some something like that yeah sorry
there's no sound right now because uh
oh there we go
oh these don't have anything to do with
these so they're more like neutral to
one another maybe none
um okay
Earth element boss it will be weak to
fire okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay even if you're here and their
opponent have the same level Elemental
relationships play a big role in battle
fire ice Earth light and dark all have
their respective Elemental Strokes yeah
didn't we already know this okay
go
that was some good damage already
I need to do my best oh wait what was
that it's like a buff skill
oh was it a hill
oh I didn't use the
oh oh oh are we good we're good we're
good
we're good
yay she's cute
she's cute
oh oh oh oh oh he got poisoned oh no you
can't escape
Sarah doesn't seem to like me much
[Music]
said something is so cute
it looks so fluffy look at those Paws
and the fluff cotton balls coming out of
the ears I don't think it hears very
well though
arcasus unless you're showing people
which wants my choice actually you can
check your bonds at the infinite Library
the library contains all the knowledge
of this world
bones are you sure it's Library another
fortune teller's house
Japan is where we just turned to the
Royal Palace okay yes once we return who
knows when we'll be able to leave again
or it will stop clinging to me
wow congratulations you've become
stronger she told me I'm ranked four now
maximum energy has been increased
clear stage clear
nice
so pretty
oh nice confirm get that get that good
stuff I can now summon
does it mean gacha
oh oh okay does that mean
already I don't know it was so soon wow
this must be the infinite library and do
I get to do my 30 pulls now
who are they
we have a way that you're coming chosen
guest welcome stranger
these books contain the fate of all
living things for their knowledge we
will come to meet those who face our
whose Fates are entwined with yours
this feels more and more like a sham
no no we are the Librarians of the
infinite Library who preserve the memory
of the Stars no one wanted
they simply informed those chosen by the
stars of their faith and connections we
most certainly are not fortune tellers
oh I would like to know my fortune
though
tap the summer button gladly
it is my pleasure
by the way you don't hear it but I do
have English dubbing on right now and
there's also Japanese and Korean dubbing
three different languages tell me you
got your game that has three different
language dubbing
I only know this one
mm-hmm
okay okay whatever don't tell me
don't tell me
shut up
and you may use various bookmarks to
summon Heroes and artifacts here
what choose the summon tag from the menu
on the right and try summoning
Covenant summon
Covenant what's that mean it'll give you
a loan free Covenant summon per day now
check your connections okay okay one per
day would you like to proceed with the
free summon it will not cost you any
Covenant bookmarks oh free what a deal
pretty book okay
is that not the one that you can do 30
times tell me epic seven people
tell me oh
she cute
edgy emo girl let's go this looks like
an emo version of fauna not yet okay
um
[Laughter]
okay okay
Misty chain she's always sad she said it
in English I'm always sad I wish you
could hear it
oh why is she sad I discovered a
wonderful connection you may now add
this hero to your team do you think
she's ready to fight she's like super
depressed she okay to fight I don't want
to force her
I'll offer you the chance to subscribe
to someone in the hopes that you keep
coming back to whoa really
this is the one you can prove your
summon up to 30 times for Selective
Summit this must be it right tap on the
summer preview button you will be able
to preview who you can meet for
summoning oh but the Epic seven players
in a chat raise your hands you have to
tell me oh which one I should keep
okay I mean surely there will be
different opinions but
now I'm gonna show you Freddie she'll
show me Freddie of my potential Futures
wow build red
is there yeah vildred is area vildred or
Destina Angelica okay but most people
saw vildred and in Syria
[Music]
oh
they're really popular
Mildred is a dude huh
Builders code for story mode
okay
Mildred build red
okay let's see let's see I'm gonna be
lucky
let's go
uh someone preview are you gonna show
them all at once I wanna go through them
slowly slowly
was that Golden Light already telling me
something who is this bizarre bizarre a
genius holding sway over the economy of
an entire continent
wow he didn't tell me anything he didn't
talk to me
next up preferably I want a girl
oh here we have a girl Mont more Mont
more Rose that's a French name I don't
know how to pronounce it a naive and
hard-working Apprentice none
that seems so strong to me
next
[Laughter]
oh I think there's some delusional eggs
okay A bit
some really really
rare and small ones
what next you can get an egg why can't
you get an egg
next door is a cursed Compass okay so
it's not just people
what
sorry
random's memorandum oh aren't as pretty
though it's a book though and I don't
read books these are artifacts
come on come on oh that looks stronger
oh Sarah Ren
oh
oh looks like
looks like uh he could be a YouTuber
it's got a pretty flower on his eye oh
husband
Mage exclusive oh there's like no
oh wait it's an artifact it's not a like
a another person
wait are they old oh hello you again
nice to see you again Mr chain
I'm already have you
that doesn't look very strong or is it
wait
well prophetic candlestick
cool well Kelly would like this as a
decoration for her home
with the skull
skip
next
give me something Epic
Epic
that doesn't look so epic ancient chief
sheep
know in German
um
Sheaf is a very embarrassing word
and whenever we used it in school back
in the day
every time I had to like read it or sew
from a book or so
the other students would always be like
giggling guess why
[Laughter]
oh cute
and assassin with a lot to hide
um what do you mean Secrets physical or
or not physical
the first page but this is not 30 right
oh wait it's one this is one this causes
one I thought we were already like I
don't know ten through
oh someone again if you'd like to see
more details go ahead and tap on the
hero artifact you're saying this
Summoner result is okay but you want to
see some other humors yeah although
connectors are something that you have
to take as they come I'll record the
summon the special for you thank you
okay
feel free to return to what was recorded
once you see the results of another
summon or make a new record if you find
wait wait you mean I can go back
eh
what even if I summon even more I could
still go back to these ones
holy that's so nice
that's so nice
normally like he would give it up and
throw it away and it will never come
back to you
that's so nice
wow
you can receive new Heroes and artifacts
for Selective summon you're given a
total of 30 chances to retry summon
results and if you see a result you like
you can record it and continue summoning
when you when you confirm a result it
will no longer be able to carry on
summoning
so the side curve okay okay
summon again Google
yeah it's okay we will find something
better
let's go thank you Luda for the red
super chat
thank you very much
again does this already show me that I
got something like rainbow SSR or so oh
she's got really long bangs it's like me
when I was a child a young teenager
um
yeah we can get better than an egg of
the loot double tap for Sr no wait
that's just
hookbook homebook
Nina
winka
Aqua Rose oh that's pretty
it's pretty nanny
oh a guy
adley wait that art style looks familiar
to me okay cool he's cool
it's kind of cool he's a Sagittarius I
don't really know much about
if if my
sign works well for Sagittarius
sadly well that looks strong
but it's an artifact
that looks really cool Knight exclusive
artifact wow
wow
this also special pretty and another
artifact one wondrous potion while she's
killed
skilled
it's pretty cute but next
potion very good it's a very good
artifact oh who's she carrot she's a
carrot
assassin magic researcher who sees all
magic as math
[Music]
We're Not Gonna Be of good terms
oh
Rosa haragana
another artifact
but um
looks kind of special to me again but
what do I know
um
cute she got a gun holy shotgun
what can
what
a butcher corpse inquisitive
Blitzer Corps soldiers fighting for the
Church of
illrias
el Reyes
cool he's very very armored very
protected
oh oh
excuse me
I think this is what we wanted
I'm recording this but I want to roll
more
wait I saw it don't be don't I already
have him like I saw him on the story
yeah what did I just see it in the dream
nice so lucky am I lucky that was my
second role
oh oh that's just support and like this
I have him as like not support
and the story is a support you can't
level him
[Music]
so okay we already got one of the best
ones
oh cool an off key
holy nice that was a good role
foreign okay so if I record it then I'm
switching out one right
that's okay
that's totally fine record okay
yeah okay
okay summoning again
I thought we would do a bit more
gameplay but it turns out we're doing
the most exciting thing for most of the
stream which is gotcha and
what happened yeah that's fine right
because I I recorded it already I don't
want to make a mistake I recorded it so
I can go do another one right
this is the
most important thing
go go go go go go go
[Music]
wow Mighty yaksha oh
cool wait is that a yaksha is that like
a like a mythical thing
an actual mythical thing
usable
scary yeah
very scary oh we know her already
yeah it is oh
oh that's pretty butterfly man Dolan
that's an instrument huh that's a real
instrument right
if I were to play this instrument in
real life I wanted a custom one that
looks like this
that's so pretty I wonder what it sounds
like I can't remember
Lima a Minstrel cute
[Music]
oh
may I say the f word
the hard worker who dreams of becoming
the world's strongest mercenary yet
in German I would say yes
I'm not saying the F word
it's a sponsored stream
what's that no I guess they're not
really Birds but
this one is a bird and that's a fox the
other two I'm not sure maybe
um not sure but it's freaking cute
it's a hollow Cube it's a console Cube
I love everyone for cube uh-huh oh
out of my shield already got it
cool down
I like the special effect makes me feel
very special
makes me feel appreciated oh a Goblin's
lamp Goblin has such a pretty lamp
the goblin has such a pretty lamp I want
that lamp give me give me
you again she really likes me again
summon again go
Speed Run Speed Run
what's going on
oh
epic artifact epic seven
wow
what do you say about this one huh
looks epic stuff
useless though don't say that
it's useful for healers usable but not
do not record okay but who knows what
else we get oh oh
pretty cute
water's origin so we were exclusive I
like the art I'm very pretty
yeah it's a it's a Miko speaking of Miko
Amigos senpai's uh 3D stream starts in
uh nine minutes yeah nice Segway kiwawa
absolutely
stunning what a pro
we have Sarah ran again oh it's already
time we didn't skip something I didn't
see Hazel
let's skip like the unimportant ones
Pearl horizon or does it skip it on its
own Grail of blood
a little
people
can we do can we do 25 Summits in eight
minutes
let's see
oh
Lots
a valiant healer searching for a rare
magical item not a huddle
probably not better than the other good
one that we had so oh oh oh oh oh
that's freaking cute oh my god look
there's even a shape
it's a shape there's so much going on
it's so cute I like it
I like it oh
Coley
a cheerful vigilance burdened with the
horrors of War
yeah understandable what do you say
about this row
what do you say about this
Timeless anchor Candlestick
summoning again let's go
squeeze your thumbs for me guys squeeze
them squeeze them
oh
Armin
unmatching him in her brave recommender
of the long tail company ears
could be friends with akirozi senpai
I'm gonna skip them so that we can do
all of them in seven minutes
oh
hell cutter
that looks hot
that is that a chainsaw
Kelly would love this chainsaw
foreign
[Music]
wow I like her mint colored hair
oh
wow
it's beautiful
who is she I want to get to know her
you like Lance hi lag Lance
nice lands at the Rose oh I like the the
whole like color theme going on
the pink with the white
and the black oh
but I guess we're skipping this again
ski poo
go go go go go go go go go go I don't
think we can do it oh
I got stressed out but okay it doesn't
look so like such a good um
salmon okay
I was like we gotta go faster we gotta
go faster
speed
oh oh wait I think it skips it really
fast because there's really nothing that
special here okay okay
we're getting so unlucky now
did I use up my luck well I mean I guess
I did get the one of the best ones in
the second row so
oh
five star great magician turned dull and
her faith oh the big guy in the
background
that looks one of our like one of our
English Stars
That's The Apprentice
the girl is not The Apprentice no no
it's the big guy in the back
that's cool
cute cute look at that one
okay okay apparently it's a skip okay
okay
uh Vesper in Bay
oh yeah I can see that
I should probably skip that
or should I oh
I have seen that before
Rose hello
oh
hello a valkyrie wait this is a valkyrie
I read Warlock and somehow read into it
that it's a black Curry wait no the do
Valkyries have wings
today
something special is coming I feel it oh
never mind not so special seen him
before
oh
[Music]
what is she eating
cute is that Zeta there's a phew oh I
like the wavy hair oh she's cute I like
the art
hmm
vampire girl
next door
go go go
that's a new one dust devil
call me
okay my My rolls are getting better
again oh
who is this cute Library girl
showing me her cute butt in the library
yes show me your magical runes
hell
very cute
yo guys my eyes are up here
oh okay
the Lance oh
Serato wow let me guess it's ice so the
snare a genius Frost will freeze
everything he looks pretty cool
it looks very cold
got a lot of abs
but I feel like we can get something
better
oh Strack Gauntlet
oh we're halfway through oh
Moonlight dream blade sick
Sid
uh-huh next next next next next next
next next next next next next
what's the girl called again that I'm
looking for
guys
that you guys told me to look for
is Syria okay
maybe it's here this one no
it's probably more like even more oomph
even more epic boom
okay
Sarah come to me come to me or secrets
oh something's happening
what is it
who is you
araminfa leader of the Phantom cic
unknown investigators investigator
she's pretty
Anna
my nice potion
but apparently it's a man
sacred is free oh
oh no no no no
I don't have time I mean it's not like I
can't overlap I think yeah I don't I
don't have to end it immediately there
will probably be like a waiting time
right in the beginning so maybe we have
like two more minutes
it's not it's not like I am not allowed
to overlap so
come on come on come on
wait Ravi I got Ravi
wait which one was Robbie ah
that's a good one she looks a little bit
too naked to be shown on stream
aggressive little girl Reborn is
better than the other one
[Music]
um
she's covered yeah but once she moves
woof
World red is slightly better
but she's cuter
and that's what matters to me
you should aim vildred I already have
Mildred in my
um recorded once
and
but you know what I'm gonna contain to
someone because
um because
um
I want to see more you know
I want to show you as much as possible
okay next
who's addicted yeah that might also be a
reason
wow
hot
caladra dust devil let's see
no it sounds hot
let's go
a couple more
f word
looks fluffy though without the armor I
would give him a hug
oh
something's coming
who is you Ken
hey Bobby hey Ken
let's go on a ride sure I can
is also good oh
aladra
oh she's cute is cute
go go go go go go
oh I like her
Dominion she's got bunny ears perfect
for the year of the bunny of the rabbit
2023 here of the rabbit pickle
used to be good oh
she's nerfed
to death
[Music]
holy sacrifice Rosa hargana they really
like giving me those
next tea
oh we have the chainsaw girl again she's
sick
come on give me mine give me my pretty
lady you serious I don't even know what
she looks like but I feel like once I
see her I will know obviously five star
Tywin Tywin Lannister Captain up to
defunders Royal Guard model of faithful
diligence
hi Lynn
it's for raids hmm
see how nice this game is I can see so
many
choices
it is so much fun to roll for gacha I
can go on forever I can't stop myself
even though I got the best thing already
in the beginning who is she
ah she's like pushing her boobies up
with the book
and she's kind of like sitting on the
books
whoever Drew this gets it they get it
they just get it
cute what's that bird looks like Korea's
mascot well wait wait a second that gun
I know from GTA what gun that is
but I forgot what is it
I think I used that in GTA
a minigun mg mgmg
I love mg I'm a fan of mg now muscle God
sorry cute she's cute yo I like her
weapon
yeah
I said weapon so
is that like a shuriken in big I don't
know what to call it
Moonlight Dreamland hello
I only want more I think we might have
to
accept the dude
last one last stop
oh
ah can you again I will become stronger
a lively fist fighter
hmm
okay
we use Dr luck in the beginning but wait
oh the mg again
okay
uh how do I
use the the the
recorded ones
no no I don't want to record this
summon results
on the menu
press confirm really
ah
okay so I'm going for this one
yes I'm pretty sure I didn't make a
mistake right
and I want to see where do you get
Karina really quick really quick
where where would I get Karina isn't
that also in summoning
yeah
oh she also has English voice acting
oh I know you guys can hear it because I
up the audio sorry but whoa
who killed do I have anything to try for
her
no I don't
wanna
[Music]
oh I got 69 of those
Oh I wanna go in the mail or maybe maybe
uh maybe I get some free stuff
receive all
what did I get
2 000 coins and two leaves
[Laughter]
yeah
oh wait there's more I know receive all
can oh no no I already did
okay
um
two million did I say two thousand
click on the gems
oh this one
give me
okay that's all I need for now
welcome to the infinite armor hey can I
do like a
live Covenant bookmarks should I do this
one
I would say yes
or
no really
okay
go
50 bookmarks
10 or bust
do I get Karina
please it looks like a no to me
when she's cute too
[Music]
well
it's okay I'll try more
I'll try more another time it's an
equipment yeah yeah I know I know
I can find some special items that have
passive skills Heroes that have an
artifact equipped to get an increase in
stats and an additional Passage
[Music]
wow guys
I will end it here
is that a weapon I will end it here but
guys check out the the new song cover
that I put up with chronini and oh
wow
very strong and check out the game link
is in the description free to play even
if you want to do lots of gaja you get
everything you want if you just play it
a little bit really it's very very very
kind worth it worth picking up and they
have cool collaborations
yeah they had three zero before they
have Espanol
and who knows what they will be in the
future some exciting things
yeah thank you so much epic7 for
sponsoring the song cover and I hope you
guys enjoyed the Stream
she's still talking to me
hello Hannah nice to meet you
yes yes nice to meet you cutie patooty
nice to meet you I actually wanted
Karina but it's okay I'll take you guys
you can come join my team I don't get a
re-roll for this do I
I accept my defeat
I take it sometimes you have to accept
things the way they are
if they don't get better then
there's no way around it except my wait
a second I could summon again with 50
but now it's okay
where's it
no I don't even have the money for it do
I yeah I don't I don't I don't it's okay
it's okay it's okay I have to stop I
have to stop
thank you guys very very much
[Music]
short stream uh but I just wanted to
leave um this whole thing on the
positive note hmm
let's check out epic seven and please
listen to the song cover always with you
and Odo crony thank you soon everybody
for the support so far please continue
listening to it and yeah give crony's
Vlog a watch too she talked about the
game
as well
uh stream today a couple hours before
hmm
yeah thanks for streaming for winning
the game it's my pleasure
it's my honor hmm
yeah I have to rise my throat again
I'm gonna try to stream tomorrow slay
this fire if possible
um but yeah
Fruitport
oh good job before Pierre go for
summoning something
I can't do Super Chat reading on this
stream sorry
and my throat wouldn't take it anyway
but maybe tomorrow I can do Super Chat
reading and not
um nuts latest buyer
we'll see we'll see
um take care of myself yeah you guys do
thank you guys for watching always have
some good rest thank you thank you soon
take care and Russell thank you thank
you
okay okay okay
thank you again epic seven
satisfire please okay I'll think about
it hope you get better soon thank you
foreign
GST
um possibly earlier hmm
but somewhere around that time maybe two
hours earlier at the earliest
I'll feed us
in my mind
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
you guys still here
kitty kitty I forgot to say one thing
I forgot to say one thing
[Music]
hi
there's a New Year's Sky Stone giveaway
event did I see that where is that
that's a lucky week
can we find it
I just want to make you guys aware of it
New Year's skystone wait did I not like
is that something you get when you log
in
and that's uh that's a thousand I got Ah
that's the one that I already picked up
ah
I think it makes a cartoon sound when I
open it at this one
happy New Year can I read the message
oh yeah it says these ones oh okay I
claimed it I claimed exactly that
without knowing standing room today yeah
as you can see you will get a chance to
get Karina and if you got her then
please take a screenshot and show it
after me on Twitter
and make me jealous okay okay
Karina
good luck guys I wish you good luck May
the fourth be for May the Epic seven be
with you
for nagacha um
[Music]
foreign