[Music]
e
n
[Music]
e
n
[Music]
e
n
[Music]
f is
having no no no hold on yeah she is no I
okay Kiara was like who's making that
sound and Kiara was like Moon walking in
place and then a l star moon walking in
place it's it's you guys no no it's you
I was standing still she was standing
still I was also standing still my my my
stream will be on my side I believe
it is never on your side you're alone P
you're alone
you you be you'll be on my side right
how do you
oh who me no no wait no
damn Nissa was uh
oh what's going on here what's going
on hello stop it and introduce yourself
stop it
stop this game is toggle Crouch I
thought it was hold this whole
[Laughter]
time p p
yeah introduce yourself
okay hello everybody can't see your face
up there yeah it's a little intimidating
it's kind of
creepy
hello yeah I'm hello
yeah no you're
W I'm W oh
of the worldwide what was it what were
we worldwide wife web worldwide I'm Wu
of the worldwide wide neb web thank you
it's not that hard to
say why are you having so many trouble
saying that I just woke
up okay oh oh yeah can you give them
like uh the story of your your your
current issues that maybe issues arise
because of your current location yes I
might stop pointing at me I feel wait
who's who's who's making
that
what wait who who's making that noise am
I noise there's no noise there's no
sound CH you hear it hallucinating
again
my chat hears
it um I'm currently also hallucinating
sorry I'm currently in a hotel in Japan
so I might poof out of existence
maybe maybe a sound from the hotel room
oh that's kind of spooky I next door
haunted spooky um anyway oh you who all
right I've heard enough of that why yeah
next next one
who oh this why we I I wo she's move
walking
again he's
not he's not I
love I thought we were all W no only
she's
Wu oh then I'm
po no
hi I'm wewa from the
world it's our first
coll I'm WEA from the worldwide wife web
y
walking I'm so
happy I'm so happy we're finally
collabing cuz we even met IRL before but
we never C so happy you
finally didn't you wait in when we met
IRL didn't you like pay for like my
whole dinner no no yes you did yes you
did a stop pointing don't dance at
me no
no that was that that was pretty cool
and handsome of you oh oh and yes I
[Laughter]
did nice thank you so much maybe this
time maybe today I can thank you for all
of that maybe I'm looking forward to
it wow W what do you what do you know
about this wife
there she got some great assets oh yeah
oh
yeah I can see though I'm embarrassed
stop what's
happening I mean yeah
I even got fan art of myself drawn in
A's outfit it looks pretty I can't blame
you you
yeah we have one
more
saw I want to he okay
weisa go on the stage the white
stage hi Darlings I'm Lisa of the
worldwide waiu
web
worldwide wife beautiful life this is
this is my wife because I'm literally
going on a honeymoon with her oh that's
so
fun dealing kiaha for
myself it's okay I don't really not if
that's really applicable because I
invited you I don't know how you're
feeling me you don't need to tell them
that
K I'll have her on
Tuesday every other Tuesday
yeah yeah yeah we just switch off
yeah okay
okay gu oh my gosh she's
moonwalking nobody's moonwalking who's
moonwalking Me Maybe maybe we don't know
about walking skill you're going
crazy I I I don't know what you're
talking
about do it again do it again
a moon
walking wow that's not Moon
walking
Moon wait that's so smooth oh my God
she's actually so smooth with it oh my
she's a she's a smooth
[Laughter]
criminal it's great how people can get
so excited over the most scuffed and
simple features of the game m wow so
easy to entertain
kaha hello I am The Mastermind behind
the worldwide wife web I am the wife of
everybody if they make me a wife I will
be everybody's wife let me wife you uh
today I came here to go to the wife
convention this is the wife convention
right yeah yeah yeah of course we just
need to pick up a few things first oh
okay then call me W your wife let's
go W my
wife
yay life life life life you guys have a
lethal company
wife uh no you you guys no maybe I think
I like the I would pick the Bracken oh
the Bracken yeah I like The
Nutcracker
what the Nutcracker existed oh is it a
Monster yeah oh okay okay I don't know
them yet well shall we set up and start
our first mission then wait we have to
explain to KI how to play okay okay this
is Ki play it yet yeah yeah yeah okay
have you ever played
phasmophobia yes and I do not like it oh
well it's like the exact same thing
except different yeah yeah yeah point of
me point of me okay so basically kiaha
we're going to be going to moons okay
and on these moons it is our
responsibility to go into these uh long
abandoned buildings and collect
materials that at the end of 3 days we
are going to be selling um There Are
Rules so you're going to actually want
to come over here since it's your first
time and go ahead and read this manual
there a manual no way yeah why does it
say it's so hard to read though my Godin
by a few species dominated by a few
species
she's
dominant first time I saw that too I was
like a manual oh can I I thought I
thought I'm reading the manual oh there
sorry I can't read read the manual so we
could also just explain to you as we go
but basically we're just looking for
things to pick up bring back to the ship
if all of us wipe we we lose all of our
items um so if everyone's dead it's best
to just
leave there will be monsters chasing to
place on the counter
and the bell until the company answers
the door and what what what is this
about what when selling C the company
yeah so Day Day Zero technically or the
last day we go to the company to sell
all the stuff that we found um and we
have to place it on a desk and then ring
a bell for them to come get it how do I
oh there oh
oh I can't I can't read and dance I
can't read dance what did you expect
what did you do did you do
something oh did you just answered
questions it's so dark oh there we go
yeah I answered question but I also
don't know how to use the
terminal I don't think we have to use
the terminal for the first one I think
we just
start Char yeah
inorder to R risk of damage that auto
pilot ship will not stay
on don't worry you'll get
it crew at home can I stay at home no no
no no no you can't no just Ty for how do
I broadcast oh whatever girl you'll tell
me you tell me all of this H um yeah of
course yeah yeah oh that's a lot okay
let's go let's go all right okay start
the ship do we how do I punch someone
you can't can if you get if you pick up
like there's like doop signs inside if
you pick it up you can hit people yeah
yeah you can hit people or you can hit
monsters yeah so when a monster Texs me
I I should try to attack them back um
well some of them you can and some of
them you can't moon walk Moon
Walkers
it's that's crab wol I feel like oh
we're moving we started there
go Val just R I will run I will run wait
did it start r start I thought the game
started Oh I thought so didn't it start
I heard a sound it sounded like start
okay moon walker I'm going to
start oh here we go oh my
gosh Okay Hand
okay all we have to do is go into the
building comp
ecosystem okay I'm AF life
for2 I see I think it's this way right 8
a.m. wow I don't know is this the moon I
think it's this way yeah are we on the
moon yeah we're on the moon we're on the
moon leave you come here wait there's no
way one
flash okay oh wait we don't need a
flashlight it's
fine wait I have nothing you girl
no now we don't have anything yet we got
to make some money
honey is it this
one am I
wrong oh I'm not
wrong ice cream time for ice
cream more ice
cream I could Le anyone where where is
everybody wait did they
oh I missed out on the ice
cream the
side ABS always be
scamming oh I just
fell can't tell if those are
good oh yeah okay those are the good
guys Hep always
[Music]
be I'm down
here oh don't go in the water no there's
no water there's the fire
exit yeah we're upstairs I think okay
I'm going
in oh it's right
beside why is there still creepy
music why is there still creepy music
I'm scared I don't want to be by myself
what am I doing am I stupid why am I by
[Music]
myself what's that music I think I'm
leaving I think I'm getting out of
here I think I don't want to be there
anymore don't call me Brave I literally
just
left in fact I'm going to
turn
our my item to the
ship my single item I think that meant
that there was something close by though
right when you hear
the do that mean that the ghost is by
the
Ambiance why is there so much music it's
freaking me
out wait where's the ship
that is Death Ship
is
uh
oh am I lost no
wait why would I be lost how do I get in
oh I'm on the other wrong side
maybe I'm a little more lost than I
imagined
Ching I got some
scrub guys hear
that oh my gosh look at them all three
together wait are they
outside have they not gone
inside
oh
wait are they outside they're
cuddling I want to
cuddle they ran into a monster already
no
way roaming
Loc
hello I guess they're not
here they found the
Bracken
uh-oh what the you can run away from
that wait okay you look at him and then
you don't look at
him
hello wait it sounds
close this is what I mean this is the
spooky music
right
hello went to the fire exit
okay hello oh hi
hi where are you guys going oh um well
there's a thumper I think and a bracket
oh right
inside oh when we were going through the
main entrance the Bracken was there and
then we went through the fire ex just
now and then there was a thumb firm no
way and the Bracken yeah you wouldn't
believe watch check this [\h__\h] out I'll
check it
out holy
[\h__\h] oh it was just a it's just chilling
I think he's stuck come here [\h__\h] are
you stuck oh you
wouldn't we're going to lose day one are
you stuck no it's fine I got a
magnifying
glass k something kill are you going to
burn him with the sun look the way
pomu I think
[Music]
he's
good job um found us yeah we lived oh
we're all good well I think we should go
it's
5 um
um you're joking
me
what do we
do
Ki I hurt my shin are are you okay what
are you doing here a moment ago you
weren here I I came in because the guy
came after me me what are you
doing what are you doing oh don't don't
oh God the Bracken oh god um I think
we're in trouble guess he can't come
here um I in in this room like for 2
minutes and I didn't see you where have
you been oh I was outside I just came
inside oh okay I think I think we're in
trouble kiaba I think um I think I think
we're in trouble I think we're in
trouble a cute boys somebody died so I
don't I don't know
who why are they such
amateurs so true okay I'm going to check
outside maybe we'll be fine yeah
maybe it's not
fine it's not fine everything's
bad where'd she
go shh sh sh sh shh don't make noise
don't make noise Crouch walk Crouch walk
okay okay try and S fast
hi
hi hi
go
okay
okay we're crouching and we're walking
shut up oh Sor shut
up my God you told me to shut
up [\h__\h] if I die because of
you follow me ice okay okay I see the
ship
the
fu why are we screaming why are we
screaming all the
P hi I made
it is that a dog made yes wait is there
a dog there no dog yes there's a dog yes
there's a dog yes there's a dog okay I'm
starting the I'm I'm I'm I'm starting
I'm starting I'm starting
was there actually a dog I think so I
saw something running oh it was a worm
there was a worm oh oh I couldn't tell
if that sound was a dog the she like I
made it I'm
like no my wife is dead who will go to
the mold with me most paranoid the M
yeah I mean yeah I'm still going to the
males with you
a yeah wait to live it's 57 no one got
anything
else no we couldn't the braen tried to
kill me the second we walked in all you
got to do this the only thing we've got
yeah I grabbed that yep I haven't played
this game since we last played it oh
yeah it's been a while then thank thank
you for 20
memberships thank you for 20 m
[Laughter]
e nice wow I'm very ped so that that was
pretty bad wasn't it that was a pretty
bad situation yeah that was a pretty
bad pretty good I mean yeah we did good
you got we just got unlucky yeah just a
little bit is that a quota zero out of
130 M yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh oh good let's
go W let's go
go oh wao W it's the same three times in
a row so you get
lost yeah yeah oh that's a good idea oh
there's the Beehive
beehive Don't Go Near The be run run oh
there's two beehives
uhoh so those are actually worth a lot
of money so if we can get them it's
really good but you got to be tricky
about it and basically yeah oh they're
close they're both close though I think
we'll be good yeah yeah we could try to
get them at the end and then just have
everyone else on the ship so let's go
get them at the end get them at the
end we're on
March no it's
December uh no the Moon is called March
wow sometimes they are oh um H that
sound is
there oh Tiara I forgot to tell you so
when you right click you scan and that's
how you can like find items and
stuff okay so
always okay okay ABS always be scanning
always be
scanning like this okay
okay here oh I got a key it's a dead
end what's
that
gun oh careful for turrets oh there's a
turret I thought I heard something I
think I heard a uh hello chunky wonking
what's a
word chunky wonky has come to
assassinate my sock
puppets that's not bless you thank you
why am I alone and why is it dark only
leave me Al who's who's
squeaking oh
nice thank you Dad oh my God you scared
me so bad there really nothing down
there I'm scar yeah I turned
around I'm just there there's nothing
here
I think we got to go to the other
entrance okay there's nothing downstairs
anymore
[Music]
okay I think we got to find oh I can't
see where the is do it no it's you can
walk around
literally you don't have to moon walk
your way over you can just do
this we go again is she dead
again no I think she was I don't she had
something I think we got to go to the
other entrance over yeah I think we got
to find it
yeah that's
go do a flip I would
[Laughter]
have I would have Chad I really would
have oh a fish oh hey my OBS guy what I
don't know just just for a moment though
you don't think she you don't think she
died to the bees right there's no way
that she died
again I will kick her out of the
collab I'll take these I'll take these
to the
ship I'll go back with
you
okay yeah the graphics scared me they're
so
bad the be the bees no those are little
flies the bees are like in the circle
they're
like
I hear them the
bees I hear the bees how do I take
that run run
run I'm I'm kind of dead but I think I
got crap it said there's a but I don't
know where she is she's walking where
are you
guys I'm in the ship oh hi oh wait that
was my
stamina that was just my
stamina
this
rain why don't we take the be yeah
they'll follow they'll follow us into
the ship that's
why okay do you want me to we do at the
end though oh I was looking for an an
entrance in a fire exent oh yeah
Emery really don't be such a loner stay
with us I'm
[Laughter]
sorry wait isn't this the way we just
came from or I see a a door it's a big
circle oh there's over here is this
where we came in before am I am I silly
any
no this is a different entrance right am
I
silly am I
silly I'm
silly I think there's something
here like what does that sound
mean hi y oh where are you guys I hear
you we went in through the emergency oh
where is
it on the floor it's like a
little my game just lag is there a
little
what sorry the second I was saying
something my game lagged and I'm like oh
is that
a it's a down the hill I don't know what
else to call it okay I'll I'll go look
for
it uhoh it's starting to get dark though
that was so funny it's a little
little that's all I
heard let's see I'm going up
here down a hill but I'm going up a hill
it's 5:00 p.m. Giants are going to come
out maybe I'll
go
I think I'm lost you
guys is it this way oh you guys I think
I'm actually lost uhoh I don't know
where
I I might swim again nobody
is that was
a I
think
I saw
something I saw it
bam
go
now you need to get back now
something
running I'm
here I'm I'm Not Dead
Yet pom get in here I think I saw a
dog oh yeah be
quiet okay um I think the other two are
dead I think it's just
us I think uh yeah so assumption is
hasn't moved there's also a little
feature um I have gotten
close yeah um well those I think are the
bees so what I'm going to do is I need
you when I say so to hit the start ship
I'm going to grab the bees okay and then
I'm going to bring them back in Nissa
you're so
brave okay are you ready yep I'm ready
I'm ready ma'am hit the Le button
hit
it
narissa when should I hit the
button
Nissa pomu hit the button get the
Beehive and run oh okay oh hit the
button get the
beehive
oh [\h__\h] I'm
running I'm
dropping I think I did
it
oh where'd she
go we got more stuff this
time get is in love with me or something
mine is 60% oh [\h__\h] oh gosh you guys
beehive it's
gone where's the Beehive i i b it in
they brought it in oh they knew that we
did it for Discord so they count it oh
my
God no way we
reported the the game developers are
watching the stream right now everybody
died for no reason6 worth of
stuff oh who who turned off the light
why you turn off the light you scared
me no cheating allow to hold you know
you know one good thing about living
alone I just realized is that nobody can
like turn off the light in the room I'm
in randomly by accident does anyone ever
no that's so annoying do people do that
to you mean I mean when I when I used to
live in my I mean it just happens
doesn't it like when you're in the
toilet I
don't what not on purpose just by
accident this is a kiar only exclusive
experience what maybe it's maybe
Americans have the light switches on the
other side of the room oh maybe the
light switches on the inside yeah yeah
it's usually on the
inside are the inside your bathroom
light switch is on the inside in the
bathroom yeah
yeah oh wait is this a cultural thing
maybe I think so
probably oh interesting I have some
light switches on uh for example my
guest room has a light switch on the
inside but my bathroom has a light
switch on the outside ohow I see him why
now I know what to do when you're on the
toilet when I see
you no wait now Rea knows now rea's
going to turn the light off
you're right you have the opportunity
you're
right you will not
there wait did you die to the braen
there's a monster there's a monster
animal he kissed me he kissed that I'm
not sure I'm scared
animal
zooming I think it's a bird
bird that's a [\h__\h] bird why is it on
the ground yeah it's just a bird
oh what that's not how birds
move
they oh I see a beehive but I don't
think we'll be able to get this
one I'm going to get it oh my God you
are you're going to get it okay I need
to I need to make up for my failure run
leave
me do it at the very end yeah we'll do
it at the end no I need to get it closer
failed construction why don't they fly
anymore why are they
only what the what the [\h__\h] what where
is the entrance where's the ENT oh I
found the entrance I found the entrance
entrance is
here oh my God oh my God who are you oh
you scared me so the hell you scared me
you
I'm just a girl just a
girl I'm just a
girl
follow you following me
okay yeah
w
w dead
end w w woman you were so cute you were
so cute in the Ninja San festival thing
no thank
you I'm in
b no um actually yeah actually it was
nihongo joou wasn't
it yeah Prett nihongo Jo oh my God and
very UT
J
no just uh you know where is
everything the light is on down there
should we go down you could
try
no try oh I found an egg
beater what let's go laa cooking stream
is happening it's happening oh my gosh I
want to try your cookie so
bad what the [\h__\h] are you talking about
what was that you have a problem you
have a problem yeah yeah are you guys
fling about me
we about what the [\h__\h] where what where
where what's wrong
what where is she um I can't see
anything it's it's too dark it's too
dark what's that oh oh there's a key key
I want to take I want to take I want to
take can I take
yeah no fully we don't die wait what's
that
sound them
walking
um I don't know what that sound is
God should we
leave I think we should go yeah we
go how do we get home long as I have
problem with me how do you have a good
such a good directional
sense uh I think it's
because there was nowhere else to
go Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy it's a
okay it's
okay we got to go the other way where
are you I can see I can't I'm like stuck
in on the wall oh I see you I see you
come here come here come here come come
here this way get away get away am I
reconnected am I
back I can't tell at
all I think I
disconnected because I lost internet um
you can keep playing until I'll I'll
join at when next
game okay okay a WEA kiata is going to
die
so are we back guys we're back okay no
oh my gosh the ship I left I left I left
Kar in
the I left
Kiara the darkness
[Laughter]
I was worried I didn't think my internet
would come back for a second
because because
um what's it
called usually it like disconnects and
reconnects pretty soon but this time I
was like you have no
internet
I'm so sorry guys I'm on Hotel
Wi-Fi
no what am I
eating it's something like a hi Chu
Safina gave it to me I didn't get the
time to get
breakfast so I have a snack candy or
breakfast
sorry
guys that now I'm just kind of stuck on
the
screen wait it's showing right okay
yeah get a proper meal while we're
waiting I'd have to like
believe oh wait I bought some toast I
could get the
toast um I don't know who will invite me
R for hotel Wi-Fi
could only AA survived yay wait what
happened to Kiara wait what happened to
both of
them host it's like a eggy
toast modded modded modded
wow jumped into
the I'm going to
say um Can someone please reinvite me
whenever you have the chat thank
you muted
we're selling stuff and then we're going
to save a file and we're going to
reinvite you thank you I miss
you I'm having so much
fun they're selling the stuff okay
good they don't have to remake the lobby
right they just have to invite
me because if they remake the lobby
they'll lose everything
right oh my chat
froze is
frozen
refresh guys are
alive thanks for letting me
know very
cool sell first and remake I don't think
they have to remake though right h
I have a save file oh okay cool cool
cool why am I always stuck at being an
intern then I never have progressed I
think you need a mod in order to invite
people mid game you need to remake
normally but when I played
with inana and
I don't remember who it was they just
invited me I don't know I'm just going
to let them figure
out
ipn who is the other person someone
else I only remember
finana oh steam friends list you're so
right
Ste hello open
oh
friends
friend
well for some reason it's only showing
Kiara as online for me currently in game
lethal
company
[Music]
o won't let me
join
oh that's
me here I go here I go everybody here I
go P
hello
Pama yo we were together and suddenly
you were gone and I was like what the
[\h__\h] yeah um my internet decided to just
I know it poop itself yeah yeah so and
now you're back yeah can you can you
tell it to not do that again please yeah
I think it maybe got really flustered it
was like so nervous around you like I
mean we were just by ourselves so oh
that no if you're so if your connection
is so unstable then I think I'll I'd
rather stay with one of the other
girls holy [\h__\h] I can't rely on you I
can't
rely holy [\h__\h] God damn call an
ambulance but not me for me people
people we want we D I just got thrown
away so quickly she looks so serious on
the computer I love you pomu wait hold
on I can't hear do something what' you
say what is she doing what is WEA doing
on the
terminal wait what' you say my my
headphones came
[Laughter]
out only stream will
know it's over for me guys what are you
doing
we how do we start the game Oh I thought
you you knew what you were doing you
look like you I picked the moon and I
ordered some stuff but
the start Oh e on this like the thing on
the here if you hold e then it'll be
like wait no it's not giving the prompt
though yeah I didn't get the prompt or
start game oh it's because I'm the host
uh yeah you have to be the first one
yeah sorry let's go
y I almost jumped yeah it's a new
map
pumpkins yum yum I like the pumpkins how
level be okay I stay with you Lis don't
die okay I heard a flashlight so I'm
going to watch for
them I'm why is it why is it echoing
we're not in a
room weo what did you say let's go
it's okay you can tell me they're gone
now it must have been really
funny yeah it was so funny is this the
right
way it was
hilarious oh God
where is the I think it's down
here I think where's oh over
here oh see main yeah
yeah wait how do we get up
there oh this is how we get up
there yeah the
ladder all right well here we go here we
go oh God it's dark it is dark I hate
when it's dark in this game I got a big
[Music]
thing I'll put this outside I'll be
right
back don't don't
die not going to die right going to be
okay are you
alive yeah oh okay I'm going the other
way dead
end what was that
sound we
to yeah think I hear
something uh-oh I found the big thing oh
okay what was that sound I heard like a
I'm scared by
myself is it you you going to try the
scrap yeah it's
me there a scrap gotcha in this game
where where are you oh oh there's a
turret there's a turret down here oh
maybe I'm near
you
ging out your turret I'm closing that
[Music]
door there's a turret that room oh okay
sorry yeah I hav let's go the other
way no no no down here yeah that's down
there yeah there yeah
okay okay other way it is did you go D
yet
uh no I haven't gone
downstairs oh it's a bug it's a bug oh
but it's nice right no it's the one that
steals what it's a loot bug like the one
that goes on your face no it's the one
that takes your stuff oh God they're
everywhere e e
is oh
God what was that look even
loot
bug maybe yeah but they don't kill you
unless you're holding something right
that they like I think so did you know
there's a mod where you can make it say
yippe what yeah it's a dead end someone
in my CH said the yipp bug yes the yippe
bug I found him he's on top of a
key what do you want Oh don't take it
what if I do
[Music]
oh what's
happening did you take
it did you take it no I just walked up
to
[Laughter]
him wait a
second Oh I thought I saw something
here oh what do I hear oh
[\h__\h]
what was that I don't know my screen is
still like woo yeah mine too what
happened was that the bracket I don't
know you're Moon
walking Hing are you okay are you okay
are okay is that her name yeah yeah
yeah um turn
around
nor way I saw two of
them yeah me
too I think one just
finished
am I
back oh gosh am I
back
literally literally I was just like a is
like I don't know how to get back and
I'm like oh I know the way follow me and
I disconnect oh gosh I'm so sorry you
guys so
[Laughter]
sorry oh I knew this would be scuffed
but it's so
bad yeah maybe I will end stream and
just uh
and just
uh play off stream I I know we wanted to
play for like two hours so maybe just an
hour of my POV and then hopefully an
hour of me being able to play the
game so um I will still be playing
obviously just uh go watch from you know
either wewa or kiar or nissa's POV so
I'm so sorry sorry guys I I I I really
there was an attempt for real there was
a try
so what I will do is maybe I can like
stream or not stream I can uh maybe I
can
uh I'll record if I if I get anything
funny I can like uh I can post it or
something fine so you
can you can see
it okay
all right guys well then I'm going to
head out um I'll of course still be in
the other in the collab in general just
uh I tried I don't know why it's so bad
today
so
[Music]
yes are you okay you want to come back I
want to come back yeah I'm ending My
Stream so I'm going to just play oh okay
yeah yeah yeah okay
[Music]
okay okay all righty then guys oh to pee
I'm so sorry we scuffed but um yes if
you want to if you want to see more go
to another
place
yeah byebye a b guys thank you um let's
raid uh like we were or something give
me a second to set it up I'm just going
to end it I'm not even going to go to
the ending screen we're just going to
we're just going to scaddle out of here
oh my gosh wait can I raid Kiara will it
let me
save I've never raided Kiara before I'm
going to try it
okay
bye
[Music]
by