[Music]
so
a hill
wasn't even the curse
sorry guys for keeping you waiting we
actually were ready to start on time but
then um
we we [\h__\h] chatted too much behind the
scenes uh in the learning center but
here we are
keyword
kiwi oh
kiwi can you keep it
[Music]
that is hard to pronounce but um don't
worry guys about what you see right now
it may say summer day one but um mummy
sees the
the fall levels yeah so she will select
it on her side
this game is cute and all but
just like last time we had some
confusing moments where it's like why is
it not more obvious like what we have to
do right moment
yes why doesn't it tell you a button to
press to get to the main menu yeah why
is that weird and it's not entered and
it's not escape i'll tell you that
it's not none of that
it's not that
whatever yeah the hud
is confusing but
uh we made it work
thank god
and thank thank you mume for keeping
the safe file safe and stored and secure
yeah oh it's good oh he's good we're
we're um
kind of partner looking today right
mummy
kimono yeah what kind of whites
wow
flowers
say so oh my god
well well well it almost looks like
we're going to a wedding but we're gonna
go to the post office
we're at the post office um oh gosh
oh i wanted to mention that
to make this work
i have a kiwi open on my old pc but i'm
playing it streaming to my new pc
so if i am bad it's lag um
it's not my fault it was it's just
that's also like uh
sad that that's necessary why did it not
you're on the same steam account right
i'm on the same steam account yeah
it's just
it's saved until i guess i don't know
why steam cloud didn't
spread over but wait how about how are
you streaming it to the other pc with a
cable or
no it's
a family stream has something where you
can connect
uh so it's just i is there something
play to open a game it says connect and
so
what's streaming from that pc style on
this pc that confuses me oh it does not
support cloud safe or is that so okay oh
my god really yeah really okay i might
hear it a bit
quiet me only a little bit
sorry i'm so loud
she says very
calmly
very calmly
sorry about that
it was okay i think maybe now maybe no i
mean she that was on purpose obviously
okay my eyes twitching since like 20
minutes before it's really annoying you
guys maybe don't see it but my left eye
is twitching i think it's the stress man
no
don't you get twitchy eyes sometimes
it's been a while but it wasn't because
of stress it was i don't know what was
happening well
well but i i unders i understand how and
why it happened oh
okay my eyes are alright though i'm
squinting a lot today i don't know why
squinting
maybe my eyes are swollen i don't know
right in your room maybe
no i just
i don't
i don't know well
well i can see you need
you need you need maybe mummy needs
glasses
but i can see or maybe you need one of
those um
pc glasses
oh the blue light filter glasses yeah i
don't know i tried them before but i
don't know if they really i mean
supposedly they helped supposedly
supposedly or is it a scam
makes me look like a
gamer i think if you wear them a long
time long term then
it will have
not a good effect but it will at least
not have a bad effect on you and
it will it will it will um keep the eye
horde away
no
someone says they really help i think
they do help but not like no we do yeah
it's not a huge difference but
it will maybe make a difference in 20
years
that's that's a good point actually i
think my eyes are so bad because i spent
so many years behind a monitor movement
what crazy things speaking of glasses
okay uh the day before yesterday
i i learned something in my stream uh in
a super chat i think
um someone told me
about
did you know there's rose tinted glasses
for chicken
no you didn't know are you taking it
like literally they're literally like
four glasses like they make glasses for
chicken but
the purpose of what it is for is kind of
disturbing
but maybe not for you because uh your
whole brain is sometimes very disturbing
but i'm just
oh my let me try to explain it
so it's like tiny glasses they look
actually pretty cool and you can buy
like sets of hundreds for a really cheap
price because you know normally you have
a lot of chickens
and
what it does is apparently chickens have
a problem with um
eating each other
oh
and eating each other yeah cannibalism
and because they're kind of aggressive
and they like to peck each other
apparently we don't have that problem at
kfp though but with those glasses it
makes their eyes
um not see not i think not see blood
i think
and then because they don't see the
blood it it makes them not want to
attack each other but if they see blood
they get aggressive and attack and and
eat each other activate something i
think yeah yeah yeah
i don't know how necessary that really
is
[Music]
or just like a normal
farm
i i think it's if anything it's probably
just used in like big factories
because then you have so many chickens
you know
that it might become a problem
yeah it calms them down yeah
it's so stopping yeah
[Laughter]
yeah i've never seen apparently this is
a pretty normal thing but i've never
seen it before
it doesn't look like cyborgs or
something
[Music]
what is this
what did you for some reason it's also
recommending me chicken helmets i'm so
like a motorcycle huh is it for the
chickens who try to escape to while
flying but they can't fly so they hurt
themselves or what maybe
i don't know what this
is glasses again
things a lot of weird things out there
um
but nothing quite so weird as two kiwis
working in the post office
did you hear that segway oh my gosh oh
that transition
bringing us back
nice
so um
uh mummy let's go let's start the the
fall season
and do our best let's see if we can
remember
and is it
segue or is it segway
wait
what say wait how do you is it
like segue into a new topic or segway
the
like a sick way you ride oh
segway but a lot of the chat are not um
actually writing it correctly
i don't know how it's yeah it's written
say go ahead but pronounce it okay okay
all right are you
oh
it says that it's waiting for a response
don't worry i was sick
i see it i was waiting for the right
moment
oh this quality is horrendous but it's
fine
oh no
you're gonna have a figure it out some
some debuffs there on you
okay so we have uh
uh what yeah
i'm gonna look at it all items now need
two different stickers
um now oh
smarter labeling okay
wait that's it oh that's it yeah oh
that's it okay
okay
three
[Music]
an urgent pile of autumn leaves
cute okay so
these aren't crushed into leaf dust on
the way it's definitely urgent but what
with the second uh perishable oopsie
parachute maybe the second one
oh they're not crushed what are these
what are they fragile
are they fragile uh
um are they
because they can be crushed
where are the stickers yeah where are
they i found there's a perishable top
right and urgent out here i'll i'll take
it
oh you got urgent i got urgent
where's fragile
uh fragile's over here
fragile is in my soul cause i'm so
fragile
why don't you use my
it's you're fragile you want to do
fragile oh no
what a word perishable was for fruit
right but i'm thinking that leaves you
know if you leave them if you leave them
for too long then they also get like
black
that's true but it did say that they
didn't want to be crushed the clock is
ticking let's just try it oh okay
um
yeah first don't we have to put the lid
on it where's the lid where's the lid
it's been so long
maybe it's just the lid
what is that a pick-up lid oh yeah the
crane
i think that is the you have to come
over here oh okay oh yeah let's do it do
it together okay okay okay
uh okay
uh
so
i'm i'm left on the right you're up and
down so ah ah wait no we put the stick
up wait damn it we put the stickers on
the lid before apparently
do it before
oh shoot okay
okay out of here okay urgent
okay so the order was right after all
well good to know
oh
sticker okay let's hope this is correct
okay
i trust you mommy i'll leave that one to
you
wait how do i
ah now i'm now i'm down and up and you
are left and right
what no no no no no i'm not i'm right
never mind what the hell sorry
i'm
that's me right
that's me that's it that's my button
this there
the button
press down what happens if you press
down
i it's that
oh
oh my god our first day back at work is
like well really bad
okay and that is like that salty flag oh
yeah the number five one one three where
was the number five one one three
five
one one one three
wait oh take it take it yes don't [\h__\h] i
got it and now i got it uh it is south
right what how do we do this one again
that way and then this and you jump on
it or this one yeah i think okay
[Laughter]
okay so now let's try faster oh pumpkin
like best scene
pumpkin you can make it doesn't form
okay
cool and dry or right oh oh
this might be heavy and perishable i
would agree i keep on pushing them see
don't worry okay i've been doing it too
uh so honey and perishable top right is
uh
oh yeah
[Music]
okay you sounded like mickey mouse
wait this one only has one
no no no no no
that was weird nice
that was odd okay i'm ready okay
uh
up lid
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
oh
yeah that one
nice
was it lake bessie i think it was like
thank you i think it was like bessie
yeah
four
one there it is
[Applause]
i got it okay and then no
i think north no no no we go
there we go
oh [\h__\h] oh god
four packages and we just did two
okay okay we're ready for this last okay
those are specially made spectacles at
home and they say we are no no no no
we're going i can't believe it
okay fragile and virgin
yeah yeah i would say so too and belle b
okay fragile urgent
okay
fragile's top left okay
and then urgent i think was bottom right
right
oh right yeah there it is
oh yeah there let me up here and then
i'm
i have it oh my gosh i forgot you have
to put your butt
your butt there
and
south i think
was it wait we gotta put the lid on no
it was north oh yeah oh yeah put the lid
oopsie
a bit more up
oh sorry
and there we go we got it
what is the heck is that
william
urgent and heavy and heavy okay urgent i
have heavy
urgent is bottom
right
yeah
yes give me it
i already did it
oops oh gosh
why did they say we're going
what was the place how do we check it
again yeah
i don't need a lake where it was was it
the lake for the boat or am i is there
are there more lakes
oh uh um
[Music]
okay okay
uh two two four one two two
ma'am counting on you
i'm gonna wait where's it
um
[Music]
excuse me excuse me
i'm sorry
let's see almost there conditions
[Music]
it's going too fast and they expect me
to work like this
what's up
okay okay okay okay okay the fourth one
here we go
[Music]
um don't count for any yeah not even
silver okay
well the first one that took us a bit
the first one took us like half the time
because we were just refreshed
okay
we needed some that's normal we needed
some time to refresh our brains our bird
brains um
yeah exactly totally normal
so
that was day one guys
that was
day one isn't it nice to go back to work
oh yes i missed the office
oh i missed it oh yes i already missed
the office can they come back for a
renewal
did you watch the office
i did watch the office
it seems like you would like that kind
of humor
i used to
it was like the show i'd have in the
background while doing literally
everything in the background for me it's
definitely a a foreground kind of show
before well i guess the first time i
watched it i watched it but then after
that it just played in the background
okay now that's okay forever that's okay
oh [\h__\h] start the day
brush your teeth turn on the office yes
turn around
watching the office in the office
transcription turmoil splice some split
spells what sentencing oh this one i
remember this one you remember it oh the
center i remember this one oh okay okay
now this one supposedly is a bit more
difficult than before or two
how so should we look at the braille
some words
bits
okay
outline bits can be cut in half once
with the
descript
how does it let me oh there we go
oh only the ones with those outlines
okay in case we need like two letters or
something from them
oh dear okay
we can do it
where am i
[Music]
uh what's the message uh
what's the message i i think he has this
tape
i'll take the tape the tape the tape we
put it in here
oh wow
then you play listen
step step poison ivy it's an iv you're
stuck okay
oh you got the poison okay we need to
get the point i see i have it here too
i'll take it evie
oh there's another over there
and this is right i can get it looking
for the words is fun look at it i like
it
you get
[Music]
it will come back it will come back we
got it nice
sun oh i have to move this one a
person's
son yes yes
my butt will take will rip away the sun
from the person
oh yes
nice make him cry make him suffer there
we go
from there
i love the toaster yeah my mommy sorry
i'm sorry this
is two one
oh you try
even though you have lag okay i got it i
always do it when you say two ah fruit
oh fruit okay
i'll
[Music]
oh you died oh that's okay that's that's
just that's what's what comes with this
job it's okay
um
squash
who is here
oh i'll get squash
[\h__\h]
squash
shed
and mine's over here in my mind my mom
my mom
yeah oh it's jumai i got this one
right here my my gore gourds what what's
what's
that fruit
or
it's like a oh what do you call them
simmer to squash
herbs
[Music]
where's pumpkin no no i mean
oh yeah wait what
the the
thing is a pumpkin
oh okay
i was looking everywhere but you're
stamping on your butt
oh do you cut this out here
[Music]
i didn't even jump properly okay three
two one
i was too fast okay
on on on
like after one
three two one
i'm uh you're not standing correctly
am i not and now you're
three two one
okay i do have to do one two i was
thinking maybe not okay okay three two
one
yes right on two okay don't think too
much
we gotta first try without thinking too
much just
we're not even at half time yet let's go
go go gold medal over here we're too
good
hyena stole my pies hyena's over here
wow that's so rude stole my not stone
stove
[Music]
oh
was the place it was pies
it was pies
ah we can get the e s from the bees and
the pie is already there yeah take the
pizza pie hi
hi
oh and then b
a e s
espanol y
guys
ready
yes
okay sorry
three two
one
yeah let's go
okay okay wait can i right can i pause
for a second this is paused
yes okay so it's just a month i want to
check if if everything's okay in the
chat
can i go to an idol meeting i have to go
really badly okay go go go i'm gonna go
really fast
sorry i coffee i'm sorry i just have to
go
to idol meetings sometimes guys
um
i think
i think chad is fine wait you guys have
you seen any any you know you know what
i don't even want to say it because i
don't want to summon it have you guys
seen something
it's fine right
are we safe
nothing suspicious okey-dokey coolio
coolio
everyone's behaving i didn't want to
have the subscriber mode on because you
know
the the humans right humans
the mummy fans i wanted you guys to be
able to chat as well even if you're not
subscribed to me but you know there you
go you could you could subscribe to me
i mean you don't have to so i didn't
want to force you guys even if you
weren't subscribed you would have needed
to be subscribed for two weeks so you
know anyway anyway uh-huh you could you
could
maybe if you wanted to i mean it's not a
must but
i would appreciate it did you know
are there even any humans where are the
humans
oh mummy is back i think i love humans
i did it i did it okay
isn't it nice to have
or is it is it is it like do you guys
because you're an owl and they're humans
you guys have problems like
communicating
sometimes
are they humans are they humans
are they
uh
it's actually not specified what they
what they are or whatever
it could be a hybrid of some sort yeah
cause of who
is humans who only communicate with hoot
hoots maybe mm-hmm
yes
okay
what's up
suddenly stressed as hell go go man
why
why is it saying i can't tap it excuse
me i'm tapping it
what it's okay i'll keep on feeding the
bird that's really weird it's lighting
up it's fun i'll i'll
do it i'll try it lights up oh maybe
it's because there's no fruit there's no
fruit
oh fruit fruit oh all your fruit
fruit i got your fruit i got your
favorite wow wow wow
middle spot what the hell there we go
right it's weird
it lit up but it was it said you
couldn't do it was it always this
difficult
no i don't remember anything about
different
time it was tapes verb big freaking verb
stop it you look weird you look like a
dinosaur stop touching our tapes
stop it
they're top secret campfires out safely
i found fires and camp
and plenty you just put them down here
punch put
camp can't come back
[Music]
it's also at the top on top of
that oh it's up there now okay i'm gonna
remove save from scene
okay
put cam and then we'll just brilliant so
it's right here okay so uh is here
i'll see
oh what campfires oh alex
out yes
oh this one is fast we have everything
already nicely um cam fires out safe
safe
do you feel it do you feel the
the teamwork yo hello i steal the
teamwork this is our fastest message
three two one
oh my gosh games you
[Music]
oh i think not even close
it's our refresh we're refreshing we
don't need that we don't need these
colors to make us feel successful
now
it's no
it's just about getting it done yeah get
the freaking job done
let's get it done and and you know
having fun at work is is the most
important thing okay
exactly you don't want to do too much if
you go too fast do too much you'll get
burned out exactly so
yeah exactly what's the next thingy day
three
okay
[Laughter]
are you okay
did you oh good
did you read something exciting
no okay is that really how you sound
to burp like i hiccup instead because i
don't want to burn
oh and uh so you know how it's like air
coming up right
i didn't know that it was an option to
hiccup instead of burping oh you can't
yeah you can you can teach yourself what
i mean i have i am able to mostly um
keep my burps quiet but i didn't know
you could do something like that so is
it is
was never an option for me
you have to teach yourself do i need a
dlc
i think so yeah you need a dlc you gotta
watch tutorials on youtube how to turn
your burp into a hiccup what
nobody ever told me
i've always been grossed out by burps in
general so i'd never let myself do it
yeah so now it's the hiccup
okay
yeah it movement it didn't sound like a
hiccup though well okay that time it
wasn't a hiccup it was what would be a
hiccup but i was speaking it so my voice
just went super high because of the air
okay it makes sense i don't know how to
like it it just sucks
um
oh yeah who's either hiccup burp or
start speaking super high
i will try that next time when i feel
like i have to burp
i'll try it out you know what yeah just
remembered i have a helium balloon
in my home right now
and i've been wanting to use it to uh
you know
um
picking up my noises
oh my gosh
[Music]
anyway let's start day free
oh you're gonna get fired yeah like no
you were caught up eventually i think
[Laughter]
you sound like you are disappearing
to be closer
let me let's do it
wait did i press start oh i need so
sorry oh
okay
i get confused i think did i first start
because it's god damn it this game
keyboard commotion this one i remember
this one i keep saying i remember it
yeah then i always need to refresh
let's go
what is the new new challenge all right
yeah what makes this even more difficult
nothing
wait nothing
okay okay it was already uh
this is as it was i'll be on the left
side again mama's like oh okay okay okay
okay um visit okay i have v
v
oh do they change did that just happen
or is it changing
this is it i should stay there i'm
getting it i have the team
visit ohio
[Music]
your buttons
wait no no you have someone else to hold
it down
oh i don't think it is i think i'm
pretty sure
this oh sorry
[Laughter]
yeah it does change that's the
difference change they didn't tell us
okay
ready yeah
only one has to push
that all right i changed that's up it's
up there i'll get it okay i'll get it
i'll get it okay oh there i didn't see
it i never look there visit uh
i have the e ah okay
space
fungus the capital capital fungus
okay i'm on the app
okay
here you go i think it's like yeah the
the capital is like kind of like time
time
it will only stay capitalized for like a
certain amount of time maybe i don't
know thank you good girl
and you asked us us
[Music]
you guys see how much
it is
all the walking i i appreciate it
uh
oh and then together we press the last
one three two one
is like
like something like a mushroom right
right
fungus fungi
fungus is like a is that in a mushroom
something you have an a here
okay
and then uh where is r or
up there
i go i got
what did you ask me fungus mushroom
fungus is a mushroom right oh yeah okay
now like
your mushroom and was like this is this
is fauna's domain
remember last time i
oh i have the o last time i told you
about my berries on my balcony
yeah
um do you like mushrooms too cause for
some reason in between my my raspberries
um
mushrooms have started to grow that's
really
oh do you like them
i don't like them but i shouldn't um
those are apparently mushrooms that you
could eat
um but
uh
only oh we're already done okay three
two one
sorry three two one
but you're only supposed to eat them
when they're really really young the
ones that i have growing you know
oh
you're talking too much wait are you on
the sea are you standing right now
okay i'm standing on the sea
but it's not letting me press it
huh
here we go
that's weird okay
so where where's the e is it we got it
cement
oh just stop it
a lot
and i have nothing
good i saw this over here
[Music]
stuck
it's running away from me i can't i
can't tell let's see
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
stop stop stop stop stop just stop stop
before it changes
here we are where you're dying and
you haven't ever have it at all
stop breaking
what my my
what could you be raking what could they
be doing
you're not standing on it properly
oh yeah you're right you were mine oh
sorry hi
i'm thinking so hard about this lee oh
oh of course i thought
but i was like what's your problem with
someone raking your leaves at least
someone is doing the the job for you
yeah i kind of thought it'd be a body
part or something
live live live i'm doing something
yeah yes nice yeah three two one
you've done it
oh how long did it take us oh that's
still silver
oh that's okay
good [\h__\h] chatted so
so anywhere at a moment i'm taking it as
a no for the mushrooms
i like mushrooms i eat mushrooms last
night oh okay but you shouldn't eat the
ones i have with my balcony they were
edible but only for only at the very
short period yeah right by the time i
visit they will be there
yeah i'm gonna
i'll rip them out because they're like
getting more and more and more and i
feel like they're taking the space from
the raspberries i'm gonna rip them out
okay
no they're not
you guys don't understand they're
actually it's just that some mushroom um
have to say uh the the spores were
probably in the soil that i bought that
happens sometimes guys it's pretty
normal my mom told me so too but um and
my mom also told me it's no problem to
leave them because they look cute and
funny it's not a parasite guys i thought
so too but my mom said no and if my mom
says no then believe it trust her
but but yeah um i'm gonna rip them out
because now they're not edible anymore
anyway because they're already too old
and i don't like mushrooms anyway so
yeah getting rid of them but they're not
really like a problem
for the for the other plants that are
growing there it's just sometimes thank
you sometimes they're just in in the
soil or they could also fly the spores
you know they could fly and plant
themselves yeah and mama tony we trust
very wise why is mama and mama buddy we
trust oh is this new no
is it no the octave what's her name is
her name
no zodian
difficult one i'll do the i'll do the
luggage again okay
because i think we
yeah there's navigate packages through
the all right right i'm gonna move the
one to south and and north i think again
never get paid for this
yeah
sometimes we have to do it together
though i think
okay ah
slam the button let's call it ground
pound to rotate male cubes
she's different what
butt slammed the button
so it rotates oh
yeah oh you have to you have to
see where if you can't find what you're
looking for then you might have to turn
some of them around mm-hmm
okay
yes i think i am on the right side here
here i am chad you're sure
um okay
okay no problem i'm i'm gonna first oh
so rotate let me rotate it
sorry oh what
what are you rotating why are you oh i
thought i don't know why i thought it
would rotate
i'm so sorry i thought it would rotate
things for you i thought
okay so what am i doing
i take letters yeah yeah yeah how do we
know what goes where
uh it's been too long huh uh there's
some letters here what's your name
supposed to go here
uh what
ah this one for example this one sits
our
door
goes up here right for example how do
you know
because it says name here
oh
this one i wrote it on the on the board
and now there's nothing else uh okay
maybe you need to get her to somehow
give you another one
uh
i don't know is this part of me it just
rotates the like where
uh
how do i i think this was like it's
mostly operated by you so i don't really
remember
i don't remember either also i think i i
don't know
okay now i do number two
uh
um
oh okay
let's go down this way you get the north
one oh oh okay
oh i see i see i'll figure this out okay
there's there's just packages left
oh no there's a i think there's a new
oh oh it was just packages left i was so
confused i was just looking
okay okay okay
and now she's going to give us a new
name okay okay again okay phantom
functions
okay
she changed oh this is she changes the
field where i can move the packages
oh
what about where's the belly thing
velvee yeah oh that one
[Music]
sure
there's some letters in in uh though and
in did you see him oh i did not see that
wait let me put it out why can't i put
it in oh
huh
i got it why is it
part of me is it wrong
i need to take it out first and put it
here
okay
uh
huh is it really the right one oh i did
i grabbed the wrong one i grabbed the
wrong one don't look at me i grabbed the
wrong one okay grab the right one i'm
sorry it's long one you need some burp
glasses after all
i might oh i died
no
did you fall into the water is that how
you die
yes
oh okay and then how do these work i
actually don't know ah orange okay i
think it switches here yeah yeah yeah uh
here okay
okay
what what's left
is there one was it not the right one
huh oh it was turn it around
huh
oh
you have to like activate the bells
somehow okay okay
okay
don't worry about it
don't worry about it we got it we got it
i'm gonna do the luggages
working hard on the luggages
okay i gotta start packing for my
vacation too
oh yeah
oh are you excited i bet why am i even
asking
actually more worried right now
oh really yeah cause it says that the
weather is gonna be stormy every day
oh no
yeah but like i'm hoping that it's like
not the whole day
or if it's stormy that it's not too bad
because it's still gonna be hot
apparently
but
we are me and dana are entering the oh
the um
the islands
at the moment where the monsoon season
starts
oh
to all my german speaking viewers right
now i am telling you ich mustorten
monsoon
it turned in bed and ended outside this
kind of thing with it
it's a german
i would say meme song
means
it wasn't so bad what the hell even
though we had so much time to think what
we were doing
if we did all these we'd get gold if we
were refreshed we get gold on
all of it so i'm still laughing about
the meme
oh my germans my germans
okay oh it's not so bad i think next
time we do that one we could get silver
so too but now it's supposed to get
harder but we remember
a night post oh it's night time night
time
it's night time working at night really
i don't know what post office does at
least not is this redacted do they work
at night
they have the same glasses the chickens
have oh [\h__\h]
does that mean that they have the same
problem with cannibalism and pecking
we have uv light to reveal oh
you have to use the uv light what
oh secret bird okay that's it
we have to run on top of everything to
see it okay i'm doing oh no
i'm the one on the bottom right chad you
show yourself what are we what are we
writing first of all
put this there yes
[Music]
ah maybe just in the very moment where
we write the message when we hear the
message yeah
thing
i see but we uh we can cut the deed if
we need to maybe
we have an ear
oh don't take it anywhere
oh no i'll put this one uh here for now
in case oh we have to cut them still
maybe yeah
is there anything else
oh here i found it
i have the easy
we need
and there's the right these phone names
or something
new
we need we need decode names we need
code name oh we don't need oh b is not
i got
co here
[Applause]
[Music]
oh god
i was looking for something to cut up
okay
three two one
for me
[Music]
okay okay here's the night shift here
all right
[Music]
okay
you got it oh i got it next tape
i'll press the button there we go meet
at the
query meet at the query and there's the
qe for the query
i'll put it down here already oh maybe
they eat two ah
yeah
and then and then we do this one
what's your
me
oh we got the apps too from that yeah
but we need to oh yeah first it's over
here i got oops i picked up the wrong
one i picked the black one get on my
butt i'm gonna get
well it man teamwork
meet me do you have the at where one's
at
the e ah there's a t-i-g here oh yeah
quick
query
[Music]
ready
three two
so one the music is really chill in the
game too can you guys hear me look i'm
pressing the wrong button
there we go
set all right next one
okay you go all right
[Music]
i look for house
oh
[Music]
three two one
that just feels so good when that works
i know right
moment actually i wanted to ask you
because we're in autumn right now
are there any kind of things that you
like to do in autumn
[Music]
she's thinking so hard she doesn't pick
up the tape
did you that heart i don't know i'm
thinking what other people do in autumn
but i don't know if i do anything in
particular in autumn
really i forgot the secret handsome the
secret handshake there's
there's a hand and there's a shake right
here so we have this
[Music]
everything that we
a second i see it
oh you already made two words nice
secrets did you put uh ah okay
yeah
see
have you ever drinking have you ever
tried the pumpkin spice latte before
i have actually not tried
the pumpkin spices
[Music]
three two one
i've never tried it before either what
the hell we're both funny no i said that
because
i was trying to think of stuff to do in
autumn and my first mine went to whereby
the first thing i thought of was pumpkin
spice i know that's an autumn one
i never i don't think i've even had one
i don't know wait why is it not working
[Music]
oh
that's always so close to silver
yeah
it's because we're talking while we're
playing yeah we could do better if we're
focused but who wants that yeah
yeah you guys want to silently uh
silently play in focus mode
yeah are we wait and which week are we
[Music]
second week which day
six okay
we just did six oh we're doing six now
we are going to do six now okay okay
we'll go though that's so we're pretty
speedy damn we did one two three four
five five levels in one hour
speed
this is with a thunderstorm just like in
my upcoming vacation okay
oh no
what does chad like to do in autumn is
there anything you guys like to do in
autumn yeah
did you say anything you'd like to do
kiara
you see i only wrote down the question
to ask you later my men wrote down the
answer
i actually don't have an answer myself
oh hi king oh hiking and all them sounds
good yeah because summer is like too hot
tonight like
watch youtubers watch kiara that's not
autumn specific
hello
you only do an autumn
these people have great ideas we should
try some of them
i want to go camping with holo
fake pies
thanksgiving feast
uh
pumpkin spice renaissance festivals oh i
i used to go to medieval festivals
when i was when i was younger
but that was not only not that was
mostly in the summer time actually corn
mazes i've never seen that before i
think that's actually a thing oh yeah i
think it's an american thing wait [\h__\h]
it's really a monsoon
oh this is too relatable
[Music]
okay let's see what we have to do here
malfunctions oh no
is this how my hotel is gonna
malfunction
are they gonna are we gonna get
electrocuted follow the changing rules
as juliet calls them out oh okay they're
gonna be changing in between overcharged
look we're charged up oh one it makes
sense oh my gosh
um
glow like where uh
banana
okay banana are you yellow
uh yellow for you
not yet when active keys must be typed
two at a time
oh
that's a match for the charge when
acting oh
okay acting keys must be typed
oh okay okay okay okay i think i
understand when active the screen shows
nonsense oh
no it's a ping one
it's a big one oh no
oh this is gonna be tough maybe
okay okay
find the roommate
all right
all right wait how do we hit
what
heights kites okay phone keys doesn't
match whatever kites okay okay okay
[Music]
there you go
okay all right i'm on the right side i
but the t must be from you because it's
red up here oh sorry yeah i forgot okay
and then i do the e
uh okay and after s down here okay okay
okay i'm blue bird right now
[Music]
have see
oh i can do the o is up here
or
and use here
ah okay oh finally
[Music]
thank god that is nice the scores kind
of described okay
three two sorry one
no
heights discouraged
double input oh no
no oh we have to do m and y at the same
time
y capital what about capital oh sorry
you're right you're right okay
okay but the y
i don't understand but this one it
doesn't really count we have to do these
two at the same time
only these two okay my
hat oh we have to do h and a at the same
time ah
oh sorry uh three two one
um
three two one
uh
i got l okay l
three two one
okay oh thank goodness this is
impossible without voice chat uh he's on
the other side it's just switched okay
three two one
okay okay three two one
away okay i got to put you okay two one
ah okay
uh oh yeah
three two one
okay okay
nice not bad but pretty fast holy [\h__\h]
double implant again okay because we
type two at a time okay where's the e
where's
e oh no capital capital oh capital first
okay okay
okay chad is asking where's the rest of
them shut up three two one
there's no rest of them three two one
okay
okay there's the teeth don't disappear
on us again
three two one
one two one
okay nine two three two one
okay
hi
three two one
oh okay
three two one it's all same right now
we'll have conversation again later
three two one
i have to count yeah i know there's no
room for calls going up here three two
one
three two one
okay
so rude changing the moment we're
jumping no three yeah
fun
oh it worked that time though three two
one i'm sorry too early oh it went down
okay
[Music]
okay cool cool story was it
evacuate evacuate okay but i still see
it where's the what it's like it doesn't
light up anymore i think it's just the
message is going to disappear oh okay
so we can't see if there's any typo okay
i mean
i got it
are you doing it okay okay okay you like
you ate
oh no oh [\h__\h] okay it is a little bit
difficult because now you're like where
did we go wrong how far back do we go oh
[Music]
what why is it red now
i pressed
e why why why a
q-u-a oh i guess we didn't press t
because it's behind on okay okay okay oh
wait him press yeah i guess what
i thought we did press key okay i i
understand there you go okay this was
more difficult okay oh
[Music]
over
evacuated areas three two one
nice evacuation successful
oh oh
it was difficult with all the counting
that takes some time man
no they don't you don't never understand
maybe i should have counted one two and
not three two one to save some seconds
okay
oh well i'm proud of us moment
i think we did we got bonus pay
oh how do you even see how much we're
making money no not really it's fake
money don't don't even
don't even get your hopes up
where is this money that we're making
what's our salary here good question i
want to see my contract what what are
the what do you think
what i'm on my contract i didn't even
sign a contract what the hell
maybe i was brainwashed into it i don't
remember how we got here
yeah right how did we turn into kiwi
burps i thought we were a phoenix in an
owl
also don't you have as much as the as a
knowledge council don't you have better
things to do anyway than working in the
post office
i could be doing such better things i am
qualified for literally every profession
that ever
totally
yeah
tote yes totally you
you could do so much better meme you
should quit this job as a kiwi post
office person
what am i doing here
life crash qualified yeah man what what
pay sucks time sucks we weren't stuck
hugs in my life though no where where
what happened what happened midlove
crisis movement
what happened oh that's what gets here
and we have to work anyway
what is this is new oh it looks fun
the basement is floating running
diving and helping so we got the mailing
mail
okay
the room looks new
[Applause]
now we get the packages to the dumb
waiter
trip into the tube to send them
chirping
it's still kind of the same like map but
it looks different though there's a
different background i think
hmm the same system bring letters to
matching baskets i'll haul them up
so we can give you a lift with a nearby
palette oh
only at certain times though maybe
does she show up whenever you get close
i wonder okay
uh
okay
okay i'll try the packages again
where am i going what do i do is this
who's this for oh i see how do i even
i make this jump no miss zolly okay i
i'll get a different one i guess
oh that's zoey oh miss zoe they all go
in here
thank you miss slowly
cries
okay and i go this way
are you doing uh okay over there
oh okay can i pick up this fish i can't
pick up the wait wait what i need to get
rid of that what the hell
this is like what do you call that this
is like one of those games the puzzle
games where you move things around
[Music]
what we're doing
where
i wear packages well it's not a jigsaw
puzzle what's that thingy
what's this
the salty scale do you see this wow i
see it that looks special kissing
okay did you hiccup again you're doing a
lot of videos i did
eating cookie a cookie you get hiccups
from cookies what the hell
apparently
what else am i supposed to do i think
this is actually much faster if i do it
with you in this case
what i'm doing right now oh yeah can you
try to move the things on the bottom
right around so that the package comes
over here
the pack
what and the bottom bottom left there's
others
you know like this
uh let's try them
yeah oh i see i see it yeah yeah it's
like that with those puzzles you know
right
this one go this way no no
is everything else done
there we go
yeah we don't see any more it looks
oh
dear
[Music]
it reminds me of those times when we
played for example alice
and we had puzzles like this and i had
the game
the word for me
[Laughter]
you know that alice gang
that disturbing alice game
you would like it
alice you love disturbing things you
should play that alice game
i'll explain it
oh
yeah yeah yeah alice madness returns do
you not know it
i don't maybe if i see a picture
like a screenshot of it i don't know
what you're talking about it's like a
got it remembering names dark alice
mcgee
oh you really don't know it huh me
i gotta google it hmm
i think i can tell you because of the
disturbness it's literally like your
your members emotes
oh really the arts that you draw that's
the vibe from uh alice oh yeah yeah
that's cute god that took me ages what
the hell okay oh that was only one
package we're done good oh wait i also
had some struggles got more stuff there
it is yeah yeah
[Music]
outfit that i drew for fauna
yeah
if you were to dress like you know an
edge lord
yes no like an emo kid what would your
outfit look like
i don't know
i was never very stylish and i also
i i don't know i don't like wearing
tight stuff we're done i think we're
done
am i done oh no there's one here sorry
hmm
i just missed it there we go
you don't like wearing time stuff yeah
i'd wear a black t-shirt oh i'd wear a
black jacket
and a
black hat
do you see this gourmet
what this is
how close like one millimeters
oh we were
[Music]
distract you a little bit maybe
no it's not yoga pants denied yeah does
that mean you don't do you not wear
leggings
i do sometimes
yeah i guess i don't like i don't like
tight uh
stuff like up above my waist
okay
[Music]
i was wearing this new um top today that
looked so cute it looked nice it just
fits so perfectly and it had like puffy
sleeves and it looked so cute i want to
show you a picture
i really like it
[Music]
it felt so pretty in it yeah it had a
really deep v-cut though so i kept on
trying to
to move you know certain things around
something
anyway
but it looks so cute
i wanna see
when you come visit me can i dress you
up in my clothes
yeah
oh my god let's play dress up the people
will not see me but i will see
you okay you know what just don't even
bring clothes i will give you my clothes
i was actually kind of i was thinking to
myself because
i was thinking
do i wear things appropriate for europe
or will i stand out why because i dress
for comfort most days i have some nicer
stuff but
i don't think you can really do anything
wrong in austria people dress like i
think probably
pretty much
roughly the same as people doing
in the other western lands
i think america we america are you are
you sure have you ever seen a walmart in
america and what people
i mean it's so if you would dress like
that in austria in summer i think it's
it's okay yeah
oh no maybe what i'm thinking of do you
dress in walmart first
no i was just thinking of the walmart
[Music]
people wear some funny stuff wait let me
look it i want to look it up well what
should i look up walmart yeah like after
something like that i've seen in
pictures or like i've never seen it
myself at walmart photos okay i looked
up oh wow oh yeah walmart's people
photos
gives you a nice meme okay well don't
dress like this please
i'll say don't dress like that please
cover up your booties and your boobies
and
everything that should not be seen
i'm gonna look at walmart fashion again
oh
photographed and they want to become
famous
for dressing badly
maybe i don't know
it's a meme so i know i guess you can't
call that typical american passion right
one more help not
oh god oh god oh god oh god okay i need
to stop looking at this it's very
disturbing
think of
particular ones
what did they just make oh this is when
i look that doesn't even show what i'm
thinking of i'm thinking of like uh
like body suits i don't know if i can
find the picture that comes to my mind
when i think of it oh my god
well okay let's play um
oh yeah how many clothes do you have do
you also feel like you have too many
clothes because i feel like i have too
many clothes sometimes but then
i feel like i don't have enough clothes
whenever mother al comes to visit she
likes to declutter so we get rid of like
oh half of what i have i don't have that
much to begin with
i wouldn't let my mom do that no no no
never never never
makes money i don't wear it to attach my
closet
not allowed no no no no no i only have
one pair of shoes right now i need more
shoes oh my god someone in my member's
message says as someone who's worked at
walmart for six yes for six years yes
walmart fashion is real and it is
horrifying
it's real it's real
oh no
honestly i think that's if you work at a
place like that
um isn't it nice to have like
something to talk about at work and
laugh about it work like something to
brighten up your day you know someone's
ass hanging out might brighten the day
you just get used to it
it just becomes your daily life if it's
that often you might get used to it
isn't really that often i wonder though
if it's i don't know if it's but
honestly i would i would maybe even make
a game out of it with my colleagues like
let's find the worst dressed person
today and then
give them a mental award
in our
[Laughter]
yeah i need to find what i was thinking
of i must i
because what i looked up was just a lot
of people wearing like basically no
clothes is that even what i was thinking
of yeah
okay anyway uh hold jump for a boost
okay
uh
butt slam their heads to dispense
stickers okay we have robots carrying
the stickers now
but they walk around okay
catch the one you need oh okay wow wow
wow wow everything's like moving okay
pilot it to attach
what
pilot robots
hover hover crane
what okay
you have to catch the when you need what
yeah we'll we'll figure it out as we go
hopefully figure it out
we're not
incoming packages
from you comments about walmart fashion
no thank you
anyway balbi
uh it's an antique a clock okay so it's
probably fragile um it's a lot it's
heavy
handle carefully did i still need two
tags though
i didn't think so it says heavy let's
let's see heavy and
careful
okay okay
fragile and heavy done okay
[Music]
okay where's the okay well that's the
top no no where's that
wait where's the top oh there's ah i see
over here
where it always was that's the only
thing that stays where it always was did
it get bigger the map is this my am i
what where are we sending it to belby ah
wait bobby two here four one six two i
have the the the numbers
wait isn't bella b oh oh sorry i was
looking at bessie don't sorry i think
yeah i think it's bellaby right
it was bobby okay now we need to pick up
the
this the the the lint i think
oh gosh oh
uh okay
okay go go go go go go go go
oh sorry i want to park this is so high
up now
i'll fix it okay
nice
wow
and then it goes uh
it goes
the new amazon drones look neat
honestly i can see a future where things
are gonna get delivered in drones
okay again bellevue again posting this
video right to your voice directly from
the impact side weighs a ton heavy but
we want you we're hoping for speedy okay
urgent and heavy i think
or yes okay all right i got your agent
oh wait i'm just kidding i fell
oh wait we have jet packs forgot about
that where is what is heavy
is it wait is it got it
up here wait this is happening
can i please get on here please
there we go
no it's 4162 again it didn't let me yeah
you uh
switch
oh
they switch it now
oh no
all right it's okay now we gotta pick it
up again
we're doing okay i would say
i think so
down please oh
[Music]
we had too much momentum
okay it's not again
chad are we still fine are we still good
chad are you guys still behaving sorry
where are we going
why not okay sorry
i'll be cookie i was looking at the chat
all so good that's okay just other stuff
[Music]
um
i would say let's just stop here but
it's only been one and a half hours
yeah i mean
we could set up another one but
no i don't wanna i don't know i'm stupid
they're not separated
yeah please
[Music]
no if i if i
ah if i re i haven't had this in a while
but if i restart obs
am i really able to connect properly
back to youtube
but i don't think it's an obs problem
everything's running fine on obvious
you could try
just
might as well give it a shot this is
weird
but
oh
[Music]
i wonder if
the the in between is going to be later
in the archive
i was just sitting there like what the
heck what's happening
what do i do
i lost you guys i thought i lost you
i said something funny chad when when we
were gone i said it's not me it's you
says obs to youtube
because obviously
obs okay youtube you good everything
seems fine now people maybe need to
refresh but
you're laughing for me
so funny man
okay
[Music]
then back to our job man no time to
waste man
yeah no no more thank god he came back i
was worried all right where the hell
where are we what are we even doing we
gotta get the package get the stickers
perishable and uh
if it's wrong then you have to give your
senpai some kisses
oh because you think it might be it
might be uh fragile let me
write down
fragile and urgent though fragile and
perishable
rush order wedding delivery contents one
custom order triple layered marshmallow
batter cake sweet red maybe not those
best eaten fresh it's so definitely
one of even perishable or urgent but
maybe it's both let's try both
let's try both first
maybe like so far we never had them
wrong so maybe
maybe we can't go wrong
yeah we can't we're too
we decide not the game no
if it's distances it may be mistreated
by the post office but it will arrive no
matter what
wait where's the location yeah i'm gonna
drink bro
and three five five six two right here
okay
[Music]
and then oh
one more
yes
this time it was not youtube this time
it was ovs i think it's the revenge from
obs to youtube
obs was like
girl susan
i can do the same thing i can hurt you
like you hurt me
if you feel pain then i want you i want
to feel pain too we're back already
though obs at least comes fast fast it
comes back yeah
[Music]
okay
it's probably fragile and it's urgent i
bet and it's called chuck
why why can't i exit out okay wait why
is the game not letting me move oh
cortana hello okay
that's
[Music]
i'll hatch it don't worry elena
i'll hatch that egg
[Music]
three five six two three five six two
five
this would we would kind of um i think
have some issues here
oh i see it
we can make it work bonk the beaks
yeah well the egg needs some padding you
guys have no idea how to send an egg
properly
uh north i know
dangerous is gonna it's gonna crack
no
oh we're done in there chuck
okay we did kind of
nice not so bad i mean i'm so bad i'm
not so bad
oh is that our money
oh we're repeating stamps i forgot about
that
we get stamps as currency well mate
they're they're probably trying to tell
us that in 30 years it's gonna be really
really really really
um
[Music]
it'll be valuable yes and it will be a
collector's stamp
i thought it wasn't
we get enough to to mail our families
that we need help
out of here
well why why are you watching a
cinematic how are you watching a
cinematic
are you watching it it said
luma is watching
i was watching it it just became
halloween why didn't it show it for you
oh cause i'm still in summer maybe
three now okay
okay that means four more shifts let's
go
tricks and telegrams they're very proud
of their costumes oh halloween costumes
and candy
let's go
let's don't get spooked
what have you dressed up
uh as before
for halloween
i
did not like dressing up so i went as
really dumb things
okay for instance one year i went as
rachel ray who's wearing trim right
he's a television she's a television
like chef
oh
anything remarkable it's basically that
you drew
you dressed up as the cheap version of
gordon ramsay for example right i guess
so but rachel ray doesn't wear anything
she just wears normal clothing guys i
just said i was rachel ray
moment
okay i don't want to go to a costume
party with you because that sounds lame
look
okay now i i dress up more now but
before yeah i think once i was like i'm
a football fan and i wore a jersey of
something
wow i didn't like dressing up wow
okay i see it bye
don't don't make sure to give this verb
the candy when it's asking for it okay
okay oh
yeah and peck the ghastly ghost oh
that's so cute all right two things okay
this candy corn that looks like my sword
okay
oh yeah wait
what is it oh m eg
where
well you want candy how do i get you
candy you get them candy eyes
again
oh it's okay okay okay
[Music]
you get for halloween you know what i
think one person i mostly has to focus
on doing the the letters and the other
one mostly has to focus on doing the
other
things
all right i'll give you the candy oh
that's a cute costume
what annoying
what did you dress up as um
i don't remember everything but for
example i once dressed up as like a
pumpkin girl
that was cute pumpkin girl yeah noise
where's the eat out there what do you
want oh where is this candy there's this
candy oh it's over here
you better don't do anything i'm on the
way
i probably also dressed up as a as a
witch before probably i mean i feel like
every girl once dresses up as a witch at
some point
i'm sorry
what does he want candy corn i got it
but wait the only one i remember was a
pumpkin my
my
oh my my my i see the end oh my
which one you want it's fitting because
pumpkin is orange and i am orange
what's y'all look at it how do you ask
me for candy corn
what do you mean how do you add it candy
corn
attic
because candy corn is gross
oh so why would they ask for i've never
had candy corn before they don't have it
here
so i mean it's like i'll eat it but i
don't understand why you'd ask for it
when you could have gummy worms or a
lollipop or a chocolate okay we're done
by the way uh oh okay three three one
all right three two one
what do you want
more candy toys
i don't like caramel
you don't like caramel i do i do i do oh
yeah you do oh sorry wait
i gotta i need the cap with the leather
thank you
[Music]
being bad at dressing up you're playing
the mom that gives the kids the kids oh
i used to actually enjoy
giving candy to the trick-or-treaters
so i like trick-or-treating myself too
but i liked giving the candy
i haven't been trick-or-treating for a
long time i don't know i did it when i
was younger but that's also thing stuck
that's not so normal in austria
oh is it very common is it like really
like on the halloween you go outside and
it looks like yes really yes like it is
i mean if you know modern family
yeah do you know they have that
halloween episode
which
what happened to them no i died i don't
know it's just uh how we know yourself
but but the streets are we're like
filled with oh so many people
it's kittens in costumes it's not really
oh there's a typo
uh yeah it's normal
every city in town does it damn just
like real yeah
that's crazy
you believe in it so depending what
neighborhood you're into yeah so people
will drive to richer neighborhoods
because they'll be giving out like full
chocolate bars instead of just the mini
ones
i want to experience oh sorry i don't
know i love you marian studs in america
halloween in america sounds like it's so
much more fun
we have to borrow someone's kid
oh no
i'm sorry i wasn't fine
where's the tea
ah up here
little kid
i'm getting kind of irritated um
oh it's my hair now it
is it's triggering me
it's triggering me
three three three two one
oh thank goodness okay give me the next
message your message uses
[Music]
if you want you can find the e ah
there's over here
do you want gummy worms i got you gummy
worm okay not so fun anymore yes okay
we used coffin
used coffee you wouldn't
it does anyone like get second hand
coffins that's like i mean understand
they're really getting coffin but that
sounds kind of
happens to the person
used it before why
maybe a good question does that ever
happen
does anyone ever get exchanged into a
different coffin or or like no coffin at
all and then they're like okay um
what if it's uh
someone that was due to die but then
they didn't and it was like
they would have been used yeah then it
wouldn't be used
for yeah maybe somebody woke up someone
they thought they were dead but they
woke up well that's that's wonderful
but yeah
we're using the coffin is maybe not
maybe not no
yeah just buy a new coffin where's the
oh here
bye
love ones are pretty expensive yeah
uh let's say sale
i see
[Music]
l
nd e
is e is
i didn't look at the time how bad did we
do
[Music]
okay day one of the last week went okay
okay three days
halloween is um
kind of triggering me though in the game
oh
did you have bad halloween experience
no but just in this game it was
triggering me right now i see it's
making you annoyed
uh i'm hungry moment did you see what i
cooked yesterday
yeah
salmon
salmon with potatoes and some kind of
leek sauce cream thingy yeah it was
really saucy really
but do you think it's is it safe to like
if i already grilled the salmon i can
eat it on the second day right
yeah
it's good right
yeah yeah you can eat it okay
wait look
what
what's your favorite mommy what's your
favorite dish
did i ask him
i don't think you've asked me
did i make or that or just in general
just to eat
oh i don't know
i like so many things i really like
lately i've really liked seafood pasta
pop like any
no no sorry i don't like not that i can
wait though i can't only have my room
because because i want i was thinking i
could cook something for you but if it's
something that i wouldn't want to eat
then
oh no oh there's something that you
could make oh i i i'm not a picky eater
ellie that's just really what i've been
liking from if i went to a restaurant
but i want to cook something that you
like
i like everything but when's there's
something besides seafood pasta
this there's so many i can't tell you i
would eat that salmon i'd eat the the
sweet and sour it was a chicken ah it
was not
i i
would have preferred it with chicken i
think but the recipe says pork and and
you know i get the ingredients from from
hello fresh not sponsored
so it's like already decided what i'm
cooking yeah yeah but it would be nice
with chicken yeah
um
but honestly the salmon that i made
yesterday might have been one of the
best things i've made so far
surprisingly
salmon is so good like you don't even
have to do much i just seasoned it with
salt and pepper
and some oil and then those little i
don't know what they're called in in
english but it's called dill in german
so oh i think it's just
oh oh okay yeah yeah but it's like so
simple i i guess lemon okay a lemon
makes salmon just
you don't need anything else just some
lemon man yeah you don't need too much
seasoning with your salmon it's already
got is
i'll make something i mean if if you if
you want i mean i feel like i would want
you to bring you guys to to restaurants
so that you get some really guaranteed
good food and nobody's stressed out but
if we have the opportunity maybe maybe
maybe maybe i can cook i'll try to help
you i'm not very good at cooking like
i'm okay i get by oh what i wanna help i
was thinking i think about this a lot
actually it's been so long since i've
had somebody cook something for me
but like i'm not counting restaurants or
takeout i guess oh
dollhouse i'm like as soon as i miss
living in the nest
because then you know you always have to
guarantee dinner
but
um
i really need to like gather the
motivation sometimes to cook but like
because i already have the ingredients
in my fridge because of you know hello
fresh it's like i feel forced to cook so
then then i do force myself to cook but
then it's really worth it because then i
have some fresh and an original food and
not always the same [\h__\h] from like a
takeout or order like pizza and all that
i know
yeah it's really good i'm not sponsored
i should be sponsored really they
shouldn't really
be sponsored you could do a sponsored
hello
no yeah i would totally do that hello
friends hello hello
look a long time ago i had hello fresh
but it was when i lived with mother al
wow
like the first two recipes we did were
nice but unfortunately the third one
made us feel so sick that we just
turned off
maybe i'm not gonna get sponsored
anymore
but you know it was a it was it was not
you hello fresh just kidding yeah yeah
i've been told from my american fans for
example that they're like i have hello
fresh food i don't get these recipes
what the hell i want these recipes and
i'm like sorry it probably just depends
where you live and like what's how much
things cost
wherever you live
[Music]
okay i'm getting really hungry so let's
finish this game uh there's okay so i've
left two tracks of tara i like these
decorations
ooh is it the luggage thing again oh it
changed again oh dear lord what is this
push carts where they need to go their
sons will tell you oh my god there's
seven changes
carts first go to either the castle or
to the forest to be scared what
[Laughter]
what express goes to either the council
or for what but good luck with that
mummy
on the square button when it's ready oh
my god
little taco
sorry skip that guys after being scared
kart's evil will go out an exit door or
down the slide
how do we know sorry what how do we know
which one it goes to
the numbers okay it's worth an honor
okay but
rotates the track
[\h__\h] this is really complicated we'll
make
i bet we can figure it out okay
maybe we need some teamwork here this
time uh there's two wait there's so many
do i send this up here
okay you
ah yes okay and then and
then oh i did one okay okay it got
scared what now now it's uh it needs to
go down to four nights oh my god what
what wait but i have this wait oh oh
wait why we'll move move
why won't they move i don't they're
supposed to do here i don't know either
right now
uh
what
i have some stuck as well what happened
there's like free down here for you too
what are we doing
move the butt button i can't press i
can't press this button let me never uh
but i can like uh you have to push the
bottom one out oh this one's underneath
it i didn't even see them oh
but there's just three at a time ah this
mine goes to your side so i have to do
this okay okay i'm moving some one to
your thumb it's usually in the forest i
see it it's like okay can you take care
of the middle one
i have to rotate it
um
shoot what
yeah you have to bring it to the floor
uh oh i see i see i see i made a mistake
i see so these ones need to come to you
here that's why they weren't scared
oh
they weren't scared because they were in
the
no no house [\h__\h] it was it would have
been right damn it okay
okay okay this one's for you this one's
for you thank you
oh
wait this one will also be for you these
two
okay so do you take that one this feels
like a boss level man
and you take this one too
put it in the middle
okay
all right rotate oh we fixed it we fixed
it
all fixed all right you all come here
problem solved problem solved
[\h__\h] sake
oh god push it or what
why can i not pull it
okay yes this scares them perfect okay
okay
all right
i don't have to go to the pumpkin
did it work did that work i think it
worked i think it worked all right
these guys have to go to the pumpkin
here oh i gotta scare these guys
that's so beautiful
all right the taco bell
is okay and then this one
um
last second one second is there for you
to go to the pumpkin
these ones go down this way this slide
and when where does this one go
what is this one
bottom to your side now oh my god one
okay
first oh sorry wait wait wait wait first
[Music]
oh okay okay okay wait what are you
doing good
give me them bring them to me i uh i
need to scare someone but it's it's
there to take basically i'll tweet them
here
oh my god
this is one ah one goes to you wait we
can keep it like that the way it is now
yeah here
you're here okay this is okay um
i have to come off you have to push pull
them
[Music]
these are the last ones i think
oh my goodness
oh wait what the hell okay
sorry guys that was a bit stressful
you didn't even get scared i think it
was already scared i think oh but it
needed to be sent there at the end yeah
wow wow was this bad according to the
game oh look good
we were so close
again
[Music]
we got silva for that one okay we
deserve silver we deserve so much next
seconds long damn i mean if we would
redo we could probably get silver but
whatever
we would if we did all of them we would
have gotten at least over yeah we needed
some time to understand wow
let's do it
oh sorry oopsie
yes castle scary meet the spirits of
wicked tide okay
okay
all right
oh goodness
what oh no no explanation okay what oh
we can't
[Music]
oh man
no no keep me okay i have to go no
what if i fall down
oh god don't fall down here i shoulda
when the mic comes back
there it is
hey
no need up desk the desk has to be cut
up i think
what's y'all i got me
or me
ma
mate
okay now it's time to move this for
the sk and the ma we can use later for
mask made mine now we need mine
i got my oh noise
i'm just moving them
and mom
yes
yes yes yes
the toaster okay okay three two one
wait i'm pressing it why does it do this
okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
my scarecrow
ran away oh mine is right there okay
eyes under you and the oh oh oh oh oh
sorry i didn't see you but uh sorry okay
i'll go ahead oh double hit i got it
i'll go to the my
[Music]
my scarecrow ran away my hair curl
scares up here scare
oh scared i have
crew
got this all right
ran
it has a different costume now it's a
pumpkin now
a scarecrow oh it's a scarecrow
it's dressed up as a scarecrow okay
they have really nice ideas they're so
into halloween and they aren't halloween
they're like dressing up my friend's
friend is a bad today
i have uh nothing
maybe
we're gonna use maybe this one for b ah
b either
am i oh that's me i'm sorry i'm so okay
friend and eddie friend dead
a
bat
your friend and a bat
me too i see dave
yeah
where's two
uh i'll find it at the top from the tomb
probably oh my god
probably now get it out of the way
it's stuck look at that can you get them
um wait i got rid of it i got rid of it
nothing
i'm getting them
sorry i was just watching you struggle
oh i gave i'm not giving any [\h__\h]
anymore about dying here
oh yeah i know we come back so fast also
also
two days
three two one
nice
real frozen
[Music]
one more one more one more one more
oh you want to play it you play you put
that in there
in the usual and i play
the moon
so we can get that o-m
oh and there's the o-m-o there's the m-o
uh here
i have the o-n
wait wait we need to get rid of that
there's too many here
okay we cut this one first you bring the
m-o over there
um
[Music]
my little my little bird legs can't hold
my weight no more
breathe
yeah
i see what the problem is i'm sitting on
top of it
we're getting silver for that come on
oh that was six and a half minutes i
[Music]
i thought that would be shorter
it just felt right i feel shorter what
the hell
the game keeps on robbing us okay do we
have one more day left or am i wrong i
think there is one more day oh my god
let's nail the last one
let's do it
and do it
let's do it and i think this is
what yeah
this game is making it uh more time than
there really is um
yes
it's gonna i think it's uh glitching
actually and yeah um yes uh we actually
should be getting uh platinum for every
single one
hundred percent thank you mommy i agree
and mail from beyond i heard a weird
noise from the shipping floor would you
go downstairs and check it out okay um
it's our favorite what is that who is
that it's so cute
big one
there are little witches this time oh do
you see the animation i see an animation
oh yeah yeah this is the last one
happy halloween
i love you there's a bonus autumn is
nice
adam is nice at least oh
wait why should we set everything on
fire moment
why do i take the match maybe
maybe uh oh
oh does it get dark maybe the final
trick of this wicker tight night
and only making with the lanterns light
four packages
all must be sent before dawn and they're
each missing something to let them pass
on
oh wait i have this the mystical map for
reveal each location
but only to those who use coral
paraching
helping lost mail to the other side is
the teleposts duty each wicker todd
[Music]
the that was um this girl cut off my my
witch laugh at the end but yes i
basically heard it and it faded away
wait so wait i didn't really i read it
but i didn't really listen i didn't i
didn't process that at all it's just
listening to your voice okay there's
four packages must be sent before dawn
they're missing something to let them
pass on invisible reveal each location
but only to those who use cardboard
how many last males on the other side
okay
but the same thing first of all i think
you need to turn on the the the
lantern here with your match
oh
desperation is the location
what
okay mom's even using the corn pansy
again before the harvest moon keep this
straw fresh you'll find it right fast
okay perishable and urgent i think
okay
who's this
oh it's not so spooky and there's no
urgent perishable urgent period
it's funny playing music
and there's howdy music going on
well you guys don't hear it probably
yeah
all right
there's desperation what is that we have
to use a ouija board what
oh but we move it ourselves what how do
we i forgot what's going on desperation
desperation potter field
rib cage rock
that's right
two free for free
another match
ah
two two three oh
ah okay
two
three
four
oh that's so fast i got it uh i'm
putting it we brought you oh what is the
key for though
okay
there we go
i know it already feels like morning
time but i guess not quite i know why do
we need matches
oh it's empty where's the stuff mommy
come back
wait where am i oh where's your stuff i
don't have
the inside of it oh wait oh
how do you move it
ah this goes this ghost needs to go
there maybe that's what the ah wait
first we need the
oh wait maybe it's one of these thingies
what do we need we need to turn on the
light first i think
oh wait there are these scissors
i don't know why scissors would do
anything here um where are these where
are these
um
chad do you know how to take the ghost
burn
the carrot nose
carrot nose it needs a carrot nose
oh yeah don't never let him lose his
carrot nose where's the carrot oh
carrot it's over here you got it
i got it okay we have to attach
something
[Music]
thank you chad we kind of ignored that
last sentence
we did ignore the last one
and uh south with myself
oh sorry i forgot sorry
lucky
okay
[Music]
rib cage rock that is a south i already
know
delicate crackers
okay so uh um
um fragile
try not to break if you're feeling
creamy inside a box close the lid but
something creepy
we got an onion we got scissors we got a
key we got a bone we got a party going
on the bone is creepy
that one doesn't work maybe the scissors
scissors is there anything else that's
creepy around here no scissors
there's a rope you're creepy go go to
him
oh you're right i can go inside
what about the balloons
crazy
[Music]
what is this creepy
what's creep there's nothing creepy
creepy
this
music is creepy what about this is this
music
not this
no
is it onion creepy
what the [\h__\h] are you focusing on the
wrong word moment
no maybe they don't care about the
creepiness what does it say
you're trying to kind of put something
creepy inside of a box and make sure
that it locks is it the key
the key
what's the key
[Music]
i was just listening to what you said
movement but the chat said
focus on her last word
uh yeah we gotta go left and you need
you to sit on it
for me left oh that's right
it seems like my brain is also uh
exhausted rib cage rock well um 11 41 11
41 11 4 3 1
you've been snacking all this
time oh yeah i need two little cookies
you okay i have the attack you stand on
the on the thingy
okay
do we even give it a good oh we didn't
even do that yeah
urgent okay it's urgent and fragile yes
okey-dokey
i got the urgentness
fragile
for being the last level the music is
way too calming
i'm getting sleepy don't be sleepy it's
still relaxed turning the light on again
thank you mommy
all right
[Applause]
left and
[Music]
up
have it
oh they popped again
congratulations
all right which way
uh south south south south south
two more
i already have the code
[Music]
oh
i went to the wrong place as well
do you hear the doki doki the chat
doesn't hear it probably but it's really
creepy
sometimes
doki doki sounds we don't even need the
lights to move the lid i think
i think it these it's like the
electricity or something oh okay
there we go
you hear it ah
it's it's me because of you chad being
too cute amazing girl donkey donkey
donkey oh my
oh my
self again i suppose
[Applause]
[Music]
probably perishable
don't go back to me i don't want them to
go battles
i bet it's urgent and perishable no it's
heavy and perishable
it's so heavy she can't lift it
okay and then we're gonna use cheers for
it where does the cheers go
scissors scissors
i put the
where'd scissors go i had them before
the scissors why can i not put it on
here mommy there's no lid oh thank you
where are the scissors
and paris i'll go i'll go get perishable
while you're looking for the scissors i
got the scissors
oh
i need some light
mama
right i thought
there would be like
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh it's the last one mermaid almost
makes me feel sad to send it off i don't
want to almost
oh no our shift will be over
you're taking me very seriously
we didn't get silver because of you
waiting for five seconds
to get over it oh that's it and then my
mind gets sober because like don't jump
seriously no no no no no that's more
than five seconds
don't worry moment we still have winter
and spring one day it's new yeah
nice good good shape good work moment
do you see the cutscene no i don't see
it no it's becoming winter it's really
cute oh no i still see summer
it's okay now don't worry i think winter
will be on mummy's channel again i would
say or
in the future
sometime maybe in maybe in june if we
can make it happen i think rest of may
it will be impossible because i'm going
for
vacations for one week and then there's
only one more week yeah yeah right may
is going by so fast
[Music]
i wish
i also wanted to slow down because it
stresses me out about when you guys are
gonna come
soon
sooner or later
i'm kind of stressed about traveling
yeah
me too
i had one more idea mommy for a stream
that we can do when you guys are here
and i keep saying you guys but there's
still one secret guest that we haven't
really announced
um don't know if that secret guest
really will come but for now it looks
like it anyway
i have one more idea
what's the idea
when when you guys are here i could put
together all kinds of austrian snacks or
like european snacks and you guys are
gonna taste test it and snack with me or
we can combine that with you know the
the watch along of of lord of the rings
we can snack and rate the snacks while
watching lord of the rings for example
is how excited it is
we should combine it or like the thing
is also like we can't do endless amounts
of streams i i will personally push to
do as many as possible because i think
it will be a nice thing to look back on
um but yeah time time is an issue
so i don't know if we can uh
do too many streams but
if we need to
save some
thing then we can
combine for example the stacking of the
movie watching
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah right it's a perfect
combination actually
i'm excited
yeah i mean i'm kind of nervous about
seeing
you for example like like callie i
already met before but
i'm nervous like if you if you come here
and then you like me less because you've
i don't know oh no
i worry about this new stuff i'm very
arlene i'm i'm a very awkward human
being yeah
i feel like i'm like he would be
uncomfortable with how awkward i am i
think it would be less awkward when when
seeing you in in real life because it's
like easier to like
like like now for example when you had
that awkward moment of silence after i
said let's not end it
i wasn't sure what was happening i
didn't think you were actually taking me
seriously i think a moment like this
would be easier to see what's going on
in real life
i don't know about that
i think so i think so because i could i
could actually like
sense and see
your
exactly i'll give you a little baby
yeah oh actually i did something similar
when
when uh we were doing karaoke oh the off
collab i made a joke about rick roll and
ahmed looked at me so confused
i was like i was like no no don't
actually play like rickroll or something
oh no no i think i said it and here's
wonderwall but we actually wanted to
play rick roll it was confusing but i
made i i gave a look
you were gonna sing rick roll but you
said uh we're singing wonder while now i
think it was the opposite i think i said
here's wonder wall or something but it
was rick roll because we i wanted to
rick roll everybody ah
and that's what i just said moment
no no but we just sing rick roll we did
the neck roll yeah i think that's what i
said
oh the first way i explained it
you got it now you understand i got it i
got it i got it and then emma was like
it but we're singing rick roll or what
yeah she gave me this book kind
no but that's not that's not you being
awkward or so that's just you being uh
good at acting and conveying the fact
that you're not singing rick roll but
you're totally singing on the wall
therefore
loki rick rolling ammo because now
you're making her expect that you may be
singing wonder why you know
you're just good he's a great actress
yeah yeah you're good at acting in that
moment oh my awkward oh my awkward is
just acting so it was just too
convincing moment that even yeah i was
confused
i'm just i'm just so good
yeah so that
even ahmed would be like
what we're doing rickroll after all oh
my god you totally don't think me there
i explained it really really bad
but like one thing i just i don't know
once we were eating dinner and
it was quiet because people were eating
and i started laughing because i
couldn't handle it being quiet
wow well okay then then don't worry
because i'm well known for uh always
wanting to destroy awkward silence don't
worry oh
okay me too but i don't know how to feel
it except the glass oh you do randomly
laugh that is a little bit scary and
worrying um
[Music]
yes everybody eat your food no just
kidding what
but i mean okay i do i guess i think i
also do sometimes feel awkward silence
with unnecessary laughter like but but
not in in a way that it sounds crazy
though
i don't think i i don't think i should
increase you you don't think so
when i started laughing everyone else
started laughing because
i don't know why
i don't explain this all i'll say is i'm
very awkward um
please don't take offense okay
i think
maybe all of us have these kind of
worries we just don't say it out loud
like we're all worried that if we meet
then oh my god what is she going to
think about me and
i worry about how i look when i speak so
ah
that is um i i actually have the same
word amen
really it's such a weird worry though
yeah like how my face looks when i say
things i don't know
what or
why do i
that's such a specific one but i i have
the same one
really yeah i don't know what it is
i feel like i've adapted a weird way of
moving my mouth over the past
um 10 years
no me too i did too
because i used to have like a dental
thing which made me not want to show one
side of my mouth
me too
rita
like one side of your mouth right so it
looks like you're pushing all your words
to one side i don't know what it is
i'm gonna cry
which side of the mouth was it for you
the the front
the front oh i had it
right i wouldn't want to
open my mouth at all
did you did you because of that did you
like adapt a one-sided smile or so
because some people have that yes
yeah well kinda
one side of my face smiles more than the
other because i always turn my head oh
man
um
i didn't think we had such a weird
relatable moment
this is more carbon than
see that one talks about that movement
isn't that like like i
i enjoy masks partially because of that
i love math
wonderful wonderful you know what's
horrible can i talk about this it's
gonna okay do it don't take this so
seriously everyone but
years before we found ourselves and what
we found ourselves in um
like like maybe a year before i was with
mother al and i was talking about how in
japan
people just wear masks yeah yeah yeah
and i was like gosh i wish here yeah oh
you had that i really enjoyed wearing
masks
in the car with her
no thank you for doing that
thank you for normalizing masks a bit
more but honestly when i lived in japan
i really really really loved it because
like i i i i've changed a bit more now i
give less [\h__\h] now but i used to really
not even want to go outside um showing
my face even if i were to go to the
supermarket
um without makeup you know um but in
japan i could just put on my mask so and
not feel weird about it and now finally
here i can also put on my mountain and i
don't have to put on makeup to go to the
[\h__\h] supermarket
exactly
like i felt a lot more pressure if i
visited japan it would like look really
nice so the masks were nice because you
can really tell
if i had makeup or not yeah then here
yeah i just stopped i have not worn
makeup in so long i just wear it
i forgot how to do my makeup roommate
oh no i never i was never good at it
you know what i always get told me
that my eyeliner is always on fleek and
then i should teach them how to do it
yeah but i don't even put that much
effort into it but apparently my
eyeliner is always on fleek
you know what
oh i just want to say
give a quick compliment crony has
perfect like
perfect eyeliner really
which is expected of perfect cronies
that's a crummy ways eyeliner huh
wear eyeliner well i don't know
i've seen it
do you do you wear eyeliner
if i wear makeup i like the uh the brown
eyeliner oh wow that's very nice
i used to like the dark like black
big winged eyeliner yeah edgy oh yeah
yeah oh yeah
that's too edgy but oh i did like it wow
i got lazy i just i don't know it's i
i've
come to learn people spend a lot of like
time in the morning on their makeup and
hair and everything yeah i didn't
realize how long it takes
because i do stuff in like 10 minutes
like you're done my code yo it shows i
guess because i don't have very good
makeup skills at all but it was like
hours dang it yeah i've never used
bronzer before um brown highlighters
i've never used any of that stuff and
apparently it's so long it's nice don't
i need to use highlighter i don't use
bronzer but i use highlight and and i
feel like i
if i mean now is maybe i'm a bit more
slower now but i used to do stuff that
people do in in 50 minutes i used to do
it in 10 minutes i can i can have
perfect makeup with with the um with the
base and then the the
concealer and then the powder and then
the eyeliner and then a little bit of
shading and some eye makeup and the
eyeliner and the eyebrows and the and
the eyelashes everything all of that if
and i think some few a few more things
in 10 to 15 minutes yo that's like speed
running makeup
yeah the more you do it i guess the
faster you get yeah
you gotta go fast
i never had i never had girlfriends who
actually wear a lot of makeup or not a
lot like who knew how to do makeup i
guess oh
well you don't realize you have to teach
yourself yo
yeah i guess so i always assumed girls
learned from other girls oh i don't
think i realized
youtube tutorials and i didn't even
really learn from youtube tutorials to
be honest
i didn't know i didn't adapt anything
from that
no
i just if if anything i would look for
some
items that
maybe i could use but they usually had
ah because you know most of the makeup
youtubers they're most of them are like
american so the items that they use they
don't sell in australia like we don't
have what's that one called sephora it's
called sephora oh sephora yeah i don't
have them
yeah
is it i think so right i think it's a
story with a bunch of brands or
something yeah
brands i think oh yeah but but that one
a lot of people a lot of youtubers use
makeup from sephora and we don't have
that here no oh
i bet it's expensive to try
buying it
and have it shipped
yeah i think so yeah i think the only
option would be
shipping if they do that but anyway yeah
so so i couldn't even use most of the
brands and things anyway this is really
girly talk chad are you keeping up chat
yeah do you guys know what we're even
talking about
do you know what this do you know what a
concealer is do you know what like
highlighter
oh they want more they want more girls
talk
oh
mommy mommy
um
besides um
besides you know
streaming for streaming purposes do you
have your bangs in place outside of
streaming too
oh i have i have something okay okay so
for me i told my my my chat before that
i i originally don't have bangs because
uh that's just the way my hair grows but
i always got bullied for having a two
huge forehead so no
yeah
in school they would be like oh why do
you have uh why why don't what was it
why are you balding and i'm like
i'm not moving
and after a couple years i was like [\h__\h]
you and i cut myself when i was like 12
or something or 11. i cut myself my own
bangs because i was like i'm done with
this [\h__\h] but of course if your roots
grow a certain way
your bangs don't want to go to the front
just because you cut them it's not gonna
work so i had to learn all kinds of
techniques to make them
go like the way they look now look how
perfect my bangs look wow so if you look
perfect yeah and what i with all the
techniques i've adapted um i have
figured out the perfect way of shaping
them and the perfect way of keeping them
in place even when there's a [\h__\h]
storm going out on outside my bangs stay
straight and even when i when i do a
handstand which i can't do but even if i
would
they would still stay straight and
sometimes girls would be like how do you
do it
well i mean obviously here's your
hairspray obviously but you need to
choose the right hairspray and also you
always need to iron your hair first curl
it up a little bit so that the bangs are
not like totally ugly shaped no no you
need to shape them a little bit inside
curl them a little bit inside to give
them a little bit of a proof and then
and then put a [\h__\h] out of hairspray but
don't get too close because if you get
too close to the hair to the strands
then it will create like
weird space in between and then you see
my forehead and i don't want people to
see my heart so yeah i'm just
perfect with that i'm like a pro when it
comes to styling bags my friend has
asked me before to style her bags
i've been debating if i want actual oh
actual straight things but
i'm really i even
i'm worse at hair than makeup
oh i'm so bad at hair
i don't know how to braid my hair i
can't even i'm not even good at putting
it in a ponytail i don't i want to teach
you um if you don't even know how to do
a normal braid then you probably also
don't know how to do a french braid i
can do a french braid
i know how to braid other people's like
i know how to do normal braids but not
on my own hair oh i want to taste
my hair up without there being a bunch
of buns
i'm going to teach you how to do a
friend's brain
this french braid like three braids made
into one braid
you braid three nights
it's called amikomi in japanese it's
like when you do a braid but always add
with every time you you overlay a strand
you add a piece of hair
into it that way it stays close to your
head and you can keep on adding more and
more you know what i mean
yes oh my gosh once i
went to summer camp and i was so bad at
maintaining my hair that the counselors
made me wear a french they french
braided my hair
because it kept getting so tangled
in one day it would get super tangled
that they would do something against it
well because when i brushed it i wasn't
really getting the tangles out or
something so i was that bad at doing my
hair
i only have to brush my hair like once a
day to get the tangles out but but um
okay here do we still have that problem
with me
not nearly as bad okay it used to be i
used to go to school with tangled hair
because mother al i talked about this
one
the mother ali used to brush my hair
before school like you know way back in
the
day and
she
okay you know how if you have longer
hair you have to not even long hair like
just hair you don't brush it straight
from the root like you kind of grab some
yeah but it doesn't hurt yeah you don't
pull on your head so she didn't do that
i developed a very tough spool from that
oh but i didn't know you could do that
oh when it came time for me to brush my
hair myself it'd be like gosh this hurts
i give up and i'd go to school
no what the [\h__\h]
you were ever laughing
information there you missed something
really important
one day i think i just decided i just
instinct instinct over like oh
kicked in and i figured it out i was
like oh this is how i can get rid of the
twinkles okay
oh you know what we should like not
maybe not only us but we should just do
um i mean probably out of the chat
couldn't relate but we should just do a
chatting stream that's themed girls talk
let's do girls cause we never do that we
never do that do we we never talk about
these topics on stream yeah i wanna
learn tips and tricks i don't think i
can give any but i wanna oh nobody
is saying yes i am for real like i never
talk about these kind of things on my
stream alone either because i feel like
you guys don't really like i don't know
also i don't have a lot of world
problems recently i suppose but
but girl problem i guess i could think
of some in the past
stuff that girls find cute um
[Music]
i don't know
what the girls talk about and when do
girls struggle oh my god
they want to hear about you know brad
problems like oh my getting the first
bra was like when did you get your
bra
that's queen girl
i remember they want to hear those kind
of stories are they hoping to hear some
of that i had i couldn't complain about
types of bras
types of bras oh yeah let's oh can we
please complain about that because i i
get really no matter which [\h__\h] bra
okay don't even get me started we should
keep these topics for another time
we can write down right right down and
write it down write it down
right that's just down you know i had i
hate wired bras so much i hate the wired
ones too
yeah
this is not even about wearing it enough
i won't say that i just want to say that
okay
some so i have ones that aren't wired
right and when you you should put them
in a pouch when you wash them but even
when i do that like i don't throw in a
pad
[Music]
stick it back in yeah yeah yeah it never
it's never the same it's never quite
right yes and the part where you put it
back in is also usually so tiny so you
even have to tear it up for like some
others yeah but you can't
it doesn't come out oh my god
the main audience is like what the [\h__\h]
are riot bras anyway
where's the difference
someone said bluetooth bruh
because wired wired brass and bluetooth
oh my bluetooth bluetooth
yeah they should make bluetooth bras
yes
please i need more i need that wireless
support on my boobies
that's okay i will from now on forever
call wireless bras bluetooth bras thank
you for that that is genius and my
friends will be forever confused
actually the people at the store i'll be
like sorry do you guys have any
bluetooth bras
be like what the [\h__\h] are you talking
about
i have an embarrassing story
i went i went to a bra store oh god oh
god okay
and um i was just looking for ones
without wire that were comfortable and i
saw i saw one and it was like that looks
comfy
and asked about it and they said that's
for if you're pregnant it's for it's a
maternity bra i was so embarrassed
really it like it i don't know i don't
think i've ever seen like a maternity
bra before anyway in the store
i was embarrassed oh it's okay mommy
it's okay
it wasn't even big it was like i was
gonna ask yeah yeah
it wasn't even a huge padding or
anything apparently it expands as you
expand but wow
well that's okay that's okay movement
you can i'm out if i were there i may
have made the same mistake well
you know it's okay moment it's okay
it was soft
ah
you know what
[\h__\h] it so so what if society tells you
you can only wear maternity brows when
you're uh pregonanted yeah
okay i know why they're so comfortable
why can't all clothes be that
comfortable like as in the material i'll
feel it and then i see a maternity sign
or a big belly to you know model and i'm
like dang it
oh
maybe maybe you know what mummy maybe
there's a secret that they haven't been
telling us maybe if you're not
pregonante and you wear the maternity
bra maybe your boobs
will
expand
automatically
so
what's what's it made of
boob expanding material
what
okay next time next time i go to the
store i'm gonna get
i will get
actually i haven't gone to a bra store
since then i was very embarrassed um
i will get
the messages
it's not for me it's not it's a baby
shower gift or something yeah oh yeah
you can say that but if it fits it sits
and um i mean you know if it's
comfortable what the hell
why not if it fits like honestly why not
use it
i think if you ever see it again and it
fits then what the hell get it and if
the lady asks you are you pregnant and
you can say yeah first week [\h__\h]
you just don't say it or maybe you can
say yeah six months and you've seen
that's very rude to ask are you yeah
that's rude hello that's rude and you're
just jealous that you can't see my prego
belly yeah i'm carrying it in my butt
and that's why my butt is so big
i said i said [\h__\h] the society i'm not
part of your system i carry my child in
my butt okay i should stop talking now
i'm like you know what happened my brain
started i tried picturing uh just a
profile view of a lady's body
oh uh-huh like like you know um
like an illustration yeah where you can
see inside
all the organs and stuff
and trying to imagine how a baby could
be in your butt
but it but i don't want to think about
it anymore i mean in the end
you could say that all that all that um
flesh in the butt
you could
i mean it happens there's no organs
there's no organs there right so you
could fill it up with okay never mind
what do you say
i don't know like i mean there's there
you're there you
[Laughter]
you're making me feel really awkward now
help me can't stop thinking
am i the weird one right now or we're
just
let me help you say something say
something
sorry i'm busy i'm thinking
um thank you everybody for um don't stop
picturing it
thank you everybody for watching uh the
the broadcast today burp cast this is
what we call it
um this is the first
uh please tune in in another episode for
some more talk about uh bras and
hairstyles and makeup and more
uh
nail polish
nail polish oh my god
no i'm gonna keep the story um oh i
should really write these things down
um i wrote it down for another time we
should really do that
girls talk
thingy yeah
[Music]
maybe even the the male audience will
come and learn some things from us if
they can apply it for like girlfriends
and so on
oh yeah
they can help the girlfriends or
understand them better we'll explain
maybe it could help them make themselves
look cuter yeah as well
yeah yeah style i mean for example bangs
like you can have bangs as a guy too so
i can give you styling tips yeah
also makeup is getting more and more
normal and sometimes i think like you
don't even know sometimes some guys are
wearing makeup and you can't even notice
because they're using it so suddenly
sadly and honestly
i feel like
you know
sometimes i feel like a little bit like
um
okay this is getting weird again but i
feel a little bit pressured by the
society that that we have to wear makeup
kind of we kind of expected to wear
makeup but i feel like you know for
example when it comes to acne
people of acne problems i'm sure that
some guys would wish that it was more
normal to wear makeup so that they could
hide their acne like i was able to hide
my acne when i had
acne for a [\h__\h] century
right i used to think about that too
like oh lucky it as a girl i can yeah
i can hide it but if i was a guy and i
was wearing makeup i'm sure i'd get
comments about it yeah
and get bullied or whatever and that's
of course like not nice you wouldn't
want to get bullied in school from
wearing makeup i get
but but if you learn like some kind of
really subtle technique
that would be great yeah
there are definitely ways to make it
look really subtle
you know i started realizing that girls
wear makeup when i think that they're
not wearing makeup there's like so many
new natural look trends yeah yeah where
i'm like gosh how do people look so nice
and clean all the time without makeup
but then i saw videos people were like
this is how you wear makeup and make it
look like you're not wearing makeup yeah
i was like oh
yeah
but then oh my god i have a pet peeve
there's like certain tv shows for
example i would say friends is one of
them i'm watching that one right now so
let's use that as an example oh also big
bang theory definitely where the women
you know there's some scenes where they
just woke up or they're going to bed and
all that and they're still wearing like
no [\h__\h] way that you go to sleep like
that because your your skin will age
hundreds of years per day if you keep on
your makeup but the tv shows they keep
on the makeup the whole night what the
[\h__\h] is up with that
imagine the pillowcase yeah
yeah
and i would understand it if you know
they would
like for
television purpose uh they would not let
them go totally without makeup but some
kind of you know subtle natural makeup
but to have them right on all the
eyeliner and i um
eyeshadows and all that like it's still
very obvious that they're wearing their
daily makeup to go to bed like that's
like
head just like waking up with perfect
eyeliner yeah it's not realistic oh my
gosh well i hate that it's so dumb no
[\h__\h] pet peeves
did you know people tattoo permanent
eyeliner yeah yeah there's all kinds of
permanent tattoos from makeup yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah that's what it is
permanent eyeliner tattoo they have
eyelash extensions and then
i don't think the actors have that
i think that's just a decision from even
the characters that's why they wake up
ah
it's an explanation that's weird that so
many i didn't know it was such a common
thing to have a permanent eyeliner and a
permanent eyeshadow
and permanent eyebrows too
yeah i think
if anything that is the most
reasonable permanent eyebrows i think
would be the most reasonable i think
because like
um
i don't know eyeliner i love
oh yeah on your eye your eyelids seem so
thin too
i don't know it's kind of yeah it's
scary scary probably use some they
probably use something different than
for normal tattoos but
we all have permanent eyebrows that's
not
aren't people born with
what we're talking foreign
we don't know what we're talking about
so okay let us explain sometimes women
are like okay i don't like the natural
shape of my eyebrow or i just have too
too much too fake eyebrows i want them
to be thinner or whatever i just like
that style i like that look or whatever
so they shave off their eyebrows and
then have a like a tattoo
on it basically but it looks pretty
natural it's not that much like a
typical tattoo and it's also in the
color of whatever you wanted to do yeah
actually i just googled it i didn't
realize how natural some of them are
some of them look really natural i guess
you don't maybe shave it you just uh
i don't know what they do with it to get
rid of it yeah what you should have to
just consistently shave your normal
shave or wax it or
i mean there's other ways that i have
tried before to permanently get rid of
your hair
not lasering because lasering they say
it's
they say it's long term but it's not
permanent lasering okay oh my god this
is another topic for her
oh i was one teacher who lasered her
armpits
i didn't laser my armpits i permanently
removed them obliterated them with light
and fire and heat
um
[Music]
what
yeah it's like what i think i think
lasering
stays like for a couple months i think
and then the thing that i did is forever
like for real forever
that's a google this is what what's
awesome
it's not so well known um
how to remove armpit hair forever
it tells me with baking soda
it's it's a procedure where um they put
some uh like ultrasound gel or something
on the area where you want to remove it
and then they put like some kind of
machine
uh that that heats up
the
like the part under your skin the the
roots of the hair and burns them from
the outside
and it really hurts at least for me it
did really hurt
but yeah you have to do it several times
because your hair also grows um in in
different stages yeah yeah so if you go
for one session you can only get a
certain amount of hair then you have to
go back like after one or two months and
and yeah and then you do it again and
again and eventually at some point you
will never have hair growing there again
wow it exists but it's also a bit
expensive
is it
oh it hurts it feels like
it almost feels like they're ripping it
out but what you feel it's like a like a
plucky plucky kind of
pain but
i don't even want to remember the pain i
cried several times oh man i hated going
there so much i hated it but now you
never have to shave your armpits again
yeah that's so nice
and i did it for my for my legs for my
under
your legs
yeah but only the under part because the
upper legs i don't have strong
hair
that's not noticeable yeah
i'm feeling embarrassed now
all right don't feel i think i'm pretty
similar i have to say though it was in
the end it was so worth it because
uh i remember the times where i had to
shave like every two days or so in the
summer
for girls like we have to shave every
one to two days okay yeah on the legs to
make to give ourselves a perfect
beautiful
yeah i mean you guys understand for you
for your beard right how fast that [\h__\h]
grows you understand
does it go that fast it grows pretty
fast
your darker hair especially because i
just know that
even when it's even it's not summer
and i wear you know like long pants i
always have to shave like around my
ankles at least
every other day i
i usually in the summer always wear mini
skirts or shorts so legs gotta be gonna
be clean for me gonna be like unhairy
unhearing but another like that's also
like something that like
if you don't want to care about it then
don't care about because i've seen i've
seen young girls for example um who had
like really hairy legs and to be honest
like whatever if you don't
want to shave your hair or so then don't
don't shave it that's you do you be
nasty or whatever
i feel like it just depends how you feel
like how you feel about it because for
some reason
i think guys like when i started shaving
it was because of yeah like because
everyone else was doing it
but now it's like ingrained where if if
i don't then i don't like how it feels i
don't like
like knowing that my legs have hair
this stuff so it's just you get too used
to it we're getting really intimate here
in private look um huh
i can tell you
one thing
when um you know how
i i obliterated my leg hair and all that
but there's like um
a thing
um
you know arm hair uh in my country it's
pretty normal like every freaking girl
has arm hair
but
when i was like very young
and
and some
um japanese people
uh because they have less arm hair i
guess or it doesn't stand out so much
they saw my arm hair and they were like
oh my god gorilla
so i was like okay
so i started from then on
and started shaving my arm hair oh no
yeah
but it was
it really wasn't necessary in austria
because like i looked at the other
girl's arms and everybody had like
the same amount of hair it was normal
and i mean i don't know you know it's
just you know sometimes internet people
are or you know evil but as a young
teenager i was just like i had that
complexes and i felt like uh maybe i do
look like a gorilla
no
oh i guess just depends like i don't
know like where you're from because i
say we're like growing up for real like
50 50. i thought it was kind of
excessive to shave your arms yeah that's
how i felt about it and
shaving your legs is pretty normal but
shaving your arms i don't really see
many people do that but you know what's
what's fascinating i've noticed for
example with like i think with my legs
like when i would shave it like
sometimes doesn't it grow back stronger
or thicker yes right
yeah so if you if you start shaving it
yeah if you start shaving it regularly
yeah your hair will come back thicker
but then with my arms to be honest i
when i look at my arms now i don't
really shave them regularly anymore and
i feel like with my arms maybe with my
my mental wishing for having less arm
hair i've actually had reduced arm hair
now and i didn't obliterate my arm here
but i just have it's it's really not
that noticeable anymore so i'm pretty
happy about that okay that's not saying
it's a myth but maybe that maybe my
body's weird then my body is weird
because
it's not like regular i have like some
hair follicles that seem to come in
stronger now yeah yeah yeah so i started
shaving but not all of it
so maybe it's just like
something's wrong with me that if it's a
myth for everybody else maybe it's
puberty
go back darker
[Music]
yeah what could that be if that's a myth
then explain that explain that
he said it's a myth but i thought it was
re i thought i
i don't want to talk about it anymore
apparently i'm not normal no no i feel
you i think a lot of people
experience the same thing i i feel like
i experienced it too in some
okay yeah sometimes
but but now i've experienced the
opposite on my arms well that's weird
i think
almost all of your chat said that the
hair growing back stronger is a myth so
obviously this was wrong with me
i didn't notice it really it's not like
my entire leg grows back darker it's
just certain parts too so i have to show
you regularly otherwise i get
self-conscious whenever i'm sitting and
i look down at my ankles yeah i look at
my ankles and have like a single hair
i'm like no
i have the perfect idea
for a stream
when you guys are visiting
do you recall coco senpai doing hair
removal streams
i have never watched them but i've heard
nobody exists would you like me to
wax or in other means i have some other
options to
remove your leg
i've never waxed before
everyone i think i've yeah i think i've
tried several things but never waxing
which could be fun if we do it for the
first time it could be a lot of fun with
me
it could be funny okay let's do it i
also tried um
when i was so desperate about removing
hair i tried a thing before that um it
it's like a little it looks like uh like
uh one of those um beer shaving thingies
beard shaving thing is but it rips it it
grabs um the hair and pulls it out and
goes really fast i don't know i mean
what that's called
um i used to use that too not a razor
not a razor it it grabs like it goes
like it rolls it rolls and rolls and it
grabs the little pieces an emulator an
appellator
i have no idea what that is but i'm
telling you that one was one of the most
painful
uh ones that i've ever used it's i
hate it yeah an electric emulator it
really hurts a lot at least for me
i think the thicker your hair is the
more it hurts
how do they make it so cute
it loves flowers on it it does look cute
but i tried it on on my leg hair and
especially on the inner side of my calf
it was so painful i would cry but this
was one thing that you have to do to
yourself so it's like how can i inflict
so much pain on myself what the [\h__\h]
is pain it is a torture device yeah
no pain no gain so we can try that
or we can try one
doesn't i have to let my ankle hair grow
out
yeah but we'll get rid of it immediately
i don't want to travel with ankles
it's
wear some see-through uh skin color ties
but then they poke out
just oh let's just do it on the do it
somewhere where maybe it's not
noticeable maybe on the
[Music]
what can't you like let's say you arrive
can't you just like from the day before
you arrive just let it grow and then let
it grow one more day after you arrived
and then on the second or third day we
get rid of it
maybe maybe this is an opportunity to
learn how to let go and just
you know expect to accept ourselves
you know what you know you are i'll tell
kelly to let it grow too all right
okay i'll do it on both of you
okay
we'll be 20 okay oh my god um
you know we can't go back on this
anymore
chad has already
put it in the calendar
[Laughter]
i agreed to the okay i i agree do you
agree to the terms and conditions of me
removing your hair
it's interesting how another orange lady
is the one in charge to remove other
people's hair
what is it with orange people what is it
with them
[Laughter]
because you have peace buzz you don't
know the pain or something i'm
continuing the legacy because you know
i'm really glad you guys are coming over
here because i couldn't remove the hair
on myself because it's like i already
have i got rid of most of my hair you
know so i need someone to come over here
[Laughter]
all right
[Applause]
you will be suffering and screaming and
it'll be so much fun yeah you know what
you you get a reward you get ice cream
or cookies and berries or something like
that
or combination of all ice cream with
berries and cookies
yes please
okay it's a deal it's a deal
um see this is the this this is where we
ended up at after doing all that girls
talk
we ended up at torturing zuma and kelly
it is still girls talk it still kind of
is yeah this is the girl
let's how you said that you never had
someone to like teach you how to style
or your hair or do your makeup
see i'll be your big sister that teaches
you how to remove your hair
oh my wishes are coming true isn't that
beautiful i'm liking my dreams yeah
the things that you missed out on
when a friend gets here
friend oh friend
when did friend get there oh oh oh wait
oh that's when people said in the chat
friend i was like what are you talking
about what the heck oh
wait when did friend get two hours ago
did did friends cover up the screen
because it does cover up a big part
[Laughter]
that is interesting
it's okay
let him be there he was listening to the
girls talk okay
it was girls talk though
but there was a little girl there were
thousands of other people talking moment
don't just if you're not girls though
what if you tell friends to not listen
and it's gonna be so unfair for all the
people who were listening
like the other way around like it's
unfair for the friend look at him angry
he doesn't want to be
no oh you're angry when you both age so
you're so connected how can you not let
him listen in when you're so connected
that even your expressions
are connected
okay
that's okay because now we're going to
end it anyway it's past midnight and i
want to eat poof
me too
oh yeah but thank you that was fun let's
really do girl girl bird cast or
something like that let's do that
yeah
just please okay okay okay
thank you everybody for watching today
uh next time we're gonna do winter on
women's channel eventually
um
yeah women's channel is in the
description if you haven't subscribed
yet and thank you thank you thank you
yeah she has a youtube channel she does
yes i do yeah
uh and
in germany
[Music]
yeah you know i thought of a funny
combination name you know how my last
name is takanasi and yours is
[Music]
huh
i will stop you there
okay don't try though good try
okay bye bye guys have a good evening
well my youtube thank you for playing
with me
thank you
see you guys tomorrow in a member's only
stream and
oh yeah
tomorrow is actually also for me past
midnight but still kind of tomorrow is
the the
stream of inna the sponsored one
yeah so look forward to that
yeah we we got implemented in a game
called valkyrie connect
yeah i saw
yeah
with cool armor and stuff yeah
and yeah so i'll see you guys there
thank you everybody and then do you want
me to say bye bye bye bye
bye bye
thank you mommy
thank you
[Music]
do
you