yeah you're starting to uh get a little
tired
oh wait no is it started now wait a
second
so uh today yeah but now it now it
should be
on it
wait am i am i on guys am i on yeah
yeah okay
sorry sorry you know youtube is bullying
me i'm here now i'm here now
this is the lady of the hour that was
totally not my fault
yes could i say hi once again for my
viewers
i would like to say guru senpai thank
you for um
except accepting my invite to collab
with you
even though the one month collab band is
not lifted yet
[Music]
and once again it is my absolute
pleasure to play with you kiana
thank you yeah
yes yes i'm yokoha you may say bye
right in my cheeks and my face what wow
okay i'm not used to it yet but i
i think i'll be used to it soon maybe oh
okay we'll see how long i can put that
act out though
all right so today we're playing uh
mario kart
which we are both totally professionals
at right
oh yes prepare to be obliterated
i still i don't really know what that
word means but you you do use it a lot
don't you
yes liberated it's like uh the tnt
a minecraft and you set it up
when you set it up when you when you
make tnt go boom it's going to
obliterate
the stone around it exploding
yeah okay
so by the way we're playing um on belt
we're streaming on both channels so you
can see both
views and we are doing you guys the
absolute
favor and honor of being able to play
with us
so well first put up the nintendo switch
boys and girls
uh wait let me copy that and post the
code in the chat once
i join myself so that we uh have space
and they don't join before us
are you ready to hide the code i am
ready to hide the code shall i begin
yes let's join okay
there we go there we go there we go
hold on go hold on i haven't joined
no no no no no
wait oh god i wonder if my people
wait wait i wasn't able to join
what are you in are you in no i'm still
putting the code in i'm still
okay okay good good good good wait if
you you were already in my room though
it should be in your list of
previously visited tournaments though
oh god there's someone in there that
looks exactly like me i don't know why
okay wait i'm here all right i will join
join yes um
yeah you probably should join quickly
because people know the code from
previous tournaments
oh my god it says
guys wait for me
hopefully there you
[Applause]
the go i first saw you in the game
you look ridiculously adorable in-game
okay we're starting right away i want to
go for sunshine airport
stand out there i have do you know which
one is me there's like three
freakies looking like me do you know
which one it is
uh yes it's the one right next to me
no it's the one with the purple eyes
yeah there you go
yeah uh yes of course i'm from australia
by the way
totally ignore it i mean that's a that's
the flag of australia don't mind it
that's the flag of australia yeah
i didn't know australia flag looked like
that educate yourself
i guess i guess i need to go back to
class
yeah let's go good ass
speed oh [\h__\h] i
missed the items i'm sorry um beforehand
i'll probably be cursing a lot i'm sorry
that's fine i'm sure how do you go off
the ball
up the up the ball i knew
hey could i say that next next to me is
that you
i'm not talking about
yeah same stuff viewers will
own us anyway we should work together
once i win this one
[Music]
[Applause]
that was both
[Laughter]
we played we played one game before this
and
pulled out the japanese that she learned
from me what did you say
what did you say i said uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
we're pretty much on the same level what
we don't seem to have much of a much of
a space between us
or we're already almost always around
the same
spot
how do you can't you like jump off the
the things you can like
jump up the cliff like when you when you
like
do a jump you can uh oh
see i don't know how to do that
because you used to shake the lead
controller ah
well if you have that if you have what's
it called again
what's the call again the fancy thing
that was close though that was really
close
hey where are you oh pretty close
pretty cool
nice one nice first match gura
oh apparently when you go off the jump
you press one of the r buttons and it
makes you do a trick and you get a speed
boost you get a little
zoom oh by the way guys
so that would give more people a chance
to join please leave the room after one
match
thank you and then new people can come
in thank you
also fake kiana you also have to leave
thank you bye-bye
oh nice everyone follows the rules
that's what i like to see
oh a new one came in which one
which one would you like to do next cola
i mean people are probably gonna mind
them
they're probably gonna vote against us
but you're gonna go for random
oh what's the code should i put the oh
yeah i put it as a pinned comment
oh oh my god i i have not done that
i am sorry guys oh there we go there we
go
i think we're already full anyway okay
i'm gonna go for a rip on the road
nice no quick hold on hold on hold on
i'm posting i'm posting it
i'm ready to rumble
i'm ready
i love how you look as a what's it
called amiibo
amiibo is that a meme a me
i think it's just a me you look like
you look like good enough definitely
just like me it's a spitting image
exactly like me even the body size is
perfect
i just pulled the slider all the way
down
gotta be realistic right so people
recognize you
i mean of course
[Music]
hey watch it link
hey where are you guru i am i went down
i'm down by the bottom oh
oh oh oh hi is that you
stay way way way
how's it going guna hello
how's the driving lessons going on do
you have a driving license
i don't know how to drive okay that's
good me too
neighbor in mario kart nor in real life
yes oh yeah actually i'm playing for the
obs
screen i don't even know which uh which
what is my placement
i'm also playing i'm not playing through
there
[Laughter]
i don't know what place i must be number
one it must be number one it makes
totally sense because people are in
front of me that means i'm so fast
that i'm catching up on the people that
are last anyway that was me
or maybe i am number no i'm not actually
i could just take a look
but you know i like this because when i
played uh mario kart against inna before
she was uh better than me but you gonna
you're like pretty much
the same as me are you you calling me
bad no
we're both fantastic
come on come on
gotta be chiara
where are you where are you are you
you're done i'm right behind you
i'm gonna stay here stay there look at
my look at my butt
look at it
[Music]
did i meet you
number nine
damn people can't see what oh well
guys it's i'll leave it up to your
imagination what what placement i have
always nice
nice one nice one
next group please who wants to challenge
these
professional mario kart drivers who
wants to go in who wants to be
humiliated by us they're you challenged
[Music]
james
what was that you showed me before we
started the stream
the turkey sound yeah i'm still
i'm practicing it but um
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah i'm not sure what i'm doing can you
do a turkey sound
a turkey where i'm from sounds like ah
that's way too cute it's way too
adorable
[Music]
yes exactly no
no no they sound more like blah blah
what the hell i'm gonna die
okay let's go i'm number one
oh not anymore
my
that was a suffering where he's
suffering turkey
do you remember anything besides the
magic
that i thought you knew oh my goodness
god on my side i'll fix it in a second
hi do you remember any other japanese
that i told you
um
[Laughter]
but it's okay i i didn't expect to you
too
hold on i'm concentrating i'm getting
sweaty
oh sweaty shark no
not in that way
[Music]
oh
wait did you send someone to me and did
nothing hit me though
ah dang it yeah i sent that a clap
okay i'm gonna wait until graham is in
front of me and then i'll shoot that on
her
no don't do that
grow you're still behind me are you
still behind me
you're taking your goddamn sweet time
careful careful
[Music]
[Laughter]
one second let me fix my image let me
get back to gooda's room once again
let me find out let me find kawda
you like the cheese
oh is it pronounced gouda in english
yeah it's spelled g-o-u-d-a
oh enjoy when you say
that that sounds even more like you in
english than gouda cheese
is it basically
exactly
okay new people come in and challenge us
the turkey sound completely messed up my
throat
i'm sorry
oh it's okay i like trying new bird
sounds and i learn a lot of things about
myself when i do that
ah a journey in self-exploration
yes like a cuckoo cuckoo
cuckoo oh that's cute what the hell
thank you
i'll add that to my real pop
how do you say
[Music]
don't quote me on that guys
oh damn it daddy good night
you don't want to be next to me huh
thank you intimidating a little well
what we'll fix that soon tm
oh hold on i'm getting tricked tricked
i'm getting wrecked
i meant to say shark what's going on
are you are you like behind are you 12
right now
yes nice stay there glad it's still it's
up
you know how you can see a glass is half
empty and the glass is helpful
now if you see it as half full then
you're number one right now
technically that means i'm about to
laugh everybody so you better stay in
the front end
[Music]
fast okay never mind it's okay though
it's okay it's okay
[Music]
[Applause]
i love this
that was a nice day
i am speed
oh i like the music in the background
it's move
meadows
oh
oh man that's on the crown though
why do i have
[Laughter]
[Music]
because it reminds me of the gamecube
times
oh i chose the i don't know what i
you chose a difficult looking one
oh there's one one person that looks
like you but it could also be a piccolo
fake
that looks like is it the tall person
yes
would you say that looks like you um
um by the way are you tall you aren't
like when you're wearing the crown and
can't see your pigtails but that is you
right yeah
[Music]
her fans are like really strong though
kawaii
[Music]
[Applause]
they're representing the glass empire
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm so slow i'm so slow right now
i need some speed
i'm so slow why am i so slow right
why am i so slow okay now here comes
me here comes pete
i like how this mario this tanooki mario
yells
oh god damn it i'm just using them the
catfish which
because she's cute i like my wife
actually surprised she's alive i thought
i eliminated her
previously when i was doing yeah
i i i might have uh eliminated mario's
whole family in my super mario sunshine
stream
but they like to respawn so it's all
good it's all good
it'll be okay i'm sure that was me
sunday
[Music]
wait number do you see how far away that
peculiar fan
is from all of us please don't let me
please
maybe that is peculiar okay
maybe she grew a mustache
who dares who dares to touch a phoenix
i do be ghosting no no no no
no where are you gura
you're second i'm dead i'm gonna lose it
[Applause]
[Music]
ridiculous where are you
[Laughter]
guys
but i love how we're on the same level
that makes it feel very
comfortable for me it's more of a
challenge that way
yeah like more chances for us to see
each other in the race and we can
improve together
of course that's what i called it is
thanks guys thanks guys
yay well
obviously because we are the best in
here obviously
we are the queens what is that alien
over there oh my god
cute i like it i like how
really creative some people can get with
their new creations
it's really impressive i think i'm very
nice of yogurt
[Music]
did you play the newest animal crossing
i did i have about
uh just under 200 hours i think
what is that a lot is that a lot well i
played it a little bit in the beginning
like maybe for a month but i quit um
already
yeah i did too oh maybe we should
get back to animal crossing you know is
also playing it i think she played it
one set on stream i think
i mean yeah i'm i'm done it's like super
chill
[Music]
this was
wait what is that flag is that what is
that flag that's not an australian flag
[\h__\h]
that's a fake australian flag look at my
flag that's an australian flag
it's australia minus the l
now there's a little bit more than minus
the l
as australia
you're close enough close enough but
it's actually australia yeah
hey i am from australia mate
hey good eye oh i thought i could
blank that dude come on
you have a shrimp challenging you go
down
i must win can you can you beat him
or her assad
must be a certain maybe
you're saying that like like a
politician dominance
must be asserted under no circumstances
may they beat me in this match
where are you by the way i haven't seen
you for a while
bye bye bye bye bye bye
now it's the other way around let me get
you let me get you let me get you
where are you dammit
i was too focused on on finding you oh
come on
money money mommy i'm just chilling on
the beach
oh isn't it nice i miss it i'm gonna
chill on the beach yeah right
wouldn't you like a nice beach holiday
yes
what the hell what is this timing oh
come on
like what would be a nice oh
beach destination
ah somewhere with really soft sand
because sometimes sand is uh
not so soft and it's your butt well if
you if
you say look how we both
10 friend 11.
go down good job good job
i like you everyone
there was only one person worse than us
and that was probably on purpose
they're probably worse not on purpose
people often when i when i stream mario
kart
my fans often like to uh wait for me at
the finishing line
very kind of them yeah well they don't
have their
they have their job on the line they
lose their job if they don't let me win
so
with their job yeah everyone works for
me
they're my employees at kfp
who is lifting my members are my
employees and they lose their job when
they
when they don't let me win and you don't
want to lose your job in a time like
this right
oh wait i'm going for a rainbow road on
purpose even though i hate it i hate it
so if i if i win does that mean that i
get promoted to uh
store manager no you you got promoted if
you let me win
that's how it is that's how it is
so but do you want a promotion go get it
[Laughter]
hey there's another peculiar fan in
there
the one with the blue hair with the blue
pigtails that's not you
oh it says i can't roll it
yeah exactly that's what the name says
i can't wrote like when i speak german
we roll the rs but i can't roll the r
when i speak japanese i don't know why
[Music]
now that's different that's a different
room we both didn't speed up nice one go
down
we were both focused yeah we're focusing
on our
aura and that's like it but
that's not it right that's like it has
it needs a little bit more l
in there right i usually when i roll my
eyes i do it at the very
tip of my tongue
[Music]
it's all right once you figure out that
tongue roll it's gonna be game over
that's all it takes right that's all it
takes
only going to be good at rolling your
eyes hoorah i see you fighting with that
no soggy without pakora then
cool turned on and off the lights man
it it completely messed up all my lights
in my apartment
on y'all
how do you call that makes me feel funny
but i can't hear you you're too far away
i'm sorry
you're gonna come back to me well
actually
i see you in front of me anyways i like
how we're always so close to each other
oh
it's so nice how we both suck i love it
i love it how are you able to play i
have to concentrate
so hard i feel like
probably if i would actually stop
talking and concentrate i would probably
be
much better at this game
[Music]
oh always next to each other are you
behind me
yeah now yeah i i was next to you for a
second but someone hit me with their
goddamn shell
[Music]
that was me
okay you know what that means my
german champion you don't know it's a
german for uh
uh speed speed let me show you some
spanish kite
how do you say this kite
we gotta do a follow-up on that japanese
lessons and teach you german instead
maybe you maybe you remember more german
than you remember the japanese that i
told you yeah that's it
so far away from me why are you six and
i'm telling you what the hell
was that getting sweaty while you were
talking i miss you guys
come back to me let's go for cheap gym
beach
i've been playing i don't think i played
the water park one before
is that the cheap cheap beach i know
that's something oh no it's on there
it's the i don't know it's not a human
being you like roller coasters
ah it seems like the time to enjoy
roller coaster but am i wrong
um i need a lot of pushing to get on the
coaster but once i'm on it i have fun
oh okay did you lift your arms
no roller coaster i like
crunch together and look down and i'm
like like my arms like pushed against my
head and like
at some point i stopped screaming and
inside i'm dying only
there was one time i was on this i was
on a roller coaster
um and it's one that like pulls you back
like a rubber band
and when you're supposed to do i didn't
know this but when you get pulled back
in one of those
because of the pressure when you get let
go you're not going to be able to
breathe in so you have to take a breath
before you get
uh before it goes
what happens if you don't breathe well
when i did that i couldn't catch my
breath so i started panicking because i
couldn't breathe and it was dark and my
eyes were closed
did you die did you die uh well now
yeah what happened
[Music]
so how long did that how about for how
long could you not breathe
it was only a few seconds but it really
felt like a long time but why
why on all places are we on the rainbow
road why did that happen
i wanted to go swimming
oh i remember this i remember something
like this
i mean there's no is that actually the
rim no that's not the rainbow road i
think there's like two roads that keep
on like uh
thinking it's rainbow road but it's not
uh-huh
is this the rainbow
maybe not whoa
speed i'm gonna keep that rachel
for when i see gooda
hey you gotta catch me in front of me
no no you're not how should i catch you
if you're behind me
where are you what place are you in i
don't know i don't see it because your
head is covering it up do you want to
move like a little bit to the right or
left
just kidding
can you tilt your head to the very left
right now
oh no i still don't see it
i only saw the th something so it's
probably not first
probably not second and probably not
third it's
thirst
time for the grandchild soon
[Music]
come on
i think that's called karma know them
climb up
not a chance not when i'm done here did
you just fall down the edge
what did you fall down the edge or no
no i have the this i think i have
there's like a thing that keeps you from
falling off the edge
i have it on too but it didn't save me
one time and
it i fell down anyway oh maybe there's
like certain places you can fall down
uh
in front of me again
[Applause]
i'm
i think i'm in front of you again
not for long oh
[Laughter]
you're just one place in front of me
that's how i like it
it seems that we are happy this name is
skill level
yeah i like it
we're destined to be together
it appears so the stars have aligned and
placed us in exactly the same spot
you know when we talked about having
this collab
and i asked you if you're good at this
game and if you have practice and stuff
you said
you're really bad and i didn't believe
you i thought you were being just humble
but you're actually bad and i really
like it
yay ah thanks i guess
oh this goes this is hard i don't know
is it like it's like a lot of rng but
also it's it's
shortcuts and and knowing when to do
your your
drifting right yeah i think you need if
you have some practice and some skill
you can do much better i guess people
keep on telling me to drift but
drifting often messes up my driving i
don't want to drift
yeah it takes a lot of uh counteracting
your own drifting like if you're
drifting left you gotta steer right
yeah yeah so did you did you figure out
how to jump because i tried the r button
but it didn't do anything
uh it did do something for me the top
button not the uh big button on the top
but the small button the audio
i will try does that make sense i will
try i will do i want you a flip
a one 180 or 360 or something like that
yeah this is yeah music yeah
give me a yeezy
[Music]
that was a cookie huh
that was a good one
there's a canadian in front of me do
something
uh hey hey hey
how about you uh go on back to your
house eh
yeah keep on dissing the canadians right
then go
back to your house good is that all you
could come up with
tim hortons is having a sale on donuts
don't you eh
better go out you better
do canadians like donuts that much
yeah i think so i think tim hortons is a
is a canadian known that place oh really
i didn't know yeah
are they good i think aren't they great
i don't know
i assume so dave heart the sponsor wants
to send them
send us some donuts that's collaborate
it was clever oh
i feel like i'm number one but i'm like
probably some somewhat around eight
wait when did i get an 11th place
don't think about it
that's double number one
you probably need to spam more yeehaws
items
would have got away
oh ruins sound like i could have been
next to you again but
master fb or some someone else hit me
with a shell again i could have been
next to you god damn
who ruined this hidden moment again
i bet they were saving that for you too
karma it's karma for and you were saving
that shell for me
that was a present i thought you like
shells since you're from
the ocean i love shells
pearl oyster shells and clam shells
there you go
there you go i wanted to help you with
your collection of shells
everyone thank you give all your red
shells and green shells to gouda
because she's collecting them do you
have a favor do her
favor and send them all to her
uh save your your fiery items for
yeah i guess the fire that's okay i'm
fire resistant barely anyone ever
guessed that item anyway that's okay
that's a pretty rare item
[Laughter]
all shadows do the turtle good you are a
turtle now you're a trouble
i am i am good at turtle
how do you say twitter in japanese uh
coming coming
home
[Music]
wait i need a cream i need a fan out of
you as green goura like
all the blue elements in your design
have to be green
somebody give me give me a comment give
me a turtle shell
not not in the raised that's so perfect
oh my god comment comment on it
don't look comedy
oh god i i i
i i feel like i i deserve some credit
for that
yeah i'll give you credit where are you
yeah no no no no
i don't want that kind of credit don't
little keep it to yourself keep with
yourself
yes
that's not rover what was that it's moe
rover what
uh is the character in the game and
marshall wow there's a character called
roving
yeah what is that it's a it's a cat
character in the one of the previous
or a few of the previous animal crossing
games
oh
no no no i'm not available right now i'm
busy
without you fire no right no no
some fire was sent to me just as you
have told them
[Music]
[Applause]
nice try with your common shells ladies
and gentlemen
[Music]
this is good grace now
i was doing so well where's the
finishing line i have no idea where i'm
right now
oh
we were supposed to be on the same level
i got i got lucky with uh lucky with a
shell uh not a shell with a
gold mushroom at the end god damn
it goddammit the next one come on i want
i wonder which one
ice skating sounds nice do you like to
go ice skating
uh i do oh it could be fun i don't know
it must have been a bit ago oh me too
but guys getting so much fun in winter
best time ever good at on skates
how how adorable would that be no i
haven't done ice skating i've done
roller blading
oh i'm talking about ice skating i know
my brain went to rollerblading it's like
okay i love rollerblading too i love ice
cream uh uh what's it called but it's
called
role playing and there's another name
inline skating
inline skating what is in line skinny oh
maybe that's just a
name we use for referred in german even
though it's english
have you seen uh people that go i call
it land skiing
have you ever seen that before eh yeah
people's keys
right
they do it online they do it up like the
on the sidewalk it's so crazy
what with the longest skis are you sure
just the two sticks on the side
i mean it looks like ski that's probably
just hiking go down
now
wait there's such a thing as gouda is
explaining it actually exists or is she
talking about
hiking hold on guys back me up you know
that's real
cross-country skiing is that a thing
actually
oh my god trekking poles right
apparently
i mean i've seen it's real i've seen
people walking around with the
those with those sticks in the in their
hands but
they're not they're not using uh
the ski skiers right their legs are on
their lane skis i promise you
really i want to see that
is that is that a thing in them is that
a thing in atlantis
and maybe i would do the same
the whole time you and me you got free
mushrooms i got three mushrooms you
gotta start i get a star
we're insane the game wants us to be in
the city
beautiful it's supporting our
relationship
hashtag summertonies
spread the love ah you sent that shell
to the wrong person my friend
should have been addressed to guratan
it's time to take a flight guru
at least i'm next to you that makes me
happy i like to see you in front of me
that
gives me a feeling of reassurance makes
me feel safe when you're in front of me
[Music]
i'm not sure if i should be worried or
because then you're gonna you're gonna
help me with all your stuff
you can take that in so many ways i i
might just really
mean it in a whole some way or it might
i might mean it in a way of i want to
destroy you
[Music]
money big money
yeah you can be happy now because now
you get a promotion
okay i lost my crown
where's my crown goddammit okay
yeah one last game that sounds good
all right all righty which one should we
go for
last game everyone last game get in
while you can
and please leave if you just we're in
the race please leave
so we give one last chance to everyone
else
kick those two how do i kick people
people telling me to kick them have they
been in there for a while
please leave thank you please
please let me politely ask you thank you
thanks you
thank you thank you thank you new people
you're welcome to come in
and and did you choose
i did random if if we choose random does
that
choose randomly from those three or from
all of the races
i don't know i assume it'd be from the
ones that are are listed
[Music]
oh
i see let's see
from oh oh it's it's from everyone
someone in the chat said all of them
they came back
whatever let's go
last race
[Music]
what up you want to race with us huh
are you there challenge yes i'm
recording
you have no chance against us
okay how about guys we're turning around
this time you guys we're challenging you
to
lose uh against us can you do it
can you do it let us see if you can take
up this challenge
are you able to lose against us huh
that's gonna be a hard one
it's actually a challenge that that is
actually a challenge
hey stop bumping me way too much in the
front
why are you like doing like second or
third or something how did you do that
well it will change soon don't worry go
down
don't get used to it
i'm so happy tiara believes in me guys
i just want you to live with me
i'm coming it's time
why are these people actually trying to
accept my challenge and lose against you
but you're also supposed to lose against
me
not only against guru
no no no no no you are yeah
there's a fake australian that's the
wrong flag my dude
mate that's the wrong flag oh i might
as your own flag together
[Music]
oh no you passed
the me luck is strong in this one oh
wow wow wow wow that thunder did not
bother me
and bye bye and bye bye
i'm driving really bad right now and
bye-bye
[Applause]
wait i'm sick and there's a
blue shell coming for the first what
what what's the item lecture
oh my god
lu yoshi you better not mess this up
right now you better not
no no no no no
that was my uncle
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
applies
[Applause]
good job good job good job that was nice
that was
down those were some good races good on
you and me were a good team
that was fun i had a lot of fun gotta
leave the race though
yes okay well
well well wow my
how do you call this my uh my
excitement my my there's a rush there's
i have a rush what do you call this
adrenaline yeah wow it's like that
oh my gosh it's that race car adrenaline
now you gotta go run three miles around
around the block a few times hell yeah
i'll go do that
thank you so much for driving with me it
was a pleasure
good luck thank you
oh thank you i'm looking forward to a
future future battle with you like
a future battle as in mario kart perhaps
smash i mean yeah i think we're probably
also on the both level and smash as well
so
you lose to the ledge too do you also
fall off the map repeatedly
of course of course i do of course okay
let's do smash next time hello
okay okay we can do that i'm down for
that
all righty uh i like to say in german to
my viewers auf wiedersehen
okay i'll see you guys oh nice one
they're cute
bye bye everyone everybody bye bye thank
you
bye-bye hashtag sammy told you forever
[Music]
bye
you