[Music]
n n
n
[Music]
uhuh uh uh uh uh welcome to
wayy welcome to wayy
birthday I think okay welcome
everybody can you guys hear the music
cuz like the music bugs out here
sometimes we need to fix the machine
even though it's a very special occasion
which is my birthday oh hello bgm is
lovely I know hold on let me um there we
go we can hear unfortunately we
do oh shoot oh shoot wait I had the logo
but I closed it and didn't save I made
the thumbnail for this stream like last
night and I guess I was just too sleepy
that I forgot to save the logo um but I
think let me if I can save it Salvage it
from the thumbnail thumbnail and I'll
put it up um oh actually no I saved it
hell yeah hold
on let's put it on the
screen so guys welcome to wayy birthday
it's my birthday today
it's my birthday today it's a don't ask
it's the 29th technically but this
stream is set on my birthday and we are
just going to have
fun and thank you so much for coming to
my party I know we're we're going to
have some fun eat some cake play some
beautiful games and stuff oh on let me
just export the export the
logo stff St yeah hold
on I hope this
works what why is it that when I quick
export spng there's no transparency it's
so annoying that's not quick export
that's guaranteed messed up
export I do not want
that anyways I worked so hard woke up
early this morning just to prepare this
for you guys so hold on let me
refresh so
cck there we go yay welcome to this
birthday yeah
so I actually have a little bit of a
problem we got the bgm set the party is
set but
uh-oh oh no it's seems that somebody has
stolen the
cake who could it
be oh my
goodness oh no we got to quickly make an
announcement I'm going to make an
announcement on Twitter somebody stole
the cake is there anybody I could ask to
for some information I
wonder I'm going to shout as loud as I
can on Twitter of
course who could have done such a thing
I know even though it's my birthday just
buy it again it's not that easy come on
I already bought a special watermelon
flavored cake for you with a taste of
disaster and um arson but there's only
it's only one of a k it's custom made we
can just like order a cake and be like
hey I want the exact same
one you know so hold on hold on let me
let me let me post someone stole the
cake someone stole the cake
anybody I can ask slash call
for for info yeah
ah there we go I have posted I have
posted on Twitter and I hope I hope I
will get info okay you know what I will
um I will turn on my notification
sound something I very rarely do I have
put it out there I have put it out there
and I guess um right now this is very
important because oh my
goodness help
[Music]
someone has
stolen the
cake
cake need
info Twitter do your magic it's just
like how I did it with the GTA RP but
this time it's
real a even if I do even if I buy
another cake do you guys know if I can
get I don't know if I if there's like
something that's like remotely similar
with what I ordered I'm so was so
excited I was so excited to show you
guys but come on nice handwriting
thanks are you joking or what if you're
not joking thank you if you're joking
then thank you
also
[Music]
yeah c order
that's why my my birthday is early
September but we can only hold this
birthday party here now because it took
one month to custom order the cake can
you imagine and now today is
stolen I don't think anyone cooking that
cake should be able to serve people oh
come on be free
real I have somebody in my phone book
of somebody in my phone book so um let
me see if I can ask around um well there
are some guests in the parties maybe I
can ask some people outside let me see
let me see if I can message someone and
be
like
Oh but before that we do have a I I
think I received something in the mail
hold on give me give me a a second guys
give me a second guys I think I received
something in the
mail what is
this this
is this is a letter directly addressed
at
me but there's no return
address huh
interesting wait hold on give me a
second guys just give me give me some
time to open this
[Music]
um
H
huh okay it comes with a
squid it comes with a spicy squid which
is delicious um thank you I think it's
like a birthday gift also comes with a
letter um rather than a
letter
[Music]
yeah what is
this I witnessed
it the
crime they did
it
huh well I guess
um I don't know if I can use this as
info ah I'll just pin this
then I'll just pin
this they did it so that's what they
look
like
okay they look like they have pants
on and they have big
feet I don't know if it's the artistic
light
Liberty of the person sending the tip
but it seems like they have big feet and
they're wearing jeans are these jeans or
just blue pants I don't know or I don't
know if they're shirtless or not but I
guess we'll find out I don't think we
can trust just this
[Music]
clue I witnessed it the crime so the
cake was really stolen see I did not
misplace it let me see if I can get
someone to um
real quick excuse
me
um let me
[Music]
see let's
see let me
see
Hello 2 three 4 2 2 three oh oh hey oh
hey oh hello hello
hi um hello what are you doing here if I
may ask no I'm just uh exercising for
the day consuming my delicious protein
consuming your delicious protein well um
well I'm having this birthday party down
the blog do you have any idea if you saw
somebody cuz so I'm having this party we
got all the music prepared and stuff but
somebody seems to have ran off with the
birthday
cake birthday cake yeah cake you
mean unnecessary
carbohydrates that's not
unnecessary it's for my birthday it's
fine I have it once in a
while you should have some protein
cake I I mean I mean I guess I could
order protein cake but this was a custom
order for i i Custom ordered it and
waited for month so I just want to know
if you saw somebody who um who so
yeah definitely not me cuz I only
consume protein you only protein you
only consume protein so definitely not
you def definitely not me I wouldn't eat
cake even if I were to die tomorrow oh
definitely not I guess so I guess that
makes sense well um since it definitely
can't be you um do you saw did you see
anybody who might be suspicious I did
see someone earlier running kind of
suspiciously uh-huh do you do you happen
to do they have like jeans blue
jeans oh I think they did have blue
pants I wasn't sure if it was jeans cuz
they were moving kind of fast okay I was
really distracted by my protein oh okay
and just one more question do they have
big
feet ooh I mean maybe maybe they did I
told you they were moving pretty fast
like like really fast like they were
like almost like an after image of thems
you know oh I was wondering man what
protein do they take to run that fast
maybe it's their big feet you know yeah
you never know you know but yeah well
okay thank you so much um can I can we
can we trade contact number so maybe if
if I can text you if there's like you
know a development the case or if you
can if you see something then you can
contact me of course of course you can
you can call 1 1800 protein 1800 protein
thank you so much I hope you don't
actually call the number oh
okay in case I need some protein cake
all right yeah next time you should
really get some
protein okay thank you so much um
protein guy I will um yeah I'll continue
my quest thank
you
bye-bye
bye have fun with the
muscles okay
so I just asked this guy who seems to be
busy
exercising thank you so much for taking
the time
to give me some info well so I guess
the catch would be accurate to some
extent cuz this person is wearing
um oh
[Music]
notification not something
unrelated oh man I wish it would have
been about the
cake call only if I want protein hold on
call only if I oh shoot I can't if I
want
protein well I guess this is the last
resort you know if we can't really get
the cake then I I can text this person
but anyways
um all right that's good
suspicious oh man I don't see anyone
else right now but um
sh hold
on uh wait hold on let me see if I can
look around and see somebody
else hold on somebody I can
ask
um I think I see someone you guys can
also help out you guys can also help out
[Music]
excuse
me excuse
me hello uh yes yes yes yes hi what are
you doing hello hello I'm doing good how
you doing I'm I am doing well not so
good actually well oh what why because
well I am see I'm having this birthday
party down the block but I will we had
all the music ready and stuff we were
listening to the music as we speak
actually but somebody seems to have
stolen the cake I just thought if you
know maybe you've seen something wait
what someone stole the cake mhm somebody
stole the cake I mean right I mean I
asked somebody earlier but um they
didn't really give much info like an
anomymous letter letter came and one
person already confirmed that they run
really fast and they got blue jeans or
blue pants at least so I I was just
wondering if you saw somebody like that
stealing the cake or something M no but
but um I may have some informations for
you oh oh oh what is it what is it yeah
uh but I cannot give it for free like I
cannot give this information so easily
wait you have to you have to Sol riddle
first you have to Sol wait why don't you
want to help
me yeah but you have to solve a riddle
first it's very easy
okay okay what's the riddle okay I'll
start so I am not alive but I grow I
don't have lungs but I need air I don't
have a mouth and I I can and and I can
still draw who am I what am
I uh sorry I I am I am not alive but I
can grow I'm not alive but I can grow
uh-huh I don't have a lungs but I need
hair you need air yeah yeah yeah and
then and I don't have a month but I can
see a drone but what am I but you can
what the what's the end drone like oh
under water
oh um but you need air
is it a balloon what is it no no um you
have no no oh what if I can't answer
it well you know got informations I'm
sorry like it is what is no do you have
2 minutes from now what do you mean I
have 2 minutes can I can I phone a
friend yeah sure yo yo guys guys what do
it tell me
yo what is it wait wait wait I see I see
people texting me they said the answer
is fire is it true that it's fire yeah
fire is correct congratulations oh thank
you so will you give me the information
now
please please okay um so I don't
actually know about your birthday cake
per but I have some clues about who made
the cake who made the cake
yes so who made the cake is probably
involved in this even though I custom
ordered from them for a month okay
yes so who made the cake has a very big
long hat and it's green big long hat
that is green thank you so much for your
information this is very valuable I'm
going to go keep searching yes sorry oh
there's two more yes there is another
thing oh yes what yes about um who stole
the cake this time okay stole the cake
the teeth was wearing something shiny
shiny on the teeth no no the the the
teeth like the who sold the cake M was
wearing something shiny okay okay okay
okay they wearing something shiny okay
yes okay like a gold brass or necklace I
don't know oh
shiny okay thank you so much I
appreciate it this is very valuable info
I learned something new about the as
well bye I'm going to go keep asking
good Lu bye-bye
byebye all right hello excuse me okay
there's somebody else there's somebody
else
hello hello may I ask you something
of course welcome welcome or am I the
welcome one oh hello well you see I'm
having a birthday party down this down
the block but then somebody stole the
birthday cake even though even though I
I already had all the bgm set up um
right now there mhm well well first off
happy birthday secondly the question is
who wouldn't steal the cake in this
neighborhood I think you could I think
you lives at the wrong neighbor
neighborhood for this kind of
scenario what do you mean I I I I just
moved here 2 weeks ago are you saying
that this neighborhood isn't
safe oh yeah yeah this neighborhood is
definitely not safe we got some crazy
people here I believe we have some some
few people that may or may not be dead I
think they're dead honestly H what do
you me or they're dead crazy I'm not
sure and then there's like a a pink
looking cat who might be human I I know
she's supposed to be a panther
supposedly but I don't know I just think
she might be a furry oh oh well um I
think I might have seen somebody like
that just
earlier oh you better be careful around
her wait but but she so she told me good
info though are you saying I have to be
careful you have to be careful of
everyone yeah you can't trust anyone in
this neighborhood they might backstab
you but happy birthday happy birthday
yeah okay okay okay um well
well thank you for the in info then is
that is that is that no problem just
just a word of warning though the next
person you me she's Ultra crazy just
saying that is it that woman over there
is no happy birthday thank you bye
I am I am so
scared oh hello so nice to meet
you the lady over there told me the next
person I'm meeting is well she told me
this neighborhood is dangerous is that
true uh I mean a little dangerous but
I'm not a dangerous person you don't
have to worry you know
really yeah
really is that really well okay well I
guess I well so I'm having a birthday
party down the block and then okay um we
all had this you know the party all set
of the beachamp also set up but somebody
stole the cake and I was just wondering
um if you have seen somebody with blue
pants very
fast and wearing something
shiny around
here h
I actually did see someone who matched
that description they ran just behind me
but it was about 10 minutes ago so
they're probably pretty far off by now
10 minutes ago um do do do you have any
um what else were they wearing so so I
can look for them more easily yeah yeah
they were wearing a black tank top black
tank top okay so they're not shirtless
they're wearing black tank top yeah they
were shirt shirtless I don't know who
would have said they were shirtless but
they had a black tank top and then they
had a very pretty necklace on pretty
necklace okay yeah pretty pretty
yeah it was um it was gold gold oh that
may be the something shiny that the
other person mentioned I think so cuz it
was quite shiny it looked like they took
very good care of it that's very nice Al
although the fact that they sto my cake
was not um anyways are you are you a
resident of this
neighborhood uh kind of I I live
actually a town over but I like to come
here to go grocery shopping you know
it's just a little fun thing I like to
do oh so you go grocery shopping in the
next town the here yeah well my town
actually doesn't have a grocery store uh
so I I kind of don't actually have a
choice oh okay okay that's good well um
do you think we can um trade numbers
like like you know if like if I have
more if you have more info then you can
call me and if I have more info I can
call you yeah of course uh my my phone
number are you ready for it yeah yeah I
have my notes open right now it's going
to be
8675 yeah 867 309
309 yeah it okay thank you so much and
what's your
name uh my name is uh Risa Risa can you
spell that h r i s a r i s a okay thank
you Arisa um you seem like a good person
I feel like I can trust you um thank you
enjoy your day I'm going to keep
searching okay good luck I hope you find
your cake thank you happy birthday oh oh
thank you thank you bye see you
bye okay well it seems I can trust that
person cuz well I guess like
um well well you know girl before this
said so the girl before before this said
that the next po woman I would meet
would be scary but I guess this girl is
from out of
town what if she's lying though what if
she's not from out of
[Music]
town
okay Risa all right well I guess she's
from out of town and the girl only
warned me from people in town so it's
all good maybe I can trust her what
about the protein guy though can I trust
him I'm not
sure
[Music]
okay
mm and well okay let's take a little
break huh
okay
uhhuh let's cha the
information ah okay so let me let me let
me make this um let me make this smaller
actually oh [\h__\h] hold on let me make
this a little bit
smaller scale yeah cuz we have limited
notes we have limited
notes special person okay this looks
good suspicious person running well we I
mean if we can trust the people then we
get the we get the stuff
okay we can just the info well I wonder
if there's somebody else I can
ask it's kind of like they're getting
kind of they're getting kind of far but
I'm not
sure well maybe I can ask uh I can ask
around hold
on there's nobody right now so far I
wonder
man what a
birthday do you guys know what protein
cakes looks
[Music]
like but I'm glad so far they can be Co
they are pretty Cooperative oh hold
on well this person seems
unfamiliar I don't think she's from this
town I don't think she's from from this
town um I'm going to
call I wonder if she speaks
[Music]
English
hello
H
hello hi um hi do you speak
English what is
English do oh sorry I speak English Okay
Okay so Ino I'm
asking I'm asking in I'm having birthday
party down the block
yeah we have music already but somebody
somebody stole the
cake what cake
cake cake in yeah watermelon watermelon
cake with uh D it's custom order one
month oh fancy oh by the way happy
birthday thank you so much well um so
far I've been asking around and some
people said um the culprit is wearing
blue jeans petang top necklace and stuff
like that do you happen to you know see
anybody like that around
you H wait wait are you the famous the
antagonist
Auntie well some people know me as that
but right now I'm having a birthday
party so I guess none of those none of
those antagonist ay ay that's only when
I'm on screen but this is just like
we're having a little birthday party
with a bunch of friends and stuff like
that you
know oh you know what I'm a big fan of
the antagonist Auntie if you can maybe
scul me like a the Mir T antagonist I me
spill some I mean sip some uh spill some
tea okay
um
guys H okay I I can I think I do this do
you promise to give me info if I do this
for
you yes I do have some juicy info though
okay was happy
enough I think that's that that's makes
uh makes me very very happy thank you so
much oh my God where's the
info where's the end okay okay I will
give you the I will I will s some I will
spill some tee for you okay so as far as
I recall the the teeth I think I saw
someone that looks like a teeth uh they
have the they wear the blue pants
yeah and then they I think they have a
long hair and also innocent face
innocent face there's nothing innocent
about a thief they're guilty
but but the face is so innocent I don't
know I might be right I might be wrong
okay is is is that all is that the juicy
info that you have is that all yeah I
think I think that's pretty that's
pretty uh detailed you know because I
know the face uh actually I live here
for quite some time but uh I know no one
here no one know me here since I'm a
hiori so ah okay that makes sense that
makes sense okay well I I don't know man
I I I think this town is dangerous
somebody just told me that but thank you
so much I think we should move some
you're welcome D okay oh bye I'm going
to keep looking
bye
[Music]
bye-bye
a oh there's somebody else I hope they
have better info I hope they have better
info please I beg
you I beg you please be use
[Music]
hey
hey who is this I'm I'm nobody I just
want to ask you something please oh my
God okay what is it
I well the thing is uh I'm uh I'm having
a birthday party right now and we have
the of the music and stuff but right as
I was about to get the cake out I just
realized that somebody stole
it so did some somebody some people told
me they were wearing tank top gold
necklace and jeans and they were really
fast with long hair innocent face I
don't know all these like yeah so do you
have anybody have you seen anybody like
that hey why you kind of look like her
what the heck never mind my mistake I
guess sorry yeah do you have any info I
just I just want to say it's definitely
not not a girl with long hair and have
you know a you know like a purple or
yellow hair and have a shiny definitely
not um and and she she definitely she
definitely not not eating the whole cake
that is a sto in the fridge
yes why are you phrasing it like that
H what why are you phrasing it like that
you didn't do anything right
no no I I definitely not eating any cake
that from the fridge
yes
what well so do you have you can you can
you probably can ask others yeah uhuh
that's that's what that's what I I say I
I have I don't I don't know I I don't
know um and I've been I've been busy
this whole things with the fruits thingy
anyway um yeah probably n me yeah yeah
yeah wait don't R she ran
away
what what she ran
away she ran away
[Music]
wait she didn't run that fast but I'm
not
[Music]
sure man I don't
know I don't know I don't know what to
do right now Well the description kind
of matched they have long
hair and I don't know something
shiny I don't know
[Music]
H there somebody sent me a voice
message somebody sent me a voice
message I don't know how to play it
here let me let me mute the music let me
check my phone first
guys
and maybe this is one of the anonymous
tips again well let me let let me hear I
did distribute my phone number if
anybody wants to like send info but let
me let me let me let me let me let me
listen to this
first oh on wait why it's so low the
sound is so low hold
on I heard that it's so low it's so low
can I save this well you guys just have
to crank the volume
up
filter filter and then
G um I heard that your birthday cake got
stolen and and I
actually I kind of know possibly who it
was but I don't I'm not sure if I should
really say it too clearly because it's
it's really hard I'm kind of torn
between you know people who I like and I
don't want to rat them out so
easily um but surely it was all just a
misunderstanding but well one thing I
can say is it might be someone who
visits you often has good access to
where you
live um who you trust very
much
maybe someone who's quite the
Kaki
Gremlin it's just because you
know I I I've seen her with lots of
cream around her mouth
and yeah that was very sus she was quite
excited
and well I should probably not say much
more but I really feel for you because
my um birthday cake a long time ago when
I I was a child also got stolen before
right in front of my eyes actually so
there was no doubt about who it was but
yeah
I I feel like your cake might be eaten
by now so it's probably lost but if you
confirm that it is or that it was who I
think it was I'm
I'm I'm ready to help you punish the
person if you
need okay so
um did you guys hear that I had to like
um you know do do the like gain uh like
I need to I need to crank up the game I
couldn't hear it if it was louder but I
thought it was
okay okay okay
okay so
okay okay well it's a m okay this person
seems to
know this person seems to know a lot it
was a misunderstanding hold on let me
turn the PGM back on
oh sorry
yeah
misunderstanding visits me
often so basically has good access to my
place and the
fridge and supposedly I trust her saki
Gremlin cream around her mouth
suspicious no
black tank top oh my God this is
so
[Music]
okay hold
on let me see let me see this the more
people I as the more confusing this is
[Music]
getting
done let me just um oh
God what what if it's not only just one
person
oh okay let me see if there's somebody
else you know I don't I I'm starting to
be like this is this a good idea is this
a good idea to ask that many
people so I don't know well maybe I
can excuse me
hello is this the police no this is not
the
[Music]
police witnessed a and I needed to talk
to the police I thought they were going
to call me back oh well you're wait wait
what's your
issue I saw somebody steal a cake really
really I absolutely 100% saw them really
well well well well well then this is
the police oh can you tell me what you
saw oh thank you thank you I see you
just undercover a little bit I make sure
on the right side of the law yeah yeah
what is it sorry yeah well I can assure
you that they were
absolutely tall no they were short
actually shorts M tall they were they
were somewhere between short and tall in
height okay between then between okay
okay and well is it true that they had
long hair and an innocent face cuz I've
been like somebody told me that kind of
info you just wanted to make sure if
that's correct or
not I can say with certainty that they
had a face yes and hair they had face
and hair so they're not bald but not
hair all over their body only only in
some places and I could see oh okay okay
okay I see I see so they got face in
here they're not bald but like just just
in some places here in some places I see
only in some places not all over such as
such as what like the hair like the hair
on the head or um um um there were two
patches above the eyes two patches above
the eyes of
hair yes okay well that's a very
distinct um yeah I wonder why nobody
mentioned it to me before for I think
that was a very striking feature you
would notice that
well okay
then thank you so I have to say if I
were to describe them as a shape it
would be a
parallelogram
parallelogram okay what's what's a
parallelogram shape like I it really had
the energy of a parallelogram
parallelogram energy all right thank you
so much I will try try to sit down and
think about it for a second you seem
like a nice lady do you live
here why why who's asking why does the
police need to know where I live no
because um we just received a tip so
okay this is um not more um so I'm the
police but also um I'm a person of
course so I just moved here like two I
just moved here two weeks ago and
somebody told me that this neighborhood
isn't safe it's a dangerous neighborhood
well that's why I always have my windows
boarded up oh all right so you don't
have like sunlight inside your house or
something sunlight is a is a
privilege only those who who don't care
about the safety of their cakes can
afford oh well I guess I know what I've
been doing wrong thank you so much for
uh calling the
police oh please please do call this
number not the central H please call
this number if you have if you find any
more info about the cake or the thief
okay thank you so much I hope you have a
nice day thank you thank
[Music]
you
okay what's a parallel energy wait
there's so okay wait wait I'm in a good
crowd I'm in a good
Crown hold on
[Music]
okay there's there's a crowd here I'm
I'mma ask I'm ask these people I'm ask
these
people please please answer
hello hello hi there um I'm just here to
ask you something are you busy at the
moment I I I don't like l
oh
no h
hello
oh do you understand what I'm
saying
yeah you want to talk with
me yeah um uh you know birthday
cake cake oh cake cake I like I tasty I
like a
cake yeah uh my birthday cake somebody
stole
it no cake no C no
[Music]
cake
tasty yeah no tasty now do you know
who's stole the cake bad person stole
cake you know who stole
it
i
c i I see I see c
p oh what um what do they look like they
um are they tall are they uh are they
standard height and do they have long
hair anything new you can tell me I'm
hungry you hungry I I buy you squid okay
you want
squid squid no I fish ew no
okay okay wait hold
[Music]
on Mama oh H um why am I starting to
talk like you
um you're funny yeah but okay um okay
I'll give you this number if you have
information call me okay I give you
candy if you call okay and give
info I know I know think
you they bigger they big than
me oh of course they're bigger than you
yes but I guess okay they big and we
have lots of uh uh uh hair hir Harry
Harry okay Harry yeah that
[Music]
matches okay
okay thank you so much for the
info ah
okay um
byebye
yes now what's that sorry
sorry what do that mean cany you prom oh
candy oh okay well okay here here here
here here's some for you okay some for
you just a piece of um squid but pretend
it's candy
okay okay okay I know you byebye love
you I love
[Music]
you well that um that was
something
[Music]
okay
okay well I don't know if that was
useful info at
[Music]
all why am I sorry I opened I opened the
squid so might as well
[Music]
eat I mean I opened it so you
know um well okay let's make this a
little smaller as
well let's make this a little bit
[Music]
smaller
okay there we
go
[Music]
okay this crowd is a little
bit okay
there's a bunch of people but I don't
know who I should approach first I don't
know if I can trust these
people I feel like the more well that
that little kid was okay
but that little kid was okay but that
that person who said I shouldn't trust
anyone their words still ring in my head
you know but I guess I need to
try I need to believe in my neighbors I
need to believe in my neighbors I need
to believe in my neighbors I need to
believe in my neighbors I need to
believe in my neighbors believe in my
neighbors believe in my
neighbors okay let me see if I can find
somebody hello there
hi
hello hi um are you one of my neighbors
I think I feel I feel like I've seen you
before oh oh that's that's crazy um you
know I would I you know maybe I I I
don't really have a good memory honestly
have we have we met before on good good
circumstances hopefully uh well I well
I've seen you before but I mean we
haven't we've never really talked before
I don't
think okay that's that's good I mean
like I
don't know like I've met some people who
are uh who I've met under more
unfortunate circumstances so uh that
that's good that's good you know if you
don't know me that's good okay well okay
well I you know sorry for taking your
time but I just have to ask um you know
well I having a birthday party down the
block but the thing
is but the thing is um somebody stole
the cake and I'm you know I've been like
asking somebody if they like have info
about them or something like that some
well I've been receiving some info some
some some I can trust some I don't know
somebody said this guy this person has
parallelogram energy and they're not
tall or I don't know it's just like a
bunch of different descriptions so maybe
like if you have seen somebody like that
then maybe you could give me some
info uh yeah you know actually I do live
down the blog I'm sorry for you know
like not really being honest up front I
just want to see what kind of person you
are first before but I I feel like I did
see someone uh with like you know it was
a pretty big cake right yeah yeah yeah
it was a really big cake um I ordered it
for like one month you
know yeah yeah like I I did see someone
like carrying a big cake and they were
they were in a rush so I was thinking oh
man they must be really you know busy
for their kids birthday or something but
uh yeah they uh I don't know they look
interesting they
were yeah I don't I don't really um
recall too clearly but I feel like if I
have some money maybe my memory will be
a bit more clear what did she just say
money what no what no like no what no
wait
maybe maybe can you repeat that one more
time may maybe like you know possibly
it's just that I told you my memory is
bad but uh if I
have if I have some sort of a
stimuli like money but like you know
well I it's like a good trigger for me
to remember I have a squid snack that I
was giving that kid get over there do
you want some squid snack does it
help do you have a
wallet my wallet well um I do I I do
but have a credit
card um you have online banking yeah
yeah but um you could probably e
transfer me oh um I um I I spent too
much they blocked my credit
card oh no no no don't worry it's not
like you know you don't have to use your
credit card for E transfers oh so just
my oh just my as long as oh oh my oh oh
oh shoot my phone's running out of
battery oh what what oh that's wait what
are you using to call then oh um um I'm
using my um my other phone that doesn't
have um any Bank apps in there
oh man you
know if that's the
case like not even the
dollar I um well oh
no oh I think my phone's going to
explode I'm
sorry what do we even get out of
[Music]
that I
thought I was yeah I was doy I
was I wasn't very alert wait we need to
you guys C what cat what you said
oh I think we should move the from I
think we should move from this
[Laughter]
neighborhood oh well I'm finishing the
squid
anyways it would be odd if I'm just like
carrying squid
snacks I'm calling in asking people I
don't think I don't think it's
safe how many people have we asked one
two three
four 1 3 four five six eight nine nine
people have asked
okay okay well um
[Music]
sounded like a pants wear if I'm not
going to
lie oh yeah hold on hold on oh
yeah oh yeah yeah yeah um wait so I
think somebody got
info somebody got
info
hey
hi hi hi um hi hi can I ask you
something
please yes hi hi so um I'm having this
birthday party but somebody seems to
have stolen the cake do you
know do you know anything about it happy
birthday oh sorry I'm really loud happy
birthday I'm really
excited happy bir wait wait you sound a
little bit low I think it might be my
phone's going to yeah my phone's going
to explode soon but you're going to wait
don't explode my phone is going to
explode it's like an old model I need
like a new one but is it okay sorry I
fixed that how's this yeah yeah that's
perfect yeah okay happy birthday thank
you so
much all right I I have to solve this
mystery of your missing cake huh thank
you m
who else has called in so far was the
cake there when you started um the cake
was um I was going to get the cake and
then it was gone so um that's why I've
been asking around there was this dude
selling proteins they um maybe like a
bunch of people told me they have you
know hair on their face or something
they have long hair they're NE neither
tall or short so I'm just like
crosschecking information right now to
see like if these infos are accurate so
do you have anything um protein you say
yeah um somebody was like selling not
selling protein he was like doing sports
and stuff but I asked them yeah she was
the first person I I called
actually okay that sounds suspicious
maybe if they're such they're so big
into protein maybe they wanted to
replace your cake with something like
meaty
ah they did were like they were adamant
about like oh protein cake is better
better protein cake is better we have
protein cake instead the heck is protein
cake that sounds
gross I don't know I didn't I didn't
want to be rude so I was just like okay
you know can you tell me if they had did
they have silver hair or gray hair um
they had the um the protein hair had
like um dark blue purplish
hair and I think like I saw their name
tag and it's the name tag
oh okay so I know who stole your cake
while I can I can get you one really
quick oh you can you're going to get me
a cake yeah yeah if you give me if you
give me 1 minute I'll get you a
delicious cake 1 minute okay yes um I I
just need to I don't worry I can still
talk on the phone I'm just traveling at
the speed of sound okay
okay so how how about how was the rest
of your birthday other than you know the
fact that you got you got your cake
stole and um yeah there's there's been
well well well the music was good I feel
like everybody's vibing to the music I
think I you know I I chose a banger bgm
for this party and people are me you are
like a professional DJ right yeah I mean
sort of I'm very good at um the brain
rot music genre so right that's what we
have playing in the
background yeah mhm are you from this
city by any chance somebody said that
the city isn't safe so I'm just like
wondering if that's true or
not uh no I'm not I'm not from here I'm
not from here I I just came into town
yeah oh okay yeah I just moved here two
weeks ago that's why I don't really know
much about it so yeah I see has anybody
given you any presents I mean like they
know it's your birthday right so well um
presents no I've been asking strangers
on the road from the cake I I feel like
I I need to like extort not ask for ask
for presents I don't know why these
people are coming empty-handed I don't
know but at least it's not important
yeah I know I think it's important to
find the cake th first and then maybe we
can move on you know with the proper
birthday
party yeah
yeah well I mean I I I do have a present
for you and oh thank you you're welcome
you're welcome and it's almost ready I'm
just taking it out of the oven really
quick are you're taking it out of the
oven I mean uh I'm finishing the
frosting on it really quick
mhm uh-huh um me giving a hey do you
like
aquariums I do like
aquariums how did
you I don't know I just I just kind of
got that vibe from me you oh okay yeah
big fish enjoyer I am a big fish enjoyer
I like fishing in my spare
time oh wait really yeah
H what kind of fish have you caught
before um I've caught um Goldfish
crackers I like my fishies small and
crunchy I see I see
all right well I have your cake here uh
it's it's it's nothing I mean I have a
backup cake just in case you don't find
your other cake you know oh thank you so
much but you know it's made really
quickly so it just has like a little
simple message on there a thank you
you're
welcome bye-bye thank you okay bye thank
you I hope you find your
[Music]
cake she's so guys I don't even know her
and she's giving me
cake no no my squid is spicy has got
into my
[Music]
eyes they're not from this town and they
gave me
cake wait wait hold on hold on let me
let me rename this so I can put it
[Music]
here
oh hold
[Music]
on wait wait wait let me cry about this
cake first
[Music]
because oh f a cake is so
difficult hold on
[Music]
they're not even from this town I moved
like two weeks
ago
and and I don't know
[Music]
I don't know what cake this is what's
inside it I don't think I'm going to I
think I'm going to store it I'm going
think I'm going
to I think I'm going to store it in a
fridge first but where can I find a
fridge is it a frozen cake no the
well there's still we can still
um we can still
um
um call the
protein
shop so we can have at least two
[Music]
cakes there are drinks in the fridge all
right hold on what am I
doing
there there we
go there we
go the cake is in the
[Music]
fridge
uh I'm just very touched to receive a
replacement
cake should have probably said yes to
the protein but then I was very
determined to find
stuff to find um yeah it was incredibly
kind of
[Music]
her
yeah I'm going to I'm going to find who
sto this cake and even if and if I don't
even if I don't I have a cake so I'm not
worried anymore we're still having a
birthday party guys don't worry
don't worry about it we're having a
birthday
[Music]
[Applause]
party she reminds
me she reminds me of somebody she
reminds me of somebody I don't know if
it's the same person they look very
similar I don't know if it's the same
they um they look and their Vibes is
very similar to a certain somebody that
I really respect and
admire and you know her name is a
what but
yeah I guess I just got emotional
receiving the cake you
know so yeah don't die I'm
fine
[Music]
hi um I'm just going to eat
squid eat squid to relax myself
no tius thank
you cake I got
cake it's so
[Music]
spicy no
okay hold
on no I think the spicy Squid got into
my eyes
[Music]
okay the spicy squid is so
dangerous I
know
[Music]
okay well let's
um let's
um let's let's let's let's compile this
in a neater way
okay
okay let's let's let's compile this in
the Neer way suspicious person so we can
sort of
confirm the blue pants Oh Sho sorry this
is
to
blue blue
pants and fast
[Music]
and then
black tank
top with gold necklace is that
proper and
then yeah the long hat belonged to the
cake owner I don't know if it had
something to do but I'm going to mention
this anyway
green hat by Cake
[Music]
Maker okay and
um long
[Music]
hair
innocent kusogaki face kind of
I know
[Music]
her that's really weird because I just
moved to
town and
um two weeks ago but um yeah a
parallelogram vibes
[Music]
and
then neither short or
[Music]
tall hair hair on their eye
ey hair is it around their eyes or like
above their eyes I don't
[Music]
remember
oh all
hold on I'm going to I think there's
somebody I can
[Music]
call I'm
still hair above their eyes and then
what else face and hair
is there anything I'm
[Music]
missing glit was so spicy I
know yeah long hair innocent face yeah I
think
[Music]
um I think I think this is it the rest
would be like either conflicting
information or like additional
information that uh um yes
hello oh
hi
hi hey there um so yeah okay sorry for
the sniffling I just had really bad
squid allergy but um uh squid all right
yeah squid allergy get too so um JY I
live down the block actually are you
from this
town uh no as I just moved moved moved
here like last year last year wait that
that means that means youve lived here
longer than me for me it's two weeks so
yeah yeah it just moved here
recently and um all
right and
um somebody stole my
cake is
it your cake birthday cake my birthday
cake so I'm looking who uh who stole it
oh wait I think uh wait I think I saw
some cake but I don't know if I'm still
Dreaming or not how can you tell it's a
reality and dream how do you tell them
apart it's reality it's reality because
if you pinch your cheeks it
hurts wait let me try ah it hurts wait
uh oh wait I think I saw it but wait
wait I think it was
I'm not sure about the color or the
thing but I wait what what kind of cake
is it like do you know the
sh okay so it's like a water it's
customade watermelon
cake
a ah I think I saw someone it's custom
made a month ago so I'm like very bummed
that it's
gone oh wait I saw someone like brought
like a big package but I'm not sure if
it's cake or not what do you
mean like I I know those big box cake
you know cake box uhuh but I'm not sure
is it is it the watermelon cake or not
okay bringing cake box okay so did they
have long
hair
H I think I'm I'm not sure probably
short yeah cuz if it's long I would
remember
but short
okay wow we have conflicting information
here oh my God maybe they cut their hair
that's also a possibility after stealing
the cake they cut the hair oh is it
maybe they kind of like tied uh their
hair in a bun or something ah could be
could be tied in a
bun I don't think looking for hair is
like a really good clue right now I
guess so uh rather
but I think from I I saw it I think it's
a girl yeah that matches our description
so far uh black uh if you see like black
tank top gold
necklace yeah it's a girl the way the
way she kind of like walk you know yeah
yeah yeah okay okay okay okay okay thank
you so much do you think she has dumpy
like
you oh
nah mine's bigger okay um smaller dumpy
no not that no no no dumpy smaller dumpy
just just more more yes yes yes yes okay
thank you so much I have so much
information please pray for me that I
will catch the cake thief all right I
will I got to back to sleep then okay
bye bye good luck yes
[Music]
H
okay and hold on give me a
[Music]
second man okay we have more info this
is
beautiful I'm going to call okay I see a
Boro hello
[Music]
Boro
H hello is a good
boy
hello can you can you can you speak
H
hell well okay are you from this
town I am from this very Town yes I'm a
local you are a local okay well maybe if
you are a local you will know more
people than I do then
so um or do I I sure hope
so okay I sure hope so you to um a my
cake I'm having a birthday party down
the block but then somebody we have like
brain rot DJ
music and it's so it's a banger but
somebody stole the cake and I've been
going back and forth back and forth to
look for cake got
stolen custom watermelon cake d i prepar
for a month can you imagine oh wow
that's wow that's bad can I check can I
check your mouth for a little bit of um
no I'm just enjoying my
new
slic uh pudding oh pudding oh yeah okay
okay you're safe you're safe it's not
you well yeah we've been getting some
tips that they have blue pants and black
tank top gold
necklace and something like that have
you seen somebody like that before for I
I I'm wearing blue pants but no no black
tank top just blue pants oh
okay are you sure are you sure it's blue
pants I mean that's what so I received
an anonymous letter and that was the
leading that was the
leading clue okay I'm I'm asking what
time did uh what time was your party um
11: 11: 11: p.m. a.m. a.m. and then it
got stolen when I was about to bring out
the cake oh blue pants black tank top
are you sure it's not like uh white gold
because you know depends on the
lighting depends on the lighting yeah
depends on the lighting I'm pretty sure
it's black and blue see not white and
gold
it's a possibility white gold yeah white
gold or black
blue M because if if it's like indoor
party definitely it will look like that
depends on where you stand yeah I guess
so oh my God this opens up a whole new
perspective I think you have you might
have you know given me a Brain
Blast can we contact can we trade
contact info so like maybe lat sure if I
can contact you or you can contact me if
you have new info or something yeah sure
sure or don't also don't forget to check
on the traces yeah uh if it like cake
they have like crumbs and everything so
don't forget to check on crumbs okay
yeah okay thank you so
much okay I hope I hope you can find a
cprit soon thank you definitely not me
yeah yeah I saw your m
lighting yeah okay thank you bye I'm
going to keep looking bye
[Music]
bye
CH wait I think I see somebody oh come
on oh please
hello
hi hello
oh
[Music]
no
myom don't are you crying please don't
[Music]
cry have you seen my
mom I could be your mom if you want have
you seen my
cake
no what cake it's a big watermelon cake
um custom order for 1 month and somebody
stole it oh no wait I think somebody
stole my toy at the park as well oh no
is this neighborhood just straight up
unsafe are you from this
town no I got
lost someone gave me a candy but then
when I I looked back and I think that
person stole my toy and what if like
what if they steal other people's stuff
like your birthday cake as well
no that would be so bad do you know what
this person looked like I'm looking for
somebody with blue pants black and gold
outfit blue
blue blue
or maybe it could be white and gold we
don't know depends on the lighting I
think they they weren't wearing pants
but I don't remember no pants that's so
e maybe I don't know maybe it's like a
like a called like a skirt maybe it's
not a skirt I don't
remember okay
scir okay maybe they could have just
changed their clothes and okay um tell
you what they changed their clothes
to
avoid uh I also think they brought like
a like a little they brought a shoulder
bag shoulder
bag yeah a shoulder bag cuz they gave me
candy and from the shoulder bag oh okay
okay okay okay I see I see I
see oh my goodness shoulder bag that is
a very useful information
thank you so
much I will I will try my best because
um I have a I have a canalon who is a a
police officer maybe um they can track
who stole your
candy okay and my mom I lost oh yeah
you're okay you're mom all right then
I'll contact the mom's Association and
see if somebody lost a kid all right
okay bye-bye auntie byebye
many kids in the neighborhood but they
keep say it's
[Music]
unsafe need to call moms in my
area all right then well
um okay let's compile
um let us compile
this is very
[Music]
okay okay make this there we
go I think we have a lot of information
already I'm still accepting oh
shoot yeah there we go
I think uh I'm still accepting if
somebody would like to I'm going to I'm
I'm putting I'm putting up a sign here
I'm putting up a sign here
somebody
someone stole my
[Music]
cake um tap my
shoulder if you
see if you if you if you know info
there we
[Music]
go now we have even
more we have even more conflicting
information so oh my
God I think oh my God I'm going to take
a break after this there's somebody
there's somebody that seems to be
looking at me at the
moment
somebody hold on maybe maybe after this
uh in order to avoid any more
conflicting info I'm going to I'm going
to S we're going to sit down and sketch
a little bit
okay oh my goodness more moms in my area
oh hi oh hello I didn't see you standing
there you smell so good what's your
perfume my perfume oh it's nothing but
pixie dust and dreams oh that's so M
yummy um but actually um um well are you
from this town I have um I have a little
bit of a problem here
actually this town no I'm from a
different Fantasy Land called fairy
manic cream girl land oh fairy manic
cream what
sorry fairy manic dream girl land oh
fairy manic dream girl land that sounds
like a lovely Place much safer than here
I think um well so the thing is I'm
having a birthday party down the block
and oh my yeah do you like birthdays do
you have birthdays in there I do we
usually put flowers on our heads and we
eat pixie bread oh it's just so
wonderful oh that's so that's so amazing
I wish I wish I could just
do how to move how to move to your
fantasy land please oh well it's very
easy see if you join right here we have
like a very good group following and
every day you will be fed and you will
join our house and you will become one
of us manic fixie dream girl
girlies oh oh okay I see um I'll I'll
think about we can talk about it after
um well I explained my circumstance
would that be
okay sure what is it um all right well
yeah so I'm kind of looking for somebody
with blue pants and it's either black
and blue like black tank top and blue
jeans but somebody said like just
because black and blue it's possible
that it might actually be white and gold
because of the lighting you know so I'm
kind of confused right now oh is it
because of the magic light fairies I'm
sorry they can be quite thankful
sometimes but I think I saw someone with
the same description as Dad oh I I I see
uh yeah so do do you know where they ran
off to or maybe you can um confirm these
um uh description do they do they have
long hair or short hair cuz we have like
two different conflicting information at
the moment H let me see let me rewind my
memories I was at the park talking to
the grass and smelling the Earthly trees
and that's when I saw someone running M
they had the same description but they
ran pretty fast too so I couldn't quite
catch it but I do remember they long
flowing hair just like a siren and a
mermaid okay yeah checks out cuz like
they run really fast as well and um so
is is the dumpy
small oh you see I'm a little bit
embarrassed to say but it was flapping
just like the birds in fantasy land it
was going hard up and down I couldn't
take my eyes off of it it was like the
orbs of Z or something okay flapping
dumpy thank you so much that's very
valuable info I guess it just means that
the other person's dumpy is like way too
big
that they say small yeah like somebody
because they ran too fast it looked like
it was flat oh maybe could be could be
could be and U okay this is another
conflicting information one more thing I
need to confirm from you do they have do
they have pants or no pants or
skirt oh dear you see um they were
running with pants but it was very tight
pants it looked like they had you know
one of those Bulls skins it was kind of
like the blue but dark but Navy and it
was shining and that's why they're dumpy
was all over the place oh okay shiny PL
pants dumpy all I'm I'm taking all this
no dumpy all over the
place okay well so far you've been
providing me very good information um is
it possible for us to cont uh to trade
contacts like so for example I can ask
you some stuff and maybe if you have
more info you can yeah oh yes I would
love your contact and if possible your
social security number as well but only
if you join us through the fantasy girly
poop uh Dreamland that we have if you
can just sign right here oh um I I need
to just sign right here yes and then
you'll be a part of us Dem manic fairy
pixie girlies it's um it's it's safer
over there than this neighborhood right
of course we we only talk about fairies
and dreams and
fantasy okay well I guess I could sign
over
[Music]
here okay and what's next and what's
next is that now you're a part of us
I'll be reporting to the Head fairy
queen then thank you so much for your
cooperation oh you're welcome if you
have any info about my cake okay bye-bye
I'll call you
[Music]
byebye I wonder if I made the right
decision I wonder if we made the right
decision I'm a little bit
worried but I think we'll be
fine but I think will be fine well it's
tough okay it's it's tough living here
like when you got somebody warning you
of like suspicious people and it's like
moving here moving to this fairy manic
Dreamland just seem to be the solution
to it all you
[Music]
know yeah so um I guess I guess I I I
trust my own judgment I trust my own
judgement but I think
um I think I think we can I think we can
start sketching out what this is um hold
[Music]
on Blue shiny dumpy over the
okay neither short
or neither short
or neither short or sorry so I'm just
going
to NE are short or I don't
know so I'm just going to draw like oh I
never asked about boas oh flapping okay
maybe flapping the dumpy is flapping
that it seems well maybe we can we can
fix the we can fix the thingy later so
maybe let's just um try to draw get
something first okay
so shiny floppy dumpy what's what's
first first we do have a what the hell
is a parallelogram
[Music]
Vibe the heck is a parallelogram
Vibe
H small and big
so maybe ah I think I know maybe
parallelogram okay okay innocent and
kusogaki
face innocent and kusogaki
face so
[Music]
maybe innocent and kusui face
Maybe M well maybe we can yeah okay
innocent and kusui face um black tank
top okay I don't know if it's like white
and gold or black and blue jeans
okay yeah so let me just um see first
maybe they're running away at an angle
okay sure sure sure sure sure
sure
um maybe it okay this this looks like a
pretty pretty good black tank top so
maybe like just just like a plain black
tank top I would
think like this like a plain black tank
top
right a gold
[Music]
necklace yes yes yes so black and then
shiny
dumpy well they said it's like really
tight really tight Navy blue dumpy oh
not dumpy sorry pants I
guess I don't know why people here
really like to wear like really tight
pants or
something wa this
is please these are pants let let me
shade
it
[Music]
okay okay m
okay and
[Music]
then
um what else hair above their eyes oh
come on long hair I forgot to ask if
it's like straight hair or not wait let
me let me see if I can ask
somebody wait wait
[Music]
wait
wait okay
well we we at least we can we can
probably oh [\h__\h] we can probably ask
more people later what what what does
the GL gold necklace look
[Music]
like gold necklace what do they
generally look like well maybe it's um
just like this maybe just like a simple
one just like a simple one
maybe maybe something like this m
okay
okay they didn't say nobody said she was
wearing any jewelry so I just assumed
that maybe she the culprit wasn't
wearing any
jewelry H so yeah I'm not
sure they neither taller shorts so I
know
okay the dumpy is covered at the back
yeah maybe just something like this all
right and long
hair hair above their eyes aren't they
just called their
eyebrows aren't they just called
[Music]
eyebrows but they do have uh okay they
said innocent looking but they also got
like cream and crumbs on her
face so maybe we
can do a little bit something like this
[Music]
this
yeah
[Music]
okay do they have bangs
or it
isn't it isn't as mysterious to just say
ibrow oh come
on need need the big
feet long hair though what what kind of
long hair what kind of long hair I feel
like well I need some I need one person
to I need one person to ask if like what
kind of hair
um is there somebody I can ask I oh man
somebody can bring a cake box well I
don't think I need to draw that because
that doesn't
really paral okay no no no no make the
gold necklace
[Music]
parallelogram the next glasses
parallelogram
[Music]
okay nice they're a fat
math if they are innocent that means
they have to have like not Angry Eyes
but maybe I I'll add the eyebrows after
I uh after I draw the hair okay well let
me let me add like a separate okay guys
guys guys guys you guys have been doing
your job right right you guys have been
asking around right now it's time for me
to ask
you what's the long hair look like bangs
or BL or what I'm going to I'm just
going to pick up a random a random tip
from you guys I think she had a big
chest and dumpy like a
parallelogram in a way look at this
parallelogram bangs soup bangs half
bangs half blood
she was wearing a wig I don't
care okay straight bangs wait I guess
wait hold on a little bit of meta talk
but last time we did someone with curly
hair so maybe we can do bangs this
time sorry someone with wavy
hair he make cut or
[Music]
swop M bald on the
top can do he make cut
today um so just like he bangs or like
straight up he
[Music]
cut you know what we can do he cut it's
been so long since I've um
drawn somebody with he
[Music]
cut just that reminds me of somebody but
I don't
[Music]
know okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah and then what else
um white gold BL same person who stole
ah shoulder bag shoulder bag shoulder
bag shoulder
bag is this a shoulder bag shoulder bag
is like a messenger bag
right I forgot
[Music]
right right like a shoulder up there let
me actually look it up what's a shoulder
bag what's a shoulder
bag okay okay shoulder bag okay shoulder
bag looks like this okay okay okay I
mean it can be a messenger bag but um I
looked it up and it's more of a this
kind of
[Music]
bag some more of uh this kind of
bag there we
[Music]
go something like
this okay
so this kind of bag let me just uh fix
it a little bit okay so yeah something
like
this she was using something like this
okay
cool maybe um let me just use my
artistic Liberty to draw a
bracelet I don't know man hold
on okay there we
go hold on this is this really bothers
me this hold
on this really bothers me can we where
there we go can we just draw this
normally I don't I don't I don't really
want to draw jeans that are too
[Laughter]
tight there we go at least it can be
tight if you want it to be just okay
there we go
[Laughter]
this this is tight this is
tight okay fine we we we'll get the best
of both worlds there we
go there I think this is
proper is she single I don't know but
she stole my cake that's that's that's
what matters
right I don't think we're supposed to be
asking her if she's
single you know
[Music]
yeah yeah some okay well okay
cool all right let's freaking
go um then what else what else what else
other info are we looking
[Music]
for is she a single mom I don't think so
I don't think this person looks like a
mom same person so say no pants yes
pants cross s smaller
dumpy hair might be tied
so I don't
know here might be TI well let's add
no okay maybe the less is more okay
um um okay and then what
else at least um there's color so like
the color of this one is like Navy
something like Navy but like really
tight pants or something right oh my
God yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah there we go so it's like kind of N
na Navy like this
right Navy like
this yeah and then it's like shiny you
know it's like shiny so um
[Music]
yeah
something oh my God hold
on okay something like that
[Music]
shiny maybe it looks like that from
lighting when it reflects light I don't
know
[Music]
man and
black and black tank top okay black tank
top huh so like this it's just straight
up like this I guess so I guess this is
it
mhm and then gold necklace gold necklace
um how gold necklace like this
right is like this okay gold
necklace something like this there we
go this is a practical outfit compared
to the other
one the last time the last
culprit wait what color was the shoulder
bag what color was the shoulder
bag what color was the shoulder bag I
have no
[Music]
idea H we didn't have enough information
so let's
um and we didn't even have ask about the
hair
color somehow I just
um depends on the lighting that's that's
a good answer actually the the color
depends on the
[Music]
lighting you know what yeah the color
yeah sure why not the color depends on
the
lighting the color depends on the
lighting
so I'm going
[Music]
to yeah it depends on the lighting
yeah okay
[Music]
sure
um it's like it's one it's one of those
bags you
know it's one of those shiny
[Music]
bags we didn't ask if somebody was color
fly either oh my God no well we we we we
like we we we we we go with what we have
okay we go with what we
have go with what we have okay oh [\h__\h]
okay hold
[Music]
on hold
on okay there we
go I think um
yeah there we go
there we
go
okay what's the eye
color don't forget the big feet Callie
no I don't think please don't like C
imposter please
no oh my
God what's the eye color I need I need I
need somebody I need somebody oh my God
it's closing though it's closing
everybody's everybody's moving away I
don't I should have asked them damn it
but I choose a guilty eye color you
can't say that red yellow red probably
okay what's our you guys remember our
culprit from last time what their eye
color let's let's make it different from
the last one
H
[Music]
okay let's make it different from last
one
red Yi said she looked innocent
okay last time was
brown maybe let's make make let's make
this one have blue eyes
[Music]
then let's make this one have blue eyes
let's make this one have blue
[Music]
eyes I'm like putting too much effort on
this I don't know why hold on
[Music]
okay okay there we go
and oh we
need okay we need
this okay we need
this the
eye
[Music]
I I'm having too much fun with this oh
help me
there we go her eyes do look beautiful
and innocent what do you guys mean she's
guilty she's
[Music]
guilty she is guilty guys do not be
fooled of the
[Music]
guilty looks innocent to me what do you
mean looks innocent
she is she is
guilty she is
[Music]
guilty she is the guiltiest of the
guilty don't be swayed by her innocent
looks she still stole my cake do you
guys forget what we're here for we're
here to see we're here to find the
culprit who stole my
cake you
know come on come on guys don't don't be
sidetracked don't be sidetracked please
I thought we remembered our
objective she may also have a band in
her child I think that was that one's a
little bit
[Music]
different May that one's a little bit
different but I don't
know I'm not
sure but yeah
[Music]
okay and um
well um what what hair
color what hair
color I don't know what hair color your
honor I think she pleads oopsie
daisies
um are you sure it's not you it's not
me hold on well like red do we do we do
red hair guys do we do just we do we do
we do we do it do we do we do we do we
do we just like do red
hair just do red hair cuz it's like the
opposite of blue at the moment I'm just
looking at the opposite
colors
orange
cool like reddish orange yeah you know
what let's do reddish orange
[Music]
what is going
on somebody somebody said this person
has access to my kitchen the thing
is but who is
this you guys know who this
[Music]
is I have no
idea Olivia
it's a little bit more orange though but
I guess you know this might be someone
in Disguise this might not this might
not even be like somebody uh who's they
probably don't even normally look like
this so we don't
know so we don't know
huh so we don't even
know we don't know so sad
[Music]
what is so what are we what are we what
are you doing
here
Sho okay and um yeah I don't
[Music]
know there we go there we go
why can I can I really trust this people
of this
town okay there we
[Music]
go I don't
know huh if you put glasses on her she
looks like
futa oh I I see it I see I see what you
mean um
well so far this is what we
have
um
maybe I don't
know I haven't colored this part of the
hair I
forgot oh there we
[Music]
go okay there we go
we um I have no idea what's going
[Music]
on I don't know why I'm putting so much
effort into
[Music]
this I'm so close to be like should we
clean the sketch
lines I'm so close to be like that
should we clean the should we clean the
sketch
lines oh hold on where where where where
there we
[Music]
go help
please
oh I think um we're supposed to we're
supposed to be catching the culprit but
we're we're a little bit sidetracked
with other stuff at the moment I don't
know what I don't know what came to me
but
okay okay guys okay
okay okay there we go we're following
artistic inspiration exactly that's what
we're doing right now okay hold on I'm
going to I'm going to redo this
one I'm going to redo the um the
thingies the
thingies what is even what are we doing
I don't know what we doing okay the
crumbs
okay it's the crumbs
it's the crumbs and the cream
right
yummy okay there we
[Music]
go
okay
beautiful I don't even
know okay well
um okay this looks right this looks
right didn't even attempt to clean her
face the audacity that's what I'm
saying that's what I'm saying come on
like
what hold on give me a second give me a
[Music]
second there we
go
okay this is the
[Music]
um
okay can't really say much about the
um can't really say much about the
outfit but
yeah the outfit is just like straight
up I don't know straight up a black tank
top nothing to
um nothing
much yeah right here would have been
noticeable I I I know I know but the
fact is that nobody said anything about
hair color is it because I didn't
ask is it because I didn't ask I'm not
sure not sure either man for
real wait this is slightly unrelated but
whole October is coming soon Yi is like
doing it as us usual I'm tempted I know
I can't do every day like religiously or
something but it's just like uh I think
it would be nice to at least be able to
make it to like drawing some of them
some of the stuff maybe so
yeah there we
go look at it we're we're revolving from
the big feet
sketch from the big feet sketch to this
one
make another furry character we can make
this one furry hold on give me a
sec you know don't don't don't threaten
me with a good
[Music]
time I just
might hold on give me a sec uh where's
the where's where's the oh shoot I'm
looking for the sketch line where is it
I think it's somewhere it's it's here
yeah okay
okay there we
go just cleaning it up a little bit you
know so it's a little bit uh more it's
like a little neater I
guess okay like this need see like we
don't really need these like this kind
of like sketchy
lines don't need it we don't need it and
put up these
yeah just just just clean it up just
clean it
up okay there we
go something like this
okay yeah this is way cleaner all right
awesome I want to make this a little bit
um maybe a little bit there maybe a
little bit brighter to make it more blue
at add some saturation oh there we
[Music]
go um all right let's see if we can do
something about
[Music]
this yeah see if we can do something
about this well they did say it's um a
very um shiny
[Music]
thing yeah it's like shiny or something
I'm not really sure what they said they
said it was shiny I have no idea how to
um how to how to how to make that into
a
drawing okay something like
that this in the top too long well
nobody said anything about a mid riff so
I just assume that it's a no nobody said
anything about it so I just assumed
that
okay well I guess um
yeah this this is what it looks like
hold on give me a second there we
go and
um
yeah yeah
like I I I don't know
[Music]
what is going on I don't even
know there we go I think we have um a
pretty good picture of um what might be
our
culprit I hope so I sure hope so I will
cry is this what our Thief looks like a
little bit hopefully so we're closing in
on a suspect
[Music]
this one looks more normal I don't know
where she fits I don't know where she
fits all her you
know
her the cake or the I don't know but um
maybe yeah it's possible that she might
have
stolen uh the little kid's toy to maybe
put it in the shoulder bag right but um
[Music]
yeah sorry this like artistic Liberty
sorry I'm
like sorry my artistic Liberty tingling
even though they didn't say anything
about bracelets and
stuff there we
go oh maybe maybe there's no cake cuz
she ate them all there's no cake cuz she
ate them all come on maybe that's it
yeah there we
go she probably stole the bracelet
too
probably where's the cake in her mouth I
assume okay wait
um there we go oh
[Music]
okay okay then we can put this in front
there we go
okay can put this in
front and have this
[Music]
yeah
yes
okay who is the cake
thief
yeah the cake is part of the dumpy I
guess and I guess we can say who she
stole the
cake she maybe she might she might be
the
culprit she just wants cake who can BL
come
on I guess it's all right she
stole the cake or maybe did she steal
the cake that's that's more appropriate
we we we don't want to
assume
did did
[Music]
is she the cake thief okay yeah is she
the cake
thief that's better that's better it's
just like not very
accusatory I can't
spell is
[Music]
she is she
the is she
the
[Music]
cake
thief or maybe thief in like all
caps is she the cake thief
[Music]
question
mark and so so this uh in this case in
this case we're not like accusing her
accusing her you know we're not accusing
her accusing her okay we're just asking
is she the
[Music]
thief we just asking questions from the
info that we got from
people right
okay
awesome thank you so much and um if
anybody has seen if somebody has seen if
someone wait hold on
if you
see
her
please
contact uh I don't know please call
[Music]
me might
have
okay there we go I don't want to accuse
her for anything else like stealing the
toys and everything but um
yeah what 18
protein well we can yeah I guess for now
we're going to have to let go of the
cake at the moment and I think we just
called the protein guy for cake it's 1
800 cake I
think and we can also eat the cake that
we received in the fridge you think
thank you so
much ah very nice I mean the the thie
the thieving incident itself is not nice
but
yes and now with the new protein and
with the new cake in the fridge we can
hold a birthday party with non-stop
6-hour Banger DJ brain rot
music parallelogram Vibe it's in their
necklace anyways yeah thank thank you so
much guys I really really do appreciate
you coming to my birthday party and with
this member kind of sort of comes to a
close but wait there is more are you
serious there's more for real for real
why yes we do have
something my first announcement is this
taada later on I will be having a cover
ah
premere of if you guys know osino
opening too I'll be singing fatal yeah
it's going to be at 800 p.m. so for
those of you who are very um you know if
you have been wanting to see me sing
lagu Jama now songs of the people these
days then this is your chance also rare
rain in Solo cover because normally I
always do like Duets and stuff like that
but yes thank you so much I appreciate
it it's at 8 p.m. rainy Standard Time so
that'll be like 10 p.m. jst later
tonight thank you so much and my second
announcement would be um on Monday the
ID people I don't know
how you know the ID Holo ID doing an
event Holo ID doing an
[Music]
event Hol ID doing an event on
Monday it's going to be from 11 a.m. to
late in the
night so I will also of course be
participating in that Holo ID X school
days for those who don't know X School
means extracurricular activity my um my
ex school will be at 1100 a.m. so it's
actually the first one so I think a lot
of you guys uh would be you know uh able
to attend it because it's just like yab
time you know just
normal
yeah the starting uh 13 p.m. jst exactly
exactly so that's when my segment starts
and my segment is
actually drum roll please I'm going to
be I'm going to be hold on the logo is
so
big I'm going to
be making I'm going to we are going to
do a stepbystep viewer participation
well by yourself of course we're going
to be doing an OC making Club original
character making Club it's not so much
of a drawing Centric stream but more of
a you know let's do a step by step make
your own OC so even if you can't draw
you can along with us um make a
character you know so we will go step by
step from Universe to blah blah blah
blah blah blah you know so I think it
would be
fun yeah and then I I'm planning to
prepare a hashtag for you to like maybe
like show off your um character if you
guys want to you know like just text
form is okay you know I want to teach
you guys the joy of introduce to you
guys the joy of making original
characters so
yeah so so far these kind of streams
have always been drawing Centric but I
want to be a little bit more I want to
involve you guys and stuff like that so
making an OC I think is not just drawing
it's about like thinking about
background Back stories and blah blah
blah and like uh thinking of the setting
blah blah blah so it's uh anybody can do
it so yes uh logo for OC making club by
Chronicle by the way yeah so thank you
that is the announcement for today Mt is
coming to a close technically the 30th
is tomorrow but tomorrow at school day
so I think uh after fatal that will be
all from me personally but then I guess
on the last day of September I will be
doing OC making Club under Holo idx
school days so uh please do mark your
calendars um I'm still discussing about
when to upload the waiting room but when
it's up it'll be up yeah thank you so
much guys and for now please look
forward to fatal
okay thank you you very much for your
attention and salamas everybody and
bye-bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
bye bye
[Music]