you
[Music]
do
[Applause]
[Music]
you
foreign
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
hmm
good evening
[Music]
i took a tiny nap because i did a lot of
stuff and i was a bit
sleepy and so i took a tiny nap
okay very tiny for my to my standards
we'll have to do a lot of stuff tomorrow
as well
so let me say first of all it's probably
not going to be
such a long time i know i say this every
time
but i really have to um
keep it somewhat short today because um
if i stay up too long i'll uh i'll not
be able to sleep the day
after and i have to wake up early
on the day after so
well tomorrow i also have to do a lot of
stuff but i don't necessarily have to
wake up early
but anyway uh the game sound is very
loud
oh wow really really
there is basically no nothing going on
there
really isn't that is it now
my quite low
uh hello
how is it going everyone
better now
is it better now i turned it down
because in the hands of a collab
everyone was like oh kiara is so [\h__\h]
loud
which is weird because uh since it was
on hatchama's channel she was streaming
and
we did a sound check before the i mean
she did the sound check
she did a sound check before the stream
and said everything's fine and then we
go into the stream and everyone's like
uh
done kiana she's so [\h__\h] loud
um i'm quite confused so i turned it
down anyway but i think that something
um
either she had me too loud independently
or
or disco discord was doing something
weird because it makes no sense that i
was
apparently peaking that much but yeah
well anyway uh i was playing
sakura a little bit off stream i did not
do any story but um i did play
like last time we were we had autumn
and um i wanted to do a little bit of
progress before the stream
so i i i played autumn
and winter and we are now in spring
dunde because i wanted to i don't know
i felt like playing a little bit but
don't worry i did not know why is this
my alarm's still going off why it turned
you up
yeah so i did some stuff
i think we're in spring now and i also
have some new
areas to explore
oh yeah i stopped at where i have to
kill the boss monster for this specific
quest
oh well also i am making my new rice
because
when i opened the game uh
it was kind of like the field was empty
it was
i think right after we got another
harvest
[Music]
and look at this are you proud of me
everyone kept telling me to put in more
fertilizer i was trying really hard to
make it better
look how look how good that looks right
i've been up and really improving my
rice field i've been really serious
about my rice okay i've been taking you
serious
yup so i don't know what did i do uh
before i
quit empty so i probably just fertilized
it and now let's go
fight i think i think we can go fighting
i also have a a new hammer
and we're saving up for a new
sledgehammer as well
and what else do i have i have a i have
a new hat i have a new hat
look see this is uh i had this one
before i have it now i have this one
[Music]
yeah so i also have some new skills
these two are new and i
i don't know that's about ah also i
opened the yeah i opened the hat shop
the weaving hut that's also what i did
off-screen
so this exists now she's making me some
hats and stuff
with that being said i have some
fighting to do
i'm sorry i'm kind of tired so
i'm sorry if i'm not like super super
um super energetic
oh [\h__\h] i should go wait let me go
outside sorry
wait which part am i yeah part one i
don't want to be
i want to start at the last part can i
please
yes we're gonna get right into the fight
okay
[Music]
foreign
what the [\h__\h]
oh my god i think i'm gonna lose the
time i didn't even warm up or anything
so ah
what the hell oh that's like um
those things are exploding
why is she jumping so much too
i don't have natural healing on oh it's
healing a little bit
oh my god
if at least there were no other enemies
are they gonna keep on spawning
yep of course they are
i think this this fight might not end
well he also attacks the bunny stuff
nice tongue though he knows how to use
it too
oh wait i can destroy them and they're
not gonna explode
i just if i leave them here they're
gonna explode
heal me please
they're burning yes burned rabbit very
nice
okay wait no no no no no
no no no okay
i'm still warming
[Music]
wait actually i think if i do it a
little bit smarter next time i can do it
i can do it like he says help so
if i act smarter we should be fine
actually i'm still alive
okay don't use strike weapon what
what you can do it if you barbecue
okay one more time guys frog
frog legs i'm ready for some frog legs
for dinner
stop it [\h__\h] frog i'm gonna send you
to france i think they'll enjoy your
marriage and i do
oh it's kind of burning there wasn't
that burning your ass
at all did that feel good
when your ass is on fire feels good huh
it must feel good otherwise he wouldn't
keep on making these bubbles
heel heel heel slowly recovering
oh god am i recovering
no no
no no no no
resistance against strike attack and
what is the strike attack what exactly
which one which
this one
is this a strike attack or this
change weapons what
[Music]
wait they're both striking
attack one attack okay oh god is that
better like attack 16
slash versus attack 27 strike
go for slash really
strike pure slash magic
okay i didn't realize that there was a
difference there okay and then we go to
slash okay
hey i wonder if i'm gonna do much more
damage now rock weak against like
magin
[Music]
oh yeah let's find again
nice
his tongue very
[Music]
cannot nice with you anymore but am i
doing more damage do you guys know this
more damage am i doing more
stupid money
am i doing more damage maybe yeah
oh it's burning i'd be out of there
am i really doing more damage
[Music]
i don't give up i give up i give up
i give up i give up just kill me
[Music]
stop over committing to death
okay
[Laughter]
oh
is already fat enough you don't need to
cover up the battlefield as well
come come here come here bunny it's not
a bunny
should grab and that's that it's a
[\h__\h] frog
that was bad though
what's proficiency raised to four first
sparrows
kill me kill me
level not high enough
okay try one last time
[Music]
i just gave up yeah
oh [\h__\h]
i hate this
[Music]
why am i flying what why did i why was i
just
levitating what the hell is going on why
was i
what was i
yeah i'm dead
i need to use dashes more
but i changed it to slash to make more
damage what the hell
your level is doable but it's too hard
you can try leveling more i don't have
to play the heart
by the way this is not like um
[Music]
time limited right
no wait wait wait i need to at least
harvest a little bit
[Music]
also i didn't beat this one yet either
should we go in here again i did this
off screen
no time limit okay
just i have to get stronger
[Music]
what i watch you guys did you all buy
the game
i think a lot of people are getting
interested in the game because also a
lot of people started streaming it
also in home alive ina also started
streaming it
uh i think she started yesterday
which i was quite happy about
hello fatty how are you doing
wow that one hit him
lots of people are screaming yeah i
would like to say
[Music]
i was one of the first ones
in her life i was uh one of the two
first people
it was just a matter of you know
scheduling
[Music]
okay hello buddy
can you play mega man series no never
did
i hate those stupid birds so much i hate
them
so so so much with a passion i hate the
birds
one thing that annoys me is they get
like when i uh
kind of stun them i can't even do damage
to them
birds at least not also not even
well still that doesn't mean that i like
all kinds of birds
some of them birds suck
[Music]
some of them just have no manners
are we finally down here i think we are
that it
was there no more to this area i forgot
is that it
i guess that was it i know it goes ah
but i already
got the item that was there but i think
it ends there
every goddamn time i'm really bad with
this uh
spider-man thing ah i missed so closely
as well
oh there we go yeah but there's nothing
here not worth the effort
that's good
how about where did i not but how much
do i have
it's still 75 what am i what am i not
finding that it is only 75
use skills to reach new heights how am i
supposed to do that
[Music]
you need to grab a bird anyway if i
go in again are there are they back
or are they all killed now yep they're
all eliminated or or maybe not wait i
hear something
oh yeah they are here okay then once
again
let's try to reach some new heights you
mean
you mean grab them like like like that
like spiderman
is that the skill that they want me to
use i'm hungry now oh that's okay
yeah hey i tried that though how high do
they want me to go
at the absolute top the absolute top
okay wait i don't need to stupid bunnies
right now
[Music]
i need to find a new height
where's the absolute top do i have to
kill all these goddamn enemies again i
was just in here
okay so this is not the absolute i
suppose
i'm looking for the job again yeah
you need to put enemy in the air and
grab it to swing yourself high i might
need a future
throw the enemy in the air
which skill do i have that does that
wait was it down
oh wait a second was i i was definitely
here before
hello
your birds right now to do something
with you to help me help me out there
i don't want to kill you right now i
want to fly with you
would you allow me to fly with you
okay i know you all are kind of angry at
me for killing your whole family but
can i fly with you
i don't know how go up to the platform
and grab the bird
to the platform
[Music]
this this flap on the right side just
leave me alone
[Music]
when i went pretty high now
the other birds are really stupid
[Music]
oh that bird just bumped me up there is
there something up there that was it no
okay
okay and let me kill them
stupid george these birds are so stupid
so annoying what are you doing down
there
now i have to go up again oh you came
down for me well thank you then you go
down you go up again okay
stay at one point
let me finish up
[Music]
okay
bird where's this bird
i didn't send anyone uh of my team for
harvesting
did it reset my weapons
[Music]
after i died once cause i didn't change
this
after i died i didn't make much damage
still
oh come on why don't you do this to me
why
for what reason why don't you do that
it's so confusing
now i see well
gotta think of changing again
[Music]
so but we reached one goal so that's at
hundred percent now i hope
oh i have a new area to check
not really why is that
grayed out
so that's hundred percent now nice i
barely have anything a hundred percent
a gathering area uh it's probably too
late
ah a gathering spot for sending people
there
[Music]
okay
but i'm really proud of my rice oh my
god there's so many
wheats i'm away for one day and there's
so many wings
there's so many why not
[Music]
let's make some new stuff for the
morning because i read
see i actually uh took some time to read
some stuff in the game
uh while using my brain and it said that
i should fertilize it in the morning
because it
works better if i fertilize it in the
morning so i make my fertilizer before i
go to sleep
and then it will work better
did you know that
oh what else do i put in some yummy
stuff
what does that do no
[Music]
do i have no salt or oh my gosh
the pesticides
[Music]
should i not care about the pesticides i
wonder
oops nothing not that
size immunity
[Music]
is
um i feel like there's much more people
who
can teach me about the game now because
when i started the game out it was it
was just released and there weren't
barely any people who already played it
and now they can all tell me much more
let's see what do we have for dinner
yes that sounds yummy
and have dinner
thank you so
raymond and fighting skill
okay how's the water looking fine
water height is all right and let's put
my
is my fertilizer done
no it's not done yet
if i run it around a little bit it will
be done soon i'm sure
some weeds no
anything here
i wonder if i can make the other weapon
now that i wanted to make
thanks for welcoming the members very
nicely
and which one did i want to make
i'm on strike right now right that's
pure so long
slash
[Music]
ah so i have the open hammer so what i
want from here
is the open space yeah i didn't want to
make that but it's strike but uh
whatever it will be of use
eventually
ah this one
[Music]
this one seems fine actually attack bar
better than the other slash weapon that
i have right
i'll go with that wait did i already
have that
i hope i didn't already have that
let's wear whatever wear
okay okay okay and then so for fighting
that monster we'll use these two things
right
that's it we're going on strike no
you may not i have not allowed it to you
is my this is come on faster i don't
have time
are there any frogs back here yeah quack
i have released the frogs
[Music]
how did you know that there was a
fracture oh what's going on
what is the matter oh no
no it's about you you ain't not listen
what we say
she promised to have moved the housework
again today but she is completely look
look today
what we're speaking of you and yes are
you sure you do not mean kinta
their names are not data-like you know
you are only good friends with you and
quinta
it appears yours no love for us
i admit i find it difficult to believe i
suppose i shall have to speak with her
what what's what's is she in there like
and what you call um those teen years
in english when you are on your like
really rebellish
what's wrong oh she's she's
lurking she's stalking kinta
[Music]
our rebellion states kiara voice acting
chinatown thank you
you're spying on kinta again
oh goddess
i'm keeping once over him to make sure
nothing bad happens
lofty realm above just what do you think
is going to happen
um by the way i had a little cha chat
with
murta and the big o you're afraid to
chase kinder around as you wish but you
must keep your promise
i wanted to watch kento forever but they
wouldn't quit haunting me
so i couldn't say no
why is he determined to ate kinta
he saved my life before he probably
doesn't remember it but
i want to pay him back he saved your
life huh
that is serious but even so
shadowing him like this i'm sorry
i can't tell you any more than that i
told
you that much because you're divine
enough but i didn't want anyone to know
really
what is this school i'm sensing
then i shall not question you any
further for now however
do you not think you would be well
served by opening up to the others
okay that's not the only one you are
living with here
yeah okay
what is what is going on
is my fertilizer done now
is it there now
normally it's like done by now how come
it's not done yet
here you just got it
[Music]
why is it not what can i do like what
can i do while waiting
do a little explore i feel like it's
already gonna be too late i want to do
it like right away when it's done
there we go see it's it's like
it's done it's such a weird timing
yes spreading spread all over it mmm
yummy poop okay
now we can go do we try again
now we have one more stronger weapon
wrong my mouth
sorry
okay i
i hope i have some healing going on as
well
so i have the slash weapons okay all
good
let's go i can do it
[Music]
we do
already starting great
see i can't even hit them when they're
on the ground that kind of sucks
[Music]
almost jumped into the hot
you little stuff they're kind of
bastards i think you're funny or
something
you're not helping out you know you know
the frog wants you to die as well
i can't do it
no don't hit that stupid bubble you're
supposed to hit
the frog
actually the bunnies are kind of useful
for grabbing on to them but they're not
always around they're not always where i
want them
here's the thing he threw against him
i guess i can smash that
[Music]
there's no healing it just heals
automatically whenever i don't fight
[Music]
um
i hate you
oh
can you just [\h__\h] chill for a second
no it's not even moving like i'm not in
the direction i wanted to
oh no it's burning me but foxy
[Music]
wait until your next starts the fight
gets much easier really
wait i got i forgot to send someone out
again
i can send them here
okay where do i go then where do i go
and if we don't need to fight him right
now then
i guess we can use my strike weapons
again
if you complete the harvest it might be
easier i i can send
it until now it was not possible see
cannot dispatch anymore
you can't dispatch anyone else
where should i call 75
00 what do you mean i was there before
get salt get powdered oh okay i mean we
can go there
zero percent maybe we'll get some salt
actually i would like some salt
and no salt there is no salt
[Music]
yeah salt is pretty good also for the
fertilizer
did i get salt no of course not of
course i didn't get it
yeah kelly likes to say that
oh my god tomorrow everyone tomorrow
is my song release hashtag
[Music]
get high quality or maybe we can get
some high quality oak
tomorrow oh i'm already hungry
hungry already
what a quiet
almost bunked myself into death
[Music]
i should have gotten rid of those
let's try to get up here oh
high quality oh there we go we need more
of that more please
there's a lot of challenges over there
but i'm not quite ready for them
i could use some new
[Music]
that's what i'm talking about
spikes man yeah they're really annoying
[Music]
funk that feels good
funk superman
are you guys excited to finally hear the
full version of my song tomorrow
it's uh tomorrow and at this time
in nine minutes 24 hours and nine
minutes
is the song
[Music]
24 hours and eight minutes do we need a
countdown
every minute i'll announce you how much
time there is left
i'm so excited it's gonna be so good
cali is uh i think still working on the
music video so i did not even see a
finished version yet only like some
working practice
i'm not recovering help so i'm oh i
should be careful
but i'll be fine i'll be just fine
coming soon
[Music]
will this be finished three hours before
release date what do you mean the what
do you mean
do you mean the music video
i can't grab onto that anyway hey i
wanna was i ever there before
is there something
hmm
[Music]
i will be fine oh it's getting dark
i want to kill some more before it's
getting dark
whoa no
let me kill you before you get immuno
yes okay okay
[Music]
there was a chance yeah i already have
it yay and we have we have 100
now nice though okay
let's go back home
tactical retreat
by the way one question if i like uh
gather a lot of stuff
and then i die and do i lose that stuff
that i gathered uh
or do i bring everything home that i
gathered
supposedly was a song actually on my
announcement stream i don't know if you
were there
but i did um i did give everyone a sneak
peek of it
i'll lose it for real
it
really i don't
i'm not talking about like game over if
that is even possible in the game
i mean like just dying and respawning i
lose my stuff
are you for real
yeah i revive at the start of the stage
yeah yeah but i lose everything
ah it rewinds to the last checkpoint so
everything i i
i gathered until that checkpoint i keep
right
okay okay okay well then everything's
cool
okay ah let's make some fertilizer
[Music]
to
japanese bros are giving me some advice
on how to make good fertilizer
yeah i need more root more root
like
wait ah now we have um now we have
salt so i can use that oh and garlic
garlic is also really good
yeah see from sixteen to minus minus six
into minus eleven
nicer what else do we wanna add in
me no it's not what do you guys always
add in
the people who actually play the game
not oak
[Music]
24 hours yeah until he no tony oh my god
amber has used by the way i know that
there's a lot of items
that are not necessarily for the
fertilizer
[Music]
oh we didn't get salt that was just my
imagination
come on what's the
vitalizing vitalizing wait is that
healing stuff that i can use uh
on the field on on the battlefield
[Music]
you want to put in some acorn
what does that do oh it doesn't do much
but i have a bunch okay maybe
[Music]
time for some dinner
i'd like to continue the story as well
but i think i have to kill that
uh mob uh in order to
there's a spider never saw that before
i think i have to kill that big uh
quack
and do until uh
until the starting point goes on um
what
[Music]
nice oh let's go for this one
natural healing is that too
we have no main dishes oh
we have some desserts right now nice
okay that's a good
if that's not a good dinner then i don't
know
just make it ulti what
do you think this is good enough to
fight the boss
maybe i have a cup of tea in the real
life too that's actually such a good
idea
like i should probably but i don't have
a
i don't have a cup here right now
but yeah i'll drink some water
should we try again to kill the frog
should we try again because at least we
have a
swift recovery as well whatever that is
[Music]
well we just continue taking care of our
rice
i mean we can try right we can try what
else can we do
how's the water level
so i also realized uh something that i
read
what i love 41 huh is that
because um you're supposed to have the
water slightly lower
and when when the rice is smaller than
when it is bigger
i thought i hope i wonder if 31 is all
right
oh already done okay
why is this going down what am i doing
wrong now
tell me
apparently i should wait trying it out
right now might be good
but in general 31 is good oh okay
if 10 water should be okay what
ask talent okay
i want to talk about the rice
fertilizer goes down over time
i have found a new farmer's market
which one is new you should probably
tell me which one
watering two rice remedies to cure a
rice disorder one must first know what
is causing it reptile
revitalizing remedies help weaken rice
is my rest weakened right now
reducing remedies curb excess
eradicating remedies helped
get rid of pests and eradicate mold corp
i don't think i have a problem with that
right now
but what about the water where is the
water stuff
watering i wanted to the amount of water
affects its temperature shallow
water will quickly match it quickly
match the air temperature
while deep or flowing water retains its
water temperature extreme heat or cold
damage is rising one level must be
adjusted in turn
[Music]
i don't know man i don't know what i
learned from that
29 no what temperature low should it be
[Music]
higher
it's very cold so flowing water would be
good oh really
flowing water like should i actually
like you mean should i actually keep it
flowing
should i keep it flowing is that a thing
[Music]
you know very low wait
that's not good it's like freezing
my rice is freezing
wait this is bad ryan
i know it's going up okay
[Music]
very low water level oh one level is
like
so
it's at zero percent now we're trying it
out what are we gonna weigh them
average there we go but this is gonna go
is it gonna go down again
high average there we go okay okay okay
[Music]
how about now it's low again
in average average there we go
i don't even like that it's average now
it seems uh like it's staying that way
[Music]
low temperature is fine high too the bad
ones are very low and very high okay
we need
[Music]
okay 21 percent
keep it on average okay okay
oh there's a bunch of snails
yummy did you guys watch the
collab i did with hataman kelly today
did you watch it everyone
yeah you did thank you thank you thank
you
that game um i i like that game but
it whenever i play the game i i really
have to focus on playing the game
thank you for the super chat you will
miss the song live
what what
no when are you gonna watch it
but yeah because i have because i have
to focus so much on the game
because it's like so much going on i i
can't really talk much
[Music]
hey thank you jacobs monkey
the help someone from australia is
calling me
you [\h__\h] stupid why i
am not in australia right now why do
people like is it it's like
even a number that i don't even know
sometimes though like sometimes some
really random countries
call me and that's kind of like
suspicious
huh is calling hatama wants to talk
about her contract at kfp
yes let's go fight
can't wait for the song thank you
[Music]
i hope you will all like it i hope
i'm very excited for the song release
so excited okay go let's go again
is there anything else i can improve i
wonder
[Music]
okay let's see if we still fail after we
have all these uh
additional healing
hey is it summer it's summer
i'm an idol stop sticking your
disgusting tongue into my face
do you know who i am
disgusting what i went all the way up
there huh
wait i'm doing actually pretty good come
[Music]
on
disgusting tongue attack you uh
[Music]
oh
okay we're doing better but we're still
going bad
come on give me hp come on come on
hp hp come on come on come on
[\h__\h] up ain't got no time for you
you
please oh
no there's nothing running there i can't
go there
this is not working am i still healing
no
did i use up all my oh my okay
[Applause]
my stomach is scrolling so fast
you want more cover health and i need
food effects will
high ass looking eye that was so fast i
didn't get to do anything
and i was doing well right
why
[Music]
by the way i wonder if i have better
chances at this point
right now on the booking
do it again yeah but i'm not recovering
anymore
from before i died oh wait wait wait
wait is it reset because i died so i'm
recovering now
[Music]
oh that doesn't count see i guess oh
because it's also
the day again even though it turned to
night time
okay oh my god i'm getting better at
this
i have to be more careful
here while i can
oh i think it's that slime that kind of
made me levitate
oh we're full health now nice okay
okay so much
[Music]
we're staying calm right we're trying to
keep our distance
oh he almost got me with his tongue
again not this time buddy disgusting
it's just disgusting didn't even brush
your [\h__\h] teeth
you're not gonna touch an idol with that
mouth my friend
you
come on come on kill me
oh not now buddy
stomach is really okay we won't recover
anymore yeah bye
morning
you got me again
okay i'm gonna die i'm gonna
[Music]
why did you not hit that bunny right now
why why why why what
damn bad timing
and i'm back and bye bye
yup just kill me now just kill me
already
just kill me
[Music]
do you think we should try again
i gotta play spider-man more often that
did go quite well
[Music]
people say i'm the top i'm not sure
about that but people do say that
so i think if anything you're gonna be
the bottom my friend
how about i jump on you for one time
for a change you know
you don't seem like a good top
honestly you're not doing a good job at
that especially right now
you're quite bad at this
[Music]
okay probably not healing right you know
maybe maybe over there
[Music]
how dare you touch me with that dog
again
[Music]
i got the bonnie
seems like they don't want to hear me
right now
we got this picture the bunnies are
sabotaging though
let me do it
because he always likes like when he
jumps towards me
and i jump away he likes to um
afterwards
jump on top of me and it's oh yeah
i need a healing now please
i can't find a quiet moment to heal
myself
it's busy amazing
what is that noise is that my my ghost
again
i think we're going home to i think
we're going home
level 8 is too low ah but why does it
give me the option to kill him then
i'm on the level oh man wait is the
level
how does the level go up
how how does the level go up is it by
story
does the story give me
a higher level by right oh really
oh okay well in that case
let's see if we still have something to
okay here for example get iron ore okay
let's get some iron ore
so we have hundred percent here as well
oh wait i can't that's right i cannot
destroy that
[Music]
oh hello bunny
never waste a day always explore every
day
make the best out of each day and get
some iron ore
can i go up there
hello
the better the rise the higher the level
remember
whoa
but still i should like i should plant
all the rice i
all the seeds i have you know
and oops as long as we have space for
them
[Music]
people still people still make fun of me
the way i say iron you guys have no idea
i'm from australia okay
come on give me iron ore come on
i'm here for the iron this is exactly
how i was saying you have no idea i got
the best braid in school in english
always okay
everyone in class was copying my
homework
and that's all the iron i was able to
get
is there no water source
oh and i'm hungry again once again
i don't want to die huh
and they're all dead but i want more
iron
i didn't get it
was there no other spots did i miss
anything
if i say it's iron then you desire it
exactly well that was it
i couldn't get it to hundred percent
percent hundred percent
oh we can try to get some some of that
uh
here was it here defeat with skipping
stone
[Music]
what
that's what that's what they want to
want me to do here okay i can do it
[Music]
let's defeat some stuff with the stone
[\h__\h]
did that count
that works quite well
i laughed too early come on let me up
there
hold on hold on
[Music]
i want up there thank you
okay get some of this nice materials
root crops nice by the way um
yesterday was the first time
since i moved into my new house that i
actually cooked something i met
i met i made pancakes you're proud of me
the reason why i didn't cook until now
well it hasn't been that long since i
moved but
um the reason was kind of i didn't want
to use the gas stove because i was too
scared of it and i'm still too scared of
it i just used like a separate
uh like a heating plate
that is not gas what is it called ibih
what was it
not sharing questionable questions
excuse me you were not there
induction yeah probably something like
that
i bought that separately because i don't
want to use
oh they're already dead i'm too strong
for them let me bonk you
monk okay one more come on come here
little buddy
let's play golf oops that didn't kill
him
one more come on
[Music]
nice one it's getting dark now [\h__\h]
actually this is quite funny
come on and make it easy for you oh it's
getting dark oh [\h__\h]
this is nice i like gold
bye-bye are we done now
who's still alive
did i never open it up
wait a second how did i get there
oh family hi yeah it's really beautiful
right oh my god shit's too
late hey did i never open that huh
because it's there are we 100 now though
14 out of 15. but there's a secret
kelly thank you for watching by the way
this game is like really nice
it's so chill and it's like really like
um
the process of making rice in this game
is so realistic you have no idea
and when it's night you you don't even
realize how beautiful the game is it's
so beautiful but
it's even more beautiful when it's
daytime but
this is even prettier when the sunset or
the sun rises
well let's see gotta pull some weeds
and make some fertilizer for tomorrow
[Music]
bamboo bamboo
maybe some sedge maybe some cork tree
branch
[Music]
maybe some acorn maybe some
bean what does that do the bean doesn't
do anything
what
okay there we go
cali is probably working on my video
right now
how's it going kelly if you're still
watching maybe she already
already disappeared how's it going
take your time though really it can be
super kitty guinea i don't mind as long
as you don't stress yourself
i'm her background sound i wonder
i think she just came by to say hi for a
moment
hey my rice is looking so fluffy wow
it's it's under 24 hours now
i wanted to do i wanted to do something
like a 24-hour tweet god damn it
i wanted to do it can i tweet something
now
i want to tweet something
[Music]
let me tweet something
20 24 hours
[Music]
24 hours left are you
are you excited
hope 24 hours left
until song and music
[Music]
okay and then i add a picture one second
i gotta do some business okay i'm a
woman after a while
do i have the oh yeah i don't have to
check
but maybe we use the promotional one
which one should i use should i use the
square one
or should i use
i'll use the promotional one
there we go
oh wait i just saw something on twitter
[Music]
wait a second my twitter just refreshed
and i saw a fan art
that miso did of me and piccolo one
minute
ago one minute literally just posted it
i'm gonna retweet that
later i think but wait that's so cute
that's so cute wait wait wait wait wait
wait i wanna
link it to you guys
[Music]
let's go check that out and that's so
cute
oh my god we're wearing each other's
clothes
wait a second
check this out everyone we did an old
outfit swap that's so cute
kiara is looking at this right now in
stream lol
already commenting already commenting
you guys are too fast
okay so my back to my tweet oh anything
else i need to write
no
[Music]
i guess it's okay it's simple enough
to remind everyone releases soon okay
everyone go to my twitter now and uh
give it
uh a height
to the net i need to
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh wait but it was already night
anyway right
once it's night time doesn't really pass
right it doesn't just
turn into the morning does it i at least
never noticed such a thing before
what it can go to the next day oh god oh
god oh god
oh god okay we're fine we'll find still
wait i did make the fertilizer right
okay
[Music]
oh we can make tea but first let me get
the natto
and the tea okay
have dinner itadakimasu
[Music]
eat the documents
okay they still want me to investigate
before wait a second why does it still
want me to do that
because of the because of the frog oh
yeah yeah
because of the frog
oh nice summer is so nice i mean look at
that
scenery wow
it's so purple
[Music]
what if i fall down i fell down
somewhere
uh else before because i thought there
would be an invisible wall but there
wasn't
you just i wonder if i can fall down
here too
probably i can oh can i go down here
what is down there
[Music]
i can really fall down there oh
it's time to harness okay i'm coming
back wait is that the right direction
that's a wrong direction right wait i
got too excited i just jumped down and
i'm ready to
i'm ready to harvest wait is it uh
when it says it's uh ready to harvest
does it mean i can harvest but i maybe
not necessarily have to
[Music]
or should i just do it right away wait
really
because one thing i noticed uh off
stream
when i did the the detailing thailand
tilling
that um just because it says i can
already
stop it doesn't mean that i should stop
i did it up to 100
even oh wait tonight
[Music]
the crabs will be frozen wait better
wait for all them
what
that's so interesting i can i should
wait okay now keep on fertilizing it and
not harvest right away
whoa all them get better
what you guys are so so
informed eh you really know how to play
the games
[Music]
better wait okay i mean i'm kind of
eager to get the next harvest because
then i would uh get a higher level and
can finally beat that
[\h__\h] frog just beat the [\h__\h] out of
him how dare he touch me anyway
how dare he touch me
[Music]
you want me to speak in german or
possibly
french whatever
wait which language is the one that you
choose
okay what else done am i done here i'm
not gonna harvest i just want to see if
there's some wheat
no okay let's go explore
in italian
[Music]
um
okay that actually was quite some text
i did speak quite a lot then and it
actually made sense
okay but not in this context
wait should i keep the water though
should i keep the water in the farm
or should i drain it where did i want to
go
it made sense yeah but it was a
completely random
stuff that i uh remembered from school
how many languages can you speak okay
and the stuff that i said in italian i
mean i studied italian in school oops
that was the wrong skill
but i don't i really don't remember much
did that count as stuffed
by stone did that count
ouch that counted hell yeah
i don't think i need the rest of you but
i'll get some of that stone
get the secret item myself yeah where
was that again
[Music]
where was that it takes time to risk
phone
john you know so much about this game
i'm so glad you're here
question
i'm gonna i don't want to talk to you
right now
we don't talk anymore wait was it here
we don't talk anymore
wait i forgot how to do the spider thing
for a second we don't talk anymore
[Music]
we don't talk anymore what was that
before
[Music]
shut up
copyright copyright don't worry i don't
get striked that easily
we got it
[Music]
feel my aggression over that item not
being so special
feel it
don't jinx yourself famous last words
this didn't age well
thanks kiara said that didn't age well
one day i want to see a compilation like
that
next it it's on you now your job
you don't have to do it right away
i don't think there's enough content to
make such a video just yet
[Music]
how many moms is it what are you going
to call your child
huh huh what are you gonna call it you
should call it sakona
because because i am
i forgot the word i forgot the word i
wanted to say something fancy but i
forgot
because i'm dominating you
or because the child possibly
was made by me is there something there
i think we can leave
are we at 100 now
yes okay zero percent okay whatever
what's here defeat enemies at night okay
so one question for the people who are
the pro-rice farmers at this game
how the hell do i defeat enemies at
night
because from what i've experienced they
don't take damage at all
or they recover like really really
really
much do i just have to get much much
stronger
you have to be stronger than them
can i do it now i want this
the night strength is only seven higher
level you can do
okay but am i too weak now
i wonder
[Music]
welcome to the membership
okay so i guess fighting enemies
in the night is not really a thing now
gotcha i got you
oh nice crack
[Music]
revitalizing remedy again nice
and it's not night already i didn't send
anyone
together maybe i can still do nope okay
too late
i'm back home
oh you didn't hear that again
at least twice the recommended level
what okay
okay
oh there's no water in here uh
[Music]
uh it's very low too
hey should i drain it it's night now so
of course it's gonna be a little bit
lower than usual but
should i add some water yeah bye
no
[Music]
add water no water i'm in the toilet
no water add water which one
keep it at 20 percent
don't fertilize it
what
more water add water less water
eh
[Music]
ah boneless water okay
well i mean fertilizer can't make it
worse
[Music]
right
it's not gonna make any worse
oh we have wheat garlic
[Music]
or can it it won't have any effect okay
we'll just keep it until next time then
in this stage it has no effect
cooked water
you guys confused me a little bit it's a
20 let's just keep it that way
who knew how to put garlic on water
are you not one of those people who
appreciate the garlic lifestyle
everything tastes better with garlic
[Music]
do you not know of that
holy grail uneducated don't absorb
fertilizer okay i trust your words
everything you say seems very legit jose
i will follow whatever you say i will
follow you
[Music]
why it was it was looking so good at the
beginning of the stream it was like
almost
completely blue how do we improve it
right now the fertilizer doesn't do
anything so
how's the water looking hi
okay which means we can put in some
water
it's fine no it's not i want the perfect
rice
[Music]
is it cooling down no it's still not
cooling down damn
should we let it flow
time to harvest oh yeah it's autumn it's
autumn
wait do i drain it first i forgot it has
been a while
so i drained it before i harvested maybe
we should cool it down a little bit more
[Music]
drain it that hard okay okay time for
harris i didn't realize it was already
autumn
oh akika
[Music]
it is closed it literally sounds close
over there
[Music]
okay okay there we go start harvesting
yay
start here
reap what sorry wait what
[Music]
okay i haven't done this in a while but
this is pretty fast okay we can do it
we can do it
[Music]
making some new races
oh my god why did i press that
[Music]
i don't want to let him do it i think
he'll be very clumsy and
roll over my rice field
i need it before it's even done
this makes me a reaper yes you have the
same weapon as cali does
i always wanted to say i always
i always wanted to be a reaper seems
like such a fun job
i want to like try her job for a day i
want to be a reaper too
sounds like exciting also
[Music]
oh
it's a sickle excuse me this is a scythe
okay just like the one cali has it's not
a sickle
it's the size okay i'm reaping i'm
reaping cells here
don't ruin it for me i'm living the
dream right now
[Music]
everything
let it dry let it dry
can't eat it yet gotta try
let it dry let it try
put it all up there and try
the next day for sure it will be
dry enough
looking forward to my rice
next step oh it's already night damn
what a long day and you didn't even you
were
only watching why are you only watching
damn okay
i guess so it's too late to go outside
now
is it too late to do anything wait can i
is she is julie still awake i think i
can i have enough hem
maybe for for whatever she makes
no she's gone why is the baby outside
then
you told him he wasn't fat because he
didn't let him work
wait am i supposed to let him work oh
see the baby is gone okay
just because i went inside
oh let's have dinner okay
[Music]
okay hello i have no ingredients
we have food we have something
else oh god we're running out of food
it's okay
that's all we have for tonight
eat some food before processing oh
is that a thing
cook what
winter's coming yes winter has been
coming for years now
drying rack drying and still not dried
oh no the white walkers
man i i really liked um
that serious but i
got into it way too late i got into it
at the i think this
almost the last season should we go
exploring
[Music]
and then i watch you know
did i watched it all i binge watched it
all
in like one week
yes hello
should i go exploring
yeah i know everyone says they messed up
in the end and yeah it was um
not the best end definitely
where do we go seventy-five percent
oh wait that's the ninth one oh let's
send
let's send someone by the way
let's send her here yeah
you take my
75 get iron oh yeah i still want that
iron ore
me that iron i'm back again i will never
give up until i get that iron
i will not sleep until i get
what i deserve when i came for it
[Music]
is there any special way to get it or
it's supposed to be from those stones
right or from the island i think it's
from the stones
on the wall and it's just a lucky thing
i think
it's just rng
it's random seems to be pretty rare
i what know they doing
these enemies are pretty stupid i mean
they look stupid as well so it seems
pretty in character
that they're they don't seem to have
much of a brain
is there any iron here
[Music]
it took me a long time finally to get
iron really
damn
okay i bunked myself against it
[Music]
it was not necessary it hurt
how did that not destroy that stone he's
so fat
actually the weight should have done it
iron rare drop mmm please come on please
my last chance no of course not
much
[Music]
i think that's that was all the spots
that i could check out
i think that was it out
this is enough this is okay
100 100
hundred percent zero percent
what was there again
what what am i
[Music]
missing out here ah can't clear dragon
for long
ah okay okay
i can't really do much well
[Music]
i'll go here just for fun
watch me watch watch
[Music]
in 23 hours
and 6 minutes
oh my god 23 hours guys
24 hours
the top the clock is ticking my friends
time is ticking
are you guys gonna listen to it like
every day
you better it's our ritual you better
watch it on youtube everything
my dream is that the music video gets 1
million views
that's my dream
i wonder if i can do it one million
views
i think all of kelly's uh music videos
reached
at least one million and r.i.p is at 7
million now i think
which is pretty amazing 7 million views
but she also reached out 1 million quite
early i think
let's
by the way did you guys see i released
um
was it yesterday or today i think
yesterday yesterday i
oh my god yesterday i released one
members only stream
to the public and i think many of you
didn't even notice
but if you have time maybe you can watch
it
if you're not a member and you didn't
see it yet
i did it for you guys for the
non-members
yesterday was also only a member's only
stream
and i was like i feel like maybe i could
publish
that one now so they have something to
watch the non-members
you're welcome hope you enjoyed it
or enjoyed it already uh
the thing is uh this is the only german
lesson that i'm going to be publishing
the only one
no
okay i think we're done
advertisement level chiata
go here as well before it gets super
dark
didn't get a notification really what
i noticed that like
probably barely anyone saw it
i did oh yeah i noticed everyone on
twitter
thank you for the membership welcome
[Music]
okay now back home
it's dangerous outside when it's dark
oh sorry i had to do and i crack
backhoe
and also by the way i'm not sure i mean
the the german lesson thing
eventually after a few lessons
maybe after 10 lessons or something i
will have to stop it because
i'm not a teacher i i don't think i can
get like into super super detail you
know
[Music]
i i don't i mean i don't want to teach
you like really detailed grammar
like i would have to do a lot of
research myself on that and it would get
so
serious it would at one point i think it
will just get too serious
so i think after a certain point the
german lessons will be done
maybe i'll start teaching you some basic
japanese instead
[Music]
teach german means i don't know german
means
teach german yeah but still at some
point like it's just
nothing more i can teach you
so you guys tell me to not process
ingredients
i should eat first and then process
sakinito
[Music]
is that why i can never make dinner
because dinner needs not dried stuff
though you can do it either way
oh no
ah
eat don't sleep and then force it okay
interesting
roast eyes the difference between roast
rabbit meat and dried rabbit meat which
one is better
but the dry one gives me natural healing
[Music]
hmm
polishing rice i mean i guess i can do
that right now right because i don't
have rice just yet
uh okay get back to work
go back inside process the food
[Music]
okay and now
i mean i guess we can sleep now
okay ah
should i check if the rice is dry okay
okay okay
let's see drying so i suppose it's not
dry
it looks pretty dark okay
let's do it yes
prices have been moved to the store okay
let's work let's let's get some work
done
or do we do it tomorrow do we do it now
joycon drift
[Music]
wait where's the difference
okay
[Music]
gotta go fast gotta go rest fresh that
rice
fresh rice gotta go fist gotta cool fast
fresh rice fresh rice
i wonder if there's a faster way to do
this i'm just like uh circulating
the joy-con and pushing y whenever
[Music]
is playing this game as well now i
wonder if she's already doing better
than me
kiana 3dw making rice oh yeah
i'm in let's do it okay i'm excited
exhausted i'm exhausted
later in the game there's a better too
oh
[Music]
my god
should we do everything right now
[Music]
i'm gonna do it until the end though i'm
gonna get the perfectly white rice
pull haul it completely
[Music]
is this gonna be improved as well at
some point and do i always have to do
just a mask though
men what i do
i don't think i can make mochi right now
in this process no no no
[Music]
it will be improved really hopefully
fast because my hand
can't put up with this for that long
sixty percent seventy percent is fine
uh-uh i'm going for a hundred percent
i'm going for a hundred percent
come on come on
bye bye thanks for coming to the stream
[Music]
there we go they did it
new rides complete that's my first ride
[Music]
excuse me in my team
she said it was not so good
[Music]
it's not it's not that much better i
mean
i know is that okay
that some improvement i wanted more
improvements
[Music]
level 12 yeah i went from 8 to level 12.
is that okay
maybe you play better off screen
maybe
it's a percentage right it's a
tremendous improvement really
looks like a lot really
good
13 rice and free rice bran
is that much i feel like we'll eat that
like in one day
because this dude eats so much
you need to go on a diet
okay but now we can fertilize it again
right
now we can start fertilizing or
or not wait do i wait until winter is
over
actually i forgot
not yet
[Music]
poor talent i'm sorry
wait till winter is over okay
that makes sense
but now okay i have no effect
so i think tomorrow we'll try to
tomorrow
in game tomorrow we'll try to get to the
frog again because now we're at high we
are at higher level
okay then i think let's just get some
ingredients
[Music]
and quickly
time for a rant yeah tomorrow tomorrow
in game tomorrow
where do i go
no i should try to get the iron
i want the iron i will not give up until
i get my [\h__\h] iron
where is where is it here yep
give me my iron
give me my iron please
by the way guys do you mind if i don't
read super chats today my throat feels
um very
rough
but i'm kind of scared because i i mean
oh wait there's
i can't get anything tonight
it's okay okay thank you
thank you but i i have a
feeling that tomorrow we might get
a lot of super chat so i'll have to do a
lot of
catching up
that's a probably gonna be
a separate super time reading stream
possibly i'm not sure if i
if i'm gonna do it yeah pro
because i have to get up early for the
peculiar stream right so tomorrow the
celebration stream
if i start reading super chat then i'll
be up
so long because for me the celebration
stream starts at
um 11 p.m
and the celebration i'll say it will
take like one hour
and if i read super jets then it's gonna
be from midnight to like
i don't know 3 a.m or something
but i have to get up at 10 am or
something
and even if i stream until 3 a.m doesn't
mean that i can sleep right away
okay so no super jets today no super
chats tomorrow
oh ooh that's going to be a lot of
catching up
i have no stream planned on sunday
because i have to do some stuff on
sunday
but oh wait maybe it since on
on saturday saturday oh wait we have a
stream
on saturday so even on first day
in the night because on first i only
have the peculiar stream
in noon time for me noon time but maybe
in the night time we can do a super
challenge okay
i teach logic and philosophy and every
day
teach about god every day
i don't wanna
please understand this stuff very
important
and we don't need your shooting
schooling
why don't you try learning to speak jana
out the right first
can we go now
be quiet
we will always understand thank you so
sweet
oh sorry i saw something
murder most assured he has your own
ideas in mind for wraggling the children
let us wait and see for a while before
landing a helping hand
if you say something
i haven't done his voice in a while it
seems that everyone
on this island has their own unique
mountains to climb
along with mining
these are these uh spider lilies i think
this is the first time i'm reacting to
those
channels
[Music]
we have rice okay okay now
we eat rice now
and then tomorrow overstuffed too is
that bad
is that bad
i should probably go for this one
does it tell me how much rice it uses
overstuffed is good
oh it's good ah too much rice five fried
rice down okay let's go for
oh no wait four red rice
ah five white rice four red red
[Music]
okay let's go for this one though
ah display buff yeah but what does the
what does that do the overshaft what
does that do
probably won't say this but your videos
make me happy so thank you for
everything you do thank you too i'm glad
you enjoyed them
hold one for detail
[Music]
i'm holding it ah there we go
not that one
[Music]
it doesn't okay
we decrease his hunger rate by ten
percent oh
okay i mean we can do it one time
can we do a main dish oh that was the
main dish
okay the rest looks all right
can we do tea as well no all right
have dinner wait i want to press it
oh actually
we can make so many things
make some pick-up stuff
should i always uh completely process at
least before i sleep
even if i don't do it now
yeah my my room feels um
very um like it's drying out my throat
right now that's why i'm coughing so
much
i'm hydrated i'm drinking but my my
throat feels so dry
process before sleep always
[Music]
press the sun because they were spoiled
but don't process all
so i want to keep some rice as well some
of that white rice
okay let's have dinner
i have a humidifier a huge one i have a
200 humidifier
next to me but it doesn't
do much to be honest i don't know maybe
i have the settings wrong or something
[Music]
let's try the process a little bit more
what do we want to make
which one do i want to make which one is
good
oh see i'm already getting rid of all
the rice
is
keep the rest okay
okay rest
rice doesn't spill that fast okay
ah it's winter yay
speaking of winter did you like the the
intro music that changed to um christmas
style
someone made an arrangement i think i
did i put
the link ah maybe i didn't put it in
there possibly i didn't put the link yet
but i retweeted it
on my twitter someone made a like a
arrangement it was really really nice
i like it so much i don't only want to
use it for the intro i also want to use
it
as a background music during chatting
streams or like super chatting i hope
that you guys
won't get sick of it okay
i will try to beat this piece of [\h__\h]
if we beat him then stream is over if we
don't beat him gonna try again and again
and again
and if i still don't manage to beat him
then the stream will be over as well
i didn't change the weapon did i
okay
i will definitely die
wait actually i'm really much stronger
i'm really much stronger right now
look how much damage you already got
from me what's in it for you could not
well i don't even care if you hit me
that often you can ground
me as much as you like i'm like
invincible right now
and that really made a big change
even your tongue will not bother me now
i'm invincible oh shut up
okay i don't even need to fight well it
seems like we have no issue today
with this stupid frog
maybe if i make my frog noises it it
will be like
friendly to me
[Music]
the jelly stuff is not [\h__\h] me
i have no idea what i'm doing right now
i'm fighting like really bad
wow that was a much easier than i
[Music]
expected
what i'm fighting much worse than last
time yeah
but i did much more damage wow that one
harvest of
rice did so much
well frog it's over i'm having you for
dinner tonight
did you guys hear my frog noises before
no no no no need
you are welcome
please stop what why do you want me to
stop isn't that
amazing like an amazing skill that's my
frog impression
i've been so proud of my frog
impressions since
i was a little child okay
he dropped an egg he laid an egg
out of his eye was that his eye ew
i actually a phoenix or a toad
can i use it for cooking
will there be a day where i can eat
fried chicken
yes fry every yeah let's let's [\h__\h]
dry everything hell yeah
[Music]
press l to light or extinguish the earth
right one
it will illuminate darkness but you oh
wait i can
i can cook with it but i can also light
up
the area
complete
that's so useful wow how do i get back
home
i guess i just leave the area in the
main menu but i don't want it
okay ciao
wait i didn't send anyone damn it send
someone now
maybe to the new spot eh spring
can i not send anyone there now
maybe tomorrow yeah it looks like it's
the end of the stream
let's go uh no wait i don't want to go
home yet i want to
look for iron one more time
give me that [\h__\h] iron you don't need
to read this out loud even if you notice
it but i wish for you to rest as soon as
possible after this change the cafe crew
really loves it
thank you you
i the thing is like um
i have a i have like zero stamina
i get exhausted so quickly
um and my throat recently
feels a bit worse than usual
i don't know if it's the weather
probably it is
oh still no iron
you know what i will um i think i'll
continue playing off screen until i can
uh plant my
rice seeds again so basically until
spring
i think i'll i think i'll continue
in spring again so
probably next week
hmm you do long streams like most days
carry your voice
yeah often i do very long streams
and i enjoy that i enjoy like hanging
out with you guys for a long time but
i have to get some [\h__\h] done tomorrow i
know i said the report
okay so in that case um
i don't know i'm just i'm just gonna
finish this map and then
because otherwise it feels like uh my my
healing
and stuff is uh multi-night getting to
waste
i don't want to waste it yep explode me
whoo i like it i like it
i missed the mineral hey but no i i know
i can't harass anything
anyway like it didn't refresh yet
it didn't refresh at least from what i
saw the first one didn't refresh
should i check them all can i refresh
like a different times
no yeah they're not reloaded
am i done again
hey no i have not been away for 23 hours
how would you get that idea
i did it i want to go up there
okay there's nothing up there anyway
i also want to know what happened to you
pick on a drawing
people keep on asking people always ask
me
people always ask where is the pekula
drawing
but people never ask how is the peculiar
and i tell you it's terrible that's why
i don't want to upload it
i know it upload it you always ask where
it is but it's just
you never ask how it is
you never ask that
[Music]
i'll think about it
let's go home you better show it to
pekora
yeah but what if she'll be like that's
disgusting and ugly
just kidding she would never say that
she would never say that but still
i don't want to get better at art though
so i should do more
art streams
well
with that being said
i shall save
and leave you guys
everyone uh super chat reading whoa was
it was it so small the whole stream
where everyone the super chat reading
will
uh not be today will also not be
tomorrow
we will have the uh song celebration
stream
in 22 and a half hours
22 and a half hours uh i will release my
song in 22 and a half hours i hope
everyone can be there it's gonna be
super special
so first of all there will be a song
premiere
i will reserve the stream at the song
premiere and not reserve talk
i'll make a i'll reserve the song from
whatever
and then five minutes later i'll start
my own stream where we celebrate it for
like an hour
and then i have to go to sleep as soon
as possible
because then it's peculiar and then then
uh on that day i'll uh reserve a gorilla
super chat reading i think to catch up
on everything okay
are you all hyped for my song
i can't wait it's gonna be
an amazing day it's gonna be
a day that goes into the history books
of the era of the phoenix
in japan is already today because it's
already past midnight
okay everyone thank you thank you thank
you so much for watching today i hope
you enjoyed it even though it was a
relatively shorter stream
hope you still enjoyed it somehow and
i'll see you
tomorrow right you will all come
wait a second let me do one more thing
please post the pickle that drawing
[Music]
hype but also possible why do you all
want me to post it so bad
what what why are you so focused on that
is it because you want to save it do it
why are you guys so
what what what does that do for you
but i'm glad you liked it so much and
you want me to upload it
oh wait i just realized i didn't show
this just chat on the stream
today god damn it goddammit i
i even it was under the
it was on the wrong layer it should have
been here
goddammit okay everyone show it to her
live
yeah maybe i can do that
okay everyone in german we say
auf wiedersehen
[Music]
i think if i upload the drawing i don't
wanna
i wanna i want everything to be focused
on my new song right now so if i upload
it it will be
after the song release so maybe right
before or right after
the peculiar senpai collaboration
if she didn't see it yet then it might
be a nice surprise
yeah that was accidental the chat thing
was accidental
bye bye i love you all
see you soon
bye bye
[Music]
hashtag
so
[Music]
you